My god! What have
you done, Kagutsu?
Is there anyone out there
who's still alive?! Anyone?!
Is someone there?!
Is there anyone at all?
Please someone
answer me!
[gasp]
HWake up! You okay?!
I'm too late. He
was just a kid!
All of this, is this
really the end result of
pursuing my ideals?
What use is a king's power
if I can't save one child?!
What do you make of
this, Mr. Fushimi?
How can there be another
Sword of Damocles?
I thought there were only
four Kings right now.
This is big trouble.
What color is
that Sword anyway?
Well, it isn't gold
and it isn't colorless.
There's only one other
color left. Although I didn't
think that it was possible.
[gasp] The Green
King's sword is fading!
The Fifth King's Weismann
level is dropping rapidly!
[growl]
[gasp]
Fourteen years ago, a
King's death triggered
the worst destruction
in human history,
the Kagutsu Incident.
And it was believed that
amongst those victims was
the Sixth King, the
Gray King Seigo Ootori.
But as it turns out,
he did survive and was
also secretly the
Green Clan's mastermind.
I must admit this situation
truly is very surprising.
You're wrong, Munakata.
The man that you call
Seigo Ootori did
indeed die that day.
And the guy you're looking
at now is Tenkei Iwafune,
the surrogate father of the
Green King, Nagare Hisui,
and someone who's basically
freeloading off JUNGLE.
I'm a chicken
that can't fly.
So stop making such
a big deal over me.
I'm a simple old man.
[harrumphing chuckle] The
Fog Sanctum is a power that
provides absolute protection.
After demonstrating that
you possess such power,
you still have the
audacity to call
yourself a
simple old man?
[gasp]
I win, Reisi Munakata.
Meow?!
Everything is starting
to get all hazy.
What's this?!
No!
Stop him!
Anna! Look out!
[grunting]
[gasp]
Shiro! Shiro!
Shiro!
Kuroh! Take care of Neko!
Get away from here now!
Shiro?! Shiro!
Mr. Munakata...
[determined yell]
C'mon, now, get it together.
What were you
even aiming at?
Taking cheap shots to win?
I suppose it's fitting
for a cowardly man like
you, who changed his name
and went into hiding
after losing his clan!
Call me whatever you like.
It doesn't bother me
one bit. I stopped caring
about my pride years ago.
The Gray Clan, also
called Cathedral.
It was a powerful clan whose
influence, in its heyday,
was second only to the
Gold Clan, Tokijukuin.
And the person who
led Cathedral was the
Gray King, Seigo Ootori.
He was said to be a
man of great virtue and
strength, widely respected
not just by his clansmen
but also by the
general public.
[chuckle] You're giving the
guy way too much credit.
Fourteen years ago, he led
his clansmen to try to
prevent Red King Genji
Kagutsu's Damocles Down.
But he failed to stop
Kagutsu. And as a result,
he lost all his clansmen.
That tragedy claimed
over seven hundred
thousand lives, including
innocent civilians.
So he decided to leave
behind his old self,
abandoning his past and
the memories of the people
that he'd failed to
save, isn't that right?!
Eh, who really knows?
It's all ancient
history now anyway.
Then tell me why, after all
this time, you've decided to
conspire with Nagare Hisui
and come out in the open!
If the world that
Nagare Hisui proposes
becomes a reality, society
will fall into chaos
and it's certain millions
of lives will be lost.
I can't believe that
endorsing such barbarism
is in line with your past
efforts to save all of
those people and
create the ideal paradise.
Did the Kagutsu
Incident truly force
you to fall this far?
Ideal paradise, you say?
A King doesn't
have the power to
create such a thing.
All of us are being played
by this goddamn Slate, and I
mean all of us, including
both you and me.
But it's different for him.
He intends to play
the Slate instead.
[gasp] Anna? You all right?
You're shivering!
This fog is so cold. I can
feel the weight of all his
despair pressing down.
The Gray King, Seigo Ootori.
The Lieutenant described
him as a pacifist who
detested conflict, but
when he was forced to
fight, he displayed strength
that rivaled even then Blue
King, Jin Habari and Red
King, Genji Kagutsu.
This is bad...
[gasp]
Oh, no! The Slate!
Hundreds of thousands
of people lost their
lives that day all
because they were
helpless, and didn't
know what to do.
If everyone has their
own power, at least
they won't have to
confront death helplessly.
They'll have the choice to
fight back on their own.
And that is the kind of
world that Nagare is trying
to create with this plan.
Nonsense!
Suddenly giving people
undeserved power will only
make them flaunt it. They'll
end up killing each other
and turning this into
a depraved world!
Society needs order as well
as leaders to oversee it all.
A world where there is order
and reason is the ideal
world, a beautiful world!
[chuckle] Oh, you and
your lofty ideals.
I guess that's the reason
why you're the Blue King.
You believe in this bullshit
about creating the ideal
world with your
own power, Munakata.
Because you're like a
little kid who's never
experienced true failure.
[chuckling]
Or is the Blue King
better than that?!
[screaming]
Whoops...
Sorry, time out.
Listen kid, you need to
stop being so aggressive.
Here's some advice from an
old man who's been around
the block a few times.
The higher your
ideals, the greater
your disappointment
is once you fail.
Moderation is everything.
You need to learn how
relax a little bit more.
I don't care to engage
in idle talk with you!
Back to playing
hide‐and‐seek, are we?!
Well, don't think I'll
make it easy for you.
Don't push yourself. You
look pretty worn out, there.
Listen, I really don't enjoy
kicking people when they're
down, but I need to
wrap things up here now.
[gasp]
Sorry about
that, Munakata!
That little game of sword
fighting that I was playing
with you was merely a
diversion to buy us the
time that we needed
to haul the Dresden
Slate out of here.
Hey, stop, you lousy thief!
Give that back to us!
They played us
all for fools.
Get that monitor
back online! Now!
I need to determine
if the Captain's okay!
Yes, sir!
I'll dispatch men to the
Chamber of the Slate now!
I guess it pays to
have insurance.
Evacuating the injured is
our top priority! Are there
any more inside the tower?
It's possible the
interior could collapse.
Rescue teams, exercise
extreme caution.
Where's that helicopter?
I'm afraid that the fog not
only acts as a smokescreen,
but it's also jamming our
radar, making it impossible
to track them right now.
I see. Well keep searching
with everything we've got.
Yes, ma'am!
Intel team! Analyze
the video footage now!
Then report to Fushimi!
Shiro, are you okay?
Shiro, what
should we do now?
[chuckle]
That's a very good question.
Honestly, I'm at a loss
for what to do myself.
I didn't think even for a
moment they'd have
a wild card like that
up their sleeves.
I failed everyone.
Stop blaming
yourself, Shiro.
We don't have time for
self‐pity. Because we're
going to take the Slate
back from them, right?
Take it back?
The Lieutenant put his life
on the line for over half a
century to keep the Slate
under control, and after his
death, Mr. Munakata
took up the task.
But now it's just a
matter of time before the
Slate's power is
released to the world.
What'll happen if the
power's released?
Will everyone become
naked or something?
You numbskull! We're
having a serious discussion!
What the heck, Kuroh!
I was just trying
to cheer up Shiro!
Mr. Shiro, we were planning
on heading out now.
Some of our guys need
their injuries treated.
Oh. Yes, of course.
Thanks for your help.
It's not over yet.
[sigh]
There has to be
something that we can do.
There's always hope
if we don't give up.
Yes, you're right,
Anna. Thank you.
There is still hope.
Man...
We let ourselves get bossed
around by the Silver King,
and still wind up
losing after all that?
C'mon, San, don't be so hard
on the guy. He did his best.
He's right. This is on us,
too. After all we weren't
able to stop the Green King.
So what do you think's
gonna happen now?
Well, since the Greens
got ahold of the Slate...
Actually, I don't have a
clue. What's supposed to
happen, Yata, do you know?
Oh hey, what do you want?
So our Clans form this
overblown alliance and we
put on this big show
of working together,
only to lose. I mean,
talk about ridiculous.
Shut up, Monkey! Quit
talking shit, will ya?! We
all did our best, and
you can't deny that!
So the best you
can do is to lose?
You're one to talk! You
just sat in the car and
typed on your keyboard!
Besides, none of this
would've ever happened if
your King had just
beaten the Gray King!
You're absolutely right.
He's a complete loser.
Hold up! You're talking
about your King!
Aren't you even going to
stand up for the guy?!
Hey...
Things are about to
get very interesting.
Try to keep up, if
you can. [chuckle]
Saruhiko?
To think the Gray King
was alive all along.
And the fact that he was
working with Hisui was
completely unexpected.
Completely unexpected? I
couldn't disagree more.
It was a
preventable mistake.
You and Yashiro Isana failed
to consider the Gray King.
That's the truth.
It seems obvious to me who
was really at fault here.
You Kings were fixated on
the struggle for the Slate
and didn't even notice the
presence of another King
right under your noses.
[sigh]
If you're only here to
berate me about what just
happened, then you
really ought leave.
I'm too tired for this now.
Too tired even to lead
us like you should?
I'm sure Yashiro Isana will
think of something to do.
You should follow
his orders.
After all, I was defeated.
I'll stay out of the way.
So you're just going to sulk
because you got your ass
kicked in a one‐on‐one
fight, is that it?
I bet what you
were thinking
is that with the Gold
King finally gone, there
wouldn't be anyone
left to stand in
your way, so at last
you'd be able to control
the world as you saw fit.
But unfortunately
another annoying old
man was still alive.
I'd be pissed,
too, if I were you.
[irritated sigh]
I can only assume that you
must be pleased with how
all this turned out.
After all, you were
against this alliance
from the start.
Just tell me the truth!
Are you secretly glad
that our plan failed?
Yeah, just like I'm
glad that you choked
and lost this fight!
Mr. Fushimi, that's too far!
[angry snarl]
[considering sigh]
If you're just going to give
up and bail on all of us,
then I'm going to resign.
Fine.
Go on, resign. If you're
harboring any complaints
against me, then leave.
You should be used to being
a traitor by now, anyway.
[gasp]
If you don't like something,
you just quit. Isn't that
the kind of person
you've always been?
That's why you could never
commit yourself to one king.
But you also refused to
remove yourself from the
Slate's influence, so you
just wander around
aimlessly in your
little world.
Pathetic...
[growl]
[gasps]
Mr. Fushimi!
Captain, should we stop him?
[chuckle]
No, let him go.
Hey there, Seri,
what can I do for you?
You calling to
discuss our next move?
Hm? Fushimi?
No, he's not here. I don't
understand. What's going on?
Hey, Yata! Have
you been in contact
with Fushimi recently?
Saruhiko? Are
you kidding me?
Why, what has he done now?
Well, it seems he
walked out of SCEPTER
FOUR after getting into an
argument, and hasn't
been heard from since.
What?
He and the Captain exchanged
some harsh words... [sigh]
To be honest, our
work is stacking
up here without him.
It seems we relied on
Fushimi's skills more than
we realized we did.
Where can that boy be now?
Does he even have
a place to sleep?
You should be used to being
a traitor by now, anyway.
Fine, then that's
just what I'll become!
The giant Green tree
blooms in full, while a
shard of Blue breaks away.
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, Episode 9 "Kid's room."
Twisted hearts are lost
and wander aimlessly.