Enemy infiltration is
at seventy percent.
We can't hold them
off for much longer.
Yukari Mishakuji
and Sukuna Gojo.
Their plan's simple:
overwhelm with brute force.
And yet it shows just
how much confidence they
have in their own abilities.
They're messing with us.
Oh my, another trap
to try to stall us?
This is really getting
quite tiresome.
My orders are to destroy
all the traps I can in
order to clear a route
inside for our King.
I understand that
that's part of my duty,
and I've accepted that.
Caw! Duty! Duty!
However...
I prefer my battles
to be more beautiful!
We'll be more than happy
to grant your wish!
Hm?
[growl]
We'll give you a beautiful
send‐off! How's that?
Phase Two of the
plan to neutralize
JUNGLE: concentrate
our military power in
the Cloud Hall on the
seventy‐fifth floor and
crush the Green
clansmen one by one.
It's all going as
planned so far, but...
Our sensors are detecting
massive Weismann
levels on the lower floors!
It's in motion!
Agh! He's here now,
The Green King!
This is Nagare.
I'm going in.
[laughter] It's so
good to see him up
and running again!
It's been nine years since
he fought the Gold King,
Daikaku Kokujoji.
And it's been over a decade
since the Kagutsu Incident.
We've been forced to
hide in the shadows
for practically ages.
I mean really, that
stubborn old fart
just wouldn't die!
[sigh]
But now Kokujoji's
finally gone.
And that means there's
no one left in this
entire world that
can stop you when
you're at full
power, Nagare.
That's it, Nagare!
Run wild all you want!
Mr. Iwa's here to get your
back, so go right on ahead
and have an absolute blast!
[laughter]
[gasp]
Holy crap! That
was way too close!
What's that noise?!
Is it more of them?!
Hey! C'mon, you Blues! Hurry
up and get into position!
Oh my, you're here
already, are you?
Here already?
You don't mean!
Yes, that's right.
He's coming...
[gasp]
How very unfortunate.
Truly unfortunate.
And just when things
were finally starting to
become interesting.
But now it's all
over. Oh, well.
Over! It's over!
What do you mean, over?
It's the Green King!
I didn't expect him so soon.
Hey, what's the matter?!
Don't act like cowards!
Whether it's a King or only
some low‐level clansmen,
who the hell cares?!
We'll crush anyone who comes
at us, so show some spirit!
Come on!
Oh? like this
boy's enthusiasm.
But I meant me when
I said unfortunate!
Hey! What the‐?!
Since my part in this
is all over, ta‐ta!
Shiro!
Yeah. It appears that
he has decided it's time
to make his move.
Although it's sooner
than I had expected...
What'll we do, Shiro?
Hey, who gave you guys
permission to talk, anyway?!
[gasp]
Ah! Damn it! Stop all
your fooling around!
Come on! Fight me for real!
Sukuna Gojo, this battle
of ours is not a single
combat that will determine
the outcome of war.
Huh?! But nothing is
more important than
winning whatever
game you're playing!
You gotta risk everything!
I'm betting my life!
So you're willing to throw
your life away, huh?
Then you leave
me no choice!
He'll use a big move here.
So counter the instant
that he first swings.
Understood.
I'm gonna take all of
you out, right now!
The sun is setting. Those
who chose to leave their
homes, and those who return.
Yukari Mishakuji!
Yukari! I'm right in the
middle of a game here!
Middle of a game!
[chuckle] Well, Kuroh...
I see being reunited
with the Silver King has
made you even more
handsome than ever.
Understandable, since
you only use your
sword to protect your King.
It's what defines
your selfless nature.
So have you come here
to assist your comrade
then, Yukari Mishakuji?
That's just dirty!
Hey, I don't need
your help, you know!
Assist? Or help?
I would never do anything as
tasteless as those things.
I just came by so that I
might pick up our boy, here.
Come on, Sukuna. Time to go.
Caw! Time to go! Time to go!
No way, man! I'm
staying to fight!
Stop being so
selfish, Sukuna.
A child throwing
infantile tantrums is
very unattractive.
And besides...
I've already decided
that Kuroh will be mine.
When the time comes, I get
to have him all to myself.
Whatever, and you have
the nerve to say that
I'm the selfish one here?!
Alas, Kuroh, it seems we
just weren't destined to
face each other tonight.
But I'm sure that we'll
meet again very soon.
And on that fateful
day we'll settle things
once and for all.
What's the deal with that
weirdo? After all the fuss
that he caused getting
up here, he just
decides to run off!
I mean, talk about
anticlimactic!
And who exactly am I
supposed to take out all
my frustration on now?!
Right, so, the kid that you
guys were just dealing with.
Yes, that's right.
I mean Sukuna Gojo.
Really? You're saying that
he just retreated along
with Yukari Mishakuji?
Okay, got it.
It's sooner than
anticipated, but we'll go
ahead and prepare to
move on to Phase 3.
Yes, Mr. Shiro.
We'll all be waiting
up at the top.
Please, sir, be very careful.
Fushimi, we're starting
Phase 3. Everything ready?
I was ready hours ago.
Mihashira Tower will now
go into total lockdown,
including all communication
and power systems.
That will isolate
the Green King.
And from this moment onward
our communication will be
limited to just the Red
King's psychic powers,
so please be cautious.
Understood.
Right! Launch emergency
Tower lockdown.
Yes, sir! Emergency
Tower lockdown!
You can't use the routes
that your henchmen opened
up, Green King.
I won't let you.
There are no lights
along the corridors.
And no one will be
able to hear your voice.
Furthermore, several
layers of thick walls
will block your way.
All of Mihashira Tower
has now become a prison,
custom‐made just for you.
Obviously, a trap like this
one could never completely
stop a powerful King
such as yourself.
However, each trap will
certainly eat away at your
limited time and strength.
You'll need to break
through a hundred walls
and get past two Kings.
All right then, let's see
if you'll make it this far.
Can you, Green
King, Nagare Hisui?
[chuckle]
Is this the damage Nagare
Hisui left behind?
His destructive power
is simply amazing.
Yeah, he's using up his
power at an alarming rate.
His speed is far greater
than I expected.
But, there's no way he
can maintain his stamina.
Shiro, isn't that exactly
the outcome you hoped your
strategy would produce?
Yes, but it's happening much
faster than I anticipated.
Its like he's not
even trying to save
his strength at all.
Just what could
he be up to?
Something doesn't
feel right.
Shiro!
Hurry up!
So are you saying?
I think Anna's in danger!
Shiro, hurry up!
Meow! Meow!
Remember, Anna will be the
key player in this mission.
There isn't very much we'll
be able to do during a fight
between Kings. We'll
only get in Anna's way.
Soon, Yashiro Isana,
the Silver King,
will join us here.
Mr. Shiro will defend and
Anna will attack. The rest
of us are all there for
diversion and support.
Right! Did you
guys get that?
Yeah!
But Yata, What about you?
Did you get it, as well?
I'm not supposed to
get carried away and
jump into battle, is that it?
[chuckle]
Even at a time such
as this one you
HOMRA are full of energy.
Please, I beg your
pardon, Red King.
We are all connected.
Huh?
I said we're all connected.
Deep down inside of
us we all share a bond.
That's why...
Our fire will never go out.
But what I don't get
about all of this
is the Blue King.
I mean, he's making Anna,
HOMRA's King, put her life
on the line while he
gets to kick back and
chill out up there!
Just who the hell
does that guy think he
is to do that, anyway?!
Yata, we went over all this
at the strategy meeting.
We can't afford to let the
Green King gain entrance to
the Chamber of the Slate.
If all of us are in here and
he somehow manages to break
through, it would be bad.
That's why Anna and Mr.
Shiro's job is to force the
enemy to use up his power,
so if he does get past us
the Blue King will be
waiting to stop him for
sure. That's the plan.
Hey, listen, don't get me
wrong, here. I have no
problem with the
strategy itself.
What I'm talking
about is his attitude
and his sense of honor.
I just don't understand
why anyone would
want to follow that guy.
Dishonest bastard...
Dumbass! Don't make
such a fuss over
other people's business!
Sorry, Seri. Forgive him.
Huh?! Oh, no, I, uh,
wasn't talking about you!
Hey!
Everyone, get back.
What is it?
He's coming now.
[chuckle]
[groans]
Agh! Shit! Didn't
see that coming!
So that is the Green King?!
Anna!
Are you injured?!
I'm fine.
I'm going. I
have to stop him.
Anna!
Hello, Red King,
Anna Kushina.
I must ask you to forgive my
rude entrance back there.
I'm in a hurry.
Apologies.
Enough, Green
King, Nagare Hisui.
Just give it up. We
cannot and will not
let you have it.
The Slate is not merely
your toy to play with.
You're right. It's not my
toy. I'm in complete
agreement with you on that.
A world where players are
granted powers that far
exceed the limits of
humankind and compete
to reach the top.
The Dresden Slate
is a catalyst that
serves that purpose.
Which means it doesn't
belong to me alone.
It belongs to everyone.
You must stop.
No, I will not stop,
nor can I be stopped.
Watch, Anna Kushina,
I'm now going to
achieve my objective.
Stop! Now!
You've only been a King
for a very short time
and yet you seem to
have great control
over your power.
I'm impressed.
You do not understand the
true meaning of this power.
Power by itself has
no intrinsic meaning.
It is the people who
wield power that are the
ones who provide it meaning.
That's not true!
Fine, then. Since we've
confirmed that our opinions
are at odds with each other.
Now the games shall begin!
[chuckle]
A lightning beast?!
Anna and Nagare Hisui
are battling each other.
Look! There!
I've arrived at last!
My goal!
Sorry, no goal just yet.
It's time! He's
used up his power.
Anna! Mr. Munakata!
So? How was it, Nagare
Hisui? Did you enjoy your
pointless little rampage?
There's no sense or
order to your actions.
In your frenzy of
destruction, you were
essentially like an animal.
Oh, it was almost unbearably
fun, Reisi Munakata.
You do realize that humans
are animals, too, right?
We're all just individual
creatures that happen to be
different from each other.
Don't you agree with
that, Miyabi Ameno?
You mean me?!
But I'm Neko!
Miyabi Ameno...
Even with SCEPTER 4's
resources, we couldn't
identify that girl.
So that is her real
name, then, is it?
Although, wouldn't you
say that she's a bit
too unique to use as an
example of what ordinary,
everyday humans are like?
You believe that
because you're a fool.
She and I are both the same...
We can define ourselves
without being limited
by whatever human
qualities just happen
to be forced upon us.
It's possession of that free
spirit that throws open the
doors of human possibility.
And now, I the one nearest
that free‐spirited ideal,
have come here to
receive the Slate.
Are you saying you're
the most suitable
to manage the Slate?
The amount of arrogance you
show is just astounding.
Don't misunderstand
me, Reisi Munakata.
Really, it's completely
impossible for anyone
to be "suitable" to
manage the Dresden Slate.
It's the wellspring of
possibilities, and to think
one can arbitrarily
control it shows a total
lack of understanding
of its true nature.
The whole idea's absurd.
Oh, I see. Don't try
to manage the power,
merely release it.
Creating unbridled chaos is
the meaning of the Slate's
existence, is that right?
Is that what you're saying?
No, there is no meaning.
Those who possess power
simply use it in any way
that they want, that's all.
But look, your power is
exhausted. This situation
you've found yourself in.
How do you explain that?
Nagare Hisui, you are
already a dead man.
According to the
Silver King's data, you
lost your heart during
the Kagutsu Incident.
Your power alone is
sustaining your existence,
and barely at that.
That explains how you're
able to manipulate your
physical capabilities
to such an extreme.
However, once your power
has become all used up
you're like a toy with a
dead battery inside of it.
Or rather, your original
self which is to say,
nothing but a corpse.
I hardly think that you're
qualified to battle me in
order to determine
who has the right to
possess the Slate.
[chuckle] Perhaps
you're right.
But then, I'm not the
one you're going to
be doing battle against.
"He" will be arriving
here shortly using the
path I've cleared.
"He" is my trump card.
Come on!
Anna our King!
Is in danger!
Ya hear?! Show
some guts, bastards!
Right!
[chuckle] At times like
these, it sure is good to
have Yata around!
Huh?!
Hey, this fog,
Where'd it come from?
[gasps]
Everyone! Be careful!
Yata! Kamamoto! Seri!
Who are you?!
What the hell was that?
[gasp] Anna!
An unknown sanctum just
appeared inside the tower!
It's another King, sir!
[gasp] What?!
Vertical over. A Sword of
Damocles is manifesting!
Impossible! Another King?!
Mr. Munakata!
Yes, I see. Nagare Hisui's
reckless actions and
surprising confidence
can be explained by the
fact that you were the
one behind this all along.
You, who were said
to have died during
the Kagutsu Incident.
The Sixth King!
The Gray King!
Whoa, hold on. Just
wait a second, Munakata.
The beginning is crucial in
human relationships.
So I just have one
thing to say first.
If you wanna talk
to me, call me Mr. Iwa!
The final sword
that remained
hidden till now, Gray.
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, Episode 8 "Kaput."
You are a coward, but
also a very tragic figure.