High school boys like
gettin' into trouble.
They'd rather hide-out with
pals than learn anything.
But if they pick a dangerous
spot they could end up
seein' somethin'
they shouldn't.
Hey, isn't it time to
meet up with the class?
Teacher'll be pissed
if we show up late.
We're still playin'!
Check it!
Read 'em and weep!
Three of a kind?!
Hold up, are you
cheatin', Itakura?
Just lucky.
Guess I won this round, huh?
Not so fast.
Damn it, Higashio!
Crap!
Is that a classmate?
Yeah, a chick!
Sweet! C'mon, baby,
give us a little show!
--She's dead!
--Shhh!
What do we do now?
I swear on all that's holy,
if you ask that one more
time, Nozaki, you're dead!
I can't help it;
I'm freakin' out!
I think we oughta
call the cops, man!
Oh yeah? And tell 'em what?
What we saw!
There's no way in hell
they're gonna believe we
watched somebody drag Yasuda's
body in, suck her veins dry,
and then eat her corpse;
skin, bones, and everything.
I mean, would you?!
And what do you think, Yamada?
I'm thinkin' who cares
if the cops believe us?
I'm freaked out about
some killer walkin' around.
That sick bastard is in
the same grade as us.
We should figure out who it is!
Think of it as self-defense!
If we knew who it was,
we'd know to steer clear.
Know what I mean?
I didn't notice anything,
but he wasn't a part
of my group either.
I saw Kanamori take
off partway through,
but he was probably with Motoi.
We wouldn't really know
whether anybody left.
Yeah, I'm sorry but we were
with a totally different group.
From what I hear,
Komiyama definitely ditched
his group at one point.
Then we have five
possible suspects;
four guys and one girl.
Can we take Nakai off the list?
She's a lot shorter
than the killer.
Might as well mark
off Maehara, too.
I mean, the guy's over
two hundred pounds.
That leaves us with...
Komiyama from Group B.
And from group A,
Horikoshi, and Yamamoto.
If we ask around we might
be able to find somebody
who'll know what they
were up to that day.
We should stop.
I just don't see why we
should dig any deeper when
we already know the killer's
one of those three.
Itakura's right.
It's not like we have
any classes with 'em.
Wait.
So you're saying all we gotta
do is stay outta their way
and we should be safe, right?
It'd suck if we got attacked
'cause we were snoopin' around.
Know what I mean?
Yeah, I guess you
make a good point.
I asked his girl,
but she doesn't know
what happened to him.
I bet he kept diggin' for
info after we split up.
He pissed off the killer
and now he's dead!
Shut up!
What if the killer's
on to us, too?!
We're goners!
I said shut up, man!
We should go and
ask Ungo for advice.
Why?! You know he's just gonna
laugh at us, don't you?
Who cares? Getting
laughed at still beats
tryin' to figure all
this out on our own.
I'm afraid we're gonna
have to part ways
'cause I can't hang
with crazy folk.
I know it sounds crazy,
but it's true! For real!
C'mon, man, help us out.
What do you want me to do?
Kill the guy for ya?
You know I've never
been one for violence.
No, of course not.
But with all your connections,
we figured you might know
someone who could help us out.
Sure, I can hook you up,
but it'll cost ya
twenty thousand yen.
We got enough?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure we do.
Here ya go.
Who's this?
He runs a hospital that's
about to be shut down.
What?! How is that
supposed to help us?
Hear me out!
When they ask you
which consultation
course you wanna take,
be sure to tell 'em that
you want the E Course.
Then what?
The rest is up to you.
This it?
Good afternoon, boys,
is this your first visit?
Uh... Yes.
Which consultation course
would you like to take?
Uh...
The E Course, please.
We'll be with you shortly.
What's with the wait?
I said E Course, right?
Yeah.
You can go in now.
Uh, okay!
Welcome. Make
yourselves comfortable.
Please, go ahead
and have a seat.
So who referred you?
It was a guy named
Ungo Sakamoto.
You really shouldn't
associate with him.
Hold onto your brain
cells as long as you can.
Uh...
Say what?
Never mind.
Now then.
I'm going to ask you a few
basic questions to determine
whether or not your case
is worth taking on.
You can save all the
gritty details for later.
Don't worry,
I'm sure she'll turn up.
Yeah, and didn't she say
that she was having
issues with her parents?
She probably just had a big
fight with them or something
and decided to run away.
C'mon, cheer up, Moe!
What do you say we go
and grab a bite to eat?
Yeah, it'll be our treat!
You witnessed this?
Yeah.
Well, unfortunately, there's
no way for me to prove
that you're telling the truth.
And even if you could prove it,
no one would ever believe you.
So.
You want to know where
you should go from here.
--Is that right?
--Yeah.
Well, the answer
is quite simple.
The best way and really the only
way to deal with this problem
is to avoid the suspects.
As long as you stay
out of their way,
they won't have any reason
to retaliate against you.
That should just about do it.
Any questions?
You're not telling us anything
that we didn't already
figure out for ourselves.
Dontcha have any
other advice for us?
Like a way to protect
ourselves against the monster?
Not without a
thorough investigation,
which I'd be glad to perform,
but I'm afraid that's
going to cost you.
How much are we talkin'?
The investigation is one
point five million yen,
plus fifty-thousand a day
and an additional two million
if a solution is found.
Sorry but that's as low
as I can possibly go
and no, insurance
won't cover it.
If you can't pay,
I can't help you.
--We're outta here.
--C'mon, man!
That would be a wise
decision considering
the perpetrator isn't too
dangerous at this stage.
And how can you be
so sure of that?
Most only eat one or two
people a day for sustenance.
Considering the number
of missing persons,
I'd say he's well-behaved.
Well, compared to
most visitors to Earth.
Visitors... to Earth?
Oh, dear.
What do you mean?
Let me explain.
You saw an Adherent Type II,
a life form that's
not from Earth.
They're known to integrate
into our society
but they don't usually
cause us any harm.
That said, this type
can pose a higher risk.
They live amongst us
disguised as humans.
Therein lies the problem.
Because they can
communicate with us,
we often fall victim
to their trickery.
I once had an
assistant go missing
while working on
a similar case.
His corpse was
found without a head.
Strains of unidentified
bacteria were found on his body.
The authorities declared
his death an accident
and refused to release
their findings to us.
Before he went missing,
his last words to me were,
"Don't worry,
this case is safe".
Well, do my investigation fees
still sound unreasonable now
considering the alternative?
How are we supposed to know
you're telling us the truth?
Excellent question.
Guess you'll just have
to trust me. Okay?
What'll we do now?
Really?
Well, then I'll
start right away.
I heard a couple of
people say that Higashio
and his pals from Group C
haven't come to school in days.
Seriously?
Your parents' rings.
But won't they be mad?
Probably so, but I'd rather
be killed by my own folks
than end up a rotting corpse
in that monster's gut.
Well okay then.
If you'll go ahead and
fill these out for me,
I'll put you boys
into isolation.
Why? How's that gonna--
My utmost concern
is my client's safety.
The investigation should
only take about a week
and don't worry; I'll bring
you all the food you need.
Guess this is it.
Higashio?! Itakura!
What's going on?!
Where in the hell have
you losers been hiding?!
Why're you here? Watch it!
Hold on, don't shut the door!
It's no use, man; you can't
open it from this side.
Why're we locked in here?!
You're not too bright, big guy.
Here's how it went down.
After we split up a week ago,
Higashio just couldn't
let the matter go.
He asked Ungo for advice,
and was sent here,
and when he requested an
investigation he was locked up.
Then after the three of us
came here together.
I came back to ask Yumeno
for advice, and I got locked up.
Which brings us to the
two of you showing up.
Are you saying each of us hired
him to do the exact same job?!
Yeah, but he didn't tell us
you guys were here already.
How come?
It's called
"client confidentiality."
Basically, he knew he would
make three times as much cash
if he kept his mouth shut.
That greedy bastard!
I start workin' for Ungo next
month to pay off my bill.
But that's nothin'
compared to Higashio!
He agreed to start working
as an assistant here!
This is stupid! Can't we
break our contracts?!
Geez, you didn't
read it, did ya?
You can't break your contract
or even get a refund.
Not once he's
started investigating.
Bonehead! Sounds like he
already has you brainwashed!
He totally pulled one
over on us! He's a fraud!
He's telling the truth.
Sure is.
How can you be so
sure about that?!
Well, you comin' or not?
What's this?
It's a bunch of stuff that
old fart's been researchin'.
But they're fake, aren't they?
Look at this and
tell me it's fake.
This thing doesn't even
have a scientific name yet,
but somehow it's able to
analyze the purity of the water.
I don't know how, but it planted
everything you see in the tank.
Seriously?
Who'd fake that?
It's the harsh reality.
Lately, our planet has
become overwrought
with these foreign life forms.
They roam the city's alleys,
they reside in apartments.
They could even
be in your class.
They're so close that
no one notices them.
I know who the killer is.
She ran away?
I bumped into her earlier.
She asked me to take you to her.
Why didn't she talk to
me before she ran away?
'Cause it was a
last second decision.
She wasn't expecting to
fight with her parents.
If you would,
please come with me.
Yamamoto?!
There are two different
ways that aliens
can disguise
themselves as human.
They either wear a
sophisticated costume
or transform themselves
to look like us.
In any case, there's an easy way
to see through their disguise.
By their fingerprints.
Whenever a human hand
touches something,
a fingerprint is left behind.
Those in costumes don't leave
prints at all, while those
who've transformed leave a
different print than humans.
I approached the three
suspects on the street
and asked them to
fill out a survey.
His pen was the only one
that came back clean.
What's that?
My curiosity was piqued so
I lured his younger brother
out of their den and then
questioned him under hypnosis.
It was a very
revealing interview.
Just try to stay relaxed, okay?
Uh-huh.
Now, is it all right if I
ask you a few questions?
Are you from this planet?
I come from the planet Conwell.
How many of you came to Earth?
Three of us: my Dad,
my big brother, and me.
Why did you come here?
We came here because our
home planet exploded.
I see.
There was a civil war.
Everybody kept fighting
until it was destroyed.
What happened to everyone else?
They either escaped to other
worlds or they were killed.
Where's your mother?
She's dead.
On my planet,
males must eat females to
give birth to children.
As we get older,
we start to get
a craving for the
female species.
Do you ever get these cravings?
Yeah, but not for just anyone.
It has to be a certain girl.
What do you do when one
of these "cravings" hits?
I take medicine
and it goes away.
But we're running low-
we're almost out.
Can you still give birth
if you eat human females?
No, my Dad said
it wouldn't work.
But you still crave them anyway.
Yeah.
On Conwell, we call
it the Hollow Stomach.
The Hollow Stomach?
And this medicine you
take makes it feel full.
Yeah, but some said
it wasn't natural.
That's what started the war.
My Dad told us he wished
our kind had never existed.
How did it make you
feel when he said that?
Sad, but I agree.
Why is that?
Because, there's a girl I like.
Sometimes, I crave her.
I'm dying to eat her.
It's hard to fight the urge!
Once it starts to take over...
Hey, are you all right?
...the craving is so strong that
I feel like I'm going crazy!
I'm sick of it!
I can't take it anymore!
Don't cry.
Apparently in their species,
the males prey on
ovulating females
and inseminate
the egg internally.
They must have run
low on females.
But, what I find most
tragic about their kind
is they develop romantic
feelings for their prey.
Their race has been
reduced to three survivors
who are tormented by guilt.
They don't pose a threat to you,
especially since you're men.
The four of you covered
my investigation fee
so I'll refund the rest.
What, you worried
about your girl?
Nah, she could put up one
hell of a fight if she had to.
Maybe I should
check on her anyway.
Man, I wish I had a girlfriend!
Moe Hibino disappeared.
Not long after, Yamamoto and
his family suddenly vanished.
Who wants chicken?
I got dibs on the thigh!
I want the breast!
Yeah, I bet you do.
I told ya, bro,
I'm a breast man!
I guess when it
comes down to it.
We're not really all that
different from them, are we?
The End.
Well?!
I'll pass.
Darker shows aren't
doing well in the ratings.
What?!
Humans deserve to know
the truth about aliens
and that's the whole
point of this show!
They exist and
they're not goin' away!
Not another one
of those freaks.
Yes, sir!
Unfortunately...
...my plan to convince
the humans of our existence
through a fictional
program on television
was a complete
and utter failure.
Baka out.
Chairman, can we try a more
direct approach now? Please?
--For my next plan...
--I have an idea!
Why don't we just tell
the humans directly?!
Sir.
There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
They've gotten so good at
disguising their appearance
and blending in
with the locals.
This is my apartment, you jerks!
It's time for you
to get the hell out!
That they've picked up
on some human behaviors.
Like bein' downright rude.
I think that should just
about do it for today, class.
Ms. Tachibana's an alien?!
That wasn't Ms. Tachibana,
that was an alien monster!
She's a cold-blooded assassin.
I heard she'll even kill
infants if the price is right.
Then why'd you have
to drag us here?!
Not cool, not cool.
She'll kill me. I'm gonna die!
Up next: Here Come
the Color Rangers!
Is it true that
you're an assassin?
It's true all right.