We were bugged?!
We've found our leak.
She's been spying
on us the whole time.
If that's true,
then who planted them?
Colin?
He's checking the garden for me,
he should be back any minute.
Found one!
It turns out Colin
was a spy, after all.
He's probably returned to
the princess's side by now.
So, what is that?
She's a psycho!
Yeah! A total psycho!
And look at all these mistakes.
Did she happen to
mention anything to you
about learning the language?
I think so.
Didn't she say she
studied it fervently?
So the mistakes must
have been intentional.
Yukitaka!
I need ten copies
of each page, stat!
Right!
Go do it yourself!
You think it's a coded message?
Watch, I'll show you.
You can run but you
cannot hide from me.
I have bugs hidden everywhere,
some of which
you will never find.
I finished decoding mine.
Hmm...
What do you get when
you put them together?
Rupachi-gata-kahamirato.
Excuse me?
Her mistakes have to
be related to the code.
What's the matter?
Hey, wha-!
No way!
So that's the trick!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
"On the night of
the round moon,
come to the peak of Mount Honeo
and I will present
you with a quiz."
"I will meet you there,
at eight o'clock sharp."
"The night of the round moon"
She must mean the full moon.
It seems all lines of
communication have been blocked.
I've been unable to make
contact with our mother ship
or anyone else on Dogra.
Have you checked the
teleportation device?
I'm sure they've
found it by now.
When did they do this?!
Well, I had no problem accessing
the system two days ago,
so it must've been
when they visited us.
But they weren't
acting suspiciously!
Maybe they were and
we just didn't notice
because we had our guard down.
They pulled a fast one on me!
This creature is
even more striking!
Damn you!
Can't you see we're on
the brink of calamity?!
You're overreacting.
We simply need to go over
the facts and devise a plan.
How can I take you seriously
when you're jumping for a bug?!
He speaks the truth, Captain.
Here's an idea; why
don't you try asking
the Diskunians for assistance?
Why them?
Think about it, Captain!
They should still have
the means to make
some kind of contact
with outer space.
So I have to go bow down
to that old fart again?
If you want to keep the prince
from getting married, yes.
Uh-huh.
Hopefully, this will shed
some light on our situation.
What do you mean?
I'm sure they assumed we'd
contact the Diskunians for help
after realizing our
communications had been cut.
They've probably already
made their next move.
You're willing to risk your
men's lives to test that theory?
Life is never boring
when you work for me.
If I worked for you,
you'd be dead by now.
I still can't get over
how crazy she is.
She seemed so normal
when I spoke to her.
She could be pretending
to be a psycho.
You never can tell.
After all, she was coherent
enough to encrypt her letter
and cut off my escape
routes- ooh, that's nice.
But why would she go
to such great lengths?
Well, it's pretty obvious she's
completely obsessed with you.
Lucky me.
Has she always been this crazy?
I wouldn't know.
Luna and I stopped
exchanging videos ages ago
and I haven't seen
my brother since
he was about thirteen
in Earth years.
Wow, then it's been
a long time, huh?
Man, I'm surprised you were
still able to recognize him
after all these years.
Right? What if he's
actually a look-alike?
There's no way!
Sure, it's been a while,
but he'd be able to tell--
Hold on.
That's it!
Yay! That one deserves
a hand shake!
Dude, what in the hell
has gotten into you?
You're wrong about me.
I wouldn't be able to
tell if he was my brother.
He and the princess could
very well be imposters!
Huh?!
So, who do you think they are?
The Magra Freedom Alliance.
Say what?
Wait a minute, isn't that
where Princess Luna is from?
Bingo!
There are some
Magrans who resent
their subordinate position
as Dogra's satellite
and they hope to gain
their independence.
This Alliance aims to free Magra
through a bloodless revolution.
Let me get this straight.
You're saying they're
a resistance movement
fighting for their
freedom from Dogra?
Yes, and they've
been very vocal
in their criticism
of the wedding.
They would do
everything in their power
to keep it from happening.
But how'd they get their
hands on the princess's ring?
Easy, they kidnapped them.
They intercepted Mohan
and Princess Luna's ship
on its way to Earth, and then
swapped them out for two
Alliance members in disguise.
Why would they do that?
Because they want me
to marry the imposter.
If the queen of Dogra
demanded that Magra
be granted its independence,
the king would be
forced to comply.
And Dogra would
lose a considerable
amount of power as a result.
Oh, no. That's why--
What's up?
What do you say we
take a little walk?
Now?!
How's it going?
It's hard to say.
I didn't expect him
to catch on so quickly.
You don't think he's figured
out your plans, do you?
I wouldn't be surprised.
"Short walk", my ass!
Why did you bring us
all the way out here?!
Show you, I will.
What?!
This is something I
think you need to see.
Whoa!
What the heck?!
I have a feeling these
ships are from planets
that resent Dogra's vast
intergalactic power.
Among them are the
Diskunians, the Macbacs,
and even the Ellerians.
For real?
Are you sure about that?
Yep. It's all beginning
to make sense now.
This explains why it
was so easy for me
to sneak off the mother
ship to come to Earth.
And why it was placed
under Dogran surveillance
at the intergalactic
conference.
The Diskunians.
The Macbacs.
And even the planet Calvary.
They all had a common goal;
they were tying me
down to this planet.
I would be out of their
reach if I returned to Dogra.
No way!
So, the Magra Freedom Alliance
is behind everything
that's happened
since you landed on Earth?!
It appears that way.
I'm impressed; they certainly
did their homework on me.
Do you think Captain Craft
and Sado are okay?
But, we don't pose
any threat to you, sir!
We're merely asking
for your assistance!
Sorry 'bout this.
I hope it don't make
ya think badly of us.
I'm gettin' pumped!
Uh, Captain?!
Aw, c'mon! You bastards
can't fool me!
You're in cahoots with our
idiot prince again, aren't ya?!
Haven't we been
through this already?!
Sado, can you
believe this crap?!
Could the prince
be that stupid?!
Yes.
Finally. I finally
outsmarted that prick!
Even a diagonally moving bishop
can be taken down by
a quick-witted rook!
Do it.
Poor Craft.
Now then.
You are a heartless man!
We need to come up with a plan.
If we're not careful,
we could lose the Earth.
Huh?!
--Wait, seriously?!
--Mm-Hm.
These forces will serve
as their insurance
in case they're caught.
What do you mean?
I mean that they'll manipulate
them into destroying the Earth
if I refuse to get married.
That makes no sense!
I thought they were fighting
a bloodless revolution?!
Yes, that's true.
But if one of the planets were
to go against their wishes
and attack the Earth,
they would be...
...guilt-free.
Those bastards!
So what do we do now?
First off, I'll expose the
princess as an imposter
from the Alliance thereby
forcing her into negotiations.
How will you do that?
Oh, it shouldn't be too hard.
The real princess has two
moles on her right shoulder.
I like to think they
represent Dogra and Magra.
They were only visible once
so she probably doesn't even
know I'm aware of them.
Here you go.
We've got this one
in the bag, you guys!
Let's party! Who's
drinking with me?!
Prince Mohan and Princess Luna!
What are they doing here?!
Check it out. Captain.
The Magra Freedom Alliance?!
Yep, you got it.
Damn it, Sado! You done yet?!
Almost there, sir.
Apparently, our captors aren't
aware that the secretions
of some Earth insects are
capable of dissolving metal.
Give me one week.
That's all the time I need,
then I'll set you free.
I can't wait for you to see all
the changes I have planned.
Ruthless hussy!
I'll show her!
I know Prince Mohan's ship
like the back of my hand!
Sir, please don't
forget about me.
Prince Mohan!
Captain!
You'll be safe now,
Princess Luna.
Hope those two are
okay on their own.
You traitor!
Uh. I'm sorry!
I wanna pull the trigger!
Not until he
tells us everything!
I must say, I'm
surprised you decided
to show up tonight, brother.
Only because I have a suspicion
I would like to confirm.
And what might that be?
I have reason to believe
you may be imposters.
What?! How dare you insinuate
that Princess Luna--
I'll handle this.
Is there some way that
I can prove myself to you?
If you're the real princess,
you should have moles
on your shoulder.
Perhaps you'll show them to me?
And how do you know about that?
Just like you, I was required
to watch your videos weekly.
And I recall seeing
them on your shoulder
in one of the videos
you sent me.
Well, if that's what it takes.
There they are.
Does this prove it to you?
Yes. Now, I have no doubt.
You are definitely not
the real Princess Luna.
You're with the Magra Freedom
Alliance, aren't you?
She has three moles on
her right shoulder, not two.
I lied about it because I knew
you were eavesdropping on me.
Remember when I said
I would expose you?
You didn't even bother
to check her moles
even though she was
on the ship with you
because you didn't
want to jeopardize
your precious
bloodless revolution.
Luna would never expose her
flesh to anyone but her fiancé,
and there's a chance
she'd commit suicide
if she were forced to.
And how did you figure that out?
Oh, I'm surprised I
didn't catch on sooner,
but during the ceremony
I heard you say.
"I hereby unite the monarchies
of planets Dogra and Magra."
Only someone from the Alliance
would refer to Magra
as a planet and
not a satellite.
Both your performances
were award-worthy,
but Mohan's actor especially.
I love how you turned away when
the princess exposed her flesh.
Nice touch, really.
No! You put that sword
down immediately!
Never, we can't afford
to miss this opportunity!
The Alliance seeks to
gain independence
through a bloodless revolution!
How many years have
we wasted on this plan?!
This was our only
shot and we blew it!
If we want to liberate Magra,
we'll have to kill him!
No, don't!
You can't win, Mohan.
If you strike me down, I
will become more powerful,
but you're not even close.
No way.
Don't move!
The jig is up.
We've got you now.
I am so proud of you, brother.
But, this was all my fault!
I never should've forced the
princess to make the journey.
Please forgive me!
No, I'm the one to blame!
I knew that you didn't want
anything to do with me,
but I couldn't overcome
my desire to marry you!
No, you didn't do
anything wrong.
And this is why I
can't stand these two.
Hey, aren't you forgetting
about something, Princey?
Oh yeah, the quiz!
Let's test your smarts.
There was only one ring
created for Princess Luna,
and it's currently on
the hand of a rebel.
Once the wearer puts it on,
it can never be taken off.
You're going to need this ring
if you want to marry
this princess.
But it's on my finger.
What'll you do?
--Princess Luna!
--Damn you!
That ring is only to
be worn by royalty!
Yeah, like they'd wanna
wear something this ugly!
Just look at this crap!
This cheap little trinket
isn't worthy of our princess!
Is this what you
think of Magra?!
So what'll you do?!
You've had plenty of
time to think about it.
Well?!
You've made your point.
I will do what I must.
I will marry the rebel!
Captain!
I just didn't think
he'd be that stupid!
The king and the rebel.
Got a nice ring to it,
dontcha think?
You're much better than
some sheltered princess!
We'll live a life of danger!
Yeah, I have high
hopes for you, lady!
You're cool! Totally cool!
Our first course of action
will be toppling the dynasty!
After that, we'll
produce an heir:
a nightmarish brat who'll
become our sworn enemy!
All this is going to keep
us really, really busy.
I'll leave my official
duties to you, Bro!
Oops. That would be you, huh?
Not me. I'm a princely
imposter; he's the real one.
I thought you'd be able to
see right through our plans
and I never dreamed you would
actually put your ring on.
I can't believe that
we outsmarted you.
What?! But I don't understand.
The imposters were the
ones being held captive!
This means Prince
Baka is married
to the real Princess Luna!
I'm not a traitor!
I was simply
following the orders
of the real prince
and princess, sir!
Yeah, you were so close
to figuring everything out.
We hijacked their ship
and planned to switch
places with them, but....
They quickly
overpowered our forces
and learned of our plans.
I've got an idea!
How would you like to help
me play a prank on someone?
If she had been your
typical princess,
I wouldn't even have considered
going along with
her crazy idea.
But she's the one who decided
it'd be fun to act like a psycho
and get all the other
planets involved.
You're a real lucky guy.
You just married the most
amazing woman I've ever met.
I used some powder to
cover up one of my moles.
When you said you remembered
seeing them in one of my videos,
it made me so happy to know
that you actually noticed me.
And now that we're married,
I can't wait to spend the
rest of my life with you!
What the hell?!
No! The Earthlings
are gonna see that!
Yeah. Princess Luna spoke to
the intergalactic conference
on behalf of the Earthlings,
and their probation was lifted!
You're fascinating!
There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
Some are friendly,
some are hostile,
and others are
nearing extinction.
Whether they come here to escape
the law, do a little research,
or just for vacation,
they do their best to disguise
their appearance and
blend in with the locals.
And now it seems, the people of
Earth have finally caught on!
Best of luck, kitty.
Wait!
I believe you're
what's called a "cat."
I suppose you'll do.