There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
Some are friendly,
some are hostile,
and others are
nearing extinction.
Whether they come here
to escape the law,
do a little research,
or just for vacation,
they do their best to
disguise their appearance
and blend in with the locals.
A UFO?
The only ones that
haven't caught on yet,
are the people of Earth!
Yamagata! Yamagata!
Ya gotta love the fresh air
outside the big city.
I wasn't planning on making
a career out of baseball.
But I was on the top middle
school team in Japan,
so I don't have
much of a choice.
My position on the team
was basically benchwarmer
but I was still scouted.
And here I am,
thanks to my "talent."
Okay, here comes
the third pitch!
I saw it as the perfect
opportunity to leave home.
Sure, I have to play baseball,
but I get to live on my own.
The center fielder makes a run
for it and catches the ball!
You from Tokyo?
Yeah, originally, but I'm gonna
be starting my freshman year
of high school out here soon.
Good ol' Kisaragi, huh?
Yeah, that's right;
how did you guess?
Easy.
They've been recruiting a whole
lot of new ball players lately.
Watch out, kid,
'cause if you're any good, the
girls are gonna be all over ya.
Yeah, I can't say
I would mind that,
I didn't have much luck
with the ladies in Tokyo.
You just watch, a handsome
city boy with a nice smile?
They're gonna love you!
These calluses are
somethin' else!
Holy- You're a hardcore
player, ain't ya?
This place is full
of baseball fanatics.
So, uh, can I get my key?
Oh, that's right!
Here ya go, son.
Well, this is it.
Woah!
Man, that is one hell of a view!
Life on my own begins today.
Who started unpacking?
It must've been Mom, I knew
she'd pull something like this.
Caught ya, Mom--
Hello. Who are you?
No. That's my line, buddy.
Just who in the hell are you?
Hold on, are you
wearing my clothes?!
You must be the joker who
started unpacking my stuff!
I'm sorry; I was just trying
to help out a new friend.
I am not your friend!
Wanna explain to me how
the hell you got in here?
It's the fifth floor!
Are you some kind of gymnast
cat burglar or something?!
A Burglar?
Don't be silly,
I'm just an alien.
I come in peace.
Take me to your leader.
Huh?
My spaceship crash-landed
on your planet.
There must be a
full moon tonight;
that always brings
out the freaks.
Get outta here, ya Psycho.
I'm sorry, but would you mind
repeating that last part for me?
I haven't completely
mastered your language yet.
I said beat it!
You can't kick me out in the
middle of a conversation.
Leave or I'm calling the cops!
Damn it!
What'd I say?!
Talk about a nut job!
I'll get the landlord
to change my--
What's with you?!
Would you at least
just hear me out
before you decide
to call the police?
Did you hear about the
object that crashed
nearby night before last?
Uh-huh, yeah.
It was just a meteorite.
No, it was an escape pod,
The one I flew in on.
It's all over the news.
Need a spoon?
Oh, Yeah, thanks a lot.
Hey, keep your hands
off my stuff!
I was just trying to help.
There's no need to yell at me.
--This is bad.
--Just drink it!
Unfortunately,
officials won't let us get
any closer to the
site of the crash.
Luckily, one of our
viewers submitted footage
of the mysterious object.
Let's take a look.
I realize the video
quality is lacking
but if we take a closer
look inside the object,
we can see what appears to be
a control system
and a pilot's seat.
--Is this for real?
--It's obvious to this reporter
that this is some sort of space
craft, and not a meteorite.
Told you so.
A space ship crashed,
no big deal.
There's still no proof
that you were piloting it.
Everyone knows aliens
don't wear clothes.
They don't look human either.
So you had better
show me a little proof
if you want me to believe you.
Come, on!
That was enough
proof for Elliott.
I'm not a kid and you're
not a little brown dude!
I have amnesia, okay?!
Which means that I don't really
have any way to prove it to you!
Except...
What is this thing?
Not sure, but I was holding
onto it when I came to.
Looks like a controller, huh.
What the-?
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is terrible!
It appears the UFO has
spontaneously combusted!
I can't see the
scene from here,
but I would imagine countless
lives were lost in the blast!
No way.
You must have activated the
ship's self-destruct device.
I feel sick.
I wonder just how many
humans were killed today.
Who knows how many SDF members,
local officials, scientists,
and engineers were lost!
The crème de la crème of
mankind wiped out in an instant!
So many families
must be suffering.
Newlywed spouses
who've lost their mate.
Newborn children
who've lost a parent.
The loved ones who've been
left behind will be consumed
with feelings of rage and sorrow
that will haunt them for
the rest of their days.
They'll forever wonder
what could have been.
"If only that blast
had never happened."
And, it's all because of you!
You shut up!
It was an accident--I mean,
how was I supposed to know
the stupid thing
was gonna explode
when I pressed the buttons?!
Murder is an "accident" to you?!
This is your fault!
None of this ever
would've happened
if you hadn't broken
into my apartment!
Oh, trying to shift the
blame to me now, are you?
The cops?
Hi, I'm Miho Edogawa,
I just moved in next door.
Here ya go, I brought
a little something for you.
She's cute!
Hi, my name's Yukitaka Tsutsui.
Thank you for the gift.
You know, I just
moved in here myself.
Yeah, the landlord
already told me;
in fact, he wouldn't
shut up about you.
He said you're a baseball star.
I'm workin' on it,
so you live alone?
Mm-Hm.
Or at least it's sure
seemed that way lately.
My dad's work brought us here,
but he's practically been
living at the lab these days.
So more often than not, I end up
with the place all to myself.
Busy man, huh?
Yeah, Daddy's an engineer.
He's investigating
the UFO crash site.
Is something wrong?
Well, uh, there was just
an explosion, so I thought--
Oh, no need to worry.
He called a minute ago
and said he's okay.
Oh, good, Wow, what a relief.
Well, I should probably
start unpacking. See ya later.
Yeah, see ya later.
If you ever need help
with something heavy,
just let me know.
Thanks a lot.
By the way, I hope we're in
the same class at Kisaragi.
Huh?
I'm starting as a freshman, too.
Miss Miho Edogawa.
My high school life
is gonna be so sweet.
Once I get rid of him.
Hit, Hit, Hit, and miss.
I pushed the
self-destruct button
and killed innocent humans!
Ding-dong!
Yeah?
Nice to meet you, neighbor.
My name Miho Edogawa!
You're quite a looker!
You live alone?
My Father busy
investigating UFO.
Wha?! But there was
just a big explosion-
He call, he okay.
What a relief!
Wow, It appears you've got the
makings of a homicidal maniac.
You leave or you die!
I have nowhere to go.
Can't I stay a little longer?
No way in hell!
I'm begging you!
I want you out of my apartment!
In that case, you leave
me with no choice.
That's one, down.
People of Earth,
may I have your attention?
Are you crazy?!
Where did you get this?
I had a feeling this might
happen, so I packed a spare.
No way!
Fine, you can stay.
For how long? Don't forget that
I've got blackmail on you.
Put that thing away!
Must've escaped from somewhere.
Why is that?
It's just that I don't think
parrots are native to Japan.
Fascinating.
I cannot comment on the subject
until we've completed
our investigation.
Can you at least tell our
viewers whether or not the
--object was alien in origin?
--So that's Miho's dad.
As I said, I'm not at liberty
to comment on the subject.
I wish you would've told me you
were picking up instant noodles,
because I prefer the
salt-flavored variety.
Just shut up and eat!
We have breaking
news to report,
according to officials
at the scene,
many of whom were
eye witnesses,
there were no casualties
caused by today's blast.
I repeat, there were no
casualties in today's explosion.
You hear that?
In the future,
I prefer fried noodles.
Listen up, you!
The lady said, that
nobody died in the blast,
which means you've
got nothin' on me now.
"That doesn't change the fact
that you blew up the UFO",
thinks the alien to himself.
Then call the cops
and tell 'em that.
You don't seriously think
they're gonna believe
a freak like you, do ya?
Tell 'em and let's
see what happens.
C'mon, I dare you to.
No, you're right.
They'll never believe
a "freak" like me.
Why should they?
Hey man, are you mad?
No.
Wait, are you goin' somewhere?
I'm leaving.
One last thing, would
it be okay with you
if I kept these clothes?
I don't have anything
else to wear, you see.
Sure, you can have 'em.
Thanks.
Ciao.
Hold it.
You can stay, but
only for the night!
Arigato.
What gives?
He's awfully quiet
all of a sudden.
That device.
Whoa, how'd you do that?
I have to get it back.
We have a sketch based
on eye witness reports.
What do you think it could be?
I couldn't say, but
judging from its design,
I think it's safe to say it
wasn't made on this planet.
They're similar.
Hey, what're you doing now?
I'm getting it back.
Wait!
I can't believe he jumped
from five stories up.
Maybe, he really is an alien.
Idiot!
That bonehead
jumps five flights
and he can't dodge
a freakin' car?!
Crap!
I can't let them take
him to the hospital.
If he's really an alien,
he'll be found out!
What, the?!
Blue blood?!
I don't understand
why you won't let me
take you back to my place.
Because, I don't want to
make a mess of your home.
I need to sit.
Right here?
No, by that tree.
Did you... save it?
Can you give me just
a moment to rest?
This is all the proof I need.
No doubt about it,
he's definitely an alien.
No. It can't be.
Hate to kick you out but I've
got morning practice, so--
Where'd he go?
Come, on! Hit it, rookie!
Don't let your team down!
I won't! Throw it!
I had no idea high school
baseball practice
could be this brutal,
I'm spent and classes
haven't even started yet.
Chin up, Mister Baseball Star!
Morning! Out jogging?
Yeah, I try to do it every day.
I've finally got
the free time for it
now that dad doesn't
come home for lunch.
Speaking of, I saw
him on TV yesterday.
Things have been kinda weird
between Daddy and me lately.
It's almost like he's
hiding something from me.
You really think so?
Well, I called him at the
Konan Institute yesterday,
but he said he was
busy and hung up.
I dunno. He never had a problem
talking to me about work before.
I should really go.
You're busy right now.
See ya!
Miho...
Well maybe, your dad's just
trying not to worry you.
I'm sure he's gonna
tell you everything
when the time is right.
Thanks.
Still not back.
Hello sir, we're
from Konan Station.
Sorry to bother you,
but we've had reports
of a wanted criminal
on the loose in the area,
We were wondering
if you've seen him.
Does this man look familiar?
No, I've never seen the guy.
Well, thank you for your help.
Good day.
'Scuse me, but what is
this guy... wanted for?
He committed murder.
No way.
He's a killer?
Bravo! An award
worthy performance!
You know, I bet you would
make an excellent con artist.
You're the con artist here!
Care for a dumpling?
I'm not really a fan
of red bean sauce.
Tell me, is what
those cops said true?
What'd they say?
They said, that you're wanted
for committing murder.
I'm the one who was
nearly a victim of murder.
Bang.
Whoa, you were shot?
Yes, but I can't
say I blame them.
The situation quickly
escalated to violence.
That's the thing we saw on TV.
Uh-huh, I bet those
"cops" were sent
by the Institute to find it.
So, what is it supposed to do?
It'll prove that I've
been honest with you.
When I was shot, my memories
came flooding back,
and I remembered this
can reveal my true self.
I'll warn you, you may find
the sight of it repulsive.
Would you like me to show you?
Only if you want to.
I'm nervous, but
I feel like I can...
...trust you.
Then let's see it.
Na'shaya.
Mene sakkhet ur-seveh.
You had me freaked
out for nothin'.
You look exactly the
same as you do now.
Just wait.
The real me hasn't
been revealed yet.
What is that?
It's an arthropod from
the planet Jacqueline S
known as a Clive.
It is extremely
adept at mimicry.
You mean that thing,
is the real you?
Do you... find it disgusting?
Are you ready?
I'm going to leave; I've
caused you enough trouble.
Were you trying to pick a
fight with the Diskunians?!
As I'm sure you know, my planet
is full of hotheaded folk.
The kind that ain't afraid
of takin' someone down--
For all we know, the military
could be hot on his trail
right now just waiting
to kill him on sight.
He's messin' with me!
Your friend's an
alien, isn't he?
No, just a commoner in distress.
Up next: Run after the man.
Are there any girls you like?