Where the hell are we?
I could be wrong, but
this kinda looks like-
It is, Koshien Stadium.
No way. I coulda sworn
we still had another round
of play-offs to go.
Yeah, we gotta make it past
regionals if we wanna play here.
It looks like we're about to
skip straight to the finals,
you guys, 'cuz we are
just that awesome.
This is no time for
joking around, guys.
There's somethin'
strange goin' on here.
Yeah, this is weird.
It's too quiet.
You'd think we'd be able to
hear the sounds of the city,
cars driving by and stuff.
Unless the stadium was built
in the middle of a
desert or something.
What's goin' on?!
This better not be the
work of another alien!
There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
Some are friendly,
others are hostile.
But they all do their best
to disguise their appearance
and blend in with the locals.
Keeping that in mind, it's not
too surprising things can go
a little haywire
from time to time.
The bus disappeared?
I watched it happen, man!
It vanished with the whole
Kisaragi High team onboard!
I swear!
That's Tsutsui's team, right?
Are you sure that's
what you saw?
Diskunians have
perfect eyesight!
I can see the
stitches on a fastball
goin' a hundred miles an hour!
Walk me through it
from the beginning.
I was riding my bike
alongside the team's bus.
I wanted to cheer them on
during the forty mile
trip to the stadium.
That sounds rather excessive,
if you ask me.
Then, all of a sudden...
It's like the car
that disappeared
on the Fujishiro
Bypass in 1963.
Did it cross dimensions?
No, it was spontaneous
spatial translocation.
The vehicle was torn apart
at the atomic level.
Wait, that's possible?
Yes, though it's an
extremely rare occurrence.
In fact, chances are
considerably greater
that the bus was somehow sucked
into another dimension.
Now how're we gonna find them?
Man, this is really
startin' to freak me out.
Time to man up, you pansies!
How much you wanna bet it's
just one of them pornogeists?
Captain, I'm pretty
sure you meant to say
"poltergeist" not "pornogeist"!
Bah! What's the
stinkin' difference?!
We made it!
Whadya say we run
victory laps to celebrate
makin' it to the Koshien?!
Are you guys with me
or what?! C'mon!
Talk about dedication.
We're stuck in the Twilight
Zone and he wants to run.
The captain's a
no-nonsense kinda guy.
He's the type who doesn't
even care how food tastes
as long as it's edible.
Shut up! That is not true!
I mean. I make a lunch
for him every day
and he always tells me
it tastes delicious.
Yeah, yeah, he has to say that.
Of all the guys on the team,
I can't believe Fujii fell
for our meathead captain.
Shut up!
You're all just jealous!
Man, I hope we're not dealin'
with another ghost infestation.
Remember the last time?
This is on a grander scale.
There's no other way to explain
our bus just popping
up at Koshien.
Hey, we keep callin'
this place Koshien
but how do we know
this is the real deal?
Yeah. Good point.
Now that ya mention it, I've
only seen the stadium on TV.
Any of you guys ever
been there before?
--Yeah, I have.
--When?
Back when the Giants
were playing the Tigers.
Does it look the same?
Yeah, but somethin'
feels kinda off.
Lemme check one thing
and I'll know for sure.
Uh-huh, their bus was
supposed to arrive a while ago
but it hasn't gotten here, yet.
Did something happen to them?
It's too soon to say.
I'll check back in
with you later on.
They're still not there.
I bet you the Ellerians
are behind this!
What?
If Yukitaka's team wins
regionals, there's a good chance
a high school team from
their turf'll get booted!
They're playin' dirty
'cause they don't want us
winnin' the championship.
I know they did this!
And we're gonna make 'em pay!
Now, now, let's
think rationally!
You don't have any proof!
I love Kisaragi High's
baseball team.
This isn't fair.
I've watched how hard they've
trained to get to this point.
They deserve to win!
We're not gonna let those
chumps get in our team's way!
That championship belongs to us!
Okay, I know you're mad
but let's calm down.
C'mon, let's take him down, too!
No!
Sado.
Do you think another alien race
could be responsible for this?
Maybe for the Norfolk Regiment
disappearance of 1915,
and the incidents within
the Bermuda Triangle.
But this is different.
Well, that's weird,
I'm sure it was right here.
What are you lookin' for?
It's just. I remember seein'
an Okayama Bizen High
sticker underneath this seat.
Maybe somebody scraped it off.
But my name is missin', too!
Wait, what do you mean?
I wrote it here.
You dumbass. You vandalized
Koshien Stadium?!
I felt bad about it. That's
why I wrote it super small.
I thought nobody would notice.
It should still be here.
Even if they cleaned, it
must've left some kinda mark.
You sure you checked
the right seat?
Yeah, I'm absolutely positive!
I memorized the number
so I'd know exactly
where to sit next time.
Look! Row fifteen,
seat fourty-one.
But none of the
seats are numbered!
They were!
Maybe your memory's off
and it wasn't actually Koshien,
but some other ballpark.
No, I was here!
I swear, you guys!
The problem isn't
Tanaka's memory,
this is definitely the place.
Yeah, but his name's missing.
'Cause this isn't
the real Koshien.
It appears to be
a failed attempt
at replicating the
stadium, gentlemen.
What the hell do you
think you're doing here?
Well, I haven't messed
with you in a while
and I thought it'd be fun.
Oh really?
I hitched a ride 'cause
I wanted to cheer you on
at your big play-off game.
I would've walked had I known
the fate that would befall me.
Hey, you didn't have anything
to do with all this, did you?!
Easy, cowboy. You don't think
I'd go to this much trouble
just to mess with you.
Damn you. Urge to kill rising!
Hey, who is that guy, Yukitaka?
Just a punk from
my neighborhood!
Hey guys, c'mere!
You have to see this!
Impossible. Is this for real?
This looks like
Konan Municipal Stadium.
Wait, hold on a second.
All locker rooms look the same
so this could be Koshien right?
No, look over there.
That green washer's in the
municipal stadium's locker room.
I'd recognize it anywhere!
Okay, if this place actually
is Konan Municipal Stadium...
...that door should
lead to the outside.
Where the hell, are we?
I dunno but it
sure looks familiar.
Yeah. 'Cause this is where
they conduct interviews
after the high school
championship.
What's goin' on?!
Is this Konan
Municipal or Koshien?!
Maybe, it's both
places at once.
Home run!
But that doesn't make any sense!
The only parts of Koshien
that have been reproduced
are what can be
seen on television.
It seems he's used a familiar
stadium to fill in the gaps.
Until this point I was
merely speculating,
but now I can say with
absolute certainty.
We are trapped inside
someone's mind.
You treat me so horribly
I don't know why I bother
putting up with you!
Poor you, spending all
my hard earned money!
Work, work! Is that all
you ever talk about?
Well, all you ever
do is complain!
You have no idea
how hard I work!
Stop it!
This is reminiscent of
the Robert Incident
of England in 1920.
It was a bizarre case
where a six year old girl
trapped her father
within her subconscious.
When the father suddenly
reappeared, he told authorities
that he had been inside
his daughter's mind.
So, you don't think
the Ellerians had
anything to do with this?
No, someone under extreme
stress inadvertently
unleashed this
paranormal power.
Then it's likely a member
of the team, right?
Imagine how stressed
they must be
going into this play-off game.
How'd we get stuck
inside someone's mind?!
This is just like
the case in England.
Someone under extreme stress has
created a paranormal dimension,
and now, we are trapped
within their subconscious.
Make it stop!
Please forgive me.
When the little girl's
father apologized,
her stress was lifted.
That's why he was able to
leave her subconscious, right?
I'm sorry!
He shoots, he scores.
All we have to do to get
back to the real world
is eliminate the
source of the stress.
Well, that's easier
said than done.
Yeah, we don't even
know who sent us here.
If I knew, I'd deck 'em.
I know it's the
play-offs and all,
but baseball is
supposed to be fun,
not somethin' you stress
out about, am I right?
Yeah, plus skippin'
the regionals and goin'
straight to Koshien would
be way more stressful.
C'mon, this ain't
funny, you guys!
Would somebody just grow
a pair and 'fess up already?!
Well, I'm so nervous
I could die.
This bein' my last
chance and all.
I feel ya. I'm nervous, too.
It's gotta be someone
who's not here.
It can't be. The whole
team is with us, right?
Anything goes when you're
trapped within
somebody's subconscious!
One of us could be a fake
created by the perp
to throw the others off!
That's right!
You're all suspects!
It could be fatty here.
The weird, pasty guy.
Or this loser.
The only person who
isn't a suspect is you!
Just know that the you
who's busy suspecting
everybody but yourself
could be a phony!
Shut up!
What is wrong with you?!
Why're you tryin' to pit
everybody against each other?!
'Cause it's fun.
I hate you so much!
Why the hell are you
lazy, good-for-nothin's
just sittin' around
when you should be out
workin' up a sweat
like my boy Yukitaka!
There's no sense worryin'
about who got us here.
Oh really? Why is that?
Obviously it's the stress
of the regional play-off
that's gettin' to him.
We'll probably be freed
once the game is over,
but we won't be able to play
as long as we're all stuck here.
That's what I like to call
a never-ending paradox!
What is that?
No way! There's nobody
in the stands!
Cheering from invisible
fans. Well, that's surreal.
Uh. Hey guys? Check it out.
It's Matsukawa Commercial
High representin' Ehime!
There's Imai,
the "Big Slugger"!
They're a tough team to beat.
They're definitely
a fan favorite.
Aw, man, we played against
those guys last year
and they totally
kicked our asses!
That's it! This is the future!
My ESPN is tellin' me
we'll get to the Koshien!
Hey Captain.
It's just called ESP--
Let's massacre Matsukawa
as a warm-up for our game
against Greater Yamagata later!
He seriously wants
to play those guys?!
I don't think we can talk him
out of it, he seems pumped.
I'm all for it! Our team's a
lot stronger than last year.
We can take 'em!
Let's play ball!
Yeah!
It looks like we're gettin'
that final game after all,
even if it isn't
for the regionals.
And hey, maybe this'll be
enough to relieve some stress
so we can get outta here.
I sure hope so.
This isn't your best
game. I'm just sayin.
With runners on first and
second base and no outs.
Kisaragi's screwed!
Geez, did they
forget how to play?!
I won't let 'em blow
this for the team.
Guess it's all up to me now.
You dumbass! They've
got runners, bro!
So the problem child's
waiting at the station.
Yes, sir. It's gotta be him,
Miho told me he's the only
player who showed up.
Well, then there's
no doubt about it.
If the kid's stressing out
about the play-off game,
there's nothing we can do
to remedy the situation.
Maybe not but we can at least
move him somewhere isolated
so the general public
isn't freaked out
when the team
magically reappears.
C'mon, we gotta
rescue 'em somehow!
There's only two
hours 'til the game!
There's no way!
You know, the prince could
probably come up with a way
--to get them out of this.
--Oh yeah!
What's the matter now?
The prince said he was gonna
make it out to the game
by hitching a ride
onboard the team's bus.
Is he okay? What's he doin'?
Thinking up a strategy
to save the prince.
You've gotta think, Craft!
This is a one in
a million chance!
There has to be a way to bring
Tsutsui and his team mates
back safely, while leaving
that imbecile there.
Oh, yes!
Oh, Captain, villains
aren't supposed to sparkle.
Damn it!
I can't believe that fat bastard
got a home run off of me!
They've got five
points now. Big deal.
Yeah, yeah, I know...
I'm betting that Terakado
is the one behind this.
He's made some major
mistakes this game,
and he's obviously
the most stressed out.
Nah, I think it's Fujii.
Everybody knows young women
are more susceptible
to poltergeists.
This may sound weird, but do you
think it could be the captain?
I know he's confident, but
he almost seems too calm,
know what I mean?
You've got a good point there.
Since this phenomenon
happens subconsciously,
the culprit may not necessarily
show signs of stress.
If so, anyone who's calm
is a prime suspect!
And you guys look as
cool as a block of ice!
Leave 'em alone, man.
Boo-yah! Right between
the shortstop and third!
Whether it's real or not we're
playin' a game at Koshien.
Might as well enjoy it, right?
Is that him?
Uh-huh. Are you sure it's
the stress of the regionals
that caused this to happen?
What do you mean?
Well, before all of
my swimming tournaments
I do something called
imagery training.
It's kinda like meditation
but I try to focus on the meets
where I swam really well.
It's pretty amazing how much
I can shave off my time
when I really concentrate.
That's it!
The phenomenon was caused by
the player's concentration,
not stress!
But how is that possible?
While both are
capable of putting
an enormous amount of
strain on the human mind.
It would actually be easier
to trigger this paranormal
power via concentration.
It must've happened on the bus.
He was using imagery training
to prepare for the game.
Unfortunately, his teammates
got caught up in it.
If that's the case,
then there has to be a
way for us to free them.
What if we asked him to try and
concentrate as hard as he did
when the bus vanished-
wouldn't that do the trick?
It's certainly worth a try.
The poor guy's in no position
to be thinking about baseball.
Actually, it's
quite the contrary.
He shouldn't be able to
think about anything but.
Why is that?
As long as the Kisaragi Nine are
trapped in his subconscious,
all his thoughts will
be influenced by them
rather than any
outside stimulation.
--Hell yeah!
--All right!
We've got runners
on first and second!
Number two.
Third Base. Kanemitsu.
Play ball!
Yukitaka's got the right
idea, might as well
make the best out of a bad
situation. Have a little fun.
Yeah, way to go, Kanemitsu!
Show those Matsukawa
bastards how it's done!
Bases are loaded!
It's up to you, Kuramoto!
Ice chips, here! Come get your
famous Koshien ice chips, here!
Number four.
Right Field. Iwata.
Watch out 'cause a grand
slam is comin' your way!
Yeah, Captain! Tell 'em!
Hit a homer and there's
a kiss in it for ya!
That's a deal, baby.
Woo!
Yes! Woohoo!
Grand slam in your face!
Thanks for playin' guys.
Yeah!
Heck yeah. We've got
it easy now, huh?
Yeah!
They don't look too
stressed out to me.
In fact, it looks like
everybody's pretty stoked
about our chances of
makin' it to Koshien.
Not good. If stress
isn't the problem,
then my escape
strategies are useless.
Then please tell me
you have a backup plan.
Strategy number one.
Identify the culprit through the
use of psychological testing.
Then cut them from the team,
thereby alleviating
their stress,
which, in turn, sets us free.
Strategy number two.
Destroy Koshien Stadium,
a place he considers sacred,
and in defense,
he will instinctively
eliminate us from
his subconscious.
Strategy number three.
Commit unspeakable acts
until the culprit's mind
simply can't take anymore.
If we do that,
I have no doubt--
You scumbag!
You wanna play at
Koshien, dontcha?!
Yeah!
I guess we'll have
to settle the score
with Matsukawa on this side!
Uh, what?
He's just talking
about a dream he had.
Yeah, that's all.
Okay. Let's do this!
Yeah!
Hey! Are you not
staying for the game?
The last thing I wanna do
is jinx Yukitaka's team
with my bad luck.
Believe it or not, the Captain
can be quite superstitious.
I was surprised the team
was in such good spirits
when they got back.
They must've played a good game
while they were stuck
in that boy's mind.
Odd. It seems like we're
forgetting something,
but I almost feel like we'd
be better off without it.
I'm celebrating tonight!
Okay. How do I get out of here?
I've gotta go into hiding!
They're after me!
Who's after you?
My younger brother
and my fiancée.
Why would the assembly approve
such a ridiculous bill
in the first place?!
It's truly an honor to meet you.
--So beautiful!
--I know that.
I guess I'll wait here while you
go get me something to eat.
Here's an idea, why don't
you go back to your planet,
marry that princess
and become the king!
Your turn, Brother! Will you
please put on your ring?
Up next: Half moon!
Things have started
goin' batty 'round here.