What is it?
The victim was not
an Earthling, sir.
It seems he was
actually a Diskunian.
Sado!
Leave him to me.
I'm proud to be a Diskunian,
but my species would be
disappointed by my actions.
Maybe I should thank you for
showing me the error of my ways.
I don't know if my death
will be enough to atone
for my shameful behavior,
but I do know that it
will enrage my brethren.
When they find out you're
responsible for this,
they'll come for your hide!
There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
Some are friendly,
others are hostile.
But they all do their best
to disguise their appearance
and blend in with the locals.
While most peacefully coexist,
there are a few bad apples
who're just itchin' to
start an intergalactic war.
And thus the war begins.
Huh?!
We are so dead.
Whenever Diskunians feel
mortally threatened,
they go into a state
of tonic immobility.
It's called "apparent death",
an ancient and instinctual
form of self-defense.
So he was playing possum?
Hey you! No smoking.
The problem is, the
Diskunians find it shameful
despite the fact that it's
an involuntary action.
And why is that?
Well, probably because
it makes 'em look weak
in front of their enemies.
I know they can't help it,
but still that's a
pretty cowardly move.
Yes, that would be true.
From a biological standpoint,
it proves that at some
point in their evolution,
their existence was threatened
by much stronger species.
After a harrowing
battle of survival,
they became the dominant
species on their planet.
So now, they see this reflex,
as a painful reminder of their
race's cowardice in the past.
And to make matters worse,
when one of them is disgraced
it affects the entire species.
They will never rest until
the offender is executed.
Seriously?
So they're basically
alien thugs?
Wait a minute.
It just hit me;
I'm the prince of Dogra!
That's old news!
Yukitaka, fetch me some coffee.
Do you let him just
order you around like that?
Colin.
I want you to send an emergency
signal to the mother ship.
Sorry, but we can't
contact them from here.
That would violate the
Developing Planet Ordinance--
You think I care?! Just do it!
It looks the same.
Huh, weird.
It's not working.
What?
I think I know
who's responsible.
Looks like we're
not going anywhere.
Hello again, gentlemen.
If you hand over the
offender by sundown,
we'll forget this whole
thing ever happened.
But if ya don't, you'll be
in a whole heap a trouble.
Ya said he was just
a commoner, right?
Sounds like you're
gettin' off easy to me.
Captain?
He's toying with us;
he knows we're not
protecting a mere commoner.
Sorry, man.
That can't be good.
Then there's only
one thing to do.
They'll drop the matter
if I'll turn myself in.
Personally, I'm all for it!
But if you don't make it to
the intergalactic conference,
the universe could be at risk!
We're all out of options;
our only hope is to
take full advantage
of their aversion to
harming Earthlings.
Would you two mind
lending us a hand
and posing as our hostages?
He's right.
Collaborating with the
humans would certainly
--increase our odds of escaping.
--Collaborate my butt!
True, but it wouldn't be very
prudent to use them as shields.
As what?!
Captain, I have an idea.
If we use them as collateral,
the Diskunians would
be forced to negotiate.
While it's true they're
incredibly protective
of the Earthlings,
I highly doubt they'd
be willing to negotiate.
They'd just kill us
and take the humans.
Good point.
Don't the Earthlings have
any say in the matter?!
I've had enough of this!
We're not doin'
anything for you jerks!
So forget it!
Watch your mouth or there
might be an "accident"!
So what's it gonna
be, gentlemen?
I dunno know why
yer still tryin'
to protect this
commoner fella,
but I want you to ask
yourselves somethin'.
'zit really worth
startin' a war with us?
Wait!
You can't attack;
we're with Earthlings.
We've become close
with these humans,
and they told us
they'd be mortified
if they witnessed their
best friends being killed,
so they're refusing--
Don't listen to
him! He's lying!
--Please help us!
--Shut up, idiot!
No problem, we'll be sure to
drag you off before we kill ya
so they don't have
to see nothin'.
One more outburst
and you're a dead man!
But I thought we were buddies?
You wouldn't go and kill
your best friend, would ya?
Geez, will you two
knock it off already!
It's a long shot, but
there is one other option.
Attempting to find
out their weakness?
Not quite.
In preparation for the
intergalactic conference,
the prince collected
copious amounts of data
on various intelligent
life forms.
I'm confident that
the Diskunians were
one of the species
that he researched.
You're saying if we can
somehow restore his memory,
we might survive?
Yes, sir.
What's up?
You're gossiping
about me, aren't you?
If you don't wipe that
smile off your face,
I'm gonna do it for--
I recall my grandfather telling
me once that you can jolt
someone's memory
by hitting them with
the same force as the impact
that caused them to lose it.
Hold it!
That's an old wives tale!
It's a cruel method and
a violation of my rights!
I realize that but
we're at our wit's end.
We're running out of time
so we have to act quickly!
Just know that it pains me
to do this, your highness.
You sure about that?
Because it looks
like you're excited.
It has to be done
to save your life!
So!
Well, Sado, did that do it?
Afraid not, sir.
Well, then, we'll try again!
I'm sorry, my prince!
Please say you'll forgive me!
--Any luck that time, Sado?
--No, sir.
Then I'll just have
to use more force!
Don't worry, my prince!
It'll come back to you soon!
Your captain's not
too fond of him, huh?
Uh-uh.
The prince is
incredibly intelligent;
he has a genius mind,
but he also has a serious
attitude problem.
Instead of using his intellect
to help his kingdom,
he uses it to intimidate
and mock his subjects,
making their lives
utterly miserable.
Captain Craft courageously
confronted him about
his behavior, but
ever since then...
...every mission he's been
assigned seems designed
to make him suffer.
So cold.
Wow, that's horrible.
He deserves a beat down.
I guess so.
Uncle? Uncle?
Look.
I know it may seem harsh
but we really need to get
that knowledge from him.
Knowledge, huh?
Any progress, Sado?!
His Crystal Data System!
That's brilliant!
Maybe we can search it!
Aw, damn it!
Guess that means
I have to stop.
Oh no, it's sundown!
Time is up. Move out!
We're about to
break in now, sir.
I'm in!
So much information.
Do you see anything
on the Diskunians?
I'll take a look.
The Diskunians
are so secretive.
How'd he find all
this data on them?
You can ask him about it later!
Just keep searching!
Look for anything we
might be able to use
to get out of this mess!
They're in Yukitaka's room.
Hurry, there's not much time!
Yes, sir.
I found... more data.
Let's see it!
Pull it up for me!
--But, Sir.
--Where is he?
Must be in the other room.
Hurry, Colin!
But sir, I don't think
it's a good idea.
Why is that?
Because the warning
says if we look, we die!
Move! I'll do it!
What's happening?
It's static.
What... is this?
No way!
Excuse me?!
Does somebody
wanna fill us in?
We can't help you if we
don't know what's going on!
We're in for it now.
Yukitaka.
Gotcha.
There's nowhere for you
to run and hide here.
Now hand over the offender.
Are you gonna kill him?
What do you think?
Wait a sec, if he dies, who's
gonna take care of the cat?
If you guys want the Prince,
you're gonna have to
get through me first!
What?!
Sure, fine. Whatever.
"I'll let this slide, if
you three offer your lives
in exchange for the Prince's."
Sorry, can't help it.
Well, then, let's see.
You're Lafferty, right?
Hey.
Did you guys tell him my name?
Nuh-uh.
You know, I wonder how
I would've responded.
As a loyal servant
of planet Dogra.
I probably would've done it.
Wait, what the hell are
you even talking about?
Careful, sir.
You're upsetting him.
So, uh, I guess this
means the jig's up, huh?
Yeah...
It is!
He's the one who
put you up to this!
I thought we fooled 'em!
Yeah, I did too!
We even broke a hole
through the wall!
I'm so confused.
Me too.
Colin, is there a way to replay
it so they can understand?
Sure, give me a second.
The cat?
The prince has been recording
everything with a camera
he hid on that cat.
Which leads us to-
You wanna test yer
subordinates' loyalty?
Correct.
Would your people be
willing to help me out?
Sounds like fun.
We'd love to help!
But, we're gonna need
somethin' from you in return.
We got strict laws against
meddlin' with the humans
in any way, but
everyone's been goin' on
about wantin' a good
look at the kid.
I think I can manage that.
You've got a deal.
Whoa! What's that?!
Testing, testing,
one, two, three, four.
Hello, who are you?
No, that's my line, buddy.
Hi, I'm Miho Edogawa.
Here ya go, I brought
a little something for you.
What does that writing say?
It doesn't really translate.
It's just that
I don't think that parrots
are native to Japan.
Fascinating.
I believe you're
what's called a "cat."
I suppose you'll do.
He's still watching.
He'll be suspicious
if I come right back
but I don't have
anywhere else to go.
My daughter's always saying
these things are bad for me.
I'll have these two stop by
the house and question Miho.
That should be enough
to get her involved.
Have you seen her lately?
She's really "blossomed"
if you know what I mean.
I knocked my front teeth
out just for the role!
You're sure you
want to do this?
Of course man, I've always
wanted to play dead!
So then I say, "I'll let
this slide if you three
offer your lives in
exchange for the Prince's."
Coming soon!
Well, that should explain it.
Do you have any questions?
He was filming us?
Wait. Why would he
put so much effort
into planning
something like this?!
The prince will go to
any lengths necessary
to watch others suffer.
In fact, it gives him great joy.
Wake him up.
I wanna give him
a piece of my mind.
Then I'm gonna
bash his skull in!
You can't do that.
You're standing up
for him even after
the way he disrespected you?!
Oh, believe me, I'm
angry, but his parents,
the king and queen of Dogra,
are two of the kindest souls
you could ever hope to meet.
It's heartbreaking.
I just don't understand why
they've been cursed with
a son who's so despicable.
The very thought makes me cry.
It's so sad!
If it's that bad,
why dontcha just resign?!
Look who's decided to wake up.
The Prince of Shams!
"Going by my face"
what kind of female am I?!
I'm sorry, man, but
the cat's outta the bag.
Evidently they'd already
figured everything out
by the time we got here.
Didn't think you'd
get caught, did ya?
Don't you have
somethin' to say to us?
Like "I'm really sorry
about all this"
or "I kinda got carried away"?
Well?
How dare you go digging
through my personal data?!
That's the first thing
outta your mouth?!
If he dies, who's
gonna take care of the cat?
If you guys want the Prince,
you're gonna have to
get through me first!
Heh.
I'm sorry, but he's
gonna have to die.
Why're you laughin'?
--Put that thing away!
--Are you insane?!
Get a hold of yourself!
I'm sorry, Sado, but that
bastard has pushed me
too far this time and
he's gonna have to pay!
Yes! He's dead!
Captain, no!
Don't shoot!
Colin, get the ship ready!
Sir, yes sir!
I'm exhausted.
Yeah, me, too.
Geez.
'Scuse me?
Yeah? What's up?
Well, uh.
Would ya mind signing
a few autographs for us?
Huh?
Pretty please?
If there's one thing that us
Diskunians are crazy about,
it's baseball!
High school, college,
minor league,
major league, or little league.
We're not picky;
we'll watch 'em all!
Yeah, baseball is the
only thing that keeps us
from causin' trouble
while we're here on Earth!
The only reason you
helped the prince
is because you're
baseball fans?
Yep!
Unfortunately for us, the
big hot spots for baseball,
like Osaka and Kanagawa,
all happen to be in
Ellerian territory.
Yeah! They love the
game as much as we do!
Seriously!
But since we don't
get along with 'em,
we don't get to see many of
the up and coming players.
We were stoked when we
heard a promising player
from the top middle school team
was gonna play for Kisaragi.
So cool!
I'm not "promising."
I'm a benchwarmer.
Well, our leader
thinks you are!
He told us!
That kid's the
real deal, alright.
And he knows his baseball!
Uh, thank you?
Thank you.
Kisaragi High has
finally gotten serious
about beefin' up its
roster this season.
So we know you boys'll go far!
Yeah, we're thinkin'
this team'll make it
--all the way to Koshien!
--Uh-huh.
And when ya do,
we know you guys are gonna
destroy the competition!
And the crimson
championship flag
will finally fly over Yamagata!
We'll do what we can.
Here ya go.
Thanks a lot, man!
No problem.
Oh yeah!
Sorry about all the
damage we caused,
but don't worry, the landlord'll
fix it right up for ya.
After all, he's
a Diskunian, too.
No problem.
If you ever run into any
trouble with other aliens,
just let us know, okay.
'Cause we'll crush 'em!
It's been three
months since then.
Yeah?!
Come on in, I'm decent.
Big news, Miho!
I'll give you one guess who's
gonna be playin' left field
as lucky number seven
at the play-offs!
Congrats! That's so exciting!
I have some other news
too, but it's not as good.
This came in the mail today.
There's no postmark.
You don't think it's
from Baka do you-?
"Dear Yukitaka,
I'm writing now because
I felt absolutely horrible
about leaving the Earth without
ever saying goodbye to you."
That's fine with me!
I'm glad to be rid of the jerk!
"I would've written
sooner, but I was held
in solitary confinement
throughout the conference.
I'm sorry."
"Thanks to my
impassioned speeches,
the conference was
a huge success.
Earth has been placed
under Dogran surveillance
and I was appointed
chairman of the Council Fighting
to Maintain Public Order."
"In other words, your planet
is now part of Dogra's domain,
and I've been made responsible
for ensuring its well-being."
"In order to keep an eye
on things, I've decided
it would be best to take
up residence on Earth.
I'll be sure and drop
by to say hello."
No way.
Hey, you heard what
Craft said about him.
That he always mucks things up.
I know it sounds crazy,
but it's true! For real!
There's no way they're gonna
believe we watched somebody
drag Yasuda's body in,
suck her veins dry
and then eat her corpse;
skin, bones, and everything.
I'm sick of it!
I can't take it anymore!
What'll we do now?
That sick bastard is in
the same grade as us.
The E Course.
Up next: From the Darkness.
Welcome. Please, go
ahead and have a seat.