"The twin-tail mermaid is
an endangered species."
"Attention. Do not tell a lie."
"This species is able to see
through any falsehoods."
What's it matter if
you know I'm lying?
I paid a small
fortune to have you,
so I'm going to have my fun,
whether you like it or not.
Now then, come on out.
Good girl! I'm not
going to hurt you.
Trust me.
There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
Some are friendly,
some are hostile,
and others are
nearing extinction.
Whether they're here to conduct
experiments, plot conspiracies,
or make some cash,
they go about their lives
pursuing their objective.
You liar.
So what now, Shylock?
She's just about earned all
the money she promised us.
What do you think we
should do with her?
The last mermaid, she sure
brought in a lot of dough.
Once the deal's been met and
the cash is in our hands,
I guess we could sell her scales
or we could always stuff her.
Get it?
Well, speak of the devil.
That didn't take long.
You end up killing him, too?
Yes, this planet is
filled with liars.
That's what makes
it so profitable.
C'mon, our next
client is waiting.
See ya later!
I'd better be going, too.
Okay, I'll see you tonight.
Just a few more boxes and
we should be all packed.
Unfortunately, his father's job
is forcing Yosh'ki Shimizu
and his family to
move to America.
When are you leaving?
--In two days.
--Wha?!
But that's way too soon!
I don't think you
should have to move
just 'cause your dad's
job got transferred.
I'd rather stay,
but my mom doesn't
wanna live far away from him.
Then let her go and you stay.
You could always
come live with me.
I couldn't mooch off
of you for five years.
What about our karate
tournament this summer, huh?
You're just gonna
ditch it, aren't you?
I'd love to say I'll see you
at the world tournament, but...
To be honest,
I was planning on dropping
karate in middle school anyway.
You're fulla crap.
No more than you!
Quit joking around!
We know you're upset!
I'm not upset about nothin'.
I can tell you're lying!
It's written all over your face!
Yeah, no joke! Why didn't
you tell us you were moving
as soon as you found out?!
Aren't we your friends?
Since when do I have to report
everything that happens
in my life to you guys?!
--That's what friends do!
--Back off, would ya?!
Cut it out.
You okay with moving?
I don't have a choice, do I?
I guess I'll just have to
make new friends in America.
Well, hello there.
You're injured, I'll go get--
No, I don't want
to see a doctor!
Thank you, but I'm
afraid I'm an alien.
Oh yeah, they'd find out if they
examined you, wouldn't they.
So what else can I do?
You're not scared?
Most kids would be
terrified of me.
Nah, I've met my fair
share of aliens, lady.
Wouldja believe my teacher's
an alien assassin?
You're being honest with me.
How can you tell?
If you had lied, I have this
reflex and it would make
my tongue shoot out
and attack you.
Wow. Glad I didn't, then.
Hey, wait a sec!
One of my buddies has
the power of healing.
I'll just go get him!
Is something the matter?
We kinda got into a fight.
Don't be silly.
Go find him and apologize.
I can't; he's really mad.
Just do it!
You never know when you might
lose those closest to you.
Don't waste precious
time fighting.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
You've got a point. Hang tight!
Shimizu?
Sorry I didn't tell you
'bout the move sooner!
It's cool. Sorry we
were so hard on ya.
Yeah. We were just
really shocked is all.
Yokota. Forgive me!
Would ya quit pouting?
It's not his fault
his dad got transferred
and he has to move away.
Yokota.
Ignore him. Is that it?
Did you just come back
here to apologize to us?
I forgot! I need you guys to
come help me with something!
I told her to wait
right here for me.
She's lost a lot of blood.
We gotta find her
or she could die!
Let's split up and
search. Yokota--
Forget it.
What's your deal?
I still haven't
forgiven you, bro.
Would you just drop it already?!
Dontcha think you've given
the guy enough grief?
Well, he deserves it.
Don't be a jerk about it.
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
Yokota, is there anything I
can do to make it up to you?
Don't ask me!
You don't owe that
big crybaby anything.
Tell him to quit whining.
Watch it, Mayuzumi!
'Scuse me?
Why, you!
Got somethin' to say to me?!
Well?! Let's hear it, runt!
Knock it off!
Quit fightin' would ya?!
We've only got a couple
of days to spend together
'til Shimizu has to move away!
Is this how you guys wanna
remember our friendship?!
What's wrong with you?!
You guys better cut it out!
You don't wanna
piss me off, do you?
Nobody wants that, buddy!
We should stop fighting before
Akagawa here blows a gasket.
C'mon. We made
the poor guy cry.
I think we should call
a truce. Who's in?
I am.
We've gotta hurry and find
that lady before it's too late.
I bet she's lost a ton
of blood by now.
Yeah.
You sure she's worth
goin' to all this trouble?
Mm-Hm. She was
really nice to me.
She's the one who convinced
me to apologize to you guys.
Oh yeah?
I think she might
be feelin' lonely.
Nice! Sounds like
she's just my type.
C'mere guys!
Check it out.
Looks like she left
a trail of blood. Ew.
Blue Charge, let's go!
Yellow Charge!
Red Charge, go!
White Charge, go!
And Black Charge!
Together we are
the Color Rangers!
So did you kill her?
No, I missed her vital organs.
There's no sense in
killin' her like this;
it's her mermaid form
that'll bring in the big bucks.
Hey, grab some tape.
We should cover her
mouth just to be safe.
Earthling children?
Go play superhero
somewhere else.
Now beat it.
Don't make me shoot you.
You healed me?
Oh yeah, you're as good as new.
I thought we had a
deal. Were you lying?
C'mon, you know
better than that.
If I had lied your tongue
would've shot out
and pierced my brain,
killing me instantly.
Ain't that right?
Are they your friends?
Not at all!
While we are from the same
planet, we're different species.
They're poachers.
They make their living
selling exotic creatures,
and I am their...
...merchandise.
That's true.
Twin tail mermaids have
always been big money makers.
When we started poaching
there was such a high demand
they were almost
driven to extinction,
but by the time we
found Lorelei here,
there were only five
left in existence.
We all just wanted to
live our lives in peace.
I remember that day well.
I felt like I had
hit the jackpot.
I knew any one of those
mermaids could pull in
at least fifty customers.
Man, this guy's a jerk!
Yeah. He's even worse than you.
All of a sudden, one of 'em
swam up to me and said...
If you'll leave the other
four alone, I promise
I'll bring in double the amount
they would make you, on my own!
I merely repeated what
my mother once told me.
Her offer gave me goose bumps.
It was just too good
a deal to pass up.
I agreed.
I told her I'd take her back
once she'd made enough money.
And I meant every word.
What can I say?
I guess I was consumed
by my own greed.
The trip to Horn is expensive
and we never planned to
go back once we left.
So the idea of making a pricey
trip just for you pissed me off.
My rage got the best of me.
I wasn't thinkin'
when I shot you.
Can you ever forgive me?
I don't buy it.
You shot her because
you didn't wanna
fulfill your end
of the bargain?
Like I said, I wasn't thinkin'.
--How could you?!
--It was stupid of me.
I promise, I'll take you
back to be with your kind.
Don't listen to him. He's lyin'!
No, he's being honest.
Doesn't this seem fishy to you?!
If he lied, I could hear it.
That's right.
Twin tail mermaids have a
unique defense mechanism,
they can hear the brainwaves
of other species.
Their subconscious then
separates fact from fiction.
They instinctively
kill liars because
they pose an immediate
threat to their safety.
Yet here we are, standing
right in front of you.
That should be enough to prove
we've never lied. Right?
Come on.
I'm sure your friends
are awaiting your return.
Let's wrap this up so
you can go back to them.
Don't go.
You believe him?
I do. He hasn't lied.
He will take me back to them.
--Akagawa?!
--What the hell was that for?!
He's obviously lying!
I'd know!
You can read their brainwaves,
but who really cares?
I don't need some stupid
power to know they're lying!
I can tell just by
looking at their faces!
Akagawa's right.
Let's go get 'em, fellas!
No, wait!
Damn brats!
You don't know who
you're messin' with!
Ah man, you are one ugly mofo!
Yeah, you wouldn't
sell for squat!
Shimizu!
Yokota!
Giga Bomb!
Why, you!
You're good!
Battle Light go!
Ready to take him out?
You know I am!
Hiya! Hiya! Hiya! Hiya!
Hiya!
Hiya! Hiya!
It's just as I thought.
They were using these to
manipulate their brainwaves.
That's why you couldn't tell
they were lying to you.
The other four mermaids,
are they still alive?
Answer me!
Tell her or I'm gonna
kneecap all three of you.
No, don't shoot! I swear
I'll tell her everything!
They...
We sold them too.
So, they're probably--
no, they are... dead.
I don't know what
I'll do without them.
All my friends are
gone. I'm alone.
You haven't lost
all of your friends.
My name is Yoshiki Shimizu.
Osamu Momochi.
Just call me Yokota.
I'm Mayo Mayuzumi.
And I'm Taiyou Akagawa!
Nice to meet ya!
I can't thank you boys enough.
I put my cell phone number
in here, so call me anytime.
I promise I'll pick up for you.
Easy, man, you don't
wanna get tongue-stabbed!
Thanks again.
I'll give you a call!
--Yokota.
--Hm?
I don't wanna move to America!
It's about time you
finally 'fessed up.
You hate me, don't you?!
Maybe.
We're cool.
Thanks, man.
Who's the crybaby now?
Wha-?! I am not crying!
Hello?
Yeah, did you see it on
the news? Crazy, huh?
Well it turns out the
guy who was murdered
was one of the top
businessmen with our company.
Remember the creepy guy
I was telling you about?
Yeah, it was him.
He was the reason we were
moving but now that he's gone,
all foreign transfers
have been cancelled.
I guess this means I
should start unpacking?
Yeah, sorry. I'll help
when I get home.
Tell Yoshiki as
soon as you can.
He'll be happy to hear the news.
Wow, your tail's split in two!
I've never seen
anything like it!
Where the hell are we?
The bus disappeared?
Their bus was supposed
to arrive a while ago.
I bet you the Ellerians
are behind this!
How much you wanna bet it's
just one of them pornogeists!
You've got a good point there.
The vehicle was torn
apart at the atomic level.
The only person who
isn't a suspect is you!
Just know that the you who's
busy suspecting everybody
but yourself could be a phoney!
Up next: Field of dreams!
Who is that guy, Ukutaka?
Just a punk from
my neighborhood!