This game of tag is over.
But Princess Saki, there's
something you should know
about that boyfriend of yours.
You can tell her
whatever you want.
But nothing you say is
ever gonna tear us apart!
Save the lines for
the movies, Romeo.
It's over!
We know you're
not really a boy!
But, I don't understand.
The name of the person you ran
off with is Kyoko Mikihisa.
She's a woman.
A woman?
It doesn't matter if
I'm a guy or a girl!
All that matters is how
we feel about each other!
Sure about that?
Tell them you love me; tell them
this doesn't change anything!
We were brought
together by fate.
Wait a second!
No matter how much
you love her,
there are some things
in this universe
that require a male and female.
It's not fair.
It's nothing personal.
It's just that I'm not into
other girls like that.
That'd be way too
weird. No, thank you.
I'm sure fate will
find someone for you!
Just not me, okay?
I was so sure.
When you came into my life,
I thought fate was finally
smiling down upon me.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
I must return to the mother
ship ahead of schedule.
I see. That's unfortunate.
I'll consult with
the previous queen.
Then perhaps I can find
a solution to all of this.
I wouldn't take it so hard,
Earth just wasn't meant for you.
You're young, so I'm sure
you can find a better match
somewhere else in the universe.
I-I wish it were that easy.
You're gonna make me cry.
I'm sorry for all the
trouble we caused you.
It must've come
as quite a shock.
Of course it was.
Can't have babies if you
hook up with another female.
That was inappropriate, sir.
This affects the survival
of an entire species.
All the same, it's not
our problem anymore.
What's she gonna do now?
You think she'll
look for another mate?
Hard to say.
I've never heard of a Macbac
choosing a second mate,
but this is a unique situation.
Either way, I feel
kinda bad for her.
I find it hard to care since
she threw Mikihisa away
the second she found
out she was a woman.
It's not like that!
Even though she felt
confused and betrayed,
she never blamed Mikihisa for
what happened between them!
You can believe
whatever you like.
I'm just happy
that they're gone.
There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
Some are friendly,
some are hostile,
and others are
nearing extinction.
Yet somehow, they all
exist in a curious balance.
Now, it would appear that
balance has been restored
and the Earth is saved!
Prince, what're you doing here?
I thought that you were
still in Southeast Asia?
This poor thing finally
deposited its eggs
only to end up like this.
Apparently, it lived a
full life despite being
infected by a parasitic fungus.
Don't ignore me!
I'm sorry, were you
saying something?
So, Craft, did anything
happen while I was gone
that you might want to
report to your leader?
Uh, no. Well,
nothing I can think of.
Oh?
I know you're trying to hide
the Macbac's visit from me,
so stop pretending!
How'd you find out?!
It was a lucky guess.
And by 'lucky' I mean that
I knew they'd be mating soon
and I figured you must've been
dealing with a dignitary
since you're wearing
your spiffy suit.
Even I didn't know
I was so smart!
It isn't your fault he's
an evil genius, Captain.
But how did you find us here?!
No way that
was a lucky guess!
Easy peezy, 'cause you used
your home phone number
to make the reservation.
You bugged it, didn't you?!
Bugging is such a nasty--
Yes, I did.
I'll kill you!
Does that mean she was
here looking for a mate?
Yes, that's right.
Interesting.
My princess.
It's a delicate situation.
We resolved the
problem on our own,
so there's no reason
for you to get involved.
You're being entirely
too optimistic.
I can't imagine the
princess of the Macbacs
giving up that easily.
But, we saw her leave
the planet ourselves.
There's no doubt.
I'll never forget the tears
in her eyes as she flew away.
You should know better than
to trust a female's tears.
That's a fundamental law known
throughout the entire universe.
What is that?
A listening device?
Wait a sec, when did she--
Damn! She played us
for a bunch of fools!
Other than the part
about her being a girl,
it seems their "translations"
were full of crap.
They certainly
underestimated us.
Considering Dogra's position,
I suppose it's only natural
they'd go out of their way
to protect the Earthlings.
My suspicions were correct.
The Dograns were bound and
determined to prevent me
from mating with a human being.
Just because my beloved
was revealed to be a woman,
it does not mean
that this is over.
Damn it! Where'd
she run off to?!
Maybe to a rendezvous
with Princess Saki?
It seems they've made
contact with her.
Yeah, but why would
they even bother?
They know Kyoko
Mikihisa's a woman!
All they have to do
is turn her into a man.
I had no idea they
were capable of that!
Oh, it's quite common.
I used to be a female
myself, you know.
Wha?!
Whoa!
That was a joke.
Damn, it's gonna take months to
get that image outta my head!
How could Princess Saki make
such an obvious mistake?
Mikihisa's brain must
be similar to a male's.
That's true! Good point.
There are differences between
the male and female brain.
For example, the part
known as INAH 3
is significantly
larger in males.
This helps dictate
sexual behavior,
so if Mikihisa's was enlarged,
it may explain her behavior
and the Princess' confusion.
What difference does that make?
She still has a female body
so it's not like
they can procreate!
I meant it when I said
they could change her.
That's not
scientifically possible.
Before poo-pooing my idea,
ask yourself this.
After generations of
successful mating, how could
Princess Saki mistakenly
fall in love with a female?
Wait, you aren't suggesting...
I suspect a study of Kyoko
Mikihisa's genetic makeup
would reveal she's
virtually a dude.
Let's go! We gotta find her!
I bet those clowns from Dogra
are in a panic right now.
But it's too late.
There's nothing they can do
to keep me from my beloved.
I've never seen you so happy!
The greater the challenge,
the greater the sense
of accomplishment.
Since I'll never
experience it myself,
would you tell me what
it's like to fall in love?
It's an almost overwhelming
feeling of elation,
like the end of the hunt,
when your prey falls,
but it's even better.
Is that an accurate
description, mother?
Indeed, it is exactly
as you said.
However, it is nothing compared
to the feeling that awaits you
after you have mated, my dear.
Watching my mate's
species slowly go extinct
was the most exhilarating
thing I've ever experienced.
It was then that I
understood what it meant
to be Queen of the Macbac.
Soon you shall know that
joy too, my princess.
Captain, look! One of the
snowmobiles is missing!
It must've been her!
Unfortunately, the snow
has covered her tracks.
I guess we'll just have
to find her on our own.
She'll be at the Shimo
Forest Park at 11 PM.
How do you know?
Y'know that note in the
ashtray? I restored it.
To hide evidence, you have to
burn it until it's crumbled ash.
Kyoko Mikihisa has a
unique genetic makeup,
in some ways male
and in other ways female.
All it would take is a
tiny tip of the scales
to change everything.
Of course, with the Macbac's
scientific prowess,
that would be easy.
What is going on here?
Hey, why do you have my scarf?
Princess Saki is anxiously
awaiting your arrival.
Damn it! Where did she go?!
Aw, crap!
I knew they wouldn't make it.
You may look like a woman,
but deep down you're a man.
Don't worry; I'll help you
show your true form.
I promise it won't
hurt, my love.
Just leave it to me.
All right class, let's give a
warm welcome to our new student.
Meet Kyoko Mikihisa.
I wanna be treated like one of
the guys, so call me Mikihisa!
You're so funny!
She wants to be
treated like a guy?
This is some kinda joke, right?
Why would you try to
kiss another girl?!
You're a freak!
Get away from me!
Sorry Mikihisa,
but you're a girl.
I'll only ever see
you as a friend.
No, wait! Don't go!
I'm a man, Satomi!
I'm not a girl!
That's right, my darling.
You weren't meant to be a woman.
Who're you?
I'll be waiting for you,
my destined one.
Whoa. What the-?!
I don't know why, but
my head feels really fuzzy.
My scarf.
Am I forgetting something here?
Crap! It's time for work!
Those are some biiiig boobs.
No kidding.
Hey! Would you please
take this seriously?!
It's part of our
observation, right?!
Since the Macbac supposedly
operated on her,
we're supposed to be
checking out her body!
If you keep making a fuss,
she'll notice you.
Let's not start out the year
with accusations of voyeurism.
It's not like we're
peeping toms! Jeez!
They've definitely
altered her somehow.
But it may be a while before
we see any physical effects.
So she's slowly going to
start turning into a dude?
Then maybe we can
reverse the process.
You think it's possible,
Mr. Scientist?
I would have to
do some research--
Hey, is the soup ready yet?
We've got a major emergency
and all you can think
about is eating?!
Who am I to butt in on
their little romance?
Why's it always about you?!
The fate of the Earth
is at stake here!
Here you go.
Sorry for the wait.
That looks yummy!
Don't ignore me!
We would be liable if
the humans went extinct.
Hey, wouldn't it be funny
if we were put on death row?
Look! It's so stretchy!
I'm already there.
New Year's Special.
One soybean and
one herring roe pizza!
I hope you guys enjoy it.
She didn't even bat an
eye. What happened?
It would appear they've
erased her short-term memory,
which means she's completely
forgotten the ski trip--
including her encounter
with Princess Saki.
Buy why would they do that?
They're probably making a second
attempt at a first meeting,
I would guess. The Macbac
are very particular about
love at first sight, you know.
Oh, give me a break.
It's believed that creatures
with complimentary genes
are drawn to each other because
it evolves their species,
that's how some
explain the concept
of "love at first sight."
In other words, the
pairing is more about
the success of the
lineage than the couple.
But is that a legit theory?
Not according to the
academic community at least.
Well, the Macbac
didn't get the memo.
Love at first sight's how they
confirm genetic compatibility.
Who ordered this garbage?
It's totally nasty!
You did, stupid!
So the princess is
after her genes?
Is there something
about Earthling genetics
that makes them more valuable?
It's hard to say, since
humans only understand
a small portion of
their genetic code.
I wouldn't be surprised if
they had a hidden treasure
buried in there somewhere.
In fact, some races
have abducted humans
to collect samples for testing.
Now that you mention it, maybe
that isn't such a bad idea.
Looks like I'll make the
delivery right on time.
What's the verdict?
I had to throw this vaccine
together on short notice,
but I'm pretty sure
it'll do the job.
Hold on.
If you haven't
done this before,
shouldn't you try running
a simulation first?
I suppose it wouldn't hurt.
What is that?
A reverse-anti-virus!
Basically, if I attempt
to inject my vaccine,
a program will cause
the virus to activate.
Are you kidding me?!
When it comes to genetics,
the Macbac are one of the most
advanced species
in the universe.
They knew we'd be
powerless to stop them.
Otherwise, they would have
kept her in captivity
instead of returning
her to Earth.
That true?
I'm afraid so, sir.
Great!
Man, they almost hit me.
Huh?! What the-?!
It was ten after just
a second ago! Crap!
All of humanity wiped out
because of one stupid girl!
And you're sure we're
completely out of options?
Even the vaccine idea
was stretching it.
Damn!
I wonder what's going
through her head right now.
We've got no choice.
The only way to save humanity
is to finish her off!
--Don't do it, Captain!
--Calm down!
Let me go!
You'll get the death penalty
if you murder an Earthling!
If I'm screwed either way,
I might as well play dirty
and save the human
race, right?!
Well, if we break a few rules,
I can come up with
all sorts of solutions.
Yeah, like what?!
It might be problematic.
What could possibly be more
problematic than this?!
I don't care what it takes-
I'll do anything to stop them!
You realize I'm going
to hold you to that.
Uh, just for the record, what
exactly did you have in mind?
Everything is going
according to plan.
Those idiots from Dogra
tried to step in,
but it looks like
they're out of ideas.
What's Saki up to?
Learning about Earth
in her sleep.
She hardly knew anything about
their language and customs,
so it's taking
longer than expected.
Well, I'm sure the fact that
she'll get to see her mate
when she's done is
keeping her motivated.
Hi, there.
I haven't seen you around here
before; my name's Mikihisa.
My name is Saki.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Wow, it worked like a charm!
Of course it did.
Now all we have to do
is wait for them to mate
and we'll be set.
No matter what, the Macbac Queen
only mates once in her lifetime.
Even if she does catch on,
it'll be too late.
Do you hear that?
The operation was a success.
Shut up!
No, you shut up.
What's your problem?
We made an exact clone of Kyoko
Mikihisa and even planted
all of the original's
memories inside of it.
Of course, that in itself,
wouldn't have
accomplished anything
so to prevent humanity
from going extinct,
we equipped the clone
with a special anti-virus
that will activate when it
mates with Princess Saki.
Then, as if we hadn't screwed
with Mikihisa enough already,
we tweaked his genes so that
he wouldn't fall in love
with Saki again, made him move
away to some distant city,
then replaced him with
the clone we created.
And we altered
his memory, too.
By that point,
we'd broken well over a
hundred intergalactic laws.
I never thought I'd end up
living a life of crime.
Are you saying there's a better
way we could've done it?
I've been thinking, but I
can't come up with anything.
The princess gets to
preserve her species
and humanity won't go extinct.
I'm sure Mikihisa is happy
to be a real man now, too.
Maybe this plan left you
with a guilty conscience,
but I think that's a small
price to pay, Captain.
What do you mean "this plan"?!
Did you come up with another
idea and not tell us?!
Hey now, don't be judgin' me!
I made a point to choose the
plan that would give you
the least amount
of mental anguish.
So you did have
another idea after all!
Just spit it out-
I deserve to know!
All right, but you're
gonna regret it.
I was a fool to ask.
No good can ever come
from his twisted mind.
Come on, how bad
could it really be?
Too bad for me to repeat.
Oh, I have no problem
telling you too!
You see, first off--
Spare him!
Even as alien races seek
out the genes of humans,
mankind continues
to destroy itself.
Transformed by radiation,
industrial waste and
unknown viruses.
It may not be long before
their much-coveted genes
become undesirable and
the intergalactic community
looks away from
the Earth in disgust.
Even as it comes to pass,
we may never know whether
that's a blessing or a curse.
"The twin-tailed mermaid
is an endangered species."
She sure brought
in a lot of dough.
...but I'm afraid
I'm an alien.
"Do not tell a lie."
I need you guys to--
Quit joking around!
We know you're upset!
--You're fulla crap.
--So, did you kill her?
No, I missed her vital organs.
She's lost a lot of blood.
--Don't be a jerk about it.
--You're okay with moving?
I guess I'll just have to
make new friends in America.
Up next: Boy meets girl.
You liar.