So are they Ellerians, Gramps?
No, that's a Dogran ship.
Ever since this planet
was put under their watch,
things have started
goin' batty 'round here.
Where's my brother?
Unfortunately, he wandered
off a few days ago,
and we've been unable
to track him down.
You, of all people, know how
difficult the prince can be.
You must find him at once.
Yes, sir!
This is the place.
The planet that he calls home.
There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
Some are friendly,
others are hostile.
But they all do their best
to disguise their appearance
and blend in with the locals.
The only ones that haven't
caught on are the Earthlings.
Coming!
Hey!
Not you again! Crap!
I've gotta go into hiding;
they're after me!
Who's after you?
My younger brother
and my fiancée.
After you.
The second prince of Dogra,
Mohan Ki Et Dogra,
is a simple and honest man.
He's very popular
amongst the citizenry.
He's the prince they trust.
They bemoan the fact that
he's the second born
because they'd prefer
him as their ruler.
Then there's the first princess
of Magra, Luna Mi Mad Magra.
Her parents contracted
us to be married
before the poor dear
was even born.
While most women
would be horrified,
Princess Luna is content to
marry a complete stranger.
I am truly baffled
by that creature.
It's incredibly hard for me
to relate to either of them
because of their
conservative nature.
Yeah, I can imagine.
Hey. That's a sweet
new bench press.
Well, after playin'
at the Koushien,
I just gotta stay
fit for the scouts.
Betcha don't make
the scouts drink this.
If you don't like it, leave!
Will I be using the
same futon as last time?
Yeah, is that a problem?
Well...
Excuse me?!
I don't know how
to tell you this,
but I'm kind of a big deal.
Here's an idea, why don't
you go back to your planet,
marry that princess
and become the king!
They got fluffy beds
waitin' for ya!
--I'll never become the king.
--Why?!
Because I went to
a lot of trouble
to convince Dogra's Succession
Assembly to pass a bill
that would keep me
from taking the throne.
What bill?
This legislation requires
the heir to the throne
to be married before
reaching adulthood.
If this condition is not met,
the right of inheritance
will be transferred to the
next in line of succession.
I'm surprised the assembly
passed the prince's bill
without an amendment.
I've approached them about
revising it but they refuse.
Why?!
Why would the assembly approve
such a ridiculous bill
in the first place?!
The first born prince has
always inherited the throne;
it's an age-old
Dogran tradition!
Well, not anymore.
You know. I think traditions
are kind of like rules;
they're made to be broken--
This bill will permanently alter
Dogra's line of succession!
Nobody wants that
idiot brother of his
to become ruler of Dogra.
Why doesn't he realize the
assembly's trying to prevent it?
Based on this planet's
measurement of time,
my brother only has one month
before he becomes an adult.
And if he fails to marry
Princess Luna within that month,
then the right of succession
will be transferred to me!
That's true. I know it
would break with tradition
but there are many Dograns who
would prefer you as their king.
But I'm not meant to
be the ruler of Dogra!
It's my duty to act
as his assistant,
and the exact same can be
said for Princess Luna.
I won't let my brother lose
his right to the throne!
I'll find him and ambush him
with a wedding if I have to!
Ah, crap.
And well, there it is.
So, basically you're playing
a game of cat and mouse.
If you avoid them you win,
but if they catch you and force
you to marry Luna, they win.
When did you get here?!
That's it, exactly.
Thankfully I have Captain Craft
and his men on my side.
They'll keep Mohan and
Luna from tracking me down.
But they've got a
month to find you!
I'll just stay in hiding.
I can't believe those
two actually think
they're smart
enough to catch me!
I mean, this is me
we're talking about.
Hey. Is it weird
that I'm rooting
for his brother even though
I've never met the guy?
Do I want ramen? Or ramen?
--Don't just help yourself!
--Okay, okay.
I guess I'll wait here while you
go get me something to eat.
But you better
get a move on.
You don't wanna miss the big
sale they're having at Q-Mart.
You can starve to
death for all I care!
Now, now, let's calm down.
Why are you so dead set against
becoming the king anyway?
You'd have the freedom to
do whatever you want, right?
No, not so much.
I'd get stuck with all
kinds of dumb kingly duties.
I'm a free spirit
who shouldn't be
bogged down with
responsibility!
All I have to do is
get through the month--
I found you!
Whoa. Who is that?!
It's my brother.
--What?!
--Huh?!
Now I hereby unite
the monarchies
of planets Dogra and
neighboring Magra.
May the marriage
of Baka Ki El Dogra
and Luna Mi Mad Magra
bring peace to us all.
Wow, your little brother is
just as brazen as you are.
I can't believe it myself.
Mohan has never confronted
me like this before.
I'm completely stumped
as to how to handle this.
Well, you better
start thinking fast!
Damn, that's cool!
And now, you'll put on
your respective rings
to conclude the ceremony.
Princess Luna will
put her ring on first.
May I say a few words?
My beloved prince, it's
truly an honor to meet you.
I've dreamt of this
moment my entire life.
And now here we are,
face to face.
Seeing you in person
has only strengthened
my feelings for you.
So, what is she
rattling on about?
Just the usual female stuff,
blah blah feelings.
I vow to be your devoted
wife for all eternity.
Is that a ring?!
Yes, it's a special
bio-ring created for royals.
Once you put it on...
...it becomes part of your flesh
and you're stuck
with it for life.
No way!
If she was infatuated with me
before we'd ever even met,
that would make her a psycho,
which is totally my type.
So you're into the
crazies too, huh?
Your turn, Brother! Will you
please put on your ring?
Just do it, and put
an end to this nonsense!
The citizens of Dogra
are depending on you
and I refuse to sit idly by
while you choose
to neglect them!
You've had your fun.
Now it's time to grow up--
You're not my boss! The real
fun hasn't even started yet!
I'm starting my Massive Fun
Earth Alteration Project soon--
I have no idea what
your brother said
but I'm pretty sure
you're in the wrong here!
Uh, Yukitaka!
He's gone?!
Brother!
They arrived sooner
than I anticipated.
Yeah, they headed
straight for the apartment
when they left our house.
I suspect someone's
leaking information.
Why aren't Mohan's
bodyguards with him?
Perhaps he decided he would
rather make the trip alone.
Uh, I don't think so.
He probably thought you two
could talk this out peacefully
so there'd be no need for them.
Mohan would never travel
without his bodyguards.
Something fishy's going on here.
So what do you think has
him so deep in thought?
Like I'd know! But I've got a
bad feeling about this, Sado.
Oh. Hey, I'm sorry.
Let me pick up that mug for ya--
No, you can leave it.
This is the mug that he was
drinking from, wasn't it?
I can sense it.
It's still warm.
Holding it makes me
feel closer to him.
Hold on. You speak
our language?
I fervently studied to master
it because someone once told me
that he is fond of
your local tongue.
Wait, who's fond of it?
That stupid--I mean, she must
be talking about Prince Baka.
There's nothing like
a good workout, huh?
You'd never hear that from
his lazy brother, would you?
Yeah, no joke.
Yukitaka?
How do you know
my name, Princess?
Well, I had you investigated.
I heard he stayed with you
when he first came to Earth,
so I wanted to learn
more about you.
O-kay.
I have a favor to ask.
If you don't mind,
would it be all right if
I stayed here with you?
But Princess, we still
have to find my brother.
I am well aware of
that Prince Mohan,
but he will not be
an easy man to catch.
We may be going about
all this the wrong way.
I think it would be best to
wait here until he returns.
Are you sure about that?
I mean, you barely
know me, right?
And my place is a bachelor pad.
In that case,
I shall stay as well.
Huh?!
There must be someone
here to protect her.
Don't worry, I promise
we won't impose on you.
You have got to be kiddin' me.
Sorry, Yukitaka, but it looks
like you're stuck with 'em.
He almost had us fooled.
But he's a schemer,
just like his brother.
A real-life princess.
So, how did he choose
to spend his time?
Well, let me see.
When he wasn't
busy tormenting me,
I would usually find
him reading in here.
Oh yeah! He also
liked watching TV.
What is TV?
It has been over
a year and a half
since our first close
encounter with a UFO.
However, it appears that the--
What is that?
What the hell do they see?
As you can see, we analyzed
the data you sent us
and as a result, we were
able to reveal the ship.
This is a bad idea. It violates
multiple space ordinances.
Good point, I suppose
we'll need a fall guy.
I choose you!
Try to keep your cool, sir.
If we're not careful, he
could become our next king.
I know that.
Could you show us the
other ship as well please?
They haven't found the
escape pod, your highness!
If you hurry, you could
use it to flee the planet!
That's odd.
Sorry?
They know it'd be impossible to
catch me if I made it into space
yet they didn't bother
looking for any spacecraft.
Doesn't that seem
rather strange?
Yes, it does.
That's true, but we all know how
impulsive Prince Mohan can be;
he probably just didn't take
the time to come up with a plan.
No, he always has a strategy.
He's without his bodyguards
and he hasn't blocked
my escape route.
Oh no.
I-Is something wrong,
your highness?
He wouldn't dare.
So early.
Princess?
I guess she went out.
You don't mind if I
borrow them, do you?
Thank you, Miho.
I appreciate it.
Oh, I'm sorry! I didn't
mean to wake you up.
No, I'm sorry! I swear I'm not
a peeping tom or anything!
It was totally an accident,
so don't call the cops!
Huh?
Go back in and close the door
while I've got my eyes covered!
Uh...
Hurry 'cause the
hand's comin' off!
Good morning, Yukitaka.
I'm sorry.
I went by Miho's apartment to
borrow some clothes from her.
But...
I hope it's okay;
I needed to take a shower.
It's cool.
Why is he staring
out into space?
How should I know?!
Where are we? And why'd he
drag us all the way out here?
Just as I suspected.
Is there something
flying overhead?
No, sir.
The clouds are in same
formation as yesterday.
Impossible!
My guess is they're using a
wormhole to create a barrier
and they're projecting this
artificial sky to hide it.
But why?!
Ridiculous! Attempting
such a thing would cause
a fluctuation in
time and space.
We would've caught
on right away.
What if the barrier surrounds
the entire planet, huh?
Then we wouldn't
notice the change.
Do you honestly believe they'd
go to such an extreme measure?
It is possible,
but the only way to know
for sure is to see if
there's anything lurking
beyond the Earth's atmosphere.
What the hell is going on?!
This is just one small area.
I would venture to guess
there are thousands--
more likely tens of
thousands of ships,
currently surrounding
this planet.
But why?
Hard to say, but,
it's safe to assume
someone went to great
lengths to summon them here.
But why haven't the people
of this planet noticed yet?
I realize the spacecraft
are hidden behind a barrier
but the Earthlings depend
on countless satellites--
It would be incredibly
easy to gain control
of their satellites'
communication.
Earth has very few
vessels that are capable
of reaching outer space,
and their primitive aeronautics
leaves them open
to manipulation.
Precisely.
The real mystery here is:
Who would stage such a
large-scale event and why?
Is it Prince Mohan?
He certainly has the motive
to be our prime suspect.
The barrier has successfully
trapped me on this planet.
But if that's all he was after,
then this should have
been handled differently.
All right, I confess!
I invited them all
here for your wedding.
How did you find us?
I knew you three were in
cahoots with my brother
from the moment I landed here.
I assure you, it's
not what you think,
and please believe
me when I say
we only have Dogra's
best interests at heart!
No need to worry.
I don't intend to
make an issue of this.
You're simply doing your job
as my brother's bodyguards.
So you mean,
we're not in trouble?!
That's Prince Mohan for you!
Princess Luna is at Yukitaka's
apartment awaiting your return.
And you expect me to
just waltz over to her?
Hey, a guy can hope.
Brother, I know you
have reservations,
but this is what's
best for our planet.
Please, don't disappoint
our invited guests.
The princess said she wants
to wait until you're ready.
But I'm prepared to resort to
force if we run low on time.
I hope it doesn't
have to come to that.
Question for you.
About Princess Luna,
do you love her?
Catch it!
Our planets have a
gravitational bond
similar to the Earth
and its moon.
Magra is a natural
satellite that orbits Dogra.
--You're out, buddy!
--Seriously?
That's awesome.
I just wish there was
life on our moon, too.
How do you know there's not?
Well, I think we
would've seen 'em by now.
Initially, Magra sought to win
its independence from Dogra,
which resulted in a
seemingly unending war.
In an effort to bring peace
to the war-torn planets,
it was decided that
Magra's first princess
would be contracted to marry
the crown prince of Dogra.
Safe!
Okay, so it's basically just
a marriage of convenience, huh?
And I guess you're
okay with that?
Yes, I am.
Since birth, we've been
required to exchange
videos of ourselves
once a month.
There wasn't a lot talking
to be done as babies,
but even as the years
passed and we grew older,
the prince remained a mystery.
Because he never spoke to me.
When I was told he
possessed a genius mind,
I dedicated my
life to academics
to prove myself
worthy of his love.
I finally broke through to him
by solving a difficult problem.
He came up with a
different solution
and proceeded to
walk me through it.
This went on for years,
until one day...
Well done, Princess Luna.
He spoke to me, and it
was the first time
I had ever heard his voice.
Sounds like somethin' he'd do.
From that moment on,
I knew that I wanted
to spend the rest of
my life with that man.
Naturally, I've heard
the vicious rumors
floating around about him.
They say he's the
nastiest man in space.
That he enjoys
watching others suffer.
And he's secretly plotting
to destroy the universe.
Then why do you
want to marry him?
Because there is no way being
with someone like that
could ever get boring!
She's so beautiful.
Yukitaka! You're up, man!
Coming!
Bye.
This sport looks like
it would be fun to play.
Hey, I think I've got an idea!
Ejiri, try to go easy on her!
Don't wanna be the guy
who hurt the hot chick.
"Go easy"? Yeah, right!
That ain't in my vocabulary!
Holy crap!
Whoa.
You wanna be on our team?
She saw right through me, huh?
Well, I have her under
surveillance, don't I?
Yes, I do.
Yeah, I think she knows you do.
She asked me to
deliver this to you.
I see.
Well, it appears that she's not
your run-of-the-mill princess.
What's that supposed to mean?
Okay, lemme see if I can get
this through your thick skull,
she came all this way
because she loves you!
Oh, and you know that because--
Because she told me!
And I don't have any
reason to doubt her.
I'll admit,
she's kinda weird
but she's also really cute,
and she's in love with you!
I'm sure of it!
Look, I don't know what
kinda crap's gone on
between your planets,
but I do know
Princess Luna's way
too good for you.
Aha! So now you've got the
hots for her too, Yukitaka.
I didn't say that!
You didn't have to!
You're such a playboy,
first it was Miho--
One more word outta you and I'm
throwin' you over the ledge!
I've already made
this jump, remember?
Get serious, guys!
We've gotta figure out how
Princess Luna knows
your every move.
There has to be an
information leak somewhere.
Hmm...
--Hey, what're--
--Shhh!
Might I borrow a screwdriver?
We were bugged?!
You got it.
We've found our leak.
She's been spying
on us the whole time.
Do you think the princess
is responsible for this?
No, it would appear that
these predate her arrival.
I'd guess they've been here
since I first came to Earth.
If that's true,
then who planted them?
Let's find out!
Not this thing again.
Well, you know I hid several
cameras around your home.
This is the footage.
I've found evidence
that suggests
he's living with an Earthling.
Hey, don't you have an
outlet on that wall?!
That means...
Colin?
He's out checking
the garden for me.
He should be back
any minute now.
Found one!
Okay, we found a bug. But who
would've planted it out here?
Hey, would you get
off my back already?!
It's amazing! So beautiful!
What did they say?
It turns out Colin
was a spy after all;
he's probably returned to
the princess's side by now.
So, what is that?
Captain!
I've been unable to make
contact with our mother ship
or anyone else on Dogra.
This is something that
I think you need to see.
Sorry about this.
I hope this don't make
ya think badly of us.
So what do we do now?
You're in cahoots with our idiot
prince again, aren't ya?!
"Short walk", my ass!
Why did you bring us
all the way out here?!
Up next: Full moon!
You're cool! Totally cool!