Can you guys believe
I made it to level 10?!
You're still level 3 or 4,
so you wouldn't know.
But around level 5 you start
getting some abilities
that might actually be
pretty useful in a fight.
Here, I'll show you.
My level 10 move is gonna
blow your feeble minds.
Little Bomb!
So are you jealous now, or what?
Hearing that level up jingle
really gets my blood pumping!
You've done well, dear leader.
Now take the day off so
you'll be well-rested
for your big showdown
with the Demon, Craft.
What big showdown?
The whole team's
counting on you, Leader.
Wait. Noooo!
There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
Some of 'em are friendly while
others can be downright hostile.
And so, five boys, were chosen
to serve as the primary
colored warriors of justice
known as the Color Rangers.
With their strength combined,
they head to Yamagata
to face off with
the Demon King's
nefarious minion, Craft.
Get outta my head,
you stupid prince!
Jeez, I wish those
cicadas would shut up.
I figured since we were going
north, it wouldn't be so hot.
What do you expect?!
Snow in summer?
What?
You need to stop complaining
and take this seriously!
We're in the heart of
enemy territory right now!
The Demon Lord's
minions could strike at-
Is that supposed to
be Craft's hideout?
Sure doesn't look like much.
Well, it says
"Dogra" right there.
Not very subtle, huh?
Looks like the nameplate used
to say "Earth Defense Force"
before they tried
to wipe it off.
Man, they're not even
trying, are they?
You can tell that guy works out.
Uh, sir? You're not
Mr. Craft, are you?
Yes. Yes, I am.
Uh, hold on a sec.
He looks kinda tough.
I'm scared! Let's go home!
Hell no! Those train
tickets were expensive!
I wanna see a fight!
Oh, come on! It wasn't even
your money, you big baby!
You can do it, Leader.
Don't give up. All of our
fates rest in your hands.
Hold on a sec!
The Color Rangers are supposed
to be a team, you know!
Less talking and more fighting!
I wanna see blood!
Hello, nice to meet you.
To be perfectly honest?
We came here to steal a key
from you, Mr. Demon, sir.
A key?
Whoooa, actually,
on second thought,
it might be better if
you just kept it here.
I mean, we don't
need that key anyway.
What was I even thinking?
Akagawa's useless
again, big surprise.
I don't know what it does
or why you need it,
but I think I know the key
you're talking about.
Anyway, come inside.
I see.
I had a feeling he
was up to no good.
But still.
He expects me to fight
a bunch of grade school kids?
He seems as torn up
about this mess as we are.
Can't say I blame him- if he
works for that stupid prince,
he must have it pretty bad.
I do indeed have the
key you're looking for.
So you'll give it to us, then?
Never. You weaklings
might as well give up.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Huh?
But why the hell not?!
It's a treasure that
the prince ordered me
to protect with my life.
In other words,
if you want it,
I'm afraid you must
defeat me first.
I'm willing to bet that
moron's eavesdropping
through your bracelets
as we speak.
I'm in a delicate
situation here,
so I can't just
hand over the key.
In other words, I need for
you to play along for now.
Fine! If you wanna fight,
then you got yourself one,
you evil demon monster!
I'd be careful if I were you!
I may be a kid,
but I know karate!
Then have at it,
foolish mortal!
Dragon kick!
No fair! Don't hit
me from behind!
Owowow. Hey,
that really hurt!
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
Please don't take the key.
I'm begging you,
anything but that!
Lucky for us, Craft the Demon
was a pretty nice guy after all.
Let's hurry up and get
these stupid bracelets off.
Right!
I don't know how to use it.
First you beat me, and
then you ask for my pity?
What do you take me for?
Sorry, but I'm too old
to play with toys.
I have no idea how it works.
Yes, who is it?
Hey Ms. Tachibana.
It's me, Shimizu.
Yeah, uh...
We got the key but
we have a problem.
See, we can't use it
'cause we don't know how.
I see.
Unfortunately, I'm not
sure how to use it either.
I could try to look it up,
but since the Prince
altered the suits,
he probably changed the way
the key works as well.
Guess you're right.
I'm sorry.
Turns out Ms. Tachibana
doesn't know either.
So we came all the
way to Yamagata
to get a key that
we can't even use?
I bet he wasn't
gonna let us take
these things off
in the first place!
The Prince sure does love
to see us suffer, doesn't he?
So, what should we do now?
I can't take it!
Hey Prince! Are you listening?
Forget it, I know you are!
You probably think this
is real funny, don't you?!
Well the joke's on you,
because from now on,
I'm teaming up with the kids!
You're gonna apologize to them
even if it's with
your dying breath!
Sado! Colin!
Get back here now!
But we're in the
middle of collecting
beetles for our research, sir.
Irrelevant! We're going
to take down the Prince!
You can count me out.
Is that it? You wanna
be my enemy now?
'Cause you are if you don't
come back this instant!
Yes, sir.
I wonder what I should wear?
Sure, it comes off. It's easy.
Yeah?
My friend's son
has one of these.
It probably works the same way.
How'd his work? Tell me.
First, you twist the round piece
on the back end of the key.
That should make the keyhole
on the bracelet appear.
Oh!
After that,
the liquid metal on the tip
of the key will take shape.
It should fit in
the keyhole now.
Oh, sweet!
And then...
State your password.
Password?!
There's a password?!
I bet the Prince made one
before he gave 'em to us!
It should have some
sort of hint function
for people who've
forgotten their passwords.
Hint function?
To retrieve your password,
state the name of the girl or
girls you have a crush on.
"I like Rina Itoi."
Oh, the girl from Class 2?
I think she already has
a crush on someone else.
Well, I like her anyway!
Yeah, suck on that,
Prince! I'm finally free!
Who wants to go next?
Mayuzumi, are you ready?
Sure, why not?
It doesn't seem like the Prince
booby-trapped it or anything.
"No one in particular."
All right. Who
wants to go next?
Man, that was pretty smooth.
I never knew he was so classy.
Here, Akagawa. Have at it.
Think I'll pass.
I'm perfectly happy keeping
the bracelet on, thank you.
What are you staring at?
Don't get the wrong idea,
it's not like I'm shy about
saying who I have a crush on.
I just happen to think
the bracelet's cool, okay?
'Kay. I'll go.
But I've gotta warn ya,
my list is a real doozie.
Uh, let's see.
Sayaka Natsumoto, Ayaka
Sakurada, Yuuko Kojima,
Kei Nakahori, Manami Maeda,
Elena Ogawa, Tomomi Kawakita,
Kyoka Kuramochi,
and Kana Komori.
I'm just getting started.
Rina Toono, Kayo Nobi, Yuuka
Masubata, Natsuki Matsubara,
Kazumi Omoteno, Renka Tada,
and Youka Nishiyama...
I think that should cover it.
Password, incomplete.
For real?
Oh! Sae Kanzawa!
Sorry. You're still
missing one.
Geez, I don't know who's left.
Maybe that girl
I met in Nakano?
Ah, come on, her name's
on the tip of my tongue.
Dude, you're a scumbag.
Go ahead. We'll
skip him for now.
Uh, I think I'll
do mine over there.
What's wrong?
Oh, don't tell me
you're too shy!
I'm not shy!
Then why don't
you tell us, huh?
We wanna hear all about
your secret crush, big guy!
C'mon!
So that's how it is?
Well, that's fine with me!
You're about to get
stomped by the toughest
elementary school kid
in all of Japan, buddy.
What does it matter if
you say her name or not?
What, is she ugly?
As leader, I command you guys
to stop fighting each other now!
That's what the Prince
wants us to do!
Little Bomb! Little Bomb!
I warned you,
but you wouldn't listen!
I swear, all you guys
ever do is fight!
You're driving me crazy!
The Red Ranger is
totally flippin' out, man.
Yeah, I guess we'd
better call it a truce.
Here, go take it off
somewhere else.
All right.
Would you think about
what you're doing?!
There, there, everything's
gonna be alright.
Sorry 'bout your watermelons.
It's not your fault.
The prince makes me want
to destroy things, too.
Nice to have that weirdo
out of your head, huh?
It's a whole lot
easier to take a dump
when someone isn't
listening in on you.
Akagawa, just take
it off already!
I don't even know what
you're so mad about!
After I remember that
last girl's name,
I'll give you the key
and you can use it
in the privacy of
your own home.
I said I don't need it
'cause I'm not taking it off.
Well, I'm not gonna force you.
But as for me, I think
I'm done with super powers
and alien princes for good.
Yeah, you said it.
That was a pain in the ass.
At least we all got
a happy ending, right?
And so the five
elementary schoolers
gave up the mantle of justice
and lived happily ever after.
Yeah, you wish.
Rina Itoi from Class 2, huh?
She's a real cutie.
Click.
You too, huh?
I dunno what's wrong with me.
For some reason,
I couldn't throw it out.
--Ditto.
--Huh?
Seems like we all brought
them to school with us, too.
I don't get it.
Hey, what's up?
Good morning!
Did you ever remember
the rest of that password?
You can't blame me.
I only met the girl once.
That's like trying to
get me to remember
everything I ate last week.
Dude, you're a total
scumbag, for real.
Hey guys!
Can you guess
who's level 15 now?
I can't tell if he's on
his medication, or off it.
Sure am glad
I kept my bracelet!
You guys are missing out!
Did you know...
at level 15 you--
You're seein' this too, right?
I don't know what it is,
but yeah, I'm seeing it.
Hey, what's that thing?
The Color Rangers retrieved the
key, but little did they know
that was all part of
the Prince's scheme!
When all five rangers gathered
in the classroom that morning,
a mysterious power
entered the key.
They were transported from
Earth to the planet Calvary,
5 hundred million
light-years away.
You seriously don't have
anything better to do?
Unfortunately for them,
Calvary is a deadly
den of monsters!
How will they survive?
We'll be rooting for
you, Color Rangers!
What's Demon King Quest?
And why is it seven?
I get it.
It's like he used some
kind of RPG maker.
A wha-?
Well, I guess you
could say it's like
a do-it-yourself
video game maker.
So basically, he made a game
and dragged us into it.
That's why we couldn't
throw away our bracelets.
They're plot items in the game.
So what you're saying is,
we been playin' this
game for a while.
Wait, the manual said there's
no way to come back to life,
so it's more like murder
than a video game, isn't it?
This is balls!
We're gonna get killed
by monsters, aren't we?
Akagawa, hurry up and
transform before everyone dies!
Okay! Red Charge, go!
Eat Little Bomb!
Yokota, what level
are you right now?
Still at one-what're you?
Two.
Damn it, we gotta find a town
so we can come up with a plan.
No complaints here.
They just disappeared,
like it was magic!
Okay, let's calm
down, everyone!
Please listen to me!
No! They vanished
into thin air! Right?
Right!
I'm sure the Prince
is behind this.
Those poor boys.
Maybe I should've
tried to help them out
a little more after all.
Whoa!
My desk just totally
split in half!
Okay. I'm taking
attendance now, everyone.
In a galaxy far, far away, there
is a role playing game creation
program that allows the user
to modify actual planets.
One such place is
the planet Cavalry,
which has been transformed into
a land of monsters and mayhem,
courtesy of the Prince's
wild imagination.
Welcome to Hamajiri-
enjoy your stay.
Hi, we're kind of
stuck in this game.
Do you think you can help us?
Welcome to Hamajiri-
enjoy your stay.
Uh, okay.
Welcome to Hamajiri-
enjoy your stay.
Could you direct us to an
inn or something, maybe?
Welcome to Hamajiri-
enjoy your--
enjoy your stay.
I'm scared!
Why's she so weird?!
Not her fault she was only
programmed to say one thing.
I've never noticed how creepy
lookin' characters are in games.
Yeah, they're a
scary lookin' bunch.
No kiddin'.
Ya think everyone in town just
walks around in circles all day
until we talk to them?
Hey, I dunno if you noticed,
but some old dude's been
following us around.
Uh, can I help you?
There is a castle on a hill
about a mile south of this town.
Rumor has it the
king of that castle
has been out of
sorts as of late.
I wonder what's wrong.
I guess we had to talk to
him to advance the game.
Usually, once you meet
all the prerequisites,
you get a little event scene.
Like that?
The Dragon Knights who
serve the Demon King
are seen flying to
the castle every day.
This strange happening might
have something to do with
the unexplained behavior of
the king, don't you think?
So... In other words
"go to the castle."
Does that mean we're gonna
have to fight those things?
At our low level,
we wouldn't stand a chance
against monsters like those.
If you wanna go now,
raise your hand...
Okay, if you wanna go after
we've all hit level 10 or so,
raise your hand.
Level 20, raise your hand.
All right, if you wanna
go after we hit level 30,
raise your hand.
Blue Charge!
Yellow Charge!
And red Charge!
White Charge, go!
And Black Charge.
Change Color Rangers!
Let's hear it, fellas!
Color Rangers!
Lame!
Right back at ya!
I actually transformed
a few times at home,
so the stupid-looking costumes
don't really bother me anymore.
Yeah, same with me.
Check this out, Yellow.
Battle Pocari!
What is that,
a sports drink?!
When you need a refreshing
electrolyte beverage,
reach for Battle Pocari!
It's delicious and hydrating!
Here goes nothin'.
Battle Light, go!
With Battle Light, you'll
never fear the dark again!
You're killing me.
I gotta admit,
as long as you don't mind
looking like a total dumbass,
this game is
actually kinda fun.
Isn't it, isn't it?!
You finally understand
how I feel!
I hate to admit it, but yeah.
And even if our powers
suck balls now,
we'll be able to kick
ass after we level up.
All right then,
let's get moving!
♪ Now is the time. ♪
♪ The flame of justice
will ignite ♪
♪ and it's lighting
up their souls. ♪
♪ Their strength
shining bright ♪
♪ as they are struggling
through the night, ♪
♪ with powers to control. ♪
I hope those boys are all right,
wherever they may be.
Look at me worrying
about my students;
it's almost as if I'm turning
into a bona fide teacher.
I wonder if I'd be better off
quitting my job as an assassin
and staying here for
the rest of my days.
♪ When you are afraid, alone, ♪
♪ there's one rule
you must obey. ♪
♪ Call upon the colors and
watch them save the day. ♪
♪ Black and red,
lift up your head, ♪
♪ yellow, white, and blue... ♪
Battle Verheffen.
♪ Oh, Color Rangers.
Fight on... ♪
This is cool, but I'm sick of
running out of magic points.
I know. We need way
more when we level up.
Sounds like they're
gettin' hooked.
If it weren't for that,
we wouldn't have to leave all
the dungeons so freakin' soon!
Boo-yah!
Shimizu is now Level 3.
Strength increased by 1.
He's learned the
Battle Shower move.
Battle Shower, huh?
Yeah, that sounds
pretty awesome.
Ah, but I still don't have
enough MP to try it out yet!
I don't wanna wait 'til
we charge up again!
Amen, brother.
I am beat!
We got addicted and
ended up over-leveling.
So? It's not like we can
kick too much ass, right?
Good point! The stronger I am,
the harder I can stick it
to that stupid prince!
C'mon, guys, we're
going to the castle!
♪ Fight on, you Color Rangers. ♪
♪ Never fail,
you Color Rangers. ♪
♪ Laugh at danger! ♪
Shut up! That song's gonna be
stuck in my head for days!
♪ Hah! ♪
The truth is something terrible
has befallen our land.
I almost feel sorry
for the poor bastard.
General Luch is level
one thousand three hundred.
Akagawa!
We're princess Apparel's guards!
Let's hope it's just
part of the game.
Not bad. I'm starting
to enjoy this.
Pardon me, Princess.
But are you normal down there?
Up next: Game over?!
I won't give you my daughter,
no matter what!