There are hundreds of alien
species living on Earth
who come and go as they please.
One such alien is the idiot
prince of Dogra, who has flung
five unfortunate children to
the faraway planet Calvary,
which has been transformed into
a monster-filled RPG world.
Meanwhile, back on Earth.
Hi!
Everyone take your
seats now, okay?
This is bad,
they're absent again.
If they aren't
back by tomorrow,
I should probably
go look for them.
I swear, if that Prince
did anything to them,
I'll make him pay.
We're here!
Hey King, where are ya?
I am the great King Iidachi.
The truth is something terrible
has befallen our land.
A bunch of grade school
kids march into his castle
and he starts
spilling his guts?
Gotta advance
the story somehow!
Perhaps you have heard
of the Demon King's
Dark Dragon Knight Air force.
Their leader, General Luch,
is determined to wed
my only daughter.
Luch's strength is truly
beyond imagination.
With one thrust of his lance,
even mighty mountains
are rent in twain.
I am willing to offer my
daughter's hand in marriage
to any man in the
kingdom brave enough
to vanquish General Luch.
Well then?
Have you the courage to protect
her from his evil clutches?
You heard him. So what now?
I don't like being tied
down to just one girl.
And I don't need a
princess when I have Rina!
All five are absent again?
Yes, unfortunately.
Yeah, Rina Itoi from
my class is absent,
and I haven't heard anything
from her parents yet.
Well, that probably
doesn't have
anything to do with
your boys, though.
I wonder.
Seems kinda harsh making us
fight the big boss monster
before we've done a
single fetch quest.
Yeah, no kiddin'!
You don't have
much of a choice!
There's a reason I went to
the trouble of finding out
which girls you like.
I like Rina Itoi.
Suck on that, Prince!
I'm finally free!
Allow me to introduce you
to my lovely daughter.
Dear, come in and say hello.
It can't be.
Is it the girl from Nakano?
Meet my lovely daughter,
Princess Apparel.
Hello, there. It's a
pleasure to meet you.
Although I am the
king's only daughter,
I would rather die
than be forced
to wed a monster like Luch.
Oh travelers from
afar, I beg you,
please protect me from the--
Then go ahead and die!
Did I say something
to anger you?
Yeah, everything that comes
out of your stupid mouth!
What's wrong- don't you
like pretty girls?
You've got a lot of
explaining to do!
I thought it'd be a funny
surprise if you were
expecting to see the girl
you had a crush on,
and then it ends up
being me- funny, huh?
Oh yeah, funny like
a needle in your eye!
And you thought we'd be
perfectly okay with this?
That we wouldn't
punch you in the face
and then tie you up with rope?
It did occur to me, but I--
Oh, I can't wait to see
the looks on their faces!
It'll be splendid!
I was so excited.
I wasn't thinking straight.
This guy's an addict, isn't he?
Or a straight-up psychopath.
Now, would you darling boys
mind untying me, please?
Yeah, right!
Send us back to earth
already, "princess"!
And stop the game, too!
It's too late for that.
So you wanna play rough, huh?
We're the ones making
the demands, here!
You must understand,
if I were the Demon King,
that would be one thing,
but since I'm the princess,
I can't control the scenario!
What?
The Demon King has an AI that
thinks and learns for itself.
I may be its creator,
but even I can't predict
what it will do anymore.
Oh, the space ship
and game system
are both in the
Demon King's castle.
In other words, until you
rescue me and beat the bad guy,
you're stuck right
here on Calvary!
That means you're
stuck here too, dummy!
You didn't know?!
Whatever shall we do?
You suck!
Like it or not,
we'll have to come up
with a solution together.
General Luch is gonna
show up any second now.
The question is, do we protect
the prince--er, princess or not?
Why would I want
to protect him?!
Yeah, let him be
that demon's bitch!
Although that would
be pretty funny,
we have to remember that he's
the one who created this game.
Having him on our side would
give us a huge advantage.
Good point.
Hey "princess", whaddya
think we should we do next?
What level are you boys?
Between 35 and 70.
General Luch is level
one thousand three hundred.
We're gonna die!
Worry not, he'll come by to meet
you but he's not programmed
to fight you right off the bat.
For now, try to impress
him with your manliness,
and he'll start to
respect you as a rival.
Get ready. He's here.
So that must the guy we're
supposed to beat, huh?
I expect a favorable
answer this time, old man.
I won't give you my
daughter, no matter what!
He's still here?!
Hate to break it
to you, freakshow,
but the lady's just
not that into you.
Why don't you screw off
and get your mack on
somewhere else, okay?
And you are?
We are Princess
Apparel's guards!
You think you're funny?
Get out of my sight
before I destroy you, brat.
Go ahead and try it you-
Next time I won't miss.
I thought you said he
wasn't gonna fight us yet?!
--I didn't think he was.
--Say what?!
It would appear that the
enemy's AI has been reset.
And there's only one person
capable of doing that.
The Demon King?
He's more cunning
than I expected.
It's too dangerous to
continue the game like this.
Head East to the Saint's Shrine.
Its power repels monsters.
You'll be safe there.
Huh? But what about you?
Don't worry, I'll cook up a
plan to get us back to Earth.
Wha-- Wait!
Please don't harm them.
I will agree to
become your wife.
--You can't leave me!
--He's still here?
Is this for real?
Let's hope it's just
part of the game.
No, I think the Prince was
telling the truth this time.
Think you can beat me, huh?
That's what he said
as he walked away.
Okay, all together, guys!
Color Rangers!
Bus gas blast! Bus gas
blast! Bus gas blast!
How much wood would
a woodchuck chuck
if a woodchuck
could chuck wood?
Yokota!
Nine nice night nurses
nursing nicely.
Nine nice night
nurses nursing nicely!
A totally tough tongue twister
is totally on the
tip of my tongue!
Is everyone okay?
Yeah, somehow.
What's wrong?
I hate to say it,
but I feel like
the Color Ranger theme
song should be playing.
There's no time to be
fooling around, gosh!
You have to hurry to the shrine!
We get it, ass wipe,
we're on our way.
Battle Light, go!
In the meantime,
let me tell you
a few things about
the Demon King.
He can take many forms and
remodel his entire body at will.
He can be anywhere from
1 to 15 meters tall and
alter his features with a nearly
infinite set of variations.
As a result, no one has
ever seen his true form.
Great. That's really useful.
Didn't you create him?
Yeah, but I believe that a good
game should hold surprises,
even for the one
who creates it.
Yeah, but normally
games can't kill people!
By the way, should you
really be contacting us
when you're with Luch?
Don't worry.
He doesn't know how to treat
a lady on her wedding night,
so he's studying up on that.
Although he is equipped with
a highly advanced battle AI,
I suspect that it'll
take him a while longer
to learn how to-- You know...
Pardon me, Princess.
But are you normal,
uh, down there?
Let's just say you have quite
the surprise waiting for you.
One moment please.
Let's examine this; there are
three ways the game could end.
One: you could all die.
Two: you could beat
the Demon King.
Or three: the game
could stop working.
Obviously, 2 or 3
would be better.
The problem is,
the Demon King's army
is guarding his castle
very carefully.
Whether we clear the
game or shut it down.
We have to find a way
to get through them first.
Just tell us what level we
need to get to to beat them
and we'll see what we can do.
Hey, did you hear me?!
Oh, guards shmards,
what's important is that
the Demon King fears "game
over" even more than we do.
Because it wouldn't just
be the end of his life,
it'd be the end of this world.
In other words, you don't need
to worry about him killing you.
Instead, he'll probably
put you under confinement
and keep you alive
as long as he--
Princess, what kind of toys
would you like to use?
Let's save the randy stuff
for when the
relationship gets stale.
One moment please.
Let me gather a bit more
information before we meet up.
Wait at the shrine until then.
That must be it.
Sure you'll be able to sneak
out on your wedding night?
I'm going to fight
to keep my chastity,
but if I happen to
be running late,
I'd rather you not
ask what happened.
I almost feel sorry
for the poor bastard.
I'm just happy we're not
the ones getting cornholed.
Come Princess, let us begin.
I have become well-versed
in the ways of lovemaking
and vow to satisfy
you completely.
Well, in that case.
I managed to
overcome my crisis.
Yeah? How'd you pull that off?
Why don't you ask me again
when you're a little older?
Bedroom Role play: A school
boy's sexy teacher asks him
to stay after class, then
promptly forgets about him.
I got a map to the
Demon King's castle.
I'm on my way to
meet you right now.
We'll be back on Earth in
no time, Color Rangers.
Count on it!
Wait a minute.
That's the Demon King's army!
You've got a ton of monsters
right on your tail,
so you'd better hurry to
the shrine right away!
Run for it!
Guys, wait for me!
Did he prepare the army
because he knew I would escape?
If that's the case,
then General Luch was
conveniently left behind
to guard the castle while
all of his troops are busy.
Not bad. I'm starting
to enjoy this.
Akagawa!
Quit being such a pain
in the ass, leader!
I guess we survived.
Hey Prince, where are
you at right now?
Sorry to keep you
gents waiting so long.
Anyway, I guess
we need a plan, huh?
Clearly, getting out of
here is going to be tough.
Maybe we should use Red
as a decoy and hightail it.
Or maybe we can offer him
as a human sacrifice.
Hey.
Hey, one of 'ems
coming over. Look.
The heck is that?
Another Prince Baka?!
I have come here to
negotiate, not to fight.
So, even if things go wrong,
I want all of you to stay back.
He's giving them orders?
There's only one creature who
can command monsters like that.
In other words,
that's the Demon King.
What's the deal?
He's coming up the stairs!
You said this place
repels monsters!
Yes. Well, more precisely,
it repels a monster's
unique framework.
Then how is he
able to do that?!
Don't sacrifice me!
Think. There has to
be a reason for this.
Of course!
So what should we do?!
It's too late to
come up with a plan;
all we can do now is fight!
No, no, no,
I think we'll be fine.
If the Demon King is able
to enter the shrine,
he must've given up his monster
form for a commoner's body.
Which means he's even weaker
than the weakest enemy
in the game right now.
Why'd he do that?
I have a pretty good idea,
but it's hard to explain.
Pleased to meet you,
I am the Demon King.
Uh, hello.
This, is the game console.
I have no intention of stopping
you from leaving this planet.
If you are not pleased
with our negotiations,
then I will permit you to turn
off this console at any time.
However, I hope you will
trust me and allow this game
to continue on indefinitely.
Wait, isn't your whole purpose
in life to like, kill all of us?
No, it isn't.
I knew nothing
when I was born.
Only one thought
echoed in my mind.
"You are the Demon King."
I had no memories, no goal,
no reason for living.
Hey Prince, you didn't
happen to forget to program
the Demon King with
a purpose, did you?
It's complicated.
The first thing I did
was acquire information
so that I could find
a purpose for my life.
In my search, I learned
of both good and evil,
and much to my surprise
that the Demon King
was to be the
greatest evil of all.
But that wasn't
the worst part.
I also learned that
my creator, my father,
derived pleasure from making
other people miserable.
I probably shouldn't
have put that
in my social network profile.
While I am still grateful
that he gave life to me,
I swore that I would never
become anything like him.
My dream is to
turn this planet
into a haven for
monsters of every kind.
To make it a world without war,
where we can act of
our own free will.
The face I wear acknowledges
where I came from,
but it also reminds me
to go someplace different.
I want the title of "Demon
King" to become a legacy that
I can be proud of, not
something that I run away from.
Please, say that
you believe in me!
So what should we do?
We could be playing
into his trap, you know.
The prince made him, and
he looks like the prince,
so he's bad!
The only...
The only lullaby
I've ever known
is the Color Ranger theme song!
Does this mean you...
We all believe in you.
Yeah, I'm cool with
letting the game go on.
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you so much!
Well, I'm against it.
Please. Tell us why.
Because if we let
him have his way,
then the game will never
achieve its true purpose.
And what is its "true purpose"?
To put it simply, this
world is my little toy box
where everyone gets to suffer
and I get to laugh at
them while they do.
What?
Of course, the story would
start out innocently enough,
the important thing is
that it draws you in...
Then before you know it
you're completely addicted
and bit by bit it
starts to corrupt you.
For example, there's a
city to the west of here
absolutely drowning
in corruption,
desire and treachery, and
even if you keep your sanity,
it's guaranteed to make you
lose faith in humankind!
Then there are the items!
A strength potion that won't
let you sleep for three days
and a perfume so strong
it gets you high!
And don't forget all
the attacks I designed
to feed the destructive
instincts deep inside you!
My favorite combines your
powers into a golden force
that can crush any enemy
no matter how strong!
Wow, and how are you
supposed to use that one?
If you point a finger at
your target and all say
"Golden Hammer" at the
same time, then suddenly,
the fist of justice
will unleash its fury!
Golden Hammer!
We'll come back to play
again sometime real soon.
And don't worry, we'll be
sure to live long lives!
Yeah! We do have to keep
the game running, after all.
It was an RPG, but now I think
it's more like a life-simulator.
Yeah, and you're the
new hero, Demon King!
Thank you.
We must never cower,
our courage will empower
and our strength
will save our lives.
When you are afraid, alone,
there's one rule you must obey.
Call upon the colors...
Good luck to you all!
I hope you have a safe
journey back to Earth!
Black and red, lift up your
head, yellow, white and blue.
Color your heart with justice--
That little guy's the nicest
evil king I've ever met.
Nothing like his dad at all.
How far is it to Earth?
We all wanna get back
home soon, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
It's about 3 hours through
the local wormhole.
Course, the regular route will
take about 11.6 billion years.
Then you should take
the wormhole, obviously!
The toll is pretty expensive.
Good thing you're paying!
Whoa, I can, like, see infinity!
Heeyah!
Good mornin', Ms. Tachibana!
Right back at ya!
Luckily, the five boys made it
back to Earth safe and sound.
Hey!
Unfortunately, they
failed to realize that
as long as they allowed
the game to continue,
they would be transported
to the planet Calvary
any time they met in
their classroom.
Maybe I should've offed
that Prince after all.
Although the boys had made
peace with the Demon King,
they soon found
themselves face to face
with the newly crowned
Great Demon King.
But that's a story
for another time.
Princess Saki of the
Macbacs is coming.
She's set to arrive
on Earth tomorrow.
I didn't realize their
princess was in heat already.
Within a few generations,
the species they mate with
always goes extinct!
All that really matters
is that we're together!
The rest of the world can
go and die, for all I care!
Why is this happening to me?!
Up Next: You're my darling!
It's almost as if fate
brought us together, isn't it?