[FUUKA] Yeah, and Koyuki's
song is what made the movie!
It was incredible. You should
totally go see it, Mom!
[SUZUKA chuckles] I'll do that.
But what about you?
Are you keeping up
with your studies?
[FUUKA giggles nervously]
Yeah, of course! You know me.
Oh, I almost forgot to tell you,
I got asked to join the
track team again today.
[SUZUKA]
How do you feel about that?
Same way I've always felt.
[SUZUKA] Well, honey, have you
found what it is you want to do?
[FUUKA] No, not yet. But I know
it's out there, you know?
Remember, there's no rush.
What's important is
being true to yourself
so you can find own path.
That's right. Mm-hm. Yeah.
Okay, we love you, honey.
Talk to you soon.
She okay? She won't join
the track team, huh?
That's so weird!
She's always been so athletic!
[SUZUKA]
It's too bad, isn't it, Yamato?
You were already busy buying
her cleats and stopwatches
by the time she
could barely walk!
Aw, it's fine. I just want
her to find something
she really loves to do.
♪
The place that I always dreamed
I'd reach one day
is too high above us
To get to
The promise we made is fading
every moment we
conform like they do
I wanna move on my own
Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat
I'm done trying to blend in
I won't be tied
to a tedious world
Repeating each day like
a broken record sickens me
(No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition)
It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening
We're in a box, stuck in a box
Meant to stifle what we feel
Forced to erase all
that we know is real
But I refuse to be locked up
Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies
Time to break free
Open our hearts to a world and
go racing forward to the light
These broken chains
can't hold us back
We're finally on track to heal
all the fractures in ourselves
As we climb and ascend
Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high
Hear these words and know your
dream can be stronger than steel
Just believe
You have the power
Let your voice be heard
♪
[GIRL A] Aren't we in a
different classroom today?
[GIRL B]
I think so. Wanna go together?
[GIRL A]
Yeah, sure.
[YUU] I have no clue
what to say to her.
[sighs]
[YUU]
Uh? Akitsuki.
[YUU gasps]
[YUU]
Why was she crying?
[YUU gasps]
[YUU] Does it have to do with
that guy from our class?
[school bell chimes]
[STUDENTS]
Hey, man, wait for me!
[BOY B]
For what, karaoke?
[BOY A]
You know it!
[GIRL C] You have such
long fingers, Mikasa.
You could be a pianist!
[MIKASA]
Think so?
It's funny, I did used to play
a little when I was younger.
Hold the phone. You're using
a new shampoo, aren't you?
Uh! I can't believe you noticed.
[GIRL D] What are
you blushing for, huh?
[GIRL C giggles]
[GIRL D]
Don't you try to laugh it off!
[MIKASA chuckles]
[YUU] Could it be that Akitsuki
likes that blonde guy?
And she's bummed
because she thinks
he likes one of
these other girls?
Like a love triangle.
[YUU gasps]
[YUU grunts]
[TOMOMI]
Hey! Anyone who's not in a club!
Come with me. I need
your help, please.
[giggles]
[YUU groans]
The three of us have to clean
this whole pool?
Yep, it looks that way.
[MIKASA]
Welp, we better get started.
What's the rush?
It's best to get it
over with, right?
[YUU grunts]
Right, so, listen.
I've thought about
you and Mikasa.
[FUUKA]
Hm? What about us?
Huh?
[YUU]
It was nothing. Forget it.
What was that about?
Man, wow. It's so hot.
There's no way the three of
us are gonna get this done.
Good form, Fuuka.
You could be a professional.
Right?
I'm staying in an apartment
owned by some relatives.
I get to use the attached
bathhouse there any time I want,
so I help out with the cleaning
as much as I can, in return.
Oh, that explains it.
[FUUKA] Hey! You should come
check it out sometime, Makoto!
It's really a nice one,
and I'll get you in cheap!
[MIKASA]
Yeah, for sure!
[YUU] Great. They sure
get along well.
I guess it's none
of my business.
[FUUKA]
Hate to tell ya...
...it's never gonna get
clean if you sweep that way.
Why don't you let a pro
show you how it's done?
Just watch and--
[FUUKA yelps]
[YUU gasps]
[splashing]
Dang. Ow! Well, that sucked.
It looked like it did. You okay?
[FUUKA grunts]
Yeah. Aw, man, I'm soaked.
[gasps]
[FUUKA]
Hm? What's up?
[YUU]
Nothing. Nothing's up.
Hey, Fuuka.
[FUUKA]
Huh?
[MIKASA] Your panties
have made an appearance.
[FUUKA]
What?! No!
You saw?
What? I wasn't looking.
[FUUKA grunts] I'm gonna change.
I know you saw, jerk!
How am I a jerk?
[FUUKA]
Stop looking at me, Perv!
Why's she like that
to me and not to him?
Fuuka's adorable,
don't you think?
[YUU]
I don't know about that.
[MIKASA laughs]
So, I've noticed.
You and Akitsuki seem
to be pretty close.
Yeah, we have a lot in common.
[YUU] Then you should really
consider her feelings more.
[MIKASA]
Hm? Pardon?
I can't believe we finished.
Yep, guess I'll go
put these away.
Great, thanks.
[YUU sighs]
You're tired? Poor little Yuu.
Making three people clean a
big pool like this is torture.
You really think so?
I thought it was so much fun.
Huh?
'Cause Mikasa was here, right?
[FUUKA]
What? What do you mean?
What do I--?
You like Mikasa. I think
that's pretty obvious.
But he's friendly
with other girls, too,
so you're in some kind
of love triangle, right?
Um...
Look, what I'm trying to say--
Yuu, he and I have only ever
been really good friends.
[YUU]
Uh...
Besides, Makoto
doesn't really...
[MIKASA]
Oh, that's right...
I forgot. He's new here,
so he doesn't know yet.
[YUU]
Know what?
o biggie. It's just girls have
never really interested me.
Uh?
[YUU chuckles nervously]
[FUUKA gigles]
I can't believe it.
So that's why you had
the wrong idea about us!
[YUU]
Yeah, go ahead, laugh it up.
Just tell me this: why were
you crying before?
[FUUKA]
When did I cry?
You were in the hall
by yourself... and I saw you.
[FUUKA] Hm... Oh! I think
I know what you saw.
I bet... I was
listening to this one.
Is that?
It's just so good!
It gets me every time.
Here, you can borrow it!
You'll have a good cry!
It was just a song?
[FUUKA] Duh! The lyrics
are beautiful and sad.
It's all about her long lost
love and how she misses him.
[YUU]
Oh, Okay.
I assumed you were really
upset about something.
Ha! You jump to conclusions
a lot, don't you?
No.
You're not wrong.
Something is bothering me.
Not love troubles
or anything, but...
...I don't know what I want.
I'm just confused.
Nothing I try to do
is right for me.
What the heck am I meant
to do with my life?!
[YUU]
Uh... Why not track?
I tried for a while,
but it wasn't right.
Well, what do you think?
Do you have any
brilliant ideas for me?
[YUU gasps] Why ask me?
How am I supposed to know?
[FUUKA] I guess that's true.
Thanks anyway, though.
You saw me crying alone and
actually felt sad for me,
didn't you?
Well, yeah.
I get the feeling "kindness"
is your middle name, isn't it?
[YUU]
Huh?
[muffled HEDGEHOGS
music playing]
--[phone beeps]
--[KOYUKI gasps]
[KOYUKI gasps]
Nico!
[YUU] Good to hear
from you again!
Our whole family has been
seeing you on TV a lot!
My friend even cried
listening to your CD today!
[KOYUKI exhales]
He wrote me back.
[STUDENTS cheer]
[NACHI] Fuuka!
Seriously, come on,
you have to join the team!
[FUUKA]
No chance! Give it up!
You could take the whole
track world by storm!
[MALE TEACHER A]
Nachi, Be quiet and sit down.
--[smacking]
--[NACHI] Ow!
It really does
seem like a waste.
She flies like a bird.
[MIKASA]
A bird...
I guess. Though, if she is,
then she's a bird in a cage.
I dunno know what you mean.
[MIKASA]
I sense it sometimes.
She flutters around and
appears to be having fun,
but it's like she's trapped.
Like she's searching
for what's missing,
but she's in too small
a space to find it.
So, yeah, a bird in a cage
is a apt description.
Um. I think you lost me.
[MIKASA]
Hm? Why? Was that weird?
It's just the first time I've
heard anyone talk like that
in real life.
Was there a point?
[MIKASA] Hm! Yes, I did have
a point, as a matter of fact.
I thought that maybe
you could be the one
to open the cage
and let her soar.
Why me?
[MIKASA] Can't you tell?
She's totally drawn to you.
[YUU]
Huh?
[FUUKA] What were you guys
talking about before?
[YUU]
Nothing important.
So I was wondering...
Are you free this
Saturday night?
Yeah, I'm free.
[FUUKA] Good! Keep your
schedule open for me!
Wait, what're we doing?
I wonder what that's about.
[phone rings]
[YUU]
Hello? Is this Tama?
[KOYUKI]
Yeah, hi! Nico, it's me!
I'm so sorry to call you
out of the blue like this.
[YUU] Oh, no, it's okay!
It's great to hear from you.
[KOYUKI]
Yeah. It's been a long time.
[YUU]
Yeah...
[KOYUKI, YUU]
So, how're you?
Oh, sorry, go ahead!
[YUU]
No, no. You first!
[HIBIKI]
Get off the phone!
I need you to go buy
me some ice cream!
Seriously? Would it kill
you to knock? Jeez.
What's wrong? You talking to
your girlfriend or something?
[YUU] No! Would you
put some clothes on?
[CHITOSE] Whoa!
Yuu finally has a girlfriend?
Maya...! Maya!
[MAYA]
What? What is it?
[CHITOSE]
Yuu's apparently on the phone
with his new girlfriend!
[MAYA]
Really? What's she like?
[YUU] Not my girlfriend!
Just get out of here!
[YUU chuckles]
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It's comforting.
Kinda nice to know your sisters
haven't changed a bit.
[YUU] They could stand to
change a little if you ask me.
[KOYUKI giggles]
Oh! hey, listen.
I have a concert at the
Budokan coming up.
Wow! That's awesome!
You're actually gonna get
to sing on the same stage
where the Hedgehogs played!
Yeah. Remember how
we always used to say
someday I'd be like Tama,
the lead singer.
And you'd be like
their bassist, Nico?
[YUU] Yeah. Too bad I still
can't play a single lick
on the bass, though.
[KOYUKI laughs]
Oh, so, anyway...
I was hoping you'd be able
to make it to the concert.
Definitely! When is it?
[KOYUKI] It's this
coming Saturday night.
[gasps]
That's good! Keep your
schedule open for me!
Shoot. I already
have plans Saturday.
[KOYUKI]
Oh, that's okay.
[YUU] I'll for sure be at
the next one! I'm so sorry.
No. please don't worry about
it at all! I understand.
[KOYUKI]
Hey.
Would it be okay if I call you
again from time to time?
Yeah, of course you can.
[KOYUKI] Oh, good. Well, I guess
I'll let you go now. Good night.
Yeah. 'Night, Tama.
I should've asked Akitsuki what
she had in mind for Saturday.
[KOYUKI giggles]
"Can I call you again?"
"Of course you can!"
[KOYUKI giggles]
[YUU] What? Tama--
Koyuki Hinashi's concert?
[FUUKA]
Mm-hm!
I kinda wish you'd told
me this was what we
were gonna do tonight.
Well, originally, I was supposed
to be coming with Miho.
But she ended up having
to cancel, so...
[YUU]
Miho?
[FUUKA]
Yeah, she's my cousin.
So, when she cancelled,
I thought,
"Wow. I have no choice
but to invite Yuu."
Come on, let's go!
[YUU]
Hey, slow down!
Feeling kinda nervous?
Yeah. When I first
got started in music,
it was my big dream
to perform here.
Try not to get psyched out.
You're here because you
have talent and lots
of people recognize that
and believe in you.
Oh, no. I know it's not talent.
All I do... is turn
my memories into songs.
[YAMADA] You mean about that boy
you used to have a crush on?
Yes, though they're
not all about him.
But, you know,
it was thanks to him
that I decided to become
a singer at all.
And I've always wanted
to sing my best.
So that one day,
my song might reach him.
Well, let the agency know if you
guys end up going out, okay?
It'd probably be
great for publicity.
Oh. I'm pretty sure that's
never going to happen, though.
[FUUKA] I can't believe what
a huge demand there was
for these tickets! It's a
miracle I was able to get them!
And right in the front row, too!
It's amazing. Yeah.
[YUU] I'll email her later
and tell her I was here.
--[YUU gasps]
--[CROWD cheers]
It's starting!
Yuu, turn around and look!
[cheering continues]
[gasps]
[inaudible]
[CROWD cheers]
[gasps]
[KOYUKI]
Nico?
[giggles]
♪ I've been dreaming of
you every morning ♪
♪ since the day we met ♪
♪ Every dream better
than the last ♪
♪ And it seems that my ♪
♪ alarm just can't
compete with happiness ♪
♪ Slept right through
and could not care less ♪
♪ All I wanna know ♪
[YUU]
Your dream, it came true...
Tama.
[KOYUKI] ♪ All by your lonesome
on this wintery night ♪
[CROWD chatters]
[MALE AUDIENCE MEMBER A]
That was incredible!
[MALE AUDIENCE MEMBER B] Koyuki
really is amazing, isn't she?
[FUUKA] It always feels
kind of lonely after
a concert ends, huh?
[YUU] Yeah, like the
end of a festival.
[FUUKA]
Exactly! Man, it was the best.
I hope I'll get to
go again sometime!
But tickets are just
so hard to come by.
[YUU]
You're really into her, huh?
[FUUKA]
Definitely.
But, didn't you think
Koyuki seemed
a little different
from usual tonight?
[YUU] Uh... Well, I guess
I couldn't really tell.
Really? I saw right away!
Her songs are sad 'cause
they're about unrequited love,
but she seemed super happy!
Usually she's sorta
bluish in color,
but tonight she was
more yellow, you know?
Colors? You're not making
a whole lot of sense.
Wait, so you don't see colors
when you hear music?
No, not really.
[FUUKA]
Hmm...
[FUUKA] ♪ You will be the
one to make me smile ♪
♪ From now until
the end of time ♪
♪ I will always
remember all this ♪
♪ Because the
memories shine ♪
Okay. So what color was I?
[FUUKA]
Hello?
[YUU gasps] You're a really
great singer, Akitsuki!
Oh, you think?
Yeah! amazing! I totally
got lost in your voice!
You flatterer.
But, thank you anyway.
I'm so glad I got to go tonight.
Nothing like music
to clear my head.
[YUU]
Oh, yeah.
You said you'd been thinking
about what you want to do.
Do you know yet?
[FUUKA]
No, not yet.
I've felt really mixed
up for a while now.
But, then, when I'm immersed
in the music I love,
all confusion and
irritation floats away.
[YUU] Hm! There's your answer.
You should try it!
[FUUKA]
Huh?
[YUU] That could be
your thing. Making music.
[FUUKA]
Mm.
Huh...
[KOYUKI] I was so blown away
when I walked out on stage
and there you were!
It was such a shock
since I wasn't
expecting you at all.
So, I couldn't wait to call you
as soon as I got home!
Yeah, it's so crazy!
The plans with my friend
ended up being your concert!
They didn't even tell me.
[KOYUKI]
Oh, so that's what happened!
[YUU] And the concert
was unbelievable!
I mean it. I was amazed!
Like, so amazed I could barely
even speak afterwards!
[KOYUKI gasps]
[YUU]
Hey, you okay?
Sorry, I hope I didn't
say anything weird.
No, it's nothing like that.
I'm just so happy.
[YUU gasps]
[KOYUKI]
I'll call again soon, okay?
Have a good night.
[KOYUKI sobs] I finally sang
for him and he loved it.
[FUUKA]
Right.
Hey, get up! Come with
me for a little bit.
Come on, hurry!
[YUU gasps]
[YUU] Can you at least
tell me where we're going?
Don't worry about it!
Yeah, that's not helpful.
[YUU]
A shrine?
[FUUKA]
Yep! But not just any shrine.
My parents made a wish
here a long time ago.
And then something really
great happened to them!
[YUU] Aren't you a little
old for fairy tales?
I have an idea! What if you
also prayed for my wish?
That'll double my chances!
Is that how that works?
[FUUKA]
You better believe it!
[YUU] So, what were we
praying for anyway?
I wished for my
dream to come true.
Your dream?
Yeah! I finally figured
out what I want to do!
[FUUKA]
I was born to make music!
♪
Looking up at the sky
I felt an emptiness
All the colors of
summer have been faded
Before I even knew the things
that made me the happiest
Were hidden and tucked away
But when I looked at you
it all felt so intense
Your eyes cut to the
core of my existence
Every word that you spoke
was like a painting in every hue
You brought calm into my world
All I can do now is breathe
And figure out just what I need
Resolve myself, pursue my dreams
I'm running
Moving forward, taking your hand
Being with you
I'm finally free enough to
spread out my wings
Let's catch the wind
and go for a ride
You and I can fly
anywhere together
We can go as high
up as we want
Following the path that's
been laid pout before us
Guided by our
bonded hearts forever
Let's keep living
out this fantasy
And chasing our dreams
Ah... Ah...
♪
Oh! You want to start
a music club? Really?
Really! And the three of us
will be its first members.
Huh? What do you mean, us three?
Oh, so that's what
she's after.
What? Can you just
wait a minute!
It's all settled.
We're starting a band
together as of today.
[YUU gasps]
[FUUKA giggles]
[FUUKA]
Next time, "Triangle!"