[music on loud speaker]
[GUY A]
Isn't that Koyuki Hinashi?
I didn't know she had
a new single out!
[KOYUKI] ♪ You fill up my
heart with so much love ♪
♪ You're everything
I've ever dreamed of ♪
♪ Every moment I've
spent with you ♪
[FUUKA]
Outta my way!
[YUU gasps]
[YUU, FUUKA grunt]
Owie, ow!
[YUU groans]
Ow. Hey, are you alright?
[FUUKA] Why didn't you listen?
I said to get out of the way.
[gasps]
[FUUKA gasps]
I know you saw.
Nope, I saw nothing.
You took pics?
[YUU gasps] No, I swear
I didn't! I was just tweeting!
[YUU grunts]
[FUUKA shouts]
I hate... perverts!
--[YUU grunts]
--[CROWD chatters]
[FUUKA]
Hmph!
Man. Why me?
[YUU grunts]
[YUU] So, that's how
I met Fuuka Akitsuki.
The girl wrapped
in a summer breeze.
♪
The place that I always dreamed
I'd reach one day
is too high above us
To get to
The promise we made is fading
every moment we
conform like they do
I wanna move on my own
Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat
I'm done trying to blend in
I won't be tied
to a tedious world
Repeating each day like
a broken record sickens me
(No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition)
It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening
We're in a box, stuck in a box
Meant to stifle what we feel
Forced to erase all
that we know is real
But I refuse to be locked up
Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies
Time to break free
Open our hearts to a world and
go racing forward to the light
These broken chains
can't hold us back
We're finally on track to heal
all the fractures in ourselves
As we climb and ascend
Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high
Hear these words and know your
dream can be stronger than steel
Just believe
You have the power
Let your voice be heard
♪
[YUU]
I'm home, you guys.
[CHITOSE]
'Bout time! Why are you so late?
Are you trying to starve your
sisters to death, or what?
Well, a lot happened
on the way.
Lemme guess, did you
crash into somebody again
because you were too busy
staring at Twitter?
If you had time to take
your phone in for repairs,
you really should've
been home earlier.
Uh? How did you know that?
How do you think?
We found your account and
we're following you now!
[HIBIKI chuckles]
[YUU groans]
You sure are a chatty
one online, aren't you?
It's such a shame he won't talk
to his family like that, huh?
I'll block you both later.
[CHITOSE] So, what? You know
we'll find a way to see it!
[YUU] Nothing good
can come from living
in a house full of sisters.
Got the food.
Thanks for that, kiddo.
I appreciate you picking it up.
[YUU sighs]
[MAYA]
Hey, What's wrong?
[CHITOSE] A girl slapped
him on his way here!
She thought he took
an upskirt pic!
Maybe he's a little
embarrassed because
he really was caught in the act!
No, I was not!
[MAYA giggles]
Not you, too.
C'mon Maya, don't laugh.
I know, I'm sorry.
So, in other news.
I heard from Mom and Dad.
They arrived safe and sound.
Yeah?
Those luckies! I wish I
could have gone too!
I wanna live in America.
[MAYA] C'mon, let's eat
dinner before it gets cold.
[CHITOSE]
Okay! Man, I'm starving!
[HIBIKI] I think I want
the fried chicken.
[CHITOSE]
No fair!
[YUU]
Up until a couple days ago,
my younger sister, Chitose,
and I were living with our
parents in the countryside.
But then, our dad got
transferred overseas
and our mom went with him.
Our older sisters,
Maya and Hibiki,
had already been living
together in Tokyo for a while.
So, it was decided that
what made the most sense
was for the four of us to stay
together in Tokyo, on our own.
[TV VOICE A] And now, at last.
This week's number one!
[HIBIKI, CHITOSE gasp]
Yuu, look at this!
Koyuki's new song made it all
the way up to number one!
Wow. yeah, it's amazing.
Hold on. Don't tell me
you're not keeping in touch
with her on your
precious Twitter!
Uh...
You two were inseparable
back in grade school.
What was it you called
each other? Nico and Tama?
[YUU grunts]
That was a long time ago.
Couldn't talk to her
now if I wanted to.
[CHITOSE]
Well, duh, she's too famous!
If you reached out now, I bet
she'd totally ignore you!
[HIBIKI]
It's kinda sad, huh?
One is a top artist and the
other's a gloomy boy
who's addicted to
his smartphone.
You couldn't be more
different if you tried.
[YUU grunts]
Will you shut up?
Hey, hold on. You're starting
school tomorrow, aren't you?
Not yet. I still have to go by
to turn in all my paperwork.
[grunts]
Sure! I can take care
of this for you.
You'll be starting
tomorrow, then.
Yes, ma'am.
You know what?
Since you're here,
why don't you take some time
to look around the school?
I'm sure you'd like
to check things out
and get the lay of the
land before tomorrow.
[YUU]
One question.
Yes?
[YUU] Well... No.
Never mind, I'm sorry.
[YUU]
What the hell was I thinking?
There's no normal way to ask
if there's a girl at this school
who would break my phone.
Probably several.
I love your new haircut!
OMG, thank you for noticing!
[GIRL A]
Hello? Of course I did!
[YUU] Oh, well. Guess I'll keep
it till I run into her again.
[gasps]
[FUUKA]
Hm?
[YUU gasps]
[FUUKA grunts]
You're the guy from yesterday!
Are you sneaking pics again?
Stay right where you are!
[YUU]
Uh...
Holy...
[YUU gasps]
Hand it over, jerk!
Uh? Why should I?
I wanna have a look at all the
pictures you've been taking.
Uh...
But, I never meant--
So you were taking
upskirt pics?
No, just shots of the scenery!
[FUUKA] Then why'd you
say you never "meant" to?
I don't know,
I guess I panicked!
If there's nothing to hide,
then just show me!
There's personal stuff on here!
Gimme the phone,
you big pervert!
Back off!
Calm dow--
[BOTH gasp]
Why?! That was a loaner
from the repair shop, too!
[FUUKA]
Uh...
[YUU] I was so sure
it landed around here.
[sighs]
[FUUKA]
Hey.
[YUU]
What are you doing here?
[FUUKA]
I'll help you look for it.
My plan is to see if
the picture you took
was really of
the scenery, and if not,
then my plan is
to kick your butt.
[YUU]
Jeez, you're violent!
[FUUKA] Maybe, but if
you're telling the truth,
it won't be an issue, right?
Well, yeah, but still.
[YUU} Hey! Let's try calling
my number with your phone!
[FUUKA]
Can't.
[YUU]
Uh, why not?
Because, I don't
have cell phone.
[YUU gasps]
You're kidding, right?
[YUU]
Man, this girl's weird.
[FUUKA] No. I'd rather
listen to music,
than blog, or tweet,
or whatever.
[YUU] But you can download
tons of music on a phone.
Yeah, but I prefer CDs.
[YUU grunts]
That's right. Here you go.
I thought I lost that yesterday!
Well, yeah, you did. I found it.
And I never tried to
take your picture.
Hey, I'm home.
[HIBIKI]
Welcome home.
You've been unusually quiet
on Twitter for a while.
Kinda bizarre.
Yeah, I lost my phone earlier.
Would you put some clothes on?
Good, you're here! Do you
know where my T-shirt is?
My favorite one with
the weird face on it?
Nope, I sure don't.
Put something else on.
Glad you're home!
You should hurry, though.
You need to take your bath now,
the water will get cold.
What are you, nudists?!
[ALL gasp]
No, it's just so hot.
We're all family.
What does it matter?
You guys, I still
can't find my shirt!
[YUU groans]
[HIBIKI] I think maybe Maya
turned that shirt into a rag.
[MAYA] Oh, that one?
Yeah, it had a hole in it, so...
[CHITOSE]
No! Maya, how could you?!
[YUU sighs]
Too many women.
[gasps] Keep forgetting
I don't have a phone.
[YUU grunts]
She really is a weird one.
Not sure what to say.
I'm Yuu Haruna.
It's nice to meet you all.
[MALE STUDENT A]
We can't hear you over here!
Why don't you speak up?
[gasps]
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[TOMOMI] Akitsuki, you know
our new student?
No. Not at all.
[grunts]
[TOMOMI] Alright.
Well, then, you can take
a seat over there,
if that suits you.
[YUU]
Thanks.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MALE STUDENT B]
See ya later, man.
[MALE STUDENT C]
Yeah, bye, gotta get to club.
I'll have to stop by the repair
shop to pay for that loaner.
That's gonna hurt.
[NACHI]
Come on! Just come with me!
[FUUKA]
Would you cut it out, please?
Hey, it's not
so bad. You'll see!
[FUUKA]
No!
What's going on?
I told you, I don't want to!
C'mon, don't say that!
[FUUKA]
Would you give it up already?
[YUU] It's got nothing
to do with me, right?
--[FUUKA] I said no!
--[NACHI] Aw, come on!
[FUUKA]
Stop it! Leave me alone!
[YUU sighs, grunts]
[YUU]
Damn it!
[NACHI chuckles] Come on, now,
just for a little bit.
Let go of me, now!
[YUU]
Hey!
What's up with you?
Look, she doesn't wanna go.
I think she's made
that pretty obvious.
So, maybe you should leave
her alone now, 'kay?
You shouldn't get rough
with girls anyway.
Who's getting rough?
[NACHI laughs]
Now I get it!
[YUU]
Huh?
I wasn't trying to force her.
That was my attempt to recruit
her for the track team.
But she's being
stubborn as hell.
[YUU]
Mm. Recruit?
Yeah, see, her father is
the great Yamato Akitsuki.
He won the silver at the
World Track Tournament?
She's what you might call
a rare thoroughbred.
She has a lotta talent, too,
but instead of using it,
she wastes every
day goofing off.
Well, it's my life!
I can do what I want!
[NACHI] But it's just so
obvious you should join!
[FUUKA] I have zero interest
in joining the track team!
[NACHI] I swear, once you
start, you'll love it.
[FUUKA] Do you have to badger
me about this every day?
[YUU] 'Kay, bye. Oh, my god.
I'm such an idiot!
[YUU groans] So, humiliating.
Why am I such a dork?
[YUU] Grandma always said that
if I saw anyone in trouble,
I should help them! That was
drilled into our brains!
How about teaching
us to communicate?
To ask a person if they
actually need help
before I make stupid
assumptions and play "hero"?
How about that, Grandma?
[FUUKA] Quit ranting
like a lunatic.
[YUU gasps]
Great, just great.
Thanks for coming to
witness the meltdown.
[FUUKA]
Here.
What do you, hey, it's my--
Did you keep looking
for this by yourself?
Sure, I did. You returned
my CD to me. We're even.
[FUUKA exhales]
By the way...
Not that you asked, but my
name is Fuuka Akitsuki.
So, you can stop
calling me "you".
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MALE STUDENT D] I'm so hungry.
Afternoon P.E. is gonna suck.
Great, it's a romance flick.
Of course, it is.
I got free tickets from
one of the regulars,
go see it with a
friend or something
Easier said than done.
[FUUKA] Hey! That movie!
It just opened, didn't it?
I should've known it was you.
Could you do me a favor and not
shout out of nowhere like that?
[FUUKA]
Huh? You're kidding, right?
This is actually me
on a low-key day.
Okay, well, that's a
little terrifying.
Yeah, anyway. Back to the movie!
The theme song's done by
my girl, Koyuki, right?
Tama. Koyuki Hinashi?
Yeah! I love her!
I'm her biggest fan!
I really love
The Hedgehogs, too.
But since they went on hiatus,
I've been totally
obsessing over her!
Then, when her single came out,
I of course had to buy it
on the very first day!
I couldn't wait! It's so good!
But, yeah, when I heard
Koyuki sings the theme song
for that new movie,
I knew I'd have to see it,
no matter what.
Oh. And...?
You have two tickets there.
Shame for 'em to go to waste.
[YUU grunts]
[YUU sighs]
A date?
Wait, you guys! I didn't mean
to make it sound like that!
Man, he's so late.
I wonder if he might be
sitting behind Hachiko.
I wonder if she's sitting
in front of Hachiko.
[BOTH]
Guess not.
[sighs] And of course,
she doesn't have a cell phone.
No way, but...
[sighs]
Huh?
Was that?
[inhales]
Yuu!
[CROWD]
Huh?
[YUU grunts]
What?
[FUUKA] I'm here! I'm standing
in front of Hachiko!
Where are you?
Dude. This girl's insane.
Yuu! Come find me!
Follow my voice!
I'm right in front of Hachiko!
--[FUUKA inhales] Yuu--
--[YUU] I'm right here!
[FUUKA] Good grief!
What were you doing over there?
--Hachiko is right ov--
--You gotta stop screaming!
[gasps]
[YUU]
Huh?
See? I told you the
other day was nothin'!
I've got a big voice!
[growls]
Let's go! Don't wanna
miss the beginning!
It's literally all couples.
Uh? What? You okay?
Be my boyfriend for
a few minutes.
Be your what?
Shush! And you tell me I'm loud!
[YUU grunts] I'm gonna
need you to spell out
what you mean by that.
[FUUKA]
Hm.
We've still got some of the
special alpaca phone charms!
Just a few left!
For couples only, please!
See? You gotta
pretend to be my guy.
Okay. I get it.
That's perfect! Now we really
look like we're a happy couple!
It probably helps
that we are.
[GIRL D giggles]
Oh, you're so sweet!
[YUU grunts]
Whaddaya think?
Should we do that?
Is that how couples
are s'posed to act?
I don't know. It probably
depends on the couple.
[FUUKA]
Hm...
[FUUKA] C'mon. We should
hold hands at least.
Oh. you think so?
What's the big deal? I mean,
it's only for right now.
No. You're right, it's fine.
[grunts] Seriously?
Hold it the right way!
Oh! Sorry, yeah, I can do that.
Too tight!
Oops. Sorry, how's that?
[FUUKA, YUU grunt]
You see? It's not that hard.
[gasps]
Are you...?
[YUU]
Wow. So, it's not just me.
[FUUKA]
Koyuki's song is so incredible!
I cried every time it played.
All you've talked about
since the lights came up
is that one song.
Well, I can't help it.
It's ridiculously good.
Oh, almost forgot.
[YUU]
Hm?
[FUUKA]
Look at these little alpacas!
You can have this one.
Uh... I don't need one.
You can go ahead
and keep 'em both.
But it's a bonus for
"couples only"!
Yeah, but we're not
exactly a couple.
I don't know. Do we
really know that yet?
[YUU gasps]
Take it!
Wait! Akitsuki!
I had a good time. It was
a great date. Thanks!
Date?
See ya!
[YUU chuckles]
[YUU] Fuuka Akitsuki,
you are a weirdo.
♪
Looking up at the sky
I felt an emptiness
All the colors of
summer have been faded
Before I even knew the things
that made me the happiest
Were hidden and tucked away
But when I looked at you
it all felt so intense
Your eyes cut to the
core of my existence
Every word that you spoke
was like a painting in every hue
You brought calm into my world
All I can do now is breathe
And figure out just what I need
Resolve myself, pursue my dreams
Start running
Moving forward, taking your hand
Being with you
I'm finally free enough to
spread out my wings
Let's catch the wind
and go for a ride
You and I can fly
anywhere together
We can go as high
up as we want
Following the path that's
been laid pout before us
Guided by our
bonded hearts forever
Let's keep living
out this fantasy
And chasing our dreams
Ah... Ah...
♪
[phone vibrates]
[YUU gasps]
[YUU]
Tama?
[FUUKA]
Next time, "Take Flight!"