[YUU]
Thanks. Well, goodnight, then.
[YUU grunts]
All right. I sent him away.
Thanks, Mom. I'm sorry.
Are you sure it's
what you want?
Yeah.
Yeah. I am sure.
♪
The place that I always dreamed
I'd reach one day
is too high above us
To get to
The promise we made is fading
every moment we
conform like they do
I wanna move on my own
Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat
I'm done trying to blend in
I won't be tied
to a tedious world
Repeating each day like
a broken record sickens me
(No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition)
It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening
We're in a box, stuck in a box
Meant to stifle what we feel
Forced to erase all
that we know is real
But I refuse to be locked up
Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies
Time to break free
Open our hearts to a world and
go racing forward to the light
These broken chains
can't hold us back
We're finally on track to heal
all the fractures in ourselves
As we climb and ascend
Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high
Hear these words and know your
dream can be stronger than steel
Just believe
You have the power
Let your voice be heard
♪
[rock music plays]
[sighs] Welp, I guess
that'll work.
[MIKASA] Come on,
it's better than passable.
Yuu's song turned
out great, man.
Nachi, you really need
to watch those rhythms.
You got way off
a couple of times.
Yeah, I know.
Sometimes I get carried away
when I'm really feelin' it.
I kinda dig your
passionate side.
I find it very attractive.
Ugh! Cut it out!
[MIKASA chuckles]
[NACHI]
You're being super creepy.
Stop laughing!
Hey, so, listen--we need
to talk about something.
Uh?
My brother got a call.
It was from that same club
where we played the last time.
They want us to come play again.
What do you think?
Can we do it?
Wow. Look, I don't know, man.
[YUU]
I'll go find Akitsuki.
And I'll convince her
to change her mind.
Are you sure?
Yes.
She'll come back.
All right! Let's do it, then!
Sounds great to me.
Okay.
I'll tell my brother
that we're good to go.
We will be!
[beep]
[YUU]
Hey, it's me.
Sorry to keep calling.
But I really need
to talk to you.
Um. See...
We have a gig coming up,
two weeks from Saturday.
Please, Akitsuki,
can I see you just once?
Everybody misses you--
[beep]
Was that Haruna?
[FUUKA]
Yeah.
I mean, I've already
told him I'm going solo.
What a weirdo!
[FUUKA]
I can't go back.
I can't be around him.
It's too hard.
[dishes clinking]
[door clicks]
[door slams]
[FUUKA gasps]
Oh, thank you!
I'm a total klutz.
Uh! Koyuki?
[KOYUKI] I know it can be
really tough at first
because everything
is so new for you.
It was the same for me.
Just remember:
you're getting to
live your dream.
Yeah.
Hey, listen.
You should know,
I've ended things
between Nico and me.
[gasps]
It's funny.
I can't even remember
not loving him.
I've loved him my whole
life without trying.
But I think, maybe that's
why I couldn't see it--
what he was really feeling.
At your gig,
I listened to your song.
The lyrics were pretty clear.
[FUUKA]
Huh?
[KOYUKI]
I don't know if you remember,
but you told me once before
that you'd never given much
thought to falling in love.
[KOYUKI] But the feeling
behind "For You"
really resonated with me.
I recognized it.
What?! It's just a song!
I thought about what it would
feel like to have a one-sided
crush and I wrote about it!
I've got a stellar
imagination, that's all!
Look, Fuuka.
I think it's time you were
honest with yourself.
[FUUKA]
Once you are, things
will get a lot easier.
I can promise you that.
I was hoping I'd get a chance
to say this stuff to you.
So, good we ran into each other.
[KOYUKI]
See ya 'round.
Okay, I'm takin' off.
'Kay. Good work.
He heading to Fuuka's house?
Yeah.
He's been going by
her place this week,
every night after practice,
but she hasn't been there,
and I haven't seen
her at school, either.
[NACHI]
Hey, do you think it would help
if we all went over there?
Nah.
Yuu needs to handle
this on his own.
But I know something the three
of us can do in the meantime.
[NACHI]
Huh?
Practice up!
So, when she finally decides
to come back, she'll wonder
why she ever left
in the first place!
Yeah! I'm so down!
[SUZUKA]
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid she isn't home yet.
Oh, no worries. Sorry I'm
always dropping by.
I feel awful that you
keep missing her.
It's okay. I'll come again.
Wait! Just one more thing!
Look, Fuuka. I think it's time
you were honest with yourself.
[FUUKA]
I'm home.
You guys might know this one.
Here's "Climber's High"
by the Hedgehogs.
[CROWD cheering]
[drum sticks tapping]
[SUZUKA]
Fuuka!
How was your night?
[rock music plays]
[FUUKA]
What are you watching?
Sorry, I thought you'd
be home late, so...
It's cool.
[FUUKA] ♪ The place that I
always dreamed ♪
♪ I'd reach one day is
too high above us ♪
♪ To get to... ♪
[SUZUKA]
You all look so happy.
You have the biggest
smile on your face.
Are you happy now?
Like, are you still doing
what you love, honey?
I just mean, it's
been a long time
since I've seen you
smile like that.
♪ I won't be tied
to a tedious world ♪
♪ Repeating each day like
a broken record... ♪
I remember being your age.
Things were really
overwhelming and confusing.
Sometimes, it seemed
like too much.
But you know,
I think the most important
thing is not being afraid to be
true to who you really are.
Well, there you go.
Advice from your wise,
old mom, take it or leave it.
I just know it's hard when you
leave things unresolved.
Here. Haruna left this.
♪ ...on track to heal all
the fractures in ourselves ♪
♪ As we climb and ascend ♪
♪ Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high ♪
[YUU]
I'm sorry to keep bothering you.
The Fallen Moon really needs
you back with us, Akitsuki.
I've written a new song.
It expresses my feelings
pretty clearly.
Please listen to it, for me.
[YUU] The thing is, I want you
to be the one to sing it.
[NACHI sighs]
So, it didn't work, huh?
Well, I guess we'd better
go tell the owner, then.
Wait!
I'll go to Akitsuki's
place right now.
Huh?
[SARA]
Mm?
[YUU] Please, give me
one more chance.
Wha--?
I think he should go.
Wait a minute, here!
[YUU] I swear to you,
I'll bring her back
by the time it's
our turn to play!
I guess it's our only choice.
Get going!
Okay. Thanks a lot, Nachi.
Look, from the moment I decided
to come back to this band,
I'd made up my mind to
follow your lead in whatever
you wanted to do.
You go ahead and we'll handle
sound-check without you.
[MIKASA]
Go on, hurry up!
Not a moment to waste.
Thanks, you guys!
[YUU panting]
Oh, gosh. You just missed her.
[YUU]
Really?
Was she going to work?
Earlier, she said
she was off today.
[YUU]
Akitsuki.
Where are you?
[YUU gasping]
[inaudible]
[YUU]
Could she be...?
[YUU panting]
Oh, man!
I was right!
[YUU]
Akitsuki!
What are you doing?
Here you are. Finally.
Shouldn't you be at your gig?
You're gonna miss it!
The band can't play
that gig without you!
I can't come back. Not now.
Tell me why not!
[FUUKA]
I messed it all up! That's why!
It was such a selfish
decision to leave the band.
I know the others must be angry.
[YUU]
That's not true.
Come on, it has to be!
[gasps]
Akitsuki, I want you to
know how I really feel,
so please, hear me out, okay?
I finally realize
the things that are
most important to me
in the whole world.
Being devoted to something.
My music, the band.
You're the one who
gave me all of that.
It was all you.
So, that's why you're
really precious to me.
All I want is to be
with you and...
[groans] This is not
coming out right!
What I'm trying to say
is that I love you!
[gasps]
So, I want you to
stay in the band!
But only if you really want to.
Well, I do.
Of course, I want to!
I want it, more than I've
ever wanted anything.
Because I love you, too!
[NACHI grumbles]
No sign of 'em.
As of yet.
[SARA grunts]
Ahh! Damn it, I admit,
I'm worried now!
What're we gonna do if they
don't show up in time, huh?
Would you stop it?
They'll be here soon!
[door opens]
[YUU panting]
Hey. We're here.
Sorry we're so late.
[NACHI]
Fuuka! You got her!
Sorry. I'm so ashamed!
[ALL]
Uh...
I left the band for
such stupid reasons.
I was selfish.
And I... hope you can...
Hey, save that for later!
What about Yuu's song?
Can you sing it?
We won't have time to rehearse.
Can you make it work?
Mm-hm.
[NACHI] Well, I suppose it's
time for our pre-show ritual!
Are you ready, Fuuka?
[FUUKA]
Mm-mm. Not this time.
Yuu should be the one to do it.
Uh. Why me?
Heh, heh. Because!
If not for you,
The Fallen Moon wouldn't have
gotten back together.
Yep, that's right.
I agree. It's all you.
Come on, guys.
Let's go become legends!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[CROWD chattering]
[MALE FAN A]
Is the next band any good?
[MALE FAN B] They've been
all over the internet.
[FEMALE FAN A] I heard that
they're all in high school!
Finally. They're next, right?
I'm looking forward to this.
It's magical,
watching new artists
spread their wings and fly.
[CROWD cheers]
"For You."
[rock music plays]
[music continues]
♪ Oh, I got so much on my mind ♪
♪ Hard for me to keep
looking forward ♪
♪ Dragging my feet,
my body's so tired ♪
♪ But still, I keep on
going my way ♪
♪ I try to... ♪
I was completely prepared to
yank my bass off the stage
if he did anything
stupid up there.
Looks like it won't
be necessary, huh?
[FUUKA]
♪ I was just lying to myself ♪
♪ Acting like I have... ♪
[TAMA]
It's resonating right here.
You've got a damn
good sound, kids.
[FUUKA] ♪ Don't know if
tomorrow will ever come ♪
♪ Or if I'm even meant
to last 'til dawn ♪
♪ So let's get real ♪
♪ Why not let it out? ♪
♪ There's nothing to lose ♪
♪ Go deep in my heart
And show you... ♪
[KOYUKI]
I hope you got her back, Nico.
[FUUKA] ♪ Hurrying
but still taking my time ♪
♪ And running
but standing still ♪
♪ all the while I'll accept ♪
♪ any challenge ♪
♪ If that's what it takes ♪
♪ For you to share
your life with me ♪
[music continues]
[FUUKA] ♪ I still believe
Now let's go our way! ♪
[CROWD cheers]
Thank you all!
This next one's gonna
be our last song.
[FEMALE FAN B]
What?
[MALE FAN C]
Let us hear some more!
[MALE FAN D]
You're so awesome!
So, hey, guys.
Do you have something
that you wanna do?
[MALE FAN]
What's she talkin' about?
[FEMALE FAN C]
What's this?
You see, till just recently,
I couldn't figure out what
it was I wanted to do.
I felt really confused.
Then, someone,
a very special someone,
suggested I try making music.
[CROWD chattering, cheering]
[FUUKA] So, I started
a band, made new friends,
and now I'm on stage,
with all of them next to me!
[piano, guitar play]
If you're not sure what
you're s'posed to do,
it's really okay to just
let the wind take you.
And to trust that eventually
you'll find the thing that
drives and inspires you most.
"Fair wind."
♪ I'll always ♪
♪ Forever, always
I'll find my way ♪
♪ I'll always ♪
♪ Forever, always
I'll find my way ♪
♪ I feel the pulsing of
my racing heart take over ♪
♪ Holding on and
trying to keep my ♪
♪ breath controlled I hear
my voice in the cloud ♪
♪ Breaking through the
shadows of confusion ♪
♪ I was standing
rooted in this place ♪
♪ For way too long Not knowing
what I really wanted ♪
♪ Or where I was going ♪
♪ I've found no words ♪
♪ To express just how I felt ♪
♪ And still I believed in me ♪
[YUU]
Thank you, Akitsuki.
[YUU] From the moment
we met, you fascinated me.
I was constantly at your mercy.
But you made me realize
how important music and
friendship really are to me.
My whole world opened up,
all because of you,
and I'm so grateful.
[FUUKA]
♪ Throw our preconceptions ♪
♪ Out an open window ♪
♪ Truth, once sealed away
Is now released ♪
♪ No longer scared to be me ♪
[YUU] I wanna go on
like this with you...
...forever!
[FUUKA]
♪ Don't give up ♪
♪ Go until we've gone
All the way around ♪
♪ I've never felt so free
I'll do whatever I please ♪
♪ So hopeful I can fin'lly
Live in reality ♪
♪ I hear your voice in my heart
Now I know what I want ♪
♪ I know what I've got ♪
♪ Blue skies'll turn to gray
But it'll all be okay ♪
♪ If you feel like the dark
Is gonna make you afraid ♪
♪ Call my name I'll be
right there by your side ♪
♪ My heart,
once filled with doubt ♪
♪ Was longing to be free
Then I saw a light that was ♪
♪ once forgotten ♪
♪ When you took my hand
Felt like I was transported ♪
♪ Riding on the wind ♪
♪ Saw a vision of the past
Moving forward ♪
♪ I might feel
scared sometimes ♪
♪ But I won't let that hold
me back, I'll Let the fair ♪
♪ wind give me a true location ♪
♪ I believe in me, So I'll keep
moving ahead Won't give up ♪
♪ Goin' 'til I've gone
All the way around ♪
[CROWD cheers]
[bell rattles]
[clapping]
Gotta ask. What all did
you wish for up there?
[YUU]
Oh, um, that my bass playing
would drastically improve.
Also, that you and I
would always be together
the way we are now.
Did you really?
This is why I wasn't
going to tell you.
[laughs]
[FUUKA] Together for always,
from this day on!