Man, oh man, Nachi was
pretty upset, wasn't he?
Maybe I shouldn't
have done that.
Who, you mean the
guy from track?
I wouldn't even worry about him.
Yeah. You're probably right.
It'd be worse to join
the team reluctantly.
[MIKASA]
That's true.
It's best for everyone if
you're honest about it.
[FUUKA] You're so right!
I'm done worrying!
A music club!
Sure, That'll be fine.
Though with just three members,
it'll be an association
rather than a club, okay?
Cool!
Someday, maybe we'll be a
great band like the Hedgehogs!
[YUU gasps]
Wow, the Hedgehogs, huh?
That really takes me back!
They haven't put
anything new out
for a pretty long time, though.
Wait. why do we have
to be club members, too?
Hey Mikasa, come on,
help me out here!
I've decided to just
let fate do her thing.
Don't you think it's possible
we all met for a reason?
So, you're basically
agreeing to do it.
In hot-guy-speak.
For starters,
we'll need instruments.
I wonder if my allowance
will be enough.
Wha--? Could we please talk
about this a little bit first?
[FUUKA grunts]
Well, have you thought about
working over summer break?
Those beach resorts
always need live-in help.
[train bell rings]
[FUUKA]
Wait for us!
[ALL sigh]
I haven't been to the
beach in forever!
Oh yeah?
How about you?
I actually go pretty often.
[FUUKA]
Really?
[MIKASA]
Yeah!
Why'd I agree to this?
I've gotta stop
being a pushover.
[gasps]
What're you doing?
What're you thinking
about over there?
You look kinda worried.
Working at the resort means
we'll be dealing with customers
and I'm not very good at
talking to people I don't know.
[FUUKA grunts] Well, if you're
gonna be in the band,
you need to work on that.
You'll be performing in front
of big crowds all the time!
Not so easy for a shy type.
Then, there's also the
minor detail that I don't
--play a musical instrument...
--[FUUKA gasps]
Look! You can see the ocean!
It's so beautiful!
Hey, could you listen?
[FUUKA] In a sec! Just look
at it shimmer! Oh my gosh!
[giggles]
♪
The place that I always dreamed
I'd reach one day
is too high above us
To get to
The promise we made is fading
every moment we
conform like they do
I wanna move on my own
Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat
I'm done trying to blend in
I won't be tied
to a tedious world
Repeating each day like
a broken record sickens me
(No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition)
It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening
We're in a box, stuck in a box
Meant to stifle what we feel
Forced to erase all
that we know is real
But I refuse to be locked up
Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies
Time to break free
Open our hearts to a world and
go racing forward to the light
These broken chains
can't hold us back
We're finally on track to heal
all the fractures in ourselves
As we climb and ascend
Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high
Hear these words and know your
dream can be stronger than steel
Just believe
You have the power
Let your voice be heard
♪
Okay, let's see.
[YUU]
Is this the place?
[FUUKA]
Looks like it.
[YAHAGI]
Huh?
Hey, are you guys the new
part-timers Tomomi found for me?
That's right. Who do we
need to report to now?
Me. I'm Yahagi, the owner.
I appreciate your help, guys.
[FUUKA, MIKASA]
Thank you for having us!
Uh. Yeah. Thank you very
much for having us here.
[YAHAGI grunts]
What was that?
You're gonna have to
learn to speak up!
You wanna be heard, don'tcha?
[YAHAGI laughs]
[YUU] Great, loud and pushy,
my favorite.
The room for both you
boys is this way.
[gasps] Hey Yahagi,
is this your drum set?
[YAHAGI] Hm? Oh, yeah.
I used to play a little bit.
But it's been really
a long time since
I've played a live
gig or anything.
Don't touch 'em, though.
Okay.
Just the two of us, huh?
[YUU gasps] You like to freak
me out by pretending
to flirt with me, right?
You know it.
[YAHAGI] Best thing for you
would be to get to bed early.
You'll be working your butts
off tomorrow, believe me. Ha!
[YUU]
Ow!
Uh-oh! Sorry about that!
[YAHAGI laughs]
Oh, we're gonna get along
just great. This is bad.
[FUUKA] 'Kay! One sec,
I'll be right over!
[FUUKA grunts]
[GUY A gasps]
Impressive!
[GUY B]
Nice job!
[FUUKA chuckles]
Wow, aren't you the cutie pie.
Are you in college?
Nope. Still in high school.
Hey you should come hang
out with us this afternoon.
Do you have a girlfriend?
[MIKASA]
I sure don't.
But that's 'cause girls
aren't really my thing.
[GIRLS groan]
How do they both
already look like pros?
[YAHAGI]
Haruna!
[YUU gasps]
Yes?
Order! These go to Table Three.
[YUU]
Right.
[GUY C]
Watch where you're going!
[YUU groans]
So, okay. I'm sorry.
Would you mind repeating
your order for me?
[GUY D] Again? How many times
do you need to hear it?
My apologies, sir.
We didn't order those,
I'm not paying for them.
Come on, why don't we just go.
[YUU]
Uh...
[GUY E] I feel like you're
not even listening to me, kid.
[YAHAGI grunts]
[YUU]
Of course I am, sir.
[GUY E] How many times do
I have to repeat myself?
[YUU]
I'm sorry.
Fried rice and ramen, please.
What? I can't hear you!
I need three yakisobas, please.
Still can't hear you.
It doesn't even sound
like you're trying!
I have an order. I need
two ramens, please.
[YAHAGI grunts]
How many times I gotta say it?!
Speak up, Haruna!
Look, kid. You need to
get yourself together.
Yeah, I know.
[YAHAGI grunts]
Take a little break and think.
Or, you could always go home.
[sighs] What did I
even come here for?
Maybe I will go.
[FUUKA]
No, you can't!
[YUU]
You scared me.
Don't say that.
Don't say you're leaving.
[gasps, grunts]
[YUU] I'm not cut out
for this kind of thing.
I keep screwing up and
embarrassing myself,
over and over.
I just look pathetic.
The band will be the same.
Nah, I don't agree.
You only mess up sometimes
because you don't handle
stress all that well.
You let it get to you.
[YUU grunts]
But I know you lead
with your heart.
Like when you tried to save me
from being recruited
to the track team.
Or when I was weepy and you were
worried that I might be upset.
If you ask me, that makes
you a cool person.
Thanks, but I don't get it.
[FUUKA]
I want you to be in the band
because I know you'll work
with your whole heart.
I know you'll try your best.
I don't want just
any old slacker.
Uh?
So, you're staying!
Now, let's go show Yahagi
what you're made of!
Time to prove you
can really do this!
[gasps]
[FUUKA]
Alright! Okay, let's get inside!
Come on, come on, let's go,
let's go, let's go!
'Scuse me, waiter!
I have an order!
Two fried rice
and yakisoba, please!
And shaved ice.
And I'll have the ramen.
Pardon me, is this table open?
Ramens up! Order for table five!
Yes! How can I help you?
Are you ready to order?
Two fried rice, yakisoba,
shaved ice, and ramen.
It is! I'll clear
it for you now, sir!
[YUU] One ramen and
a yakisoba, please!
[YAHAGI]
Okay...
Next, two fried rice!
[YAHAGI]
Got it!
Two ramens, please!
Yeah, got it! He, he...
See? I knew you
had it in ya, kid.
[YUU]
Okay, great.
Let me just repeat your order
back to you, two ramens,
one yakisoba, one fried rice...
[GUY H]
Excuse me, miss!
Be right there!
[YAHAGI] And... with that,
the day is done. Not bad work.
Thanks so much for the job.
So, about that Haruna kid.
He doin' okay?
It was just mild
heat exhaustion.
I think he should be
alright as long as he gets
to rest a little.
It's no wonder, the way he ran
around all day with no breaks.
Anyone would keel over.
But without him,
we couldn't have handled
all the afternoon customers.
He made a huge difference.
Yep. There's no doubt.
[YUU snores]
For somebody who's
usually so awkward,
today, you found your groove.
We'll begin filming almost
immediately after we arrive.
[KOYUKI]
Thanks.
Oh yeah, also...
I was wondering if we'd have
any free time this evening.
Yes, it's only a
daytime shoot.
So you should be free tonight.
That's good to know.
[YUU] There's something
I don't understand.
[MIKASA]
What?
Why does Akitsuki even
bother with me at all?
Come on, man.
Don't doubt yourself.
It's pretty obvious that she
acts differently towards you.
It's like I said before.
I think Fuuka is just naturally
drawn to you, my friend.
You really think so?
In all seriousness?
Yep, but if you ask me,
the important question is
how you feel about
that fact, you know?
How I feel?
I'm off! You're on your
own while I land a date.
I saw a really hot
lifeguard back there.
[YUU]
Have fun.
How do I feel about
Akitsuki being drawn to--
[grunts] What the--?
[FUUKA gasps]
Wanna come play with me?
[YUU gasps]
Uh, sure.
[FUUKA]
Huh?
C'mon, kick faster and
swim harder, Yuu!
I know you can do it!
Giddyap, cowboy!
[gasps]
[FUUKA sighs] We're definitely
heading the wrong way.
Try to keep your eyes forward.
[YUU]
Nope. I'm good like this.
Huh?
[YUU] You physically assaulted
me when you thought
I saw your panties. Yet that
bathing suit is somehow okay?
[FUUKA]
Mm... What'd you say?
[YUU]
Nothing! Nothing at all!
[YUU] I'm beginning to
think I was just imagining
that she liked me
that way at all.
It's more like... she just
doesn't see me as a guy.
Yuu, what's going on with you?
You look like you're
lost in thought.
No, just daydreaming.
So, tell me something.
What made you suddenly decide
to start a band, anyway?
What do you mean? You're the one
who said I should make music.
Don't you remember?
[YUU] Well, you said
you like Koyuki Hinashi,
so I guess I assumed
you'd go solo is all.
If I'm gonna make music,
I think it'd be the most
fun to make it with you.
[YUU groans]
[FUUKA gasps] Woah. I think
we've drifted out way too far!
[YUU gasps]
We have to get back!
[FUUKA grunts]
[FUUKA pants]
My leg... cramped!
Akitsuki! Are you...?
Just hang on, I'm coming!
[FUUKA grunting]
[YUU grunts]
[YUU coughs]
Oh, thank goodness!
You're alive!
[YUU]
Was that...?
I'm sorry. You almost
drowned trying to save me.
You had stopped breathing.
I was afraid you
were already dead.
No, that's... awful.
Yeah, it was. I was
so worried about you!
You jerk!
Guess we'll have to get the
rest of the footage tomorrow.
I'll fit it into the schedule.
Great, thank you. Wanna
go grab something to eat?
[GUY I]
Sure.
[KOYUKI giggles]
Hey, we're back from our break!
Good! Welcome back.
[YUU exhales softly]
What is up with him?
Look at his eyes.
It's like he's totally
dead inside.
[FUUKA]
Hm? Yuu? What's going on?
[YUU]
Uh?
[FUUKA]
Hm?
[YUU, FUUKA shout]
Dude, chill!
Don't freak out like that!
What's wrong with you?
[YUU]
Uh. Sorry, I don't know.
[YUU grunts]
[FUUKA]
Hm? You're really weird.
[YAHAGI]
Well, seeing as no one's here,
I guess we can
close for the day.
[YUU] How can she act
so normal after that?
I mean, I can barely
look her in the face!
Fuuka. You have a good swim?
[FUUKA] Mm-hm. Hey, could I
have a sip of your drink?
I'm really thirsty.
Yeah, no prob, but It'll
be like an indirect kiss.
Well, that doesn't bother me.
It's not like we're
kids anymore.
[FUUKA sighs] Besides, it
doesn't seem quite so weird
if it's you.
[MIKASA laughs]
Thanks, I guess!
'Kay. I am irrationally jealous.
[YUU]
Hm.
[YUU] The fact is, I know she
only did it to save my life.
I look like an idiot,
getting all worked up.
[groans]
Are we alone? Let's talk.
Please don't tell anyone
what happened, okay?
Why? What happened?
[FUUKA] You know. what I
had to do with you before,
right after you almost drowned.
\Oh, the CPR?
Shut up! Would you keep it down?
But I thought, you said...
Earlier, you said you didn't
care about an indirect kiss.
So, it doesn't mean anything.
But it does mean something!
[YUU]
Hm?
It really does. Because,
you see, it was my first time.
[YUU gasps]
Keep it a secret, okay?
[gasps]
Yeah, I won't tell anyone.
Do you mean that?
Yes. I promise you, I won't.
Thanks, I believe you.
Also... Thank you for saving me.
I mean it.
[YUU gasps]
[YUU] What was that?
Does that mean...?
She'd only been pretending
that it hadn't affected her!
So that means I
wasn't the only dork
feeling super
self-conscious about it!
What's up with you?
[YUU yelps] Oh, I...
It's nothing. I'm cool.
Huh...
So, it's a secret, huh?
I guess posting it on
Twitter is out, then.
[phone buzzes]
[KOYUKI]
You must be tired from work!
I'm in Shonan, too, because I'm
shooting a music video.
I have some free time tonight.
Do you think maybe
we could meet up?
I can't believe
Tama's here, too!
[YUU]
Tama!
Nico!
I'm sorry! Did you wait long?
Oh, no. Not at all!
Thanks for coming.
It means a lot.
Well, I wanted to see you, too.
It's been ages, hasn't it?
Yeah, it's been
since grade school.
I almost can't believe it.
If not for the age
of cell phones,
I doubt I would've
seen you again.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I'm so glad that's
not what happened.
[gasps]
Oh. I almost forgot!
I brought fireworks!
No way. Cool! I love fireworks!
Yeah. I remembered, so I
thought this might be fun.
Huh? No, Yuu went out
just a little while ago.
Said he had something to do.
Aw! I was hoping that he
and I could talk about
what kind of guitar to buy.
Guess you'll have to
wait 'til he gets back.
Man... He's out there
in this yucky rain?
I think he'll survive.
But listen,
is it just my imagination or
is Yuu on your mind a lot?
Uh! No, not really.
Did something happen?
When you were alone?
Don't know what you mean.
[MIKASA]
Hm...
Hey, you know what? I think I'm
gonna go out and look for him!
[MIKASA chuckles]
What is it? You okay?
Uh, yeah. I'm fine.
It's just... I was thinking how
you've gotten really pretty.
[KOYUKI gasps]
Oh. Well, thanks.
[YUU exhales]
Well, of course you have, right?
I mean, just look at you!
You're a top artist who's
got fans all over Japan!
It's like you're part
of another world now.
Even if that's partly true...
With you, I'm just Tama.
So, be the same Nico. I'm still
the same girl I was, inside.
Okay, I will.
[KOYUKI]
Hey, I wanted to ask.
On Twitter, you mentioned
you'd be playing
in a band pretty soon.
[YUU] Uh, yeah.
That just sorta happened.
[KOYUKI] That's cool, though!
Who'll be in it?
[YUU] Oh, um.
A girl from my class.
Uh, you're in a
band with a girl?
[YUU]
Mm-hm.
That's cool.
[KOYUKI shouts]
You okay? Did it--
[KOYUKI gasps]
Nico, I...
[YUU]
What is it?
Akitsuki?
Koyuki and... you?
♪
Looking up at the sky
I felt an emptiness
All the colors of
summer have been faded
Before I even knew the things
that made me the happiest
Were hidden and tucked away
But when I looked at you
it all felt so intense
Your eyes cut to the
core of my existence
Every word that you spoke
was like a painting in every hue
You brought calm into my world
All I can do now is breathe
And figure out just what I need
Resolve myself, pursue my dreams
I'm running
Moving forward, taking your hand
Being with you
I'm finally free enough to
spread out my wings
Let's catch the wind
and go for a ride
You and I can fly
anywhere together
We can go as high
up as we want
Following the path that's
been laid pout before us
Guided by our
bonded hearts forever
Let's keep living
out this fantasy
And chasing our dreams
Ah... Ah...
♪
[FUUKA]
Next time, "Live!"