Koyuki and... you?
But how?
[YUU gasps]
This isn't how it looks.
[FUUKA gasps]
[YUU gasps] Wait, Akitsuki!
Let me explain!
[YUU gasps]
[KOYUKI sighs]
♪
The place that I always dreamed
I'd reach one day
is too high above us
To get to
The promise we made is fading
every moment we
conform like they do
I wanna move on my own
Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat
I'm done trying to blend in
I won't be tied
to a tedious world
Repeating each day like
a broken record sickens me
(No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition)
It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening
We're in a box, stuck in a box
Meant to stifle what we feel
Forced to erase all
that we know is real
But I refuse to be locked up
Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies
Time to break free
Open our hearts to a world and
go racing forward to the light
These broken chains
can't hold us back
We're finally on track to heal
all the fractures in ourselves
As we climb and ascend
Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high
Hear these words and know your
dream can be stronger than steel
Just believe
You have the power
Let your voice be heard
♪
[footsteps]
You're totally soaked!
What happened to you?
Yeah. I guess it was raining
harder than I thought.
[laughs]
I bet you can't even
tell I used an umbrella!
Yep, that's a fact.
You should prob'ly dry
off and get changed, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, didn't he come
back with you?
[FUUKA]
Couldn't find him.
[MIKASA]
Huh?
Tama, are you okay?
[KOYUKI gasps] I'm sorry,
I just slipped, that's all.
So, who's your friend?
Is she the one you're
starting a band with?
[YUU]
Well, yeah,
We might've given her the
wrong idea. I mean, after all...
...you and I are
just friends, aren't we?
[YUU]
What a mess.
She definitely got
the wrong idea.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
There you are!
Listen, do you think we could
talk about last night?
[grunts]
[YUU gasps]
Sorry if I messed
up your evening.
Don't worry, I won't tell.
Wha--? Wait, No!
You've got it all mixed up!
[FUUKA]
Which part?
Tama and I--
Koyuki, I mean.
We're really just friends.
[FUUKA grunts]
If that's true,
then why didn't you
tell me you knew her?
[YUU]
I don't know.
I was looking for the
right time to say it.
You had plenty of chances!
You could've done it at
the movie, or at her concert...
[gasps]
Just forget it!
Akitsuki!
[clattering]
Uh-oh. What's goin'
on over here?
A little teen drama?
Earth to Yuu?
You spacin' out, "Teen Drama"?
[YUU exhales]
[GUY A]
Excuse me, miss!
[GUY B]
Can I order?
[YUU]
Uh. Hey, could--
What is with her?
Which guitar do you
think we should get?
[MIKASA]
First we should probably decide
who's playing what.
Yeah, guess you're right!
[MIKASA laughs] Got a little
ahead of yourself, there.
[FUUKA laughs]
I'm just so excited!
I love this time of day, when
we're finally past the rush.
[MIKASA sighs] Yeah, me too,
but it's a lot easier now.
[YAHAGI]
Easier, huh? Good to know.
I'd be happy to give you
some extra work tomorrow!
Thanks for the dinner!
[YAHAGI]
Huh? Sure.
[YUU sighs]
[FUUKA gasps]
Something happened between
you two, didn't it?
[gasps] No, I don't
know what you mean.
I think you do. It's obvious
when you're together.
[FUUKA grunts]
Wanna talk about it?
It's just that we're
having a little tiff.
[YUU grunts]
Akitsuki, watch it, will you?
[GIRL A]
Oops! Sorry about that!
Watch where you're
going next time!
Shut up, I was!
[GIRLS laugh]
[GIRL B]
Did you see his face?
Wanna come play with me?
I can't let this go on.
[YUU]
Akitsuki!
What do you want?
I'm sorry!
Huh?
[YUU] That's what I wanted.
To apologize.
[grunts]
Koyuki and I were, we were
friends when we were younger.
And we reconnected
on Twitter recently.
But, see, she was using
a private account,
so I couldn't
tell a stranger.
A stranger?
It happens all the time!
Some random person leaks a
celebrity's private account
and then they get spammed.
[YUU gasps]
Oh, right.
You wouldn't know since
you don't have a cell phone
Do you understand
what "spammed" means?
It's like when you get
bombarded online.
I mean, since you
don't use Twitter,
I bet this all sounds
pretty dumb to you!
It's just dangerous--
So, you thought if you
told a stranger like me,
I'd freak out and blab
to everybody, right?
Wha--? Uh, no. It's not that.
It's just that
on Twitter, it's--
[FUUKA] I get it, okay?
Don't make fun of me!
I don't get why it's
turning out like this.
[sighs] Why'd it have
to turn out like this?
[YUU, FUUKA gasp]
[YUU gasps]
[MIKASA gasps]
[YAHAGI]
Huh?
[TOMOMI] Hey, everyone!
Not working too hard, are you?
Uh. Miss, Tomomi, hello!
You brought Nachi
senpai with you?
I came to see how
you were doing!
[NACHI grunts]
[BOTH]
Uh...
[NACHI] Come back to
Tokyo with me right now
and join the track team!
It isn't too late.
Please don't start
with that again.
I don't get it, what are you
even doing here, Nachi?
Miss Tomomi told me at
school that the three of you
were working here
for the summer.
So I made her bring me along so
we could talk about track!
You had nothing better to do?
[NACHI]
What?!
I'm beginning to think
maybe I should've kept
their summer job to myself.
The way things are going, I'm
pretty sure I'd have to agree.
Hey, Haruna.
You think Fuuka should join
the track team, right?
Uh... I, well, I don't know.
[MIKASA] You shouldn't keep
pressuring her, Senpai.
Forcing someone to do
something they don't want,
that never yields
good results.
Yuu agrees with me,
right man?
Uh, sure.
[NACHI grunts]
[YUU]
Uh...
[FUUKA]
Jeez! Would you give it a rest?
I've already decided.
I'm gonna make music!
And we'll work our butts off
and become an awesome
band like the Hedgehogs!
Oh, wow!, Hearing you call
the Hedgehogs awesome
is making me blush!
[ALL]
Huh?
Why would calling them
awesome make you blush?
Come on, stop teasing.
Haven't you noticed?
Uh, no.
Uh. Hey, wait!, I think
I know who you are!
You're the guitarist for
the Hedgehogs! Hisa!
Uh-huh. There it is.
[TOMOMI] You got it!
So you know who I am now?
[YUU]
Hm... Maybe their manager?
[gasps]
I'm the keyboardist, Tomo!
[FUUKA]
Huh...? Huh?
[TOMOMI whimpers]
And of course you know,
Yassan's our drummer, right?
[FUUKA]
What?!
[YAHAGI]
Huh?
[FUUKA] Why didn't you tell
us this before now, huh?
[TOMOMI] I thought it'd
be fun to surprise you.
It's not like there was a
reason to come out and say it.
I can't believe I didn't
recognize you guys.
We've all gotten older, so we
look pretty different now.
I mean, look at Yassan.
He's already an old man.
Hey, Shut up.
I could've asked questions
and learned so much
from you if I'd known!
I am an enormous fan
of the Hedgehogs!
Same here, I'm a huge fan, too!
I listen to your CD every day!
So? I do, too!
[BOTH grunt]
Uhh, Thanks,
[FUUKA, YUU sigh]
So, wait a minute, Where are the
other members, Tama and Nico?
Those two disappeared
a little while back.
[FUUKA]
Huh?
Yeah, Tama just left out of
the blue without a word to us,
and then Nico took
off after her,
determined to track her down.
Well, that seems weird.
That's actually why the
band has been on a hiatus.
'Cause we've been
waiting around for 'em.
Yeah, they've been
gone for a while,
but we know they'll
come back eventually.
Hey, Yassan. When we get back
to Tokyo, you gotta teach us!
I promise, we'll do our
best to be like you guys!
Woah, You're a pretty
impulsive kid, aren't you?
[NACHI]
Hang on a minute, Fuuka.
What's your problem now?
This is pretty ridiculous.
Do you really think it's that
easy for a random person
to become a pro?
Well, no. Of course I don't
think it'll be easy, but--
Listen to me!
You know the track team's
a much better fit for you!
You can't even say for sure
that you have musical talent!
I say she does!
[gasps]
I've heard her sing before.
She's really wonderful.
You've heard her?
[gasps]
[YAHAGI]
Uh...
[TOMOMI sighs]
Okay. Why don't
we test her, then?
Man, this is such
a pain in my ass.
Such a complainer.
So, she's really gonna
try out in front of the pros
using one of
their own songs?
There's no way she
can handle that.
Once they give her
their brutal review,
you'll stop encouraging
her to do this, right?
[YUU]
But...
...I know she can do it,
[YAHAGI]
Haruna! C'mere a sec.
Yeah, I'm coming.
This bass belonged to Nico.
I think you should
play it, today.
Wha--?
I've never even touched a bass,
let alone played one.
No worries, no one expects a
newbie to play it exactly right.
All you have to do is hold
down these two strings
in time with the song.
And this one on the chorus.
Here, Try to use this thing.
[YUU]
Uh...
Not quite, that's upside down.
[MIKASA]
Yuu. Do you have a second?
[YUU]
So, what's up?
Be honest, are you and
Fuuka still having a fight?
Oh, I dunno,
Well, did you ever try
really talking to her?
I really want to, but it
never comes out right.
I think you're both
letting your pride
get in the way of
your own happiness.
[YUU gasps]
You want to make up,
isn't that right?
Yeah.
When I'm fighting with Akitsuki,
I can't enjoy my work or
any other part of my day,
And the hours seem
so much longer.
When I eat, it feels
like I'm choking,
and nothing tastes good.
Even sitting out by the ocean
feels lonely without her.
I think maybe I'm just
no good for anything
if she's not smiling
next to me.
So, yeah... I want to make up.
Good for you, but I
think the lesson here
is you should've just
told her all of that.
Isn't that right, Fuuka?
[YUU gasps]
[FUUKA whimpers]
Why'd you do that?
[MIKASA] 'Cause she was
feeling the same as you.
Said she had no idea
how to apologize, either.
[whimpers]
You two can handle it
on your own from here.
[YUU]
What? Mikasa, wait!
[YUU] I think I blurted
out way more than I
ever wanted her to hear,
"Maybe I'm just no good if
she's not smiling next to me."
What was that? A confession?
[gulps]
Stupid.
I'm sorry.
[YUU]
Oh, no. I'm sorry, really.
[FUUKA] And, listen. Thank you
for sticking up for me earlier.
[grunts]
Not bad, that bass suits you.
You look cool!
Wha--? You really think so?
I'm ready, I'll sing my best.
Welp, she's got some
stage presence at least.
[YAHAGI chuckles]
Let's do this.
♪
[gasps]
♪ The place that I always
dreamed I'd reach one day ♪
♪ is too high above
us to get to ♪
♪ The promise we made is ♪
♪ fading every moment
we conform like they do ♪
♪ I wanna move on my own ♪
♪ Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat ♪
♪ I'm done trying
to blend in ♪
♪ I won't be tied to
a tedious world ♪
♪ Repeating each day like a
broken record sickens me ♪
♪ No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition ♪
♪ It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening ♪
♪ We're in a box,
stuck in a box ♪
♪ Meant to stifle
what we feel ♪
♪ Forced to erase all
that we know is real ♪
♪ But I refuse to
be locked up ♪
♪ Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies ♪
♪ Time to break free ♪
♪ Open our hearts
to a world ♪
♪ and go racing forward
to the light ♪
♪ These broken chains
can't hold us back... ♪
♪ Wow, What's that? ♪
I remember this song,
I'm just trying to place it.
"Climber's High"
by the Hedgehogs.
One of my favorites.
Yeah, that's what it is!
They must be a cover band,
But they sound pretty good!
It brings back memories.
♪
Koyuki, we're loaded up
and ready to go.
'Kay, thanks.
♪
Is this for TV or something?
Dunno, but I'm digging this
girl's voice. She's great!
What's going on?
Looks like a band.
Let's go check it out!
♪ Feel a pulsing
that reaches ♪
♪ Out to the limits ♪
♪ Blowing fear away
with a vengeance ♪
♪ Growing faster
with every moment ♪
♪ Closing up the distance that
once seemed to be unending ♪
♪ Out of my despair ♪
♪ I can finally see ♪
♪ A new and perfect world ♪
♪ That's spread out
before me ♪
♪ No more walls
to close me in ♪
♪ An endless sky
of blue above ♪
[CROWD cheers]
That was awesome!
What is this for? Is there,
like, a festival going on?
Man, How did she do that?
[giggles]
Oh my gosh, that felt
so amazing!
How was the singing? Okay?
If you ask me?
It was rough,
but you've got potential.
You should keep it up.
[FUUKA cheers]
You hear that, Nachi?
I got approved by a pro!
Yeah, do whatever you want,
I still think it's a mistake.
Sure, you say that now, but you
know you were tapping along
through the whole thing.
Were you, really?
[NACHI gasps]
Liar!
If I was, it was only out of
habit from when my brother
used to make me play
drums for his band!
Wait, I have the best idea.
You, Senpai, are gonna
be our drummer!
Huh?
[FUUKA] Makoto will be
on keys, and of course,
Yuu will be our bassist.
[YUU]
Huh?
[FUUKA] And I'll be on guitar!
Our band is complete!
[NACHI]
Hang on! Do I get a say in this?
As soon as we get back to Tokyo,
we have to start practicing!
It was almost like we had
Tama back with us again.
You prob'ly could've
been a little nicer to her,
dontcha think?
You're an idiot. That would've
given her a big head.
Besides, you really think
this bunch of total amateurs
can make a go of it?
I think you forget. Sometimes
one person is all it takes.
[TOMOMI] One special person,
of overwhelming talent.
[YUU]
Mm?
Hey, Yuu, what's up?
What are you doing out here?
Well, since we're
going home soon,
I wanted to take a better look
at the stars before we left.
So beautiful.
[FUUKA gasps]
Are you okay? Dressed like that,
you must be cold.
[FUUKA] Yeah, hey, would you
let me use half of that?
[YUU]
Uh, wha--?
[FUUKA sighs, giggles]
See? Now I'm warm!
[gasps]
[FUUKA]
You gonna post it on Twitter?
[YUU] No, I don't think so.
It wouldn't do it justice.
See? a black screen.
Oh, wow, it is! Can't do
much with that, can ya?
[FUUKA giggles]
[YUU] Guess we should
probably head back.
[FUUKA]
Huh?
Um...
Well, I'm embarrassed,
I swear this wasn't on purpose!
[FUUKA growls]
You perv!
--[smack]
--[YUU groans]
♪
Looking up at the sky
I felt an emptiness
All the colors of
summer have been faded
Before I even knew the things
that made me the happiest
Were hidden and tucked away
But when I looked at you
it all felt so intense
Your eyes cut to the
core of my existence
Every word that you spoke
was like a painting in every hue
You brought calm into my world
All I can do now is breathe
And figure out just what I need
Resolve myself, pursue my dreams
I'm running
Moving forward, taking your hand
Being with you
I'm finally free enough to
spread out my wings
Let's catch the wind
and go for a ride
You and I can fly
anywhere together
We can go as high
up as we want
Following the path that's
been laid pout before us
Guided by our
bonded hearts forever
Let's keep living
out this fantasy
And chasing our dreams
Ah... Ah...
♪
Feels like it's been forever
since I've been home.
At least they can't complain.
I remembered to get them
all some souvenirs.
I'm home, Hey,!
Oh! Welcome back home, Nico!
Thanks, Tama,
[FUUKA]
Next time, "One of Us!"