[gasps]
[yelps]
[KOYUKI giggles]
Hey, it's just me.
Oh, thank god.
Starlet in disguise, I guess?
[laughs]
♪
The place that I always dreamed
I'd reach one day
is too high above us
To get to
The promise we made is fading
every moment we
conform like they do
I wanna move on my own
Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat
I'm done trying to blend in
I won't be tied
to a tedious world
Repeating each day like
a broken record sickens me
(No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition)
It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening
We're in a box, stuck in a box
Meant to stifle what we feel
Forced to erase all
that we know is real
But I refuse to be locked up
Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies
Time to break free
Open our hearts to a world and
go racing forward to the light
These broken chains
can't hold us back
We're finally on track to heal
all the fractures in ourselves
As we climb and ascend
Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high
Hear these words and know your
dream can be stronger than steel
Just believe
You have the power
Let your voice be heard
♪
[KOYUKI]
FYI.
This area's called "Little Edo"
or "Tiny Kyoto." I was here
filming a variety show once
and I fell in love with it.
[YUU]
Oh, that's cool.
Now I think I understand
why you picked this place.
So it did seem weird
to you at first?
[YUU]
No, why?
You know what I mean.
Don't most people prefer
to go to a restaurant?
For a first date?
Do they, really?
Well, I'd prefer this any day.
I'm so glad!
I was afraid you'd get
bored just walking around.
I shoulda known we'd
like the same thing.
[gasps] We're gonna
miss it! C'mon!
[YUU]
What'll we miss?
Where're we going?
Good, We made it!
That's the Bell of Time.
It'll ring any second now.
It's special 'cause it rings
just four times a day.
Wow.
And they say if any
couple hears it together,
they'll be connected to
each other for all eternity.
Huh?
That's a long time!
Have you heard that somewhere?
Maybe so.
So, wait, is that
really thing? Or no?
No, I made it up!
[YUU]
Uh?
[laughs]
[bell rings]
Sometimes I really love just
walking around, you know?
It's a great way
to clear your head.
Yeah, I agree.
Hey. Is your voice
feeling better?
It is. Thanks for
asking about it.
[YUU]
That's great.
Yeah, it's a big
relief, for sure.
But I'm glad I lost it,
because I learned something
new about myself.
I never truly realized
how much happiness
singing brought me
till it was gone.
I'm really lucky to have
a job that I enjoy so much.
That's cool.
I've never really had
a job like that--
one that I enjoyed, I mean.
It must be nice.
I bet you'll know soon enough
if your band keeps
getting bigger and bigger,
and I think it will. I do.
Well, I guess if we
went pro, then, maybe.
To be honest,
I can't wrap my head
around that possibility, though!
You haven't forgotten. have you?
Our promise to stand
on the same stage.
We pinky swore!
Oh! No, I didn't forget.
[gasps] Yes, you did,
I can tell!
There's no way! Whatever!
[KOYUKI huffs]
Well, anyway.
There's no doubt in my mind.
Music will be your bread
and butter someday, too!
[KOYUKI]
Don't laugh.
But I did a report
on this place once.
Wow, you did?
I'm getting the sweet
potato cream anmitsu .
[YUU]
Cool! I'll get that, too.
[LADY 9A]
I hope you both enjoy.
Let me know if
you need anything.
See? Doesn't it
look scrumptious?
[YUU]
Yeah!
Good?
[KOYUKI]
Oh, that.
So crazy!
I've just never seen your
autograph before.
When we're together
like this, it's like
I've gone back in time.
It's easy for me to forget
how famous you are.
In my mind,
you're still the same.
I see you as you were then,
that girl that I was
friends with as a kid.
I prefer it that way.
Uh.
When I'm hanging out with you,
I get to be the same
person I used to be.
In these past few
months, it's like...
I've lost sight of some things
because my life's been so crazy.
I feel like I was really
only thinking about myself.
I know now that it's my fault.
Things got so messed up.
Come on, you didn't do anything.
No. I was selfish. I was.
And then because of that,
I caused a lot of trouble
for you and my manager.
And a bunch of
other people, too.
But my fans were cheering
me on anyway,
and that gave me the strength
to get back up on my feet
and keep going.
This whole experience
has really driven it home.
I want to keep singing forever.
Honestly, having you back in
my life makes it all worth it.
[gasps]
Thank you for being
here for me like this.
It means the world.
It's my pleasure.
I should thank you.
I hope that means we
can be together this way,
all the time now.
I'm sorry I couldn't
hang out any longer.
[KOYUKI] That's okay.
Good luck at practice!
Oh, also, I really had
a lot of fun today!
Since I came this far,
I think I might stay here and
walk around a little bit more.
Will you be okay by yourself?
[KOYUKI] Uh. Wait, is this
you judging my disguise?
I think I'd give it
a six out of ten.
Hey, now, you be nice!
[BOTH laugh]
Well, be careful, okay?
[KOYUKI
'Course.
See ya!
[YUU]
Bye!
[KOYUKI]
Uh, Nico!
[YUU]
Uh?
Next time, you get to pick
the place where we hang out!
So, start thinking!
I will!
This is bad. I'm gonna be late.
I'd better get ready,
she's gonna be pissed.
Though, in my defense,
she should really get
a freakin' cell phone.
Sorry I'm so late!
[panting]
No, no, we love sitting around.
[YUU]
I'm really sorry!
I guess you couldn't help it
if you were on a date
with your girlfriend.
Keep that in mind when
it happens to me.
Not that you even
have a girlfriend.
Shut up, you!
You were so late,
we were worried.
Thought you might've
gotten into some mischief
and something bad happened.
You little pervert! What kind
of mischief did you--
[yells]
[NACHI groaning]
I apologize.
It won't happen again.
Well, now that everyone's
finally made it,
I think we should get started.
[YUU]
Uh.
What's wrong?
I was just expecting
you to chew me out.
The others have already
done that for me.
There's no point
in wasting time.
Well, thanks, I appreciate that.
[FUUKA inahles]
Okay, let's do this, guys!
[drunk sticks tapping]
[music plays]
Wait, we're an opening act?
That's right, you missed the
news because you were so late!
I'm never gonna live that down.
'Kay, here's the deal:
Hisashi introduced us
to his friend's club,
and we're the opening act!
He said it's our chance
to try something new
and polish our skills.
We're really lucky
your brother's
doting on us like this.
We finally get to strut
our stuff alongside
some other bands.
I am so freakin' pumped!
Whoa, cool it down
over there, tiger.
You know it's not a
competition, right?
Next thing we know,
you'll be beating your chest
and flexing shirtless.
Don't you wish. I'll flex
shirtless in your dreams!
This is so amazing!
Our first chance to play as
Fallen Moon in public together!
Yep, it's historic!
But what are we gonna play?
Just some more Hedgehogs covers?
That's a good question.
Actually, I kinda wanted to
talk to you guys about that.
Is everyone free right now?
Here's the thing.
I have a proposal.
I think that we should
write an original song.
[GROUP]
Uh...
That's all well and good.
Who's gonna write it though?
[FUUKA]
Mm.
Uh. You're gonna write it?
[FUUKA]
Mm-hm.
Okay, let's slow down.
Can you do it?
[FUUKA]
Mm!
'Kay, remind me. Do you play
any instruments at all?
Come on!
Just because I can't play
an instrument doesn't mean
I can't write a song, you know!
Easy as pie.
[FUUKA humming]
This is painful.
So, it's unconventional.
That suits Fuuka.
I guess.
Who cares how she does it?
As long as it's done
before our gig.
I promise you, I'll finish
in plenty of time!
Well, I think it sounds great.
Fallen Moon's first original.
Music and lyrics
by Fuuka Akitsuki.
Yeah, pretty cool.
[FUUKA gasping]
No pressure, but it
needs to rock, 'kay?
Yeah, about that. I was just
mulling it over last night.
Before I start writing, I think
we should have a discussion
about what our
influences should be!
--[MIKASA] Sure.
--[NACHI] Yeah.
[MIKASA]
Hm. That's a very good point.
I agree with that.
[phone vibrates]
Sorry, be right back.
Okay, but I still
think it should be
something that fires up
the crowd at our show.
[NACHI] Then I think
we should listen to
some of the Hedgehogs
stuff for inspirati...
[KOYUKI] Wow! Fuuka's
writing an original?
[YUU] Yeah, but we're still
trying to decide
what type of song it should be,
so I'm a little worried about
whether it'll be
finished in time.
[KOYUKI] I guess you'll
just have to trust Fuuka
to do her best.
When we asked how
she'd write it,
she said "like this!"
and she started humming!
[KOYUKI laughs]
That's just like her.
Yeah, it sure is.
You sound happy.
Well, I know I just saw
earlier you today,
but I already have
so much to tell you!
[YUU]
Yeah, I know what you mean!
[YUU sniffles]
You getting sick?
[YUU] No, I'm just standing
outside a restaurant.
Uh.
[YUU]
We were having a band meeting.
Oh. Sorry I called
at a bad time.
I'll try to catch you
again later, okay?
Wait. It's just...
I'm really glad that you're
feeling much better now.
[KOYUKI]
It's mostly because of you.
[YUU laughs]
Talk to you soon, Tama.
I'll call you next time.
Uh. Sorry. Just finished up.
Oh. Cool.
[singing]
[FUUKA singing]
Yeah, I think this one works
the best out of all of 'em.
Okay, so that takes care
of the melody, then.
And now for the lyrics.
I guess you couldn't help
it if you were on a date
with your girlfriend.
Talk to you soon, Tama.
No, no, no, I need
a change of pace!
[FUUKA]
Know what, Koyuki?
Listen, I'm rooting
for your love, okay?
I've tried rooting for her.
[FUUKA] But I still have no
idea, what it's really like
to be in love.
What's this feeling?
I don't like it.
[bass guitar plays]
[YUU]
Hm... Let's see.
Uh?
[FUUKA]
Look at these little alpacas.
You can have this one.
I remember this.
That was a good day.
I wonder how her new
song is coming along.
There you are!
I'd better make sure
I don't fall behind.
[FUUKA]
Ta-dah!
I'm finished with the new song!
[GROUP]
Oh!
Well, c'mon then,
let us hear it!
Sure!
[FUUKA singing]
[singing continues]
So, it doesn't have
any lyrics yet?
No, and I can't help that!
Hey, it'll be cool.
I'll transpose the melody
into sheet music.
And Sara, maybe you could
take care of the chords for us?
[SARA] Yep, on it.
[music plays]
That was amazing!
Hey, now, you're
the one who wrote it,
don't you remember?
But it turned out even better
than I could've imagined!
Well, of course it did.
Anything's better than that
humming you recorded for us.
Oh, jeez, would you let
me off the hook on that?
By the way, what's going
on with those lyrics, huh?
Yeah, honestly,
it's goin' pretty slow.
[GROUP]
Huh?
I'm sorry! Give me
just a little more time!
The thing is, we don't
have a lot of time.
Ya' think I don't know that?
Yeah, I'm really not
trying to rush you,
we just have to work
out the harmonies.
You're right, I'll try.
Uh, we're all aware you
can't rush great work.
Yeah. Feel like the
important thing is
that you're happy with
the final product.
Thank you.
[footsteps]
[SARA] So, I was
practicing the song for
a while in the studio
the other day,
and my brother
came in and said it
sounded pretty good.
Are you for real?
[SARA]
Mm-hm.
Getting a compliment
from Hisashi
makes my whole life!
It's not surprising.
It's a really great song.
Yeah. Have some confidence!
You know, I have to say, Yuu.
It's like you're not even
the same person now.
Huh? Are you serious?
Sure am.
I can totally tell
you've been practicing.
It's pratically
like night and day.
Well, thanks.
Maybe I won't end up holding
the band back forever after all.
Ooh! Yuu's a big boy now!
[laughs] Aw, stop it.
Akitsuki?
Is something wrong?
Listen, you guys.
I'm really sorry
about the lyrics.
I swear to you, I'll
get them done in time!
You can trust me!
We know that.
We're looking forward
to hearing them!
I have a feeling they're
gonna be worth the wait.
I'll write the best song ever.
That way you'll forget how
long you had to wait for it.
[laughs]
[sighs]
[guitar strumming]
[phone vibrates]
Hey, Tama! Oh.
Are you still at work?
[KOYUKI]
Yeah.
But I'm on break right now, so
I thought I'd give you a call.
What're you up to over there?
I've been practicing
our new song.
[KOYUKI]
Uh-- New song?
You mean the one Fuuka
said she was gonna write?
She finished it?
That's right!
I think it turned
out pretty good.
And it sounds exactly
like something
you'd think she would write.
It has a certain feel to it.
Wow, that's so great.
[YUU] The only thing is,
the lyrics haven't
actually been written yet.
Oh.
[YUU] We're all really
eager to hear them.
I can't wait to see
what she comes up with.
[KOYUKI]
Yeah. Sorry, Nico,
but I think I'd
better get back now.
[YUU]
Oh, of course. I'm sorry, too.
Good luck with work, though!
[KOYUKI]
Thanks.
Oh, do you have any
time tomorrow night?
[YUU] Ah. We actually have
practice in the evening.
I was hoping I could
maybe see you
before that just for a minute?
[YUU]
Sure.
The secret to writing
a great song!
You see, I'm in a band.
And I want to start writing
some original music
for us to play together.
It's one-sided, but, yes.
I guess I write songs
as a way to express it.
I've never actually
told him how I feel.
[FUUKA]
Unrequited love...
Use your music to tell
someone how you really feel.
There you are, Fuuka.
You've got a call
from someone named
Hisashi Iwami?
[gasps] It's so early, though!
[MIKI]
Yasunobu, did you hear?
Miyamoto is coaching...
[HISASHI] Sorry to call you
out of the blue like that,
but there's a good reason.
I'd like to introduce you
to one of my colleagues.
You're a music producer?
My name is Akira Mogami.
This guy used to be in
a band just like I did.
At one point, he claimed
to aspire to be like us.
But just look at him now,
a big wig in the industry.
[chuckles] Oh, please.
So then, what is it that you
wanted to talk with me about?
Our concert?
To tell you the truth,
I could hardly believe it.
Not only were you not outshined
by Koyuki Hinashi up there,
you actually ate her alive!
I'll go ahead and get
straight to the point.
Do you have any interest
in going professional?
[gasps]
Are you asking us to go pro?
Well, not "us" exactly.
The band does a really good job,
but I'm only after your singing.
Huh?
When I saw that video,
I was stunned,
I couldn't believe
what I was hearing.
I felt I'd found a raw
diamond lying in the rocks
by the side of the road!
But gravel roads aren't for you!
Walking down a red carpet--
that's where you belong!
You are nothing less
than a shining gem!
That's kind of you, sir.
I appreciate the offer, but
I'm afraid I have to refuse.
Sorry, but my real place
is with my band mates.
[AKIRA grunts]
See? I told you so, didn't I?
[sighs] Oh, man, what a bummer.
If you ever change your mind,
I want you to promise
to contact me, okay?
Okay.
Although, I'm pretty sure
that's not gonna happen.
[gasps]
I always take the worst selfies.
So, now that I see it,
it looks blurry.
[KOYUKI] I think I'd give
it a six out of ten.
--[YUU] Oh, okay...
--[FUUKA] What is this?
My head is all confused
and my chest feels tight.
I don't like this.
♪
Looking up at the sky
I felt an emptiness
All the colors of
summer have been faded
Before I even knew the things
that made me the happiest
Were hidden and tucked away
But when I looked at you
it all felt so intense
Your eyes cut to the
core of my existence
Every word that you spoke
was like a painting in every hue
You brought calm into my world
All I can do now is breathe
And figure out just what I need
Resolve myself, pursue my dreams
I'm running
Moving forward, taking your hand
Being with you
I'm finally free enough to
spread out my wings
Let's catch the wind
and go for a ride
You and I can fly
anywhere together
We can go as high
up as we want
Following the path that's
been laid pout before us
Guided by our
bonded hearts forever
Let's keep living
out this fantasy
And chasing our dreams
Ah... Ah...
♪
[FUUKA]
Next time, "Fate."