The thing is...
...I've been scouted, so I'm
going to make my solo debut.
[YUU]
No. What's she saying?
This can't be real.
[NACHI]
Damn it!
Haruna, c'mon! Say something!
I've gotta take a step
toward my dream.
I'm sorry, guys.
Which means I'm gonna
have to quit the band.
[gasps]
[NACHI]
Come on, man!
What can I say?
She's already made her decision.
It's over.
[YUU]
Isn't it...?
The place that I always dreamed
I'd reach one day
is too high above us
To get to
The promise we made is fading
every moment we
conform like they do
I wanna move on my own
Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat
I'm done trying to blend in
I won't be tied
to a tedious world
Repeating each day like
a broken record sickens me
(No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition)
It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening
We're in a box, stuck in a box
Meant to stifle what we feel
Forced to erase all
that we know is real
But I refuse to be locked up
Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies
Time to break free
Open our hearts to a world and
go racing forward to the light
These broken chains
can't hold us back
We're finally on track to heal
all the fractures in ourselves
As we climb and ascend
Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high
Hear these words and know your
dream can be stronger than steel
Just believe
You have the power
Let your voice be heard
♪
[AKIRA]
That's our standard contract.
Have your parents look
it over and let me know
if they have any questions.
[FUUKA]
Okay.
[AKIRA] You seemed
so sure when you said no.
That's kind of you.
Sorry, but my place
is with my bandmates.
So, what made
you change your mind?
[AKIRA] "A maiden's heart
is as fickle as autumn."
Actually, that's about
first love, isn't it?
I thought about it and decided
this was the right choice.
Good. Then I'm glad
we can agree.
Thank you
for everything, sir.
[phone buzzes]
[KOYUKI]
Hey, it's me!
Oh, gosh, you're not
in class right now, are you?
[YUU]
No, school's out.
What time is it there?
[KOYUKI]
Seven in the morning.
I think I'm finally
getting over my jet lag.
Good thing, too,
because we're filming
a music video today.
[YUU]
That's great. Good luck.
Nico, is there something wrong?
[YUU]
No, not really.
[KOYUKI] You sure? You sound
a little bit down today.
[YUU]
Nah, I'm okay.
[KOYUKI] I've bought
a ton of souvenirs.
I hope I'll see you
as soon as I get back.
[YUU]
Yeah.
[KOYUKI]
Hey, are you really all right?
Did something happen?
[YUU]
No, nothing.
[KOYUKI]
Well, if you're sure.
I just can't wait to see
your face after so long.
Talk to you soon, okay?
[YUU]
Sure.
[MIKASA]
Wow, it's been a while.
Feels like forever
since we've met up.
That's because there's
no point in meeting up.
What's a band without a vocalist
supposed to do, anyway?
Or are we actually
going to discuss
finding a new one?
We can't do that.
You know there's
no replacement for Fuuka.
[NACHI] I agree. So, then,
what's the point of this?
[MIKASA]
It just...
...doesn't feel right for it
to fizzle out this way
with no closure at all.
Okay, so you need to
hear the words out loud?
Fine, we're breaking up!
[SARA]
Would you stop it?
You're not helping
anything, you know.
That talk about
creating a legend.
I'd actually started
to believe what she said.
I tried so hard
to get Fuuka to join the
track team, but she managed
to drag me into a band instead.
Crazy.
But, honestly, I think
I was looking for something.
As you know,
track was pretty much
my whole life before this.
Truth is, things haven't
gone all that
well for me in school.
So, when I look
back on it now,
it seems obvious that
the band was an escape.
[SARA]
An escape from what?
Well, from disappointed
expectations, I guess.
Turns out, there
are still some track
scholarships available and my
coach even said he'd be happy to
put in a good word for me.
He was glad
I came back, and seems
to think my running still has
some potential for success.
And so it's time
to stop playing around.
I'm gonna do what
my coach suggests...
...and be happy.
Time to stop
playing around. Maybe...
...it's not bad advice.
Perhaps I should
take it, myself.
[gasps]
God, Haruna. Why are
you just standing there?
Don't you have a single
thought in your damn head?
[growls] Don't you? What were
you even thinking that night?
Only you could've stopped her!
Are you that blind?
--[YUU gasps]
--[MIKASA] Nachi, come on.
[SARA]
Stop it!
Hell. Not like
it really matters,
but I'm officially done
with this band.
[YUU sighs]
[FUUKA] ♪ Don't care how
far away we might be ♪
♪ Whatever we're both doing ♪
♪ We'll never be apart ♪
♪ No matter how hard we try ♪
♪ We'll always have each other ♪
♪ A shoulder-- ♪
Wow, that was
absolutely fantastic!
Such great work!
Thanks, I'm glad
you're happy with it.
I gotta admit, when I
get it right, I get it right.
[FUUKA]
This is all good.
I made the right decision--
it's gonna be okay.
[HISA grunts]
Hey. Have a good shower?
Hey, Brother,
what're you doing home?
[HISA] I came by to
pick up some scores.
[SARA] Does that mean
the Hedgehogs are
getting back together?
Looks like it,
now that those two are back.
[SARA]
Good for you.
[HISA]
Hmm?
Sara, would you
be interested in subbing
for other bands?
[SARA gasps]
[HISA] There's a band that
comes into the studio a lot.
They have an important gig
coming up but one of their
members got injured.
[SARA sighs]
So, they're looking
for a guitarist right now.
[SARA]
I don't know.
[HISA]
Yeah, I didn't think so.
You're not the type to
be happy as long as you get
to play a few gigs.
[SARA]
No, wait. I'll give it a try.
[gasps]
What? Are you serious?
Yeah, and what's
with the reaction?
It was your idea, after all.
I know! I know
it was, but I guess I...
You just answered
so quickly, so...
Well, look. To be honest...
...I feel bad about
the way it all went down.
I was the one who
introduced them to
each other, Fuuka and Mogami.
Doesn't matter, she
decided for herself in the end.
Fuuka is responsible
for her own choices.
[MIKOTO] Makoto, are you
really sure about this?
About what?
I mean, you moved
out because you
wanted to pursue
your music, isn't that right?
[MIKASA sighs]
[MIKOTO] But if you're
coming back home,
that means you're throwing away
your dream and following
the path Dad decides
for you, doesn't it?
I hate to see you give
up and decide to admit defeat!
Listen to me, Mikoto.
It's not always about
winning and losing.
I finally realized.
I never even tried to convince
Dad of my point of view.
I just ran away instead.
[MIKOTO] But, the piano!
Your dream of playing music!
What about that?
[door creaks]
[YUU]
Huh? Tama?
[giggles] I was determined
to surprise you.
Did it work?
[YUU]
This really is a surprise.
[KOYUKI giggles] It's been
a crazy long time, huh?
It was your concert,
the last time I saw you.
[YUU]
That's right.
It was such a great show.
I was so proud of you.
Thank you.
[gasps]
Something did happen, didn't it?
[YUU sighs]
[CHITOSE] Hey, don't
you think we should take
some snacks upstairs to them?
If they want any, Yuu will
come down and get some.
Yeah, he will.
I think maybe I'll go ahead
and bring some up there.
Would you forget it?
They're together in their
own little world right now.
Don't barge in.
Let them enjoy it.
[whines]
[KOYUKI]
So, Fuuka's moving on?
[YUU] Yeah, I think
what really hurts is that
none of us saw this coming.
So, now, the rest of us
have kind of lost
our motivation.
It's like a hole just
opened up right inside my chest.
[KOYUKI sighs]
Now I realize, the heart
and soul of this band
really was Akitsuki.
So if she isn't in it
anymore, there's really
no point in keeping it going.
[KOYUKI] But maybe
this is all for the best.
[gasps]
Even if The Fallen
Moon might be gone,
you can still keep
pursuing music.
Huh?
[KOYUKI]
Did you forget?
We made a promise to each other
that we'd stand on the same
stage together someday.
Yeah. And as much
as I appreciate
you bringing that up right now.
I'm not ready to play--
I don't care about all that!
[gasps]
[KOYUKI]
Don't you see?
All I've ever cared about
is being with you.
It's all I want.
Nothing else matters!
Tama, wait.
I love you
and I always have, my Nico.
That's why...
[gasps]
Tama, don't do this.
[KOYUKI]
Why not?
Well, because I...
[YUU]
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[sighs]
I knew all along.
[KOYUKI]
I knew it couldn't be me.
What do you mean?
I knew it all,
the feelings you didn't
know you had for Fuuka.
And the feelings she
didn't know she had for you.
All of it.
[sobs]
So, listen, Nico.
Just be honest
with yourself from now on.
Tama!
[KOYUKI sobs]
[KOYUKI]
Goodbye, Nico.
I don't need one.
So, you can go ahead
and keep 'em both.
I can't! It's a bonus
for "couples only"!
[HIBIKI]
Yuu! The bath is free!
Are you deaf or what?
Hello? Can you hear me?
[MAYA]
How did he look?
He's sitting at
his desk working really
intently on something.
[CHITOSE] What is it?
What's he working on?
I have no idea.
He hasn't eaten
anything today, either.
I'm getting worried about him.
[gasps]
I bet I know what it is!
Koyuki must have dumped him!
[HIBIKI] Well, I think
he'll be just fine.
[BOTH gasp]
Those were the eyes
of a guy who's
looking forward to
something. You'll see.
♪
[SARA sighs]
[GUITARIST A] Wow, I can totally
see why Hisashi recommended you!
I know that you were
only supposed to be
helping us out
with this one gig,
but would you want
to join the band?
--Huh?
--Seriously, we sound
a bazillion times better
with you playing!
[BASSIST A]
Yeah, for real.
Welp, we can talk
about it again after the gig!
--Yeah!
--[GUITARIST A] Cool!
[NACHI pants]
[MIYAMOTO] So, Nachi? What do
you think of college practices?
Honestly, it's all
I can do just to keep up.
But I'm enjoying it!
[MIYAMOTO]
Hmph. I see.
Once you enroll,
you'll be dedicating
a lot more time to track.
I hope you're ready.
I am!
[MIKASA sighs]
[YUU groans]
Okay!
[NACHI]
Why are you doing here so early?
[YUU] Because... I want the
band to get back together.
Why are you
doing this? It's too late.
Yeah, I get it. But, I--
Enough. I told
you man, I'm gonna
focus on track from now on.
[YUU] Please, just listen
to this, would you?
Then we'll talk again!
[NACHI grunts]
Hey!
[YUU]
Haah.
[MIKASA]
Yuu?
[YUU]
I want the band to keep going.
With you in it.
[gasps]
I'm sorry, Yuu.
Moving out of my father's house
was an act of rebellion.
But now,
that has to be over.
[gasps]
I've decided
to listen to my father.
I mean, he's literally
promised me a happy future!
So I don't have to
stress myself out any more.
Chasing pointless dreams that
won't come true, anyway!
Listen, I know it's unfair.
I have no right to
interfere in your future.
I know it's a lot to ask.
But, my friend,
I'm asking you, anyway.
Help me put this band
back together again.
[MIKASA sighs]
[YUU]
Here.
[BAND MEMBERS laughing]
[BASSIST A]
Man, we killed it today!
[DRUMMER A]
I know, right?
So you really wrote
this song for the band?
[YUU] Yes. Sara, I'm putting
the band back together.
[YUU]
Please come back.
I'm really happy
that you asked.
But I'm already...
I do believe, it's
thanks to all of you that
I'm able to get along
so well with these guys.
I'm truly thankful
to you for that.
And I know I always will be.
But, I... think it's
best if I stay where I am.
I understand that.
But even so,
I refuse to give up.
[SARA sighs]
[door bell ringing]
[door bell continues ringing]
[YUU] Hey, guys.
This is a song I wrote.
I know I don't express
my feelings much.
[YUU] But this song
is honest, from my heart.
Would you do me a favor
and please give it a listen?
And if you feel anything
like me after you do,
meet me at 3 on Saturday
at our favorite place.
[pants]
[NACHI sighs]
You coming?
[NACHI]
Uh... Yes!
[door bell rings]
Yeah?
Umineko Movers!
Thanks for helping out,
I appreciate it.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[YUU]
Sara!
Aren't the others here?
Their loss.
I'm so glad
you're here, though!
Your lyrics got me.
They spoke to me
in a very real way.
[gasps]
[MIKASA]
So sorry I'm late!
I had to cancel
quite a few things
before I could make it here!
The three of us, huh?
Well. I'd say that's pretty good
since it's so last-minute!
Don't make him
feel bad, Mikasa!
Not what I meant.
[MIKASA] I wrote sheet
music of your song.
Thanks, man.
[NACHI]
Hey!
Who gave your permission to get
things moving before I got here?
I listened and it was hot!
Thank you so much, my friend.
Come on.
You wouldn't have gotten
anywhere without me, right?
So? Where's our singer?
Yeah. I reached
out to Akitsuki, too.
[SARA]
Hmm?
[YUU] I know it's selfish
of me, but she just has
to be a part of The Fallen Moon.
It's hers. So I'm determined
to bring her back.
[MIKASA, SARA grunt]
Well then, we'd best
start practicing so
we'll be ready for her
when she comes back!
[YUU]
Right!
♪
[KOYUKI giggles]
So, you're starting it up again?
[YUU] Yeah. Except,
we're still waiting
for Akitsuki to come back.
Tama, thanks so much.
Because of you,
I was able to take this step.
You made me believe I could.
[gasps]
I dunno.
I'm pretty sure you already knew
what mattered to you.
You didn't need me
to realize that.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
[KOYUKI giggles]
[KOYUKI] Thanks for
everything, old friend.
[KOYUKI giggles]
Looking up at the sky
I felt an emptiness
All the colors of
summer have been faded
Before I even knew the things
that made me the happiest
Were hidden and tucked away
But when I looked at you
it all felt so intense
Your eyes cut to the
core of my existence
Every word that you spoke
was like a painting in every hue
You brought calm into my world
All I can do now is breathe
And figure out just what I need
Resolve myself, pursue my dreams
I'm running
Moving forward, taking your hand
Being with you
I'm finally free enough to
spread out my wings
Let's catch the wind
and go for a ride
You and I can fly
anywhere together
We can go as high
up as we want
Following the path that's
been laid pout before us
Guided by our
bonded hearts forever
Let's keep living
out this fantasy
And chasing our dreams
Ah... Ah...
♪
[doorbell rings]
[SUZUKA]
Coming!
A-ha! You wouldn't be Yuu
Haruna, now, would you?
Uh. Yes, I am.
Hi, there, I'm Fuuka's mom.
Nice to meet you.
[YUU]
Nice to meet you, too.
Um, is Akitsuki here?
[SUZUKA] Sorry,
Fuuka's out for the night.
She told me she'd
be back pretty late.
[YUU]
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Could you tell her
I'll come back later?
[SUZUKA]
Sure.
Thanks. Well, goodnight, then.
All right,
I sent him away for you.
Thanks, Mom. I'm sorry.
Are you sure
it's what you want?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm sure.
[FUUKA]
Next time, "Fair Wind"