♪ I want to believe
we were meant to be ♪
♪ but we lost somehow
I realize that now ♪
♪ It was you I always loved ♪
♪ Always you who
held my heart ♪
That's strange. She's not
quite up to par today.
I know.
[KOYUKI] ♪ ...as snow
melts into fireworks ♪
♪ cause I gave you all of me♪
[MALE STAFF A]
Be safe!
We got a really good take!
Even if it took a while.
Sorry about that.
Oh, no worries,
that's the way it goes.
Some days are just hard.
Yeah, they are.
Oh, man. It ripped
me up back then, though.
Because I never got the chance
to tell you that I liked you.
[KOYUKI]
I should actually get going.
I have work tomorrow, so...
[YUU]
Bye.
On tomorrow's agenda, you've
got more time in the studio
and five interviews, plus,
the big production meeting.
So, it's shaping up to be
a particularly busy day.
Oh, and the details
on that drama.
[KOYUKI] It feels like it's
happening all over again.
♪
The place that I always dreamed
I'd reach one day
is too high above us
To get to
The promise we made is fading
every moment we
conform like they do
I wanna move on my own
Step away from the crowd
I wanna dance to my own beat
I'm done trying to blend in
I won't be tied
to a tedious world
Repeating each day like
a broken record sickens me
(No matter how I try
I can't escape repetition)
It's hard to change it up
When no one else is listening
We're in a box, stuck in a box
Meant to stifle what we feel
Forced to erase all
that we know is real
But I refuse to be locked up
Won't live in this prison
Gotta fight for open skies
Time to break free
Open our hearts to a world and
go racing forward to the light
These broken chains
can't hold us back
We're finally on track to heal
all the fractures in ourselves
As we climb and ascend
Aiming high to the end
We'll feel a climber's high
Hear these words and know your
dream can be stronger than steel
Just believe
You have the power
Let your voice be heard
♪
Come on, hurry!
You're takin' all day!
[YUU] Just hold on!
It's really scary!
[KOYUKI]
Are you crying again?
Maybe. Shut up.
Such a baby. You gotta be brave!
Owwie...
Uh, what happened?
I don't know. I guess
I cut my finger.
Just hold on. I can
give you a Band-aid!
Wait! Don't go too fast!
You'll fall!
[YUU]
Nah, I'll be fine!
Here you go.
Thanks, it's really
not a big deal.
Yeah, it is.
It'll get all infected.
[YUU]
There.
Well, thank you.
[chuckles]
[KOYUKI grunts]
C'mon, let's go explore!
[YUU]
Uh.. Are you sure we should?
It's dark in there.
[KOYUKI grunts]
We're doing it!
[YUU groans]
Tomorrow, let's turn it
into our secret base!
[YUU]
Okay!
[KOYUKI]
Cool! Have a good night!
See ya tomorrow!
[KOYUKI giggles]
[YUU'S MOM] Goodness.
How'd you get so dirty?
[YUU]
Well, we were exploring!
[KOYUKI exhales]
[KOYUKI'S DAD] I told you!
I've had a lot going on at work!
[KOYUKI'S MOM]
You're such a liar!
You think I don't know
you're cheating on me?
How dare you!
While I clean our house and
take care of our child!
[KOYUKI'S DAD] What did you say?
Go on, say it again!
[KOYUKI'S MOM] I'll say it
as many times as it takes!
You always use work
as your excuse,
but we both--
[KOYUKI'S DAD]
Are you kidding me?
I work so hard to
support this family!
[YUU]
Hey, isn't it time to go home?
No, not yet.
I wonder if it'll snow.
What do you think?
Snow?
Yeah.
I dunno. It seems like it
hardly ever snows here.
I know, you're right.
Then again, maybe it will.
[KOYUKI]
Huh?
I mean, after all,
you never know!
Hey, if we do get snow,
we've gotta build a snowman!
Igloo, too!
[KOYUKI gasps, giggles]
You're on!
♪ When I look deep within ♪
♪ There is a town I see
It flickers like a flame ♪
♪ That's fading slowly ♪
♪ The things I used to know ♪
♪ The things I
once believed ♪
♪ Are fading from my mem'ry ♪
[gasps] You're a
really good singer!
Huh? Are you being serious?
That was "The Town Where
the Stars Fall," wasn't it?
Wow, you know it?
Oh yeah, the Hedgehogs have
always been my favorite band.
And you sounded almost
exactly like Tama just now.
My favorite member is Nico.
I know! As soon as we grow up,
let's be in a band together!
Just like the Hedgehogs!
Huh?
It'll be the coolest, ever!
Of course, I need to learn
to play an instrument!
Yeah!
And I'll keep practicing my
singing so I can get better!
We're just like Nico and Tama!
Oh hey! How about I start
calling you Tama?
Oh cool, yeah! From now on,
I'll only call you Nico!
Our band, it's a promise!
[YUU]
Yep!
Promise to make a snowman, too!
[YUU]
Sure!
[gasps]
You're going out?
My parents are taking me!
Since today's my birthday, they
said we'd celebrate tonight!
You seem really happy, Tama.
It's been ages since we
all went out together.
Oh, I see. That's great, then!
[KOYUKI gasps]
Mom! Dad! Ha, ha!
I'll see
you tomorrow, Nico! Bye!
Okay, bye!
[KOYUKI]
Later that night...
...I watched the snow fall,
for the first time in my life.
[YUU gasps]
Hey! Tama!
Where's she going?
Sorry, honey. But, I won't be
able to be with you any more.
[sobs]
Do you remember your
grandfather in Tokyo?
Well, from now on, you and
I will live with him.
I can't. I don't want
to say goodbye to Nico.
I wanna stay with him forever!
[sobs]
[YUU]
Tama!
[KOYUKI gasps]
Hey, Nico.
I've been waiting for you!
Come with me!
Come on, hurry!
We gotta go fast!
Where the heck're
you taking me?
There wasn't enough
for an igloo, but, look!
[gasps] You built snowmen!
[YUU]
Just like we promised.
[KOYUKI giggles]
You remembered every word, huh?
Sure, I did! I like it when
I get to make you smile.
[gasps]
[YUU]
Uh...
Uh, what'd I say?
[KOYUKI] I'm really sorry
that I can't say goodbye.
I feel like if I saw you,
all I'd do is cry again.
[KOYUKI] I promise. I'll do
my best to get stronger.
That way, I'll always be able
to smile, no matter what.
[KOYUKI] It's time for me
to stop being afraid.
[KOYUKI] So, the next time
I see Nico, I can tell him.
[KOYUKI]
Yamada.
So the Christmas concert
that's coming up.
I need one of the tickets.
What? If there's someone
you want to invite,
just let me know.
No, I've got to do
this in person.
[KOYUKI grunts]
[doorbell rings]
Not home.
[gasps]
[YUU]
Excuse me.
[KOYUKI gasps] Oh, gosh.
I swear, I'm not a stalker!
Tama! Hey!
[giggles]
Uh, I'm really sorry.
No one else is around today.
No, it's fine.
I should apologize to you
for randomly showing up!
Nah, really, no worries at all!
Okay.
[KOYUKI]
Just give him the ticket
and apologize for
the other night.
You have to make
things right with him!
[KOYUKI]
Um... Here.
[YUU]
Mm... Uh...
I have a concert coming up
in Yokohama next month.
I was hoping you might
be able to make it out
if you aren't busy.
Uh, you were?
I'm so sorry about last time.
I was just taken
off guard, you know?
And then I was worried
that you might hate me now,
so I was afraid to
even email you.
[gasps]
But I couldn't stand to
leave things like that.
So I worked up the courage
to come here again.
I feel exactly the same!
I've been terrified
to message you because
I thought you hated me!
[KOYUKI gasps]
You know, you could've
just come out and said so!
I've been super stressed
about all this!
Well, I was really upset, too!
My bad, you're right.
Some things never change.
I can't believe you still mope,
just like you used to.
Okay, that's harsh.
[KOYUKI exhales]
[YUU groans]
Are you coming to
the concert, or not?
I swear I'll be there.
Okay. Then, I guess
I forgive you.
Good, I'm so glad.
[giggles]
[YUU] It's amazing, you know.
I can't believe you've had
so many big concerts
booked in one year!
And those aren't easy
set lists, either!
It's a pretty long show
and I have a new song!
Yeah? I can't wait to hear it!
You're in luck!
As a matter of fact...
[YUU gasps]
Oh, that reminds me!
My band's gonna be
playing a concert, too!
At the school fair!
Yeah? That's so cool.
Yep. I've been practicing a ton,
but I'm still worried
I'm gonna screw it up.
[KOYUKI] With that same girl
you were with at the beach?
Uh-huh. She's kinda nuts.
I think you'd like her
if you got to know her.
She's super impulsive and does
crazy things like gathering
a bunch of newbs
together to be in a band,
which is pretty absurd.
But she's also loads of fun
to be around most of the time.
And she's got an
incredible voice!
You should hear her!
We ended up performing at
a beach house over summer break,
and she sang "Climbers High"
by the Hedgehogs!
She totally knocked
it outta the park!
I get it!
[YUU]
Uh...
Sorry, she sounds great!
But, it's just that I-- I didn't
realize how late it was,
so I have to get
back to work now!
Good to see you.
Sorry I intruded.
Well, intrude longer next time.
I know my sisters
are dying to see you.
Deal.
Anyway, I'm just
really relieved.
Now we can be friends again!
[gasps]
You okay?
[KOYUKI]
I was just thinking...
Could we renew our
promise from before?
Uh...
Oh, come on, you couldn't
have forgotten.
We promised we'd perform
on the same stage!
Sure. We can do that.
We will do it!
Hey, pinky swear!
Right! It's a promise.
See you later, Nico!
[YUU]
See ya!
Does he feel the same way?
I can't tell.
[KOYUKI gasps]
[FUUKA] Stop! Wait!
Look what you did, you jerk!
[FUUKA]
Hey, are you okay?
Sometimes, I think they
actually try to do that.
Akitsuki, right?
[FUUKA gasps]
What the--? Koyuki?
That's me.
[FUUKA] If you want, I can
wash these dirty clothes
before you go.
Okay. Thank you, Akitsuki.
Oh, call me Fuuka!
I live just upstairs.
The bath's aren't open yet,
but feel free to use
'em if you want,
since you'd have the
whole place to yourself!
[FUUKA giggles]
What am I even doing here?
Good grief.
[FUUKA]
I can't believe it!
What on earth brought
you over here?
Jeez, you poor thing!
Your clothes are soaked!
[KOYUKI grunts]
It's fine!
I can grab a taxi
home to change!
[FUUKA]
Nope! This way!
[KOYUKI gasps]
Um. Where're you taking me?
You'll see! Just come on!
Mind if I get in with--
Wait a minute!
[KOYUKI]
Huh?
[FUUKA] Sorry but you
can't actually take a towel
in the bath with you!
What? But, I thought
people always did that
at the Hot Springs resorts.
No, no, no!
That's just on TV!
Uh, right, of course.
I'm sorry about that.
Never been to one of these,
as you can tell.
Oh, well that explains a lot.
Then I hope you will allow me,
your friendly
bathhouse professional,
to instruct you in some
useful bathhouse etiquette!
[FUUKA] You've always gotta
wash off before you get in.
So many people use
these public baths,
so we've hafta keep 'em clean.
Thanks but, I can
probably wash myself.
No, it's my pleasure. Think of
it as a special service!
You know, I've gotta tell you.
I think you've got
the perfect hair!
Uh? You do?
Yeah. I'm jealous!
Well, thanks, but I could
say the same thing to you
about your beautiful skin!
[KOYUKI]
'Bout the same.
What? You okay?
[KOYUKI] O-Oh, yeah!
Yeah! I'm just fine!
[FUUKA]
Hm?
Hey, Akitsuki.
I told you, Fuuka's fine.
Fuuka, then...
Yeah?
Thank you for
washing my clothes.
And for the bath.
You don't have to thank me!
I mean, I've always
wished I could somehow
get to know you, so...
Uh, why's that?
Because I'm your biggest fan!
Your last CD was so amazing!
Omigosh! Could you please sign
it for me before you go?
I will love you forever!
Sure! Yeah. I'd be happy to.
Wa-hoo! I just love
your music so much.
Most of your lyrics make me cry!
[KOYUKI chuckles nervously]
Thanks, I think!
So, tell me. How do you write
songs that are so powerful?
Um, what exactly
are you asking?
The secret to writing
a great song!
You see, I'm in a band.
And I want to start writing
some original music
for us to play together.
So, I'd love to hear all
about your writing method!
[KOYUKI]
Uh...
My band's gonna play
a concert, too!
At the school fair!
I don't really see how my music
could be of much help to you.
I don't have a band.
What?
No, but I wanna write songs
that move people like yours.
Honestly, I think something
a little more cheerful and fun
would suit you better!
'Cause, I mean, my songs
are about unrequited love.
What a drag. And about
how nothing I do pays off.
That is not true!
Uh...
[FUUKA sighs]
Ah! Your songs are just so...
how do I put it?
It's like your whole
heart's in every word.
What do you mean,
my whole heart?
[FUUKA sighs]
Every part of you.
The good stuff and the bad.
You're a human doing her
best to love no matter what.
That's what I like most
about the things you write.
[KOYUKI]
I see.
I never thought you were
saying nothing you did paid off.
Your songs are...
really optimistic.
To me, for what it's worth.
Thanks, Fuuka.
So, you see?
That's why I want you to
teach me how you do it.
So I can write songs
that make people feel
how I do about yours!
Okay.
Back when I was little, I liked
this boy and he's never been
far from my mind since then.
He inspires most of my songs.
Your feelings are still that
strong for him? Even now?
It's one-sided, but yes.
I guess I write songs
as a way to express it.
I've never actually
told him how I feel.
That makes total sense.
It's no wonder there's so
much yearning and emotion
in your lyrics.
Anyway, that's how I do it.
I don't know if that helps you.
[FUUKA sighs]
Do you have anyone in your
life who you like that way?
Huh? Who, me? Nope, not-a-one.
A relationship has never
really been on my radar.
Oh, I see.
Thank goodness for that.
[FUUKA]
Huh?
Uh, it was dumb! Never mind!
[FUUKA]
Know what, Koyuki?
Listen, I'm rooting
for your love, okay?
Huh?
I want you to be happy and
all your dreams to come true!
And maybe if I
really support you,
somewhere along the way,
I'll learn what it's
like to be in love!
[FUUKA] So, what's a practical
way that I can help you out?
[FUUKA gasps] I know! We can go
to that shrine right over there.
My parents went there
once to make a wish!
Uh! Hey, your towel!
[FUUKA]
Huh?
[KOYUKI gasps]
[FUUKA, KOYUKI giggle nervously]
Come by again some time!
Sure. Thanks for today, Fuuka.
[FUUKA]
See ya soon!
[KOYUKI chuckles]
[KOYUKI]
Mm.
It was you I always loved
Always you who held my heart
I see your tears
As snow melts into fireworks
And I give you all of me
I don't regret one day with you
The greatest love I ever knew
You and I can laugh at anything
Unafraid of what
the future brings
Now our time has passed but
I don't want to say goodbye
I want to believe we
were meant to be
But we lost somehow
I realize that now
It was you I always loved
Always you who held my heart
I feel my tears
As snow melts into fireworks
'Cause I gave you all of me
Hey, check it out, man.
I got this amazing shot today!
[GUY B]
Huh? Is that for real?
[GUY A]
Think I should post it?
[FUUKA]
Next time, "Blown Up!"