Let's move!
Hange?
Get, get me a horse.
Section Commander! Where're you going?
Back to the village where we
caught the Titan that couldn't walk.
Not Ragako!
I need to see.
Have you lost touch with reality?
You're in no condition to ride horseback right now!
There's something important there.
I feel it in my bones.
All right, fine.
I'll go myself.
You stay here and quit trying to move!
Be on the lookout! All riders assume formation!
Eren.
You're awake.
Welcome back.
What the hell? My arms!
Eren.
I'm, uh, not in any better shape here.
Seems we're both having a shit day.
Ymir. What did they... What did they do to me?
Sorry. That was... That was my fault.
You can pin your injuries on me.
Guess I was in kind of a hurry back there.
Bit your nape without thinking about your arms.
Is that right? So. I lost.
Eren! Don't do it!
Easy there, hothead.
Take a look at where we are.
This is the giant forest within Wall Maria.
Wall Rose is leagues away.
Which means... we're deep in
the heart of Titan country. See?
I think our buddy down there is an abnormal.
It may look like he's just kickin' back,
but those eyes haven't left us once.
Lot of smaller ones down there, too.
That's plenty bad enough. Another big one over there.
Fixated but keeping his distance.
Strikes me as the shy type.
And then there are these chumps.
Dirty bastards.
They had the foresight to suit up in full gear.
'Course Reiner took yours.
Point is, changing into a Titan isn't
gonna accomplish very much right now.
One, they can do the same thing if they want.
Two, they can zip into the trees if not.
Three, we're basically surrounded on all sides.
Power or no power, getting out of this would
be tricky as hell, even at the best of times.
Y'read me?
There's nothing to gain by being a dumbass.
She's right.
Y'can't turn into Titans right now anyway.
Don't count on that ability coming to the rescue.
The body can only take so much.
It's a little preoccupied with healing at the moment.
Nice try. You expect me to sit
here and take the word of liar?
Yeah, well. We're sort of at a disadvantage here.
It's not like we know the ins and outs of how this works.
Unlike you guys, I'm basically
clueless about the whole thing.
Hey, Reiner.
You said you'd start talking once Eren was up.
Don't'cha think it's about time somebody
explains what you plan on doing with us?
We're taking you to our hometown.
Of course, I realize neither
of you is just gonna do as I ask.
Like Ymir was saying, though,
this place is crawling with Titans. They're everywhere.
We could beat the living shit out
of each other if that's what you want.
But I wouldn't recommend it.
Our friends down below are hungry
and not prone to discriminate.
Whether you try to cut and run or stick around,
believe me when I say our options are limited.
We wait for nightfall.
So, why didn't you just stay in
Titan form and run all the way home?
What's the point of stopping here in the first place?
You get winded and have to take a break?
Why don't you use your imagination?
Let me think. Suppose I wait for an opening.
If I assume Titan form, running away
wouldn't really be that much of a challenge.
Question is, can I assume Titan form in this condition?
Reiner doesn't seem to think so,
and it's not like he and Bertholdt would
risk stopping here without a good reason.
What if I couldn't transform to full strength?
Does that mean the other Titans would be able to eat me?
So we're just gonna sit on our
asses till the sun goes down?
It's a possibility.
No. Why give us the chance to recover?
If they wait for nightfall we'd only be harder to rein in.
They'll make their move while we're still helpless.
At this rate I can't do anything. We're screwed.
What happened to everyone else?
Where are the Scouts?
Don't tell me they're coming here to save us.
Oh god. If they show up, none of 'em will...
Wait a second.
Those Titans at the castle had
no problem moving around at night.
What's stopping these guys?
The Titans here can't move after dark.
But then you know all about that, don't you, Ymir?
How is it she's able to transform into a Titan?
Doesn't seem to catch her off-guard like it did me.
What's her angle?
Who's side is she on in all this?
If I thought she was hard to read before...
I've made up my mind. I need information.
Anything I can get.
Keep my eyes and ears open.
When the moment comes, make a break for it.
Before I can do that, though...
I have to keep my emotions in check.
Give myself a chance to recuperate.
Titan spotted at three o'clock! Use the flare!
We've got a smoke shell fired from the right wing!
We stay the course! Tell the right wing to
merge with the center and maintain direction!
The shortest path is our only option.
Straight ahead. We have until sundown!
Mikasa. Hey, Mikasa. Hello?
Stop pushing so hard.
You're drifting up into the vanguard.
You wanna break the whole formation?
Look, I know how you feel. But what'd I tell ya?
Eren's not gonna let those assholes
get the best of him without a fight.
Agreed?
Mm.
Kid just doesn't have it in him to give up.
All we gotta do is have a little faith.
He'll hold his own till the rest of us get there.
Always has, always will.
Hey, Reiner. Got any water?
Help a girl out. I'm dying over here.
Sorry, there's not a helluva a lot I can do.
Even if it is a matter of life and death.
That's comforting. Well, at least
now we know where we stand. Sort of.
Speaking of which. We've been working
our asses off. No food, no sleep, no nothing.
Ever since those Titans showed up.
That was yesterday, right?
Man, we're lucky the wall hasn't been destroyed.
Still, you'd think that means they'd give us a break.
And don't even get me started on promotion.
What the hell?
What? Aww, come on. I don't think
that's too much to ask, do you?
God knows we've done our share of heavy lifting
all things considered.
I mean, I get it, we're soldiers. Duty first.
It's just nice to be acknowledged.
You bang your head or something?
What're you even talking about. Seriously?
Ugh. Don't give me that.
I'm not sayin' we storm in and
demand the rank of captain or anything.
No. That's not what I mean.
Oh, yeah. Where'd you find that cannon, by the way?
I owe you one for saving my bacon.
Really nice of Christa to patch me up afterwards.
I'm starting to think me and her might become a thing.
Hey.
Right? It's not just me?
She always treats me like we're...
Hey!
What's wrong with you? You've got to be kidding me.
Huh? What're you so pissed about all of a sudden?
Take it easy, man. Was it something I said, or?
If you wanna die, then just keep talking!
Hold up, Eren.
I think somebody's gone off the deep end.
Is that what this is, Bertholdt?
If you know something we don't,
now would be a good time to put it on the table.
Huh?
Reiner. Snap out of it.
You're not a soldier, okay?
You and I are... We're warriors.
Reiner! What are you doing?
Hey. Why...?
Why is Marco... being devoured?
Right. I see. That's how things are.
What the hell's he doing?
I have a pretty good idea. At least I think so.
Didn't add up at first.
Why would the man who broke the
wall risk his neck to save Conny?
It's like the poor bastard's
personality is compartmentalized.
Everything he does is a contradiction in terms.
He can't help it.
On one hand, he's a warrior bent
on pushing mankind past the brink.
On the other he's pretending to be a soldier.
I'm thinking maybe he got a little lost in the role.
See. He can't resolve those facets of himself.
Can't bear the weight of what he's done.
The only way for him to manage his
conscience is to fall for his own act.
He thinks he is a soldier.
This is what you call a split personality.
He's gone insane.
His heart and mind are at war with each
other, and judging by Bertholdt's expression,
this isn't the first stalemate.
Blows me away!
Wow, someone as brutally honest
as you losing their grip...
Shut up!
Not another word.
I'm sorry. Must've really hit a nerve.
Is this some kind of joke?
Where do you get off pretending to be the victim?
You're wallowing in self-pity?
How dare you. What was going through
your head the day I told you my story, huh?
Remember that, Bertholdt?
I'm talking to you, lackey!
I told you everything.
You sat there and looked me straight in the eye.
Watched me relive seeing my mother eaten alive.
Stop it! No!
Don't you remember?
Well, it just so happens the chunk of
wall you kicked out fell on our house.
It's what kept her from being able to run away.
Ring any bells? Take you back?
Let me ask you again.
What was going through your
head when I told you that story?
Want me to be honest?
In the moment I felt... sorry for you.
Huh. Sorry for me?
So, then. You're not...
You're not warriors or soldiers. You're just murderers.
Psychotic mass-murderers who snuffed out the lives
of countless people that never did you any wrong.
Don't you think I'm aware of that fact?
I don't need you shoving it down my goddamn throat!
Then stop acting like you've got
any right to feel sorry for yourself!
We're living in a hell you two created!
Are you proud of yourselves?
You're not one of us! You've never been!
You're not even human anymore!
You want an apology?
Is that what you hope to get out of calling us murderers?
Want us to feel bad? Want us to take the blame?
Who are you talking to?
The people you thought you knew don't exist!
They're dead! But hey, if screaming does it for ya,
go ahead and scream your goddamn head off!
You're right.
Who am I? What do I know?
Still. I've got to do something. Anything.
I swear to you, one way or
another, the two of you will pay.
And it's gonna hurt.
You can't be for real.
Huh?
Eren, grow up. Keep spouting off childish
bullshit like that and I've got no hope for you.
Tell me something.
What's with the giant monkey?
Monkey? What're you talking about?
Huh. I thought for sure you'd know.
That's surprising.
From the way you guys were ogling it all slack-jawed
I figured we were seeing some kind of living legend.
Weird.
A monkey? Don't be cute.
Shut up and listen. Monkey, Beast Titan. Whatever
you wanna call him, he's behind this latest fiasco.
It's why Titans are cropping up out of nowhere.
I get the feeling he's gauging our strength.
Reiner and Betholdt are trying to get wherever he is.
It's how they're getting back home.
Feel free to correct me if I'm way off base.
Wait. How did you know? Who are you?
What else haven't you told me?
Be patient. I'm caught up in circumstances of my own.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Eren. If you think killing these morons will
put an end to all of this, you are sorely mistaken.
Huh? But then who's the enemy?
The enemy?
Look, if I told you, things would get too...
Ymir! There's no future for this world and you know it.
You have a solid grasp of things.
What d'you think comes next?
Joining our side wouldn't be out of
the question if you were so inclined.
And put my faith in you guys? That's rich.
Neither of you trusts me as far as you can throw me.
Come on. That isn't true.
We know what you really want.
All you care about is protecting Christa.
If we can all agree on that, I don't see the conflict.
I'm being absolutely serious.
Is it so hard to believe we want what's best for her, too?
Hate to break it to ya, but you're not the only one.
Then again, you could always put your trust in Eren,
see where that leads you.
What?
You're probably leaning toward escape.
Better to take a chance with
him than throw in with us, right?
Because if we end up taking you,
there's not much hope of being rescued.
I'll be straight with you. That much is true.
Even if you came willingly, we're not
in a position to guarantee your safety.
But if it's Christa we're talking about,
we might be able to do something.
It's your call. What's it gonna be?
Is it Christa's future? Or your own petty existence?
Is there really no future for this world?
Why? And the monkey.
How does he figure into this?
Come clean! Who's the real enemy?
Tell me what you know!
Who is it?!
Couldn't say.
All right, then. Sorry, Eren.
The Scouts are here? Already?
Son of a bitch!
No. Damn you, Ymir!
Only one hour left until sunset.
Night approaches swiftly.
The Scouts close in, intent on
rescuing Eren from Reiner and Bertholdt.
The traitorous pair attempts a bold escape
using their ODM gear.
Conflicted, reflecting on her dark and bloodied past,
Ymir offers an alternative.
Next episode: "Children."