The report was right.
The whole village has been devastated.
But there's not a drop of blood, let alone any bodies.
It's eerie. Still, maybe they got out?
It's not unheard of.
In theory, I suppose.
But then the question becomes why
Titans would smash up empty houses?
Bit difficult to believe.
What's more, how far were these people
hoping to get by leaving their horses here?
That's a good point.
So what do you think happened?
Moblit, I found it! Look!
There you are.
You, uh... you should see this.
A portrait of Conny Springer's parents, I presume?
Seems very likely, sir.
It's alive!
No! Stand down!
What the hell is going on?
It's your call. What's it gonna be?
Is it Christa's future? Or your own petty existence?
Hey! Talk! Who's the real enemy here?
Tell me!
Couldn't say.
All right, then. Sorry, Eren.
You're kidding.
The Scouts are here? Already?
Son of a bitch!
Talk to me, Reiner. What are you right now?
A warrior. Calm down.
Do you really think it's wise for us to trust Ymir?
Even though she's the one who devoured Marcel?
Sure. Don't you see?
We have a handle on her motives.
When she turned human again,
odds are she just wandered around
aimlessly only giving a damn about herself.
But then Christa came into the picture.
That's the kind of girl that can change your whole world.
We need her, and not just because she's cute.
The people she comes from are an
important family within the church.
Plus, suppose Eren's not the coordinate?
Our job wouldn't be over.
If it comes to that, having Christa
around will make the search a lot easier.
They're close.
What are they talking about?
They still plan on clearing out before sundown or not?
Please, let's just be done.
The next time we come, we'll take all three.
Annie, Christa, and that. It'll be clean and simple.
Then we won't have to come here anymore.
Right. And we'll have completed our damn mission.
Just do me a favor, huh?
Once we're home, try telling Annie how you really feel.
What's that supposed to mean?
Ugh. Come on.
I've seen the way you stare at her.
I don't stare!
Bertholdt, please, life's short enough as it is.
Just go for it, 'kay? Besides, you're both
killers so she understands where your head is.
What're you two doing now?
I thought we were waiting till dark.
There's been a slight change of plans.
I'm gonna ask you nicely not to try to put up a fight.
Easy. There's no need for us to get all violent.
It's not like I can resist like this.
I mean, take a look at me. Just, calm down, okay?
Die! Die! Die! Die! Die, you evil...!
Bastard! I'll... I'll kill you!
I'll rip you apart!
Explain to me why we're leaving early.
Ymir. When you changed back into a human,
d'you have any memory of the person you ate?
Huh. No, not really.
We're talking about something
that happened five years ago.
But the way you're asking, I'm
guessing that it was someone you knew?
I see. Then I'm, uh, sorry for not remembering.
Hey, it's not your fault that you don't.
It was the same for Reiner and me.
Yeah?
Eren doesn't remember either.
Is that how it works?
You hold that against me?
I don't think so. I mean. I don't know.
Suppose I have to believe you didn't want to eat anyone.
How, uh, how long were you wandering outside the walls?
Oh, about sixty years. Hell on earth.
Every day was like waking up into a nightmare.
Red smoke signal, sir.
The hell?
Commander Erwin, we're surrounded!
There is a way around. Should we head towards it?
No. We don't have time for a detour.
We'll forge ahead! Soldiers! Prepare to fight!
For now, we find a place without Titans!
As far away as possible!
I haven't recovered enough to outrun these guys.
They surround us, there's jack
shit my Titan form can do right now.
Then why the hell didn't we
just wait for the sun to go down?
Smoke signals? Did the Scouts come to save us?
Damn it. That Formation wouldn't work unless
they hoisted a bunch of horses over the wall.
Who gave that order?
I honestly thought we had more time than this.
It's gotta be Commander Erwin.
Hard as nails, that one.
Damn. They're already that close?
It's Eren's fault for losing his cool.
Wait. Is she...?
Christa's here.
Reiner! We have to go back! Now!
Christa's with them!
...What? ...This is our best chance!
You're full of it! No way you can see that far!
Look, I just know! Think about
it, okay? She's a big softie, right?
Stupid girl's come to rescue me! She had to!
Yeah, well so what?
I'm sorry! It'll have to wait!
What?
We can't grab her the way things are now!
There's no way to bust up that formation!
Another time!
How long you want me to wait?
Maybe I should just hold off on that until
I've been gobbled up by one of your warrior pals?
Oh no! I don't think so!
Don't be that way!
Nobody's trying to trick you, I swear it!
Prove it, then!
There's no time like the present, asshole!
Damn you! Get down there and bring her with us!
I need to see her!
You don't understand.
The way things are going, I never will.
We can't.
Let it go, Ymir.
Who knows whether we'll even manage to
survive this. Sorry. It's just too risky.
Listen to me. You have my word.
I want her out of this as much as you do.
Bear with me. You have to trust us!
This is what's best for Christa!
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand. Real question is, do you?
Of course!
All right, then.
Thank you for that.
It's happening again. I've come so far.
Done so much. And still wound
up falling for my own bullshit.
Well. They look promising.
What about this one?
Mm.
Hello there.
How would you feel about coming to live with us?
Think of it as the start of a brand-new life.
Of course, a brand-new life needs a brand-new name.
Don't you agree?
Huh?
That day... That was the first time I lied to myself.
Told myself I had no say in the matter.
That I never had a choice. But...
It is this Lady Ymir that inherits
the blood of His Majesty the king.
So long as she graces us with her
presence, immortality shall be ours.
To be fair, it wasn't all that bad.
My food wasn't cold. I no longer slept in the dirt.
Lady Ymir.
Best of all, I knew what it meant to feel needed.
For the first time in my life, I
actually meant something to someone else.
That, by far, was more precious than anything.
Then, one day...
It's her fault! The girl's to blame!
She said the blood of the king flowed in her veins!
We're only guilty of believing her!
I was cruelly reminded that
everything I clung to was an act.
Is that so?
I-I only...
It's true.
I am Ymir!
The king's blood runs through me!
Lie once, the rest follow easy.
If it saved their necks, so be it.
Trouble was, things didn't quite work out that way.
Help me!
Stop this! I'm begging you! It's not right!
That's when I realized I'd had it coming all along.
I'd deceived those gullible bastards,
but that wasn't what I was being punished for really.
It was for deceiving myself
into thinking someone needed me.
What else did I expect?
That's what comes of looking at the world through a veil.
Titan! Run!
No!
When I opened my eyes,
the first thing I saw was freedom.
The first thing I thought
was if there's such thing as fate,
she's a fickle little whore.
Right then and there
I made a vow.
No more deceiving myself.
No more falling for my own line.
From then on, I'd be real.
So, how did that play out?
Ah, the child was given the name "Christa Lenz."
Then, she was packed off to the Cadet Corps.
That is a pity.
Poor wretch. Would've been better were she never born.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
All right, sure. Makes no difference to me.
And then...
What do we have here?
This your idea of trying to be nice?
Well, uh.
And then I met you.
Immediately, I could tell.
You and I were the same.
You nourished yourself on lies.
Together, we give our hearts!
Sir!
Here was someone desperately trying to
convince herself of something she knew wasn't true.
I get it. Believe me.
And don't worry.
I'm not asking you to understand.
No. What I want is very simple.
Just let me be honest with myself one last time.
That's all.
Let's face it, guys. I'm the one best suited for this.
What are you doing?
Hey, shut the hell up and use your head for a second.
In a forest like this I'm the one who can shine. Right?
Ymir! Knock it off! We'll fall!
Do you think that I give a damn?
I have the advantage.
Any other time you two would outclass me.
But my Titan form's more agile.
I could leap through the trees, grab Eren, and
rendezvous with the Scouts before you knew what hit you.
Wouldn't be that hard.
Either you agree to take Christa with us today, right now,
or so help me I will throw your whole plan out of whack!
Uh! Are you completely insane? That doesn't help her!
I thought that you genuinely cared!
I do. In my way.
If it robs her of a future, then life's a bitch,
but by god I will live to see her again!
I've made my peace with what that says about me.
You guys have no idea what it's like.
She knows what a shitty person I am,
but she still smiles at me. I can't...
Damn it.
Don't be pissed. I have a fairly decent plan.
Besides, if I stay and fight,
it'll be easier for you three to get away.
Then again, if you don't like it,
we can always tear each other apart like animals!
That light.
You saw it, too, huh?
It's coming from the forest!
I think someone's transforming into a Titan!
We're out of time. Soldiers, disperse!
The enemy has assumed Titan form!
Find Eren and get him out of there!
Another MP.
Battle is not our objective!
Locate, recover, and retreat!
Round up the horses!
Right away, sir!
First thing we do is pinpoint
the enemy and tell the others!
They're fleeing through the woods, so stay sharp! Break!
Eren.
Where are you?
That's the scream of a Titan!
It came from just up ahead!
I can see you!
No, wait a second!
It's actually Ymir! This is her Titan
form. She's one of the people they took!
What the hell happened?
Where is everybody else?
Is Eren okay?
What about Bertholdt and Reiner?
So this is Ymir.
Did she assume Titan form to take on Reiner and escape?
Ymir! What's the deal? Did you
manage to get away from them?
What direction did they go?
Give us something to go on! Anything!
Say something already!
C'mon, ugly! We're kinda in a rush!
Is she keeping an eye out for Reiner?
Something isn't right.
Why... Why is she looking at us one by one?
Ymir!
There you are!
Thank goodness you're all right!
What?
Did she just...? Ymir, what are you doing?
Don't just stand there! Move your asses!
She's fast! We're losing her!
Why would she do that?
What's wrong with you people?
Am I seriously the only one who saw this coming?
Well, it's clear where her loyalties are now!
She and Reiner are on the same side!
We were lured into a trap!
Heads up. She's back.
Good.
Oh, no!
No! They're getting away with Eren!
Move it! Get on your damn horses!
This ain't over, y'hear me?
I'll get him back if it costs me my life!
Pursuit and battle become one.
Hunter versus hunted.
Emotions run high between friends turned enemies.
Betrayal calls for blood.
Loyal soldiers perish in droves.
In a game of chance for the fate of mankind,
Commander Erwin bets on a do-or-die strategy.
Next episode: "Charge."