The odds of there being any Titans
hiding in the 104th Cadet Corps are low.
We've got multiple Titans incoming from the south!
Wall Rose has been compromised!
Suspected by some of unknowingly
harboring the enemy among their ranks,
the 104th Cadet Corps was kept isolated.
With the sudden emergence of a Titan swarm,
couriers were dispatched to alert surrounding districts.
As you have guessed,
today marks the darkest hour in humanity's history!
Don't lose heart.
If ever we needed to give our
all, that time is now! Look sharp!
However...
No! They're coming at us full tilt!
Their origins and how they got here remain a mystery.
Mankind is still in the dark.
Ah, an exceptionally clever idea, I must say.
Commander Pyxis!
Titans have been spotted, sir!
We think Wall Rose has been breached!
Great. Somebody explain to me what this means.
I don't know. But they're Titans, right?
Would they break a wall with Titans in it?
Wouldn't be the first time.
It's how they got into Shiganshina.
That was a gate.
Armin. What exactly are you getting at?
Fall in!
The walls are different.
There are no signs of stress, no
cracks, no crevices between the rocks.
We can't even really tell how they were constructed.
Suppose they're built with the
same stuff Annie's trapped herself in?
Must be versatile material,
and we know it's virtually indestructible.
So the walls are made of Titans?
Section Commander! Why are you taking so long?
Please! They're leaving in
five minutes with or without us!
You've got to wrap it up!
Hold your horses, I just need another moment.
Hange. Get moving.
Uh, right! Sorry! And our guest?
He's been ready to go for a while.
Eren, you'll get cold. Wear it tight.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Took longer to prepare than I thought.
He's, uh. He's a priest from the Order of the Walls.
I know! Ol' Nick and me are thick as thieves!
It's fine. Makes about as much sense for him
to be here as the rest of us, don't'cha think?
We're random.
No, on the contrary.
Erwin's thrown us together for a reason.
Open the gate!
The status of Wall Rose in unclear,
but everything up to Ehrmich is safe.
That's the route we'll be taking.
Let's move out!
Yes, sir!
You heard 'im.
Sir!
This whole time, Titans have been
protecting us from other Titans.
Wait, wait! Back up!
You're joking, right?
This guy knew? He knew and he kept quiet?
Uh-huh. Afraid so.
Just about sums up where we are with him.
Cat's out of the bag now, of course.
He's not willing to talk yet,
but we'll see how he feels after a harsh dose of reality.
Faith keeps him quiet.
Firsthand experience, though?
To hell with that!
No! We're doing this backwards!
If this son of bitch knows
something he needs to come out with it!
Humanity's on the brink of extinction
and all you care about is keeping your oath?
Hey. Take it easy.
You're still not fully recovered.
There's more than one way to get at the truth.
Granted I may not be in top form at the moment,
but it doesn't take much strength to squeeze a trigger.
That said. I'm genuinely hoping I won't
have to blow a hole in you to settle this.
How 'bout you?
Threatening him doesn't work, Levi.
Trust me on that.
Agree with him or not, there's no denying
our priest here is a man of principle.
Which of course leads me to wonder:
if he's so unwilling to talk,
what in heaven's name do you imagine
he's putting above the fate of humanity?
Up ahead, you see? That's the village!
Where you're from?
No, but it's close. My people live the forest.
It's okay. Go on.
All right. Find your home and raise the alarm.
Yes, sir!
Good lord! Again with this?
Sasha! You can't always be stuffin' your face!
Give it here!
Spit it out!
We're smokin' that for the winter!
Oh, for cryin' out loud!
You little... Show some restraint!
Fine.
Eat your fill.
Hm! Idiot kid.
Sasha. Look around ya.
Ever wonder how things got to be the way they are?
Why the forest is disappearing?
Why game's so hard to come by these days?
Or doesn't it concern you?
Sure it does.
People are comin' in here and helping
themselves to what used to be ours.
It's why I'm hungry all the time.
Yeah, that's true.
On the face of it.
But where else you expect folks
to go when they lose their homes?
They've got a right to live, don't they?
It's their fault for losin' their homes.
Not like that gives 'em the right to steal.
They lost their homes 'cause of Titans.
Monsters punched a hole clean through Wall Maria.
Where else were people gonna go?
Wasn't their choice. They had to survive somehow,
so they cleared the forest and used it for farmland.
Maybe it's time for us to let go.
Surrender the old ways.
We're not gonna starve.
Government's willing to pay us, y'know.
We'll make money raising horses.
What? If we turn our back on
hunting, we turn our back on who we are!
Why should I care about what happens to
the people who've always looked down as us
like we were a bunch of savages?
I'll tell you why.
We're in this together.
The world belongs to each and every one of us.
We're human. Humans are social animals.
It's all fine and good to move to the beat
of your own drum, but when land is scarce,
you've got to fall in step with the herd.
Think about the greater good.
No! I won't do it!
We've lived here all our lives
the way our ancestors taught us to.
I'm not gonna change!
Screw the "greater good"! What about us?
Right, then.
If that's how you really feel.
Eke out a living in these woods.
Live by the old ways, like the others.
But I'll tell you somethin',
you'd best be willing to die by the old ways, too.
'Cause make no mistake, Sasha,
trouble is comin' sooner or later.
And when it does,
there'll be no beggin' for help from
the people you've turned your back on.
If it means the difference between being
a part of something larger than myself
and scraping by on my own, I say screw tradition.
It's time to move on.
What about you?
Are you brave enough to take that step with me?
Trade the wilderness of your
ancestors for a share in civilization?
Or is our fellow man just not worth the hassle?
How long has it been? Three years?
Surely he'd have had the sense
to pick up and leave by now.
Impossible! All the way out here?
Can they really have gotten this far?
That's does it. This place isn't safe anymore.
Whoa. When did that get built?
Shit! If I don't cut it off,
it'll just keep healing!
Oh no.
I'm so sorry. Forgive me.
You got a name, sweetie?
I know you're scared, but it'll be okay.
What will?
Uh. Well, um, actually, I, uh...
Uh, easy now, easy. Right, so. The
thing is, I'm going to take you...
You do this now? Really?
Ugh! Wait for us!
Okay. No need to worry, understand?
He'll be right back, I promise.
How come you're talking so nice to me?
Huh?
We need to run!
It's gonna be okay!
No it won't. Everyone's already gone.
The whole village.
Even though Mama's legs were bad.
They knew, and none of them came to help her.
All I could do was watch.
Don't look back! Just keep running!
It's gonna be okay.
You're startin' to piss me off.
Huh?
Why you gotta be so friggin' polite all the time?
What, you above talking like one of us plebes?
Well, actually. No, not at all.
Oh yeah? So why don't'cha, then?
Scared we'll hear where you're
from if you let your guard down?
That's it, isn't it?
Oh, wow. Kinda blows my mind.
Why do you even care?
I mean, it's like a wild boar getting all bent outta
shape 'cause someone's bad-mouthing him behind his back.
Be honest: the military's your
last hope of being respectable.
Your folks're probably first cousins...
Ymir, stop it! You're being mean!
Whatever! Hey, you gonna pretend to be
someone you're not for the rest of your damn life,
or you gonna be Sasha?
Take it from me, honey: acting like you
think people want you to act is a crock of shit.
Don't censor yourself!
Um. Thank you very much?
I appreciate the advice.
Really?
Sorry, I-I'm not really sure what to say.
Leave her alone! It's her life! If she wants
to talk politely to people, why do you care?
Sasha is who she chooses to be.
It's called reinventing yourself.
Whatever she says, it's still her.
Heh. Well, aren't we philosophical.
I say however she tries to sound on the outside,
the inside Sasha'll always be a pain in the ass.
Knock it off! Would it kill you to
show some compassion every now and again?
E-Excuse me? I'm just bein' real!
Compassion.
Hey! What are you laughin' at?
Uh. Nothing! Sorry!
Really? Why is that coming back now?
Of all the stupid things for me to dwell on.
Still, it's the only thing I can think about.
All right, listen.
You're gonna be fine. Just
keep following the path we're on.
Run as far away as you can.
There'll be someone willing to help. I promise.
It may take you a little while to find them.
But keep on! You'll bump into them eventually!
Now go. Get out of here!
Don't give up hope!
If I can take out the eyes,
it should buy us enough time.
Eeh!
Damn it. Only two left!
Relax. It's nothing.
Just a big... slow-moving...
...target!
Bull's eye!
Last arrow. If I miss, that'll be it.
End of story. Period. I'll be...
She'll be...
I slipped out because of the blood.
Now to find the girl!
Is that Sasha?
We've been doing what we can.
Giving horses to folks who need 'em.
That little girl told us there was
someone back behind her on the road.
Said they helped. Saved her, 'n fact.
Apparently fought off a Titan single-handed.
Mm.
Nicely done. I'm proud of ya.
Thanks, Dad.
It's good to be home.
Conny, slow down! Get ahold of yourself!
There could be Titans around every corner!
Wait for us!
This isn't real.
Hello? Can anybody hear me?
Somebody! Please! It's Conny!
I came home!
Find my house!
Dad. Mom. Sunny and Martin!
Please just be okay.
What are you doing? Get back!
But it-it's my house.
I...
Conny.
Cadets, fall back!
I'll scout out the area!
What the hell? This is new.
Can it move?
Not with those legs.
But... then...
I don't understand.
How did it even get here?
"My family got out of harm's way."
So Conny tells himself to shake
off the terror of what he's seen.
Again, he puts home behind him.
Battle erupts across the land.
The Titans remain a mystery.
As the situation goes from bad to worse,
Eren and the others head for Ehrmich District
hoping to find some shred of the truth.
Next episode: "Southwestward."