Me? Only thing I want is to go back home.
That's all I care about now.
I joined the ranks hoping for
assignment to the Military Police.
Tucked away in the Interior.
What about you? Why did you sign up?
Why'd I join?
I decided I have to kill them.
I won't stop till every single Titan is dead and rotting.
Dead. Every last one.
You saw what those monsters are capable of.
And you still want to take them on?
I know you've got what it takes.
I can see it in you. Am I wrong here?
Damn you! You traitors!
Eren!
What's wrong with me?
Why didn't I slice their goddamn heads off?
That was the perfect chance.
Why did I hesitate? Why?
That was it.
There won't be another opportunity.
Move! Everyone!
It's got Ymir!
Oh, hell! She's not the only one!
Shit!
No. This isn't happening!
How can Bertholdt...?
Soldiers! Prepare to attack!
The Colossal Titan doesn't walk away from this!
It's a threat to all mankind!
Swarm and terminate!
Freak's as slow as they say.
Size is all he has going for him.
Compared to Titans we're usually up
against, this one's a piece of cake!
Simple!
He's wide open! Slice the nape!
What the hell?
It's too hot!
Argh! All of you fall back!
My hand!
Water! We need water!
He's vanishing!
I don't know. Something's different here.
The last time he disappeared,
it was more or less instantaneous.
He's maintaining his form to emit heat.
I think he's protecting himself.
As long as he generates steam our rigs are useless!
What-What do we do?
Now? Nothing. Except wait.
Squads three and four take position behind the target.
Rashad has command.
Got it!
Squad two, stay put. Lauda has command.
Understood!
How long he can act like a
blast furnace remains to be seen.
But he'll come out of there eventually.
When he does, we'll rush the big bastard.
Listen up.
I want you to forget about taking them alive.
Destroy them. No second thoughts.
You're with me.
Right, squad one, look alive!
We've got a date with the Armored Titan!
Christa! Conny! Move further back!
For now, just take care of those two.
Ymir, she...
She's not dead. It just isn't possible.
I know it. Please save her!
Don't worry.
Hang on! What about Reiner and Bertholdt?
They're screwed! Neither one of them has their ODM gear!
I'm begging you, wherever they are, bring them back!
Reiner. You lying piece of shit.
Going off on what it means to be a soldier.
Always talking about honor.
Played us all for fools, huh?
Combat training must've been a joke to you.
How much were you holding back?
And here I took you to be real stand-up guy.
Calm under pressure. Intensely focused.
The sort of man who puts his comrades before himself.
Damn you. I'd have given anything in
the world to be half as strong as you.
You were my hero.
That did nothing!
He barely flinched when Eren hit him.
And my blades don't even make a dent.
He's not like Annie. His armor's head to toe!
Eren!
Hey, Reiner. Asshole.
I don't know what kind of face you're making right now...
...but I hope you miserable pieces
of shit are pleased with yourselves.
I bet I could scour through the history of
mankind and not find anyone a fraction as evil.
You should be erased.
Trash like you can't be allowed to exist.
What was going through your head?
You disgust me!
Just thinking about your face makes my insides churn!
You make me want to puke!
You're a pest! A revolting, oversized pest!
And pests have to be exterminated!
Hey, take it easy! That hurt!
We're just sparring.
You're supposed to hold back a little.
If you want to hold back, that's your business.
I defend myself assuming you're coming at me with
everything you've got. Otherwise, what's the point?
Let's remember I'm the girl. I'm weaker.
I have to protect my frail
little body from the big bad man.
What? Ha-ha, Annie.
Very funny. You're a riot.
Frail little nothin'. I'm the one who
just got shoved in the dirt, you know.
Good point.
That last move wasn't about who's stronger, okay?
I was using a special defense technique.
Comes in handy when your opponent has a few pounds on you.
Trust me. You could benefit from learning it.
Sure, uh...
What do you say we take a break for now, though?
Right. That's enough, Annie. You can let go.
Come on. I've barely shown you how this
works and already you're surrendering?
There's a two-fold benefit here.
Or don't you want to learn how to talk to women?
Fine! Whatever! Just please stop strangling me!
Ah. So you are interested in what I can show you.
Not really sure I wanna know how you got here.
Hey, Annie.
Your technique seems pretty solid.
Teach me.
I'm flattered, but...
...it's a method for normal people.
So, why would you ever need it?
Still, I'm curious to know if it works on animals.
Let's find out.
This is happening? Oh crap.
Hold up! Are these two actually about to fight?
This is gonna be epic!
...Who...? Who do we bet on? ...What d'you mean? Annie.
What? Idiot!
Dinner says Mikasa wipes the floor with 'er!
Which one of 'em you think's gonna win?
Well, I...
How should I know?
Wait. How did that play out?
And why's it coming to me now?
Is this...? Is this my life flashing before my eyes?
So what? Who gives a shit?
It's not like it matters. Not when I feel like this.
No! Back down!
You can't win in a fistfight!
Make a break for the wall!
Eren, please! Don't be rash!
Eren!
Oh, no!
He's blinded by rage!
What the hell is he doing?
Wait, that... Holy crap!
That's Annie's technique!
You know what?
There's no telling what you murdering
hypocrites were trying to accomplish.
But now that I think about it, your
master plan seems to have a few holes in it.
Wanna eradicate humanity?
Maybe next time don't teach me how to kick your ass!
It's working! I've got him locked!
There's still a chance!
I don't think so!
Eren!
You're not going anywhere!
He did it!
Eren! Can you hear me? Run away!
You've got to get closer to the wall!
They're trying to abduct you!
We can't let them do that!
Trust me. Escape is our best option!
You say that, but Armin, come on.
They're not just gonna let us leave.
Both of you fall back! Now!
Nice one, Eren! Good call!
Looks like he's in control again.
Yeah, but Reiner's not just gonna let him go.
You're right; escape's impossible.
What the hell?
The Colossal Titan. I knew it!
Why'd he show up here of all places?!
What's going on with Eren? Where is he?
Uh. He and the others are over that way!
What? So I take it that's his Titan form, huh?
Listen up, Eren!
If we're going to get you out of here,
you've got to buy us some time.
Stop Reiner dead in his tracks!
Think you can manage to break off his
leg with another one of those joint holds?
Our blades don't do much good against him.
He can't be outmuscled, but he can
be outsmarted if you play it right.
Mhmm.
Oooooo!
Mikasa! Take my blades.
I want you to use them.
I'm counting on you!
This is the one time where
running away guarantees victory.
You guys are screwed for letting us see your true colors.
You've backed yourselves into a corner.
...What the...?
...He's fast!
Shit! The leg! Go for the leg!
Don't let Reiner pin you! Get up!
Throw him!
Dammit! There's too much power behind his attack!
Since when is he so light on his feet?
We're completely and utterly useless!
No. It's not feasible that his body
is as hard as stone from head to toe.
He couldn't move as fast if that were the case.
Warriors used to sheathe themselves in armor.
Way back in the olden days.
They had to leave certain sections
uncovered for freedom of movement, though;
like the armpits and groin or the spot behind the knee.
I can't dodge this.
Well, if I'm gonna get slammed...
Bring it!
There we go!
You're mine, you son of a bitch!
Yeah! That's how it's done!
Got him! Now it all boils down to strength!
Damn it. I'm slipping!
Mikasa.
Nice cut!
Try fighting back minus a leg!
You've got this!
Go for it, Eren! Rip the traitor's head off!
Drag him out into the open!
I can win. I can beat Reiner.
He's going down!
Wha... What's he...?
Heh. Good luck, pal.
You've got him! Keep it up!
What's he doing?
Why would he stop here?
Everyone be on guard! He's calling for backup!
No visual on incoming Titans yet.
He ain't got a chance in hell.
Try screaming for help without a head, asshole!
It's almost off!
Um, I don't like this.
Had to be some reason for that scream.
What the...? No, no, no, no, no!
Above you! Look out!
The battle between Eren and the
Armored Titan comes to an abrupt end.
Mikasa sustains injury as the Colossal
Titan plummets violently from the wall.
Hannes rushes to her side.
From the beginning, through chaos and tragedy,
Mikasa and Armin have shared a common goal:
to protect Eren and save him from the worst in himself.
Next episode: "The Hunters."