There it is again!
Wh-Where is it coming from?
Setting camp at the ruins of Utgard Castle for the night,
the Scouts found themselves overtaken by a Titan horde.
Their chances of survival low.
Nanaba. Gelgar.
I'm sorry, Daddy! I'll be a
good girl from now on, I promise!
But when all seemed lost.
Listen to me.
When you break it down,
this is really just more of a hope.
Christa. Live a life you can be proud of.
Ymir! Wait!
One of their own made a shocking transformation.
Yeah! Atta girl!
Wanna live? Grab on tight.
That's not good.
They're eating her!
No! I still haven't told you my name!
I promised you!
The main force of the Scout Regiment
swooped in and engaged the enemy.
Die!
The Titan assault fell before their blades.
However, standing on the wreckage of battle,
Eren and the others bore witness
to a heartbreaking confession.
Ymir.
Just as promised.
My real name is Historia.
That's it. Bring it up slowly.
Steady the ropes, please.
What's the verdict?
How bad a shape is Ymir in?
Well, she's missing an arm and a leg.
And her insides are scrambled.
If she was normal, she'd be a goner.
Normal, huh?
Here, grab my hand.
Thanks.
Please, you've got to believe me!
I'm telling the truth!
Ymir could've run away any time she wanted!
She chose to fight the Titans to save our lives!
She had nothing to gain putting
herself on the line like that.
Doesn't that speak volumes about where her loyalties are?
She should have told us before, yes.
She had no right to keep her power a secret.
It's hard to look past how much humankind might've gained
from knowing what she's been keeping to her self, but...
I think... I think she was just
worried about what people might do to her.
Clearly her priorities have changed now.
This isn't nearly as complicated as it looks.
No one is closer to Ymir than me,
and there's no question in my mind whose side she's on!
Is that so?
Well, under the circumstances it
certainly behooves us to be friendly.
Her priorities aside,
I'll wager what she can teach us about
the enemy is beyond measure. Probably.
Even so. You say this isn't as complicated as it looks,
but from where I'm standing the
world gets more complicated by the hour.
Oh, uh... Historia Reiss you said your name was?
I did. That's correct.
Isn't Reiss the name of a noble family?
Yes, it is.
Huh.
Historia, nice to meet'cha.
Thank you.
How's she doing?
Comatose but stable. The bleeding's stopped,
though steam appears to be coming out of her wounds.
Best course of action is taking her back to Trost
where the poor girl can get proper medical care.
She's in your hands.
Consider it done.
Right, then. On with our mission.
Finding the hole and patching it up.
Son of bitch.
You okay over there, Reiner?
Not by a long shot.
Titan almost gnawed my arm off.
Pathetic. All I could think was "this it how I go."
What else you s'posed to think at time like that?
You're only human.
Don't you get it? This was my second time!
Armin! Remember?
Huh?
Go on!
Tell him how Annie nearly crushed me like an insect!
Yeah.
That's twice I've nearly died now.
What are the chances I'll survive a third time?
This is what it really means.
What it is to be soldier.
Your spirit breaks and the body follows.
Eh. No good whining about it now.
'Least not till we can plug up the wall.
That's true. The two of you have been driven
far enough away from your hometown as it is.
This is it.
This is where we draw the line.
Truer words were never spoken!
Home! Let's go! We've been here long enough!
Compared to everything else we've
had to go through, the rest is easy!
You're right.
We don't have much further to go before it's done!
What are guys talking about?
I needed that. Thanks.
Are you injured?
Nah, I'm okay, but, Reiner's wounded.
And Ymir's sure seen better days.
Who would've ever pegged her for a Titan?
Are they...?
Sasha.
We all on the same page?
We'll decide what to do with Ymir later.
Oh, and Conny?
Chin up. I'll order a squad to investigate your village.
For now, stay focused.
I want our energy on the task at hand. Clear?
Crystal!
It's troubling.
You would expect this area to be teeming with Titans.
Hm?
Hannes?
Is that the Garrison advance squad?
Tell me they've located the breach.
Wall's perfectly fine.
What?
Spent all night trying to find
out where they're getting in.
But between Trost and Krolva District, there's nothing.
No hole anywhere.
That's impossible!
We ran into a search party from
Krolva and retraced our steps.
Not a single Titan on the way here either.
But we know for a fact that there
are Titans on this side of Wall Rose.
Oh, C'mon.
How much have you had to drink, seriously?
Why you little!
Hold on, wait a second.
What the hell are you kids even doing here?
If there's no breach, then I
guess we have to change tactics.
We head back to Trost immediately.
You'd be smart to keep your guard up.
We'll go on ahead of you.
How can there be nothing wrong with the wall?
Excellent question.
Nothing like this has happened in five years.
Why now all of a sudden?
Feels like everything's spiraling out of control.
Eren.
We should talk. You got a moment?
Sure, I guess.
Five years ago, we compromised Wall
Maria and launched an attack on humanity.
Oh no. What if there's a species of Titan
we haven't seen yet that knows how to dig?
Ugh. That would definitely make
their entry point hard to find.
I'm the Armored Titan. He's the Colossal.
We can hypothesize later.
Our first concern is Ymir.
Titans being a close second, even with the horses.
What are you talking about?
Why are you telling him? Reiner, no!
...Stop!
...We were on a mission.
Our goal was to ensure mankind's extinction.
But now, there's no need for that.
Eren, if you want the walls to remain standing,
it's simple. Just come with Bertholdt and me.
Do you understand?
Understand? What the hell is there to understand?
Listen to me. I need you to do exactly as I say.
Look, I know this is sudden, but we have to go.
Right now? Where would you take me?
I can't tell you. Not yet.
Just think of it as our hometown.
Okay? So what's it gonna be?
Not a bad deal, right?
The chance to avert a major crisis?
I'm not so sure.
You guys! Get a move on, we're heading out!
Damn it. I didn't want to believe
what I was hearing yesterday.
Hmmm.
Section Commander? Something wrong?
Uh... Huh?
Oh, uh, well I was finally able to get my hands on
the background report I requested for Annie Leonhart.
Annie?
Yeah. Took longer than I was hoping for.
The paper trail's a bit of a catastrophe at the moment.
Bureaucracy, huh?
Anyway, according to this, there were two other
cadets in the 104th who haled from the same region.
I have their names.
One Reiner Braun and Bertholdt Hoover.
Not much survives in the way of records,
and thanks to the chaos five years
ago, what we have on them is unreliable.
However, we do know that during the long-range
scouting formation, their unit was given false intel.
They were among those intentionally misled
into thinking Eren was in the right wing.
Wait just a minute. That's the section Annie attacked.
What? What does that mean?
Well, it's entirely possible they
told Annie where they thought Eren was.
Huh? Why would they do that?
Where are you going with this, Armin?
You can't just accuse...!
I totally agree.
Coincidence doesn't establish relationship.
Bearing that in mind, I'm curious to
know how the three interacted while training.
What can you tell me?
I knew Bertholdt and Reiner were from the same
region as Annie, but I never saw them act friendly.
Same with me.
You'd never catch 'em shootin' the breeze.
And when they did talk it was pretty curt.
Plus, it's not like Annie was very social to begin with.
Yeah, at meals she always seemed
to prefer eating by herself. I dunno.
Ah! I think I've got something
that struck me as weird at the time.
I, uh... heard she liked sweets!
I've got nothing. Except maybe that...
Guys. What are we doing?
These are our comrades we're talking about.
Yeah, sure. Bertholdt never has a lot to say.
But Reiner's like everyone's big brother, y'know?
You really think he's capable of lying to us?
Eren does have a point. Think about it.
Reiner fought the Female Titan with everything he had.
Almost got himself squeezed
to a bloody pulp in the process.
What's the matter?
He burst free of her grip at the last minute.
Afterwards, though, Annie changed her course.
In fact, she ran straight toward where you were.
I... I mentioned that you
might be rear of the center rank,
but there's no way she could've heard me.
She wasn't in earshot at the time.
You've gotta be kidding.
Do you recall if he seemed unusually
interested in Eren's location?
So, where the hell do you think he is?
Oh, no.
I only brought his position up in the first place
because Reiner asked me where I thought Eren might be.
Something else. Once he broke free,
the Female Titan stood there staring at her palm,
possibly transfixed by something
he'd carved onto it with his blades.
Maybe Reiner...
What is wrong with you people?
The man's been with us from the beginning!
...You don't just...
...Enough!
All of you. Listen up.
If we cross paths with the pair in question,
don't give them any indication of what we've discussed.
And under no circumstances are you to broach
the topic of Annie Leonhart in their company.
Before we can ascertain whether they were co-conspirators,
we must find, lure, and contain them underground.
That's the plan. Are we clear?
Yes, clear!
You're just tired. That's it, right?
Help me out here, Betholdt.
Your nerves are shot.
You don't know what you're saying.
Uh. Yeah.
It's the battle fatigue talking!
It's okay. You're okay.
If you really were the Armored Titan,
what's the endgame here?
We wouldn't be having this
conversation in the first place.
What'd you expect me to do? Say yes?
Let myself be kidnaped just 'cause you asked politely?
Right. Not thinking straight, am I?
Barely know what I'm saying here.
Must've gone off the deep end.
C'mon, let's go.
That's the problem.
Heh.
I've been here too long for my own good.
Three years of this madness, surrounded by idiots.
We were kids. What'd we know about anything?
Why did there have to be people like this?
Why? Why did I let myself devolve
into such a half-assed piece of shit?
It's too late now.
Damned if I know what's right anymore!
Who cares? It is what it is.
No choice but to face what I've done.
As a warrior.
No road left but the one that leads to the end!
Reiner! Right now?
Here? We're doing this?
Yes. Right here, right now!
We settle this once and for all!
Eren! Get out of here!
Bertholdt!
Eren! Run away!
Ymir!
No!
I'm going to return to the home that was taken from me.
I will do it. No matter what.
Bertholdt. Reiner.
Damn you! You traitors!
The Colossal and the Armored.
Two terrifying enemies from the past
have resurfaced and made their move.
If driving humankind to extinction
is indeed the all-consuming goal,
they've gone beyond to the point of no return.
Yet Reiner and the others devote themselves
to their cause because they are warriors.
Next episode: "Close Combat."