Eren...
You want them to think that you're strong?
Exercise restraint.
Try protecting Mikasa once in a while.
Stop it! No!
He tossing Titans now?
That son of a bitch has gone berserk!
Damn you, Commander Erwin!
I had this all planned out.
Why'd you have to go and screw it up?
Ymir! Conny! Over there!
I see!
Commander!
I'm not your objective.
Don't waste time on someone who's replaceable.
Retrieve Eren and go.
Get down!
Are you insane?
Can you believe this luck?
Ha! Crazy, right?
Watch me! This is the least that I owe your mother.
She'll finally have the vengeance she deserves!
No! Hannes!
He needs backup!
Aah!
Reiner. What the...?
Doesn't he care if Eren gets eaten?
Move it or lose it, asshole!
I'm tired of your shit!
What are you doing?
Honestly? Hell if I know.
Do I trust Reiner, or gamble on
the Scouts and hope for the best?
Suppose I actually manage to live through this.
What good's another day on borrowed time?
Life inside the walls will be a nightmare.
That's a fact.
This may be my only shot at
bringing her over to the other side.
I'm just one person.
I can't protect her forever.
Christa!
No. No more.
Sorry, from now on I'm Historia.
Okay, so tell me.
What did you mean exactly by "handing me over"?
Would it really have saved you, or was that a lie?
Stupid question. Of course it was.
Why, then? Why go to the trouble?
Was it me?
You were trying to protect me again!
Heads up!
Listen to me. You need to take your own advice.
You understand me?
Stop putting yourself on the line!
You need to live your own life! Live it with me!
I never told you this before,
but however bad things get, as long as we're together...
...I'm not afraid!
Mikasa, stop! You're in no shape to...!
My hands! Help me!
What'll you do?
Come on!
I have to be the one who kills that thing!
I ain't done with you yet!
This one belongs to me! Wait here.
Eren! Don't go! We have to get you out of here!
Not until I've settled the score. Stand back.
What?
Commander!
Sir! The Armored!
It's coming this way!
Jean!
No!
Oh god. Stay with me, Jean!
No! Don't do this!
Not now!
Eren, stop!
Commander!
Come on! Transform, goddamn it!
Don't let this be for nothing!
Eren.
Look at you!
You haven't grown up one goddamn bit!
You're still as useless as you've ever been!
Nothing's changed!
I'm sorry, Mother. I still can't do anything.
No matter how hard I try, I'm just a worthless little kid.
Eren.
Stop. That isn't true.
Hey. Thank you.
I've been meaning to tell you that.
For fighting. For always standing by me.
Thank you.
For pushing through.
For showing me how to live with purpose.
I'm grateful.
My scarf.
For always wrapping it around me.
Thank you.
Mikasa. I will always wrap your scarf.
Always and forever. That's a promise!
Huh?
Why're they...? What's going on?
They're eating it!
Don't know, don't care. Let's go!
Could be our only chance!
Right!
That's what this is about.
No wonder Reiner was desperate to get his hands on him.
Maybe there is a future inside the walls.
I'll be damned.
This isn't good. Why'd things have to be this way?
Why'd the Coordinate have to fall to him?
Unless we can get it back, we're finished.
No two ways about it.
Of all the people in the world
that power could've gone to,
Eren is by far the worst.
Get away from us!
Rat bastards! I'll kill you where you stand!
Son of a bitch. Bertholdt!
I can't protect him like this!
What the hell is going on?
Eren!
Can you ride?
Yeah!
Then hurry!
This may be our only window! Soldiers, retreat!
What is it?
Hey, ugly! Get with the program!
We were given an order!
Please forgive me.
Wait! What are you doing?
...Let her go!
...But she'll be killed!
At the time,
Ymir's decision to turn back puzzled me,
though I suspected it had something to do
with why the Armored Titan didn't give chase.
I don't get it.
What the hell possessed you to come back?
Uh. Can't say, really.
Probably wasn't the smartest thing.
Seemed a little unfair to send you guys home empty-handed.
Just, think of me as a consolation prize.
Are you serious?
Look at it this way, if you
hadn't come to bust up the wall,
who knows when my nightmare would've ended?
I owed quite a debt.
This is me giving back what I took from you.
'Least somebody knows the shit you've been through.
Even if it is only me.
Yeah, well... thank you. Sorry.
No worries.
Being a goddess had its perks while it lasted.
With reports maintaining the likelihood
of Wall Rose having been compromised,
citizens of the region were forced to take refuge in
a subterranean city within the confines of Wall Sina.
However, though emergency provisions
had been stockpiled for the purpose,
with over half the population relying on them,
rations could only last, at most, a week.
Beyond that lurked a terrible choice:
turn on each other like animals,
or face the prospect of starvation.
To avoid a humanitarian crisis
of catastrophic proportions,
within a week of the Titan onslaught,
authorities declared Wall Rose secure.
Hange. Come in.
Pardon the intrusion, Erwin.
Commander Pyxis. Glad we caught you.
Um, this is... State your name.
Sir! Conny Springer, sir!
Hundred and fourth Cadet Corps!
Conny here is originally from Ragako.
Ah, yes. Where the invasion seems to have begun, correct?
Yes, sir. In fact, he's corroborated a
valuable piece of evidence in that regard.
I think you'll find his story supports our hypothesis.
Soldier, if you would.
I allowed myself to be kidnapped. It's my fault.
Because of me the Scouts lost over
half of their veteran contingent.
All in a single rescue attempt.
Still, though. There were no casualties on the way back.
The Titans completely ignored us.
They were too fixated on Reiner and the others.
Jean and I, we mulled it over between us once we got back.
Huh?
Hear me out. Suppose they acted that way...
...because of you?
Just a thought, of course.
But as far as an explanation,
it's about as good as we've got.
I'm not saying I envy the position you're in.
Maybe all those people really did die for nothing.
That all depends on you.
If you're really worth the sacrifice,
you'd better prove it.
There's no time for second-guessing.
You're right. I have to be decisive.
If this is real... if I can control Titans...
I have to plug up Wall Maria.
Then make Reiner answer for what he's done.
People died for me. I have to earn what they gave.
Come again?
You're saying the Titans responsible for this
were the citizens of Ragako?
I see. So, in actuality, Titans are human beings.
Well, we don't have proof yet.
Great. Perfect.
I've spent all this time. All this energy.
And the things I've been carving through like carrion
were people.
Look, we don't know for a certainty.
Now what?
Um, excuse me.
What's with that smile?
Oh, it's nothing.
Just... seems to me we've taken
one more step toward the truth.
Wow. One whole step, huh?
At this pace we'll run out of
people before we actually reach it.
Not a good rate of return.
Everything comes at a price.
One day we'll get close enough to break through.
The wall barring us from the truth... will tumble.
Not just yet.