No.
Huh?
Die!
Eren!
Ymir!
Ymir?
Ymir.
Yeah.
Ymir!
Whoa!
Ymir.
Dammit.
Mikasa!
Got it!
Christa.
Christa!
Bullshit.
Ow, damn.
It's okay.
Hey! Eren!
Keep it up!
I know you.
Well, we...
Son of a...!
Go on ahead.
It's just...
I mean, how?
Who are you?
I'm with you!
No, it's not.
So why, then?
Wait! Please!
Thanks, guys.
I'm so sorry!
We found 'em!
That's not...!
Daz! Is he...?
She's the one.
Christa, wait!
No. No, please.
I promised you!
What's going on?
It's about time.
Yeah, all right.
Yeah! Atta girl!
That's not good.
You left one out.
Uh, actually, no.
Just as promised.
In the cabin. Now.
Where did they...?
We should be okay.
Tell me the truth.
She never told me.
But, Christa and...
What's it gonna be?
They're eating her!
Enough of this shit!
It was her that day.
We were inseparable.
Don't you die on me!
Don't make me laugh!
It's a zero sum game.
Some wanted her dead,
No! I still haven't...
Right! I'm sorry, sir!
Nine hours, 12 minutes.
How could you possibly?
Thank you, Reiner. I...
Hey! Take it easy, man!
And yet, I had no idea.
Not sure what to think.
They're still not dead?
This begs the question:
Don't worry, sweetheart.
Why would you even care?
Look, somebody's coming!
Just... gimme your word.
Christa. We're the same.
Stop, you're hurting me!
Whoa! What is she doing?
Next episode: "Warrior."
Yeah, well he's not here.
Says they never saw them.
We'll only slow you down.
I intend to live my life.
And even if you did, how?
My real name is Historia.
or die a cozy little trio.
If you're a selfish bitch.
From all the way up there?
Eren was caught off guard.
Wanna live? Grab on tight.
Ymir! Don't do this to me!
Can't be. She's really...?
Hey! You guys seen Christa?
Ymir isn't back yet either.
Could be. I'm not positive.
Look, don't try to stop me!
Nothing's keeping her here.
I'm why you're... a soldier?
Make my name mean something.
By becoming your own victim!
Like our instructors said...
What was that? An avalanche?
And still... She's fighting.
Why are you doing this? Why?
Come on! You're almost there!
You're not worried about Daz.
Well, uh. You could say that.
Great. Then count us in, too.
Disperse and canvas the area!
Ha! You have got to be joking.
Really? What the hell is this?
You can't do this on your own.
That's enough! Let go! Let go!
She could've chosen to escape.
Christa, all of you, get back.
Ha-ha! My very first ODM kill!
Thought we were dead out there.
Do you want more people to die?
I never meant... That's not me.
Quite a story I got treated to.
Unless we're due for a miracle,
Idiot! I told you to fall back!
Anyone else not feel their legs?
and claim a share in his legacy.
I... That's not how... I just...
I say we dump him off the cliff.
What are you doing? Put me down!
I'll handle Daz, you get moving!
One that will change everything.
Daz and I'll be right behind you.
He's a small price to pay, right?
Exactly. She didn't have to stay.
Damn it! We had a deal, remember?
Uh-huh. There go any doubts I had.
Did you want us to become friends?
Your true identity is safe with me.
...was to be given a second chance.
He had no clue till he transformed.
Oh, come on! You're kidding, right?
Not in a hovel like this, damn you!
Too late to think about heaven now!
Way I see it, we've got two choices.
You decide to take the scenic route?
But you didn't have any rope on you.
A chance to finally live for myself!
You had to have been in on all this.
and we never suspected a damn thing.
Well, it's possible she didn't know.
It's okay. Let us take care of this.
Bewildered, hearts heavy with doubt,
Why won't they let us inside already?
They'll have frozen to death by then!
Screw you and this stupid death wish!
It's possible he'll survive the fall.
Yeah, I know. Stupid move on my part.
How she'll use it is anybody's guess.
Tear it to pieces! Live for yourself!
Third option: you're completely wrong.
The base is a straight drop from here.
It would've taken hours to repel down!
Maybe. It's a hell of a power to hide.
Hey, ugly! You've got a job to finish!
If they find him then he might be okay.
But, if he falls he'll die for certain!
You're, uh, gonna need a lot more gear.
Ymir's a Titan. How could you not know?
It's us. She's risking her life for us!
You're a selfish bitch and you know it!
Wait! You're not part of the offensive!
You want to be the hero all of a sudden?
You'll die protecting this stupid tower!
where, then, are the Titans coming from?
Whoa, hold on. Do you think they're lost?
Seriously, give it up. This is pointless.
I dunno. Maybe I relate to your struggle.
That's precisely why I'm coming with you.
Then again, Ymir did seem to have a plan.
Ha! Hoping to go out in a blaze of glory?
Nobody to blame but himself if you ask me.
You're just using him as an excuse to die.
Snuck inside a church in the interior once
I haven't told a soul and I don't plan to.
I brought some extra rations just in case!
Hold on! I still haven't told you my name!
Search as they might, Wall Rose is intact.
There's no reason for you to stick with me.
She's worried about the tower falling down?
En route, Eren discovers a terrible secret.
So we... have more in common than I thought?
I can't just sit around here and do nothing.
You'll make it back a lot faster on your own.
It's better if you guys let me do this alone.
the Scouts begin their journey back to Trost.
They're probably mixed in with the last squad.
This is how you want your story to end. Right?
Talk to me. Somebody tell me it's all a dream.
Some people just aren't cut out to be soldiers.
I suppose we could use all the help we can get.
All this time she's been keeping it under wraps
I have to go back out there and try to find 'em!
Leave Daz to the elements and save our own skin,
Unlike you, I embraced the name I was born with.
Look at yourself, Christa... or whoever you are.
Sounds like the storm's letting up a little bit.
Rate we're going, we'll be lucky not to join him.
That's just it. Thomas was leading the last squad.
Dumb bastard's got one foot in the grave as it is.
Promise to take back your name and live your life.
I used to curse the day I was born, just like you.
Shit! Brace yourselves, people. This is happening!
The world despised me for having the gall to exist.
What a shame. Here I thought you were the good girl.
The only thing we have in common is a second chance.
Look, don't try to read anything else into it, okay?
Dammit. Nobody said training was gonna be this rough.
If I throw it away and reject who I am, then they win.
But even then, what I wished for more than anything...
Not bad given the conditions you had to trudge through.
We know. A rescue team will be sent out at first light.
We don't want more people to die than may already have.
You're the mistress' daughter with the price on her head.
If I have to trust someone, then it might as well be you.
You'll end up just like the folks you're trying to rescue.
For all we know she could've been on their side all along.
Sure, it's a long shot, but
that's what we're dealing with.
Wait a second; are you trying
to say that Ymir is a threat?
Trust me, there's no revenge
in the world sweeter than that.
If you kill yourself, you'll
be doing exactly what they want!
Not for a while. She was with
Daz, and he wasn't doing so good.
So, uh... You got something
against asking me for help or what?
In the end, clever bastards
forced her to join the Cadet Corps.
scrounging around for whatever
might keep me alive another week.
When the day comes for me to
reveal myself to everyone, promise.
The more eyes you've got in your
search party, the better, right?
I bet they're busy laying out a
massive banquet for us as we speak.
You've been a victim all your
life, and how do you get your revenge?
I didn't mean to get us into this
and now there's nothing we can do.
Hey. They'll remember you as a hero
who fearlessly sacrificed herself.
Heh. I thought the only way to put
things right was to give up my life.
He'll be long gone by the time you
make it to the foot of that mountain.
Should've known how much he could
handle before trying to boost his score.
So was, was your whole reason for
joining the Cadet Corps just to find me?
Ooof. Man, if they get stuck out there
in this snowstorm, they're done for.
Let's just say I have a knack for being
in the wrong place at the right time.
some wanted to strip her of the family
name and hide her among peasant stock.
The rest of you follow me to where the
Titans are gathering and cut them down!
Know what I think? I think saving this
moron is the furthest thing from your mind.
I told Reiner and the gang I'd wait out
here to be your welcoming committee, so...
I reach base in plenty of time to save his
life and by morning this is all a bad memory.
Apparently a high-ranking noble produced
more heirs than his people were comfortable with.
An illegitimate girl was floating around
they all feared might come out of nowhere one day
Of course, if you can make it look like you were
trying to save his life, no one will be the wiser.
even if you live to drag him down there all you'll
have in tow by the time you make it is a frozen corpse.