I can win. I can beat Reiner.
He's going down!
Huh? No, no, no, no, no!
Above you! Look out!
Eren!
Ugh.
You're kidding me. Wake up, Commander.
You'll catch your death sleeping out here.
Tell me you didn't drink all this yourself.
God. Sir, please.
Keep tossing it back like someone half
your age, I'll end up putting you in diapers.
Doesn't sound so bad to me.
Old men like to be doted on.
What's the situation?
Well, several patrol units were sent out.
Not many Titans between the
first and second defensive lines.
And the few that did crop up seemed
like they were pretty far apart.
Hmm.
If Hannes and the advance squad have
managed to follow the wall without incident,
they should be getting back before too long.
Fairly straightforward operation.
They'd have run into the unit from Krolva
about halfway and turned around for home.
It's a safe assumption they
encountered few Titans, if any.
If Wall Rose had been breached,
sightings wouldn't be so random.
Commander Pyxis.
Hm?
Ah, Commander Erwin.
Is it true what I hear about you
catching a troublesome little mouse?
Well... technically, yes.
Not that it's helped us.
Hm. Well, at least those goons in the
interior might start using their heads.
Might even be forced to reconsider their belief system.
Morally bankrupt as it is.
Agreed. Seems they have.
Look over there.
Military Police putting in an appearance
where Titans aren't just an academic problem.
Damn. Can't believe we didn't see one.
You really sayin' there weren't any?
I know, right?
It's unusually quiet out there.
Wonder if they're still alive.
What a joke. I thought this
was s'posed to be an emergency.
Yeah. We just come here to sit on our asses, or what?
Hey Levi! Where you hidin' all the Titans?
Problem?
You seem eager to be eaten alive, soldier.
Huh. Sorry we couldn't make that happen for you today.
Plenty of opportunities outside
the wall if you're lookin'.
Lots of scouting expeditions.
I'd be more than happy for the help.
We could all fight Titans together.
Well, you know.
There's our work in the interior, so...
Hey! The advance squad is back!
Go! Tell Commander Pyxis!
I see. No breach as far as you could tell, correct?
That's correct, sir!
Mmm. As I thought.
But, sir! A situation has developed!
You see, we ran into another
group on the way back to Trost.
It was the Scout unit led by Section Commander Hange.
There were recruits from the 104th Cadet
Corps with them, none of whom had equipment.
This may sound crazy, sir, but three of them
were Titans!
What the...?
Hang on a sec. Seriously? You
mean like there were three... more?
But... who were they? Who, damn it?
Actually, I, um...
Jean, calm down.
What happened when their Titan forms were revealed?
The Scouts faced them. The Armored
Titan and the Colossal head on.
But by the time our unit arrived
on the scene it was... too late.
I'm sorry.
Oh, man. What a mess.
Count your lucky stars we were all the way up here.
Rest of 'em got blasted by steam
and debris; nothing much they could do.
How badly is Mikasa hurt?
Well there aren't any wounds to speak of.
I think it's just a concussion.
Could be worse.
Armin, I've got food if you're hungry.
You eaten?
Be right back.
Mikasa!
Come quick! Eren's in trouble!
What kind of trouble?
It's those three bullies again.
They took the bread I just bought.
I... I told Eren about it and...
I didn't want him to go!
Wait!
Give it back.
You have dirt in your ears or somethin'?
Like I said, I already ate the whole thing.
Tasty.
But that was three days worth of food for them!
You gotta be kiddin' me.
Those table scraps?
Knock it off. You'll make me feel bad.
Whatever, you want it back so damn much...
Pay him back what the bread was worth!
Whoa! What are you doing?
Hey! There's a situation over here if you hadn't noticed!
Get off your drunk asses!
Ugh, come on. They're just kids
bein' kids. Let 'em work it out.
They're demolishing my stall!
This, uh, ain't our thing.
Best wait for someone more qualified
to come along and sort it out.
Huh?
Eren!
Eat this, punk!
Mikasa...!
I've got this. What are you doing?
Eren, you need to go home and chop wood.
You want your mom to get angry?
You little... Now it's a fight!
You asked for it...!
No! It's okay! She can handle it!
Let go!
Oh-ho! Nice one!
Don't let her do all the work!
What was that for?
Don't cheer the little bastards on! Damn freeloaders!
Freeloaders? D'you just call us freeloaders?
Hey, if the shoe fits, shove it up your ass!
You son of a...!
Hey. Hey! He's got a point, y'know.
I mean...
Heh. That's some right arm.
For a chump who runs a stall!
Yeah! Get him, Hannes!
Come on, man!
Don't get beat by a soldier!
Stop it right now!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Act like adults!
Give it back!
Damn it!
That's enough!
Uh-oh. Hey, guys?
This is gettin' kinda serious.
Screw this! We're outta here!
Get back here!
...Where d'you think you're...
...No, Eren!
I don't care about the stupid bread!
Let it go!
That's enough. We're going back home right this instant.
Like hell! Go without me!
Eren! Wait!
No you don't!
Hold on! Eren!
Eren!
Mikasa.
Where is Eren? Where did he go?
Whoa! Calm down!
Wait! You shouldn't...!
We don't know how badly you're hurt!
Where is he?
Eren and Ymir were taken.
They're gone. Reiner and Bertholdt abducted them.
He fought, but the Armored Titan was just too...
That was about five hours ago.
Somebody's gone after them, right?
Tell me somebody went after them.
I'm sorry.
Why not?
We wanted to, but the horses
are on the other side of the wall.
Our only option is to wait.
The mounts can't be hauled over until
the lifts make it here and that takes time.
There's nothing else we can do right now.
Section Commander Hange and the
other officers are too injured to move.
We don't have enough soldiers to form a scouting party.
Even a small one would need more than this.
We just can't do it.
You understand?
Damn it. Not this again.
You feel any pain?
No. I hit my head, but I think I'm okay now.
Don't worry about it.
It's just...
...not the first time I've been down this road.
Except when Annie took him,
I didn't waste a second. Not one.
That's how Captain Levi and I were able to get him back.
But... it's already been five hours.
Hey, Armin.
Why's he do it? Always leave?
Always end up someplace we're not?
Yeah, it does seem to happen a lot.
Ever since we were kids Eren liked to run off on his own.
Leave us worried sick.
Who knows? That's just the sort
of person he's meant to be. Maybe.
I don't want much.
Just to be near him.
That's all.
Good. You're awake.
Must be starving. Here.
Heads up, Armin.
Sorry it's only field rations,
but better than nothing, I guess.
Not bad. Not good either. Nothing new there.
Aaah.
Speaking of which, this feels familiar, huh?
You two've been runnin' damage control for that little
hothead since the good ol' days, if I recall correctly.
Doesn't seem very fair, but what do I know?
Different time, different place, same problem.
Not exactly what I'd call a healthy relationship.
Am I wrong?
The neighborhood bullies weren't quite so tall,
but I suppose there are similarities.
Yep. That's our Eren. Heh.
Can't hold his own for shit,
but always lookin' for a fight.
Five guys wanna take him on, he'd wouldn't think
twice about jumping into the fray like an idiot.
By the time Mikasa gets there or the
MPs show up, he's beaten all to hell.
But you know...
I may not've ever had the privilege of seeing Eren win,
but I never saw the little
son of a bitch back down either.
Kid's got fire.
To tell the truth, his persistence
scares the piss outta me sometimes.
He gets knocked on his ass, he gets right back up again.
It's in his blood.
You think he'd let himself be snatched
away without fighting tooth and nail?
Not a chance.
Whatever strength he's got left, he'll use it.
What's two guys next to a whole gang?
If you can count on anything,
it's that Eren'll give 'em hell.
At least till you or me shows up to help.
That's how it's always been, right?
Yes, sir. Those good ol' days were somethin' else.
'Course if you ask Eren,
he'd tell ya they were an illusion.
Just us kidding ourselves.
But I for one was never happier than when folks
thought of me as a freeloading waste of space.
There's not much I wouldn't do to get us back
to how things used to be. Call me sentimental.
But I'm willing to fight for it.
He needs us.
Whaddya say we stick to what we know.
It ain't the good ol' days 'less
the three of you are together.
They're here.
Is that?
Oh, wow.
Ah!
Commander Erwin!
With MPs!
Never thought they'd ride on top of the wall.
Probably the quickest route here.
For the record, I know you won't,
but I'd much prefer if you stayed behind.
No, not happening. Nice try, though.
As long as Ymir's in danger, nothing will keep me here.
Sorry. That's just how it is.
We're all in this together, Armin.
You're not special.
Every one of us has a reason for going.
Still trying to process mine, to be honest.
Why did Bertholdt and Reiner do what they did?
I wanna ask while I look them dead in the eye.
Good to see you, Commander Erwin.
Glad you're here.
Is the situation still the same?
...Yes, sir.
...Good.
Right! Deploy the lifts!
Hange?
Don't just stand there. Gi-Give me a map.
It's a gamble, but the trees in this forest
are massive. I say we ride straight for it.
See, even if they had a way to
cover the Armored Titan's footprints,
this is almost definitely where we would find them.
Why's that?
They need to recoup.
They have the power to assume Titan form,
but other Titans on that side
of the wall still pose a threat.
Especially after putting up such a fight.
Yes, Eren was the worse for it,
but they've got to be spent.
Remember when Annie went out cold?
Let's suppose they're headed somewhere beyond Wall Maria.
That's not a simple hike.
They'll need all the rest they can get
before covering that kind of distance.
They're in no shape to make it in a single push.
And if so, they'll want to catch their
breath somewhere other Titans can't get to them.
Odds are they'll hold out till it gets dark.
You're awake.
Welcome back.
We have until sundown!
If we can reach the forest by then, we
might just have a chance to save them!
Let's move!
Eren wakes, surrounded by trees.
Desperate to escape, he attempts to transform,
only for Ymir to convince him otherwise.
Deep in the isolated forest,
emotions reach the boiling point.
Eren and Reiner clash.
This must be settled once and for all.
For themselves, and for all who've perished.
Next episode: "Opening."