Heads up. She's back.
Good.
Oh, no!
No! They're getting away with Eren!
Ride! Let the Titans chase you!
All squads, follow my lead!
Do what? Erwin, you conniving bastard!
You're using us as bait again?
It's the only way!
You've fought well as MPs. Now give your all as soldiers!
The Armored Titan must be stopped before he takes Eren.
Failure is not an option!
Reiner's too slow! We've got 'im!
I won't hesitate this time.
I'll kill them without a thought.
If Ymir feels like getting in the way,
so much the worse for her.
This ends here and now. I swear it!
Christa!
Ymir.
Ymir!
Christa...
No...
Historia, I'm sorry about eating you.
You're uh, probably pissed.
Wha-What is this? I...
What's going on? Talk to me!
We came to rescue you and Er...
Just shut up!
I don't need rescuing. Things have changed.
I'm with Reiner and Bertholdt now.
Like it or not, you're coming with us.
There's no future inside the walls.
Hear me out for a second, okay?
Life outside isn't as bad as you think, believe me.
For starters, there's no one saying the world
woulda been a better place if you'd never been born.
Yeah, I don't think Titans would say much either way.
They'd be too busy trying to devour me!
We've all got flaws!
They're not so bad if you'd just give 'em a break!
It's complicated, all right? Get off your high horse!
Ymir! I don't know what's going on in your
mind, but you're not making any sense! Come on!
What did Reiner and Bertholdt say?
You're doing this against your will, they threatened you!
It's the opposite, actually.
I'm right, aren't I? Let go!
Whatever they've got on you, I don't care!
We can fight them!
Put the past behind you!
What matters is right now!
I'm here! I will always be your ally!
Ymir!
Look. In case you haven't
noticed, the Scouts are closing in.
If we'd left earlier, there might've
been a decent chance of outrunning them.
Going back for Christa was your idea.
You forced us. Remember that.
We waited. For what? Damn it, Ymir!
What the hell did we do this for?
You can't have a change of heart!
You want her to rot inside the walls?
Does that seem acceptable to you now?
Don't be a fool! Think!
Let go! Don't listen to him!
I can't!
I wish I could.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I know you think I did this for you.
But at the end of the day, I did it for me.
A long time ago I stole the Power of
the Titans from one of their comrades.
Not much I can do against them.
Sooner or later, I'm screwed.
But, they said if I cooperate, hand you over,
maybe I've got a shot at leniency.
Maybe my crime gets overlooked.
You're crucial to the Church.
You know the truth about the walls!
My family? That's it, isn't it?
Sure. Why not?
When this world started going to hell
I thought to myself, "couldn't hurt to
have a bargaining chip in my back pocket."
The castle's as close to death as I ever wanna get.
Whole experience traumatized me.
Gave me perspective.
If I have to play dirty to stay alive,
then I have to play dirty.
Pathetic, yeah. Doesn't make me the ideal friend.
Like I said, though, I didn't do this for you.
You deserve better, but there it is.
I need you.
Please save me, Historia!
Well, like I said.
I'm here, and I will always be your ally!
Reiner! Protect us!
All right, then. Looks like Ymir goes first!
Mikasa, no!
You're not going to kill Ymir.
That all depends on her. What'll it be?
She can step aside or she can die. Her choice.
That's not fair! She'll die if she doesn't go
along with what Reiner and Bertholdt tell her to do.
She's screwed either way!
Listen, there's only so many
lives I can give a damn about.
Cruel, but that's the world
our enemies gave us six years ago.
Sorry. I don't have any
heartstrings left for you to tug on.
If you want compassion, move on.
You want fair, tough shit.
Time's wasting. Pick your side, Christa.
Eren? Or the bitch I'm gonna kill?
Ymir, stop!
Look at her face! She means it!
Don't make a move!
Quit struggling! It's not going to help!
Good luck talking sense into that one, Bertholdt.
When something lights a fire under him, that's it.
Getting Eren to calm down's a lost cause.
Take my word for it.
I've been on the receiving end more than you have.
Whaddya say we teach him patience?
C'mon. Show yourself.
Give him back! Right now!
Guys, really? This is some kind of joke, right?
No way this is you.
You've been lying to us this whole time?
We were supposed to be comrades!
They still are! This is all just a misunderstanding!
Where d'you think you're going?
You can't keep running forever.
We're not gonna let that happen. Rat bastards.
Through thick and thin we slept under
the same roof as soldiers for three years.
Matter of fact, the positions you could
sleep in were an art from, Bertholdt.
I'm not kidding. We all loved waking up
to see your contortions in the morning.
Used to predict the weather with 'em.
How'd you do it, Bertholdt?
Must not've had a care in the world.
Lying beside your victims, yet you slept like a log.
Was it all just an act to you?
What about the way we used to
talk about surviving this together?
About growing old, looking back
on the worst of it over drinks.
Remember? Was that all bullshit?
Answer me!
Go on. What was the point? What were you trying to do?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Shut up and focus on opening the traitor's neck.
Hesitate for a moment and we forfeit Eren.
Who cares what they pretended to be?
This was their choice.
No! You're wrong!
Who chooses to be this? Tell me!
What d'you think I am? Huh? What?
You think this is what we aspired to be?
People loathe us. And why wouldn't they?
We're monsters!
We deserve to die for the things we've done.
We're lost. We could live a thousand
years and never again know peace.
Try to imagine that darkness.
The only light was our brief time as soldiers.
It was never a lie! Do you understand?
We're not who we said we were, but it wasn't an act!
We genuinely thought of you as our friends!
I'm not stupid. I know I have no right to ask forgiveness,
but please. I beg of you.
If we were comrades, someone find us.
Give him back. I won't ask again.
I'm sorry. I can't.
One of you has to do it.
One of you has to stain your hands with my blood!
Guys! Get down from there and take cover!
What the hell's Erwin doing?
He's off his rocker! Look!
The lunatic's leading the Titans straight for us!
Jump, damn you! Get the hell out of there!
Squadrons break! Make the Titans scatter!
Historia!
What's going on? Is this hell?
Not yet. But it will be.
All soldiers charge!
Huh?
We've come to the moment of truth!
Mankind's fate is decided now!
There is no future in which we reclaim these
lands without Eren... and there never will be!
Go! Recover Eren from the Armored Titan and retreat!
Your heart and soul to the cause!
Mikasa, wait!
This is madness.
The Scouts have taken one too many hits to the skull.
...Look out!
...Huh?
What's happening out there?
Ugh! If only I could see!
I can't move. 'Less I can shake these Titans,
it'll only get worse.
Okay, then. Heads up, Bertholdt.
Brace yourself!
That's right. Just a little more!
It's working! His hands are down!
Now's our chance!
Uh, Mikasa? You can see those Titans, right?
I mean, I get it, you're strong.
But that's one hell of a mess.
Slipping through isn't gonna be easy.
Advance!
Commander Erwin!
I said advance, goddamn it!
Eren's right in front of you! Do not falter!
Mikasa!
You piece of shit! Get your hands off her!
We've come too far to give up now.
We are going home. And Eren is coming with us.
No. This is all on me.
People are dying because I got caught!
Bertholdt!
Armin?
That's the irony, really.
If you can't let it go it's not worth holding on to.
Advance!
Think. What is it I have to let go of?
My life? Or something else?
So, you're okay with this?
Leaving your friend behind to face the music?
I guess Annie was weighing you down?
D'you know where she is?
Way up north in the Utopia District. Being tortured.
The silent treatment only goes so far.
The body may heal, but her screams are an
object lesson on the limits of endurance.
Oh, don't worry, they're taking special
care she doesn't die... or get a moment's rest.
So many methods, so little time.
Mustn't waste a prize specimen like Annie.
She's too precious.
Shut your mouth, hell spawn! I'll kill you!
All soldiers, retreat!
I did it.
I actually killed one. You all right?
Get away from her!
What the hell were you trying to pull?
We're leaving!
Yeah, couldn't you go for some grub right about now?
You don't understand! Let me down!
Please!
Huh?
Reiner and Bertholdt are going to kill
Ymir unless we both agree to go back with them!
She'll only be free if she hands me over!
I'd already decided to let that happen.
Are you nuts? What if it's a trick?
It's not! Let me go!
Conny's right! Whatever she said, it's a lie!
Don't listen to her!
This doesn't make sense.
Why would someone who fought tooth and nail to
save your life just turn you over to the enemy?
What's the end game?
The only time Ymir bothers to make
an effort is when you're in danger.
I don't know what kind of trouble she's in,
but for now just calm down till we know more.
Exactly. Either way, we can't stick around.
Whatever Ymir needs you for, I'm
sure you won't be much good to her dead!
Damn straight. Even I could figure that one out.
He's tossing Titans now?
That son of a bitch has gone berserk!
Eren! Mikasa!
Eren.
Eren encounters the very Titan that devoured his mother.
He stands paralyzed with fear
as Hannes rushes to protect him.
Who is the real enemy?
What is the nature of this war?
Not knowing against whom to brandish their blades,
the Scouts nevertheless fight on.
What does the future hold?
And at what cost?
Next episode: "Scream."