Help!
H-Help me! Help me someone!
Get out of here.
Oh god. What is this
thing? What is that?
Didn't you hear me?
Get out of here now.
Or perhaps your life
doesn't matter to you?
Move your ass.
The fun's... just
getting started.
Well, I guess I'm not gonna
be able use that anymore...
Lightning?
It was terrible!
Is that woman really a demon?
There's no mistaking it.
The town fell into ruin soon
after that woman arrived.
There are people who saw
her commanding demons.
My parishioners.
Members of the faithful!
Go on.
And I saw it too, my dear...
That woman
manipulating lightning...
and burning people
of our town to death!
I've been looking for you.
So you're the devil
laying waste to this town.
Why don't you take
your true form?
That's when you're at
your strongest, right?
You don't think you're
a little cocky?
So you prefer to remain
in that form, do you?
Well... regardless
of the form you take,
I'm going to hunt you
down and kill you.
Dammit!
I'll wipe that smile
right off your face.
Well it looks like
my job won't be over
until I take that little
blonde bitch out...
Ridiculous...
Who the hell's gonna wear
anything that expensive?
With that much money, I could
drink all night at Cindy's bar
and still come home
with some change.
Damn... That sure was
a stupid bet I made...
Thinking about
dressing up in drag?
Let me know if there's anything
you think would look good on me.
God... Your jokes
are always so lame.
So, what do you want?
If you're here to
collect money from me,
I don't need that right now.
Relax. I just dropped by today
because I have
something to ask you.
The truth is that, yesterday,
the demon I was supposed
to bag got away from me.
Poor bastard. So I
guess you're gonna be
hunting him until
he's dead, huh?
Well, he's got my sympathy.
You wouldn't know anything
about a she-devil...
that commands
lightning, would you?
Lightning?
Yeah. Though she looked human...
Don't have a clue...
But I can tell ya there's
a ton of demons out there
in the world that could
totally pass for human.
Huh...
Oh yeah, and she was
packing heat too.
Well, demons do have fingers...
That's all you need
to pull a trigger.
You got a point there.
It's just that...
this she-devil...
kept shooting at me with a
gun in each of her hands...
Just like you.
Later.
This chick sounds interesting.
You should introduce us.
On the slim chance you're
able catch her, that is.
Then I could teach her how
to use those guns of hers.
That won't happen...
next time I see her she's dead.
You're one scary lady...
Hey there, Lady!
Are you leaving already?
Yeah, gotta go.
Maybe the next time we'll
hang out and play together.
Sure.
Dante! So did you have
a good look at this?
Listen to you... did you
forget how old you are?
There aren't any clothes
for kids in there.
Look here. If you're
going to buy me clothes,
I want to get some cute stuff!
Remind me why I should have
to buy you cute clothes...
You promised you would!
You said if you
lost to me at cards,
you'd buy me some clothes!
I didn't say I'd buy
them for you today.
That's not fair!
You have any idea how
much those clothes cost?
Didn't you get paid yet
for tracking down that guy?
That "guy" ended up being
just some runaway lizard...
You can imagine what that pays.
No, I can't.
Well, it turned out
that it pays three pizzas
and two strawberry sundaes.
Pizza... again?
So if you want
clothes like that,
you better do something like
find a rich guy to marry.
But this is just a
regular fashion magazine.
It's not like it's only the
expensive brand-names in here.
Are you telling me little kids
really wear stuff
that costs this much?
That's how it is for girls!
You don't understand
anything about girls' fashion!
For crying out loud...
Lightning...
"Devil May Cry..."
So, it was you... I knew it.
So what's the big game
you're after this time?
Actually this target
isn't big at all.
Just about the size of a human.
What?! You go and shoot
'em with a gun like that
and they'll be nothing
but minced meat!
That's fine if you're
looking to become a butcher.
Well... I doubt that
I'll end up using it.
But just in case,
it's good to have.
--Hey!
--Huh?
Is that good looking woman
out there someone you know?
She's gone! I know
I saw her here.
W-What the...?!
What just happened?!
So that's revenge
for yesterday, is it?
You don't do things half-assed.
So what... What the hell
did you do to her?
Nothing yet, really.
We're just having a
little spat, that's all.
Huh?
Looks like I had better change
before I go to work. Damn.
Thanx. Think I'm gonna
take this with me.
That woman always gives
me the heebie jeebies.
Though the other chick
must be something, too,
to be spatting with her.
You had better get
ready... demon-bitch!
All these expenses!
I should bill that
priest for this stuff,
but I doubt he'd cover it...
Excuse me, I'd like
to try this stuff on.
I'm sorry, but there's
another customer
in the dressing room right now.
Would you wait just
a moment, please?
What awful style.
A demon out shopping?
My, aren't we full of ourselves?
Get the hell outta here.
I'd hate to go at it
with you and destroy
this nice boutique and
all the designer clothes.
All this? You want to
purchase all of these items?
This is all from
this year's collection.
I think you'll look fantastic.
Make sure you come
back next week.
Can't shake it. Feel like
I'm losing a fight...
Hello! I need some
clothes from that rack
by the goddamn front door!
What do you think you're doing?!
You let that dangerous
devil get away?!
If things continue like this,
the damage could spread
to other towns as well...
She's terrible!
That's what you say,
but I didn't think
she was all that terrible...
What are you saying?!
Do you know how many of
our brethren she's killed?
What will she do next?
Alright... I will admit...
she is pretty strong.
I even bought this thing.
Take care of that demon
as quickly as you can.
Use whatever means you have to.
Got'cha. Besides, it looks like
the bitch is here anyway...
We just keep running
into each other today...
I may have let you get
away at that boutique,
but this time I'm going
to kill you for sure.
I don't care if this church
falls to the ground...
Not to mention I'm a little
pissed off at how much
these clothes cost that
I had to buy because of you!
I don't like being ignored.
You're in the way.
You should get out of here
now and say your prayers.
He's out of the way.
Now we can do as we like.
A two-gun toting demon bitch...
It's not often I
run into enemies
that I'm so averse to losing to!
Well it looks to me like
your clothes have
been ruined again...
But your body seems to
be holding up quite well.
So, I guess you'll have
to allow me to use this!
You bitch! You shot my hair!
What's the matter?
It feel's like I'm just
fighting another human!
If you're going to
continue like that,
you should go find some
underground club or something.
Your little show could
probably bring in some money.
Dante, that's
the bitch that I--
--You're late.
--Am I?
What time is it?
Too bad, it doesn't look like
there's a clock around here.
I told you not to be late.
You never did listen.
I'm here, aren't I?
Just a minute...
I mean everything's fine
since we're both okay.
But... what would you have
done if one of us was killed.
What about then?
Relax...
Neither of you seem like you're
gonna go and die that easy.
Hello!
Hmm?
What is going on here?!
What do you mean,
"what's going on here"?
Are you two playing
some sort of joke on me?!
You better not tell me there
were cameras rolling all along.
I don't watch reality tv shows
and I'm not gonna be on one!
Umm....
And who are you?
You can speak, huh?
Are you telling me
you were playing mute?
Seems that you're
quite the actress.
Don't just stand there.
Say something will ya?
Hey! Don't look at me.
You're the one opened
your big mouth.
And it looks like you
were having some fun
with that little
misunderstanding.
Well yeah, maybe, but...
"Misunderstanding"?
Would you explain this
thing from the beginning
so I understand it?
Yeah, I'm sorry
I had to put you on.
You can call me Trish.
And I am Dante's partner.
Ex-partner. Nowadays
we work independently.
That's not a very
nice way to put it.
It was your idea, wasn't it?
That we'd probably work
more efficiently apart.
Are you pouting? Maybe you're
lonely being all on your own?
Don't talk down to
me like I'm a kid.
I totally dig being on my own.
Plus, I can eat
all the pizza I want.
Didn't I tell you for years
to go easy on the pizza?!
And don't tell me that's all
you're eating every day.
God you're pathetic,
you know that?
Please don't talk to me
like you're my mom.
You're not the maternal type.
That's enough. Look.
You better explain this.
I don't give a damn about your
personal lives. Start talkin'.
If you're feeling
a little bit jealous,
you should just let
yourself express that.
Jealous?
You think I'm jealous?!
This bastard's a
strawberry sundae freak,
he eats pizza every day,
and he never pays back
the money he borrows
from me or anybody else!
How exactly am I supposed
to fall for him?!
Oh! So I'm wrong?!
Take a wild guess!
Say something, you!
Like I said, don't look at me.
Why didn't you just explain
things to me right away?
Then we wouldn't have had to
ruin our clothes
and hair, right?
I think you understand...
that in this business, sometimes
people want to test themselves
against a powerful enemy.
Can't blame her since recently
you and I haven't been
getting that much of a
workout from our opponents.
And at any rate, when I
first saw you running around,
you seemed like you'd give
me more fun than my quarry.
Your quarry?
Why don't you come on out?
You've been watching us
all along, haven't you?
I see...
I'm here at the request
of another person.
Since this strange
priest showed up,
this town has become
a den for demons.
And he felt like he was in
danger so he hired me...
What a clever little father.
Don't misunderstand me.
Putting an end to you three
do-gooders will be easy.
I just thought I'd like to
avoid the hassle of doing so.
I always thought this
guy was a little weird.
But I wouldn't have
guessed he's a demon.
Now that you know me for
what I am, I have no choice...
It's a hassle but you're all
going to have to die here.
Tell me, Dante. Whatdya think?
Unfortunate for him.
Since this horny little
devil is new to town,
he probably doesn't know
what we do for a living.
I could almost cry knowing
this dork had me fooled...
Boohoo. Boohoo.
Enough with your jokes!
Joke's on you pal!
So where are you headed
off to this time?
I've got a lot of them
that I'm following.
I guess it depends on them.
If you get sick of it,
you can always come back here.
Why that's uncharacteristically
kind of you!
But, for the time being, I think
I want to travel around a bit.
Take care of yourself, alright?
You too, baby.
Let me drive you partway.
Jump on.
Nice suit. Looks good on you.
Don't suppose you did a
little shopping recently?
Of course I did.
And I sent him the bill...
You did? What a coincidence.
Whatdya mean by that?
I got a dress.
Good for you.
Um... Are you Dante?
Huh?
I was told to
bring you this bill.
We take cash, check,
or charge, sir.
No, you got the wrong guy.
No, no, no...
I'm sure this is the place!
Two separate women
gave me the address.
Two women?
What?! They what?!
Would you please pay this?!
Just... Just a damn minute!
I don't have any money now!
Well I need to be paid!
I can't give you money
if I don't have it.
Whatdya want me to do?
I can't just let
you off with that.
What is this for in the first
place? What did they buy?!
Clothes.
Clothes? Why the hell would
clothes cost this much?!
I hope Dante won't be mad...
that I bought some clothes.
Well, it should be fine.
He's the one who said
he'd buy them for me!
Every now and then,
there's someone who likes to
sneak around and spy on me.
I don't know what
anyone gets out of
following around
and investigating
a normal, upright
citizen such as me.
Must be a boring job...
I gotta tip my hat off to 'em.
But if anyone is gonna
follow me around,
they better be ready for all
the danger that comes with it.
'Cuz there are plenty of demons
that like to follow
me around too.
Make sure you don't
miss my next mission.
In Private.
Available only on DVD. Level 2.