Yee-haw!
Hey, Michel!
What is it?!
You're ridin' way
too fast tonight!
If you don't want to push it,
you can always slow down!
Michel!
The sound of the wind is
exceptionally sweet tonight!
There's no way I'm stoppin'!
Y-You want a race? Bastard!
Ah... This rain
sucks, doesn't it?
So, who you waiting for?
Your boyfriend?
Your husband?
You'll freeze if you
hang around here.
Hey, why don't you forget your
boyfriend and come with me.
I'll find us a warm place.
I can buy you a nice dinner.
Good answer, little lady.
H-Hey! W-Wait up!
What's going on here?
There's nothing here.
Is that what you think?
Wh-What's going on here?
Why, have you forgotten?
That's so insensitive of you...
considering you're the
very man responsible for this.
Recently, there have
been a string of women
gone missing in
Elahnay City...
Each one of them was
picked up by some guy
and treated to dinner,
then spent a night with him
at a hotel, and ultimately
went missing when he brought
them to this abandoned building.
Oh come on...
you think I did this?
Give me a break.
Do I look like the
kind of human being
who'd do something like that?
You don't look
like a human being.
I prefer you in this form!
Impressive skills...
Who the hell are you guys?
My associate and I represent
the Highway Department.
We've been searching for
you for some time now.
The female Devil Hunter.
The one we've heard about
who takes out any
adversary without fail...
Miss Lady...
And your real name would be...
What do you want from me?
We might have...
a little job for you.
Unbelievable! Guys'
places are such a mess!
No one's going to want to
come to a sty like this,
much less any clients...
Mr. Dante!
It's a customer! Hello!
Yeah I got one basil and spicy
salami pizza, no olives...
Thanks. I'll pay you everything
I owe at the end of the month.
Pizza again...?
So when do you think clients
will start coming today?
I suppose... I probably better
decorate the outside too.
Give me a break.
You saw the pizza boy's
reaction didn't you?
Nobody who comes here can
appreciate your fancy tastes.
Just put everything back
the way it was and shut up.
Welcome come on in!
Hmmm...
Seems like your sense of
style has improved a lot
since we last met.
Hasn't it, Dante?
And then you...
if I'm not mistaken
would be Patty Lowell...
Huh? How do you know?
Am I famous or a kind of
celebrity or something?
The little girl hanging
around the "Devil May Cry"
has become quite the subject
of gossip in this town...
But it's not like
you came all this way
just to have a look at
this brat, now is it?
What are you here for?
If it's about some job,
thanks, but no thanks.
I see you're as
cold as always...
Cuz the only jobs you
bring me are shit jobs.
And they don't pay.
That's a fine way to talk.
Are you aware of how much money
you owe me? Don't you get it?
I'm here today to collect.
You're the detective. You
should've figured that out.
Whoa, Lady. I think you're
the one who doesn't get it.
I'm so deep in debt I
can't even keep track.
I couldn't pay you back
now even if I wanted to.
Which I don't.
Well, I was aware of that at
any rate. What can you do?
How about a bet?
If I put the 8 ball in,
you take the job I got
for you unconditionally.
Are you game?
You can never do things
the simple way, can you?
It's a deal.
And if you miss, you forgive my
debt and pay me 20,000 in cash.
Done.
That was great!
Shit. Alright...
Dammit.
You should just be a hustler,
you'd make more cash,
donch'ya think?
Just hitting a ball
doesn't do it for me.
I have a need to
annihilate and destroy.
So... who's the poor
sonofabitch this time?
Demons... of course.
What the hell is this?
There is no way in
hell these morons
can be the demons you
were telling me about.
Look.
As far as the Highway
Department is concerned,
these guys are real demons.
Are ya scared?
Don't mess with me.
Why would a "Demon
Hunter" waste time
taking out a bunch of bikers?
And that's exactly
why I'm giving the job
to a jack-of-all-trades
like you.
Because I don't know what the
Highway Department was thinking,
but they came to me
with the job, so I...
The hell with this.
I'm going home.
Huh? What's wrong?
I can't use swords or guns
when dealing with humans.
In a way, they're more of a
pain in the ass to deal with
than real demons.
And to make matters worse,
they won't listen to a
goddamn word I say. Bye.
I mean really...
Who needs words or weapons
to deal with these pansies?
Follow me.
Well... Is he here yet?
No luck.
Might as well just
forget about it.
What?! I dare you
to say that again!
Say it!
Knock it off.
Who do you think you are, honey?
I'm not interested in talking to
you guys where's your leader?
What the hell is your problem?
I'm Vincent, the leader.
What do you want?
Don't mean to bust the party but
you guys need to hit the road.
What are you talking about?
We do what we want,
where we want!
See? Like I said...
Talking to losers
who don't even know
what a pain in the ass they
are is a waste of time. Bye.
What did you say?!
I'm sorry about the
inconvenience to you guys,
but would you let us
do our thing for now?
There's this asshole
that I'm looking for
that I have to fight.
My older brother ran
against him 3 weeks ago...
and got killed.
This guy's a legend
on the highway,
and everyone who's run
against him is dead.
And come hell or highway
I will avenge my brother!
So you and your girl here
need to move on or else.
What a load of crap...
If you ask me your
brother getting killed
racing others around
is dumb enough...
But you're dumber than he is...
for trying to get
revenge for his death.
What'd you say!?
Hold on. If you want to
pick a fight so bad...
--Why don't you race him?
--Huh?
If you lose you and your crew
leave this place quietly.
Hey, Lady! What do you
think you're doing?
It's fine, isn't it? If you win,
your job's finished.
and the money will be all yours.
Wait a damn minute! I'm not--
This guy you're talking about,
his name's "Red Eye", correct?
Well if you race him...
chances are this Red Eye
will probably
show up, won't he?
Maybe...
Here you go.
I don't need it.
Didn't think you would.
Me either!
H-Hey dude, what are you doing?
That's crazy...!
And you... What're
you up to exactly?
Oh, come on now...
Don't say it like that.
All I'm doing is trying
to take care of you
so you don't end up
starving to death.
Shit... In for a penny,
in for a pound.
I guess I'll have to stick
around a little longer.
Here, I probably
won't be needing this.
Probably not.
At least not right now...
How do you like that?
You're gonna have a hard
time avenging your brother
if you ride that slow.
Shit!
Look at you!
This race is all mine!
See ya back at the
Sands, ya dickhead.
He's got nitros! Idiot!
Brother!
Don't be stupid don't do it!
Brother!!
Stop!
Brother! Brother!
Can't stop now!
Not when the wind's this good!
That sound!
What are you trying to do,
going this far to
follow your brother?
I shoulda known...
That was her plan all along.
Alright then...!
Shit!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
You called me 'cause you knew
you couldn't take
this thing out.
Not on your own anyway!
Well, if you already knew that.
Then what are you
waiting for? Go get him.
You make it sound so easy.
What's wrong?
Is it too hard for you?
Nope, easy as can be!
Haven't you learned that
speeding causes accidents?
My Brother...
My Brother!
You had plans to
use me all along.
Sorry. Actually
this is the real job
the Highway Department
wanted to have done.
Girl's gotta do what
a girl's gotta do.
You can never do things
the simple way, can you?
Maybe. But you can't ever
simply do what I ask you.
You're damn right I wouldn't.
Brother!
Brother...
Brother... Brother!
Even with this room
put back the way it was,
I still don't see any clients.
I'm all about a one-day
workweek, little drummer girl.
And I should be getting paid for
that recent job any day now...
When you say recent job,
do you mean the devil
on the motorcycle thing?
Yep. After all, I am
the one who ended up
getting rid of
the Highway demon.
And Lady's negotiating
with the Highway Department
to get us a big wad of cash.
Here we go!
I was waiting to hear from you!
Oh, about the money...
What? You added it to my debt?
Yeah.
Of course you and I got paid for
taking care of old Red Eye.
But there might've been
a few other charges.
Like repairing that
city bridge you tore up.
What? Our pay?
Well naturally, I'll just
deduct it from what you owe me.
What? Just a goddamn--
Shit! That woman...
You're the most unlucky guy
I've ever met. You know that?
Shut up.
Here you go!
That lady friend of yours
told me that your office
was down here...so I thought
I'd drop by to say "thanks."
So, thank you, man.
If I had kept on like
I was, I'd be dead too.
For some reason I
thought I heard him...
The voice of my brother saying,
"It'd be a waste
for you to die."
I'm done chasing the
memory of my brother.
From this day on, I'm gonna
ride for me and me alone.
That's why I gotta ask.
Would you please race
me just one more time?
Let's make a little bet.
A bet?
If none of the balls
go in, I'll race you...
But if I sink the 8 ball...
The 8 ball...
Then you buy me dinner.
There are people out
there who would say that
there's nothing more
important than love.
But is love really that great?
There are women who,
because of love,
get chased around by men.
And there are men that, because
of love, get killed by women.
To boil it down,
for love to be so great,
there's gotta be something else
behind it that's even greater.
But I'm not going to
tell you what that is.
It's not my style.
Check out the next
Mission: "Not Love."