If I miss my curfew...
father will yell at me again!
Ow...
Are you okay there?
Um... yeah...
I'm okay I think
I might have just
sprained it a little,
that's all...
Just stay still.
What...?
I want you to try standing up.
It doesn't hurt anymore...
That's good.
Ah, I can put my
shoes on myself...
There you go.
What did you do? Was that
some trick? Or magic?
Bye.
Please wait!
What's your name?
I'm Bradley.
Bradley...
Can we... meet again?
I'm so sorry, Brad!
Do you understand me Angelina?!
I forbid you to see
that man anymore!
Why!? Brad is
such a good person!
I don't care.
You are not to meet him!
And you'll stay in this room
until you promise
me that you won't!
This is for your own good.
I'm counting on you.
I understand, sir.
This darn thing!
Hey, keep it down...
You can mess around with
that broken TV all day...
But it's not like some genie's
gonna pop out and fix it for ya.
And today's is the
final episode...
Well, that's too bad...
Me, I'm bummed because my
nap's been interrupted...
Go and buy a new one now!
If I had the cash...
How in the world do you blow
through all your money so fast?!
I got that devil woman
that's taking all my money
and a tightfisted
bastard for an agent...
You can look for some
change in the couch if want.
Hey, who ya callin tightfisted?
You here with some more jobs
that won't make me
any more money?
Nope. You know me. I only
bring you the jobs that pay out.
On the condition that
they're done right.
Hey, Morrison...
Can you fix a TV?
A TV?
It's broken,
and today's the last episode
of "Bolero in Spring"!
You got your car
here today, Morrison?
Yeah.
I'll take the job if you let me
get some sleep in it on the way.
I've been losing sleep
due to that broken TV.
What are you waitin'
for? Let's go.
I don't care where,
just as long as I don't have
to hear her whining anymore.
Good day, Miss.
You're not going to fix the TV,
Morrison? I need my fix.
You can have Dante buy you one
with the money he
makes from this job.
Wait, Morrison!
That won't be in time
for the last episode
of "Bolero in Spring"!
Hey! You jerks!
Come back here!
Miss, your father wanted me to
tell you your meal is ready.
I don't want anything to eat...
Please Miss...
If you don't eat something
I'm going to be in
trouble with your father.
This is a pretty swank pad.
What kind of racket does he run
to afford something like this?
He's the mayor of Capulet
City, so try to be nice.
Gentlemen!
Hello, sorry I'm late.
That meeting dragged out longer
than I thought it would...
Thanks you so much for coming.
I'm Mike Hagel.
I'm Morrison.
Nice to meet you.
Look, counselor, how about
we all cut the formalities
and get down to business
before I fall asleep again?
That's him?
You got my word. He's good...
Even if he is a little
rough around the edges...
I want you... to kill this man.
Please...
Kill him.
I've got a daughter,
my only child... Angelina.
My wife died a long
time ago, and since then
I've raised my little
darling all on my own.
My daughter means
everything to me.
And this Brad
guy is planning on
taking my daughter away
from this town and from me!
I won't allow this
worthless drifter to just
run off with my daughter
because he feels like it.
Surely you gentlemen
can understand that?
I mean, it's my only child.
My baby girl.
And so... you want to kill him?
Well that sure makes
for a grand story...
Turn it into a soap opera
and Patty would love it.
I smell ratings.
Um... Um, Miss...
You know the rules.
I should at least be able
to use the washroom alone.
Haven't you heard that
there's some killer
running around loose
in Capulet City?
It's been all over in the news.
Had your head under
a rock or something?
My TV's broken, remember?
Oh yeah, I forgot.
At any rate,
there's been a lot of ugly
little incidents around here.
This is it.
These murders are so hideous.
So gruesome there are even
some people saying that
the culprit isn't human.
So he's not human?
These random assaults
started happening
right around the time
this Brad guy showed up.
So you're saying...
that this "Brad"
isn't just a murderer,
but a devil in disguise?
That's a little hard to
swallow. I don't buy it.
I saw it with my own eyes.
There's no doubt about it.
He's a demon!
This job's right up your alley,
don't you think, Dante?
I'm begging you!
Kill this Brad!
Brad...
Brad!
Please! Let's run
away together! Please.
What's wrong with you, darling?
Try to calm yourself down
and tell me what's going on.
Brad... Listen to me...
I think my father has hired
someone... to kill you!
To kill me?
But why would he...
try to kill me?
Because of your strange power.
My father thinks you're a devil!
He must have seen you do
something. I don't know what.
Does he now?
We can run away.
Let's leave here!
My dear Angelina...
I'm sorry, but I can't let you
get wrapped up in all of this.
But I...
I don't you to worry about me
in the slightest, Angelina.
I'm going to be alright.
I promise you.
Someday your father
will understand too...
But, Brad!
You should be going home now.
I'm glad I could see you.
Mind if I grab a seat?
Huh?
Yeah, I don't mind.
Go right ahead.
I'll take a beer...
...and a pizza.
Any kind... As long as it
doesn't have any olives.
Go about your reading.
Don't mind me at all.
Oh, thanks... I believe I will.
What? You still can't
find Angelina!
Don't even think about
coming back here until you do!
Is she at that greasy
bastard's place again?
I offer you my deepest
apologies, Sir.
This is all because I took
my eyes off her. Please--
Miss, you're back!
Father I...
Do you understand me?!
From now on your meals
will brought to your room,
and you'll be watched
everywhere you go!
Oh... my Brad...
What's this book
you're all into?
It's a romance novel actually.
Hmmm... any good?
Yeah, really good.
One person's love for
another is a wonderful thing.
True love is a thing of beauty!
You find that strange?
No.
One beer.
Well it sure took you long
enough to get me just a beer...
And my pizza?
They're making it now.
Damn...
Drink up.
Uh, yeah... To you...
By the way, you seem
kind of like a drifter...
Where you from?
Okay. You don't have to
answer if you don't want to.
Well, I'm going to
be on my way now.
Here's your pizza.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey, there's olives
on this thing...
Of course there are.
Dammit.
Everyone has been saying that
the gate will open tonight!
Will it, now?
But to leave the
living world like this
would kind of be a shame...
So I guess it's you then...
who's responsible for
that string of murders?
I'm very fond...
of the warm and tasty
blood of the living ones...
Who did that!?
Did you follow me?
Eating a large pizza
in five minutes...
That's a new personal
record for me.
Don't you mess with me!
That's some handshake
ya got there.
You're as strong as I'd heard.
That almost makes it sound
like you know all about me.
I've been in the living world
for over a month now.
I've heard the rumors about
Dante, "The Devil Hunter."
So I guess I can take
that as a confession
that you're not human, right?
Yes.
Well, then I guess
you've got no objections.
No. And I tell you the truth,
I have no intention
of running away.
But there is one thing that
I would like to ask of you.
What's that?
I heard that you're
a half-breed...
Born from the union
of a human and a demon.
If that's so, can you tell me...
Were your parents in love?
Was there a love between
human and demon?
Who knows? You always hear
stories about the lovers.
They look like they were
made for each other,
but inside their hearts
are cold as ice.
That's not what I--
But I think a lot of those
couples truly loved each other.
Deep inside their hearts.
You think so?
Was that all you wanted to say?
Yeah.
I almost thought you
were gonna try to pull
a surprise attack on me...
I know I can't defeat you.
You're kind of a wimp for
being a demon you know that?
Even though I am a demon...
there's no way I could
vanquish an opponent like you.
Besides... my role here is
finished. I'll be leaving.
What do you mean by that?
Tonight, my master will arrive.
He will come from the demon
world into this plane.
I was summoned by a
human to prepare the way.
I have done his bidding
my job is over now.
And why are you telling
me this exactly?
Maybe because...
I want you to put
an end to all this...
My master is greedy...
I'm sure that he will try
to devour this entire city.
That café with the
wonderful coffee...
And the hill with
such a beautiful view
of the setting sun...
Everything...
And Angelina too?
What should I do?
I don't want to lose her...
She was so kind to me.
I've always been treated so
cruelly in the demon world...
But she'd smile at me...
And I don't want to think
about the possibility
of her being devoured
by my master...
But I'm... I'm just one demon...
I don't have the power
to defy my master...
It's true, you're pretty
pathetic... for a demon.
But if you can love
Angelina that much,
you'll be able to
live as a human.
A... human? You mean it?
Get up and let's go.
Got a little welcome for your
friend when he comes to town.
Father? Father, what's happend?!
Father!
Father?!
Father! Father!
Father!
Hang on, Father!
Don't move.
If you had just stayed in
your room like a good girl,
you could have died
without having to feel fear.
You... Why would you do this?
Soon the powerful
demon will be summoned
to this city by the
ritual I have performed.
Together we shall
destroy this world!
Dante!
Sorry. I guess I knocked
a little too hard...
I had a bad
feeling about you
from the moment I saw
you with the mayor.
But, you're too late I'm afraid!
Angelina!
Brad!
Mr. Mayor! Hold on!
What are you doing?!
Are you actually planning
to betray Belphagor?!
You're already too late!
The great Belphagor will
be here any moment now.
I'm sure it must have been
a long, hard trip for ya...
It's too bad entry to
this world is off limits
for the likes of you.
So, I just gonna have
to ask you to leave!
Angelina!
Father!
What is this...?
Don't try to speak.
Just lie still, Father.
Brad, can you please help him?
I've never tried it on a
wound as serious as this.
I'll do everything I can though.
What... do you think you're
doing to me... you demon...
Do you really think...
that by doing this for me...
I'm going to allow you...
to see... my daughter?
Father!
Don't worry yourself.
That is not what I'm
concerned about, sir.
No, I'm doing this
simply because
I don't want to
see Angelina sad...
Sorry Mr. Mayor,
But it doesn't look
like I'm going to be able
to grant your request.
Brad understands love.
He's gonna make it just
fine as a human being.
And the only things I personally
choose to exterminate
are demons.
Hey Morrison, didn't
you get it fixed yet...?
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
How much longer am I
going to have to wait!?
Just wait a little bit longer,
okay? I've almost got it here.
By the way, I've been
meaning to tell you, Dante...
It's a nice story
about how those two
finally got her dad's approval.
But I don't see how your
passing up the money
should result in
my fixing this TV...
My days of TV repair
are long gone.
Less talking and more fixing!
My afternoon soap
opera's about to start!
You fixed it!
I'll just deduct my repair
fees from your next payment.
Whatever...
Oh, for the love of...
At this rate you'll never
get your debt paid off,
no matter how many good
jobs I bring you...
But you seem happy, Dante...
Even though you usually
do nothing but complain
when you don't get your money...
You complain a lot!
Every now and then there
are days like this...
I sure hope those two
will be happy, don't you?
I've always had pretty
bad luck with women...
I'd be lucky if
they'd just beat me up.
But they also do things like
stick swords in my stomach,
and shoot me in the forehead...
If I wasn't who I am,
I'd probably be dead.
Damn... To make matters worse,
the women that do those
things are the very women
that I can't seem to
boot out of my life.
I wonder when my luck
with women will improve...
Next Mission: "Rolling Thunder."