I'll show you the
power of Abigail.
It's over. Abigail is back,
sealed away no longer.
The world is coming to an end.
Hey, what the hell's going on?
What is that light?
It's so pretty.
Dante...
Lady! What are you doing here?
Looks like it's finally started.
What's finally started, Lady?
Who's Alan Lowell?
Once upon a time, there was a
powerful alchemist by that name.
He might have been just a human,
but he was also a sorcerer
who just so happened to
employ various demons.
You mean to tell me
that was Alan Lowell?
Right.
Lowell...
There was just one demon
that Alan couldn't
bend to his employment.
And that was Abigail,
the demon said to have
powers on par with
the demon king's.
Using every bit of
power he possessed,
Alan successfully sealed
away Abigail's powers.
But seal them away
was all he did.
He was unable to
accomplish any more.
So to prevent Abigail's powers
from falling into
anyone's hands,
Alan constructed many magical
barriers and spread them around.
Barriers so tight, even a single
ant couldn't pass through.
Something came into
being during the process
of making those barriers:
the magic stone, "Alan's Tear."
You know more about that than
anyone else, right, Nina Lowell?
Do you know how long I
protected that magic stone?
It was an age-old
responsibility.
That pendant could unlock
the seal on Abigail...
All I could do was run.
Run and keep on running.
Why didn't you try to do
anything about the pendant
before you spent ten years
running from all this?
What was I supposed to do?
Throw away a pendant that
can summon the demons of hell?
And yet, even if you
destroyed the stone,
all it would do is
just break the seal.
Either way, it's all over.
The seal on the pendant
has already been broken.
With Abigail's powers on
his side, no one can stop him.
Because I'm afraid
that Alan Lowell...
...is no longer in this world
walking among the
living anymore.
Then what about Dante?
It's impossible! No matter
how strong he may be,
there's no way he could
defy Abigail's power.
Watch out!
Hurry up and get going.
Get your ass in gear and
get the hell out of here!
There's no point
in running away.
He won't be stopped now.
No one can stop him!
Looks like he's shown himself.
Jesus! What is that thing?!
And that would be Abigail...
What is that?!
It looks like the end
of the world. Christ.
Hey, hold it there, Patty!
Where do you think you're going?
Let me go! Let me go, Lady!
What are you going to do?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm going to go get Dante!
That's crazy.
--You'll get yourself killed!
--I don't care if I do!
Patty!
Wait. I'll go too!
You...
Honestly! All he does
is give me trouble.
I'll leave the rest to you!
What do you mean by that?!
What do you think about
placing a little bet?
The two descendants
of Alan Lowell...
A "little miracle" might happen.
I didn't think you're type
to believe in miracles...
Yeah... in this case, I agree.
I might want to start to want
to believe in miracles, myself.
Patty! Don't go
charging on ahead of us!
It's no good, we can't
get through this.
But if we don't
get through here,
we can't get to the
south wing's top floor...
There has to be a manual control
for the sprinklers somewhere.
You wait here. I'll be back.
I'm sorry.
I didn't imagine that something
this bad would ever happen; I...
Mommy?
No, I'm sorry, Patty.
I'm so sorry...
Oh, my darling Patty.
My poor little girl!
I'm so sorry, Patty...
...for leaving you so
alone all these years.
Mommy...
Well, this beats me.
A little cooler
in here now, huh...
How many more of these small
fries do we have to fight?
My, are you tired already?
Oh yeah, right.
How nice for you.
It looks like this fry
isn't quite so small.
Well, not small in body, anyway.
Shit, when I think about how
I'm not gonna get paid for this,
just makes me want to cry!
Why not send Dante a bill
when this is all done?
Sure, that is if
he's still alive.
Awfully quiet, isn't it?
So, what are we supposed to do?
I don't know either.
What do you mean you don't know?
Isn't there a rite or
a spell or something?
Dante...
Patty!
Dante!
What's with those damn demons?
Patty... That pendant
you have...
--Patty!
--Hey, wait, Patty!
What the hell's going on here?
Where did Patty go?
The demon realm, I would think.
The demon realm?
But the pendant Patty has
contains a shard of Alan's Tear.
It doesn't have as much
power as Alan's Tear,
but it should be enough
magic to protect her.
Dante...
Where are you, Dante?
This way?
Man, there's just no
end to these things!
Agreed. And it looks like he's
creating these minions, so...
So basically, if we
don't take him out,
this'll just keep on going?
Probably.
Hey, how about
lending me a hand?
Pretty pathetic, huh?
So basically we just have
to rely on him, is that it?
Dante!
Dante! Dante!
Dante...
Dante!
Dante, wake up! Run away!
I'll get that out
of you right now.
There's no way you'd die of
a little wound like this,
right, Dante?
Please, wake up!
And then take down the
demons like you always do!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
It's my fault, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Dante.
Are you mad at me?
But I don't want this!
I can't stand to have
this be our goodbye!
I... I haven't even
said thank you yet!
It was so much fun getting to
be with you, but I haven't...
Dante! Dante, please,
open your eyes!
I won't get mad at you for
messing up your office anymore!
And I won't eat your strawberry
sundaes without asking, either!
Please!
Dante!
Dante...
There's no need to be
afraid, little lady.
I just wanted to
say "thank you."
After all, thanks to you,
I was able to get enough
power to rule the world.
Hmph, you're no match for Dante.
When he comes he'll
take you down for sure!
Dante's dead, girl.
There's no way
Dante would die
at the hands of
someone like you.
Mommy... Morrison...
Run, Patty...
Dante!
What?!
Is it... Is it
really you, Dante?
You know another man
as good lookin' as I am?
The correct answer
is no by the way.
Dante, you're hurt...
Oh, this?
It looks like a certain someone
was playing a trick on me.
While I was having myself
a nice little nap.
Perfect timing. The rest
of the show is adults-only.
Well Patty...
If I'm not mistaken,
this is one time I might owe
you a little "thank you."
You wait there.
As a reward, I'll give him
a good lashing from you.
After I deliver mine, that is.
Anybody who pulls
pranks like this
needs to be taught a lesson.
Morrison, I'll leave
the rest to you.
Damn, you make me wait forever,
and then you go making
selfish requests...
Sorry.
It looks like it's
finally going to begin.
Shit, Dante sure
took his sweet time!
Hey... You've grown
since I last saw you.
I'm gonna pay you back.
Make no mistake.
Can you?
After all, right now I
have enough power to rule
even the human world,
let alone the demon one.
I've had just about enough
of your arrogant attitude...
You ugly prick.
Child's play like
this is all you got?
You continually
disappoint me, Sid.
Th-This can't be!
You can grow as big as you want.
And you can get
as ugly as you want.
You can even get yourself
world-dominating power,
but I tell ya Sid...
...it's pointless!
What now?!
Wh-Why? Why can't I win?!
I got power that was
top-class in the demon world!
I don't care how strong you are,
something is wrong
with this picture!
Dammit, this is totally unfair!
Is it decided from the
moment we're born, then?!
That demons born
without much power
are fated to be
stamped out by you?!
I can't believe that!
If this is how things are,
no matter what I do,
it's meaningless...
That's not it. It's about souls.
Huh?
Basically, here's
the story, Sid.
Someone like you
who's let his soul rot
can't measure up just
by getting some power.
Not to someone with a real soul.
That's not how it
works down here.
Well then, Lord Dante of the
strong and gentle "real soul,"
you'll let me live
even now, won't you?
Just like you have before.
No can do. You went too far.
But you know, I kinda liked you.
Y-You bastard!
And jackpot.
Dante!
Hey, now, go easy on me.
I'm injured, you know.
S-Sorry.
--Patty.
--Huh?
You're gonna be staying with
your mother from here on out.
I want you to have a
happy life. You got it?
Hey, Morrison,
drive me to the office.
Your car will still move, right?
You're such a slave driver.
I'm injured here too for
your information, Dante!
I see someone's in a bad mood.
Patty's departure really
did a number on you, huh?
What do you want?
Don't be stupid.
There's only one reason
I'd come all the way
over to your office, right?
Then hurry up and
tell me the deal.
You can cut the small
talk, thank you very much.
Apparently a large number
of demons have showed up
in a certain country.
It's a sweet job.
The client's filthy rich,
so the pay will be good.
I hear little Patty's doing
pretty well with her mom.
Sorry, hot stuff.
But I'm on my way to a job.
I really don't have time to
hang out with you right now.
My, what a coincidence.
We too are on our way
to another job as well.
I believe we're all
going to the same place.
So, in other words...
The payment for
this lucrative job...
...goes to the fastest
one, of course!
Fine, bring it on ladies!
Go ahead Morrison, floor it.
I knew it.
Really, that Dante trashes the
place as soon as I'm not around!