Hey. So what's
the problem, baby?
Get it.
That was fast.
I figured you'd be
coming in sometime soon.
Kinda hard to believe you've
been waiting for me too long.
I missed you so much.
Fredi, could you come here?
Hey, hang on! Cindy!
Hush! If you keep bothering me,
I'll never get any work done!
What's your problem with me?
To be honest...
I don't really care
for guys who keep
trying to chase after me.
Actually, I'm the type of girl
who likes to do the chasing!
What are you talking about...?
So tell me what kind of guy
you're looking for then, baby.
A real he-man! I like 'em
wild, sexy, and intelligent!
But still kind to women
and always relaxed.
And he's gotta be
to die-for cute.
A real head-turner...
just like Dante is!
Dante?
Him.
If you could become just
a little more like Dante...
I might think about
going out with you!
Hey, Cindy!
That guy? She thinks
he's a real man?
I don't get it...
So just what does Cindy see
in a guy like that anyway?
What the...?
Did I...? I guess
I drank too much...
She's not here!
What gives?
Where'd that woman go?!
What's his deal?
Hey dude! Hey! Whassup?
Cindy, forget about that guy!
My god! what happened
to your face?!
Ow!
Cindy. Listen up.
And listen good.
That Dante guy is no "real man."
He's nothing but a pervert!
Forget you ever met him.
What?
I saw it with my own eyes!
He went right into the girls'
restroom! What gives?!
What are you talking about?
Cindy! What I'm saying is...
he picked up some girl
took her to the women's
restroom and...
Ow!
Hey, what gives?
God dammit.
Dammit... I swear I'm going
to get the dirt on you.
Hey, What d'ya think
you're doing?!
Uh, n-n-nothing...
Looks like business
is slow as always, eh?
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Let's just see it.
Now, take it easy.
Look, here we go.
You watch your back.
Heh... Like you give a shit...
What the hell are you doing
here, Dante? Hit the road.
I came to give you
a little message...
"You guys don't need
to be messing with
a little thing like
this, now do you?"
No way! He's going to
take on the Mafia?!
Holy shit! He really did...
Jesus Christ!
Who is this maniac?!
He's gotta be crazy!
He's out of his mind!
Stay away from that guy!
He's a heartless,
cold-blooded killer!
It doesn't matter even if
it's the Mafia or whoever!
That dude will even
kill people for money!
It wouldn't matter
if you had nine lives!
If you're with that guy,
you'll just get used up,
Cindy, trust me.
You'll wind up
riddled with holes!
He said "riddled with holes."
We should tell someone, Ted!
No, wait! You're
misunderstanding me!
Cindy!
Just go home.
Ah, don't be that way...
What gives? The door
isn't even locked...
This is what I should have
done in the first place.
I don't care what it is...
I just need to find
something that will
land this freak in the slammer.
I could make your
wish come true.
It's my imagination...
No... I'm the only
one fit for that job.
You despise Dante,
right?! Me too!
You gotta let me out of here!
You?! What the hell
could you do?!
I'll make this worth
your while, little boy.
Let me out of here, and I'll--
Don't listen to those morons!
Me, I'm the one you need! Yes.
I'm the one who found
this guy! So get lost!
Hey! Let me out of here!
I'll make your wish come true.
What the hell were
those things?!
They're devils.
Wh-Who are you?!
I don't think you've
got the right to ask
since you're the one who's
broken into someone's house.
I... That's...
Just relax, my friend.
I won't tell Dante about this.
You want to know...
Know the real truth
about Dante, do you not?
Huh?
If that's the case...
I've got something for you.
What gives? What is this?
Don't ask. Just take it and go.
When you open it, you'll
know what Dante really is.
Dante?
You're home, aren't you?
Morrison told me about it.
It's sounds like you've made
a bunch of money, haven't you?
Hey, it's true, Cindy!
You gotta believe me! I promise!
I swear I saw it
with my own eyes!
That dude isn't
normal. He's crazy!
There's something
really weird about him!
He's weird?
You broke into Dante's place!
And when Dante
wasn't even there!
That? Well that was...
just because...
It's 'cause I wanted you to
know that he's dangerous, baby!
Shame on you!
Why did things turn
out like this?
Dammit, that hurt!
What the...?
Dammit!
Trying to make me look stupid...
My family have been pacifists
since my grandfather's time,
but not any more!
Well, it's just a little kitty!
It's all right. Come on...
It's not like I'm going
to eat you or anything...
Who is it?
Who's that over there?!
What the hell is that?!
There he is!
You idiot. Get outta here!
Nice timing there, ya dickhead.
Seems that lately
I've had nothing to fight
but a bunch of weaklings.
I've been wanting to
go up against someone
that can give me
a little workout!
A... A de... It's a demon...
All bark and no bite...
It's true!
You gotta believe me, Cindy!
--Cindy, listen!
--Isaac!
I saw that dude hack
a demon in two
with this big sword
that he carries!
Listen!
He's a demon! It's true!
That guy's a demon himself!
A demon, I tell ya!
That's the only
explanation for all this!
I cannot believe you!
It's after noon and I'd swear
you're still asleep
and dreaming!
Nonsense! I didn't
dream up any of this!
How can I make you believe me?
Come in, Dante. The usual?
Hey, settle down!
So, who's that?
Your little boyfriend?
Well...something about
him made me actually
think about maybe dating him.
But he's been acting like a
stalking psychopath lately.
Maybe he kind of misunderstood
that comment I made
the other day.
I mean the only thing
I meant was that
I'd wish he was a little
more like you are, Dante.
It looks like he took what I was
saying totally out of context.
And now he says I should
stay away from you
'cause you're a demon!
Well he's got things
about half right...
And get a load of this, Dante.
He swears he saw you
kill a demon last night.
Isn't that crazy?
I mean it's so stupid.
It's just that I wanted to
be the one to chase him...
Oh, I'm sorry!
I'll be right with you.
Yep, that's right.
You can be a little
devil, you know that?
Who's the devil?!
You'd be a lot better
off giving me money
to pay off what you owe me,
rather than having
me take it from you
'cause you lost at pool.
Are you saying you're
really that far in debt?
I mean, and some
weirdo man's been
spying on you
office lately, too.
A weird man?
Mm-hmm. But he seemed
like a total wussy wimp,
so I got rid of him pronto!
That reminds me... there was
some visitor in your office
when I had stopped
by recently, too.
A visitor?
Dammit!
U-Um... behind you...
Look out behind you!
Dante...
Dante!
You called?
You ready?
Cuz it looks like now...
this party's just
getting started.
N-No, stop!
Stop! What are you
doin' man? What gives?
All right, bring it on!
Just a minute.
You forgot something.
If you're going to skip town...
you should at least
let her know about it.
If you don't, she can't chase
you, even if she wants to.
What do you mean by that?
Why don't you ask her yourself?
You mean... you came to...
just to tell me that?
I'm just a demon, man.
I just hadn't had
my fill of fun yet.
Dante!
What are you?
I mean, who are you?
Who knows... Maybe you should
try asking God or someone...
I'll have what he's having!
Huh?
I said I want one of those too!
All right!
Fredi, one strawberry sundae!
So what, are you planning
on eating with me?
Mmm-hmnm.
There you go.
Okay. One strawberry sundae
with extra berries. Enjoy!
You're kinda making me
lose my appetite, dude.
I'm not sure when it started,
but before I knew it, I was
always listening to her songs.
Tougher than any man,
softer than any woman,
she sings of the sadness
in human hearts.
If I ever get to meet her,
I'll probably thank her.
Because she
made me realize that
even I have enough emotional
depth to understand songs.
Keep on playing.
Next Mission: "Rock Queen."