Wow! This is amazing.
You would never
know we're on a ship.
This is the renowned official
casino ship of Port Verlington.
Along with the casino, there
are restaurants, a pool bar,
a health spa and everything
else you can ever want.
All those people
are all gamblers?
Oh, no... Most of them
are just moderately rich
with too much free time
and looking to have
a night of dreams
and excitement.
By the way, where is Dante?
I don't see him anywhere.
This way.
Two pairs.
My apologies, but I
believe this hand is mine.
Three of a kind.
Dammit...
Well, no big deal...
This game's just
getting underway.
The fun's just beginning.
Yes. I'm looking forward to it.
The longer one gambles, the
more interesting it becomes...
The same as a kiss.
If you're able to beat me,
I'll give you a nice, long kiss,
the likes of which
you've never experienced.
Now that's something
to look forward to.
I'd better be careful not to
lose the clothes off my back!
The man who just
won is Gold-Arm Joe,
said to have a "Golden Arm."
The woman across the
table is also well known.
They say that she has
the luck of a goddess.
She's known as "Lucky Amanda."
The older gentleman next
to her is "Santa Claus,"
a poker ace that they say
can read people's thoughts.
All these people are
trying to act so refined,
but their eyes are
burning with greed.
Alright, lets play.
Please... Save my husband, Paul.
He likes to gamble?
Yes, he was a
straight-and-narrow man
before we got married...
But then it's like he
became a different person
all of a sudden, and got
addicted to gambling.
Gambling is like a sickness.
But there's one big difference
between a gambling addiction
and getting a common cold.
There is no medicine
they've found yet
to cure yourself of it.
You might as well
just give up on him.
Please! If my husband goes on
like this, he could be killed!
Come on... Hey, don't
be so cold, Dante.
Huh?
You know, you should always be
nice to the ladies. Or try to.
I know it may not sound like it,
but this job could
be up your alley.
Huh?
Next, please.
Pass.
R-Raise. I'll raise you 500.
Fold.
I'm dropping out too.
I'll call.
Call.
Three of a kind.
Nothing.
Sorry kids, full house.
Well, if the night
keeps up like this,
I'll be going home with
a bag full of money again!
I see, so that's why
you're "Santa Claus."
It's a clever nickname.
Thank you. When tonight's
game is over,
why not let me treat
you to breakfast.
Sure. That is, as long as
you're not thrown out by then
for being flat broke.
We have quite a collection of
inflated egos here, don't we...
By the way,
have any of you heard of
a gambler known as "King"?
Yes, one hears about him
quite a lot as of late.
Apparently he's supposed
to be a gambler from hell
who takes the lives
of his opponents.
Hmph! Nothing but silly rumors!
They most definitely are.
However, it is true that a
certain number of gamblers
have died after losing to
this mysterious individual.
Some say he is a white
bearded, elderly man.
Others say "King" is a
charming, beautiful woman.
But the truth is that
no one knows for sure
what he OR she looks like.
But still if such a
person actually exists,
what would you give
to play a hand or two
with this "remarkable
competitor"? Hmm?
King?
Yes. It's said he's a
gambler who brings death.
There have been a number
of well-known gamblers
who've recently gone missing.
The only common thread is...
They all went out to play cards,
and then they never came back.
Before long there were
rumors all over the city
with people saying that
anyone that plays this "King"
will end up dead.
So, this "King"
could be a demon.
Is that what you're
saying, Morrison?
If that's true, I guess I
gotta gamble with the demon.
You'd probably be better
off not doing that.
Do you even remember how much
money you owe me right now?
I mean, you totally
suck at gambling.
Because I'm nice to
the women when I play.
Hey Dante, when are
you gonna pay out
for our game you
lost to me earlier?
I'm nice to the
women and children.
But how do I find a guy
when I don't even know
what he looks like?
If I just play cards wherever,
this it'll take forever.
And infinite amount of money.
Shut your face.
A letter?
It's an invitation to
that luxury cruise ship
turned casino operating
in the next town over.
It was sent by "King."
Since he went to the
trouble to invite us,
it would be bad
form not to accept.
And since you'll
be going anyhow,
you can grant that
woman's request.
You did say you're nice to women
and children, didn't you?
Damn.
I don't know who
this "King" guy is,
but he seems like one
stuck up son of a bitch.
That is, if anyone's asking me.
But it's interesting.
If "King" is really here
among us... and I beat him...
my reputation will
soar even higher.
Yeah, if King is among us,
I have a feeling we'll
all eventually find out.
3,000.
Fold. I'm out.
I fold as well.
I don't have enough chips.
Well then,
I guess you'll just have to
sit there and watch quietly.
I'll raise...
I'll raise 5,000.
Ohhh! The game is on!
Hey, you.
You're shaking like a leaf.
Don't you think it'd be
better for you to go home,
before you make
your pretty wife cry?
Leave me alone! Just be quiet!
Let's just see your hand.
He's holding three of a kind...
His face down card could
give him a full house...
Just to be safe...
Alright, let's play. I'm all in.
Well, it's time
for a showdown then.
Full house!
F-Four of... a kind!
I... I did it... I won! I won!
Th-That's not...
Sir?
He's dead...
Could this possibly
mean that you're "King"?
N-No!
What are you saying?
I'm... I'm...
Just take it easy...
Let's take a deep breath.
Miss, call the person in charge
and I'd like a hot
cappuccino, please.
Right away, sir.
Wherever King appears,
that place is governed
by Death's rules.
Maybe the rumors are true.
I wonder... If you're scared,
you should just head home,
get in bed, and go to sleep.
Well, aren't we arrogant...
Maybe you're "King"?
Maybe I am. But we'll
know the truth soon enough
and I bet the reveal will
be the most fun of the night.
You can have your fun,
but don't you think you're the
most likely to go broke next?
The real pleasure of gambling is
turning the tables completely
right in the final
moments of the game.
What are you talking about?!
You're losing just like
we predicted, aren't you?
You're totally
hopeless without me.
I'll take over from here.
Hey, Patty!
Interesting... It's best to
teach them just how cruel
the world can be while
they're still young.
What are you...
I didn't expect to see you here.
I heard there was a big
poker tournament on this ship,
and... and I just had to come.
Are you that worried?
I'm jealous.
It's OK. Your husband
hasn't lost anything.
You'd probably be
better off not doing that.
So you're not going to go
and see how he's doing?
No. It's not like I could
get him to stop anyway.
Alright then.
What? This child is
really playing for him?
This isn't a kid's game.
I'm not here for kids' games!
So you can lose the pompous
attitude until you beat me.
Deal the cards!
What the hell...
What's Patty doing here?
Well now that she's here,
there's nothing
we can do about it.
Shit...
So tell me, genius. Have you
figured out who this "King" is?
Not yet. I'd say
he's a clever one.
I guess the only thing
to do is keep winning.
Guess so...
But you know, it's a risky bet.
But that's what gambling's
all about, now isn't it?
Be careful.
Sure.
Come on, honey, make up your
mind. Are you in or are you out?
You seem to have aptitude,
but you've got a long way to go.
Time for a substitution.
Hey! What's going on?!
I was just getting warmed up!
This is my job.
Nice work, Patty.
I played it safe like you told
me, but these people are good.
Dante's going to
get eaten alive...
That I don't doubt at all.
But Dante's got a job to do, and
that's a game he never loses.
The only thing we can
do now sit around,
pray he succeeds, and
have a cup of coffee.
Fine then. But I'll take tea,
cause coffee's way
too bitter for me.
Okay, okay.
I fold.
Hmmm... Two pairs, eh?
She's the only one who
seems to have a decent hand.
With those cards, she could
have three of a kind...
If she does, I'm finished.
Ah, she always plays with her
hair when she's bluffing...
She's not holding three
of a kind. It's a bluff!
I'll raise 8,000 and call.
I fold.
Very smart boys.
Hold on. I'll raise 15,000
and call. I'm all in.
Trying to bring me
down with a bluff?
I see right through
you, young lady.
Fine, it's on. I'm all in.
Aww, too bad.
Looks like I got you,
Grandpa. Three of a kind.
I win.
So you did get me... Looks like
senility is setting in for me.
Please excuse me.
The loser will silently take
his leave from the stage.
Now we know for sure.
Someone here is "King."
Let's continue the game.
Interesting... But I won't lose
out to anyone with my luck.
You watch, I'll
annihilate this "King."
It's just not normal.
Don't any of these people
think they can lose?
Aren't they scared of dying?
Straight flush... I win.
This can't be!
I am known as Lucky Amanda!
There's no way could
I lose! I don't lose...
That's another one. Now it's...
Yeah. This is the end.
Well now. I guess it comes
down to you and me then.
I didn't think you'd be
left standing this long...
If I beat you here,
that would make me King!
Well come on, deal the cards!
What's with these hands?
When this is all dealt,
both could be holding
a royal straight flush!
That's not...
All in.
You're still on
your fourth card.
How about we say that whatever
happens next, we showdown?
It looks like both of us have
got a final attack to launch.
Fine... So it's all or nothing.
I accept. But I'm afraid
I'm a little low on chips.
If I lose, I'll pay the
difference with my life.
Sound good?
That's a deal.
Now come on, let's have it.
Let's see the last card!
So, it's a showdown!
A king of hearts!
That's a royal straight flush!
And Dante?!
Royal straight flush.
When two players have
the same hand, spades win.
S-Sara... I'm sorry...
He did it! Dante won, Morrison!
Morrison?
There's nothing in this
world as interesting to me
as when people are gambling...
Especially when they're
betting their lives.
It's the greatest!
Dante, what are you doing?!
This isn't over yet. Lady,
the next game's against you.
The rules are simple.
Whoever gets a bullet through
the other's heart first, wins.
Got it?
Dante...
Dante!
Stop, Dante!
Dante! Why?! Why would
you shoot him, Lady?!
He's your friend, isn't he?!
Let go of me, Morrison! Let go!
Dante...
Congratulations. I suppose
that you are tonight's winner.
It's you...
So in the end you're shot and
killed by your own friend...
It makes for quite
a beautiful ending.
Stay back! So you're
the demon... this "King"?!
You're half right
and half wrong.
What do you mean by that?
It didn't matter
who played as King.
Whoever held an item into
which I bestowed my magic...
would be captivated by gambling
in exchange for
extraordinary luck.
And that person
would act as King.
I wish this man had won for me,
but maybe I was
hoping for too much.
So it was a trap
from the beginning?
Please don't fret!
Soon, you'll be
as dead as he is.
As will those two,
and all the passengers
on the ship!
Sorry to spoil your party...
But I've been waiting
for this moment...
The moment when you show your
face to brag about your victory.
Dante!
How did you...
You're wondering if
your magic failed on me?
No, it worked just fine.
To be honest I only figured out
what was going on by chance.
Patty?
A game, Dante.
Let's play a game...
Are you going to die, or am I?
Patty?!
Stop!
And that's how I figured it out.
The watch was the
"mechanism" of King.
You were using this
to turn regular people
into King and control
them weren't you?
So you just pretended to
be possessed by its magic?
No, I was entirely
possessed by it.
I knew it was the only
way to keep winning
and stay in the game to the end.
And ultimately I'd draw you out.
It was a gamble.
I avoided hitting your heart
as promised, didn't I?
Actually you grazed it a bit.
Damn...
I've got a lesson for you.
Successful gambling is
something you can't do
without an accomplice!
My, my, you're a tough one.
Okay then... How about
something like this?
Dante!
King of hearts.
Ace of spades.
I win.
So basically, it was
all part of your plan.
You letting yourself
be possessed,
then having Lady snap you out
of it if push came to shove?
Hey, I said I was
sorry already, didn't I?
Don't sweat the
small stuff, kid.
Come on, you guys.
Let's do this.
Sure are confident.
Must have some good cards there?
Hmmm... I'll pass this time.
I'll take three.
All right...
let's see who's got what.
A full house!
How do you like that?
Royal straight flush.
I win.
We'll just add your
losses to your debt.
Damn...
The hell with this.
My father betrayed demonkind,
and fought for mankind.
From the human perspective,
he's a legendary hero.
In the minds of the demons,
he's the perpetrator of
an unforgivable crime.
But... There may have
been some demons out there
who could understand
my father's thinking.
If there really is
such a demon out there,
I'd sure like to meet him.
Next Mission,
"The Last Promise."