What'll it be?
Strawberry sundae.
This is a bar, Mister.
No place for a kid.
Really?
Just tryin' to sweeten
up the air in here.
Smells like shit.
Or more like...blood.
That's fine with me...
What I'm interested in
is this rumor I heard.
They say that somewhere
around here there's some bar.
More like a dive.
A place where they'll
take someone's life
in place of money.
Kinda scary.
Sorry. Forgive me pal.
Royal Straight Flush, is it?
Laying a hand like
that could kill a guy.
How about... I buy you a round?
Not bad, Mr. Royal Flush.
The next time you open up shop,
don't forget to add strawberry
sundaes to the menu.
Bingo.
Yeah, my usual pizza.
The special with prosciutto and
garlic potatoes. And rush it.
What, my tab?
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Soon, I'll pay you
everything I owe ya.
Oh yeah no olives and be
sure to make it a large.
Don't forget.
Are you listening to me, Dante?
Didn't you hear me?
I'm studying.
I may take the occasional
odd job here and there,
but I have no desire
to baby-sit some brat.
Brat?
Sorry, young lady.
Maybe in 10 years or so,
I'll ask you out on a date.
And I'll tell you
"no" in 10 seconds.
Me, I'm only into younger guys.
Listen, Dante.
She may be a kid, but...
Oh I'm sorry. My apologies.
But the young lady standing
before you is not just any girl.
She's Patty Lowell.
The Cinderella girl
who is heiress
to the Lowell family fortune.
She sure doesn't look it.
That's because all this
time she's been living
as an orphan downtown.
I can tell.
Kinda like Cinderella but
after the magic wore off.
Actually it's the opposite.
The head of the Lowell
family passed away.
When the will was read,
the existence of an
illegitimate child
came to light.
And the lucky winner was
our young lady, Patty?
Precisely.
In other words, the magic
is just about to begin.
If you like, I could
always hire you
as my very own
personal servant...
Yeah.
Basically, it has been
requested that you escort
Miss Patty back to the Lowell
Mansion by 6:00pm tomorrow.
Think you can handle that?
That's all?
That's all.
I won't do it.
I've got a pizza on the way...
There's no pizza on the way.
I stopped by and talked
with Andy at the pizza place
and told him that, until
you pay your tab in full,
they are not to deliver a
single pizza to you. Capisci?
You bastard...
What right do you have to...
Shit. not again.
If you win, I'll pay
your tab in full.
And if you lose...
Fine. Alright.
I know the routine.
Heads.
You're not much of
a gambler, are you?
Shut up.
Dante!
You forget something?
You've got a show
to play, right?
A show?
Don't forget,
I'm counting on you.
I could come and
see your show...
I mean, there must not be anyone
who comes to see you
otherwise, right?
Sorry, but my shows
are for adults only.
So the woman in that picture is
coming to your show then, huh?
Picture?
Well whatever you do, you
should buy yourself a new car.
I don't see any romance
happening in this car,
that's for sure.
It's dirty, it stinks,
and it's falling apart.
Don't you know?
When it comes to women,
it's not where you take
them that's important.
It's how you get them there.
Dante.
This girl's life is mine!
Hey! Are you even
listening to me!?
What are you doing?!
What's wrong with you?
What was that all about?!
Don't you think that's
a little dangerous?!
What are you trying
to do, kill me?
Can't you do something
about this, bro?
You are a lawyer, aren't you?!
There's nothing
that can be done!
If the person who sent
that letter, Patty Lowell,
actually does exist,
the fortune belongs to her.
You're kidding me!
Relaaaaax.
Take is easy, big bro.
If that letter isn't a fake,
then Patty Lowell
will come here around
6 o'clock tomorrow evening.
That's what I'm worried about!
Tomorrow at 6 in the evening...
That makes exactly
one week, doesn't it?!
Ha, ha...
"If Patty Lowell's existence
is authentically proven
within one week of the death
of the Lowell family's head...
then the entirety of
the family fortune
is to go to Miss Lowell". Well.
Unbelievable. That our
ever-so-serious brother
had an illegitimate
child all this time.
So...you can look
cute when you want to.
Is that a picture
of your boyfriend?
No! It's my mom, you halfwit!
And she's a lot prettier
than your girlfriend!
But... I don't remember
anything about her...
My mom got sick and died
when I was just a baby.
That's what the
hospital director said.
That's why I don't remember...
anything... about my mother...
The only thing I have...
is this picture of her...
Wow! That is one pretty lady!
That wouldn't be a picture
of your mother would it?
Hey, and you're pretty
charming yourself!
Mind if I sit here?
Huh?
There are open seats
all over the place.
Here you go!
Thank you!
I hope I am not bothering you.
You're not botherin' me,
but I can't promise
that you'll live long.
And what is that
supposed to mean?!
I mean really!
Why would anyone need
some promise like that,
just because they sit...
Good grief...
That's why I told you...
He's dead.
Oh Mommy... oh Mommy...
He was beat to death. Damn.
I can't be! Was it you?!
Over here!
Geez! What is this!?
You. How 'bout you... start
telling me what's going on here.
Sure, so how about I run
this little scenario by you.
For the ten seconds or so that
this train was in the tunnel...
in this car there were
those three, me and the girl.
And then our dead friend
here. That makes six.
First off, the old man.
He didn't do it.
And the couple there was
making out in the dark.
And that's how she was.
So that only leaves you!
No, there was one more person.
Or to be more precise,
one more thing.
That man on the train...
Do you know killed that guy?
Who knows...
It was a demon. He was killed
by a demon, wasn't he?
Could... Could a demon
be hunting me, too?
Dante! Dante!
Let's go.
Checkmate.
Damn. I lost again!
Ever since we were kids,
you've always run out of
steam in the closing stretch.
And that is why Jenny left you.
It's because you got in the way!
No, that was because
you were at fault
for jumping to conclusions.
Shit.
But what I'm wondering is
why you seem to love
that painting so much.
Yes. I guess it's
because looking at it
puts me at peace. And I think...
When we divide the
fortune among us,
I'll take the
artwork that's here.
Me, I'll take cold, hard cash.
Hey! Don't get
ahead of yourselves!
We know. But we have to be
prepared for the worst...
That's all we're doing...
Welcome to our hotel.
Give me your cheapest room.
I don't give a damn
if it gets sun or not.
We'll be out of here first
thing in the morning anyhow.
One adult and one child.
Oh, she's not a child,
she's a young lady.
What're you doing? Come on
move it let's get to sleep.
That's my mother.
What?
My mom!
Mister!
Yes? What is it?
Where can I go to
meet this woman?
Well...
What are you talking about?
I thought your mother died.
Come on.
Ahhh. This is a tight fit.
Get to bed. Tomorrow's
going to be an early day.
I didn't tell you the truth.
My mom didn't actually
get sick and die.
She disappeared.
I happened to overhear
the hospital director
talking about it.
My mom was being
hunted by a demon.
And she didn't want me,
a baby, to be in danger,
so she put me in the
care of the orphanage.
Anyone hunted by a demon
is as good as dead?!
Is my mother really dead?!
Tell me Dante am I going to
be killed by a demon too?!
Who knows...
I don't care. About any fortune.
And I don't care... about
my family's inheritance...
If I were to get a little
money, I'd just want to
use it to buy lots of clothes
and sweets and stuff like that
for the other kids
at the orphanage.
But then...
clothes and sweets
and those kinds of things aren't
really what they all want.
Like me...they just want to see
their mothers and their fathers!
More than anything.
You're probably just
going to laugh at me...
Nope.
Everyone wants to
see their parents.
Dante...
Well, sorry...
But I've got a date with some
pretty girls in Sandman Land...
You get to sleep too.
Hey! Where's my daughter!?
Daughter...?
The kid I checked in with!
Hmmm... I don't know what
you're talking about, sir.
Bastard. What the hell are you?
Speaking of hell you should
know I know all about you.
Yeah, then you know that
thing won't be enough
to kill me, don't you?
So, where is Patty?
Well alright.
Well, you see, right
now in the underworld,
the four most powerful
demons are vying for power.
Things are pretty
dangerous out here.
--So who's callin' the shots?
--Huh?
Who's the douchebag who
told you to go after Patty?
It must be someone from
the Lowell family...
Someone who doesn't want
Patty to claim the inheritance.
I have no idea.
I'm telling the truth
I'm just one of their grunts.
They don't tell me
anything at all.
It's mommy!
Mommy! Mommy! Mommy!
Mommy!
Oh, Mommy! Mommy, I wanted to
see you so bad for so long!
I'm sorry, Patty.
I won't do anything to
make you feel lonely again.
Oh, mommy, you promise?!
Because you're about
to die right now!
And your mom's
going to kill you!
Hey there.
You're not actually into lame
operas like this, now are you?
Dante!
Um... I was... I thought
my mommy was...
But...looks like we'll have to
wait for our touching finale.
Sorry honey, but this
show isn't for kids.
I'm so sorry, miss.
But I'm afraid that it is
now time for you to die.
Because I was
promised I would be
greatly rewarded
by my masters if
I killed you if the
others failed to do so.
Hit the road.
Time's up.
Brother, we did it!
The fortune is ours!
This letter was just
a bunch of nonsense.
You have a guest.
A guest?
Thank you.
And who might you be?
Oh my, that's not funny!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Patty Lowell.
She's just a child!
No, that child is
nothing but a fake.
I took every situation
into account.
fortunately for me,
I was able to find
a girl with the same
name quite quickly.
I had it arranged so that
all the media attention
would be on her and not me.
Thanks to her, my trip
here was quite pleasant.
Well then.
Why don't we just hurry and
deal with the formalities?
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
your claim is invalid,
Miss Patty Lowell.
Speaking as the lawyer,
I regret to inform you
that you have renounced
your right to the inheritance
as you missed the 6PM deadline.
You are aware you've
missed it, right?
Even if is... just by
a mere second or two.
Really now! In his will, it says
within one week of his death.
I'm quite sure that my
dad will have been dead
for exactly one week at 6:28.
And look! I am on time!
Will a driver's license
suffice for my identification?
No... It's no longer necessary.
What do you mean by that?
Because Patty
Lowell's existence...
...will never be confirmed!
Brother?!
And neither will yours!
The fortune... is all mine!
And I'm not handing
it over... to anyone!
So it was you...
...who requested I serve
as a bodyguard for Patty.
Did you think you were
making some small atonement
for your sins against her?
You've got a pretty face,
but you're more terrible
than those demons.
Well, if you were a demon,
I'd be able to kill you without
thinking twice about it.
Okay. If I can't let this go...
I'll work off the anger...!
Guess this'll be
one helluva party!
I saw it all!
The adult-only part...
Wait! Please wait a minute!
I'm begging you.
That child...
Please let me care for her!
I want to do what I
can to make amends...
So, is it alright that you're
not staying at the mansion?
It's fine. I received
compensation.
Compensation?
Yep. Because I'm a little
girl who's been scarred
from being exposed to
the ugly world of adults.
And those clothes, are
those the "compensation"?
As well as clothes and sweets
for the kids at the orphanage.
In all, three truckloads!
That's great! Well done.
Ah, Morrison, you're here?
Yeah.
Huh? I thought my
strawberry sundae
would be delivered here by the
time I got outta the shower...
That strawberry sundae?
What?!
Hey, that was mine!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
This is MY place!
Let's get this straight.
My place. Mine.
It was totally filthy and dorky,
so I cleaned it and did
some cute decorating.
Cute's a relative term.
I'm more concerned about
my goddamned dessert!
That's what I
charge for my work.
Thanks! It was the
best Sunday ever!
What a pain...
The only jobs I get are
those that don't pay anything.
My debt just keeps growing...
And now, I got to look after
some brat on top of it all.
On nights like tonight,
I like to open up the throttle
on my bike and
blow off some steam.
And if a demon
should come my way...
Well, that would
make it just perfect.
Don't miss my next mission.
Highway Star.