As payment for the potion that
would grow the princess legs,
the witch demanded
the princess's voice,
which was peerless in beauty.
So the mermaid princess
had her little tongue
cut out by the witch, and could
use her voice no more.
Who's there?!
Wh-What are you?!
But man, Dante...
Every time I drop by, you're
further and further in debt.
What do you expect?
Everyone leaves me bills
instead of a damn paycheck!
Hey Dante, are you here?
Sleeping again...
You're kidding me...
What kind of adult
spends all of their time
sleeping or eating pizza?
It's pathetic.
What happened to the jukebox?
Just find a way
to fix it, will ya?
Don't be ridiculous.
You're just too violent.
You've never been
able to handle things.
Whether they're simple
machines or good lookin' women.
You need charm
school, my friend.
I totally agree.
Lay off.
The only ways this
thing's going to get fixed
is by getting parts for it.
Or you could find some way to
get a different one altogether.
But I bet that
would be pricey...
This jukebox of yours
looks vintage to me
and that's gonna cost ya.
There's a lot of freaks into
vintage stuff out there,
you know...
And you're one of 'em.
Hey Dante, why is this the
only record you have framed?
I've played that record
more than any other,
but it got scratched...
I framed it 'cause
I couldn't bring myself
to just throw it away.
If you like it so much,
I don't understand why you
don't just buy another one?
Look at it and you'll see why.
I don't know the name of
the singer or the song.
Back in the day, that was one of
the records in that jukebox.
It's no use... It'd
be a helluva lot quicker
to just go out and buy
a new one, Dante.
Yeah, like I got the
money to do that....
Of course you don't.
All right then, it doesn't have
anything to do with demons,
so I was planning on handing
it off to someone else, but...
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
a job, of course.
There's this abandoned
building up north.
And a secret room
was discovered in it.
Luckily, the room was airtight,
so its contents were
in good condition.
A ton of never-played records
were miraculously
preserved there.
The treasure hunters who
got wind of this came to me
because they're looking
for a bodyguard.
Yeah, I know what
you're thinking.
Why would they need a bodyguard?
Well, Dante, it's
your job to find out.
Mr. Dante. Thank you very much
for accepting this position.
We feel much more at
ease knowing we have
a man of your talent
serving as our bodyguard.
I'm afraid that our profession
is simply treasure hunting..
We are admittedly quite lousy
when it comes to fighting.
So this counts as...
treasure hunting?
It certainly does.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but
didn't you accept this job
because you thought the goods
were going to be worth it?
There are a lot of people
out there willing to pay
enormous sums of money
for priceless antiques.
Sometimes people will
even kill the owners
to get their hands
on what I find.
Some people must really
dig their antiques...
Hey Tim, we should
liven things up...
Why don't you play something?
Yeah, you bet.
What's that?
Oh, you mean this?
Now this... is
something special...
It's by the legendary
rock queen, Elena Houston.
First record she ever recorded.
And it's all mine.
The real thing.
But this record is
filled with her soul,
the purest thing there ever was.
Really?
I don't suppose you'd
be interested in playing
that one for me?
Yeah, let's give it a spin.
It's good to have a listen
to it every now and then...
I can hear it...
That's... my...
Not bad... It strikes
you right to the core...
Doesn't it? Her voice is kind
of husky, but it's really good.
Did you know she started
writing the tunes and lyrics
for these while she was just
a musician on the street.
You seem to know your stuff.
Yeah, well...
Well, time for me
to get to work.
Oh no you don't... let it play.
You gotta have music
if you want to party.
Elena...
So, she ran away.
Thanks a lot there, man.
There's no doubt about it.
That was Elena back there.
Elena and I were
childhood friends.
I was just a plain,
good-for-nothing kid,
but Elena was different.
She was this brilliant singer.
How can I say it...
Her voice had this strange
power that drew people in.
And I was one of those
who were just spellbound
by the very sound of it.
I had this intense
desire to have
more people listen to her songs.
Even if it was just
one more person.
In the beginning all
she has was a guitar...
But before long,
she got a band together
and put on shows
out in the streets.
And soon the whole city
got to know her voice.
And me? I just played dressup.
Put on the suit and the tie.
Went all around town
making the sales pitches.
I needed to help her
any way I could.
But the road was paved
with so many rejections.
With no backing from anyone,
just putting out a single record
was further away than a dream...
but it's a dream
we had together.
How long I am going to have
to keep doing this crap?!
Hey. Take it easy.
We just have to be patient.
What we need to do
is grind away at
building a bigger
fanbase however we can.
Grind away, grind away.
I swear you're always like this!
Always the business!
Always sales!
I wanna be famous!
I've had it with this!
Take it easy...
The next show's going to be
at a bigger venue I promise.
The next show?!
How many damn shows
has it been now?!
I'm goddamn sick of this!
The only thing I want
is for more people
to lose themselves in my music.
That's the only
thing I care about...
That's all I want.
Why can't you
understand that, Tim?
Elena, please...
Then suddenly, all of our work
finally paid off for something.
We got our shot at a major debut
and she gradually got more gigs.
When we finally got that
first album released...
Something we wanted
for so long...
we started getting popular.
But... these really strange
things started to happen
to all of the fans who were
listening to her records.
What strange things?
The fans lost themselves
in excitement, and in the end
all kinds of people
started committing suicide
or even murdering one another
for tickets to her concerts.
--Elena! Elena! Over here!
--I love you, Elena!
And then Elena, herself,
began to change...
And then the more that Elena's
spellbound fans went crazy
and outta control the
further she withdrew
from me and the other
guys in the band.
And then she just...
Sing... Sing, Elena...
You have to sing for us.
Sing for us.
What's going on?!
Is there something
you're not satisfied with?
Who are you?! What's
happened to everyone?!
Isn't it just what you wanted?
A spellbinding voice that
your fans couldn't do without.
A devilishly beautiful voice...
That's what you
wanted, isn't it?
And you got what you wanted...
Nothing more.
That's not what I...
If you want something,
you have to give something.
It's what we say in the
business, a tradeoff.
You are me, and I am you, Elena.
We are both of the same...
mind and body.
So you'll use this on her?
Yeah... I think she's
searching for this record.
I believe that she might be
looking for her own songs.
It sounds crazy, I know.
So tell me, Dante...
What is the "Devil Hunter"
going to do with her?
The woman you knew as Elaina
Huston isn't here anymore, man.
What you saw...
...was nothing... but a demon.
I... suppose you're right.
This music's a little
rowdy for a funeral, though.
My voice... My song...
You want your songs
back, don't you?
If you do, you're
going to have to kill
those who stand in the way.
You have to kill for your
precious, precious songs.
Let's kill them...
Let's crush them...
Let's do it for your songs,
the most precious
things to you...
Let's kill, kill, kill...
and then let's kill some more.
You said it, didn't you?
That for your songs
you'd sacrifice anything...
For... my songs...
Yes... For my songs. Let's kill!
Ah, wonderful! Wonderful!
The best... The rock queen...
Elena, please stop.
Please don't do this
anymore. I'm begging you.
Your voice...
Your songs...
I know this isn't
what they were for...
I'm begging you, Elena...
Enough already...
Enough... Elena, please...
Please...
Elena!
Mark my words... you're
all going to regret this.
Elena! Elena! Elena!
Please Elena, just open
your eyes and look at me.
You can do it!
Elena!
You just hang in
there a little longer
I'll get a doctor for you.
My record....
What did you say,
Elena? I can't hear you.
Oh... It was you, wasn't it?
I can't believe it.
You still...
had my... record...
Tim?
Oh, Tim...
Of course! Because it's...
Because you're
truly the greatest.
I wish we could be...
together again...
Elena...
A tribute to the
spirit of the Queen...
What would you ask for if you
could have your wishes granted?
Would you ask to be rich?
Or to have the woman you're
in love with be yours?
You can wish for whatever you
want, it's your business,
but to have one's wishes come
true always comes with a price.
Every deal has a catch. You'd
better be nice and careful.
Next Mission,
"Wishes Come True."