Attention, ladies and gentlemen.
We are now on final approach
to our destination port of St.
Lowel, the largest city on Mars.
We hope you had
a pleasant flight.
Today's temperature is
a cool eleven degrees Celsius.
The oxygen percentage
reading is seven percent.
Reports have come in of slight
unrest throughout the city,
due to public demonstrations.
We hope you have an enjoyable
time during your stay on Mars.
Thank you.
No!
Jennifer!
Please remain seated and
keep your seatbelts fastened
until we have come
to a full stop.
We wish to thank our
passengers for their patronage,
and we look forward to
servicing you in the future.
Have a nice day.
Huh?
The cargo area?
Make sure units are covering
the rooftop and the rear!
All in a day's work, Lieutenant.
And don't try and
bill me for that bike!
Hey, watch out!
Hmm.
Freeze!
Get your hands up!
I said get your hands up! Now!
What's up?
Detective, you'd
better stay back.
Handle it.
Get back!
Tell me you're
packin' a gun, sheriff.
How 'bout you?
Shit! A bunch of
cowboys up the ass,
and not one of 'em's got a gun.
Stop, now!
Let me down! Let me down!
Look, that bastard's
getting away!
What the hell?
No!
Stay out of this, Detective!
This is the Martian Police
Department, Detective Sylibus.
Did you have a nice trip?
It's McCanon!
He killed her!
The country singer?
Haha!
Dammit!
Huh?
Hey wait! What the
hell are you doing?
You damn lunatic!
This is insane.
Where'd you go. I was
so worried about you!
Dad.
Her name was Kelly McCanon.
She was a famous country singer.
In fact, the only country
singer in the universe.
I guess this means
they're extinct.
And the suspect?
Tell me, is that crazy
get-up you're wearing
a standard issue
Martian police uniform?
Course not!
So, what's your name?
The name's Armitage.
Ooh, what a sexy back.
I just love broad shoulders.
Hey!
What was that for?
I was just being nice!
Listen, what's going on here?
Is this somebody's
idea of a sick joke?
Annie Oakley here
isn't even human.
It's a damn robot.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Spaceport police.
This is their jurisdiction.
In response to the
Kelly McCanon incident,
the Martian Police
Department has created TCS,
Technological Criminal Swat,
to investigate.
Lieutenant Randolph, of the MPD,
declined further details.
The million dollar
question is...
Just what do we have here?
A woman or a robot?
Sir, results from my
preliminary findings are,
well, uh, very interesting.
I learned that the uh,
victim, shall we call her,
is not a human nor a cyborg.
After examining the body,
I concluded she was
entirely a robot.
Her body tissue was of
manmade organic origin.
And she functioned through
artificial intelligence.
While no one is capable of
creating a human brain, yet,
her computer brain
was very sophisticated.
And, as I mentioned,
her physical construction
was created organically.
But it was done using
a technology much more advanced
than the Second series models.
I believe that the
victim was a prototype
built outside of regulations.
It could also, um,
mean that there are other
illegal models like her,
running around under our noses.
Yes, thank you.
And now Detective Sylibus will
give his report about the scene.
Hi, I'm Ross Sylibus, from
the Chicago Police Department.
Uh, the suspects appeared,
I mean, they seemed like
they wanted to transport the
body without anyone noticing.
Um, probably to finish their
work somewhere else in private.
Officer Armitage there had
been trailing the suspects,
and then all hell broke loose.
Armitage, can you fill us in?
Well, I trailed the suspects
and saw they were equipped.
I didn't think they were
carrying a dead robot.
So what the hell
does that mean?
That it was McCanon's
imposter riding the shuttle?
Shut up, Eddie.
What did her manager
have to say?
Well, sir, according to him,
he didn't see any difference
between the woman he sat with
and the real
country-western singer.
And nobody saw her come out
of the arriving terminal.
The only suspicious passenger
he saw was Detective Sylibus.
Well, it seems that
the trick for us
is to find out where
the real McCanon is.
You know, maybe she's
feeling her wild oats.
Might've found herself
some kinda wild lover.
Christ, Eddie, will you zip it!
Just how was she acting
inside the shuttle?
She acted fine.
She was holding a normal
conversation.
Nothing seemed unusual
about it to me.
Hell, I wouldn't have been able
to tell her apart from a human.
Uh-huh. Uh...
Are you tellin' us that this
robot was really McCanon?
You think that prima donna was
a machine from the beginning?
No, I'm saying you
can't distinguish it
from a human being.
Oh, hey, yeah, Armitage,
when you realized the corpse was
a robot, you seemed shocked,
even upset.
Did you think
something was wrong?
Well, did ya?
No, sir.
I hope you like your new place.
It's probably not as nice
as you're used to,
but there's a
housing shortage here.
Besides, the rent is
reasonable on this end of town.
Gee, a regular Park Avenue.
Hmm.
Whoa.
Twelfth floor.
I'm sure it's better
when you get inside.
Hmm.
Ugh, it smells stale.
Hey, is that all your luggage?
Well, you know,
with all the excitement at
the baggage claim today...
Ah, just as well.
Probably stuff I wouldn't
have needed anyway.
There's enough trash
from Earth here already.
Well, you do have
a point about that.
Oh, look at this.
This is a tape sent by the
suspect of yesterday's
St. Lowel spaceport shooting.
♪ Here where we belong. ♪
What is this?
Some kinda memorial program?
The following scenes
contain graphic content,
and viewer discretion
is advised.
If you have children,
please set your monitor to "L."
Hey that's the guy!
I'll go take care of
the baggage, babe.
Alright, hurry back.
Who are you?
Ah!
What are you doing?
Leave me alone.
Somebody help me.
Please.
Oh, no, don't!
How did you know I was a-
My god.
Jessica.
This has been unedited
material from video files
as sent to us by
the murder suspect.
Here to comment on the footage
is Miss Julian Blanshin,
an activist in the movement
to drive out robots.
It's amazing.
They're everywhere you look.
Ya'd think they could
build something else.
You're here pretty early,
Detective.
She's gone already,
the badge-toting
terror in hot pants.
Hey, you want some free advice?
Try not to get your
partner killed this time.
Here's one more thing,
when she puts on
her visor, watch out!
And before I forget, here.
She's clean, gassed,
and waiting downstairs.
And welcome to your new home.
Robots get out!
Get out right now!
Give us back our jobs!
I'm sorry to have
to break you in so soon,
but we may as well get started.
Uh, but Lieutenant,
is our section supposed
to handle this matter?
Hmm? Just what do you
mean by that, Ross?
Well, you see, the victim
was definitely a robot,
so I don't see why MPD should
get stuck dealing with it.
Shouldn't we let some
other government agency
take it off our hands?
I wish it was that easy,
but it's the robot's
origins that we're interested
in finding out about.
As you may not
be aware, Sylibus,
people here consider illegal
robot technology and replication
to be a criminal offense.
Yes, sir. I guess so.
Are you going to tell me why
you wanted to transfer to Mars?
Well, I'd rather not, sir.
As you like.
Let me warn you. If you have
misguided compassion for robots,
you won't make it here.
Do you hear us?
We want our jobs!
Wow, what a place.
Excuse me, Miss.
Why not?
I'm very sorry, but
I've explained to you
that I cannot allow
you to see him.
You're telling me
he doesn't remember
the name Armitage at all?
Mr. Asakura said
he's never heard of you.
Listen, don't mess
with me, you little bitch.
You'd better get out of here,
or I'll call the
security gadget.
Yeah, I guess it's useless
talking to a Second like you.
Hey!
Ah, just cancel
that appointment.
Let me go!
How dare you!
I have business here!
Robots get out, now!
I can't believe this!
Put me down right now!
And just what the hell were you
trying to accomplish back there?
Robots get out, now!
You know, you really
should move your car
or it might get
trashed by those idiots.
So, now what's next?
Well, immigration seems
like a likely place.
Oh, Ross.
I already went there
and couldn't find
our guy on the list.
Hmm.
Oh, I doubt we'll
find any record of him,
because 37% of the population
isn't registered here.
Or I guess you
didn't know that.
So then just who the hell
were you trying to see
at the Conception Company?
That is private.
By the way, I've already
done some leg work.
Conception was the company
that set the standards
for the Seconds.
So, there you go.
Ah, but you know,
I still pity 'em.
The other manufacturer,
Hu-Gite passed 'em up,
and it killed their aspirations,
but that's the way
it always goes.
Say, does this fancy machine
have reclining seats?
Huh, partner?
If you're looking for a partner,
then stop flying solo.
Hey Ross, as your partner,
can I make a suggestion?
Yeah.
Let's eat. I'm starving.
Alright.
Ice cream.
Junk food? I thought we were
gonna get something to eat.
Oh well, whatever.
This is some kinda town.
Things are just gonna
get worse with all these
remodeled Seconds.
There's no way humans and
robots are ever gonna get along.
Besides, you can't trust robots.
Oh, you're no different.
Hmm?
You and that guy
are both the same.
What do you mean, that nutcase?
It just seems that both of you
have something against robots.
Well, I'm sick of all
these cyborgs and humanoids
and machines that
only seem to copy us.
Since I'm allowed
to make a choice,
I choose not to like something
that pretends to be human.
Huh?
Hmph!
Now you're positive that
the woman on the shuttle
with you was Kelly McCanon?
Well?
Ah, of course I'm sure!
Scuse me.
Aw, please tell me you found
Kelly! Won'tcha? Huh? Huh?
No stinkin' robot could play
a guitar or sing the way
Kelly does! I'm her manager!
I know her better than anybody!
She's the most
human woman I know!
Armitage!
Your client is history buddy.
Just learn to live with it.
Hey wait!
Hey, wait up! Armitage!
I want to go!
Your conduct was
hardly professional.
Sorry, but that whiner
was nothing but an asshole.
Maybe you can sympathize
with him, but I don't!
Hmm.
That jerk can't
figure out how a robot
could possibly be as good
as his precious human star.
Don't you understand?
All of McCanon's
talents, personality,
and dreams were
inside that machine.
Oh my god.
Yeah, what is it?
I didn't realize.
Sylibus here.
Uh, it's Chris.
I'm receiving a weird
voicemail transmission.
Is Armitage with you?
Uh...
No, I'm afraid I don't
see her right now.
Okay, listen, it's coming
to us in real time.
So I'll transmit it
to your mailbox.
Log it and show it
to Armitage right away.
I told you, an officer
named Armitage!
Okay, okay, lady we're
looking for her right now.
Please! You've got to help me!
I'm a Third.
Right. What's your name again?
Wait a second, let me get a pen.
Alright, go ahead.
Manning. It's Jessica Manning.
I'm keeping a list of all
the Thirds from Pluto.
I can't go outside because
of the protests.
And the man on TV
who killed that singer
has been sending me mail.
Something's going to
happen unless you help me!
Who are you?
Huh?
Huh, why are they all females?
TV piracy is a felony, pal!
You could get eight years
of hard labor in prison.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Rene D'anclaude.
Huh?
It's my name.
So just who do you
think you are, mister?
There are other things to
concern yourselves with.
Let me show you.
Robots are disguising
themselves as humans.
Am I wrong?
It's my duty to do
something about this.
You must be rid of
those so-called Thirds.
First contestant:
This is Jessica Manning,
Shit!
a snobbish,
bourgeois artist who lives and
works right here among you.
She had you all fooled.
What should we do about her?
Hey are you okay?
Where's Ms. Manning?
Oh Jessica!
Save her, please! Why...
It's all right.
You just wait here.
Robots get out now!
Let me through! Police! Hey!
Give us back our jobs!
Get out right now!
Huh?
It's them.
The list of Thirds!
Yes. And then? No, wait!
Goodbye Jessica.
Slow down!
You of all people should
understand my work.
After all, didn't a cyborg
kill your partner?
They're a pestilence.
Hmm?
But your leg!
Hey, sailor, what's this?
You've gotta be kidding!
A fake leg?
Surely the ironic humor of
this hasn't escaped you!
You're almost a stinking
cyborg yourself, you freak!
Huh?
What's that?
It's you.
Until now, you've
never witnessed
the true power of a Third.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Here bitch!
Burn, you misfit!
You monster.
Yeah, that's right,
I'm a monster.
Just another name for
a Third in your book!
What're you gonna do,
destroy me?
Why, what did we
ever do to humans?
If humans don't want me,
then why did they create me?
Don't do it!
Just cuff him.
You're a police officer
first, Armitage.
And you know what your duty is.
Armitage, it doesn't matter
that you're a Third.
You're a cop...
and you're my partner.
No! Don't look at me!
You'd already figured out that
I wasn't a human, didn't you?
I feel like
some kind of grotesque puppet!
I can walk and talk.
And I can laugh.
And I can cry.
But I'm only a monstrous doll!
No!
Armitage carries a special
A Class license.
I know.
But she chose to
become a cop. A good one.
You understand what
I'm getting at?
Yeah.
The reason she disappeared
is because of you, Ross.
Lt. Randolph, you can
interrogate me all you want.
I'm used to it.
Ross, that won't be necessary.
If you say you
don't know anything,
that's good enough for me,
and leave it at that.
I'm no Sherlock Holmes,
but I've learned from experience
to follow my instinct.
I have a hunch there's some kind
of connection between Armitage
and the killing of
the Third types.
This could get real fun.
If an officer is
rumored to be a humanoid,
the shit could hit the fan.
So let's keep this between you,
me, and the wall.
Armitage isn't a good cop.
She's a great one.
Always hurts like hell
when the rain comes.
Hmm?
Start message.
Hey, where are you?
Are you okay?
Your partner's concerned.
Lieutenant Randolph's no dummy.
He suspects you're a Third.
It appears D'anclaude
is working with someone,
because Thirds are
still being murdered.
Armitage, don't let
bitterness change you.
Come back. Please.
This makes number seven.
Oh god, I think I'm gonna puke!
Who the hell is doing this?
I can only think of two people
with the means and motivation.
Hmm?
I'm talking about
Rene D'anclaude.
And Armitage.
What's that?
Yeah, I know, it's
weird to think about,
but she talked to me
about it once.
She pities the robots
used for crime,
so she kills them quickly.
But I can't believe
she'd actually...
Not on your life.
Sure the village is artsy,
but downtown is a pit.
I wouldn't move
there for anything.
Listen, I've gotta
get some writing done.
I'll talk to ya later.
Continue writing mode.
Novel in progress, untitled.
Chapter 2, paragraph 5.
"How could she greet the ones
from the deep far away?
"She, who has spent a pleasant
and enchanting afternoon...
"who had never given a
thought about the person
from the Luluie,
the same one who had once picked
her up, now cold and dead."
"A phantom.
"Her battle with
the old gods ended.
"As a spiritual
truce was struck,
she felt her soul unburdened.
"She smiled. Already the
feeling of harmony was-"
Who's there?
Who are you?
Are you Armitage?
Are you the one
who contacted me?
You fooled me!
I don't wanna die. I don't wa-
Do you mean that
Armitage is a suspect?
Well, you can't just
deny the evidence.
The woman's last words
said it all.
The whole department is shocked,
but the lieutenant had
suspicions about her all along.
He's already issued
a warrant for her arrest,
and there's an APB out on her.
Why that sly old dog.
Access mail. Log file, Armitage.
Open file.
This is Pluto.
I'm sending this message
by using Armitage's ID.
I'm a Third, just like you...
Hey, Chris. Let's find out where
this mail originated from.
You got it.
Hey Kelly, wanna see
a movie Saturday?
Hey, I was worried about you.
I used to love the
playground after school.
I was a pretty
clumsy kid, though.
I took a tumble off the
see-saw once and bawled
all the way home.
Listen, did you know that MPD
has been searching for you?
But you're looking
for Pluto, right?
Let's go.
Armitage.
What?
I believe in you.
There! That's him,
I'm sure of it.
Huh? But he's a boy.
How do you do, Pluto.
It's nice to meet you.
Please don't call me
by my handle again.
You can use my given name,
Julian Moore.
I'm sorry!
By the way,
shouldn't you be in class?
No.
I'm transferring my thoughts
to the main memory at
the Navigation Center.
Hmm?
What for?
To make a backup
of myself. Obviously.
Well, let's go!
Huh? Where?
To the memory server at
the Ad Tower, of course.
You want to learn the purpose
of the Thirds, don't you?
I can't believe it!
You're a Third?!
Yes, I'm a Third.
The last one made.
What's wrong?!
Why'd the elevator stop?
I don't know.
Huh?
It won't stop!
We're dropping pretty fast!
At this rate,
we're gonna die for sure!
Ross, hold on tight to him!
Do you really think
this is gonna work?
You got any ideas?
Ross.
I think my right arm
and ribs are broken.
Armitage, don't get any closer!
Damn you!
He's fast!
Come on, we gotta run for it!
Go on. Leave me here.
No! I'll help you! Let's go!
Oh my god!
Looks like the only
choice is to fight!
Aim it up.
If Armitage is killed, then
there's gonna be no hope for me.
It's D'anclaude!
I just don't believe it!
Surprise, surprise.
Hah! Didja miss me?
You son of a bitch!
I won't let you
die alone, cherie.
The other two will join you.
Fucking bastard!
He's not human!
Nice right hook, but now I'm
going to crush the three of you
and get on with my life.
I have places to go
and robots to kill.
Huh?
Huh? What the-
Hi there. Bon Voyage Rene.
You crazy bitch! Give me the
keys! Please, unlock it!
Bye bye!
I'm curious. Why aren't other
Thirds as strong as you?
Security should be
here any minute.
I'm sure they'll
take care of you!
No.
You don't have to
run and hide now.
Officers don't leave
their injured behind.
You're cold, lady.
Huh?
I will always be cold.
Armitage.
I'm amazed he survived with
all the injuries he sustained.
His entire chest area
was damaged,
and the right arm was severed.
Over fifty percent of his body
will be artificial
replacement parts.
Isn't that gonna be a
problem for a policeman?
Eh, for a recruit, maybe,
but not for this cowboy.
Pal, I sure hope you
feel better than you look.
I can't understand why my
other arm hurts so much.
The doctor threw in some kinda
new nervous system for ya,
so it's probably
just a side effect.
At any rate, there's
something I wanna show ya.
It's Kelly McCanon.
Why haven't they
disposed of her body yet?
Hey, she's a real find.
You don't just throw
something like her away.
Except for a few functions,
Thirds are perfect
synthetic organisms.
They can simulate every physical
aspect of the human body.
The big mystery that's had
everybody running in circles
is why all the Thirds
have been female.
Do you know?
After the victims
were autopsied,
we discovered that
this wasn't just
a case of robot destruction.
It was murder.
I'll show ya.
Our country-western
singer, here,
she was pregnant.
No stinkin' robot
could play a guitar or
sing the way Kelly does!
I'm her manager!
I know her better than anybody!
She's the most
human woman I know!
I can't believe I'm
capable of giving birth.
Quite a revelation, isn't it?
That's the whole purpose
of the Third types.
You can step beyond the
bounds of conventional robots,
just by getting pregnant,
Mommy Armitage.
Hmph.
Not funny.
It's too weird.
But you, what's your role?
I'm still trying
to figure that out.
What's the point in
creating a male kid?
The CPU showed my serial
number as the last Third made.
The final model off the line.
Not quite.
We can breed now.
Now I understand why the Thirds
were made to seem so human,
not just in appearance,
but emotionally.
Like the murdered singer
and that novelist.
They weren't just machines.
They had souls.
It takes more than the
right plumbing to procreate.
Yes, sir. The perfect
receptacle for human babies.
What the hell is so funny, huh?
Jerk.
What's the matter?
Have I touched a nerve?
Maternal clock ticking?
Maybe you'd like Detective
Ross to set your alarm.
Shut up.
I was just kidding.
Julian, do you know
why they made us?
I don't.
But I'll bet Asakura does.
Or...D'anclaude.
He must have some part in this.
How are you feeling, Ross?
Have you made a full recovery?
Yeah, I'm fine.
It just takes some time getting
used to these new body parts.
Ironic, isn't it?
What?
Little by little,
you're becoming like the
robots you hate so much.
Let's get down to
business, shall we?
Why is the investigation
of the Thirds over,
that doesn't make any sense.
Maybe it does.
Bullshit.
But we have to follow orders
in this department.
Tell me, was the
decision forced?
I'll tell you what it is.
It's a goddamned order
that you're gonna follow!
The Third investigation is over,
because the murderer
was apprehended.
Even after we've discovered
the Thirds are robots
that can actually conceive?
Why stop here?
D'anclaude's under full guard.
Yeah right.
He's over at Shinora General
Government Hospital.
I can't accept the contradictory
report that you filed.
But sir.
Our job is to investigate an
arrest technological criminals.
Don't forget it.
That's all I have
to say for now.
Ironic, isn't it?
Little by little,
you're becoming like the
robots you hate so much.
That's where all my memory
was backed up and stored.
I'm saved for posterity.
And if we're all
murdered, you know-
Will you give it a rest!
Bingo!
Warning.
Only authorized personnel
are permitted within
the memory bank I/O room.
Please vacate this area at once!
We're lost.
Which way is magnetic north?
There is no department
by that name.
You must vacate
within 10 seconds, or-
Asakura was quite a designer.
He created the ultimate
woman who could kick ass
and raise children!
He designed you, too.
Yeah, but I can't get pregnant.
That's it.
Here goes! I hate that
this is the easiest way.
Hey, will you hurry up?
Hey, I'm doing this for you,
it hurts like Hell, so shut up!
I need to know about myself.
Who am I and why.
I'll look.
I'm searching
for Asakura's file.
Armitage...
Help me out!
My virtual monitor.
Yeah?
Open it from my
navigational system.
Good, I've located
the still image file.
Hold on, just another second.
That's my father!
But why is he standing
next to D'anclaude?
I don't believe it.
Julian!
Damn it! I think
someone's discovered me.
We're logging off now!
Oh, god! Something's in me!
Please help me!
Little Naomi Armitage.
Went looking for knowledge
and only found trouble.
You can't stop the Third types
from being killed, my dear.
Shoot me. I don't mind.
Pull the trigger, I dare you!
So, you're not a human.
Are you a Third type?
You won't find my name
in the membership of
that club for failures.
What are you saying?
You make me retch.
Cheap imitations
pretending to be human.
There's no comparison
to our superiority.
I couldn't agree with
humans more on one thing:
all Thirds should
be annihilated.
I'll kill you!
Julian! No!
That bastard's
not the original.
Oh my god!
What's wrong?!
I'm going.
I'll finally meet
the real D'anclaude.
Get back!
Armitage...
Goodbye.
Oh, no, Julian, no!
Ross, it-
Huh?
Ross.
No.
Ross, I need your help.
Ross, it's D'anclaude, again.
I need you.
Julian. I need you.
So one of my men got
a little carried away.
Hmm, well.
I'm Judicial
Vice Minister, Jusup,
and I'm visiting as
a representative of the
Legal Affairs Bureau.
I need an accurate picture
of the MPD's operations.
I'm just a bit confused.
Help me to understand why
an inspector from
Earth's government
has come here.
Oh, don't mind me, Lieutenant.
I'm simply an observer
for Mr. Jusup.
Think of me merely as
a fly on the wall.
Hmm.
Well, since you're observing,
I'm sure you have noticed
that the robots here
on Mars don't quite
reflect a feminist society.
Very well. You understand
us, uh, Mr. uh...
Randolph.
Let's call it a day
and have lunch.
I'm sick of the
whole damn system.
Armitage...
Didn't Julian say that
he had his memory backup
stored somewhere?
The backup?
That's right.
If we can somehow
access his data,
we could still bring him back.
Get it?
His body's gone,
but his mind's alive.
Funny, I didn't think
I would miss him so much.
Maybe his information will help
us and avenge his death as well.
Julian said he was gonna
meet the real D'anclaude.
Maybe he was telling us
we could do the same.
Ross?
Shinora, right?
Will you come with me?
What's up?
The internal troops are active.
Are we at war?
No. They're guarding.
What, the President?
No, Shinora Hospital.
Shinora?
Jesus H. Christ, will you
look at that arsenal!
What the hell are
they doin' there?
Hold on a minute.
I'm picking up something.
What is it?
Aw, it's just a car.
Holy shit!
They've lost it.
Fire!
Here.
It's him.
Finally, the real D'anclaude.
Or I should say
Dr. René D'anclaude.
You must be...
Asakura's daughter,
the failure.
We gotta hurry! Come on!
Let's go, while we still can.
What's the matter?
Ross, something's coming.
What is it?
Not again.
D'anclaude! There's no way!
Hey, let's rumba!
Over here!
This way, hurry!
Wait, don't run off!
I wanna play with you.
Come on! Wait!
There's no way that damn
gargoyle is a Third type!
Hmm. My, look who's talking.
Don't tell me you have no
clue who your brother was.
You have more in common
with that prototype gargoyle
than you might realize.
Did you truly believe
you were a Third?
Liar!
You could always ask Asakura,
but he's tucked away safely
in a dome on Dunwitch Hill.
Armitage, don't stop.
No!
Oh no, I can always tell when
you're gonna do something crazy.
Hi kids.
Oh, does she want a showdown?
We're both gonna bite it.
That'll make everyone happy,
cause you know, nobody
on Mars wants us here.
Wrong! You're the
one who's through!
No!
Human suffering is such
a unique privilege, isn't it?
He's pure data.
Cease function!
Next in the news, the
Martian Police Department
is investigating
the terrorist attack
at Shinora General
Government Hospital,
which occurred during an
antirobot demonstration.
The police are asking
for our viewers' help
in locating these two suspects:
Ross Sylibus and Naomi Armitage.
The MPD confirms there is
a definite connection.
If you have any information,
please notify the police.
Let me pick out our next
meeting place, okay?
Tables, with umbrellas.
If that makes you too sick,
I know a vending machine
and a clean bench.
I guess maybe this
is the worst place.
The worst place?
Only if I was in your shoes.
Will you cut the crap!
Did you find anything?
Yeah, your Dunwitch Hill
exists, but not on any map.
Found a good highway going
smack blank into a mountain,
but there's no Asakura
address box inviting
any mail from a rogue cop.
No sati-topographicals?
C'mon!
Like I really got a couple of
moons to power this thing.
Hey, what're you doin'?
A loss on duty.
Yeah, the dearly departed.
Hey, Ross!
Can you tell those guys...
the Martians, tell 'em
Eddie says "What's up?"
Sure.
So, what's wrong?
Well, are you gonna tell me?
Are you O.K.?
No, I'm not.
My CPU's all messed up.
They say the mind's
the first thing to go.
Humans say it.
Come on, Armitage,
machines don't go senile.
They also say life
is pretty short.
It's like an expiration date,
you know?
Hey, how come?
What?
What's the reason you're
doing all this for me, huh?
So tell me how come
you're still with me,
and driving me all
the way out here anyway?
I mean, why change from
a good cop to a criminal?
How come-
Stop! You're asking stupid
questions like some little kid.
Why? How come?
There's no answer.
That's it, isn't it?
Coordinates.
Virgin? Yeah, maybe if
you just landed here.
Hey, it wastes fuel
to keep the motor running.
Yo, anybody here?
We're looking for
a guy called Asakura.
Is anyone here?
You got visitors!
What happened?
Alright, take it easy.
Move away from it nice and slow.
Don't shoot!
It's only a robot.
Yeah, a big one.
It's somehow just like me.
I think it's a bioroid type.
What the hell is it,
some kind of a prototype?
May I help you?
Huh?
Talk about your family trees.
It's another D'anclaude.
That same face and voice.
I heard someone calling
for Dr. Asakura.
I did.
Appointment?
No, I suppose not.
Would you follow me, please?
Dr. Asakura, visitors! A Mr...
Sylibus.
Papa!
The new man from Conception!
It's been so many years,
and you even brought one
of the models along.
Mr. Sylibus.
Uh, but I'm not-
Papa!
Oh, but she's only a Third.
She's so inferior.
The poor little thing,
but you needn't be so kind.
It's outdated.
Oh, I'm sorry. Here,
take a look at this.
A fourth type that
Conception can be proud of.
There's no longer any need to
copy humans or plants anymore.
They live. They're ALIVEs!
Oh, no, we should
call them "phobians."
What? Yes, a new life, my
Marforteans, but you won't.
You'll just be calling
them anything you want
when you market them.
The stupid company you work
for is just going to call them
the Fourths aren't they?
They're ALIVEs!
A grand conception!
Then it all goes wrong.
The doctor's mind was
unfortunately altered.
Reduplication of his
thoughts is very difficult.
Please, be patient.
His memory, was it erased?
Who are you?
I am Wilbur D'anclaude
and Dr. Asakura's aide.
Oh, well yeah he might look
to you like he's one
of those damn assassinroids,
but I fixed up his crazy head,
just as you can see.
Indeed he did.
The violent tendencies I had are
now gone, due to the upgrade.
What's the reason?
Pardon?
Dr. Asakura. His mind,
just what's wrong with it?
Forget it, Ross.
That's enough.
Are you still cold?
Yes, it's affecting
my nervous system.
I'm sorry I lost my temper,
I was just hoping the doctor
would be able
to help you somehow.
Never count on hope.
You'll lose.
When wishes are gone,
hope gives nothing.
And then you hope that
your father might know.
And hopes are really fragile.
They get all ruined,
every time you believe
that somebody else is gonna
help your hopes come true.
A hope is a feeling.
Maybe you'll be okay.
If I was a Second,
then I wouldn't even be able
to think of all
this stupid crap.
But I'm programmed
to be a human,
and I don't even know
what that means.
Hope is a human feeling,
isn't it, Ross?
Come on, tell me more-
Hey, I know one.
He's a human,
and he's less real
than all of the things
you're talking about.
You wanna know what he said?
"Don't give up."
Ross.
Are you sure?
Armitage, I think it's
the only thing I've been
sure of since I got here.
How 'bout you?
Well, at least something
is normal here on Mars.
But I'm not normal.
I'm a robot.
I'm half robot too.
But I know a true heart
when I've met one.
We interrupt this broadcast
for the following announcement.
Good evening,
we've just received word that
as of 11:00 PM, UTN time,
the economic agreement
has been signed at last.
Mars and Earth have
finally signed the treaty.
Officials from both powers
are quoted as saying,
"This is a first step toward
one world, one nation."
Follow me, there's something
I'd like to show you.
Where's the doc?
This morning,
he's with his ALIVEs.
He's concentrating on
further hybridization.
He intends to
continue and complete
the initial terraforming plans.
But that's impossible.
Yes, rational thought
would agree.
Don't worry. The unborn
sister poses no threat.
Dr. Asakura gave up
weapon production.
He left this new model
unfinished. But why?
A difference of opinion with his
partner Professor D'anclaude?
I... that's enough.
Let's go.
Is there something else?
I brought you here, because I
felt you had previous knowledge
of the Thirds being
created as assassinroids.
Nice, upgrade. Go on.
It's the unfinished work.
Professor D'anclaude began
work on female assassinroids,
which would some way compliment
the multitude of my brothers.
Along with myself and Armitage,
we were the pinnacle
of robotic creation.
Although our strength and
abilities far surpassed humans,
it was quite simple
to assimilate ourselves
into their society.
Then, Dr. Asakura used us as
a base of synthetic organisms
in developing the Thirds.
Programming creativity and life
instead of the directive
to destroy.
Unfortunately, all the
prototypes had an imperfection.
There were many instabilities
within the logic boards
of the Third CPU.
Of course, Dr. Asakura's present
state of mind prevented him
from ever quite perfecting
the female models.
I'm nothing.
He couldn't finish. I'm useless!
He doesn't even care!
No, wait!
I don't understand.
Why even create a Third type?
I mean, the Seconds were
good enough, even on Earth.
Perhaps being from Earth,
you do not have the knowledge
of the difficulties there are
with low Martian birthrates.
No. I've heard.
What's it mean?
Any colony desiring
independence,
requires a populace.
Otherwise, they can't
develop a new identity.
And Mars will continue
to be weak, as long as it
remains dependent upon the
Earth for its immigration.
Well, what about Conception?
There's got to be more
behind it than just
the money that's
involved, right?
Indeed, manufacturers of
Thirds, which can give birth,
gain strength through numbers.
The more people they represent,
the stronger their
position grows.
Logical. But then the
assassinations make no sense.
They do. If you're the
government and hope to sign
a treaty with the
Earth Federation.
Nah, they couldn't.
Do you think they've
really done it?
Mars has no other recourse.
The Earth Federation
is now strongly feminist.
A robot who can conceive,
contradicts the basis of
the Terran Party's position
of basic humanity.
For Mars to agree, Mars
must eliminate the Thirds.
They are now an obstruction.
Is that what you think?
That I'm just old Martian
garbage to be thrown out?
You're wrong.
I'm gonna stay alive
for as long I can-
Exactly, your programming
for self-preservation
is exactly equal to ours
for eliminating your kind.
But I am now refined.
Unlike my brothers, I respect
your wish for continued life.
Heya Eddie.
He's on suspension...
Huh?
for aiding a fugitive,
section 10.
No sir, not if
I forced him into it.
Perhaps he'll be pardoned.
I'll submit it.
This Dunwitch Hill Dome
has become a military
attack point.
The government has made its own
connections between you two
and the terrorist
attack at Shinora.
This is an official notice.
You're a threat
to the government,
the MPD officially denounces
all of your activities.
So Eddie freakin' squealed.
He didn't. How could an officer
who I put on suspension
say anything at all?
Thanks a lot!
Sorry.
Sorries aren't good enough!
And just what the hell
are we gonna do now?
Survival!
It's basic training.
Lieutenant Randolph
and friends, signing off.
Great.
You're in charge. What now?
We gotta get my father out.
Good morning! And this morning
is our day of new hope.
Our planet,
often beleaguered with
nightmarish social confusion,
has been finally
pieced together again,
with the help from
our true home world.
Federation Chairwoman
Everheart has taken two planets
and given us one world,
one nation.
Today we are reborn as
a unified humanity.
Listen to me, they're going
to blow all of us up!
Straight to hell!
My ALIVEs are not yet
ready to leave.
They're gonna be your tender
logs in a few seconds.
Papa!
Wilbur, get the important work
into the old storage backups.
Don't worry about me,
I'll be safe.
It's you I'm-
Maybe you are a nut,
but I'm your damn daughter,
and you know it.
This is a police order.
Evacuate.
You're still a little fireball,
aren't you, my Naomi?
Papa!
Armitage!
She's alright. You must think
I'm a great coward, Mr. Sylibus.
But if the ALIVEs
and myself are to die,
I must at least save one thing.
Poor child.
Daddy will fix it.
Daddy will fix his little girl.
There, it's finished, Naomi.
Now you are real.
Last night's slogan of
"one world, one nation"
has this morning blossomed into
a new Martian thought toward
"two worlds, one humanity."
Hey listen, I think that Eddie
knows a guy that can hide us
as cargo on an Earth shuttle.
I still got friends
who can get you a new I.D.
I don't want that.
I'm going back.
Back to St. Lowel.
I don't want to see you die.
You won't have to.
We'll say goodbye here.
I think that's a great idea,
don't you?
It's a pretty place,
if you just ignore the
smell from all the bombs.
Armitage,
you know I hate it when you
talk like shit that way!
So what?
The whole planet
hates your kind,
without any damn reason at all.
Just like I did.
I know they do, but if...
there's someone else.
Oh, Ross, I love you
so very much!
Hey, go wherever you want,
but you're never
gonna lose me now.
Thank you for coming, sir.
This is an MFN
special news break.
Chairwoman Everheart's
car has just turned onto
the main thoroughfare
in downtown St. Lowel.
Her bright smile of success is
met with the cheers of literally
thousands of admirers
lining the streets.
The humanity of Mars
is now whole again.
One world, one nation.
Two thousand.
Look what Dad gave me!
What?
It's a little too
angelic for my taste,
but now I've got
some real power.
We'll need it.
Let's show 'em.
Look at all the space
we've got out here.
Room as far as the eye can see.
I grew up in a small house,
which was hard with a lot
of brothers and sisters.
It was always a battle
to find some small corner
to call your own.
When I became a man,
I thought I'd live in some
wide open place like Arizona.
But as I grew older, I realized
that I belonged in the city,
surrounded by the buildings
and the bustle of people,
a place like this is
too spacious for my taste.
So long as I've got
the right partner,
that's where I'll make my home.
And I won't care
who my neighbors are,
whether they're
Martians or robots.
A place we can
claim for our own.
Do you suppose
there is such a place?
If we can't find it,
then by god,
we'll create a place
just for the two of us.
Do you think there's
room for three?
You're kidding.
Well, when that happens,
I guess I'll just have
to think of something.