[BEOPETLE growls]
The cowards ran.
[VESTULSE growls]
[GUIDORO]
Relax, Vestulse.
The prince is nearly as useful
out of our custody as in it.
Let's proceed.
Hey. The heck was that light?
No clue.
But it was timely, huh?
Yeah.
[BOTH laughing]
So, uh... Any idea what
might've been the source of it?
[ALICIA]
Emilio, you jerk!
[SHUN]
Hey there! How'd you find us?
[ALICIA growls]
You'd better have
an amazing excuse.
I only left you two because...
Because you're an
inconsiderate jerk?
Anyway...
What did you boys think of
that incendiary light show
I put on?
I've discovered
a delightful metal,
which, when applied to heat,
emits a flame far hotter and
brighter than one would get
from burning wood.
Needless to say I found a
way to augment that property
by mixing the metal with a
highly combustible catalyst,
which not only sped up
the reaction,
but also resulted in a--
Sounds cool.
You'll have to fill us in
on all the details about that
sometime in the distant future.
Oh, I see. You youthful
types have no appreciation
for the nuance of science.
I must ask, both of you.
Why did you come?
What? Can you really
not figure that out?
We're your friends, Emilio.
We'll always come
when you need help,
even if you didn't ask us to.
Speaking of...
I'm curious about these
new friends you've made.
Where did the rest
of the Ignauts go?
A good number
fell in battle, or fled.
I told the rest to
split up and lay low.
So... What's with the professor?
Something tells me there's
more to him than meets the eye.
I'm nothing more than an
old tinkerer, I assure you.
Been retired for a while.
[SHUN]
Uh... Is it just me,
or do things feel a
little tense right now?
[EMILIO] I didn't expect
them to track me here,
but these two are
old friends of mine.
They won't bring any
harm to your cause.
If they're old
friends of yours,
then wouldn't that also make
them associates of the king?
[EMILIO]
Uh...
What's he getting at?
[DEMETRIO]
Let's go.
Wait... You're leaving?
[LOUISE]
As should you.
Hang around here, and you'll
be due for another visit
from the Truculent soon.
Hey! Wait for me!
Shun! Slow down,
we're coming, too!
[DEMETRIO]
Let's rest there a bit.
Make some plans.
We've been dealt a blow,
but we aren't finished.
[LOUISE]
We'll catch you later!
Later? Can't we come?
[PASCAL] So these new
companions of yours...
What are they about?
[EMILIO]
Don't play dumb, Pascal.
You've already worked
that out for yourself.
[PASCAL] Then you've joined
a band of revolutionaries
who'll stop at nothing
to end Delzaine's reign.
[PASCAL]
Hmm...
It's true...
You really did attempt
to assassinate the king,
didn't you?
Now I understand
why you were hesitant
to tell me about your
trip to the dungeons.
I know you two never
saw eye to eye,
but regardless, I didn't
take you for the kind
to kill his own father.
He's not my father!
He's the man who raised you!
And I'll be the man
who tears him down.
I've joined these rebels because
we share a common goal.
I'll align myself with bandits
if that's what's required.
To avenge my father at last.
I'd understand...
If you were sure what
you've heard is actually true.
But you're not sure.
You can't be, because
no one knows what occurred
between Delzaine and
the king but Delzaine.
[EMILIO]
I know what I've heard.
And do rumors count as proof?
I taught you better
than that, Emilio.
Trial comes before
the verdict. Use reason!
Even if he did kill
the previous king,
we can assume that he
had some kind of purpose.
Not everything in this world
is black and white.
Don't you think it
would be worth knowing
what drove him to do it?
He wanted the king's
throne for himself!
He killed my father to
satisfy his lust for power!
[PASCAL] That's just the
assumption you've made.
You have no proof.
Has it ever occurred to
you to ask Delzaine himself
to tell you what happened?
The path of vengeance is simple.
But that doesn't make it right.
Before you take revenge,
you have to learn the truth.
[SHUN] I wonder what those
two are off talking about.
I'm sure it's
just a good scolding.
Pascal can give
some lengthy lectures,
and after what Emilio pulled,
he deserves one.
And so do you!
Why didn't you talk him
out of it when he told you
what he was planning?
I don't know; does it matter?
[ALICIA] Those people you were
with are trying to overthrow
the kingdom. They're
willing to kill over it.
And Emilio's the last person
who should be around them.
Well when you put it
like that, I mean,
of course it's gonna sound bad.
Because civil war
is obviously a bad thing.
I get where you're coming from,
but the Ignauts are
good people. I think.
I wonder...
Did he tell you why he didn't
wanna bother asking me to come?
Huh? Is that
all this is about?
It sounds like you're just
mad at him for not inviting you
to come with us.
Idiot!
[FALARION squeaking]
[SHUN sighs]
Well that sure was awkward.
Like I care.
What does he know?
Emilio...
[ALICIA]
Emilio!
Huh? Oh, hi, Alicia!
Any trouble sneaking
in this time?
Nope! A couple of maids
saw me, but I'm too fast.
[EMILIO] They'll be mad
when they catch you.
They always are.
But exploring around
here is worth it.
[MAID 1A]
Alicia!
You know you're not allowed
to be inside the castle!
[MAID 1B] Let's not have
a repeat of last time!
Come out here!
Oh, Prince Emilio.
You haven't seen Alicia
around here, have you?
I have.
Looked like she was running
towards the east wing.
Your help is quite
appreciated, sir.
My, that girl can run.
[ALICIA laughs]
Thanks for getting rid of them.
No problem.
Although I don't really
understand what makes
this castle worth the trouble.
I dunno.
Usually I play in the forest,
but that can get kinda boring.
'Specially since there's
no one to play with.
That so?
I've actually been bored with
the castle for a good while now.
I've never been
to the forest.
It sounds interesting.
Come see!
I'll grab you before
the next time I go, 'kay?
You're gonna love it!
There're giant boars
and mushrooms,
and weird bugs and every
color you can think of!
This is gonna be so much fun!
Oh yeah?
[BOTH laughing]
[EMILIO grunting]
Emilio, why?
What are you doing?
[ELJUIA] I gave the
town a thorough sweep.
It doesn't seem that the Royal
Guard has any influence here.
[LOUISE] We were about
due for a bit of good news.
[DEMETRIO]
Still... We can't stay long.
Right. So what's our
next course of action, then?
First off, we
replenish our numbers.
We sustained more
casualties than expected.
And most of those
who weren't lost
are scattered about
the countryside.
[ELJUIA]
What of Emilio and Shun?
Shall they stay with us?
Do you still trust them?
We're not in a position
to turn away allies.
And I don't have to trust
the prince to see how
he might prove to be useful.
Besides...
Besides what?
[DEMETRIO] It might
have taken both of them,
but Emilio and Shun did
manage to hold their own
against a Truculent in battle.
That has to put them well ahead
of most of our current recruits.
And the other two?
We'll just have to
watch them closely.
[SHUN] Look, have you seen a
group of four weirdos around,
or haven't you?
Get lost.
I'm tryin' to close shop.
Just hear me out.
One of 'em has a big old
feather sticking out of his hat.
And there's this other guy
who looks a lot like a lady.
I was fooled.
No, haven't seen 'em.
[DEMETRIO]
You can let him through.
[SHOPKEEPER]
Huh?
This one's a friend.
[SHUN gasps]
[ELJUIA]
I see you came alone.
Where are the others?
Pascal and Emilio are
having some sort of argument
right now.
And somethin' happened
to piss off Alicia too.
So basically everyone's
mad and I'm tired of it.
Oh. Sorry I forgot to
introduce you earlier.
I think you'll
get along, though.
Don't fret about it.
So how exactly do you know them?
Well, I met them
through Emilio,
but they've been friends
of his for years.
I think maybe Pascal
used to tutor him.
Like back when he was
still the head of research
at the Royal Laboratory.
That's an interesting
line of work.
Yeah, anyway...
I'm tryin' to get to Babylon.
Know what I should do?
Babylon? Why?
It's where the only way
I have of getting home is.
And since Eljuia saw me
there in the future,
I figure I should stop wasting
time and go for it.
That is what I saw.
Look, guys, I don't really
care about politics or revenge.
I just wanna find
a way back home.
The road to Babylon
is fraught with danger.
[DEMETRIO] The waters
between here and there
are far from welcoming.
The people whose lands
we'll pass are even less so.
Take one faulty step,
and you'll be dead.
Dead? It's that bad?
Does that news frighten you?
Yeah. But that doesn't mean
I won't go through with it.
I have to get back
no matter what.
Dad's never around,
so mom's stuck worrying
at home by herself.
[DEMETRIO] As chance would have
it, Delzaine is going that way,
so we're heading
to Babylon as well.
He won't be half
as well protected
as he is while
he's at the castle.
We haven't had a chance
like this in a while.
I'll let you come with,
but don't expect us
to babysit you.
It's pure survival of
the fittest out there.
That's not a problem.
I can protect myself fine.
That's excellent to hear.
[SHUN]
Hey. There you are.
Been looking for ya.
[EMILIO]
That so...
Sounded like you got a pretty
good scolding from Pascal.
He put ya through
the old guilt trip?
He tried his best to,
but he doesn't know
what he's talking about.
And you seriously
think that you do?
[EMILIO]
What?
Look, whatever it
is that Pascal said,
he said it 'cause
he cares about you.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
bothered to come after us.
Sure.
Well anyhow, it's pretty late.
We should get some
rest while we can.
Demetrio and the others
have already started
setting up a campsite.
It's this way.
[FALARION squeaks]
Go home, Alicia.
This isn't your fight.
There's no reason for
you to involve yourself
in what I have to do.
It's my choice,
and I'm coming.
[FALARION squeaks]
You can do as you like.
That's what I just said!
[SHUN]
By the way... Where's Pascal?
[laughing]
Check it out!
It's my handy-dandy
flamethrower!
[LOUISE]
Amazing!
You have to let me try it!
[ELJUIA] So how does this
contraption of yours work?
What do you know...
Here I thought I'd have
to help him find the place.
Ah. I see you boys
made it back.
This fellow's pretty
savvy for an old timer.
But I felt so young!
Weird. But I guess everyone's
getting along, at least.
Excuse me.
I need a few men
to scout the area.
You two go with Felix.
[SHUN]
Hey! Stop!
[EMILIO]
Release me!
Welcome to patrol.
[SHUN]
Stop draggin' me, dude!
Now, then.
I guess we ought to start
getting ready for our journey.
Yes, sir.
[LOUISE]
Hey.
How goes it? Are you that
Alicia I've heard about?
[ALICIA]
Um... Yeah.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, then.
I'm Louise,
another of those rebels
your friends joined up with.
Nice to meet you, Louise.
[FALARION squeaks]
So tell me.
Do you plan to join us
for this little trip?
Yeah.
As long as Emilio's going
to go, I will as well.
Interesting.
Is there a problem?
Not at all.
It's just that I've
been getting sick of being
the only girl on
the crew, you know?
Well, I mean, it's pretty
hard to tell with Eljuia,
but the point
stands nonetheless.
What I'm getting at is that male
company can get annoying.
Which is why I'm
excited to finally have
another girl around
to suffer with.
I just wanted to offer you
an extra warm welcome.
Thanks.
But listen,
you and your friends
are plotting to overthrow
the kingdom, aren't you?
[LOUISE]
That we are.
Then why is everybody...
so positive?
It doesn't really seem to fit.
You thought we'd be all
conniving and bitter, right?
I mean, rebels are just
self-righteous bandits, really.
Aren't they?
Yeah, well...
When you get down to it,
there aren't a whole lot of real
differences between you and us.
If you change the
circumstances we grew up with,
our roles could
have been reversed.
By the way, Alicia.
If I'm correct,
Emilio is the heir
apparent of the kingdom.
[ALICIA]
Uh-huh. Yeah, he sure is.
So then who is that Shun kid
to be confident enough
to pick so many fights with him?
Honestly, there's not
much I could tell you.
I mean, he says he came
from the surface, but...
He can use a Warp Relic.
Huh...
[ELJUIA]
Oh, Louise!
Could I trouble you to
give me a hand with this?
Yeah, sure.
Sorry, dear, duty calls.
I like you, Alicia.
I think we're gonna
make great friends.
So what did you
need help with?
Demetrio wants us to pack
our essentials tonight.
Think you could help me
decide what's worth keeping?
[LOUISE]
Yeah, sure thing.
--What a weird girl.
--[FALARION squeaks]
[SHUN]
This is purgatory.
Emilio's way too
pouty to talk to.
And Felix is about
as chatty as a boulder.
[SHUN]
Maybe he's just shy.
Only one way to find out.
[SHUN sighs]
[SHUN]
Here goes nothing.
Hey, Felix, I was wondering...
What exactly did the king
do to make all you guys
want to depose him so bad?
His soldiers are tough.
What makes it worth
fighting them?
I'd like to know, too.
[FELIX] Throughout all of
Endora, injustice runs rampant.
Whether it be due
to race or money,
many are born without
a fair chance at life.
They have it hard
from start to finish,
offered nothing
but pain and cruelty.
Many of our comrades
are drawn from such lives.
That's why they come
to fight with us.
They're hoping
for a better world.
For the world that Demetrio
is working to build.
That's why I fight with him.
Change the world?
That's ambitious.
[SHUN]
Huh...
[FELIX] We'll cover more
ground if we split up.
You two look around that way.
I'll see you back at camp.
I guess we're
on our own, then.
[FELIX groaning]
[HOOLIGANS laughing]
[DEMETRIO] Seems to me it's
a bit late into the night
for you to be doing
a chemistry project.
[PASCAL] Yeah, not the
best habit I've picked up.
Though, I must say, it's not
entirely without its advantages.
Really?
Did you pick it up while
you were working
at the Royal Laboratory?
That was a long time ago.
Do you know what Delzaine
is trying to accomplish?
Afraid not.
I was just an employee.
[DEMETRIO] I can tell
you aren't lying, but...
I'd like to know
more than anyone,
but he's never once
stated his intentions.
King Delzaine is not
the kind of man who shares
the workings of
his inner thoughts.
Not to anyone.
Not even to his own son.
I can hardly blame
the king for that.
Our prince is
still a spoiled boy.
He has much to learn
before he'll be fit to be king.
[PASCAL] Like Rodney said,
warp particles would appear
to be falling in number.
Could this have something to
do with Babel's restoration?
All right! Everybody
get ready to move out.
[SHUN]
I can't stop.
I have to get
back to the surface.
[LOUISE]
Next episode, "Girl."