[GUIDORO]
We can't let Ibelda run rampant.
I'm going after him.
[ALL gasp]
[SHUN]
Wait, what, by yourself?
You can't, he's way too
strong. He's a monster.
And don't forget about those
creatures that fight with him.
If you fight him alone,
you'll be outnumbered.
[GUIDORO] It doesn't matter.
I have to try.
Well then I'm coming with you.
That'll still be
no match for him.
Think about our last
battle. Demetrio?
[DEMETRIO]
Mm. Felix. Mischa.
I ask you both to assist Guidoro
and Louise on my behalf.
[gasps]
[FELIX] If that's the
task you need us for.
Fine, I'll do it.
Slow us down and
I'll cut you loose.
Duly noted.
Now we're talking. Ibelda
won't know what hit him.
It still isn't enough.
[SHUN]
Huh?
I appreciate the back up.
[EMILIO] Yeah. I only wish I
could join the hunt myself.
[GUIDORO] I know, but you
have burdens to deal with.
Building a future
for this kingdom,
to name the most obvious.
That's exactly what
Demetrio said.
[AARON]
Prince Emilio.
You have my word; your comrade
will come back alive.
[EMILIO]
Make sure you return as well.
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
Until we meet again.
You always were bossy, but
now it's almost a cool thing.
Shut up.
[SHUN laughs]
This book could be useful.
I have my doubts about this one.
[PASCAL sighs] It was hard to
find any texts concerning Babel.
The trouble with
Warp Particle research
is figuring out where to begin.
Yes, I agree.
The volume of literature
on the subject only
complicates matters.
Well, we knew what we were
getting into, right?
It'll be fine. With Rodney
and Alicia's help,
I'm certain we'll
find what we need.
That we will.
[ALICIA]
Here's the last load.
[RODNEY] Huh? Thank you, Alicia.
You've been a great help.
[FALARION chirps]
[RODNEY chuckles]
The field, look.
[FELIX]
All dead.
[GUIDORO]
How awful.
[MISCHA] Seems like Ibelda's
not our biggest problem.
True, but at least he's
one we can solve.
[DEMETRIO] We've received
reports claiming that numerous
areas of farmland
across the country
have dried up and withered.
Practically overnight.
Yes, but this isn't just
a matter of crop failure,
forests and grasslands seem
to be suffering as well.
For real? How come?
I would wager that this is the
first of many ways that the
loss of Warp Particles will make
itself known in this world.
It's all well and good to
bring an end to the violence.
But it won't mean much if we
all starve to death afterwards.
And is that to be the
fate of the farmers
who lost their fields?
Some of them had stores
to fall back on,
and we're helping out the rest.
But if the problem
continues to perpetuate,
supplies won't last for long.
It'll turn into a famine, then.
Even as we speak,
Pascal and Joseph
are doing their best to discover
why our Warp Particles
have been disappearing.
Until their work is completed,
the most we can hope to provide
is a little bit of
damage control.
And maybe some peace
of mind for the afflicted.
[JOSEPH] There are a few regions
that have retained Warp Particle
concentrations. Perhaps these
people could relocate.
A good thought, but it could
only work in the short run.
It's purely chance those
regions have been spared.
Diminishment rates
aren't changing as
the particle count lowers,
so if we can't stop this--
Life is a fragile
thing down here.
if we want to ensure
it continues,
then we can't waste time.
[JOSEPH]
Agreed.
[SHUN]
Well, this sucks.
I mean, talk about things
taking a turn for the worse.
[EMILIO]
Shun.
Uh? That's a somber
face. What's up?
There's something we
should go check.
[SHUN] If you're gonna drag me
around, at least say why.
Can't you guess?
[SHUN]
Uh?
This is the exact spot where
you appeared in Endora.
Oh, yeah. So it is.
Is this a nostalgia thing?
[EMILIO]
Do you sense anything?
Like...?
[EMILIO] If this is the place
where you appeared,
it could be where you go back.
[SHUN] That's the dumbest
thing I've heard all day.
[EMILIO]
Just try it.
[SHUN] Come on, dude.
If it was as easy as that,
I'd've gotten home
ages ago. Sheesh.
Thought you brought me here
for somethin' important.
You heard the same
reports I did.
Endora's running out of
time, and quickly.
Soon enough, this really will
be the land of the dead.
There's no reason for you
to bear witness to that.
You should get back to the
surface before it ends.
[SHUN]
Hey! What's down here, anyway?
Any idea how deep it goes?
Maybe we could drop a torch
or somethin' and check.
Shut up and listen. I'm trying
to save your life here.
[SHUN] You shut up!
You need to stop tryin'
to solve my problems
and deal with your own.
[gasps]
[SHUN]
"The land of the dead?"
It sounds like you've
already given up.
[EMILIO]
I'm not giving up, I'm--
[SHUN]
Well then do something!
You're the prince! If
anyone can, it's you.
Fine, so what do you
think I should do!?!
Or do you not know either?!
As if you would listen! You'd
rather go cry in the corner.
[EMILIO grunts]
Bastard!
[SHUN gasps]
[SHUN laughs, yelps]
[EMILIO]
Shun!
[SHUN, EMILIO scream]
Are you all right, Shun?
Well, uh. I'm still
in one piece.
Uh?
Hey look! Stairs!
[EMILIO]
Good. Try to swing to them.
[SHUN]
That was my plan.
[grunting]
All right!
They're solid, so come on down!
[EMILIO grunts]
I wonder where these could lead.
No tellin'. They're part
of your castle.
I figured you would know.
[EMILIO]
Well, I don't.
[SHUN] There's the useless
prince I remember.
[EMILIO]
Shut up!
Unless you have some
climbing gear,
I guess we might
as well head down.
Yeah. Down it is.
To think that the dungeons
used to go this deep.
Feel free to say sorry. Man.
If you hadn't tried
to push me we'd be--
I'm sorry for overestimating
your ability.
Nice one. If these kept going,
d'you think they'd hit
the surface sometime?
[EMILIO]
Don't know.
[SHUN] Well it doesn't
feel like they do.
I'd say look,
but I'm blind here.
[EMILIO]
Same.
[SHUN] So what do you think
we should do now?
You're the one who grew up here,
so if there's a way out,
you oughtta know how to find it.
[FRAMA]
Who's there?
[gasping]
[BOTH]
Uh?
So, who is this guy?
A prisoner.
[gasps]
[EMILIO]
Tell us who you are.
Why should I acknowledge
your question when
you refuse to answer mine?
I am Emilio La--
My name's Emilio.
Emilio... Emilio...
That name's familiar to me.
[EMILIO gasps]
[FRAMA]
Or it used to be...
Who put you down here?
Was it Delzaine?
[FRAMA] No, it wasn't him.
It was King Alzerm.
[EMILIO]
Really?
King Alzerm was your
real dad, wasn't he?
Correct.
I am employed in this castle as
a servant. What did you do?
I fought in the
service of the king.
A short eternity ago, I was
the leader of the Truculent.
[EMILIO] And how did
you come to be here?
[FRAMA growls]
[BOTH gasp]
With one great blunder,
I brought the crown's wrath upon
myself and was cast down.
But I am ever loyal to the king,
and it was on his
behalf that I acted.
I would try the same
again, I swear.
What exactly--
[FRAMA yells]
[FRAMA]
I did not betray my king!
I think we should get a little
further back from this guy.
And having served him, what
do you think of King Alzerm?
[FRAMA] The King was an
incredible man. A great leader.
His ambition was second to none,
as befits a mighty ruler.
We of the Truculent
served him proudly,
happy to be both his
shield and sword.
Our loyalty was limitless. We'd
follow any order from our king.
Our only purpose
was to serve him.
The new Truculent weren't
nearly that devoted.
All right, then.
Let's say that the king was a
good man and you were loyal.
Why would he throw
you down here?
[FRAMA] Because he...
He became corrupted.
Turned into something he wasn't.
[gasps]
[FRAMA]
By a man...
Just one? Was it Delzaine?
[FRAMA]
Of course not!
[EMILIO]
So then who?
[FRAMA] He made a fool out
of everyone in this castle.
He disarmed us with his smile.
Undid us with the
sweetness of his words.
[FRAMA] That traveler... He was
equal parts vile and charming.
He went to work the
day we brought him in,
turning us into his pawns.
[DELZAINE] A corpse near
the castle will bring bad luck
and disease.
Deal with it, Frama.
[FRAMA]
Right.
[FRAMA] I believe he's
still alive, My Lord.
[ALZERM] Then finish what
nature couldn't, and go.
[FRAMA]
I shall.
Would you like to keep this
strange machine of his?
What?
He's from the surface.
Get him to the castle,
now, quickly.
Should we?
We don't know what a surface
dweller might be capable of.
He's just a man.
If he proves himself
to be ill-tempered, we can
always kill him then.
[DELZAINE]
As you say.
[FRAMA] My one regret is
that I stayed my hand.
I should have killed him as soon
as the king commanded me to.
And that would have
been the end of it.
Like everyone, I had heard
the stories of travelers
from the surface
appearing in Endora.
But I never truly believed them.
Certainly never expected
to find one myself.
Before long the traveler
made a full recovery
and was able to
set out once more.
He returned to the surface and
came back bearing gifts.
The king's fascination
swiftly grew into respect.
Too quickly, the traveler
gained his trust.
[ALZERM] So how is it that
you're able to travel freely
between our worlds?
[TRAVELER]
I fear I might bore you.
Suffice to say, it took
years of research.
Then I take it
you're a scientist.
I am.
[ALZERM]
Tell me everything you know.
As you command.
[FRAMA] That's when the traveler
gained the king's ear,
and began to feed it poison.
What tales did he tell?
How was this man able to
maintain Alzerm's interest?
He saw the king's
ambitious nature
and took advantage of it.
Alzerm had just
established dominion
over the last few independent
states of Endora,
and with the entire continent
united beneath him,
he sought to conquer even more.
And lifted his gaze
up to the surface.
[ALZERM]
This level of technology
is common on the surface?
[TRAVELER] Yes. Endora
is a marvelous place.
Beautiful beyond measure.
But thanks to advances
we've made on the surface,
my people have luxuries
that yours do not.
Oh? I would hear more
of these luxuries.
To name a few,
larged winged vehicles
that expedite travel.
Handheld tools that allow speech
to cross great distance.
And weapons more powerful
than you could imagine.
I can imagine much.
You've piqued my interest.
[TRAVELER]
Your Grace, if I may.
There is a proposal I
would like to discuss.
Wilderness abounds
in this world.
It's as if you never
thought to harness it.
To bend nature to your will.
You mean such a thing
is actually possible?
[TRAVELER]
Yes.
I've contrived a way involving
the science of my world,
and the Warp Particles of yours.
[gasps]
I have my doubts.
Is it not unwise to alter
the course of nature?
[TRAVELER]
As I was saying.
I could take the power
of the living world,
and place it at your fingertips.
[FRAMA]
That cur.
He always had the words to
bend us to his schemes.
[ALZERM]
Nothing?! You had one task!
How are you no
closer to reaching
the surface than
when you started?!
[RESEARCHERS gasping]
Leave my sight.
Uh!
[ALZERM] Useless fools have
no place in my company.
[DELZAINE]
Please reconsider, Brother!
These men have done great
work in every other field.
Don't make me
dismiss you again.
[RESEARCHER 18A]
Sir.
[ALZERM grunts]
Useless, the lot of them.
They cannot hope
to compare to him.
Permit me to speak my mind.
I fear we've forgotten the
words of our ancestors.
They warned us to
never deal lightly
with those from the surface.
[ALZERM]
Be silent!
[DELZAINE]
Uh!
[TRAVELER] Ah. So this is
what you call a Warp Relic.
Yes. You must not have
these on the surface.
[TRAVELER] No. The power to
draw in the energy around you
and shape it with your
own is exclusive
to the people of Endora.
It's magnificent.
[ALZERM]
Hmph.
[TRAVELER]
Your Grace. What say you?
I could combine the mighty
force you've shown me
with the technology
of the surface.
But only if you will it.
[gasps]
[ALZERM]
I will it.
[gasps]
[FRAMA] He fooled my
king with honeyed words
and promises of strength.
[TRAVELER]
Your Grace,
I think you'll enjoy what
I brought you today.
[ALZERM]
Mm?
And what might this do?
--[ALZERM gasps]
--[FRAMA] Wha--
How--? What is it?
[TRAVELER]
A weapon.
Here.
[TRAVELER]
It's called a pistol.
[ALZERM]
Can anyone wield it?
[gasps]
Show me what it takes
to kill with this tool.
[gasps]
I would happily instruct
you in its use,
but it might be safer
to do so in the Garden.
[FRAMA]
From that day forward,
my king was changed
beyond return.
Uh! Awestruck by the
traveler's display of power,
he became deaf to
any other voice.
Especially with Babel.
[BOTH gasp]
Babel? What did Babel
have to do with it?!
[FRAMA] It was that man who
told the king to restore it.
So it was Alzerm who
started rebuilding it?
[FRAMA]
Yes.
The traveler promised
that once it was complete,
Alzerm could go to
the surface as he did.
But that isn't all
that would go.
[EMILIO]
What else?
He wanted to siphon
off our Warp Particles
and use them on the surface.
[BOTH gasp]
[TRAVELER]
I believe that Warp Particles
are the reason why this
world is so verdant.
By manipulating them,
we could render snow-capped
mountains arable,
or reverse the effects
of over-farming.
You would become the king
who mastered nature.
Your name would echo
through the histories
of both our worlds forever.
Would this enable
us to exterminate
the dragons who live
in those mountains?
[TRAVELER]
Of course.
Don't do this. We depend
on Warp Particles
in more ways than
we could understand.
They shouldn't be
meddled with at all,
let alone shipped off to the
surface, never to return--
[TRAVELER]
Another superstitious myth.
Frankly, if it weren't for
outdated beliefs such as this,
I doubt that Endora
would have fallen
so far behind the surface.
Instead of dwelling in
the past with your dead,
seek out brighter
truths in the future.
Look rather to the golden
age of prosperity
that your country
is about to enter.
From the results I've seen you
produce, I don't doubt it.
But Brother--
I have decided!
[FRAMA] Lord Delzaine
had been suspicious of
the traveler's motives
from the beginning.
But the king was deaf even
to the words of his brother.
He was practically brainwashed.
[FRAMA] He'll ruin this world,
stealing our Warp Particles.
I won't allow him to
take Endora's soul.
[gasps] Stop!
Frama. That is your name, right?
What are you plotting,
you charlatan?
If you intend to
force my confession,
you'll need to use more
than stern words.
Convince me you're
advising the king with
the betterment of our
country as your goal.
And I will walk away.
[TRAVELER chuckles]
[FRAMA]
What do you find funny?
[TRAVELER] If it was
possible to convince you,
we never would've
come to this point.
Luckily, I don't care.
I've more important
things to do
than ease an old
lizard's worries.
[FRAMA]
You bastard!
[FRAMA growls]
[TRAVELER]
Supposing I told all.
Do you think the king would
believe your side of the story?
[gasps]
He sees you as little
more than a loyal pet.
And yet you dare to draw your
weapon on the man he's entrusted
with the keys to the kingdom?
[FRAMA grunts]
[TRAVELER groaning]
[TRAVELER] Guards! Somebody,
help! He's trying to kill me!
I was right about you.
[SOLDIER 18A]
What happened?!
[SOLDIER 18B] What'd you do
to him? Frama, you cretin!
Have you lost your damn mind?
[FRAMA]
No! He's faking it...
That's one fool down.
[FRAMA]
My Lord, I--
You tried to take
my dear friend's life.
[FRAMA] Forgive me sir, please.
That man, he framed-
That's enough!
You truly are a vile,
jealous creature.
[FRAMA screams]
[EMILIO] So you've been down
here all these years?
[FRAMA] Yes, I'm sure they
thought I'd starve down here,
assuming I survived
the cut, and the fall.
Did you find out anything else
before you were dropped?
[FRAMA]
No.
Anything that might help us
to reverse what was done?
[FRAMA]
Nothing.
Could you tell me what the
traveler from the surface
looked like? Or do you
know his name at least?
His name? The name...
I don't... I can't remember!
If you noticed anything
about how he was able
to travel between here and
the surface, please tell me.
[FRAMA] He had something,
but he kept it hidden.
Did'ja ever get a glimpse?
If I could find the thing that
he had. I could go home!
Wait, go home?
Do you mean the surface
is your home?
[SHUN]
Yeah.
[FRAMA] You're the same then.
You're just like that man!
Huh? No, not really.
[FRAMA grunting]
[screams]
[gasps]
[FRAMA]
I will never make the mistake
of sparing a surface
dweller's life again!
[SHUN whimpers]
[FRAMA yells]
[gasps]
[EMILIO gasps]
What's this? Where are we?
[car horn honking]
[gasping]
[FRAMA]
Next episode, "Surface."