This place. Where are we?
[SHUN]
I'm back. I'm really back.
I'm back home!
Back home?
You mean we're on
the... the surface?
[SHUN] Damn straight!
That's the real sky up there!
And we're about to see a real
sunset! This is awesome!
There's no way.
How could this happen?
[SHUN]
I'm finally home!
Well. This is my place.
Wow.
Can't believe I'm here.
[MAKIKO]
Hello?
Hi. Uh. Long time no see.
How have you been?
[crash, footsteps]
[gasps]
Hey there, mom.
Um. Sorry for pulling
that disappearing act.
I'm sure I must've
given you a scare.
[MAKIKO cries]
Shun! You're all right!
Sorry for making you worry,
but I'm perfectly fine.
What a relief. It's so
good to see you home.
[laughs]
Uh...
All right, mom, it's
good to see you too.
I'm a little
overwhelmed right now.
Mom, this is Emilio.
He helped me out while I
was stranded in his world.
Well...
It's more like helped
each other out.
And somehow, he ended up
coming back here with me.
From where?
[SHUN]
Oh. Well, uh...
I'll just say it.
This whole time,
I've been underground
in a world called Endora.
An underground world?
[SHUN]
Yeah, I'm guessin' that sounds
pretty far-fetched
to you, doesn't it?
But take a look at his outfit.
No one from our world would
be caught dead in that.
Solid evidence, right?
Pure science.
There is nothing wrong
with my outfit, Shun.
All I'm sayin' is that the only
people who dress as weird as you
in this world are cosplayers.
How dare you compare me to them!
Who is "them"?
I don't know who cosplayers
are, you tell me!
Ah, geez, uh... Cosplay's
hard to explain.
[EMILIO] Don't think that
you can use my ignorance..
Aren't you two quite a pair!
I'm glad to see you made such a
good friend while you were away.
--He's not my friend, okay?
--He is no friend of mine.
[SHUN] I've gotta admit,
I'm kinda surprised by how
not freaked out you are
to hear about this.
Don't get me wrong,
it's shocking.
But I'm an archaeologist.
This is hardly the first time
I've heard about a secret world
existing beneath us.
Now, ancient texts are subject
to interpretation, but some of
them seem to claim knowledge
of specific entrances to it.
The eastern Himalayas, Northern
Russia, and there's one more.
Around the north-western
border of China.
Then some people do
know about Endora.
So it would seem.
[gasps]
[MAKIKO] The majority of experts
say it's all fake, of course.
But there have always
been a few holdouts
who at least believed
it was possible.
[SHUN] And it sounds like
you must be one of them.
Yep. Or I was until
you confirmed it.
Your father believes it as well.
Dad, really?
Okay, but even if you figured
an underground world
might secretly exist somewhere,
you can't have thought
that's where I was.
That was our theory
as a matter of fact.
Wait, seriously?
I can't believe you two!
So I guess you didn't
lose your minds worrying
about what'd happened
to me after all, huh?
[MAKIKO] You cannot imagine
how panicked we were!
Since you went missing,
your father has spent
every waking moment
trying to find out more about
that world you were stranded in.
I didn't realize, sorry. I guess
he's at the office right now?
Yes, he's taken to sleeping
there to save time,
so I barely ever see him.
I doubt he's gotten better
about answering his phone.
Cool! You know what, I think
I'll go there tomorrow
and surprise him.
Would'ya care to tag along?
What else do I have to do?
I can't wait to see
the look on his face.
[doorbell chimes]
[DELIVERY GUY 19A]
Got a delivery!
[SHUN] Whoa! This is
the good stuff, too!
I thought you might
react like that.
I don't know too much
about the underground,
but I doubt it has great sushi.
Thanks for the meal!
It's delicious!
I've been fantasizing about
surface food for so long,
but tasting it is-- Uh.
What's the matter? Dig in.
Feel free to have
as much as you like.
We have plenty.
So this is what food's
like on the surface.
Oh yeah, this'll be the first
time you've eaten up here,
won't it?
You must've put a great deal
of effort into preparing this.
Someone did.
It's actually delivery.
[EMILIO]
A strange name for food.
[gasps]
[SHUN] Delivery just means
someone brought it to us.
She already said that
we call this stuff sushi.
I was raised with the
luxuries of a castle.
Yet, I've never seen
such a beautiful meal.
What?
Yeah, sorry it tends
to slip my mind,
but Emilio here's a prince
back in his world.
Wait, I'm hosting royalty?
I'm so sorry.
I would've found us something
better than delivery
if I'd known.
We could at least go out
somewhere if you'd like.
Don't worry, I can tell you for
a fact he's used to way worse.
This is a finely made and
tastefully decorated dish,
well suited for the
food it contains.
Yeah, I'm pretty positive it
came out of a factory, man.
This factory must
have great artisans.
These engravings are sublime.
On second thought,
perhaps it's for the best
that we didn't go out.
You're weirdin' out my mom
dude, shut up and eat.
This is high class sushi!
Eat it before it dries out.
You might as well be asking
me to eat a fine painting.
[SHUN sighs]
I give up.
Pretty dang good, right?
[EMILIO mumbles]
[SHUN]
Uh?
[MAKIKO]
What's he trying to say?
Probably that his mind's blown.
[EMILIO groaning]
Emilio?
[EMILIO] This flavor. I think
it might destroy my mouth.
My nose! It burns!
Wasabi?
[SHUN laughs] There wasn't
even any on it! Hey.
[EMILIO]
Mm?
Look, Emilio, it's totally cool
if you can't handle
the taste of spicy tuna.
It's fine. There are a lot
of children on the surface
who can't take the heat,
so don't sweat it.
You think you can goad
me just like that?
[MAKIKO laughs]
[SHUN]
Don't pretend you can take it!
[EMILIO]
Shut up!
[MAKIKO] So, I have to ask, how
did a trip to your father's work
end with you finding
another world?
And what was this Endora like?
Guess I'd better
start at page one.
Well, basically, I found a
weird crystal in dad's office,
and the next thing
I knew I was gone.
The first thing I saw
in Endora, was this guy,
and it turned out he had
plenty'a problems of his own.
There are all sorts
of people in Endora.
Most of them are basically
the same as us,
but there are also these
guys called Zoozians.
They're pretty different.
No two look quite alike.
[laughs] Would you believe
I flew on a dragon once?
The people aren't advanced,
but some have cool abilities.
They get 'em by summoning
these things called Warp Relics.
Believe it or not, I can do it
too. Not sure how that works.
You can what?
[EMILIO] He can materialize a
weapon from his body, as can I.
[MAKIKO]
A weapon?!
The first time we fought Ibelda,
I was shakin' so bad
I thought I'd drop it.
If we hadn't been able
to summon Warp Relics,
I doubt that either one of us
would've survived that battle.
Why were you fighting, Shun?!
Is this place really as
dangerous as it sounds?
[EMILIO]
No. It isn't always, but...
...at the moment, the whole
country's in a state of chaos.
[SHUN]
And following him around put me
smack-dab in the
middle of most of it.
If it was really that dangerous,
then you shouldn't
have followed him.
Why act so reckless?
[SHUN] I didn't have
much choice at the time.
I wanted to find a way home
more than anything,
but I didn't know
where to start.
Emilio was my guide there,
I needed him. A little.
But all that is in the past now.
You're on my turf here, so if
you wanna get home, you need me.
[EMILIO]
Very well.
I humbly request that you
repay the favor I am owed.
[laughs] Looks like the tables
have turned, doesn't it?
If you wanna ask
anything about the surface,
you'd better hope
I'm in a good mood.
[SHUN laughing]
Stop lording it over him, Shun.
Forgive his rudeness,
we raised him better.
It's fine, mom!
Emilio would talk to me
like this all the
time back in Endora.
[MAKIKO]
That's because he's a prince.
A bit of haughtiness is
to be expected of him.
[SHUN] Don't expect anything
from him. He's useless.
[EMILIO]
What's this?
You know, just one
of a million things
we have up here that
you've never heard of.
It's called a photograph.
They're like, instant,
perfect paintings.
[MAKIKO] They're great for
preserving little moments.
Thanks to photos, anyone can see
how adorable baby Shun was.
Here!
[SHUN]
Whoa! Stop, stop, stop!
Why are you showing
him that? Not cool!
You're not even
naked in this one.
Now simmer down.
[SHUN]
I'll simmer down when I'm ready!
And please don't pull
out those other ones.
[SHUN]
Gimme that. You've seen enough.
He gets red when he's
super embarrassed.
No more pictures, got it?!
[MAKIKO]
Hm... Can you not handle it?
[SHUN]
Mom!
I suppose the others
back in Endora
must be wondering
where we've gone.
Yeah, they're prob'ly just as
worried as my parents were.
[EMILIO] I can't stop thinking
about that crazy story we heard
from the prisoner.
[SHUN] About the traveler
from the surface?
Yeah, I wish we knew
the end of it.
The end is still on its way.
[SHUN]
Don't worry.
[EMILIO]
Mm?
My dad's pretty smart.
If there's a way to get back
to Endora, he'll figure
it out in no time.
[EMILIO] I hope you realize
how lucky you are
to have such loving parents.
Where did that come from?
[EMILIO]
Nowhere.
Well, I guess it's true.
My mom gets a little
kooky sometimes,
but she's always
been there for me.
And dad's pretty awful at
the whole being there thing,
'cause he works so much.
But that might just be his way
of showing that he cares
about the family.
I see.
Goodnight, man.
Night.
[SHUN] Are you... sure you
wanna go out in that?
[MAKIKO] I can run and grab
you something of Shun's.
I do appreciate the offer.
But I'm much swifter
in my own clothes.
If something happens...
Nothing's going to happen.
I told you, dude.
We're not in Endora anymore.
[EMILIO]
Well, I like to be prepared.
Fine. But don't take it
personally if I pretend
not to know you.
--[laughs]
--[EMILIO] Loyal, aren't you?
[SHUN]
See ya later tonight!
Uh.
If you're going
to act like this,
then just walk a few feet ahead.
Nah, you're like a kitten.
If I let'cha outta my
sight, you'll get lost.
[FRIEND 19A]
That you, Shun?
[SHUN]
Hey!
Feels like it's been forever!
Say, weren't you supposed
to be taking a break
from school to go travel
overseas, or something?
Uh! I guess my parents
came up with that story
when I went missing.
[FRIEND 19A]
So you're back! How was it?
Yeah, it was fun! [laughs]
Well next time,
send me at least a postcard
or somethin', will ya?
[SHUN]
Yeah, sorry.
Uh. Did ya bring back a friend?
Oh, yeah. You could say that.
[FRIEND 19A] I've never
seen clothes like that.
Where ya from?
Oh, nowhere, he's uh--
It's cosplay.
Uh.
[FRIEND 19A]
Ah, that explains it.
You're pullin' it off
pretty well, man,
that wig looks super real!
[laughs]
[FRIEND 19A]
Anyway. We'll see you at school!
[SHUN]
Later! [sighs]
Have I even explained what
cosplay is to you, yet?
No you have not, but it would
appear that if I mention it,
then I can dress
however I please
without anyone bothering me.
I guess that's the gist.
Ya know you're kinda
smart when you wanna be.
Let me guess, you expected
me to lose my composure
when confronted with
an unfamiliar world.
Yeah, that's pretty on the mark.
Your weaknesses are your own.
Hey! I did just fine!
Don't make me stop helping you.
[EMILIO]
Hush.
[inaudible]
This is nothing like Endora.
Bet you're startin'
to wish you could stay.
I have to admit that I
haven't felt so carefree
in a long while.
Knowin' that there's zero chance
of getting attacked here
does take the edge off.
It still doesn't make
any sense to me
that I was transported to
the surface along with you,
but I never imagined I
would like it this much.
You keep on talkin' like that,
I'm gonna think you like me.
[EMILIO]
Whatever.
[SHUN]
Okay. I had fun, too.
And regardless of the why,
I'm glad you're here.
Yes. I'll see if he's available.
[phone rings]
[ASANAGA]
Mm?
[click]
[RECEPTION 19A]
Shun is here to see you, sir.
[ASANAGA] Very well, then.
See him through, please.
[EMILIO gasps]
[gasps]
Yo, Dad!
[ASANAGA]
Shun.
Sorry for the scare.
Came back as quick as I could.
Yes, well I'm just
glad you're safe.
And who's this?
This is Emilio.
He's one of the people I met
while I was down in Endora.
[ASANAGA]
Endora?
The underground world.
You guessed it right.
You and mom.
You don't say!
It seemed like a long shot,
but some part of me just knew.
It's all as I expected.
[SHUN]
Dang it.
I was hopin' I would get
to surprise you with it.
[ASANAGA]
Oh, I'm surprised, all right.
I always am when one of
my theories is confirmed.
That's not what I meant.
[ASANAGA] Come! You'll have
to tell me the whole story.
Sure!
[ASANAGA]
I see.
That crystal must have enacted
some sort of spatial transition.
[SHUN]
Yeah, a spatial transition.
The crystal that pulled
you into this "Endora"
was actually discovered
by your mother,
back when she was still
an archaeologist.
I assumed it was special,
but a key between worlds?
It's unheard of.
Pretty amazing.
I'll investigate thoroughly
and let you know what I find.
I knew we could count on you!
[ASANAGA]
Sure.
Emilio? You look troubled.
Is there anything you'd
like to talk about?
[EMILIO]
No. It's nothing.
It's too soon to know, but I
have some promising leads
on getting you home,
so don't you worry.
For now try to be patient.
I appreciate your help, sir.
Well, I know exactly how
worried your parents must be.
Since we got Shun back,
it's only fair I see the
same happen for them.
[EMILIO]
Uh...
Actually. The thing is--
[ASANAGA]
Huh?
[SHUN] Emilio's father passed
away a few years ago.
Oh, I see. Please, I'm so sorry,
my mistake, I didn't mean
to make you uncomfortable.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
Emilio's father was actually
the King of Endora,
up until he died.
We think that he was killed
by his successor, Delzaine.
But now Delzaine's been
assassinated too, so...
...there is no king.
I can only imagine
the resulting chaos.
This must be a difficult
time in Endora.
[SHUN] It really is.
And if anyone has the power
to make things better
there, it's Emilio.
[ASANAGA] Mm. All the more
reason to hurry then.
I trust that you'll keep our
lost young prince here close
by your side, Shun.
His safety is paramount.
Yeah! I'll keep an eye on him.
[ASANAGA]
I know you will.
[EMILIO]
This feeling. It's out of place.
Why would I feel so disquieted
from the sight of Shun's father?
What is it?
What could it be about this
man that feels so wrong?
[EMILIO gasps]
[SHUN]
It really is crazy, isn't it?
They made such a big fuss
about Babel back in Endora,
but here we've got a crystal
that does the same thing.
Uh. Hey, what's the matter?
[EMILIO grunting]
[EMILIO gasping]
[EMILIO] This memory.
What is it? Why is it back now?
Emilio...?
I almost have it back.
It's right there!
I'm so close to remembering!
Look, I don't know if you're
feeling sick or what,
but we should head
on home either way.
Mom can take care of you,
and I don't want her to worry.
[EMILIO gasps]
[ALZERM] The final arrangements
have already been made,
my friend. As per our
earlier discussion.
[TRAVELER laughs]
[DELZAINE] There's a reason
why our ancestors warned us
against dealing with
the surface, Brother!
This conversation is over.
Please listen. You must
not trust Asanaga!
[SHUN] Emilio! Seriously.
Snap out of it, man.
Asanaga...
Uh!
That was his name.
The traveler who stole our
Warp Particles. It was him.
What are you saying?
[EMILIO panting]
Hey, wait up!
Slow down, will ya?
[panting]
[ASANAGA]
Hello. Did you forget something?
[SHUN] Hey, Emilio!
Leave him be, he's busy.
[EMILIO]
I found out the truth, Asanaga.
[SHUN]
Uh.
[EMILIO] Endora's existence
wasn't just a theory to you.
Don't lie. You knew what that
crystal did. You've used it!
What the heck are
you talking about?
How many times
have you gone back?
How many times since
my father lost his life?
Don't do this, man.
He's trying to help you!
Answer me!
[ASANAGA]
What are you going on about?
[gasps]
It was you. There's no mistake.
You are constantly
causing me drama, dude.
Say something, Dad!
Calm him down.
I remember you abducting
Delzaine's baby.
[gasps]
After that...
You took my father--
[gasps]
No. Dad, why?
[ASANAGA]
Don't do anything rash.
What are you doing,
Dad? Put it down.
You're not really
that slow, Shun.
Stop calling me that.
You aren't my son.
[SHUN gasps]
[ASANAGA]
Next episode, "Past."