So when you say you're a
scientist, what does it mean?
Well, you see,
I work to discover new
ways of helping people
and to bring us all a little
closer to a better future.
That sounds awesome, Dad!
You think so? I do, too.
Thing is, for me to do it
there must be sacrifice.
Wait, no.
What do you mean? Please, don't.
[SHUN gasps]
[SHUN]
Why'd you do it?
Why, Dad?
[MAKIKO]
Shun! It's time to eat!
Shun?
I'm such a fool.
I did all of these things
out of love but I hurt him.
I think some part of me
knew this would happen.
Well, there's no point
letting it get cold.
Hey, Shun. Makiko worked
hard on this meal.
You should eat it.
[SHUN] Thanks. If that's all
you came for, then get out.
I'll be happy to leave
just as soon as I see
you finish your meal.
[SHUN]
Emilio.
What's up?
[SHUN]
It's funny.
I could never understand why
you wanted to kill Delzaine.
I knew you were mad, but...
The idea of hating the man who
raised you enough to kill him--
It seemed so horrible.
I get it now, though. Now that
my father's the monster.
I know exactly how you felt.
Knowing all the things he's
done, the lies he's told.
It's screwing with my head.
I'm not any different.
You are different.
[SHUN]
Yeah, how?
Stop thinking about it and eat.
Your mother is an
exceptional cook.
She puts the best chefs
in my castle to shame.
[DEMETRIO]
That from Guidoro?
[GRADIDO]
Yeah.
A basic field report.
Complete with a
list of complaints
about his new comrades.
Well, I suppose that's
to be expected.
With any luck they'll learn
to get along eventually.
Ha. We can hope. He said
they'd found Ibelda's trail.
They're closing in on him.
That so?
[ALICIA] Demetrio!
Hey! We've got news!
[ALICIA panting]
I think we've figured out what
happened to Shun and Emilio!
Let's hear it.
We're pretty sure the
only place they could've
ended up is in the
castle's dungeon.
You sure?
[RALPH] Yeah. Talked to
one of the guards.
He saw them heading that way
before they disappeared.
And there's no one in the castle
who's seen either of them since.
I think Shun said
the dungeons are where
he first showed up
when he came here.
[chirps]
Let's have the men take
another look down there.
[RALPH]
Right!
[GRADIDO]
I'll see if I can help, too.
Good, thanks.
[ELJUIA]
Demetrio.
[DEMETRIO]
What is it?
With your leave,
there's something I'd
like to look into alone.
It pertains to the
end of the world.
What do you mean?
[ELJUIA] I had another
vision this morning.
Much like the one that
came to me near Babel.
Still think it has to do
with the disappearance
of Warp Particles?
[ELJUIA]
Yes. I confess I've been afraid.
I've yet to truly
push my ability
to its fullest potential.
But the end is coming,
whether I look or not.
Something has caused
this imbalance,
and I have to find out what.
[BOTH gasp]
The letters are starting
to show again!
I thought this might work.
Excellent thinking, Joseph.
Thanks, sir. But I can actually
trace this idea back to you.
After all, it was your thesis
that our eyes don't have
the capability to see every
single wavelength of light.
That's how I knew that
these pages might have
more to show than we thought,
and from there it was just
a matter of finding the right...
We both saw! You did great.
I'm glad Rodney here chose to
keep these dilapidated books,
although before now I couldn't
have guessed why he would.
It would appear that my
propensity for hoarding
has finally paid off.
[PASCAL]
Well. Let's get to work.
[EMILIO] Just call!
I have to speak with him.
[RECEPTION 21A]
He's out right now.
Can I take a message for you?
You're lying, and I know it!
Just listen!
You're making folks
uncomfortable.
I have to ask you to leave.
You don't get it! I have to--
What are you doing? Unhand me!
I have to see Asanaga!
[ASANAGA]
What's all this commotion?
You are here.
You're alone.
It seems strange that you
would come here without Shun.
He's the subject I wanted
us to talk about.
[ASANAGA] Hm. Please escort
the young man to my office.
[gasps]
[ASANAGA]
Sorry, Emilio.
I wish that holding you at
gunpoint weren't necessary.
But I'm not entirely convinced
you didn't come here to kill me.
No. I didn't.
Although you have given me
more than enough reason.
Well, then what do you want?
What's important enough to
make you take such a risk?
I have a question. What
could've possibly driven you
to murder my father?
He get in your way?
[ASANAGA] Alzerm getting
in my way was part of it.
However, it was far from
my primary consideration.
[ASANAGA] I could have left him
alive easily, if I'd cared to.
[EMILIO growls]
[ASANAGA]
But I wanted to kill him
because he was
unfit to be king.
What?
[ASANAGA] He was a small-minded
creature of avarice.
Easy to persuade. And a tyrant.
How many Zoozians could have
avoided enslavement if they
hadn't been captured by your
father's military conquests.
[EMILIO gasps]
[ASANAGA] Did you not know?
To be honest,
I'd expected that once
Delzaine became king,
Endora would see a few
improvements.
[EMILIO]
You're... lying.
[ASANAGA] If I recall, you said
that he died protecting you.
[EMILIO]
One more question.
What is it?
Do you love your son?
Even though you never
should have had him.
[ASANAGA]
Yes. I do.
What I said before was
wrong. Shun is my son.
Even if we share no
blood, I raised him.
I've loved him from the start.
[EMILIO gasps]
That's why you're alive.
Because killing you would
upset Shun. And I need him.
I need him to understand
what I'm doing.
Every last thing I've built
here, I built for my family.
I will not see it fractured.
Shun is precious to me.
He's my son, and nothing
can replace him.
Provided that you
stay out of my way,
I'll have no reason to harm you.
But if you try something
stupid. Well...
[SHUN]
Uh.
So do you plan to sulk
in here forever?
[SHUN]
Well no, but...
[EMILIO] I went to your father's
office and spoke with him.
You what? He almost
killed you earlier.
What the heck were you thinking?
And what did you say to him?
I needed to confirm
a few things.
What kind of things?
[EMILIO] I asked him if
he actually loves you,
and he told me that
he does indeed.
[gasps]
[EMILIO] He took back
what he said before.
Said blood aside,
you are his son.
And that everything he's done,
he did for you: for his family.
Yeah?
[EMILIO]
Look.
When I wanted Delzaine dead, you
said I should speak with him.
Emilio...
But I had allowed myself to
be blinded by an anger
borne of ignorance.
I wasted my chance.
Shun, do not make my mistake.
You'll regret it.
[EMILIO] Go to Asanaga.
Go to your father and talk.
Hear what he has to say,
and make a choice.
Don't think about my father.
Don't worry about me.
Decide what you want for
yourself, and go from there.
All right.
If I don't go talk to him
then nothing will change.
And I can't stand the way
that I feel right now, so...
Thanks for the advice, Emilio.
I've done nothing
worthy of gratitude.
[SHUN laughs]
Give yourself some credit.
I'm guessing you have news,
since you called us all here.
We've made a very
significant discovery.
I wanted to update everyone.
Though Eljuia seems
to be missing.
He's closed himself
off in his room.
Doing something between
meditation and a psychic ritual.
He asked us not to
interrupt him,
but I don't think he
has food in there.
Do you think he'll be okay?
[chrips]
He'll be fine.
We just have to trust that
he knows what he's doing.
Anyway. What do you have for us?
Oh, right. To put it plainly,
we've discovered a
new medium for travel
between Endora
and the surface.
[ALL gasp]
I think it extremely likely that
this is what landed Shun here.
[SHUN] That building. It used
to be where my dad worked.
His whole business started
with that little workshop.
Way back then he'd actually take
me to work with him sometimes.
Sorry about that. The client
had a lot of questions.
[SHUN]
Mm-mm. Don't worry 'bout me.
I know you only work this
hard cause you're gonna
make things better
for everybody, so...
[ASANAGA] You're a good boy,
Shun. Ready to go?
It's time.
We've got another
doctor's appointment.
Aw. Could we skip
just this once?
We can't if we want you
to stay healthy, son.
[EMILIO] Doesn't look like
this place is still in use.
[SHUN] No. The equipment Dad
was able to afford back then
can't even compare to what
he has in the tower now.
I see. But regardless,
he's left this place intact.
Makes me wonder if it
doesn't hold some kind
of sentimental value for him.
[ASANAGA]
Shun. Sorry to keep you waiting.
[gasps]
I thought we'd be alone.
I assure you I won't interrupt,
so feel free to pretend
I'm not here. I only
came to support Shun.
[ASANAGA]
You don't look well, Shun.
It was never my intention
to cause you any pain.
I don't know what I'm
supposed to think about
any of this stuff.
But I... I know
I don't hate you.
You annoy me sometimes.
Like when you work straight
through your own birthday, but
I still can't accept
that you're a killer.
You were such a kind person.
Why would you do this?
Why would you destroy a country?
All right. Fine. I'll explain.
[gasps]
[gasping]
Wait. That's...
[ASANAGA]
It's called a Parinblue.
They're the only objects I
know of that allow transit
between Endora and here.
Your mother found them.
The last traces of a culture
far greater than our own.
[PASCAL] Endora's creation
is shrouded in myth.
There are legends and fables
which suggest that our world
was fashioned deliberately
by superior beings,
come from a far distant planet.
Yeah, I remember my parents
telling stories like that
back when I was little.
[FALARION chirps]
[PASCAL] Mm. Apparently, those
makers left a few things behind.
These were called Parinblue.
They're quite rare, of course.
When the link between Endora
and the surface was severed, the
majority of them were broken.
They bond to the hearts
of their owners.
To make use of one you'd have
to feed it a strong emotion.
It seems that any would do.
Anger.
Fear.
Even passionate curiosity.
Given the appropriate
stimuli, it takes the body
and disassembles it into
countless particles.
Then it guides those particles
across the divi--
Let's spare them
the technicalities.
The point is,
if Shun came to Endora
through the power of
one of these devices,
well, that gives us
a pretty good idea
of where he and
Emilio vanished to.
[ALICIA]
So they're on the surface,
but they can still
come back, right?
[PASCAL] As long as they've kept
possession of the Parinblue,
yes, it should be possible.
Although I can't really
say that with certainty.
Hold on.
If we're to believe that Shun
had one of these Parinblue
this whole time, then why
has he never mentioned it?
I wouldn't take him for
the kind to keep a secret.
It's possible that he possessed
it without knowing.
My guess would be that the
Parinblue's been inside of him.
You're saying that I
have one in my chest?
[ASANAGA] The Parinblue you
found in my office didn't just
transport you to Endora.
It bound itself to you.
It can grant you passage between
our worlds at any time.
I've spent the majority of
my adult life studying
the ebb and flow of this
world beneath our own.
Through that work, I discovered
something great.
An energy source
unique to Endora.
More plentiful than
anything the surface had.
Warp Particles?
[ASANAGA]
That's right.
I realized that if I could
harness them on the surface,
I could improve the
lives of millions.
Exactly like we talked about
when you were a child.
When I went to Endora,
I went with that purpose.
To obtain Warp Particles
for my people,
through whatever
means were needed.
How is that enough to
make killing okay?
This was hardly the first time
that a contest over resources
ended in bloodshed.
Wars have been fought over
things far less valuable.
Just look at what
we've achieved.
The siphoning of Endora's
Warp Particles
is one of the main factors
that have allowed
this nation to
prosper as it has, Shun.
I haven't hoarded this power.
I've given it almost freely.
As a result, the specter of
pollution is on the decline,
our production is up, the
average person here lives well.
These are good things, son.
You think the loss
of one life compares?
How? Even if it destroys
their whole country.
Once I can scale what I've done
here to the rest of our world,
it will have been for
the greater good.
Dad...
[ASANAGA] I'll never regret
what I've done.
Because that's what
it took to save you.
[gasps]
[ASANAGA] Your Endra father gave
you to me because you were sick
from a pandemic that was
untreatable in Endora.
Yeah, I... I heard.
If you hadn't taken me
to a hospital up here,
I probably wouldn't be alive.
[ASANAGA] It took money
to pay for those treatments.
Even after they'd
officially cured you,
your body was still so weak.
You were in the hospital
as often as you weren't.
And I'm grateful.
[ASANAGA] If it weren't for the
massively successful work
I've done with Warp Particles,
I never could have
paid those bills.
I did what I had to.
And you're still here.
[SHUN]
But what about Endora?
Shun, you're too kind a
person for your own good.
There's no point in lamenting
what's as good as done.
Endora will soon die, forget it.
[SHUN gasps]
Its Warp Particles
are nearly depleted.
It won't be long before
there are too few remaining
and the world in its current
form won't be sustainable.
[BOTH gasp]
[ASANAGA]
For all practical purposes,
you could pretend that
it never existed.
Hey. Wait a sec!
[ASANAGA] What is it?
You're acting like
this is inevitable.
But that isn't true.
You're the one doing
this, aren't you?
I am.
Well then put an end to it!
[ASANAGA] What are you talking
about? I could never stop.
And why not?
Because of everything
I've told you.
Warp Particles have
enabled me to perform
near miracles on the surface.
Why would I stop
the work that's improved
millions of people's lives?
It's like the people of Endora
don't even really count as
human beings in your mind.
Uh. Yes. That's right.
[gasps]
[ASANAGA] Endora served
to advance humanity
by leaps and bounds.
It's a good cause.
And when I'm gone, you will
ensure that its legacy endures.
But...
We have nothing to worry about.
Before our supply runs out,
I'll have perfected a system
that will allow Warp
Particles to replicate
even on the surface.
After Endora has collapsed,
we'll still be able to mine it
for a few years. Ample time.
I won't let you!
What's that?
If you think conveniences
are worth people's lives,
then you've lost your mind.
You weren't in Endora that long.
Have you really
grown so attached?
I suppose it's natural to love
the place where you were born.
It's hard to admit,
but in the end,
it would seem that you
do belong to Endora.
[SHUN gasps]
[EMILIO gasps]
[ASANAGA] I can't let anyone
hold me back. Not even you, Son.
So if you won't work with me,
then at the very least
get out of my way.
I would like to avoid
having to kill you.
[EMILIO]
Enough, Asanaga!
[ASANAGA]
Damn it!
You bastard!
Emilio!
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
[ASANAGA laughs]
I would never shoot you, Shun.
You're my darling boy.
You don't have to do this, Dad!
Are you the reason why my
son has turned against me?
How annoying.
Just when everything
was perfect!
If you hadn't shown up
and poisoned him
with your friendship, he would
be laughing at my side!
The hell he would have.
Given the circumstances,
I'd recommend that you
keep your mouth shut tight.
You're a nuisance. You ruined
him. You've destroyed my family!
[SHUN] Leave him alone!
[ASANAGA]
Uh.
[laughs]
[SLIME roar]
[FELIX grunts]
Felix, I need you to
hold still, all right?
Get out of my way!
There're too many of them!
We can't keep them
off you much longer.
[GUIDORO]
Yeah, I know!
[IBELDA yells]
[GUIDORO gasps]
[EMILIO, SHUN grunt]
[IBELDA]
Huh?
[gasping]
[SHUN]
Damn that hurt.
[EMILIO]
Is this...?
No way.
[SHUN]
We're back.
[EMILIO]
Next episode, "Crisis."