[SHUN]
Hey.
Where are you takin' us, anyway?
Hello?
Look, man.
I think I deserve some
friggin' answers already.
Like if you're
actually a prince,
then what were you doing
locked up in that dungeon?
Hey, "Your Highness,"
I'm tryin' to talk to you.
You sure you're a prince?
Ya look more like a
wannabe rockstar--
Shut up.
What the hell, man?
I broke you out of prison;
you owe me big time!
I could have escaped
on my own with ease.
[SHUN]
Oh really?
Do I need to remind you that
you owe me your obnoxious life?
You would've drowned
if not for me.
You pompous little--
[FALARION growls]
[SHUN yells]
Could we please stop with
all the bickering, boys?
You scare easy.
Just because a guy gets
taken by surprise
doesn't mean he's scared, okay?
Well, since I've
got your attention,
would you answer
my question already?
[EMILIO]
It'll be dawn soon.
We should move on. Quietly.
[SHUN growls]
Hey! I'm not done with you!
Come back here!
Look, I'm not shuttin' up
until you start talkin'!
Hey!
The day begins.
[SHUN]
The sun?
I can feel it pulling me in.
No. It's too late.
I'm already in.
[SHUN]
Sure enough, no signal.
Now it's just a
crummy flashlight.
[EMILIO]
Hey, dimwit, we're leaving.
With or without you.
[SHUN] It's like everything you
say is meant to piss me off!
Believe it or not,
I've got a real name.
It's Shun Asanaga! Use it!
A pleasure.
I'm Emilio Langheim.
That... was weirdly polite.
You can call me Alicia, and this
little guy's named Falarion.
[FALARION squeaks]
That means he's
pleased to meet you.
Yeah? Likewise.
So... I have to ask.
Did you really come
from the surface?
Well--
[ALICIA]
But how did you get here?
Did the surface people send you?
Why you, though?
Will you please stop
with the interrogation?
Aw. Now you're the one who
won't answer any questions.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I have literally no idea
what's happening here.
[EMILIO]
Hey. You.
We're leaving. And don't make
me repeat myself again.
[SHUN]
My name's Shun!
[EMILIO]
This way.
[SHUN]
What the heck is that way?
I can answer questions later.
For now, though,
we need to hide.
[SHUN] Could you at least tell
me where we're gonna hide?
Course not.
[ARMY CAPTAIN 2A] My men have
scoured the entire castle,
but they were unable
to locate the prince.
He's escaped, then.
Send forth a search party.
[ARMY CAPTAIN 2A]
My Lord...
I understand that
somebody aided the prince
in his escape.
A young man who
possesses a Warp Relic.
Find out all you can about him.
[ARMY CAPTAIN 2A]
As you command.
You say Emilio and his
accomplice fell into the river,
is that correct?
[GUIDORO]
Yes sir.
Decided that's all he
needs to know, did ya?
Be quiet.
The boy's determined.
I doubt he would die so easily.
He has but one
place left to run.
We'll have him soon.
[EMILIO]
We're close now.
Right.
Don't suppose you'd like to
tell me what we're close to?
Or is walking and talking
too hard to do at once?
I think we're
heading to Pascal's place.
Yeah? Who's that?
Well, he used to be in
charge of all the research
back at the castle.
But on top of that, he was
Emilio's childhood tutor.
[SHUN]
Gotcha.
[squealing noise]
I could use some help.
What?
Falarion!
[FALARION vocalizes]
[FALARION growls]
No way! You're kiddin' me!
How did it get so massive?
You just gonna stand there?
What else am I
supposed to do?
Phew. Looks like
Falarion's got it covered.
[SHUN yelling]
Whoa, way to go!
[SHUN sighs]
[ALICIA, SHUN yell]
The hell just happened?
Tell me I'm not
where I think I am.
[FALARION growling]
[EMILIO]
Pascal.
Long time no see, my boy!
I've missed you!
So tall! Either you've gained
inches or I'm shrinking
with age.
Thanks.
[SHUN]
Hey!
I don't mean to spoil
your touching reunion,
but we could really use a hand
getting down from this thing!
You know that fella up there?
Doesn't look familiar.
You're a liar!
Help us, please!
That you, Alicia?
What are you doing up there?
So it was you who
built these traps, right?
It was!
Well, probably.
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, I can't keep
track of everything I make.
Well you haven't changed a bit.
Please tell me
if I'm wrong here,
but it sounds like you could've
booby-trapped the whole forest
and we'd only find out
by walking on one!
Good.
You'll need that sharp mind
to avoid my famous spike pits!
I'm pretty sure anybody could've
figured it out, but thanks.
Say, I don't understand
who you are.
Emilio's new bestie?
--Ain't no chance in hell!
--There's no chance of that!
[PASCAL]
Oh.
I see you have a Warp Relic.
I didn't think that
people from the surface
could actually use Warp Relics.
Forgot it was out.
Let's see if I still remember.
I think I'm startin'
to get a feel for this thing.
So you--
You're from the surface?
[PASCAL]
Come in, come in!
Make yourselves at home!
Sit down somewhere!
Wherever you like!
[SHUN]
But...
I don't see anywhere to sit.
[SHUN]
Whoa, cool.
I definitely haven't
seen these before.
Hey, moron.
It's not yours. Don't touch it.
[SHUN] It's not yours either,
so bite me!
[PASCAL laughs]
Haven't had meat
like this in ages!
Hey...
You've been taking care
of yourself, right?
Don't tell me that you still
get so lost in your work
that you forget to eat
and faint like you used to.
There's no need
to fret about me.
I can fill up for a week
off a meal like this.
[PASCAL] So... That kid is
really from the surface?
Well, yeah.
That's what Emilio told me.
[PASCAL]
And yet he has a Warp Relic.
Weird, right?
I don't get it either.
For that matter,
how'd he even get down here?
[EMILIO] I told you not
to touch anything.
Yeah, well what about that thing
you're touchin' with your butt?
[EMILIO]
This is called a stool.
You know what?
I'll make you a deal!
If you shut your
stupid trap right now,
I will stop touching
things happily!
What I'm telling you
is basic etiquette!
Are you all this rude
on the surface,
or is that why
they sent you down?
[SHUN]
Excuse me?
Who do you think you are, man?
You can't leave them
alone for a minute.
I think they're
getting along just fine.
Then I'd hate
to see 'em fight.
[PASCAL]
Wow!
It looks delicious!
[ALICIA] The fresher the meat,
the better the meal!
And this meat couldn't be
fresher unless we ate it alive.
Uh... You don't mean those
things that attacked us...
There's a whole lot more
where that came from,
so eat as much as you like!
[ALICIA]
Here you go!
Endora frogs, guts and all!
So good I just
grill 'em as they come!
[SHUN]
Ugh...
It must be in
a great deal of pain.
Eat it.
[SHUN yells]
[EMILIO laughs]
Wow. After all that talk
about my manners...
[EMILIO laughs]
[ALICIA]
Here! For you.
[PASCAL]
So good! Mmm!
Rancid.
[EMILIO] If you don't like it,
then you don't have to eat it.
[SHUN] Oh, I'll eat it all,
just watch me!
I knew it'd be bad, but wow.
[PASCAL]
So, Shun.
About your journey here
from the surface...
[SHUN]
Yeah?
Well, I was wondering
just how you did it.
I was looking for
my dad in his office.
I found this crystal.
And I picked it up.
Before I knew what was
happening, I was here.
[PASCAL] And you believe
the crystal is responsible?
I think I can say
that much for sure.
I could feel its pull.
Now, suddenly, I can make
a sword out of nowhere.
I've seen.
There's no doubt
it's a Warp Relic.
[SHUN]
Question.
What'll it take for me
to get back home?
[PASCAL]
Hmm...
You've gotta know about
something I can try,
or anything useful?
Prince Priss over here couldn't
be bothered to answer me.
I haven't even figured out
what the heck this place is yet!
Well, if that's the case,
then I suppose I should
start explaining from there.
[SHUN]
What's that?
This is a cross-section
map of our planet.
We are here in
the land of Endora.
Beneath your surface.
[SHUN]
We're underground?
But at school they said
it was all lava down here.
If it's hollow...
It feels like I've
been living on a shell.
[PASCAL] This beauty here
is called Adamas.
Your sun brings
light to the surface.
Adamas does the same
thing for us beneath it.
So then it pretty
much is your sun, huh?
Although...
The real sun is nowhere
even close to that beautiful.
[PASCAL] Are you
familiar with this place?
[SHUN]
Uh...
It's the North Pole, right?
[PASCAL]
Yes, good.
Your sun's light enters
our world through here.
Adamas magnifies that light, and
scatters it throughout the land.
You might think that Adamas'
light would disappear
come nightfall,
but it doesn't.
Adamas magnifies and
redirects most light,
but it also captures some.
Overnight, that
captive light escapes,
producing a glow not
unlike that of your moon.
So if you've got a sun and
moon, then what about stars?
No, the only light in
our sky comes from Adamas.
Its moon form sees no phases.
We experience no
change in seasons here.
I never would've guessed it.
A whole other world
hidden right under mine.
I understand that
whoever created Endora
went to an awful lot of trouble
to keep you
surface dwellers out.
[SHUN]
Oh yeah?
Think of religion.
The underworld is always hell.
[PASCAL] That myth
was spread for a reason.
By popularizing the idea
that the underworld
is a place of torment,
our ancestors meant to
dissuade you surface dwellers
from seeking us out.
Or so I've been told, anyway.
Wait, though...
If Endora's cut off
from the surface,
why do all of you
still know about it?
Now Endora's founder
did conceal its location
from the surface, but there
was still a fairly decent bit
of contact between the realms
for some length of time.
I'm afraid they put
the nail in that coffin
a while back, though.
[SHUN]
A book on the whole earth?
It was written on the surface.
I borrowed it from the royal
library on the day I left.
I intend to bring
it back someday.
Almost everything I
know about the surface
I learned from these pages.
Obviously, I've never been
able to see it for myself.
[SHUN]
Huh.
If that publishing date's right,
then this book isn't
much older than me!
So then this proves that Endora
had at least some contact
with the surface within
the past few decades!
[PASCAL]
It does.
How did people
go between worlds?
The only connection
between Endora and the surface
was a city known as Babylon.
Babylon? I know that city.
It was in my history books.
But you're saying that
Endora had a Babylon as well?
Yeah, and somewhere
in it, you'd find Babel,
the only device ever
created capable of making
an ascent to the surface.
But Babylon was struck by
some sort of catastrophe,
and Babel was demolished.
Since then, our worlds
have grown close but divided,
intersecting only
on the rarest occasions.
But King Delzaine
plans to change that soon.
He's put a great deal
of time and resources
into building Babel anew.
So what happened,
has he finished it?
Well, uh...
It was actually about
to be completed,
but he ran into
a little problem.
All I'm hearin' is
that Babel isn't ready.
'Fraid not. Apologies, kid.
[PASCAL] I'm sure he'll get
it sorted out eventually.
[SHUN] But I shouldn't
hold my breath, right?
[PASCAL]
Anyway...
You wouldn't mind if
I took another peek
at that Warp Relic, would you?
Uh... Do you mean like,
here and now?
[PASCAL]
Yep.
The thing is, I can only
seem to summon it
if I'm in some kind of pinch.
I bet Falarion
could help with that.
Yeah, thanks, but I'm good.
I should try this on my own.
[SHUN]
I did it!
It's magnificent!
I present to you: Excalibur!
What was that?
Uh, nothing!
Forget it happened, please.
[SHUN] So... Do
you wanna hold it, or--?
[PASCAL] No, I'm good!
I just wanted a peek.
[SHUN]
But you--!
[PASCAL]
Thanks!
Feel free to put it away now.
[SHUN]
'Kay, if you're sure, man.
[EMILIO]
Strange...
His skill with a Warp Relic's
improved greatly.
And in such a short time.
[SHUN] Why don't'cha
show me yours now, Pascal?
I appreciate your interest,
but I can't show
what I don't have.
[SHUN]
What?
The power to create a
Warp Relic isn't universal,
even amongst us Endras. The gift
is granted largely at random.
To the best of my knowledge,
things like genetics,
strength, and intelligence
don't even factor into it.
It boils down to
an invisible coin toss.
Some of us won it,
and some of us lost.
In case this isn't clear yet,
I lost that particular toss.
Wow, tough break.
I feel as if everyone
I've met down here
has a Warp Relic
except for you.
Mercy.
Stop rubbing it in, please.
Don't worry 'bout it.
Alicia doesn't have one,
and she gets by.
Huh?
Oh no, I've got mine
on my shoulder.
Give him a big
battle roar, 'kay?
[FALARION squeaks]
No way!
You're tellin' me that
your Warp Relic is alive?
[ALICIA]
Sure!
[PASCAL]
Allow me to explain.
Warp Relics can
take on many forms,
and are comprised of what
we refer to as Warp Particles.
[SHUN]
What's a Warp Particle?
It's a very special type
of energy that I believe
is unique to Endora.
These particles have
the lifelike ability
to self-replicate, dividing
in half not unlike an amoeba,
but without the need to eat.
They can't exist on the surface,
but multiply steadily here,
charging our air
with their presence.
[PASCAL] A Warp Relic is simply
a host of Warp Particles,
given form by your mind.
Honestly, I'm not quite
sure I followed all that.
I did catch that king
what's-his-face is almost done
makin' my ride home in Babylon.
So... I think I'm
headin' that way.
[ALICIA] Look, you say that
like it's gonna be this simple,
easy thing, but it's not.
Maybe you don't realize
how far we are from Babylon.
The distance doesn't matter,
because my mom and dad
must be worried sick about me.
[ALICIA] I understand where
you're coming from, but think,
what's the point
of getting to Babel
if it doesn't even work yet?
You said that it was really
close to being finished,
though, right?
Uh... I... I did.
Then I'll make my way to
Babylon now, and wait there!
That way, when they
open Babel for business,
I'll be the first guy in line!
[EMILIO]
Shun. You may prove useful.
Geez.
You act like you hear me,
but  you ignore what I say.
Hey, Emilio,
help me criticize him--
Am I really this ignorable?
[EMILIO]
What's that?
Shun's decided he's
walking to Babylon,
and I need you to
help change his mind!
Let him be.
Shun has every right to run off
and pick a ditch to die in.
Are you good at anything
except pissing me off?
Better question, do you have
any idea where Babylon is?
[SHUN]
Of course I don't!
[EMILIO]
Then find a ditch.
It's finally done.
[PASCAL]
Yes.
But is this really what we want?
[PASCAL]
Your Majesty.
Please forgive my insolence.
But I feel that
renewing contact
between Endora and the surface
would be a dire mistake!
Our ancestors,
in their wisdom,
taught us that Endora must be
kept permanently concealed
from the world above.
This system is in place
to protect not just--
If only you had
listened, your grace.
By this point, I suppose
they must've found me out.
[CASTINA]
Welcome, Your Majesty.
Have you come to observe
our progress for yourself?
I am honored.
[DELZAINE]
Begin.
[CASTINA] The good news is
I have found the problem.
It lies with this circuit here.
Once I can resolve the
issue or replace the circuit,
Babel will be able
to resume operations.
Is there something else?
The fact of the matter
is I find it a bit odd
for such a flaw to be present
at all, and to be frank,
I find it difficult
to imagine that Pascal
would have failed
to observe it himself.
I suggest you
hasten your efforts.
[CASTINA]
I shall do that, sir.
I'll work as
swiftly as I'm able.
[DELZAINE] Seems you've
turned against us, Pascal.
So be it.
The time has come at last.
[FALARION squeaks]
What's up, lil' bud?
You hear something?
[rattling]
The alarm!
[PASCAL]
Oh, that's bad.
Looks like the Royal Guard!
They're after us!
[PASCAL]
Put that up!
They've got horses,
hounds, armor, and manpower!
We're gonna have to run!
Full throttle!
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
Catch ya on the flipside, boys!
[ALICIA] How did you find
time to make this thing?
I knew this day would come
eventually, so I prepared.
[SHUN]
Way cool...
[ALICIA]
What do you mean by that?
The only reason Babel
isn't complete yet
is because I kept
something secret
to slow down their progress.
Though I always knew
they'd work it out
sooner or later.
Wait, so if you know the secret,
that means you could finish
it yourself, doesn't it?
If I were ever so inclined,
of course I could.
Yeah! All right!
Oh, I'm pretty sure that
Emilio's the reason those guards
were after us, anyway.
Shut up.
[SHUN] He recently busted his
way out of the castle's dungeon!
Well at any rate...
We can catch up on
all that once we've landed.
[ALICIA]
Where are we headed?
I call it Hiding Spot #1.
No way, we've got a
jet! Let's go to Babylon!
[PASCAL] Stop it boy,
you'll doom us all!
[ALICIA]
Stop it, Shun!
[SHUN]
Gimme the wheel, old man!
[EMILIO]
Shut up!
[SHUN] By the way,
which way is Babylon?
[EMILIO]
Next episode, "Journey."