[SHUN]
Ah, man...
I was hopin' they'd fly us
all the way to Babylon.
They did what
they could for us.
It wouldn't be safe for them
to stray too far from home.
They could be spotted.
Dragon hunters
are still out there.
I mean, I can definitely
understand them
wanting to go home.
Have you ever not been homesick?
So sorry if you find
my pain boring!
[LOUISE]
Apology accepted!
[SHUN] I don't talk about
home that much. Do I?
[FALARION squeaks]
I can't believe
you're trapped in there.
[DEMETRIO] Those dragons took
us a pretty good distance.
We ought to reach Babylon
within a day or two.
Hey...
It seems weird we haven't
seen any sign of Delzaine.
Makes me wonder...
Do ya think he might've
beat us getting there?
It's hard to say.
He was traveling
straight from the castle,
so he took a different route.
I'm worried that if
he did get there first,
he could do something
to screw up Babel.
If it used to be broken, it
might just be good for one ride.
[EMILIO] Shun's needs aside,
keeping the king
from using Babel
should be a priority.
If he wants to reach
the surface, he has reasons.
And knowing him,
they can't be good.
[ELJUIA gasps]
Is something the
matter, Eljuia?
Eljuia!
Hey, look, he's awake!
Glad you're back with us.
That was a pretty dramatic
fall you took earlier.
I assume you saw
the future again?
I don't fully
understand what I saw.
However...
Our world was desolate.
[ALL gasp]
What was the cause?
Well... What keeps
Endora whole...
That unseen life force.
It would seem that power
is beginning to fail.
So what does this mean?
[ELJUIA]
Maybe the end of our world.
All I know is that
no vision I've had before
has left me with such
a feeling of dread.
If it's really that bad,
can't we do something?
If we at least knew what
was causing this to happen,
we'd have a place to start.
Too bad we don't.
[ELJUIA] If only this vision
had been clearer,
I could tell you
something more useful.
[LOUISE]
The end of the world, eh?
Too much for me to
wrap my head around.
I'm not gonna worry about it.
[CASTINA]
Needless to say, Your Majesty...
The development of a method
for restoring Babel
required a great deal of
painstaking labor and research.
Even for someone with
my superior intellect,
this project--
[DELZAINE]
Is your work complete or not?
Uh...
There are a few final
adjustments that need
to be made, sir.
It will take time
to implement them,
though I am not sure how much.
Very well.
I've been waiting years
for this moment to come.
I can wait a few days more.
Forgive my
impertinence, Majesty,
but could I ask what you plan
to do once Babel is restored?
After all the
effort I've put forth,
I feel that I deserve
to know what exactly
I've been working towards.
[DELZAINE] You know
everything you need to.
But sire, this project is mi--
I wonder, are you
secretly an imbecile,
or is it your wish to
have your head removed?
[IBELDA] Why don't you cut
the man some slack, my lord?
I mean, he's only a scientist.
[GUARD 10A]
It's those damned Zoozians!
You're in the
presence of the king,
so hold your tongue!
[IBELDA growls]
Enough, Ibelda.
We have news of the prince.
[DELZAINE] So, the Ignauts
have formed an alliance
with the island Zoozians.
Tell me, Ibelda.
Do my orders
somehow confuse you?
Should I say them slower?
Not sure what you mean, sir.
[DELZAINE]
You've obtained a new scar.
Who gave it to you?
If memory serves,
I last ordered you
to observe the prince's party.
I do not recall giving you
permission to engage.
Very good.
You know better than to
give me excuses, at least.
I don't need an excuse.
[DELZAINE] You will do exactly
as ordered from now on.
Understood?
[IBELDA]
Damn that royal prick.
[VESTULSE grunts]
Agreed.
Let it go.
Ibelda went against
the orders of the king,
and was reprimanded accordingly.
Yeah, but I wasn't
the only one, was I?
[IBELDA growls]
[GUARD 10C]
Look at those savages go.
They're scrapping like dogs.
I don't understand why the king
allowed them into his service.
[IBELDA] Which one of you
wants to see his own insides?
[GUARDS yell]
Stop it.
If you kill one of
the king's soldiers,
it'll put our position at risk.
I'm sick of it!
I'm done bending over backwards
to help these Endra feel good!
[VESTULSE grunts]
Agreed.
[IBELDA laughs]
Now that scientist
has got me curious
about why Delzaine's so obsessed
with rebuilding the Babel relic.
What exactly is he planning?
[IBELDA]
She send news?
[GUIDORO]
Yes.
Apparently, the Ignauts
are set to get to Babylon
a bit sooner than we expected.
[PASCAL] Almost all the
literature regarding Babel
has been either
lost or destroyed.
The few texts I have been
able to find are like this one.
Redacted beyond legibility.
Just what is the king
so desperate to hide?
Could it explain his fixation
with reaching the surface?
The only thing I've learned
is the depth of my ignorance.
The king must've
missed one book.
If I'm to get Shun to the
surface, I should keep looking.
[JOSEPH]
A-ha! There you are!
[JOSEPH panting]
Forgive me, sir.
You might not know
from looking at me,
but I'm not
particularly athletic.
Too bad I can't save
the calories I waste
running around the
place for my brain.
Hmm... I suppose with
the right gear sequence,
you could make the
floor move for you.
Say, what if you made
a vehicle that uses
a ferromagnetic alloy--
Neodymium!
I'll begin work on the
diagrams immediately.
We'll store the charge it
draws in a lithium polymer!
I've been working on
this insulated circuit,
and this'll be just the
thing to test it with!
Hopefully all the static
won't ruin my hair--
I get the feeling this
isn't what you came here
to talk about.
Right, thank you!
I wanted to inform you
that the lab's regional
Warp Particle measurements have
been completed and analyzed.
I still can't fathom why the
chief was so reluctant
to continue research on such
an important phenomenon,
but I'm glad we
ended up doing it.
I agree. The diminishment of
Endora's Warp Particles
is an extremely
important discovery.
Your powers of observation
must be well honed indeed.
Ah! I can't express what it
means to receive such praise
from Pascal himself!
Although I must say that
I never could have noticed
that Warp Particles were
dying out if not for the device
you created to detect them!
Once I'd gathered
sufficient data,
I had a flash of insight!
[PASCAL] Warp Particles
are a vital part of Endora.
If they continue to
deplete at this rate,
our entire world will
doubtlessly suffer.
[SHUN] Things are startin'
to get out of hand here.
All of this doomsday talk,
and with the king
so close to Babel...
I wonder...
Am I really gonna
make it back home?
[EMILIO]
You will. I'll make sure of it.
These problems don't affect you.
They belong to Endora.
You have troubles
enough without adding
any of ours to the list.
Wait, are you being serious?
Go to sleep.
Uh, okay.
[SHUN] He might've just
said that to shut me up.
I'm sure he's got his
own problems in mind.
I mean, he was raised by
the man who killed his father.
Anyone would be
torn up after that.
Hey, listen.
You might be a piece of work,
but you've also had
my back through this.
No matter what you
decide to do, I'm with you.
You can count on me
to make good on our deal.
But... Killing Delzaine
to take revenge
isn't gonna make
anything better.
Isn't there another option?
[SHUN]
Hey. You asleep?
[EMILIO] You don't understand.
How could you?
Do your worst.
Never make it past me.
What do you think?
How do I stop Emilio from
going through with this?
[LOUISE]
Up and at 'em.
The rest of the watch is yours.
[ELJUIA]
Right.
Hey there.
Why are you still awake?
[ALICIA]
No reason.
Well, we're getting a
pretty early start tomorrow,
so as long you're up to nothing,
you might try and
do it lying down.
Right, I'll give that a try.
What's on your mind?
[ALICIA]
Nothing. Good night, Louise.
[SHUN yawns]
He's up early.
[EMILIO]
Seriously?
[DEMETRIO] You couldn't
have done better, Ralph.
[RALPH]
Thanks.
It looks like this revolution
might really have a chance.
[DEMETRIO] Yup. The tides
are turning in our favor.
We've become a force
to be reckoned with,
even for the king.
About time you woke up.
Whatever. So who's this?
Don't you remember me?
[SHUN]
Uh...
Surely the two of you
must have met back at
the Ignauts' old encampment.
Ralph's one of the soldiers
I sent off after the attack.
Uh... Oh yeah!
I thought you
looked kinda familiar!
You remembered!
No worries. I was just
another face in the crowd.
[DEMETRIO] When we left
to court the Zoozians,
other Ignauts like Ralph
did the same elsewhere.
The goal was to obtain
the support of as many lords
as they could sway.
[RALPH]
That's right.
We focused on areas
far enough away
that fear of retaliation
wouldn't be much of a concern.
And I guess it paid off,
because most of the
lords we spoke with
offered their support
to the cause.
You don't say?
So by "support" you mean...
Full alliances across the board.
Council, supplies, and
a slew of additional soldiers.
That's amazing!
I should on my way, then.
There are still plenty
of lords out there
I haven't gotten
to speak with yet.
[DEMETRIO]
Fair enough. Go get 'em!
And if negotiations
with the king
do somehow go south,
get word to us as
quickly as you can.
Your men will come.
I appreciate it.
But for now, let's just hope
it doesn't come to that.
Right. Best of luck, sir.
It's about to get
busy around here.
First the Zoozians
and now these nobles.
We finally have
the power to do this.
Guess we do.
[LOUISE] Shake it off.
It's how life works.
What's right for one
is pain for another.
[DEMETRIO]
Louise?
[LOUISE gasps]
Goodness.
What's with the mean mug?
It's nothing.
I was just surprised.
Aww, c'mon.
If you've got a problem,
let it out.
[LOUISE] I was thinking about
what Eljuia said, okay?
Just lay off.
Yeah, that's been weighing
on my mind as well.
By the way,
we just received word
from one of our more
itinerant comrades.
Apparently, they've
been gathering support
from sundry lords
across the land.
I'm so sorry.
[ALICIA]
Emilio! Shun!
[SHUN]
Hey. Good mornin'.
[EMILIO]
What is it?
Did you hear?
The Ignauts who split up
were out looking for allies,
and now a bunch of lords
have joined our side!
Oh yeah, I already knew that.
[chuckles]
Yay, you.
Yup, I was one of a select
few who got to hear it
from the messenger.
His name's Ralph.
We go way back.
You would've liked him if you
hadn't been busy sleepin' in.
Please, you didn't even
know the man's name.
And the only reason you
stumbled into consciousness
is because we spoke
beside the tent.
Look. It was on
the tip of my tongue!
Like that gross strand
of drool you woke up with?
What? You're kiddin' me!
I am.
Uh... You little...
[chuckles nervously]
You two are the same as ever.
I still can't figure out
if you get along.
No one cares if you look
like a slack-jawed imbecile
when you first wake up.
It's fine.
I care! Now take it back!
Tell me I'm handsome
all day long!
You know it's true!
You're just jealous!
Moving on to a
subject that matters...
Between the Ignauts,
Zoozians, and lords,
we've gathered a force
Delzaine must recognize.
If all goes well, then...
Emilio.
So, uh, I guess you
are still planning
to kill the king, aren't you?
My father is dead.
Vengeance is all I can give him.
I've thought about
this for too many years
to betray him now.
[SHUN]
But why kill him?
Someone must!
And no one else seems
to care if my father's spirit
can rest in peace.
I've given everything for this.
Even my place as a prince.
No way.
You really think
you know everything?
Shut up!
I know far more than--
This has nothing to do with you.
[SHUN]
Oh yeah?
And when did that
get decided for me?
[EMILIO] Since you were
an outsider with no stake
in this world!
You're leaving.
Remember?
When you do,
you'll forget about this!
You dumb piece of--
Hey, let him down, Shun!
Has it ever crossed your mind
that people worry about you?
You have to let go
of this hatred.
If you don't, you're
gonna end up like Falarion!
Like Alicia's dad!
I've promised to
see this thing through
to the end with you,
and I don't wanna see you get
trapped inside of a Warp Relic!
Are you really okay
with that happening?
With losing who you are?
I'm not. I won't let it happen.
And what makes you
so sure about that?
That's enough! Let me go!
Idiot!
--Stop it!
--[SHUN growls]
You say your problems
don't concern me.
You're wrong.
I've never thought like that.
Not once since I got here.
Shun!
[EMILIO] I've come too far.
I'm not quitting now.
Emilio...
Thought so.
This data is quite conclusive.
Warp Particles are
steadily falling in numbers
in every region of Endora.
The results are even
worse than I hypothesized.
And I've still no clue
what caused this!
[PASCAL] If the Warp Particle
count drops too much further,
it won't just be
life that suffers.
The very structure of
Endora could collapse.
[gasps]
[JOSEPH] There's not too much to
see with those measurements.
We took them back
when concentrations
were still normal.
I'm missing something, aren't I?
Perhaps.
I can't help but notice
that the particle count
was perfectly normal
right up until King Delzaine
took the throne.
Whoa, that's right!
Are the dwindling Particles
and the King's rise related?
Although it's possible that this
could be a mere coincidence.
No way.
Correlation might
not show causation,
but I refuse to believe that it
means absolutely nothing.
Not when the vibrations
of a fish swimming
have been shown to impact
the photosynthesis of algae.
[PASCAL] Only one man
understands the events
surrounding Delzaine's
crowning: Delzaine himself.
[JOSEPH] ...is actually
quite likely to be of use.
[PASCAL] It would seem that the
answers I seek lie in Babylon.
But can I get there in time?
[JOSEPH chuckles]
[PASCAL] You've got
quite the lab here, boy.
Color me impressed.
[JOSEPH]
Why, thank you.
It was no simple feat
relocating all of these
heavy instruments.
But I had a hunch that
the chief and Delzaine
were starting to take
their research to a place
I wouldn't want to follow,
so the move was needed.
I still work at
the lab, mind you,
but I've taken to doing all of
my personal research over here.
It is our mandate as scientists
to distance ourselves
from any sort of
political authority,
so that we are free
in our pursuit of pure,
authentic truths.
I learned that
from your example!
You have my assurance.
This bad boy is the fastest way
to Babel that a man can find.
[JOSEPH]
The chief has no earthly idea
I've been building this thing.
Sometimes we scientists
have to be sneaky.
We'd best get going.
King Delzaine and the chief
could be walking into Babel
as we speak.
It is time.
Open the gate to the surface!
[EMILIO]
Shun.
What do you want?
[EMILIO] I may have
said too much before.
Wait, what?
Oh, well...
sorry for hitting you.
But that doesn't mean
I've changed my mind.
I'll have my vengeance.
You're still on that?
[DEMETRIO]
Hey, take a look!
There's Babylon.
I'm here. We made it.
And none too soon.
[IBELDA]
Next episode, "Depths."