[EMILIO]
Delzaine!
Emilio.
I followed you here to
finish what I started.
This time I will not fail!
[ALICIA, SHUN panting]
[LOUISE, DEMETRIO grunting]
If you suspected
I was the traitor,
why didn't you do anything?
[LOUISE grunts]
[LOUISE] What? Did you think
I wouldn't go through with it?!
You're stronger than before.
[gasps]
Shut up!
Get out your weapon,
Delzaine!
Aren't you even going
to put up a fight?
I would like to know what you
plan to do after you slay me.
Do you understand the
consequences of killing a king?
When Endora finds
itself without a ruler,
what do you intend to do then?
[gasps]
[DELZAINE] If you choose
to move forward with this,
then it means you have come
to take the throne for yourself.
[EMILIO growls]
[EMILIO yells]
[IBELDA yells]
[FELIX grunting]
That portal should take
me straight to Babel.
Hey, Louise!
I'm gonna leave these
chumps to you.
[BOTH gasp]
[LOUISE yells]
[DEMETRIO grunts]
[DEMETRIO]
Mischa! Felix! Go after him!
I can't!
Don't worry about me! Just go!
[LOUISE yells]
[ELJUIA]
He'll be all right.
[BOTH gasp]
Very well.
Come on.
[MISCHA grunts]
Risky move, letting them go.
One you're going to regret!
I still wanna know
why you let me live.
[DEMETRIO grunts]
You knew that I'd betrayed you.
Why didn't you just kill me?
[DEMETRIO grunts]
[gasps]
[DEMETRIO]
Stay back!
You should take whatever
help you can get!
Don't underestimate me,
Demetrio, or you're dead!
[LOUISE yells]
[DEMETRIO]
Listen to me, Louise.
[gasps]
I know why you joined
up with the Truculent,
and it makes sense.
Your Zoozian father
and Endra mother
had been persecuted
for their marriage,
and you wanted to help
them live in peace.
And in order to do that,
you needed money. Even so...
What will making them happy
do to your happiness?
Or can you tell me
you're content?
[gasps]
[DEMETRIO]
Be honest.
All this time you've
been with the Ignauts,
were you really just
playing a part?
What about the island?
When you stepped in to save me
from Gradido and the Zoozians.
Was that an act?
Part of your deceit?
[gasps]
[ELJUIA]
It wasn't all a lie. Was it?
[DEMETRIO]
Be honest with me. And yourself.
[LOUISE]
Of course it was all an act!
I was only trying to earn
your trust, nothing more!
[ELJUIA]
Louise!
Stop deluding yourself,
Demetrio!
I sold you a lie, and like
a fool, you bought it.
Stop this!
That's it!
I'm done talking now!
My job is to kill you both.
Get ready, Demetrio.
I'm starting with you!
[LOUISE yells]
[LOUISE]
Die!
[LOUISE gasps]
[LOUISE whimpers]
You're dead inside, is that
is what you believe?
That you've already
killed the real you?
[gasps]
To do what you've done,
you had to bury your heart.
Am I wrong?
[DEMETRIO] You don't have
to live like this anymore.
There is another way. And I
would like to help you find it.
If you'd let me.
[LOUISE]
This has been... so painful.
The Truculent are
the king's dogs
and are happy to do
all his dirty work.
As long as they're getting
coins in their pockets,
they do whatever he wants
without asking any questions.
When I was given orders
to join up with the Ignauts
and report on your movements,
I expected it to be
like any other job--
work and nothing more.
At first I scoffed at your idea
of a bloodless revolution.
It sounded like a
ridiculous plan to me.
I thought it the naïve dream
of some spoiled noble
who didn't know any better.
But you showed me I was
wrong--that someday,
your dream for this world might
actually become a reality.
And if that day did come,
I wanted to be there.
Because I believed
in your dream too.
[LOUISE] But then, the prince
showed up out of nowhere,
and events spun out of control.
And I was brought back
to the cruel reality.
My place was not
with the Ignauts,
but with the Truculent.
Yes. It's just like you've said.
I spent my days lying to myself,
and regretted it, every minute.
And I'm tired... so tired.
You've said enough now.
It's all right.
[ELJUIA]
Here.
Eljuia.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, about before.
The moment you aimed
your sword at me,
I saw your heart and
knew its true color.
[LOUISE gasps]
It was perfectly clear then.
I knew that you weren't
actually going to harm me.
[gasps]
I'm so sorry.
[DEMETRIO] Hey, now. We don't
have time for crying.
[BOTH]
Uh?
Let's get to Babel!
[FELIX grunts]
[IBELDA growls]
[yells]
I'll create an opening.
I need you to sneak
around behind him.
You're not my boss!
[FELIX growls]
[IBELDA]
I'm surprised at you two.
[BOTH gasp]
[FELIX]
Why's that?
[IBELDA] Because you're
over here fighting.
[MISCHA]
Why wouldn't we be?
Without his friends
to back him up,
that precious leader of yours
is probably getting torn apart
by Louise as we speak.
[yells]
[roars]
[FELIX, IBELDA grunting]
[IBELDA]
Huh?
[IBELDA] I wish I had time
to waste killing you.
But I've got better
things to do. See ya!
[IBELDA laughs]
Uh!
[growls]
[DEMETRIO]
Felix!
[FELIX]
Demetrio! You're-- [gasps]
Yeah. I'm still in one piece.
Hey!
[DEMETRIO]
Mischa.
Put it up. We're
all friends here.
He made a smokescreen
and got away.
That's not a problem.
We already know
where he's going.
[PASCAL]
You know, Joseph, I must say
I really have enjoyed getting
to spend time with you
and seeing all of your
great inventions.
I can't tell you how
much it means to get
that kind of praise from
the man whose mind
I most admire in
the entire world!
Well, I don't know if I'd
consider it praise or not.
But honestly, well seeing
you sort of takes me back
to my own time as
a young scientist.
Oh, really? In what way?
[PASCAL] This craft
we're in, for instance.
I made one just like
it in my younger days.
You mean I came up with
the same invention
as an intellectual giant?
What greater praise could
there be than that?
That's very kind
of you to say, lad.
[EMILIO grunting]
You monster!
You took away everything
precious to me!
[DELZAINE]
What have I taken?
[EMILIO]
You stole my father's life.
Then you forced Pascal
out of the castle!
Stole your father's life?
Yes, that's right.
And to avenge him,
I will take yours!
[SHUN]
Emilio!
What?
Just hold on.
Please stop.
Shun.
[IBELDA]
Huh?
[BEOPETLE, VESTULSE groaning]
Got hurt.
[VESTULSE groans]
[IBELDA]
Look at you two.
You really got it handed
to ya. You gonna die?
[BEOPETLE]
Maybe.
[VESTULSE groans]
That's a shame.
We've almost made it
to the famous Babel.
I bet it would be interesting
to see the surface, don't you?
Well?
[VESTULSE grunts]
Sounds nice.
Yeah, it does.
And I'm sure you're hoping
I'll bring you along.
Thing is, you two would only be
dead weight holding me back,
and I can't afford that.
[IBELDA]
Nice knowin' ya.
[gasps]
[groans]
[GUIDORO]
Ibelda? What was that for?
Why are you doing this?
Uh?!
Beopetle? Vestulse!
Was it you? Don't tell
me you did this.
[IBELDA] The way you see it,
I killed my comrades,
so you're disgusted.
Because to you, the Truculent
are partners working together.
But to me, working
for the same person
doesn't make us some
kind of brotherhood.
Don't you get that?
I don't think you understand
what you've done.
How could you?
Oh, I know what I'm doing.
When Delzaine goes to the
surface, we'll be abandoned,
left behind to fend
for ourselves.
And that would mean
we'd be going back
to the way we used to live.
[GUIDORO exhales]
[IBELDA]
I don't know about you,
but I for one don't
intend to go back.
So how about you stay
out of my way?
[CASTINA gasps]
It's truly working!
[PASCAL, JOSEPH gasping]
Is that what I think it is?
Babel is operational again!
[ALL gasp]
It seems they've got it working.
We're too late.
[SHUN] Stop! Don't do it,
Emilio, please!
You should stay out of this!
[CASTINA] My lord! The gate will
be opening soon. You must hurry!
[DELZAINE grunts]
[EMILIO]
So, what?
You're running away
to the surface?
[DELZAINE]
Hmm...
I won't allow it.
I'm not done with you.
This is the day I've
worked towards so long.
[gasps]
[EMILIO gasps]
It can't be.
No. It's impossible!
This ends now!
[CASTINA]
My Lord! Babel has opened!
You have to make haste!
[BOTH grunting]
You're finished.
No, Emilio. Whether you
understand it or not,
there is still something
left that I have to do.
I don't care!
[SHUN]
Quit! That's enough!
Move! You're in my way.
I'm helping you!
[EMILIO]
What?
I'm here to help
you get answers!
Huh?
Blind revenge like this will
only hurt you in the end.
Tell me, Delzaine.
Do you consider him
your son or don't you?
Yes, that's right.
Emilio is my son.
[gasps]
All right, then what's
all this about you
killing his real father?
You owe your son an explanation.
Was it really just
to take the throne?
Emilio deserves some answers!
[BOTH gasp]
[IBELDA laughing]
[IBELDA]
So this is where everybody is.
Mind if I drop in?
--[IBELDA yells]
--[EMILIO grunts]
Emilio!
[DELZAINE] That's enough,
Ibelda! Stand down!
[IBELDA] Heh. I don't think
so my lord, not this time.
[DELZAINE]
Excuse me?
If I don't settle things
with this spoiled brat,
I don't know if I'll be
able to live with myself!
[SHUN groans]
Well, time to say goodbye!
You're in the way,
my lord! [yells]
[IBELDA yells]
[DELZAINE gagging]
[IBELDA]
Heh.
[SHUN gasps]
Father, no!
[IBELDA grunts]
[CASTINA] The king!
He murdered King Delzaine!
[RESEARCHERS whimpering]
So, this is the way
to the surface?
[EMILIO yells]
What's the matter, Prince?
Missing your daddy already?
Shut up!
[SHUN]
On your left, Emilio!
[SHUN yells]
I hate leaving
with you still alive,
but I guess there's
no helping it.
I'm off to the surface.
What?
[EMILIO gasps]
See ya.
Hold on!
If anyone's going,
it should be me!
[IBELDA screaming]
--[ALICIA sobs]
--[FALARION squeaks]
--[ALICIA gasps]
--[FALARION] Mm?
What the hell happened?
What was that?
[EMILIO]
Father!
Uh!
Emi... lio...
Can we help?
[footsteps]
What in the hell did
all of us just miss?
[footsteps]
[PASCAL, JOSEPH panting]
It can't be!
Emilio-- What? Your Majesty!
[PASCAL] Babel worked, but did
it function as it was meant to?
I still need to do
more research.
[sighs] I had hoped I'd be able
to ask King Delzaine something.
But, I fear I may
have come too late.
You've become so strong.
I'm proud of you.
[gasps]
[DELZAINE exhales]
I'm so sorry. [cries]
--[crying continues]
--[footsteps]
Why?
[SHUN]
We have many names for the place
beneath the surface
of the Earth.
It has been known over the
years as the underworld,
or Hades,
or Hell.
People speak of it as a place
of death, inhabited by demons.
But despite all those
frightening stories,
I've always been curious
about what Hades or Hell
would truly be like.
Actually, I kinda doubted
there even was an underworld.
I thought it was just a myth.
[SHUN]
Now here I am.
In this underground
world called Endora.
Whatever I was expecting,
it wasn't a place like this.
Not at all.
[SHUN]
Next episode, "Tracks."