[LOUISE] Well, it
certainly has... character.
[SHUN] We're sailing
in this hunk of junk?
It'll sink as soon
as someone touches it!
Sorry.
The ship's been out of
commission a few months now,
but the port inspector would
notice if I gave you a new one.
Don't worry about it.
You made the right call.
The last thing we need is
any troops from the city
coming after us.
I'm always happy to lend
a hand to the Ignauts.
Did as much as I could
to patch her up last night.
She'll get you
where you need to go.
That much I can promise you.
[DEMETRIO]
You have my thanks.
All right! Everyone aboard!
No point in gettin' anxious yet!
If we sink,
it'll be way out at sea!
[SHUN] It's gotta be
bad luck to say that!
[ALICIA] Hurry up!
Boat's not gettin' any younger!
[SHUN]
There's a comforting thought.
And now to finish it.
That's enough, you two!
Come on, Felix,
you of all people
should know better than to
summon your Warp Relic
in the middle of
a sparring match.
So next time I'll just
let her slit my throat?
You know, I gotta say,
going against a fighter like
Felix is pretty impressive
for someone as young as you.
I could destroy him with ease.
I don't understand how
they can even walk around
on this rickety old salvage.
[SHUN gags]
It's not hard.
Unless of course you're seasick.
[FALARION squeaks]
Just gimme a break, will ya?
I've never been on a real ship
before, let alone one like this.
It feels like every time
we hit a wave,
I'm gonna get knocked
right out of this thing.
[ELJUIA]
You look a bit ill, Shun.
If you're feeling seasick,
then you should try eating
some of these.
Sure.
[SHUN coughing]
What the hell?
It's one of those cures
that's almost worse
than the ailment, am I right?
I honestly thought
you'd decided to kill me.
But you were right.
I feel way better now.
[ELJUIA]
I'm pleased to hear it.
Hey, have either
of you seen Emilio?
No. Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen him
since we set sail.
Whoa, there. If you
need to hurl, go up top.
I'm perfectly fine.
Don't lump me
together with Shun.
Just cause he can't keep
his food in, doesn't--
[EMILIO groans]
[DEMETRIO laughs]
I came here to ask
if you're serious
about taming the Zoozians.
Well, I wouldn't
use the word "tame."
But yes, I do plan
to seek their help.
You seem displeased.
Of course I'm displeased!
You shouldn't need
reminding about how many
of our allies they killed!
I won't blame an entire race
for the actions of a few.
In serving Delzaine,
the Truculent have severed
all ties to their people.
These waters will
only get rougher.
The Zoozians didn't
settle here by choice.
They were shipped off
with the intention
that they never make it back.
It's a natural prison
of rock and current.
How is this old wreck supposed
to help us get through that?
I did say this
would be a rough ride,
especially for a spoiled priss.
The next time someone c--
[EMILIO gags]
[SHUN yelling]
Swear you'll never
call me Priss again.
What? No way, dude.
That name fits you
like a friggin' glove.
[SHUN]
Ah! Okay, fine, whatever!
You're not a priss!
You're a total badass!
Just let me up!
[EMILIO, SHUN yelling]
Will you two ever stop fighting?
[SHUN, EMILIO]
Hmph!
--[ALICIA yelling]
--[FALARION squeaking]
It's kinda choppy out here.
It certainly is.
One of the boards
in the forward keel
got busted somehow,
so we need to patch it
or we're gonna sink.
[ELJUIA] There's a chance
I can hold her together
with my Warp Relic.
[EMILIO] Are the Zoozians
really worth all this?
We didn't die, did we? Say no.
Don't even think of
asking me to carry you.
Yeah, as if you could.
You look even worse than I feel.
Stop talking. Your voice
makes my head throb.
[ALICIA sighs]
[FALARION squeaks]
Everyone's safe. Don't worry.
From the looks of things,
she's made her last voyage.
Well then, we'd better
secure that alliance
with the Zoozians.
It's our best hope for a ship,
and our only chance
of staying free and alive.
Sad but true.
It's hardly the first
time we've been
on the verge of destruction.
Yeah, you're right about that.
Well, we may be walking
on a bit of tightrope,
but at least it's
pointing out the way.
Wow.
I'm pretty sure there's nothing
that could keep those guys down.
[SHUN gasps]
They're here!
The Zoozians!
We appreciate
the warm reception.
You landed on the
wrong Island, Endras.
We should try to strike first!
I forbid it, Mischa.
We went through
a lot to get here.
That wasn't because we
have a shortage of enemies.
So you must be the chief
of the Zoozians here.
We need to talk.
What the hell are you
planning to do with us?
[SHUN gasps]
So that's how it's gonna be?
Listen, I know you're
only doing this
to protect yourselves,
but if you'd hear us out, I--
Shut your mouth.
We'd have bound you with them
if you weren't part Zoozian.
Don't make me
regret that choice.
These Endras are
trespassers on our lands,
and that's how
they'll be treated.
Hey...
So is it just me, or do we
seem completely screwed here?
Astute observation.
Endras and Zoozians have
been at odds for generations.
Of course this is
how they greet us.
What does Demetrio
think he's doing here?
The usual for Endras
who end up here
is to cower at my feet and beg.
I find it refreshing
you've opted instead
to give a stoic glare
and a silent tongue.
Isolated though we are,
some rumors do reach us.
If what we've heard is true,
you're the Ignauts.
A band of rebels led by the
charismatic Endra, Demetrio.
I'm flattered to hear
that you remembered my name.
It's quite the honor.
I've no use for
your pleasantries.
Tell me what you want with us.
We want you to join us.
To add your strength to ours.
[GRADIDO grunts]
Our revolution stands
no chance without you.
King Delzaine is
too formidable a foe.
[ZOOZIANS chattering]
These Endras really
think we'd help them?
I'd rather toss 'em to sea!
Supposing that for some
reason we were to help you.
What would we stand
to gain in return?
Your freedom and dignity.
Once Delzaine is defeated,
we'll change the laws
to ensure Zoozians everywhere
are treated as equals.
You have my word.
And what is that worth?
Since when have you
Endras ever upheld
your end of a pact
made with my people?
What is this but a
thinly veiled attempt
to take the throne for
yourself by using us?!
I promise I have no
intention of becoming king.
Your promise means nothing.
'Kay, so I get that Zoozians
really don't like Endras,
but I'm still a little
fuzzy on the why.
I mean what did
y'all do to them?
Zoozians are quite strong.
Physically, they're superior
in almost every way.
Endras saw them as brutes.
Used them as slaves.
Forced them to work
until they broke.
Once they were used up,
they were tossed aside.
The Zoozians you see here...
They're the descendants
of those who were too sick
or injured to be
of use to my ancestors.
That's awful.
My people have earned
every last bit
of the disdain and mistrust
that Zoozians have for us.
[GRADIDO growls]
[GRADIDO]
I'll tell you what...
Your word is nothing now,
but you could prove
its worth through action.
What will it take?
Not much. Only your life.
[DEMETRIO gasps]
His life?
What are you offering?
If you do surrender your life,
then I'll give your cause
my full support in exchange.
[ALL gasp]
No. You can't do this!
The only one I'm
speaking to is him.
If you refuse me,
you can keep your life.
But your cause will get no aid,
and your followers...
Well, they'll die instead.
If your true motive
is not ambition,
but your faith in this cause,
then your life should be
a small price to pay
to see it succeed.
He'll see nothing!
If any of you attempt
to harm him,
I'll kill you.
[ZOOZIANS chattering]
Stand down, the both of you!
It's not a bad deal.
If you die, that's it for us!
You are the only reason
we've made it this far!
Felix is right;
you can't agree to this.
This is ridiculous. Don't
even think about saying yes.
Without you, everything we've
worked for would fall apart!
You say that...
But it just isn't true.
The seeds of
revolt are planted.
They're growing
on their own now.
The king himself knows it.
This revolution will
happen with or without me.
And with your
Zoozian allies secured,
he'll have no way to stop you.
Are you serious?
Demetrio, no.
You can go on and kill me.
[ALL gasp]
But first, make me a promise.
In exchange for my head,
you'll fight to
bring down Delzaine,
and you'll treat all
of my comrades
as if they were your own.
Give me your word,
and I'll take it.
Consider it given.
Stop! It's not worth it.
[SHUN sighs]
Are you planning to fight us?
I thought you were part Zoozian.
If you want to kill him,
you go through me.
Please don't do this.
I beg you.
Let him go, and kill me instead.
If that's not enough,
slay me as well.
I say we put down
the whole bunch of 'em!
Good plan! Kill 'em all!
[GRADIDO roars]
[GRADIDO]
I didn't say you could speak!
Do you wish to die, too?
[ZOOZIAN 8D]
Huh?
So your word is good.
Let's go have that talk.
[SHUN sighs]
That was way close.
I thought that Zoozian guy
was gonna kill us all for sure.
It's a good sign
that they untied us.
I think we can assume
this means we've gained
a bit of their trust.
It's a start at least,
but they haven't given us
permission to leave yet,
and I bet they've
got people watching
to make sure we don't try.
And Demetrio?
You think he's safe?
If they do anything
to hurt him,
then I'll make sure they pay.
He'll be perfectly fine,
I'm certain.
He always pulls through somehow.
[footsteps]
What're you kids up to?
Hey, come back!
[ZOOZIANS muttering]
Do they seem scared to you?
Yeah, they do,
but I can't imagine why.
I mean, they're... Zoozians.
We're weaker.
If we tried to attack them,
they'd beat us.
And that thinking is a big part
of why they've been persecuted.
Zoozians are quite
a bit stronger,
but you Endra outnumbered them.
And once weapons
got into the picture,
that's what mattered most.
The Endra subjugated
them easily,
and used them like animals.
The Zoozians here remember.
They know what
it means to suffer.
Saké is a precious thing here.
We drink it only
on special occasions,
or to signify our highest
respect for a guest.
Quite delicious.
[GRADIDO chuckles]
Let's suppose I poisoned it.
Do you know why?
Your Ignauts have a reputation
as resourceful fighters.
But if I kill their
leader secretly,
I can deal with the rest
later or use them for myself.
It didn't happen, but it
must've crossed your mind.
Yet you drank.
Because you care more about
your cause than your survival.
Or I just didn't take you
for the poisoning type.
Anyway, I seem to recall
you saying we were gonna talk.
And since I haven't
keeled over yet,
I'm assuming you meant it.
[BOTH chuckle]
I forgot to introduce myself.
You can call me Gradido.
As you might've guessed,
I'm the chief here.
As for your request that
we take part in your revolt...
I'm interested.
Glad to hear it.
That said, before
I can commit to this,
there are things I have
to ask about your plan.
[DEMETRIO]
By all means. I'm listening.
When you explained your
need for our assistance,
you mentioned our
strength in particular.
Am I to assume you'd like us
to fight the king's army?
No.
If my plan's successful,
there'll be no need to fight.
I want this
revolution to succeed
without any further
loss of life.
That sounds naïve to me.
It's not a bad idea though.
We'll send a message.
Proof of our strength
and resolve.
We have to show
this king with numbers
that his people want better.
So he'll refuse to
negotiate unless he believes
you stand on equal ground.
And you want us with you,
because the stronger you look,
the more likely he'll
be to hear your terms.
Yeah.
[GRADIDO]
One more thing.
You said you wanted to depose
the king but not to replace him.
What did you mean by that?
I meant exactly what I said.
Society will collapse if there's
no one on top to direct it.
You can't want to end
all civilization.
I don't.
There'll have to be a
new king, I realize that.
So why not take
the job yourself?
Thing is, if I did become King,
then regardless of what
I actually intended to do,
people would suspect I revolted
to take power for myself.
We can't build a country
off of a foundation of doubt.
When the time comes,
we'll choose a king.
One who treats all
their subjects as equals
despite their species.
A king who judges people
only for their deeds.
Have you met someone like that?
No, I haven't.
Hey! I was wonderin'
where ya went off to.
And now you know.
[SHUN]
Didja hear?
It looks like the Zoozians are
gonna help us out after all!
I wonder what Demetrio
said to change their minds.
Yeah.
Geez, dude, try not
to get so excited.
It's not like we just
took a huge step towards
bringing down Delzaine
or something.
You look all pensive.
What're you thinkin' about?
[EMILIO]
Look.
Before all this began,
I never really left the castle.
Must've been pretty
sheltered living there.
Yes, that's true.
I realize now how
ignorant I was.
Those hungry kids in Ametius...
The Zoozians who
were sent here...
I just now realized that
back when Demetrio asked me
what I would do
once the king was dead,
people like them
didn't even exist to me.
Yeah.
The weird thing is,
it wasn't that long ago.
[EMILIO] Back then I thought
that nothing else could matter.
I would take vengeance
for my father.
And then, that would be the end.
It's not, though.
All those lives will go on.
Maybe I can stop Delzaine,
but the kingdom
will still be there,
as will the lives
that depend on it.
I wanted to ask you...
Was your life really so
different on the surface
from how it is down here?
[SHUN]
Well, yeah. It was.
[EMILIO] Could you tell me what
it was like to live up there?
What kind of life would
an average person have?
What the heck's
gotten into you, man?
You never asked me to tell
you about the surface before.
Never thought to.
So are you gonna answer?
[SHUN]
Well, it's not perfect.
But compared to here,
I guess life is kind of easy.
Things are more
convenient, for sure.
We have some pretty
crazy technology.
[EMILIO]
Really, now?
[SHUN]
Yeah. Like, uh...
You know all those weird
gadgets Pascal likes to make?
Literally everybody I
know's got stuff like that.
[EMILIO] Everyone up there
has inventions like Pascal's?
The surface sounds
kind of dangerous now.
Stuff like jets
and flamethrowers
are a bit harder to come by.
But people do have them.
Most of us have
plenty to eat.
Discrimination's illegal,
and there's no war,
least not in my country.
It almost sounds like a utopia.
Yeah. I guess it does.
Hm? Is something wrong?
No, I'm good.
Don't worry. It was nothing.
It would appear they
managed to convince Gradido
to join them somehow.
[VESTULSE grunts]
What a nuisance!
Really?
As much as he hates Endras, I'm
surprised they could sway him.
Guess our job is
that much harder now.
[GUIDORO]
There's something else, too.
It's rather interesting.
So spit it out.
That boy who wounded you
with the prince's help...
It seems he's from the surface.
Huh?! That cocky little freak?
[growls]
So what now?
Should we report to Delzaine?
No. We'll continue as planned.
[FELIX] Next episode,
"Father and Child."