[SHUN laughs]
[SHUN]
Woo!
[laughs]
[SHUN]
I'm the king of the world!
[SHUN inhales]
[ALICIA]
You're acting like a little kid.
Haven't you ever seen the ocean?
[SHUN] Sure, but oceans don't
look like this on the surface.
They're not nearly as... green.
[DEMETRIO] It's actually
a canal, not an ocean.
Ametius is one of the biggest
port cities in Endora.
All sorts of things funnel
through here to the inland,
whether it be goods,
people, or information.
[PASCAL]
That looks like a seabird.
We'll have to cross the canal
to reach Babylon, right?
Eventually, but first we're
going to have to make a stop
at one of the islands out there.
[SHUN]
What for?
To try and recruit the Zoozians
that inhabit the island.
Oh!
So you guys have finally
decided to make your move, huh?
We still need to find
a ship and provision it,
but we should be able
to leave tomorrow morning.
Dude, we're going on a boat!
This adventure just got real!
[ALICIA] Geez, you're easy
to impress, aren't you?
Simple mind, simple pleasures.
[SHUN]
What's that supposed to mean?!
You calling me stupid?
[PASCAL chuckles]
[SHUN]
A bed! A real bed!
I'm finally gonna
get some sleep!
Oh, come on, you sleep
like a dead man
in the tent every night.
I do not!
Yes, you do!
Even plugging your nose
doesn't stop the snoring.
So you're the reason
I keep having dreams
about drowning, you jerk!
They're at it again.
If you boys
have so much energy,
why not use it to go out
and explore the city a bit?
Yeah! Sounds good!
[EMILIO] Go by yourself.
I'm staying here.
Did you get a look
at that seabird
that flew by us this morning?
Yeah. I've never seen
one like it before.
That's because their species
prefers colder climates.
Outside of mating
season, anyway.
I expect we'll find the
weather across the canal
to be very different.
Without some warmer clothes,
you boys will probably
freeze to death.
Aw, man...
I'm more of a warm weather guy.
I'm sure you can find
whatever you need in town.
Better do your shopping now.
Once we board the ship,
you're outta luck.
In that case,
I'm headin' into the city.
You coming, or you wanna
be a prissy popsicle?
I can take care of myself.
Unlike some people.
[PASCAL]
Go together.
This far from the castle,
no one should recognize you.
There's safety in numbers.
You're better off
not splitting up.
Thanks, but I think I'll pass.
Yeah. I'm sick of his dumb face.
The guys shouldn't go alone.
I'd better come
along too to make sure
they don't kill each other.
Besides, I'm pretty
good at haggling.
[EMILIO]
I told you not to call me that!
[SHUN]
Forgive me, O Mighty One!
Would you idiots
shut up and follow me?!
[ALICIA]
What about you, Pascal?
[PASCAL] I'll stay back and
rest these old bones.
Suit yourself.
Should we pick up some warmer
clothing for you, then?
Not necessary.
I have a marvelous invention
that should do the trick
quite nicely.
Okay. Rest up.
We'll see you before dark.
Good. Keep a close eye
on those boys.
Now...
I have preparations
of my own to make.
[SHUN]
Finally, a real city!
I was starting to think
this place was nothing but
backwards villages and
untamed wilderness.
I'm just excited that
we get to go shopping!
[ELJUIA] Hello!
Where are you three off to?
Going out on the town? What for?
Shopping for warmer clothing.
What about you?
There are some
people we need to see
to arrange our
passage out of here.
You know, Shun, you shouldn't
walk around looking like that.
Huh? Looking like what?
[DEMETRIO] Like you come
from a different world.
You stand out like a sore thumb.
Guess I kinda do, huh?
[ELJUIA]
I think I can help.
There, now you fit in.
I think it suits you.
That was a quick fix. Thanks!
Of course.
Now go run along and have fun.
Shun.
You should buy an amit
while you're in the market.
The city's famous for them.
[SHUN]
Okay!
Be careful out here, Prince.
You don't want to get lost.
I won't.
[SHUN]
Ah!
[ALICIA] We have plenty
of time before dark.
Why don't we wander
around and explore a bit?
I vote we start with snacks!
Cool! What do they have?
[gasps]
There something wrong?
[SHUN] I don't think I
can buy anything with this.
That's a weird looking coin.
Money from the surface?
Agh! The only cash I've
got, and it's useless!
Emilio, will you
lend me some money?
I'll pay you back.
No way.
Help a guy out!
You're a prince.
You've gotta be loaded.
Nope.
I have no money.
[SHUN]
I think you're full of it.
No, wait... It makes sense.
I mean, why would he
need money in the castle?
So what good are you, then?
[EMILIO]
What was that?
[SHUN]
Whew!
For a second there, I thought
we were royally screwed.
You're a lifesaver, Alicia.
Thanks!
Sure! Don't mention it.
Although... You boys'll owe me.
And I'll be charging interest.
Those are creepy...
They're dolls people set
out on nursery windowsills
as protective charms for babies.
They ward off curses
and evil spirits.
[SHUN] Oh, yeah?
What about bossy jerkwads?
Are you talking about me?
No.
[EMILIO]
You are, aren't you?
What? No!
Anyway, what's that?
[ALICIA]
A local delicacy.
Nobody's there. Strange...
[ALICIA]
Emilio! You coming or not?
[SHUN] So this is the "amit"
that Demetrio was talking about?
We call these gyros.
[ALICIA]
Ametius is known for 'em.
You can't find them
anyplace else.
The sauce smells like...
Yeah, wow! It's teriyaki!
Six hundred endo for all three.
Right.
You might be the first
dish I've seen here
that actually
resembles decent food!
Come to papa,
you beautiful thing!
What's wrong? Don't you like it?
Yeah. I actually like it a lot.
Then why are you
making that weird face?
[SHUN]
I'm just glad it's not boar!
So whadja want the
notebook for, Shun?
To write down stuff
about Endora
so I won't forget anything
when I go back to the surface.
[EMILIO]
How cute! He's got a diary!
I should punch you!
Guys...
He took my knife!
Emilio!
[EMILIO] Hasn't anyone ever
taught you that stealing
is wrong, urchin?
[ALICIA]
Calm down, Emilio.
[LITTLE GIRL, LITTLE BOY]
Brother!
Run!
He's trying to
feed his family.
Would you like
something to eat?
You can have this if you want.
We bought more than we need.
They can have some, too.
How's that sound?
Yummy!
Can we eat like this every day?
[ALICIA giggles]
Thanks a lot.
And I'm sorry for
trying to steal from you.
[EMILIO]
You don't like being a thief.
If you know it's wrong,
then why do it?
[ALICIA] Because he doesn't
want his family to starve!
You think they're
the only ones?
There are so many
others like them.
So many families
that resort to stealing
because that's the only way they
can feed themselves.
That isn't so uncommon
on the surface, either.
[ALICIA]
Even back in Endora's capital,
there are people
struggling every day
just to make ends meet.
If my father hadn't
left behind his shop,
I would be in the same
situation as these kids.
I didn't know.
Not right now.
Oh, wow, awesome! Look at that!
You guys wanna shoot some hoops?
[LITTLE GIRL]
Whoa!
[CHILDREN laugh]
Shun seems like
a pretty good guy.
I wonder if everybody from
the surface is like him.
[SHUN]
You try!
[LITTLE GIRL]
Okay!
If they are, it might
not be such a bad place
to visit, y'know?
Hey! Want some more players?
[SHUN]
Sure! Come on!
Well, are you coming?
You go ahead.
[ALICIA chuckles]
[CHILDREN laugh]
[SHUN]
You guys're killing me!
I can't sink one shot!
[ELJUIA]
Well, we've got a ship now.
So it should be
smooth sailing from here.
Pun all you want, but the
hardest part is yet to come.
All we can do is believe
in the cause and keep moving.
It got dark quicker
than I realized.
Can we hurry? I'm starving.
[EMILIO gasps]
[EMILIO]
Get down!
Who is it?
I don't know.
[SHUN]
A little girl...
Alone on the street after dark?
Maybe she needs help.
She could be lost.
[EMILIO]
Are you alone?
Where are your parents?
[SHUN gasps]
[EMILIO gasps]
[SHUN]
Look out!
[ALICIA gasps]
A Warp Relic?
But she's just a kid!
Kid or not,
she attacked us. Let's go!
Hey, hold on!
[EMILIO yelling]
Kill him.
Kill the prince.
[SHUN yelling]
Damn!
Shun!
Kill... the prince.
Emilio...
Emilio, no...
Eljuia!
[DEMETRIO]
Sorry about this, little one.
Play time's over.
Man, good timing!
So was that carpet-thing
you threw your Warp Relic?
Yes, and it certainly
came in handy.
Yeah, and look at
Demetrio fight!
That girl doesn't stand
a chance against him.
Can't say I feel great
about fighting a little kid.
[MISCHA]
Let go!
Don't struggle.
[DEMETRIO]
I thought so.
That girl is an assassin.
[SHUN]
You're kidding!
She is a murderer.
A professional killer.
For the most part,
assassins in Endora
are orphaned children.
Those born with Warp Relics
are snatched up
by black market traders.
They're trained to fight.
Then they're sold
to the highest bidder,
usually a noble
with deep pockets.
I don't know how
it's done exactly,
but they're brainwashed.
After they've been taken,
their trainers break them,
and the children are
taught that they must kill
in order to survive.
Their options are either
to eliminate their targets,
or be eliminated themselves.
If they fail or disobey,
death awaits them.
Before long, they aren't
really children anymore,
but efficient killing machines.
[ALICIA]
But she's so young.
[ELJUIA]
Don't let that fool you.
I'm not sure who sent her,
but she is an assassin.
[SHUN]
I think you're right.
You heard. She said,
"Kill the prince."
[ELJUIA]
So Emilio was her target, then.
Which means she was
probably sent by someone
holding a grudge
against the royal family.
[DEMETRIO grunts]
All right, then.
I'll kill you first.
[DEMETRIO] You're welcome to
try, but I doubt you'll succeed.
This is quite interesting.
It looks like I'm going to have
to step up my game a little.
[MISCHA]
I've lost...
[DEMETRIO] I'm not as
young as I used to be.
Let's wrap this fight up.
What d'you say?
I--
You are free to move on.
Forget your past.
The assassin inside you is dead.
There's no choice.
I kill or... die.
That's not true anymore.
Now you have the freedom
to choose how you live.
Don't worry. You'll get
the hang of it before long.
Freedom. I don't know
what that means.
Stick with us, and
we'll find out together.
If you choose to use it,
you have the power
to help change the world.
But still, it's your
decision to make.
But I don't know...
how to be normal.
It's not too hard.
For now, just hold your doll.
And smile when you can.
[LOUISE]
Late again!
I wonder what super lame excuse
they're gonna have this time.
[door opens]
Where were you guys?
Wait, what the hell?
[DEMETRIO]
Sorry we're late, Louise.
We got just a little distracted.
[LOUISE] Is that girl a love
child of yours or something?
[FELIX] Who's the mother?
Is it Eljuia?
[ELJUIA] You aren't as amusing
as you think you are, Felix.
[DEMETRIO] As you've noticed,
our company has increased.
We're not so hard up we
need to start bringing in
little girls.
What's your name, kid?
[ELJUIA] She's a bit shy.
Give her time.
[DEMETRIO] Well? What is
your name, little one?
I'm Mischa.
[DEMETRIO]
All right!
From now on, Mischa's
one of the Ignauts.
Welcome, Mischa!
[ELJUIA]
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
[SHUN]
Really, they're nice.
[ALICIA]
At least most of the time.
Gimme a break.
[SHUN laughs]
[SHUN]
That's Louise for ya.
[PASCAL]
Oh good, you're back.
What's all the commotion about?
[ALICIA]
Hey, Pascal!
Who's that?
The recruits sure are
young these days.
I have to be leaving soon,
but I'm sure these three
will look after you.
[PASCAL]
What did you think of the city?
Well, I...
I was really surprised.
Living in the castle, I didn't
realize things were that bad.
Something has to change.
It's not right.
[PASCAL]
I agree with you.
[EMILIO] You're really
going back to the castle?
[PASCAL] Yeah. There's
something I need to look into.
And I think I'm going to need
access to the Royal Laboratory
in order to do it.
[EMILIO]
Oh.
Don't worry, I'll
catch up with you guys
when I'm done.
I look forward to
analyzing the changes
that occur in you
while I'm gone.
It's not like I'm one
of your experiments.
Course not!
I'm saying that as a friend.
See you all soon!
Take care of yourself!
Don't do anything
I wouldn't do!
And off he goes.
[DEMETRIO]
Hey. We need to get going, too.
Yeah! Adventure, here we come!
Woo-hoo!
[ELJUIA]
Next episode, "Lone Isle."