[EMILIO grunting]
[SHUN coughing]
We thought you could
use a little help waking up.
Why do all men
behave like children?
Sometimes all you
can do is keep fighting
until you see eye to eye.
I don't know how else
to explain it.
That's just how it is for guys.
[DEMETRIO] We still don't have
nearly enough support.
We'll have to go further afield.
Almost all of the
lords near the castle
are in Delzaine's good graces.
[LOUISE] True. They don't
share our outrage.
If they've been
well treated by Delzaine,
what reason could they have
to oppose the current rule?
If we could bring
them to our side,
it would do a lot
to further our cause.
Of course it would.
But what's the point in hoping
for that when they dismiss us
without even
listening to our views?
[DEMETRIO] So, near the castle
we'll find few friends,
but the further north we go,
the fewer lords will
bend to Delzaine's will.
We should have better
luck gaining support
in those areas.
[LOUISE]
That makes sense.
The king forces those who
fall out of his favor northward.
They should be eager
for his rule to end.
At least we have
that going for us.
Still, I'd feel a
lot more confident
if we had more information
about the Royal Guard.
[EMILIO]
Eighty thousand.
[DEMETRIO]
Huh?
That's how many soldiers
there are in the Royal Guard.
Nearly eighty thousand.
I see.
That's more than
we had expected.
If we were to revolt now,
we'd almost certainly
find ourselves fighting
a losing battle.
I don't want to lose
one more person
than we absolutely have to.
A war won by great sacrifice
isn't what I'm after.
[LOUISE]
I agree, of course.
I'm no more eager to
lose men than you are.
But it will take a
lifetime to amass an army
equal to the Royal Guard.
[DEMETRIO]
Yes, that's true.
And it's exactly why we
are gonna need help.
The Zoozians. Right?
[DEMETRIO]
Yep.
You would ally
with those beasts?
Are you mad?
You don't really expect them
to listen to reason, do you?
And have you ever had
dealings with Zoozians before?
[EMILIO] Delzaine employs some
of them as his enforcers.
Oh! The lion guy! We were--
I was attacked by
one outside the castle.
And he was crazy strong.
Way stronger than Prince Priss.
Shut up.
To be honest, he didn't
seem especially interested
in talking things out.
[DEMETRIO] But did you actually
try talking to him?
Uh... Well, no.
You should at least
give it a shot next time.
Huh? Yeah.
[DEMETRIO] The Zoozians
have long been oppressed
by royalty and nobles.
They very well may be
willing to side with us.
We should hope for it.
If they choose to,
we'll gain a powerful ally.
Be ready, Louise.
When the time comes, we'll
need you to be our negotiator.
Sure. You can count on me.
We want them to stand
beside us as partners,
willing to fight
until the bitter end
to uphold what we stand for.
They deserve to be more
than just pawns in a battle.
[SHUN] I don't really
know anything about
the local politics.
All I want is to find a way to
get to Babylon so I can go home.
Tell me something, will ya?
[DEMETRIO]
Huh?
[SHUN] What you really want is
to bring down Delzaine, right?
I mean, that's the whole point
of this revolution of yours.
[DEMETRIO]
Yeah.
Then I think you should
know that he's most likely
heading towards Babylon now.
The king is going to Babylon?
[LOUISE]
Come on, boys.
Let's get those wounds
patched up, shall we?
[EMILIO] Is Demetrio seriously
considering an alliance
with the Zoozians?
There's no denying
they're strong, but still...
Does he really think
they can be relied upon?
If his plan does work, though,
at least I won't need
this clown's help anymore.
[SHUN] If I can convince these
people to take me to Babylon,
I can ditch this punk and
finally get myself home.
Argh! Just looking at his
stupid face pisses me off!
I don't even want to breathe
the same air as this jerk.
[SHUN grunts]
[LOUISE]
Hm?
What's with the grunting?
Are you in a lot of pain?
No! I'm fine, thanks.
[LOUISE] You two boys sure
went all out on each other.
Don't worry, though.
When I'm done,
you'll be as good as new.
[LOUISE]
Here we are. Go on inside.
[SHUN]
In that hut? With him?
[EMILIO] We have to
go in there together?
--[SHUN] Dammit.
--[EMILIO] Dammit.
[LOUISE]
Why are you two standing there?
Go inside already.
Stand around here for too long
and you're basically asking
to get bitten by
an Endora mosquito.
Uh... Some bug doesn't
really scare me that much.
Now hold on!
Endora mosquitos
aren't just "some bug."
If one bites you,
you'll be lucky to escape
with a drop of blood
left in your body.
Damn!
They related to
Dracula or something?
[LOUISE]
Dracula?
[SHUN]
Uh, just forget about it.
[LOUISE] I've got to go grab
some medical supplies.
I'll meet you two inside.
So, about that
scary-looking Zoozian guy.
Is there a reason none of
the other people of Endora
look like him?
[EMILIO sighs]
Well?
[EMILIO]
Don't talk to me.
[SHUN]
Huh?
[EMILIO] We're done.
I don't need you anymore.
What was that?
[LOUISE]
Are you serious?
I leave for two seconds
and you're fighting again?
[SHUN, EMILIO]
Hmph!
[LOUISE sighs]
[LOUISE]
It has to be in here somewhere.
You're close to Demetrio.
Is he really going to try to
ally with the Zoozians?
They look like monsters.
Does he seriously think
they're going to listen to him?
[LOUISE] Not everyone is born
to an equal station in life.
Regardless of social standing,
every person deserves
the right to live freely.
That's what Demetrio
always says.
If the Zoozians are violent,
it's for good reason.
Those in our
world known as Endras
are people born of
a cross between humans
and a species called Anadua.
The Zoozians, on the other hand,
are a cross between
the Anadua and animals.
Long ago, the Endras and
the Zoozians lived together
in peace and harmony.
That changed when the Endras
began persecuting the Zoozians.
The Endra kings sought
to unite Endora by force.
Hungering only for
power and control,
they cared little for who
might be harmed along the way.
Now the Endras, too,
are being oppressed.
As the Zoozians
have been for so long.
Both of my peoples,
brought so low.
From that shocked
look on your face
I'm guessing you had
no idea I'm half Zoozian.
No way!
Surprising, isn't it?
You would never know
just by looking at me.
Zoozians typically have rather
frightening appearances,
and most aren't
much for talking,
which is why people
tend to fear them.
I, um, I'm sorry.
Anyway, let's work
on those cuts.
Who's up first?
Me!
No, me!
I said it first!
You really are children!
I'll do you both
at the same time!
--Hold still!
--[SHUN] Ow, ow, ow, ow!
[SHUN]
Hey, Louise.
Does Demetrio have
any personal experience
with Zoozians besides you?
Yeah.
You may not realize it
looking at him now,
but Demetrio is
from a noble family.
He lived a pampered life--
A spoiled boy without
a care in the world.
Or so he described it.
And he could have
continued on like that
if he didn't give a damn
about anyone else.
But things didn't
turn out that way.
Largely because of a
friend of his. A Zoozian.
[animal whinnies]
[DEMETRIO yelling]
[DEMETRIO groaning]
[DEMETRIO] It's gonna be
dark before much longer.
[DEMETRIO gasps]
Wait! Please don't kill me.
Here, I'll give you
everything I have!
You a kid from the estate?
What's your name?
I--I'm Demetrio.
Okay. I'm Lucio.
I can help you get back home.
[LUCIO whistles]
[DEMETRIO gasps]
You scaredy cat!
[LUCIO] You think you'll
be okay from here?
[DEMETRIO]
Yeah. Thanks a lot.
All right then, take it easy.
Hey, Lucio?
Can we hang out again?
Sure.
If you're ever looking for me,
just whistle.
[whistles]
Cool!
[DEMETRIO gasps]
[DEMETRIO yells]
Demetrio!
What are you doing?!
[LUCIO grunting]
[DEMETRIO]
That was so cool!
I didn't realize
you had a Warp Relic.
[LUCIO]
Yep!
I don't have one, you know.
I wish I did.
Then I wouldn't be so weak.
Warp Relics aren't what
matter. It's training.
Easy for you to say!
You've got a Warp Relic.
Without one, I'm not ever going
to be stronger than this!
You're such a baby!
No I'm not!
[LUCIO]
You little--
[BOTH grunting]
[DEMETRIO yelps]
[LUCIO] You're already brave.
That's worth a lot.
That beast before...
You're the one who
stood up to it first.
If you train hard,
you'll be strong,
but courage is different.
You're born with that.
Hey. I'm hungry.
Why don't we go
find something to eat?
You sure that's okay?
I thought you needed
to head home.
Won't your family
start to get worried?
Nah, it'll be fine.
I'm gonna be turning
15 next month,
so I'm pretty much an adult.
Ahh. Yes, oh wise one.
[whip cracks]
[MAN 5A] Stand up,
you worthless slacker!
I don't recall giving
you permission to rest!
You're just a dumb animal.
[DEMETRIO]
What are you doing? Stop that!
Who the hell asked you?
Run along now.
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
[MAN 5A]
Shut up!
Lucio!
You scum!
I can't believe
an animal like you
would dare draw a
Warp Relic on an Endra!
You should know your place!
No, stop!
Leave him alone!
[MEN grunting, laughing]
[DEMETRIO]
Lucio...
I'm sorry.
So sorry. This is my fault.
[LUCIO]
Quit your whining.
You did nothing wrong.
[DEMETRIO]
Lucio?
I don't regret any of it.
I'm glad we met.
Glad we became friends.
It's been fun.
I swear I will become stronger.
[LOUISE]
Demetrio?
[DEMETRIO]
How are our guests?
I treated their wounds,
but nothing I do
is going to make them
like each other.
You sure about
leaving them alone?
Don't worry. They'll be fine.
But what if they try
killing each other again?
Well?
[DEMETRIO]
It's like I told you.
They just have
to keep on fighting
until they see eye to eye.
It's the way men settle things.
That's a stupid way
to do it if you ask me.
[SHUN] I don't care about
this revolt of theirs
or killing the king.
I just want to get home
as soon as I can.
[EMILIO] Does Demetrio
really think the Zoozians
will side with him?
That's ridiculous.
The man is deluding himself.
[SHUN] Maybe if I can get
more info out of that guy
who sees the future...
[EMILIO] Who cares what
happens with their revolt?
I just want Delzaine dead.
If I'm lucky, maybe
he's gone for good.
[SHUN]
Eljuia?
[ELJUIA]
Hm? Yes?
Can I borrow you a sec?
I just wanted to ask
you more about yesterday.
You know, that stuff you
told me about my future.
All right. What about it?
If you saw the vision again,
think you'd understand it more?
That does seem quite possible.
Okay, good to know.
Whoa! Over there, look!
I think I saw something move!
What was it?
You know this area
better than me.
You should check it out!
[ELJUIA sighs]
[SHUN gasps]
There's nothing over here.
[SHUN growls]
[SHUN]
Yah!
[SHUN gasps]
Dammit!
[ELJUIA sighs]
[ELJUIA]
Hold on!
I don't understand why,
but I'm seeing something
about needing to find
an Endora bluebird if you
want to be able to return
to the surface.
Really?
And what's more,
I think I sense one of them
in that direction.
Sweet!
[SHUN yells]
My butt! Ow!
[ELJUIA chuckles]
[SHUN]
Endora bluebird, here I come!
The Endora bluebird
doesn't exist.
I would say it's more
than fair payback
after he tried to trick me.
So whenever you're in danger,
do you see the
future every time?
No, that isn't
always the case.
I don't know how it works.
I'm never sure when or where
or even if it'll happen.
I see.
[GUIDORO] It appears that the
scout has detected the scent
of the rebel army in this area.
The prince and that unknown boy
also seem to be with them.
We've found the Ignauts!
We should set up an ambush.
Agreed.
[VESTULSE grunts]
What about the kid
with the prince?
I'd like to punch
his bratty face in.
Agreed!
[VESTULSE grunts]
Do what you want,
but we are not
to harm the prince.
[IBELDA]
Deal! You made my day!
That's the boy.
Good. Leave him to me.
He said it was this way.
Shouldn't I have
seen it by now? Man...
Maybe it's hiding in the trees?
Fancy meeting you here!
[SHUN]
Hey!
You're that Zoozian guy
from the castle!
I'm so flattered
you remember me.
[birds cawing]
It's him!
[BEOPETLE growling]
[MAN 4B yelling]
[MAN 4B yells]
So, why aren't you
with the prince?
[SHUN]
I hate that guy!
You know, you're a
smug little punk.
But I actually
like that about you!
[IBELDA growls]
[SHUN]
He's too strong.
No way I'm gonna survive this.
[EMILIO]
Dammit! What am I doing?
It's not like I give a damn
what happens to him.
[SHUN]
This is it. I'm screwed!
[EMILIO] Would he come
running to help me?
[SHUN] It couldn't
have been anyone else?
[EMILIO]
Shut up!
[SHUN] Get outta here.
I don't want your help!
[EMILIO]
Stand up and fight!
Don't just sit there!
Quit bossing me around!
I'm sick of it!
[EMILIO] Let's deal with
him first and then fight!
[SHUN]
Okay, fine!
Hey, Prince.
I'm supposed to bring you
back in one piece.
Personally, though, I think
you'd look better as a corpse.
[GUIDORO] Is it safe to
assume you're the leader
of the Ignauts?
[DEMETRIO]
That's right. My name is De--
[GUIDORO]
Your name means nothing to me.
And by the time
I'm done with you,
it will mean nothing
to anyone else.
Not a chance in hell!
[IBELDA growls]
[SHUN yelling]
You're gonna have to
get past me first!
Oh yeah?
Good, I don't care what
order I kill you in!
Shun!
[IBELDA yelling]
[IBELDA]
What?
[yelling]
Wait, what happened?
Did his Warp Relic
really just evolve?
[SHUN]
Emilio! Now!
[SHUN, EMILIO yelling]
[IBELDA yelling]
Did we just... win?
[VESTULSE yells]
[LOUISE yells]
Can you really tell
me you're satisfied
and that it's not pathetic
being Delzaine's pawn?
And I'm sure all you rebel scum
lead virtuous and
rewarding lives.
We offer our services
to the powerful,
and are compensated in return.
I fail to see what's
wrong about that.
That's something called selling
your soul to the devil.
Damn you!
Now die!
In your dreams!
[DEMETRIO]
Next episode, "Determination."