[SHUN, EMILIO scream]
[EMILIO, SHUN grunt]
[IBELDA]
Huh?
[gasps]
[SHUN]
Damn that hurt.
Is this...?
No way.
[SHUN]
We're back!
[IBELDA] You! Where the
hell did you come from?
Get ready, Shun.
I'm with ya!
[GUIDORO]
Emilio!
[LOUISE]
Shun!
[SHUN]
Our friends are here too.
Looks like Dad wasn't lying.
Your Parinblue brought us back.
[IBELDA laughing]
It's been too long since
the last time we played.
I'm glad to see that you've been
taking care of yourselves.
[SHUN]
That was close.
We could've shown up
anywhere in Endora.
Why'd it have to take us here?
You're asking me?
The thing's lodged in your
chest, why don't you know?
[SHUN]
Uh.
Explain yourselves.
How did you suddenly
appear from the sky?
Well, the surface is
pretty high up from here.
So I'm guessing we had
to fall a little bit?
So dumb.
Wait, did you just say that
you were on the surface?
You can finish catching up once
I've sent you to your deaths.
We'll explain more later.
This won't take long.
[IBELDA growls]
[FELIX grunts, yells]
I can deal with these easily.
[laughs]
[gasps]
[LOUISE grunts]
You didn't have to do that.
We need to focus on
the battle at hand.
Yeah, I know.
[IBELDA yelling]
[EMILIO]
I'm sorry, Shun.
[SHUN]
Huh? What are you getting at?
[EMILIO] You finally managed
to get back to the surface.
But now you've landed yourself
in Endora all over again.
[SHUN] Did you just consider my
feelings? I'll be damned.
[IBELDA yells]
[EMILIO, SHUN grunt]
To be honest, I'm not all
that worried about it.
I mean, as long as I've got
Dad's crystal with me,
I can come and go as I please.
Maybe, but if I were you,
I wouldn't get my hopes up
until I'd worked out how to
activate that thing at will.
Dude. You're a killjoy.
I'm sure I can figure it. I just
need to practice a little.
What is this?
We're reunited at last and
you completely ignore me?
Pay attention so I can drink
the fear from your eyes
while I kill you!
You'll get yours!
But the more you interrupt us,
the longer you're gonna
have to wait for it.
[IBELDA]
What?!
You heard me: the world
doesn't revolve around you,
so deal with it!
Now wait your turn!
Stupid brat!
[BOTH gasp]
Not too bad for a rookie!
Forget them.
I'm the foe who
should concern you.
Your blood is useless.
And I've already proved
you can't stop me.
So get out of my way!
You've grown into
an abomination.
A blight that must be purged
from this world... by me.
I don't have time to
listen to you rant.
I have plans and they're with
those Endra brats behind you.
They're the ones I want!
[GUIDORO gasps]
[GUIDORO screams]
Let's go!
I'm gonna make damn sure
you die this time, Guidoro.
[EMILIO] You said you wanted
me and Shun, right?
[IBELDA]
Huh?
[SHUN]
Well good, cause here we come!
[SHUN, EMILIO yelling]
[IBELDA screaming]
[MISCHA, LOUISE gasp]
Sounds like they got him.
[IBELDA screaming]
Heh. About time we took him out.
Uh. What's up?
Something isn't right.
[gasps] Whoa. What's happening
to him? Did we do that?
[IBELDA groaning]
Hold on. Was that--
What's going on?
[ELJUIA groaning]
[panting]
Almost there...
Just a little further.
[ELJUIA screaming]
He's in pain.
Leave him be.
[gasps] I can't.
If you break his
concentration now,
he'll have suffered for nothing.
Yeah, I know. But still...
[DEMETRIO]
Eljuia knows what he's doing.
[gasps] Demetrio.
Connecting your spirit
to the pain of the world
is no pleasant task. Especially
if the world in question
is being slowly bled
of its life force.
Then why don't we stop him?
If he keeps this up,
who knows what'll happen?
You heard the screams.
Aren't you worried?
Of course I am, but this
was his choice to make.
We have comrades
throughout the continent
risking their lives
to protect Endora.
Eljuia has every right
to do the same.
[ELJUIA screams]
[IBELDA (SLIME) growls]
[IBELDA (SLIME) roars]
So, uh... Is Ibelda
somewhere in there still,
or is that dark stuff
all that's left?
And why's there so much of it?
What are you asking that for?
We should focus on finding
a way to kill it.
Do you have any bright ideas?
Watch out.
[EMILIO, SHUN gasp]
[IBELDA (SLIME) growls]
[SHUN]
Nice shot! Thanks.
[LOUISE] I thought you cut
him down. What happened?
Yeah, uh. It didn't quite work.
Be cautious.
He isn't just bigger.
Any vestige of sanity he
had left is likely gone.
He'll be completely
unpredictable now.
[SHUN]
That sounds about right.
[IBELDA (SLIME) growls]
[gasps]
I can handle myself.
Stop protecting me!
Look, this isn't about you.
I won't go easy on this monster
just to soothe your ego.
[MISCHA growls]
[FELIX]
Mischa, wait!
[gasps]
Above you!
Are they okay?!
[BOTH gasp]
How did I--
Oh, no. Felix...
[MISCHA cries]
You fiend!
[MISCHA gasps]
[LOUISE gasps]
She saved her!
[MISCHA]
I-I told you.
You didn't... need to do that.
It's like I said before.
I didn't do it to save you.
[laughs]
[EMILIO] Where are the
men I sent with you?
[GUIDORO]
They had wounded and casualties,
so I sent them back
to the castle.
I see.
We're no match for
this thing as we are.
We have wounded ourselves.
We should fall back too.
[GUIDORO]
Hmph. I think you're right.
[ELJUIA]
I am the seer, Eljuia.
I would commune with the
spirit of Endora's depths.
I beg for your counsel.
So that I might
help preserve you.
[ELJUIA]
Please, let your voice be heard.
And your pain be shared.
[ELJUIA]
Warp particles...
[ELJUIA gasps]
[ELJUIA]
Is this...?
[ELJUIA gasps]
[crash]
That's it, I'm going in!
Hey! Alicia, wait!
[ALICIA]
Oh, no! What happened?
[ELJUIA grunts]
[DEMETRIO]
Eljuia.
[ELJUIA]
Demetrio. You're here.
[ALICIA]
We heard you fall. Are you hurt?
Did you learn anything?
[ELJUIA] Yes. I called
to the spirit of Endora.
And my call was answered.
It showed me where the
Warp Particles have...
have been taken.
Tell us what needs to be done.
[ELJUIA] I'm sorry. All I can
tell you is the name.
It's called Tir Na Nog. Go.
[DEMETRIO grunts]
We'll handle it. You rest.
[DEMETRIO]
Well, doctor? How is he?
[DOCTOR 22A] He's about as
exhausted as I've ever seen.
And the only cure
for that is rest.
[PASCAL] Demetrio. Can I
borrow you for a moment?
[PASCAL] I've confirmed the
information Eljuia gave us.
The Warp Particles
aren't just disappearing.
They're converging
at a single point.
They wouldn't do this
on their own.
Something's pulling them in.
We can't be sure what
that something is.
But thanks to him,
we know exactly where
we have to go to find it.
[GRADIDO] Do we really have
no idea what to look for?
A creature? A machine?
[RODNEY] This thing can
draw in Warp Particles
from across the continent.
I can't imagine anything alive
with that kind of power.
I would wager it's some
kind of a man-made device.
A construct like Babel, perhaps.
But the spot circled on
the map is in the middle
of the Great Sea. I doubt
something like this would
just be floating, but I don't
see any islands, either.
Fair point. It isn't possible
to build that far out at sea.
Not for us.
But this construct wasn't
made by us. It was them.
Hold on. What do you
mean by "them"?
The beings of Tir Na Nog.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
That's my theory.
There is said to be an
ancient ruin in the sea.
A heavenly place, far beyond
the reach of mortals.
I don't know if they
were men or not.
But someone made the Parinblue,
and their civilization was far
more advanced than ours.
I've heard the stories
same as you.
They seemed farfetched.
There are those who
have the same doubts
about tales of the surface.
It's hard to believe
without seeing.
[RALPH] So we don't actually
know what's going on, right?
There's a chance that Warp
Particles just group up
every few thousand years.
It might all sort itself out.
There's no use talking about it.
Let's find Tir Na Nog.
If it's real.
I wouldn't call myself
convinced either.
I've heard nothing to prove
that this mystical ruin
is actually out there.
Eljuia's word is all
the proof I need.
I understand, but--
[SHUN] I'd bet money that those
ruins are real, if I had any.
[ALL gasp]
[DEMETRIO] Hey.
[ALICIA]
Emilio!
Oh, thank goodness, how have
you been, are you okay?
We're fine.
Yeah, it's the others we
need to worry about.
Huh?
[DEMETRIO]
Felix.
Louise.
Apologies. I should not
have let this happen.
[SHUN]
So, how bad are they?
[ALICIA] Their lives
aren't in danger, but...
Gotcha. What about Demetrio?
Well, he tries to stay
strong for everyone else.
[chirps]
[SHUN]
Yeah. That sounds like him.
The two of you did well to
get back in so little time.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
[ALICIA]
"Worry" is an understatement!
I was completely freaked out,
where did you two
end up this time?
I finally got to go home.
He just played tourist.
[EMILIO grunts]
Guess that means
Pascal was right.
[PASCAL]
Yes! I knew it!
[ALICIA]
Uh!
It had to be the surface.
There was no better explanation
for your disappearance.
Sorry if this breaks the
flow of conversation,
but I wanted to ask you about
what you said earlier, Shun.
Are you sure that it's all true?
I said what? I really
don't remember.
That there's an ancient
ruin in the sea
we should be looking for?
[SHUN]
Ohh, that.
All I know for sure is
that there's some kinda
science thingy suckin'
up Warp Particles.
Honestly, it might be anything.
But yeah, it could
be in the sea.
[PASCAL] And you found
this out on the surface?
How? Is that where
they're being sent?
Uh... About that--
[EMILIO]
Shun. You don't have to--
[SHUN]
It's fine. They deserve to know.
Your Warp Particles are
being stolen on purpose.
And we know who's doing it.
Because he's my father.
[ALL gasp]
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[PASCAL]
Keep up the pace!
Ibelda's much stronger now, and
he could attack at any moment!
This work has to be
done before dawn!
Work hard and fast. If he
reaches the castle, we're lost.
[ALICIA]
I don't know. I'm surprised.
I'm sure that everyone was.
It's a crazy story.
I can't believe that Delzaine is
actually Shun's real father.
So you're saying his father
is the man who raised you
and the man who
raised him is the one
who killed your real father?
So confusing...
[FALARION chirps]
[EMILIO]
Hm.
[ALICIA] You leave tomorrow,
right? For Tir Na Nog?
Shun's father will steal
everything our world has
if he gets the chance.
He must be stopped.
[ALICIA]
I'm going, too!
[EMILIO]
Uh! Listen, Alicia...
[FALARION chrips]
Relax, okay, I was only joking.
You bought it, though.
[EMILIO]
Uh. Uh...
Thought it over,
and I'm pretty sure I can do
more good here than out there.
Endora's in a pretty
bad way right now.
And sometimes I
feel kinda helpless.
I mean, what's the point in
trying when you're too weak
to make a difference?
But I'm not weak.
And there's something out
there that only I can do.
I'm sure of it.
So I won't follow you.
Just promise me that you'll
come back safe, okay?
I promise.
If you break it, I'll kill you.
Noted.
[SHUN] Hey! Less talk,
more shovelin', okay?
Kay!
[FALARION chirps]
[ALICIA]
Falarion.
[chirps]
Hello, Father.
All right, then.
Good luck. N'fly fast.
Just leave it to us, kay?
I trust that you'll
defend the castle.
[DEMETRIO]
Right!
Take care, Dad. Please
protect my friends.
I'll be waiting for you!
[roars]
Well, are we ready to go, then?
I think so. Falarion, let's go!
[ALL gasp]
What was that?
Trajectory's good.
It's right on course!
[IBELDA (SLIME) roars]
He's growing.
So this is what's
become of Ibelda.
I wouldn't wish such
a fate on any foe.
Everyone take your positions!
We can't let him
get to the castle!
Joseph!
Sir! Let's do this, guys.
Remember, it's just
like we practiced.
[AARON] Right! Take your
places in the forest.
I can smell the rot from here.
What a loathsome creature.
I don't get it.
How does he manage to
keep growing like this?
[IBELDA (SLIME) roars]
[DEMETRIO]
There's your chance. Get moving!
Falarion!
[gasps] That's a trap.
[PASCAL] Didn't really have
time to hide the thing.
We're lucky he's lost his wits.
[IBELDA (SLIME) roars]
[FALARION groans]
Falarion! Hang in there!
We're not gonna fall,
we're not gonna fall!
They're gonna fall!
Any idea how to cut them loose?
[roars]
[grunting]
[screams]
Uh! Pascal!
[EMILIO] Pascal!
Uh! Huh?
[EMILIO]
Hold on, I'm coming down.
[PASCAL]
No! Just leave me!
[EMILIO] Wait! What are
you saying, Pascal?
[PASCAL] I'm saying we
have a mission here!
That has to come first!
Understand?
I'm not about to let some filthy
monster get in our way.
Emilio... Shun...
The future of Endora
is in your hands.
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
What did... he do?
[EMILIO]
Pascal!
[SHUN]
Next episode, "Showdown."