[gunshot]
[SHUN] The hell, Dad.
Why did you do that?
Why would you say
I'm not your son?
The truth can be
an ugly thing.
We'll discuss this more once
I've put our prince here
to sleep. I'll make it quick.
Just like I did with his father.
[EMILIO]
What?
[ASANAGA] Alzerm was an arrogant
fool, but Delzaine...
I think he knew
what I was planning.
[EMILIO]
So then, you admit it.
[ASANAGA] Yes, I killed
your brute of a father.
And I'd do it again.
There's no way...
Damn you!
Uh!
What? My Warp Relic!
[ASANAGA]
Heh, heh.
Now, come to my side, Shun.
[SHUN gasps]
Don't listen to him.
Uh... But he's...
It's true that we
share no blood.
But it's also true that I
brought you into this world,
and raised you as my own.
So, I'd say you're mine.
As would your mother.
You're lucky that
Shun cares for you.
Otherwise I'd kill
you right here.
And how precisely
would you do that,
when you can't even
summon your Warp Relic?
[EMILIO grunts]
[ASANAGA]
Step away from him, Shun.
[ASANAGA grunts]
[EMILIO]
We're leaving.
[BOTH panting]
[EMILIO groans]
[ASANAGA] So, Delzaine
followed me after all.
What happened?
[ASANAGA]
How strange.
Where the hell am I?
[DELZAINE]
You slept a long time.
How do you feel?
[DELZAINE]
Welcome, stranger.
For what purpose have you
travelled to our kingdom?
I have none. I was
in my research lab
and then I was pulled
into this light.
I suppose I owe you my thanks.
You can thank my brother.
If you're from the surface,
he would speak with you.
The surface? What do you
mean? What is this place?
[DELZAINE] A world below yours.
Called Endora.
[gasps]
[ALZERM]
To think,
there really was another
world on the surface.
Tell me, Asanaga. How different
is your land from this one?
Four hundred years ago,
I would say that they
were fairly similar. But
my people now have tools
which allow us to shape
our world as we like.
[ALZERM]
This level of technology
is common on the surface?
[ASANAGA] Yes. Endora is
truly a marvelous place:
beautiful beyond measure.
But we've made advances
on the surface.
My people enjoy luxuries
that yours have never known.
Oh? I would like to hear
more of these luxuries.
To name a few, large winged
vehicles that expedite travel.
Handheld tools that allow speech
to cross great distance.
And weapons more powerful
than you could imagine.
I can imagine much.
You've piqued my interest.
[ASANAGA]
I'm in your debt, my prince.
I'll repay the favor someday.
[DELZAINE]
You intend to return, then?
Yes.
At least for as long as the king
continues to find me tolerable.
After all, what scientist
wouldn't leap
at the chance to explore
an entirely new world?
[ASANAGA]
Amazing.
I've just made the discovery
of the century.
[ASANAGA]
Remember that crystal you found?
Well I've been analyzing it,
and you would never guess
what I've discovered.
It's truly incredible.
Revolutionary!
[laughs]
What's funny?
Nothing really, it's just
refreshing to see you
get so excited about something.
I feel like it isn't a side of
you I get to see very often.
Yes, well I don't think anyone
could avoid getting excited
about something this big.
So? What is it?
[ASANAGA]
I can't tell you just yet.
But believe me when I say that
once this research is finished,
everyone will come
to admire my work,
and my lab will grow into one of
the world's largest companies.
[MAKIKO] That's quite the
vision. I hope it comes true.
Just remember that no
matter what happens,
I already know what an
amazing scientist you are.
It's all right, dear. I know
how crazy this sounds.
Thanks for being so
patient with me.
If I play this right, I can make
a better life for all of us.
For you, and for our baby boy.
[MAKIKO] Thank you. But, don't
push yourself too hard, okay?
This little one
needs both of us.
Yeah, and we'll be there.
Makiko!
Is she okay?
Your wife will recover within
the week, but we lost the child.
[ASANAGA]
Uh... What happened?
[MAKIKO whimpers]
You weren't there. I'm so sorry.
[ASANAGA grunts]
[ALZERM] So the surface
has no Warp Particles,
nor anything like Warp Relics?
[ASANAGA]
To be perfectly honest,
I was almost skeptical
when you first told me
of their existence.
The existence of such a particle
defies almost everything
I've been taught as a scientist.
So Endora possesses something
the surface does not.
I'm glad to hear you haven't
surpassed us in every aspect.
[ASANAGA] That's one point, but
Endora has other advantages too,
our simple sun cannot hope to
compare with the spectacle
of Adamas. Nor is our land
quite so rich with life.
Yes, you'd be hard pressed
to beat us in that.
Huh?
Allow me, sir.
What is that thing?
[ASANAGA]
A ferrocerium lighter:
it's essentially just a
more efficient version
of the flint and steel that
you're accustomed to.
[ALZERM]
I see.
[DELZAINE]
Mm...
[ASANAGA] If it's of interest,
you're welcome to keep it.
[ALZERM]
Are you sure?
Ahh! The more you teach
me about the surface,
the greater it seems.
[door opens]
[EMILIO]
Daddy!
[MAID 1B] Lord Emilio!
You mustn't interrupt!
[ALZERM]
It's fine. Leave him be.
[EMILIO coos]
[ALZERM] He's strong willed,
like his father! [chuckles]
Uh. Who's that?
What, you don't remember him?
This is our old friend Asanaga.
[ASANAGA]
It's been too long, Lord Emilio.
[EMILIO]
Asa... naga?
[ALZERM] You were quite young
the first time you met him,
I'm don't think you
could even walk yet.
I recall you expecting
a child of your own.
How does fatherhood suit you?
I... Yes.
It suits me just fine.
Well, the next time
you come to Endora,
you should bring
the brat with you.
I bet you'd like to have a
playmate from the surface,
wouldn't you?
Surface?
That's right.
Uh. Uh!
[ALZERM laughs] This is the kind
of thing they play with there!
What do you think?
[EMILIO]
I wanna go there.
Here's a thought, Delzaine.
Why don't you have Asanaga
examine your son,
and see what can
be done for him?
Medicine isn't my
field of expertise.
Can you tell me what
it is that ails him?
I cannot.
All I know is there was some
kind of outbreak last year
and he was one of the victims.
Delzaine's boy was born with
a fragile constitution.
A great deal weaker than Emilio.
[ASANAGA] I understand, sir.
I can't make any guarantees,
but there is a chance that
surface medicine could save him.
Our only other option
is to keep watching
as his condition worsens.
You've heard how
advanced the surface is.
You should let Asanaga
seek care for him there.
I want nothing more than to
help my son get well again.
However...
[ASANAGA]
I can certainly sympathize
with your reluctance
to part with your son.
But, if his highness
would allow us to restore
the ancient ruins of Babel,
you could accompany us
to the surface, and oversee
your child's care.
Do you actually believe
such a thing could be done?
The mechanics are a bit
different from what I'm used to.
But I should be able
to manage, and if I do,
it would allow you to import
the surface's technologies
and take what you'd like.
Indeed. My dream of uniting
our worlds under one banner
might not be so
farfetched after all.
[DELZAINE]
We mustn't consider this!
Babel can never
be opened again!
Our ancestors
explicitly forbade it!
[ASANAGA] I apologize.
If your ancestors are here
at this table, please tell
them I meant no offense.
I was merely hoping to help
your king usher his people into
a new age of wealth and
progress while saving
the life of your son, but not if
it offends their sensibilities.
Careful. He has a sharp
tongue, this one!
[laughs]
[snoring]
[growls]
[inaudible]
If Asanaga can change my
brother, what will he do to you?
[gasps]
[DELZAINE]
Take care of him.
[ASANAGA]
Of course. As if he were my own.
I can't fully describe
the wonders
that physicians on the
surface are capable of.
[DELZAINE]
Thank you.
You've made the right choice.
[ALZERM]
Well done, Asanaga!
I never imagined that
Babel could be restored
in so little time.
[ASANAGA]
I'm honored, Your Grace.
I'd like to reward
your great service.
Name anything you desire,
and I will make it yours.
It's reward enough to know
that I've been of help
in some small way, Your Grace.
[ALZERM] Why hold back?
We're friends, you and I.
There must be something
you would ask.
[ASANAGA] It's less of a
request, than... a suggestion.
[DELZAINE]
I understand that you intend
to take my brother
to the surface.
Listen well. You will bring
me my son and close Babel.
[ASANAGA]
Spare me the brash talk.
I have done absolutely
nothing here
that your brother
didn't ask me to do.
[DELZAINE] I'm sure that
compared to the civilization
you have on the surface, we must
seem barbaric. But Endora has
prospered for thousands
of years exactly as she is.
I can't put this
beautiful world at risk
just to satiate my
brother's greed.
[ASANAGA]
Sounds like your brother's
abusing his throne. Maybe you
should take it from him.
[DELZAINE]
Huh?
Yes. You could simply kill him.
The kingdom would be
better off and you know it.
[DELZAINE]
How dare you?!
[ASANAGA]
Heh.
[DELZAINE growls]
That blade must leave
a very recognizable cut
unless you're willing to be
banished for the crime,
I'd murder me with
something else.
But remember, I have your son.
[DELZAINE growls]
Don't worry, I'll be
gone soon enough.
There's just one last
thing I have to finish.
You bastard! After all this
time, you'd betray me?
[ASANAGA] Wrong. Betrayal
implies past loyalty.
[ALZERM]
Why are you doing this?
Let's see. You've ceased to be
of use, and I don't like you.
[ALZERM]
I'll make you pay.
[ALZERM yells]
[gunshot]
[DELZAINE]
Brother!
How could you? He thought
you were his friend.
[ASANAGA] He thought he could
use me to get weapons
from the surface. I want to make
sure that will never happen.
[gunshots]
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
No, wait! Give me back my son!
If you love him more than I do,
then follow me to the
surface and prove it.
[EMILIO]
I'm sorry, Shun.
[gasps]
You've got nothin'
to be sorry for.
But I've given you
a bitter memory.
[SHUN]
No. That's not your fault.
It's funny. He told me to my
face that I'm not his son.
But I still don't believe it.
I'd rather fake like
we're okay. Weird, right?
Welcome home, what
kept you so... long?
I'm sorry.
Whatever this is, we can talk
about it inside. Come on.
Yes. What he told you was true.
So you knew as well?
The truth about Endora?
He was always careful to
keep the details from me.
Honestly, I didn't want to ask.
[SHUN]
Well...
[MAKIKO, EMILIO gasp]
I... There was a part of me
hoping that Dad had maybe lied
to both of us, somehow.
At least that way I'd know
something had been real!
It was real, Shun.
From the day you came home,
you were mine. My son.
And there's nothing that
could ever make that a lie.
[gasps]
[MAKIKO]
Where've you been? I...
He's sleeping.
Why on earth do you
have a baby with you?
He's very ill. I'm taking
him to the hospital.
[SHUN cries]
Aw. Well then, we should
head there right now,
he's burning up.
[SHUN laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[ASANAGA]
Up you go! You like that?
[MAKIKO] He's healthy now.
We should give him back.
Do you really think that
would be the best for him?
[ASANAGA]
He loves you. I can see it.
He was on the brink of death.
But we took him in, and he
lived. Haven't we earned this?
[SHUN coos]
[MAKIKO]
Yes. I knew it was wrong, but...
When the time came to let
you go, I couldn't do it.
[SHUN]
Mom, I...
[MAKIKO] I know, if I'd really
cared about your happiness,
I would've made him take
you back to your world.
I'm sorry.
[SHUN]
No, you can't say that.
[MAKIKO]
It's true.
[SHUN] I was happy here
and you know it.
Don't pretend that isn't true!
I don't care how you got me;
you're the only mother I have
and no one could replace you!
[MAKIKO gasps]
I don't know the mother
I was born to,
and I'm sure she loved me,
but I can't think of one way she
could've done better than you.
And honestly... I feel
the same way about Dad.
I mean sure, he works too much.
But I've always
known he loved us.
I was never unhappy here.
Shun. My sweet boy.
I'm so happy that I
got to be your mother.
Why, though? Why did he do it?
[MAKIKO]
Hold out your hand for me.
[SHUN]
Oh, yeah.
This was always in my room.
[MAKIKO] On the day he brought
you home it was on your wrist.
It's the only connection to
your parents you came with.
[EMILIO]
Shun.
[SHUN]
Uh.
That bracelet you're holding
bears the emblem
of the Royal Family.
You mean your family?
You're a Langheim.
We are cousins.
Wait. That would mean that
my real father was...
[EMILIO]
Yeah.
[SHUN] Do you consider him
your son, or don't you?
[DELZAINE] Yes, that's right.
Emilio is my son.
No, he's your dad.
I might be the son he
raised, but he dedicated
his entire life to rebuilding
Babel and finding you.
[SHUN gasping]
Can't sleep either?
[SHUN]
My head won't stop spinning.
I thought I was a normal guy.
Not the son of a dead king
from another world.
[EMILIO] You know, I
actually remember you.
[SHUN]
Uh.
[EMILIO]
How long'll he be sick for?
His father's looking for
the best doctors in Endora,
trying to figure out what
kind of medicine he needs.
You'll be able to play
together once he finds it.
Uh? Don't worry! We're gonna
play together soon, 'kay?
[EMILIO] You were the only
person I knew who wasn't
an adult. I felt like I'd made
my first friend that day.
Delzaine tried everything to
save you. He was desperate.
And when all else failed,
he... sent you here.
I admire him.
Yeah?
[EMILIO] Everyone blamed him
for killing his brother.
I despised him to
the core of my being.
Even tried to kill him.
But he did everything he could
to find his lost son again.
And in the end, he did.
I... I don't...
I do understand how you feel.
It's exactly how I
felt with Delzaine.
He's the man who raised me.
Yeah, but that wasn't my
father we talked to today.
He confessed, flat out.
He killed my father.
Yes, I killed your
brute of a father.
No way--not Dad.
He's not a killer.
[SHUN cries]
[SHUN]
Why, dad? Why'd you do it?
[ALZERM]
Next episode, "Confrontation."