We've done our best to
stop all this violence
against the villages.
But with mixed results.
We're a stopgap at best. The
only way this strife will really
end is if the
kingdom steps up.
[RALPH] Yes, but what can a
kingdom hope to accomplish
when it doesn't have a king?
[ALICIA laughs]
The castle! We've reached it!
[FALARION chirps]
[SHUN laughs]
There it is. The capital!
Home at last.
[sighs] What's the point
of maintaining a castle
that doesn't have a master?
I'm sure that Prince Emilio
will return someday.
[MAID 1A] How can you say that?
We don't know how the king died.
[AARON panting]
He-He's come back!
[MAIDS]
Who has?
[AARON]
It's Emilio.
Our prince has finally
returned to the capital!
Ah! It's awesome!
Castles on the surface aren't
even close to this cool!
[EMILIO] You've seen it
once before, remember?
[SHUN] Yeah, but I was too
busy running for my life
to take it all in.
It's unusually
quiet for a castle.
And I can only sense
a few people inside.
[gasps]
Prince Emilio!
Thank goodness you're safe.
Ha!
We are so honored to welcome
you home, Your Highness.
Glad to be back.
How have you been?
It's the same as
always with us.
Alicia, you're back too!
Yeah, about that. Sorry for
leaving without saying 'bye.
[chirps]
[MAID 1B]
Not to worry, my dear.
We're just glad
that you're safe.
Well isn't this nice.
It's a little reunion.
[DEMETRIO]
Heh.
[AARON]
Prince Emilio!
Uh?!
Aaron!
I'm glad you're well.
We've been waiting.
My men and I are at
your service as always.
Thanks, and it's good
to see you, too.
If I may, who have
you brought here?
Uh? These are my comrades.
I trust them with my life.
[gasps]
[MAID 1A] Of the soldiers
that went with the king
on his pilgrimage, less than
half returned after his death.
So few, but they didn't even
suffer a dozen casualties!
That may be true but...
[DEMETRIO]
The rest deserted, right?
They watched their paycheck die.
And knowing the chaos to come,
many decided they'd be
better off as brigands.
[EMILIO grunts]
[SHUN]
Well, screw those guys.
The capital is in a bad way at
the moment so many have left.
That's true for
the castle as well.
The few of us who remained
did so out of hope that
you might return someday.
[AARON] Stop right there! What
do you think you're doing?
[EMILIO, DEMETRIO, SHUN gasp]
[AARON]
On whose behalf are you spying?
If you're curious
about this castle,
I can show you to the dungeons!
This one's rather blusterous.
You need not die.
Submit yourselves
to arrest peacefully,
or we'll have no choice but to
bring you both in through force.
[SOLDIERS grunt]
[MISCHA grunts]
That's enough!
[ALL gasp]
[SOLDIER 17A]
Prince Emilio!
[SHUN]
You two started another fight?
All right, tell me
the truth of it.
These soldiers decided to kill
us for walking down the hall.
[AARON]
These are dangerous times.
So when I find strangers
wandering about where they have
no business, I assume
they're up to no good.
As I said before,
these are allies.
They pose no threat
to our cause.
[AARON]
But, they--
Now sheathe your blades.
As you command. I apologize
for my insubordinate words.
[DEMETRIO]
Hey. You two do the same.
Please understand, my prince.
We only wish to keep you safe.
I realize that. You've
been truly vigilant.
I trust them just
as I trust you.
[AARON]
If I could make a request.
Your comrades aren't known here,
so please have them refrain
from wandering alone,
especially the Zoozians.
We shall take our leave.
[SHUN sighs] Guy kinda
reminds me of a rent-a-cop.
But well done! Look at you,
mediating disputes and what not.
Your princely potential is
really startin' to shine buddy.
"You'll sheath your swords
at once, or else!"
Shut up. You've never
treated me differently
for being a prince before.
Uh!
Don't start.
[JOSEPH]
Where'd everyone go?
[PASCAL] They probably
left when the king died.
Some scientists see what they
do as nothing more than a job.
But what could they have chosen
over the unparalleled potential
for discovery possessed
by this lab?!
Surely there is no higher
joy than true learning!
I'm not incorrect, am I?
Nope. Not for us.
Now, let's sort out that
data we brought from Babel.
[JOSEPH]
Sure!
[RODNEY]
It's about time you showed up.
[PASCAL, JOSEPH gasp]
[laughs] Rodney! I'm glad
to see you made it!
Yeah. Now listen.
I'm not a scientist anymore,
just a simple man with a bakery.
I only showed up to collect
that baking pan you promised.
Well you won't have too much
use for it if the entire country
gets destroyed, now will you?
I suppose you have a point!
Who is he, sir?
Rodney was my senior when
I started research here.
You might not know his name,
but you've seen his work.
I've based much of mine upon it.
[JOSEPH]
His work influenced your own?!
Amazing! Well then it must
have double-inspired mine!
Wow! Again I find
myself face-to-face
with one of the pioneers
of my field!
I'm unworthy of
this blissful day!
Well. You're exactly
like I heard you'd be.
Nice to meet you.
He's excitable, but talented.
Together, we'll break
into research mysterious
as the world's ceiling
and develop instruments
to detect that which
once was fiction!
We will one of these days.
But for now, I'd like to focus
on the subjects of Warp
Particles and Babel.
Oh. Right, sorry.
You've found yourself
quite the protégé.
[laughs]
[DEMETRIO]
Planning to sit?
Uh! Demetrio.
Why'd you follow me?
Because I saw a young man
wander past me looking lost
and thought I'd ask him if
he knew where he was going.
I'm far from lost.
I grew up here.
Right. So what's up?
[EMILIO]
I was thinking.
About how small this
throne really is.
When Delzaine sat in it,
it seemed massive. Regal.
That's the thing
about a throne.
It's meaningless
without the man.
Long as it's empty, it's
nothing but a gilded chair.
[EMILIO]
Then, why is it needed?
[DEMETRIO] This castle,
this city, this country.
All began their
descent into ruin
on the very day this
throne lost its master.
[EMILIO grunts]
[DEMETRIO]
It wasn't Delzaine's army
that held this country together.
It was the union of his
name with this throne.
I wanted them divided, but not
like this. We need a new king.
I know.
When I think about King Alzerm,
or Delzaine for that matter,
they may as well be strangers.
I want to know who
those men really were.
I'm sick of hiding
from the truth.
Fine idea.
A man should know his
predecessors for what they are.
Not the heroes or
monsters a child sees.
I shouldn't have to
help make dinner,
I'm grossed out enough by
this stuff when it's cooked.
Hey! No one cares!
[SHUN]
Hmm?
No one wants to hear
you complain.
'Specially not the people
who're really working.
The servants here need
all the help they can get,
and everyone's pitching in
somehow. So stop the whining.
[FALARION chirps]
[ALICIA]
Besides, you know how it is.
New recruits always get
stuck with the crummy jobs.
It's tradition.
I am not a new recruit!
And even if I was new,
Guidoro and Gradido
are the real rookies.
Wait, that's brilliant,
I should go get 'em!
Huh?
Then again, maybe not. Nope.
Gradido would get
fur everywhere.
And if Guidoro saw that
we were cooking fish...
[MAID 1A] Excuse me Alicia,
do you have a spare moment?
Who are these people you've
brought back with you?
I've never seen such
a mixed assortment.
[ALICIA]
Well. How can I put it?
I know!
They're part of
a volunteer army.
Like if an innocent village gets
attacked by brigands or some
out of control petty lord,
they come in and protect it.
And the Zoozians
are part of this?
[ALICIA]
Mm-hm!
Are you certain? I don't think
they're kind enough to do that.
Uh!
[LOUISE]
Nice evening for a stroll.
[GRADIDO] Yeah. It beats
cramped walls and stale air.
Especially in a place where
I'm clearly not wanted.
[LOUISE] Heh. They are blunt,
aren't they?
Humans can't even make
peace with themselves.
Ha. One of the only
things that unify them
is their disdain for us.
Perhaps when the chaos has
ended, these Endra will see
what we've done for them,
and put their hatred to rest.
It'll depend on their king.
[GRADIDO] Tell me, do you sense
that presence in the woods, too?
Yeah.
[SLIME growls]
[PASCAL exhales]
As I feared...
Everything seems to confirm it.
Life can't be supported
without Warp Particles.
[RODNEY] Bad news. It looks
like the capital's in danger.
What exactly is the threat?
The report was vague,
but apparently there are
creatures of unknown origin
gathering in the forest
near the castle.
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS chattering]
What kind of monsters
are we up against here?
The castle's well-fortified.
[SOLDIER 17C]
Why don't we just wait in there?
Don't give in to craven thought.
It's our sworn duty
as Royal Guardsmen
to defend the capital
with our lives!
[SOLDIER 17B]
I'm willing to fight
when there's a chance
of winning, but--
[SOLDIER 17A]
We don't have enough men to win,
and I don't want
to die for nothing.
So what? Does that
make me a coward?
[gasps]
[DEMETRIO]
If you're really that nervous,
then why don't you leave
this little scrap to us?
[AARON]
You're fighting?
[DEMETRIO]
Hmph.
[AARON, SOLDIER 17A gasping]
[GRADIDO]
As are we.
[SOLDIER 17A]
The Zoozians...
I fail to see why you Zoozians
would risk your lives
to protect us.
You and your men have done well.
It's due to your efforts that
I had a castle to return to.
Now let us repay that favor.
You can't mean to enter
the fray yourself, My Lord.
It's too dangerous,
if you should fall--
Whatever this is. I've fought
against worse, and survived.
[SHUN]
Don't you worry about us!
[AARON gasps]
We might not all look like it,
but we're actually
pretty dang tough.
Emilio does screw up
and almost die a lot,
but that's 'cause he's got me
around to save his dumb ass.
We've both read
your diary, Shun.
You know I've saved
you more often.
[SHUN]
What?! You're bluffing!
[EMILIO] I tend to be hungry
after a good fight.
Why don't you run
back to the kitchen?
You can make yourself
useful there.
Keep flappin' that jaw
and I'll break it someday.
Has it ever occurred to you
that you might be destined
to be a chef?
You could put your Warp
Relic to good use for once.
If you're tryin' to say
I'm no good at fighting,
then step up and prove it!
With pleasure. Only way I'd
lose is if I stabbed myself.
[DEMETRIO] You're fallin'
behind, boys! Hurry it up!
[SLIME groan]
[DEMETRIO grunts]
[yells]
[SLIME groans]
Never seen anything like
these things. What are they?
They're with Ibelda.
Or they're from him at least.
[SHUN]
Kinda crampin' my style.
Why don't you go back to the
castle and dry some clothes?
You can use that
spear as a hanger.
On second thought,
you should probably reconsider
your dream of being a chef.
Vegetables are wily
compared to you.
They'd be tough
to land a hit on.
Shut up!
[SLIME yell]
[BOTH]
Get out of the way!
They're not strong.
But there're too many of them.
--[SLIME yells]
--[gasps]
[GUIDORO grunts]
[MISCHA gasps]
I could've handled that
myself, you know.
If you're as strong as that,
then don't waste my time
by looking like
you're about to die.
Guidoro has a point.
You--!
[SLIME growls]
He does not.
[GUIDORO grunting]
That's his scent.
[IBELDA grunts]
I'm getting much closer.
I feel them writhing in pain.
I taste their screams!
Soon they die! [laughs]
I can't wait to tear into them.
To show them how I've burned!
I'll soothe this wretched scar
with a splash of fresh blood!
Soon...
[BOTH gasp]
[IBELDA yells]
[IBELDA chuckles]
It's Ibelda! What do we do?
[IBELDA] Mm... I hoped I
would get you two alone.
We can take our time now,
have fun. [laughs]
Dammit, no.
[LOUISE gasps]
[ELJUIA gasps]
[DEMETRIO] Shun! Emilio!
[IBELDA] Ha, ha!
Are you ready for your scar?
Is it just me, or is this guy
even crazier than he was before?
[gasps]
[EMILIO]
Move it!
[IBELDA grunting]
[IBELDA laughs, grunts]
[SHUN]
Emilio!
[GUIDORO]
Ibelda!
Get the hell out of my way!
We're not gonna
breakthrough in time!
This doesn't look good.
[yells] No more holding back!
[SHUN grunts]
[IBELDA yelling]
[laughing]
We're in trouble.
Thanks.
[laughing]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIERS yell]
[BOTH gasp]
H'ya! There's glory
to go around still!
If the prince should
march to battle,
then so will his Royal Guard!
[AARON gasping]
[FELIX]
Hmph.
Don't strain yourself.
Heh. If I was afraid to give
my all, I'd have died long ago.
[yells]
[SLIME groans]
So this is what it's like to
fight with Endra on my side.
I don't mind it.
[IBELDA laughing, grunting]
Get back!
[screams]
Got him!
Let's go! [yells]
[EMILIO yells]
[IBELDA]
Huh?
[screams]
[EMILIO] Not deep enough!
[IBELDA]
Again? You've marked me again?
Piece of cake right?
[EMILIO]
Yeah.
--[SOLDIERS cheer]
--[SHUN, EMILIO gasp]
We've done it men,
the capital's safe!
I'm surprised they
made it out alive.
[AARON gasping]
[FELIX] I told you not
to strain yourself.
[AARON]
Uh?
[SOLDIERS laugh]
[SOLDIER 17A]
We did it! We really did it!
[SOLDIER 17B] We protected
the city! We're heroes!
[SOLDIER 17C]
We sent those monsters running!
[AARON]
It would seem I misjudged you.
You have my thanks.
Victory was only achieved
because you took the vanguard.
My men were frightened
to the brink of mutiny.
Till they saw you
march with the prince.
It's fine. Your job is
to protect the castle,
and you carried it out well.
I'd have done the same.
[AARON]
Hmph.
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[SOLDIER 17A]
Lift him up for all to see!
[SOLDIER 17B]
The hero of the battle!
[SOLDIER 17C]
All hail the prince!
[EMILIO]
Uh...
[SOLDIER 17A]
Amazing. He's gotten so strong!
[SOLDIER 17B]
Prince Emilio!
I saw you defeat the enemy
leader! I'm in awe, My Lord!
Check out Emilio's expression.
It's like he thinks
they're gonna eat him.
[ALICIA laughs]
He's managed to inspire faith
in the men around him,
but now he has to
prove he deserves it.
Early on, his light
was hard to see.
But it's slowly brightened
ever since we met him.
This one will go far.
I can't see it. But I hope
you're right anyway.
[EMILIO laughs]
[GRADIDO]
Next episode, "Prisoner."