Look at that!
It's way bigger than I imagined!
[ELJUIA]
Ancient Babylon.
Ages ago, it was a thriving,
prosperous citadel.
These days, legends
are all that remain.
That it's inhabited by devils.
Or that it's a gateway
to the land of the dead.
Sounds familiar.
I've heard stuff like that
about Endora on the surface.
So where is the entrance?
There are four.
Each one of the towers
that you see here contains
an entrance of its own.
However, only one of them
will take you to Babel.
That's assuming this map
from the antique shop
is real and not a
well-executed forgery.
Which tower is it?
Does all that old
writing give any clue?
[ELJUIA]
Yes. I think so.
It mentions Zhurong,
god of fire and protector
of the south gate.
I believe that tower
is the one we want.
[SHUN] We're tryin' to
find some kind of key?
But how the heck are
we supposed to do that
if we don't even know
what it's gonna look like?
Over here!
[DEMETRIO]
Is this it?
That hunk o' rock?
Give it a try.
[SHUN]
Well, that was easy!
[ELJUIA]
This underground path
should take us
directly to Babel.
Sounds good! Let's go!
Calm down.
Mischa.
[DEMETRIO]
If this is the route to Babel,
then there might be
booby traps along the way.
There's nothing there.
Thanks for checking.
I didn't do it for you.
[FELIX exhales]
All right, let's move.
[FELIX]
Look at these footprints.
They're still fresh.
It's Delzaine and his men.
It looks like they got
here before we did.
Let's hurry,
or we'll be too late.
Anyone see a door
around here somewhere?
[FELIX]
No.
[SHUN]
Uh?
[FELIX]
We'll have to climb that wall.
[SHUN]
What? You're kidding, right?
Can't believe I ever wanted
to go rock climbing.
What now?
I know! Hey, Falarion.
Why don't you get big
and fly us up there?
[FALARION squeaks]
[SHUN]
Uh...
It doesn't work like that.
Just thought I'd try.
All right down there?
Yeah. Peachy,
don't worry about me!
[EMILIO gasping]
Emilio!
You're damn heavy.
Man, that was close.
It was. I think you
just saved my life.
What?
I said, "you just
saved my life."
Uh. Whoops. Didn't
mean to do that.
[EMILIO]
Hmph.
[DEMETRIO]
Hey. You two!
Quit screwing around.
Hurry up and climb!
[sighs] It can only
get easier from here.
I don't think we can
relax just yet.
First a giant wall
and now a maze.
I wonder what else we're
gonna have thrown at us.
Should be good to go.
What are we waiting for?
[DEMETRIO] I want to
make something clear.
Whatever may happen here,
I have no intention
of killing Delzaine.
[EMILIO]
What are you saying?
You've built an army. You've
allied with the Zoozians.
True, but the revolution I
desire is a bloodless one.
Yes, I understand that. But--
[DEMETRIO]
But what?
It won't work.
Do you really think Delzaine's
someone you can reason with?
That's not something
I can answer,
because while I know what
he's like as a king,
I don't know what
he's like as a man.
[EMILIO] He's a monster!
What more do you need to know?
Think about it for a second.
His death will mean a better
life for everyone.
Isn't that what you want?
Killing the king
won't magically solve
all the kingdom's problems.
I'm sorry, prince,
that's not how it works.
The army we've gathered exists
for one reason and one reason
only: to force Delzaine
to surrender the throne.
[EMILIO gasping]
[DEMETRIO] Why are you so
desperate to kill the king?
[EMILIO growls]
Fair is fair.
What right do you have
to ask for our help,
if you're not willing to
explain what you're after?
You need to be straight with us.
I want revenge.
Uh?
Delzaine isn't my real father.
He's the man who murdered
my father--the former king.
I seek vengeance for him!
I swore I would
do that long ago!
And now I have the chance.
So it's revenge.
That's actually what
I'm after, too.
Many years ago, a good
Zoozian friend of mine
was killed by a pompous noble.
[EMILIO]
Uh.
[DEMETRIO]
I trained hard so I'd be ready
to exact my revenge
when the time came.
But I grew older, and as I did,
I came to realize that
wasn't the right path.
Nothing would be
solved that way.
Blood cannot be washed
away with more blood.
I could kill the man responsible
but then his family would
come after me in turn,
and the tragic cycle of violence
would only have
been perpetuated.
So now, I seek revenge
against the world.
This revolution is
about avenging those
the world has mistreated.
[EMILIO grunts]
I've asked you once before.
I hope you're ready to
give me your answer.
What happens once
Delzaine is dead?
What do you plan to do?
What will become of
our kingless kingdom?
[EMILIO exhales]
Whatever you plan,
I will open negotiations
with Delzaine.
Don't you dare draw your
sword before I have
the chance to speak with him,
do you understand me?
I'm sorry, but I can't
promise you anything.
[DEMETRIO]
I see.
[ALICIA]
Finally made it!
[DEMETRIO]
Y'know, Your Highness--
[ALL gasp]
Fighting isn't the only
option. Just one of them.
[ELJUIA] I believe we just
have to make our way
through this labyrinth, and then
Babel will be waiting for us.
I'd be surprised if it's
as straightforward as that.
Whatever happens,
I will protect Demetrio.
Well, that's a relief.
Shut up.
Let's move!
[footsteps]
Demetrio and his compatriots
will most likely
have reached Babylon by now.
Do you think they'll make
it safely to Babel itself?
Unless I misjudged him,
I'm sure they will.
We must prepare the
army so we're ready
for whatever happens.
[IGNAUTS chattering]
We will be departing shortly!
Everybody, gather around!
[exhales] Demetrio.
Read the stones.
Listen to the wind.
It's this way.
[ELJUIA] Noxious fumes stir and
fill the air with their stench.
And yet, this is
the only way forward.
[FELIX]
We've come so far.
Whatever it takes, I will see
Demetrio's dreams fulfilled.
That is all that matters.
[MISCHA] Whatever it takes,
I will protect Demetrio.
[ALICIA]
Shun?
[SHUN]
Uh?
Does Emilio seem
a bit off to you?
[SHUN]
Yeah, he kinda does.
[ALICIA] Maybe something to
do with what Demetrio said.
[SHUN]
Yep.
[ALICIA]
You must be excited, huh?
[SHUN]
About what?
Because we've almost
reached Babel,
so that means you get to
go back home to the surface.
[SHUN]
Oh. You're right.
It's strange.
When we first made it to
Babylon, I was so excited.
But then, something
changed. I think...
Hey, Emilio!
Yes, what?
Well, um... We've almost
gotten Babel.
Which means that, y'know, I get
to go home pretty soon.
But I made a promise to you, and
I don't want to go back on it.
So I guess what I'm
trying to say is,
well, I just want to
ask if you know, um--
Would you get to the point?
Are you still trying
to kill your father?
[ELJUIA]
We're through.
[footsteps]
[ELJUIA]
I think that's the entrance.
It should lead us to Babel.
You sure?
Hey, wait!
[EMILIO grunts]
[EMILIO gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[IBELDA] Hello there, children.
Welcome to your funeral.
We've walked into an ambush!
[EMILIO grunting]
Your Highness will
be the first to die.
[roars]
[EMILIO gasping]
[IBELDA growls]
Damn it!
Remember. Don't kill the prince.
I'm just trying to scare them.
This guy again?
Just give up already!
Stand aside! You're not
the one I want to kill!
Too bad, 'cause I sure
wanna kill you!
[GUIDORO, BEOPETLE,
VESTULSE grunt]
Well now, here we are again.
[GUIDORO] We didn't expect
you to arrive so soon.
Unfortunately for you, all it
means is that you'll die sooner.
What a shame.
Actually, I'm all right with it.
I'm not an especially
patient man, you see.
So, the sooner I
beat you, the better.
I'm Guidoro of the Truculent.
Your name means nothing
to me, king's man.
[VESTULSE grunting]
[gasps]
[BEOPETLE grunting]
[DEMETRIO grunting]
[GUIDORO grunting]
[DEMETRIO]
Bring it on!
[GUIDORO grunts]
I still have a score to
settle with the two of you.
[EMILIO, SHUN growl]
I owe you filthy little brats
for the scar you gave me.
And I always make
good on my debts.
I'll rip holes in your flesh,
tear the bones from your bodies,
and leave your rotting
corpses for the birds!
[VESTULSE gasps, screams]
[BEOPETLE, FELIX grunting]
[FELIX grunts]
[BEOPETLE laughs]
[FELIX]
Uh?!
[BEOPETLE groaning]
It's over. Stand down
and surrender.
[GUIDORO growls]
[DEMETRIO gasps]
[IBELDA yells]
[SHUN, EMILIO groan]
Emilio!
[EMILIO grunting]
It really is a shame
that the king forbids us
from killing you.
What?
I don't understand it.
Delzaine's far too generous,
allowing you to live.
Son or not, I'd want you
dead if I were him.
I want you dead anyway.
[IBELDA, EMILIO grunting]
[IBELDA roars]
[EMILIO groans]
[IBELDA roaring]
[EMILIO whimpering]
[SHUN yells]
[IBELDA]
Die!
What's that?
[SHUN gasps]
[EMILIO]
I don't have time for this.
I have to go.
Delzaine is so close!
[EMILIO panting]
Emilio!
[IBELDA]
Not so fast!
Huh?!
That's enough.
--[SHUN] Hey, wait for us!
--[ALICIA] Emilio!
[IBELDA] I'll destroy anyone
who stands in my way. Move!
That is something I won't do.
I may not have the physical
strength to stop you,
but at the very least I should
be able to slow you down.
[IBELDA growls]
[gasps]
You've never been one
to follow orders, Ibelda.
Long time no see, Louise.
What's going on here?
[IBELDA]
You still don't get it, do you?
Despite that pretty face of
hers, she's part Zoozian.
Your little revolution doesn't
mean anything to her.
Why would it? Tell him, Louise.
Wait. What's he talking about?
[LOUISE]
He only speaks the truth.
[gasps]
[LOUISE] Most people are blind
to it. But I am half Zoozian.
Given my appearance, however,
I can live as an Endra.
And for that reason, I've
had it easier than most.
Still. I knew that something
was wrong with the world.
My father was skilled
in medicine.
And my mother was an
excellent seamstress.
Unfortunately, they were never
able to truly use their talents.
The Endras ostracized them.
My father because
he was a Zoozian.
And my mother because
she married a Zoozian.
They were forced into
awful work that no Endras
would ever think about doing.
Even as a child, I could
see the injustice of it.
Yes, that sounds terrible!
But isn't that why you
rallied behind Demetrio
and joined the Ignauts?
Are you really that naïve?
I need money to live,
just like everybody else,
and that's what this is about.
Don't lump me in with you fools.
[LOUISE]
Feeding the Ignauts' movements
to the Truculent
is very lucrative.
The money I earn makes it
possible to support my family.
Revolution is a luxury,
not something everyone
can afford.
Do it, Louise.
[gasps]
Well, this is goodbye, Eljuia.
You poor, pathetic fool.
[DEMETRIO]
Stop!
[LOUISE]
Uh? Demetrio!
[DEMETRIO]
If I had to take a guess.
You'll earn more for killing me.
So why not give it a try.
How do you expect your
revolution to succeed
when you can't even tell
who your allies are?
Shut up, you traitor!
I already knew it was you.
[LOUISE]
What?
I didn't know the motivation,
but I knew there was someone
leaking all of our movements.
[LOUISE]
Uh.
[DEMETRIO]
I wasn't sure at first,
but after the prince joined us,
it became clear that there
was a spy in our midst.
[LOUISE grunts]
[DEMETRIO] That's why I
kept our group so small.
Initially, I didn't
want to believe it.
But when we were ambushed here,
I knew it was true--that you
were the one who betrayed us.
[LOUISE growls, yells]
[LOUISE growls, grunts]
I am not playing
around, Demetrio!
I will kill you if
that's what it takes!
Do what you have
to do. Go on.
But...
[SHUN]
Listen, I can't do it!
Do what?
I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna
help you kill the king.
You know, I had a feeling that's
what you were gonna say.
You get cold feet?
That's not it!
[EMILIO]
Then why back out?
I agree with Demetrio, you
need to talk to him first.
[SHUN]
Come on. Emilio?
[EMILIO] Leave me alone.
You don't understand me at all!
Emilio...
You're right, I don't.
I haven't been through
half as much you have.
But I know revenge
isn't the right choice,
no matter how bad you want it.
[gasps]
Don't do this!
Let go!
[SHUN groans]
You guys!
[footsteps]
[ALICIA]
Come back!
Ow.
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks. But we
have to stop Emilio!
[CASTINA] My Lord.
We will begin the process
of activating the
gate of Babel shortly.
And it will remain open
for a limited time only,
so haste is essential.
Once it opens,
please step this way.
At last.
I have waited for this moment
for so many years now.
[EMILIO]
Delzaine!
[DELZAINE]
Uh?
Emilio.
[DELZAINE] Next episode.
"The Light of Babel."