[SHUN] Now there's a ship
that's not gonna sink
at the first sign of a storm.
Supplies and a grand ship.
That's pretty generous.
We're allies now.
It's in my best interest
to see you're well-provisioned
for your journey.
At any rate,
thanks for all the help.
We're grateful.
[GRADIDO] There's no need
to thank me, friend.
We're all hoping we can get
through this without a fight.
But if your negotiations
with Delzine fall apart
and you need help,
use this to contact us.
A whistle?
[GRADIDO]
Give it a try.
[SHUN blows]
I think it's broken.
It didn't make any sound.
[GRADIDO]
Patience.
Is this one of those
Endora bluebirds?
[GRADIDO] We use birds like
this to carry messages for us.
[SHUN]
An avian telegraph.
Whatever happens, don't
forget we've got your back.
Reach out to us and
we'll be there to help.
Yeah. I know I can
count on you, Gradido.
It's so cold!
I'm freezing my ass off here!
Shut up. Crybaby.
You've gotta be cold.
How come you're not shivering?
I trained my body not to.
That's a neat trick.
I wonder how long
you can keep it up.
Think you'll make it all
the way over the mountain
without shivering?
[SHUN]
We're climbing that?!
I can feel my hands.
Hey. Move over.
You're hogging the fire.
[SHUN] I thought your royal
hide was impervious to cold.
[EMILIO]
Shut up.
[ALICIA]
Scoot over, boys.
We want some of that, too.
[SHUN]
Fine, fine.
What're you doing here, Mischa?
I thought you were basically
glued to Demetrio's side.
You must be tired.
Children usually
go to bed early, right?
I am not a child.
I hate to break it to ya, but...
[COMRADE 9A] It's gonna be
a hell of a morale boost
when the others
find out you're here.
From the sound of it, things
are starting to come together.
Recruitment in the north
is going well too.
We've been able to gather
more troops than anticipated.
[DEMETRIO]
Really? That's great.
Good work!
You've done some amazing
work yourself, Demetrio.
I can't believe you arranged
an alliance with the Zoozians!
I couldn't have done it
without my comrades' help.
[LOUISE] You could've done
it without scaring us all
half to death.
Just thinking about it
makes my stomach hurt.
I agree.
So, what's our next
step going to be?
Our people are ready
whenever you give the word.
We don't want to rush things.
First order of business
is to start negotiations
with the king.
[COMRADE 9A]
Right.
Considering the
size of our force,
Delzaine might prefer to bargain
than risk a costly fight.
Well, they seem
pretty confident.
Who knows, maybe this
whole thing can be settled
without anyone else
having to die.
[EMILIO] At least one man
still has to die.
There's no point negotiating
with someone who won't listen.
What are you saying?
Our only hope of success
is Delzaine's death.
[ALICIA]
Should I go?
[SHUN]
Leave him.
How long's it gonna take
to get to the other side?
There's no way of knowing.
What, you can't even guess?
Weather on the mountain
is very unpredictable.
If a blizzard hits, we'll have
no choice but to wait it out.
Seriously?
[DEMETRIO] Keep moving
or we'll leave you behind.
Okay. I'm going already.
[ALICIA]
Shun!
What's up?
Uh...
I want to talk to you
about last night.
[SHUN]
Oh. You mean Emilio?
[ALICIA]
I'm worried about him.
Do you really think
he'll try to kill Delzaine
when we get to Babylon?
I don't know, but I'm sure
hoping he changes his mind.
Especially since I
promised I'd help him.
Same here. He's so secretive.
I know he doesn't get along
with his father, but why?
[SHUN] I don't know all the
specifics, but he's serious.
He really, truly
wants to kill the guy.
It's like he's obsessed.
He seems to think killing
Delzaine is the only purpose
his life has anymore.
Doesn't he see
that he's lucky?
What do you mean lucky?
[ALICIA] I don't have
a single person left
who I can call my family.
[FALARION squeaks]
But it's different for him.
He could try to make
things better with Delzaine.
This way'll be
worse for everyone.
Yeah, I know.
[ELJUIA] If you don't want to
freeze to death, hurry up!
What's he talking about?
[DEMETRIO]
Time to make camp.
Storm's on its way.
Is this blizzard
ever gonna end?
I'm sick of waiting here.
[EMILIO] Damn it. We're so
close to Delzaine, too.
[SHUN] So, you said you want
to avenge your father, right?
What does that mean?
[EMILIO]
That's none of your business.
Come on, don't be like that.
I'm helping you, remember?
I think that entitles me to a
little bit of background info.
Shun.
[SHUN] It's not like you've
got a whole lot else to do.
Just tell me.
He raised me, but Delzaine
isn't my real father.
When I was a little boy,
I wanted to be just like him.
I thought he was so
strong and so brave.
[SHUN] What happened?
Why do you hate him now?
I found out he killed my father
so he could seize the throne.
I was a fool.
Idolizing him without ever
suspecting what he was.
[SHUN] That explains why
you don't trust anyone.
I guess I can't blame you.
It must've been lonely in the
castle after you found that out.
[EMILIO]
At first I had Pascal.
I felt like he was the
only person I could trust.
But Delzaine banished
him from the castle,
and I was alone again.
[SHUN] Does Pascal know about
your plans for revenge?
[EMILIO]
He doesn't approve.
Hence the fight you got into.
[EMILIO]
Shun. What would you do?
Would you forgive the man
who murdered your father?
[SHUN] I would probably feel
the same way you do.
And I'd want to make
whoever was responsible pay.
[EMILIO]
You see?
But there's still my mother.
I don't think I could bring
myself to hurt her like that.
And what about you?
You've got Pascal and Alicia.
And y'know, I don't
think your real dad
would want you to do it either.
He would.
Why wouldn't he? It's for him.
I'm doing this to avenge him.
[SHUN] You think there's
a parent out there
who wants to see his kid
become a murderer?
'Cause I sure don't.
Miss you, Mom.
I'll be home soon.
[EMILIO]
Father, I--
[EMILIO] His face...
Why can't I see his face?
[SHUN laughs]
Woo! Awesome!
Look at this snow!
[DEMETRIO] That blizzard sure
dumped a bunch of it on us.
[SHUN] Aw, man!
I wish I could go boarding!
[ALICIA]
What's that?
[SHUN]
Snowboarding!
You hitch yourself to a board
and go sliding across the snow.
Yeah? That sounds like fun!
[SHUN] I'm actually
pretty good at it, too.
Snow like this is perfect.
If I had my board with me,
I would tear this mountain up!
[SHUN laughing]
Children.
[LOUISE]
Stop wasting energy.
We've got a lot of hiking ahead.
I'll be fine. Don't worry.
[SHUN]
What the hell is that?
Looks like a dragon
footprint to me.
A dragon?
Yeah.
There used to be dragon nests
all over the Canis mountains.
They were everywhere.
But thanks to
overenthusiastic dragon hunters,
they're almost extinct now.
[FELIX] Seems there's
one nearby, though.
[SHUN]
What? Wait, For real?
Shouldn't we all start
running about now?
[LOUISE] After everything
we've been through,
this is what's
gonna scare you off?
I mean, if you think about it,
you've been traveling with a
mini dragon this whole time.
Huh? What do you mean?
You think Falarion could
be related to dragons?
[FALARION squeaks]
Maybe you'll make some
friends while we're here.
Alicia's got more
guts than Shun,
but that's no big surprise, huh?
[SHUN] Hey!
I'm scared for good reason.
Dragons breathe fire
and eat people.
We'll never beat one
unless we're max level!
Oh, so dragons on
the surface breathe fire?
Well, not exactly.
Up there, dragons are
just fantasy creatures.
I mean, I've never seen one
outside of video games
or movies.
Video games. Movies.
These are places where
your surface dragons live?
That's not what I meant.
The dragons we have in
Endora don't breathe fire.
We'll be fine.
[ELJUIA yelling]
[SHUN]
Eljuia? Eljuia!
[FALARION squeaks]
What's the matter?
[squeaking]
[JOSEPH] It's always
so dark in the archives.
But for a scientist,
darkness represents
the mysterious unknown,
and banishing the darkness
guides us to new
revelations and frontiers!
With this lantern,
I will shed light
on the darkest
secrets of the world!
[PASCAL]
Huh?
[JOSEPH screams]
[whimpering]
The light you're wearing...
That looks like a variable
plasma energy lamp!
Are you who I think you are?
Sorry to bother you;
don't mind me.
Whoa!
[PASCAL] I think your name
was Joseph, wasn't it?
Yes!
[PASCAL]
That lantern of yours...
You make it yourself?
[JOSEPH]
I did!
Building that sort of
thing is a hobby of mine.
It's just a toy compared
to your lamp, though!
No, don't belittle
your accomplishment.
To make a voltaic electrode lamp
at your age is impressive.
[JOSEPH]
I can hardly believe it!
The great Pascal
is praising my work!
You're the whole reason
I became a scientist!
Emulating you is what
drives all my research!
Uh... That's very
nice, young man.
But could you stop
shaking the ladder?
[JOSEPH]
I'm sorry!
You know...
I think your most impressive
work was that ingenious trick
with the Babel design.
It reminded me that
in the right hands,
science can also be an art!
So you know about that, do you?
Were you the one who
figured it out, then?
[JOSEPH]
Yes!
I was so proud to
have discovered it,
I could barely contain
my excitement
when I told the chief about it.
And he was so impressed
with the final design
he insisted on accompanying
the king to Babylon himself.
[PASCAL] When you're the
one who fixed the problem?
[JOSEPH]
I don't mind.
Just getting to spend so many
hours studying the design
was more than I
had ever hoped for!
If I ever see
that chief of yours,
I'm going to thank him
for leaving you behind.
[JOSEPH]
Huh?
[ELJUIA] I need to find
a way back to the others
as quickly as I can.
But I don't think it'll be easy.
[growling noise]
[SHUN] I can't believe
there was a giant cave
buried under the snow!
How does your little guy know
what direction we should go?
It's a talent of his.
He can track the Warp Relics
inside of people.
That's how we found
Emilio and Shun
when they ran away before.
[LOUISE]
Hmm...
He couldn't help us if
Demetrio got lost, then.
Good thing I've got an
excellent sense of direction.
[LOUISE]
Ha!
If you get lost,
I swear I'll come find you.
[LOUISE laughs]
There's nothing to worry about
with Mischa at your side.
[MISCHA]
Don't laugh.
[FALARION squeaks]
What is it, buddy?
What's the matter?
[FALARION squeaks]
[heavy footsteps]
[ICE DRAGON growls]
I'm getting the feeling
we're not welcome here.
A dragon?
Holy crap, look at that thing.
It's huge!
And mad. Really, really mad.
[DEMETRIO]
Run!
What do we do? Fight it?
Fighting a dragon
won't do anything
besides getting us killed.
We don't stand a chance here.
Not without Eljuia.
All we can do now is run.
[SHUN]
Where'd that one come from?
[ALICIA]
We're dead!
Falarion?
Impossible!
Whoa...
Falarion... It's you, right?
[ALICIA]
Where are we?
Hey, what's going on?
You brought us here?
[VOICE]
Alicia.
[SHUN] I didn't think
Falarion could talk!
What's happening?
Do you know?
You okay?
My... dad...
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
Alicia. I've missed you.
So it's you?
It really is you, Father?
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
Yes.
I always hoped I would
speak with you again.
[ALICIA] But why like this,
through Falarion?
Where are you?
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
I no longer have an Endra form.
I'm a spirit now.
What happened?
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
I will tell you everything.
How I came to be
as you see me now...
How I found myself trapped
within a Warp Relic.
[ALICIA'S FATHER] Years ago,
I made my living as a hunter.
I loved adventure
and the thrill of danger.
I willingly risked my
life to hone my skills.
Then one day I met my match.
The monster had me cornered,
and certain death loomed.
I accepted that
the end had come,
but in that moment,
my Warp Relic evolved,
and I defeated the monster.
That encounter reminded
me of an old legend.
That Warp Relics are influenced
by their wielder's spirit,
evolving as a person's passion
and determination increase.
Bent on becoming more powerful,
I became obsessed with
evolving my Warp Relic.
When it evolved twice
and no more,
I assumed that was
the limit of its power
and I had realized
its full potential.
If I had known then
that my obsession
would ultimately be my undoing,
perhaps things would
have turned out differently.
Time passed and I met my wife.
We married, and you
were born, Alicia.
This doesn't make sense.
The father I knew never
hunted any monsters.
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
Because I realized my family
was more important
than a Warp Relic.
I gave up being a hunter
and became a carpenter.
But if family was
so important to you,
then why did you
disappear after Mom died?
I was only ten years old.
I needed you!
[ALICIA'S FATHER] Your mother
was killed by bandits.
I thought it was an accident!
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
No.
Angry at myself for
not protecting her,
and consumed by revenge,
I left my young daughter
and searched for the bandits.
I found them,
and killed them all.
When the last one was dead,
my Warp Relic evolved
without warning.
It pulled me in,
and I was trapped within it.
Impossible...
How could something
like that even happen?
Warp Relics are connected
to their users' emotions.
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
Indeed.
My obsessions with
power and revenge
led to my downfall when
the relentless hatred I felt
triggered its final evolution.
And that's how I became
a living Warp Relic.
What does that mean, exactly?
[ALICIA'S FATHER] A living
Warp Relic belongs to no one.
It is an independent entity that
possesses a will of its own.
Except that Falarion
comes with me wherever I go.
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
Because whatever else I am,
I'm still your father.
My spirit is always sleeping,
lying dormant inside Falarion.
It is only when you are in
grave danger that I can awake
and come to your aid.
[SHUN] Can all living Warp
Relics do what you can?
Make a place like this, I mean?
[ALICIA'S FATHER] No, it is
not normal for any Warp Relic
to have this power.
But my situation is
something of an anomaly,
and so I have abilities
beyond what is usual.
Because of our connection?
Because I'm your daughter?
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
I believe so.
Alicia. I am so sorry for
leaving you when you were young.
But remember,
I am always by your side.
I want you to know that.
[ALICIA sniffles]
This means... I've
never been alone, have I?
[ALICIA'S FATHER]
No, and you never will be.
I'll watch over you forever.
So keep smiling, Alicia.
Yes. I will.
I don't think I fully
understood all that.
I don't either.
[DEMETRIO]
Hey! Snap out of it!
What was that about?
What happened?
[SHUN]
Well, that's a good question.
Sorry, but we don't
really know either.
[ELJUIA] There you are.
Is everyone okay?
Are we okay?
Hey! Behind you!
Don't worry. It's all right.
They don't mean us any harm,
though this one
seems to be injured.
We stumbled upon a nest
belonging to a dragon family.
My fath--Um...
I mean, Falarion told me so.
[FALARION squeaks]
The parents were only trying
to protect their child.
Just like any creature would.
[SHUN] They probably attacked
us thinking we were a group
of dragon hunters.
How could Falarion tell you?
I've never heard him
say a single word.
Sorry, but that's a secret.
[LOUISE] I think the
weather's going to hold.
[DEMETRIO] Good! Let's try to
reach the summit before sunset.
I don't know if
that's gonna happen.
We've still got a whole lot
of ground to cover.
[growling noise]
[FALARION squeaks]
Now this is the way to travel!
Dragons are very fast.
It looks like our journey
just got a lot shorter.
Sweet! Just like a movie!
[MISCHA]
Next episode, "Feelings."