[SHUN]
Nice.
[SHUN lauhgs]
[SHOPKEEP 1A]
Just listen to you!
You're really into
this stuff, huh?
[SHUN]
What are those?
Are they the ones
that just came in?
Yeah.
[SHUN]
Awesome!
What are they called?
This one here's a rutile quartz,
and this beauty over here
is a garden quartz.
Pretty cool, isn't it?
Yeah. Do you mind if
I see what it feels like?
Of course I don't mind.
Well, not if you buy it first.
Aw, man...
I'm just messin' with ya.
Here.
[SHUN]
Whoa.
[SHUN laughs]
[clock chimes]
Better hurry,
you're gonna be late.
Hey! I'll stop by
on the way home.
Hold it for me, will you?
You do know I'm running a shop,
and not a museum...
[SHUN]
Please just hold it!
No need to worry. It'll be here
for you when you come back.
[SHUN laughs]
Cool! Then I'll see you later!
[SHUN] I've been fascinated
by crystals for a long time.
The multi-faceted stones
have been an interest of mine
ever since I was little.
I still remember the feeling
I had when I saw one
for the first time.
Since that day, I've imagined
there were unseen worlds
trapped within each stone.
And if I stared into one long
enough, I'd be sucked right in.
The truth is, I think I was
hoping something like that
might happen.
[SHUN] Seriously, though.
I wish you'd been there!
I've never seen
anything like it.
The inside was awesome.
It's like it contained
a whole other world!
I'm gonna go ahead and guess
that you were looking at
a garden quartz?
You know that
without even seeing it?
Of course.
That's a retired
archeologist for ya!
Have you ever thought about
starting your research up again?
Sometimes.
No need to worry about me,
if that's why
you're holding off.
I'm a big boy.
I can take care of myself.
[MOM]
Yes, I know.
Maybe I will in a year or two.
Guess what I found out today!
What's that?
The Moai statues
on Easter Island--
They're not just heads.
They've got bodies
buried underneath them!
Oh, really?
And they're sitting like this.
[MOM laughs]
Feet down at the
table, please.
Sorry.
[MOM] You looking forward to our
little celebration this weekend?
[SHUN]
I am!
We're gonna give Dad
a great birthday,
and I'll make sure
he actually comes home
to celebrate this year!
[MOM] I've been worrying
that he might forget it again.
You know how he is.
Well, I have been texting
him every day to remind him.
If he doesn't show, I'll just
have to sneak into the office
and drag him back.
That's very brave.
Thanks, Mom, I've got this.
[SHUN]
Okay, see you later!
Remember, today's the day.
Everything's all planned out!
Celebration starts at seven.
You'd better be there!
Don't be late, and don't
even think about forgetting.
Yeah, that oughta do it.
All right, Dad, see you tonight.
[MOM]
Let's go ahead and start.
I'll chat with him
about punctuality later.
For now, why don't we eat?
I'm starving.
I'm sick of this!
I'm gonna get him.
I told you, didn't I?
He's coming home if
I have to bring him myself!
[MOM]
Wait!
[MALE WORKER 1A]
Professor Asanaga?
Sorry to bother you, but
could you take a look at this?
[MR. ASANAGA]
Sure, what's the problem?
[phone vibrating]
[MALE WORKER 1A]
Professor?
Big shock.
[SHUN] Here to speak
with President Asanaga
about a personal matter
of some importance.
[TERMINAL VOICE 1A] Please
take the express elevator
to the highest floor.
[elevator dings]
[SHUN]
Yep. Just what I thought.
Figured he wouldn't be here.
[SHUN]
Oh, cool. What's that?
[SHUN] Huh? I've never seen
one like this before.
[SHUN gasps]
[SHUN yells]
[EMILIO]
My father's enemy.
[DELZAINE]
Emilio.
That afraid of me?
Only a coward attacks
somebody in their sleep.
Who are you to talk?
What right do you of all people
have to call me "coward"?
[DELZAINE]
So angry.
Avenging the former king,
your father?
Useless sentimentality.
You should have planned a coup
and tried to seize the throne.
That would've been
a good way to die.
Shut up!
[EMILIO grunts]
[EMILIO]
This is it!
You'll have to be far stronger
and smarter than that
if you hope to kill me.
[footsteps approaching]
[GUARD 1A] Your Majesty!
Are you all right?
[DELZAINE]
Escort him to the dungeon.
[GUARD 1A]
Yes sir!
[MAID 1A]
Oh, my!
I didn't realize how much
you looked like him.
[EMILIO]
Huh?
The late king, I mean.
It's so sad he's
not with us anymore,
but your eyes are
the same shade as his.
Are they really?
Yes.
Well, I wish they looked
like the new king's instead.
Maybe then I would
be as strong as he is.
Maybe so.
[MAID 1A] It hurts when he
speaks of the new king.
He doesn't know the man
was his father's enemy.
So the poor boy adores him.
[MAID 1B]
Isn't it terrible?
He's just so
innocent and trusting.
It's almost too
painful to watch.
[EMILIO]
I don't understand.
What do they mean?
[EMILIO] Around every throne
swirls a storm of chaos
and discord.
In their desire for power,
even family members
turn on each other.
It's almost common practice.
However, it's one thing
to know about that storm
and another to find
yourself in the heart of it.
[EMILIO]
It's almost time.
Soon I will end your traitorous
life, with my own hands.
[EMILIO]
Dammit!
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
[SHUN yelling]
[SHUN groaning]
That freakin' hurt!
[EMILIO]
Hey!
How did you get in here?
[SHUN]
I have no idea.
What do you mean?
How can you not know?
[SHUN]
Calm down, will ya?
Gimme a sec.
I've got a lot to process.
Who are you and
what are you doing here?
[SHUN]
A prison?
So you're a criminal, then?
I see.
You're from the
surface, aren't you?
The surface of what?
What're you talking about?
You know what, never mind.
Just tell me how
to get out of here.
[EMILIO]
First answer my question.
I want to know how you got here.
[SHUN] I already told you!
I don't know!
One second I was
just suddenly here.
[footsteps approaching]
Not good.
[SHUN]
Why? What's wrong?
The guards are coming.
If they see you, it's over.
What do you mean?
[EMILIO] I mean
they're going to kill you.
Kill me? Why?
[GUARD 1B]
What's going on down here?
[GUARD 1C]
Identify yourself!
[GUARD 1D]
How did you get past us?
[SHUN]
Um... I didn't...
I think this is a
misunderstand--
[GUARD 1B]
I don't want to hear it!
[SHUN]
This is it.
I'm gonna die.
How did this happen?
A Warp Relic?
What are you waiting for?
[SHUN yelling]
No way!
Don't just stand there!
We need to go!
[SHUN]
Hey! Hold on a second!
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[MOM]
Hey, I'm looking for Shun.
Is he with you?
[SHUN]
Can't we just hide out here?
It seems like a
good enough spot to me.
[EMILIO]
That won't work.
Hiding's no good. They'll
find us no matter where we are.
[SHUN]
Seriously?
We have to leave the castle.
That wall doesn't exactly
look very easy to climb.
It's okay. I have a plan.
Shut up and follow me.
You shut up! I'm not gonna
take orders from you.
I'll do things my way.
All right, Excalibur,
give me strength!
[EMILIO] Do you want to
wake up the whole castle?
Put your sword away
and stop shouting!
Uh, what?
How does that work?
You can't even manage that?
You are clueless.
I can see I'll have
a lot to explain.
[SHUN]
About what?
For now, just think of the
most relaxing thing you can.
Then take a deep breath.
Okay, something relaxing.
The interior of
the garden quartz.
It's gone!
How did that happen?
What did you do with it?
Never mind. Come on!
Hey, stop running off
like that, would ya?
[EMILIO]
Here it is.
[SHUN]
That was cool.
How did you know
about that hole?
Did you put it there
yourself or something?
That's right.
Not a bad escape plan.
[IBELDA] And yet,
it's not going to succeed.
[SHUN]
Who's that?
Is he here for us? And what's
going on with his face?
He's a Zoozian.
And loyal to my foster father,
King Delzaine.
A Zoozian? What are
we supposed to do?
Get yours out!
You mean that sword?
Just do it!
But wait,
I don't remember how!
[IBELDA growls]
What are you waiting for?
I'm not sure how
I even made it appear!
[IBELDA growls]
I could use help!
I don't know what to do!
Maybe I should get rid
of the toothless one first.
[IBELDA growls]
[SHUN yells]
[SHUN yelling]
You're gonna pay for that!
[IBELDA growls]
Stop standing around!
Filthy brats! Take this!
[SHUN, EMILIO screaming]
Watch it.
Our objective's not to kill.
The king's orders.
An unfortunate accident.
I didn't plan it.
[SHUN coughing]
Are you all right?
I've been better.
[SHUN]
Shouldn't we hurry?
They'll come after us,
won't they?
The tunnels down here are
only known by a few people.
First that hole in the wall,
now these sewers.
You seem to know a lot of ways
to sneak around this place.
What are you, a thief?
If there is a thief
around here, it's not me.
It's this kingdom's ruler.
King Delzaine.
Huh?
Never mind.
More importantly, how does
someone from the surface
come to have possession
of a Warp Relic?
A Warp Relic?
I can't really answer you if I
don't know what you're asking!
Where are we?
I don't even know that!
We are in Endora.
Endora?
I'm not cut out
for this kinda thing.
[FALARION squeaks]
[SHUN yells]
[EMILIO]
Come on! Keep it together.
[ALICIA] I had a feeling
you'd run away, Emilio.
Looks like I was right.
How did you know
I would be here?
Let's call it woman's intuition,
O Royal Prince.
[FALARION squeaks]
[ALICIA]
This a friend of yours?
No way! I hate this guy!
Did she call you "Prince"?
So who is he?
He's dressed funny.
A visitor. From the surface.
Huh?
[FALARION squeaks]
[SHUN]
Next episode, "Endora."