[SHUN laughing]
[PASCAL]
Coming in for a landing!
I'd recommend holding
onto something.
Why do we need to do that?
[ALL screaming]
[screaming continues]
[PASCAL] Not a bad landing,
if I do say so myself.
For real?
"An adventurer is no stranger
to thrill and danger!"
Is that some sort of saying?
I wrote it!
[chuckles]
Pretty catchy, huh?
[ALICIA]
Hurry, Shun!
You want us to leave you behind?
[PASCAL]
Here we are!
This is your hiding spot?
[FALARION squeaks]
[PASCAL] That's right.
Impressive, isn't it?
No one will ever find us here.
[ALICIA]
But it's just a gigantic hole!
[SHUN yelling]
Awesome rocks.
[ALICIA]
What are you doing back there?
We're going on without you!
[EMILIO]
Hmph.
I'm coming!
[SHUN growling]
Come on, guys!
[SHUN]
Damn you!
What's this?
[ALICIA]
Wow! Nice setup, Pascal!
I take back what I said.
I guess it's more than
just a gigantic hole.
[PASCAL chuckles]
What's the blue thing?
A sleeping bag?
Why would you sleep in a bag?
Well, it's more like a
blanket you travel with.
[ALICIA]
Then, yeah. That's what it is.
Easy there. Don't pull so hard.
You'll rip it if
you're not careful.
[PASCAL]
King Delzaine gave me that.
It's quite a piece of work.
I assume you have
yours with you, too, eh?
[PASCAL]
Here.
So now that we have a moment,
maybe you can tell me
the whole story.
How did the prince come
to be locked in the dungeon
like a criminal?
[PASCAL]
And what about the other boy?
Shun's his name, isn't it?
Tell me more about
how you met him.
Honestly, there's
not much to tell.
I was in the dungeon
and he just appeared.
[PASCAL]
Huh?
[EMILIO]
It was strange.
A ball of light
formed out of nowhere.
[PASCAL]
Indeed?
I looked inside it, and
what I saw there was amazing.
It was a land like
none I've ever known.
[SHUN yelling]
Then, while I was watching,
he came flying out of it.
What I saw...
The strange place
inside the light...
Do you think that
was the surface?
[PASCAL]
That seems likely to me.
[SHUN]
Oh, wow, look at this!
[ALICIA]
Hey! What are you up to?
Uh, just taking a look around.
Does everyone from
the surface love rocks?
[SHUN]
No, not everyone.
My mom was an
archaeologist, though.
An archaeologist? What's that?
[SHUN] They study human history
by looking at material remains.
[ALICIA]
Oh, cool.
[SHUN] My mom would freak out
if she was here right now.
She'd love this!
You know, I've heard of
the Hollow Earth Theory,
and I always thought
it was freakin' crazy.
Now it turns out
it was true all along!
Except I thought this place
was supposed to be called
Shambhala or something.
Well, it's not.
I've never heard it called
anything but Endora.
Hey, is it really true that the
people where you're from
don't know about us?
Yeah, no one has a clue
there's a world down here.
From the time
we're little kids,
we're taught that
the Earth is solid.
What would happen if
word got out about Endora?
Would they get all excited
and call it a great discovery?
Would there be
a big celebration?
Uh, somehow I doubt it.
So we don't know about you,
but you know about us.
Have you thought of going to the
surface to see it for yourself?
Huh? No, not really.
[PASCAL]
Endora and the surface.
Two worlds that
must remain separate.
Even if they have
knowledge of each other,
they cannot be
allowed to intertwine.
Ancient texts warn us
that contact between the two
will bring no benefit
and may do great harm.
In the mythology of the surface,
the underworld is hell.
It is the world of the dead.
That idea was spread to
keep surface dwellers away,
and so there must have
been a good reason for it.
But not all of those
from above feared our land.
Some from the surface
ventured into Endora.
They returned to tell of
an underground paradise
called Shambhala.
Babylon was the city that
connected Endora to the surface.
Within it was Babel, the
portal between the two worlds.
Several decades ago,
Babel was restored.
But not for long.
Shortly after its restoration,
Babel ceased functioning.
King Delzaine hopes to
bring it to life once more,
and so he called me
and other scholars
to the Royal Laboratory
to help him determine
how it might be accomplished.
I came, but...
You were against his plan.
Yeah.
So you left.
Because you didn't want to help
the king get Babel working.
[PASCAL]
Pretty much, yes.
This is something
I truly believe.
Endora and the surface
must not have contact.
[EMILIO]
How can you be so sure?
I just am.
I know it in my bones.
[EMILIO]
Intuition?
That doesn't seem
terribly scientific to me.
Being a great scientist
requires more than
intelligence and dedication.
Intuition plays
an important role.
There is only so much that
can be proven using logic.
But science is all about logic.
[PASCAL laughs]
It's all right. I wouldn't
expect a young pup like you
to understand this stuff.
Shut up, old man.
The king is a fiend.
You can oppose him if you want,
but in the end he isn't going
to listen to anyone but himself.
A fiend, eh? Don't you think
that's going a bit far?
He is your father, after all.
[EMILIO]
He's not my father.
He's the man who raised you,
so I'd say that makes
him close enough.
[PASCAL] Let me guess...
You argued and he grounded you.
[laughs]
Is that why you
were in the dungeon?
You planned your
escape thoroughly.
Why were you so sure
they'd be coming for you?
I tampered a bit with the
master diagram to make sure
they would have a
difficult time completing
the restoration of Babel.
I knew they'd figure out
what I had done eventually.
The new researcher must be
pretty good to have done it
this fast, though.
[laughs]
That bastard succeeded?
Take it easy.
If they know what you did,
does that mean they're
on their way to restore Babel?
I suspect they are.
If I can, I would like
to arrive before they do.
That's the only way I can
do what needs to be done.
Once we get to Babylon,
we'll return Shun
to the surface,
and then I plan to destroy
Babel once and for all.
Also, whenever you feel
like talking, I'll be ready.
Talking?
About the real reason you
were locked up in the dungeon.
[PASCAL]
Now come on.
We should go inside.
You can keep the blade.
[EMILIO]
Hey, Pascal!
Do you envy the researcher
who replaced you in the lab?
Do you hate him?
[PASCAL]
No, why would I?
I can pursue my
research anywhere.
In fact, I actually
enjoy it more now
that I have some freedom.
[EMILIO]
I can't let him get involved.
It's too dangerous.
[EMILIO grunting]
Perhaps we should play
a different game, Highness.
Did I ask for your opinion?
[MAID 1A]
No, Highness.
[EMILIO yells]
[MAID 1B] It's like
he's a different person.
I don't recognize him!
[MAID 1A]
He's out of control.
We must find a way to stop this!
[PASCAL]
Those poor puppets.
What did they do to deserve
such harsh punishment?
[EMILIO]
Huh?
You dare speak to me?
A good day to you,
too, Your Highness.
Might I say how happy
I am to meet you?
[EMILIO yells]
[PASCAL laughing]
[EMILIO]
You jerk!
Forgive my little joke.
There isn't much time for humor
in the Royal Laboratory,
so I must take it
where I can get it.
If you'll allow me to introduce
myself, my name's Pascal,
and from today on I will be
in charge of your education.
I admit that I'm not
very skilled with a sword.
Nevertheless, I think you'll
find that I have a number
of tricks up my sleeve.
Should you wish it,
I would be happy
to teach them to you.
I think the two of us could
get along well, Your Highness.
[PASCAL chuckles]
[EMILIO laughs]
[PASCAL]
Please listen to me!
Majesty!
Sire, please, if you would
listen to me for a moment,
that's all I ask.
I beg you!
Restoring Babel may be more
dangerous than you realize.
It'll mean disaster for Endora!
Please, don't do it!
What makes you so
certain it's dangerous?
My intuition as a scientist.
And what use does a man of
science have for intuition?
Please, sire!
When I give orders,
I expect them to be followed.
I make no exceptions.
If you will not obey me,
I have no use for your service.
[PASCAL]
Wait, you don't understand!
[GUARD 3A]
Let's go. You've been dismissed.
[PASCAL]
Majesty!
[EMILIO growls]
That bastard.
He takes everything
I care about away from me.
[GUARD CAPTAIN 2A]
It was uncanny.
Almost as if he knew we were
coming and had prepared for it.
[DELZAINE]
So, he outsmarted you then.
That doesn't surprise me.
[GUARD CAPTAIN 2A]
Apologies, my lord.
I've ordered the
second and third platoons
to continue searching without
rest until he is found.
[DELZAINE]
No need for that.
[GUARD CAPTAIN 2A]
But your orders...
[GUIDORO] Will be carried out
by someone more competent.
Now run along and
find a wall to defend.
We can take care of it.
[GUARD CAPTAIN 2A]
What?
King's orders.
Get out of here, soldier.
Ugh...
I still don't get why you
used the grunts for this job.
Seems like a waste of time.
Better to have us go
after Pascal straight off.
[DELZAINE] I wouldn't
be so sure about that.
You are only to
assess the situation.
Your orders are not to kill.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
We will make sure to
remember our duty. Right?
Yep.
Agreed.
[VESTULSE grunts]
[PASCAL] I don't know how
long we're gonna be stuck
on this mountain.
It could be a while.
It's best to be prepared,
so I'm going to
get us some supplies.
I'll head down to the
nearby village on foot.
[PASCAL] It only makes sense
to wear a disguise.
I'm a wanted man.
Right. Good idea.
You look great.
Yeah? I'm not so sure.
I think he looks more
conspicuous like this.
[ALICIA]
Well, uh, maybe.
I have taken some precautions
to ensure our safety here.
The herbs I scattered
along our trail
should distract their
wolves from our scent.
But that doesn't mean you
shouldn't be careful,
understand?
Don't leave the cave
if you can help it.
[SHUN]
Right.
If I'm not back here
by tomorrow night,
then your best bet is to
look for me at the village.
It's called Megido.
[PASCAL] However, you'll want to
be extremely careful about it.
'Kay. Sounds good.
[PASCAL]
All right.
Wish me luck.
Good luck!
We'll see you later.
[ALICIA] Well, I might as well
go out and get us some water.
[SHUN]
Okay.
You want a hand with that?
[ALICIA]
Nah, I'll be fine.
[SHUN]
You sure?
What do you want?
I think we should talk.
How sweet!
Did Pascal tell you
to make nice?
It would be great if
you stopped bickering.
You know, for the record,
none of it's my fault.
He's the one who's
always snapping at me
for no apparent reason.
[ALICIA] Sure, whatever
you wanna tell yourself.
See you guys in a bit.
Try not to kill each other!
[SHUN] All right, what do
you want to talk about?
[EMILIO]
Sit down and I'll tell you.
I'm sick of being bossed around.
Why don't you sit down first?
Okay, what do you want?
Are you ready
to shut up and listen?
You ready to stop being an ass?
We need to get out of here.
Why do we have to leave?
[EMILIO] You want to go back
to your home, don't you?
Uh, yeah.
[EMILIO] Well, then...
I'm going to need your help.
My help with what?
Bringing down King
Delzaine once and for all.
Huh? Bringing down a king?
Find somebody else to help you.
I'm sure not gonna do it.
No way!
[EMILIO] I thought that
you wanted to go home.
Of course I do, but I'll
bet that I can find a way
to get there without
overthrowing a monarch.
Delzaine is likely on
his way to Babylon right now.
If he gets there before us,
you might never be able
to go back to the surface.
But if we defeat him, you'll
get to see your mother again.
[SHUN]
Come on, this is crazy.
You realize that, don't you?
It's not. I have a plan.
Is it a good one?
Yeah. But to make it work,
I'll need help.
Fine, I'm in.
So, where do we start?
We make our move tonight.
We'll leave when
Alicia's asleep.
[SHUN] Hold on.
We aren't bringing her with us?
No, and she can't
know about this.
She'll only interfere.
[ALICIA]
Anybody thirsty?
Hey! How's it goin'?
[ALICIA]
You're acting weird.
What's happening?
Huh? Nothing! Really!
You sound stupid!
You're giving it away!
Hey! I'm doing the best I can!
Do better!
She'll know we're
up to something.
I can handle this.
Really, what's up with you guys?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
[ALICIA]
Whatever.
Anyway, Emilio, shouldn't we
be making ourselves useful
by gathering
mushrooms or something?
Yes! A splendid idea!
And you think I'm
going to give us away?
Listen to yourself!
Shut up!
What has gotten into you two?
[EMILIO] You know...
we could use some meat.
I think I'll go hunting.
You're coming with me.
Hey, let me go! Geez!
Would it kill you
to ask first?
You're a terrible actor.
It's your fault
if she figures us out!
Yeah, well, you're not
gonna win any awards yourself.
I summon thee!
"I summon thee"?
It pumps me up;
gets me ready to fight.
What's so wrong about that?
[EMILIO] He may look stupid,
but he's getting better
with his Warp Relic.
[boar snorting]
Here's the plan.
You're going to
chase it over this way.
I'll stay hidden here.
When it's close, I'll
ambush it and finish it off.
[SHUN]
Yeah, sure.
There a problem?
I don't care if
you take the easy role.
[EMILIO] Idiot! Killing the
beast is both more difficult
and more dangerous.
I should've left you
back at the cave.
[SHUN]
Man, you sure whine a lot.
I'm going.
[yelling]
[SHUN yells]
Coming your way!
Drive him a little bit further.
Now!
[gasps]
I'm dead!
[boar squealing]
[SHUN yells]
How do ya like me now?
[SHUN]
You didn't think I could do it!
Sounds like they're back!
[EMILIO] You only got the
kill because I set you up.
[SHUN]
Oh yeah?
And what about that
part where you fell over?
--Was that just an act?
--How was the hunting?
[EMILIO]
You're making things up now?
That's just sad.
Wow, you got a big one!
[EMILIO]
Uh... Yeah.
No, I got it while Prince Priss
was tripping over his feet.
Not true!
I'm the one who got
the kill, and you know it.
Shut up!
You shut up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I will not shut up!
Both of you need to shut up!
[ALICIA]
All right. Dinner is served.
Please tell me we're
not having more boar stew.
What's the matter
with boar stew?
Don't get me wrong,
I'm sure you're a good cook.
It's just...
This boar is kind of an
acquired taste, that's all.
[ALICIA]
So acquire it.
--Come on, dig in!
--[EMILIO] I'm famished!
[SHUN]
Gimme a sec.
Mmm. Pretty tasty.
It's either this or starve, huh?
Are those tears?
You like it that much?
Hey... Wake up. Let's go.
Take this. Try to keep up.
[EMILIO gasps]
Good, we found them.
Found what, exactly?
What we're looking for.
[SHUN]
Could you be more specific?
[EMILIO]
Reinforcements.
[SHUN]
Reinforcements?
You've lost me.
What do you mean?
[FELIX]
Make no sudden movements.
[LOUISE]
I'm surprised.
A member of the royal
family should know better
than to set foot
in our territory.
You and your pal are dead men.
Everyone knows this territory
belongs to the Ignauts.
So there are only two
reasons you'd come here.
You're either astonishingly
brave or astonishingly stupid.
I'm curious to find out
which of the two it is.
[SHUN] Hey, you said
something about reinforcements?
Should we be
expecting some company?
Well? Where are
these reinforcements?
One move and I'll kill you.
They're right here, Shun.
These are our reinforcements.
Huh?
Congrats. You have my attention.
[ALICIA]
Next episode, "Ignauts."
[FALARION squeaks]