[RADICAL MAN 16A] People of
Endora, heed my warning!
Delzaine, our trusted king has
sinned gravely against us!
I shall tell you of the truth
he sought to conceal!
This country stares
up at the face of calamity!
The Warp Particles that sustain
our world have been leaving it.
You have heard that
the king was killed.
I tell you that he
has abandoned us!
Rather than aid his people,
he's left for the surface!
Make your peace, my friends.
Soon Adamas will lose its light,
and we shall be
left in darkness.
[WOMAN 16A]
The plants will wither.
The livestock will starve.
[MAN 16A]
We have no future without light.
[MAN 16B] This can't be real.
I don't wanna die!
[GRADIDO] So the king was
killed by his own man.
[DEMETRIO]
That's right.
This Ibelda must be quite
formidable to have been
able to wreak so
much havoc alone.
And I can tell you in
no uncertain terms
we'll have to deal with
him again before long.
But for now, the defense of
your island takes priority.
How's it look?
[GRADIDO] Well, the enemy
has five ships with cannon.
They're awaiting our surrender.
[DEMETRIO]
Hopefully we can get to them
before they decide
to land troops.
The men I sent should
help prevent that.
[GRADIDO] I'm trying not to
think of what could happen
in my absence.
The Ignauts' help has been
invaluable, we won't forget.
Truly, your people have
done more than enough
to earn our support.
[door opens]
[GRADIDO]
Huh?
[SHUN]
So what?
Did you figure out what
the deal is with Babel?
[PASCAL]
All will be revealed in time.
[SHUN]
Whatever you say.
Joseph and I have
gleaned some more
information regarding
Babel. Care to hear?
I certainly would.
[JOSEPH] Here it is. The
ultimate Babel diagram!
[SHUN] Yeah that picture's
pretty useless to me.
Uh!
[SHUN] Ugh. Just walk
me through it, will ya?
As everybody knows, Babel is
essentially an ancient tunnel.
A gateway that allows
individuals to travel freely
between Endora and the surface.
Ah...
[PASCAL] The work I've done on
Babel has only ever dealt with
the parts of it that
are within Endora.
We can find nothing
wrong with those parts.
So it stands to reason
that there's a blockage
near the surface.
The data we got from
the gauges we repaired
only served to confirm the utter
flawlessness of Pascal's design.
So, while Ibelda did experience
particle disassembly,
he obviously was not
transported to the surface.
[PASCAL] I believe that event
is what corrupted him.
Babel's essentially
a dead end alley now.
Who can say what Ibelda
found in there?
Could be that their
particles were blended.
And to think, I wanted to
be the first one through.
[PASCAL]
There's also one more thing
to be learned from all this.
[SHUN, ALICIA gasp]
There is? What is it?
It pertains to the
disappearing Warp Particles.
Wait, what are those
things again? I forget.
Just the energy that gives form
and life to all of Endora.
Oh, that rings a bell.
It's the stuff that lets us
use our Warp Relics, right?
[PASCAL]
Precisely.
And we've discovered that
for reasons unknown,
these particles have diminished
in number over recent years.
At one point, Joseph and I
hypothesized that the phenomenon
was somehow connected to
the reconstruction of Babel.
But if we look at the
example of Ibelda,
it seems that most particles
entering Babel
do eventually come out.
So essentially, we're back
to the drawing board.
[DEMETRIO]
Rough news.
And the particles are
still disappearing
after Babel's failure?
[DEMETRIO] If so, it's
starting to look like
Eljuia's apocalypse
might happen after all.
[SHUN, ALICIA gasp]
It makes sense.
When he said that Endora
was losing the forces
that keep it whole,
he must've meant
the Warp Particles.
[chirps]
He saw an apocalypse?
The message I received
this morning
makes a lot more sense now.
Message?
It came from an ally
in the capital.
Seems your psychic
friend's not the only one
who thinks the world
might be ending.
A radical group is
preaching the same there--
inciting the people to panic.
Not good!
The darker the rumor,
the faster it will spread.
And people who feel like
they have nothing to lose
are prone to riot. This rumor
has effectively crippled
the Royal Guard's ability
to keep the peace.
As if there wasn't enough
chaos before all this.
Spreading panic about
the end of the world
is the last thing this
divided country needs.
There's yet another fire
that needs putting out.
Emilio...
[JOSEPH]
We can do it!
The first step is to put
everything we have
into ascertaining why
the Warp Particles are
beginning to disappear.
Once we know that, we should
be able to make a plan
and assuage the fears
of the people.
I agree.
[PASCAL]
No need to worry, Shun.
This is our priority,
but I also fully intend to help
you find a way back home.
[SHUN]
Oh, no, forget about me.
I don't wanna distract
you from figuring out
how to save your country.
Sounds good!
I'm sure that Pascal
can handle both.
Of course! It'd be foolish to
underestimate the greatest
scientist in Endora.
Him or his sidekick!
They might be weird,
but they're also geniuses.
[FALARION chirps]
And here I thought we had
a difficult road ahead
of us before.
At least we know it
won't be boring.
You have a remarkable
knack for optimism.
[crash]
Stop. Please.
There's no reason why we
shouldn't all get along here!
[LOUISE] And that's what I've
been trying to do, but Guidoro.
[MISCHA] What could Demetrio
have been thinking?
[FELIX] Recruiting the
head of the Truculent.
Well he's never
led us astray before!
[GUIDORO] I had one reason
for joining this group
and it wasn't to gain approval.
If you don't want me here,
then make me leave.
Will you please stop
trying to provoke them?
[GUIDORO]
Hmph.
I know he's rough
around the edges,
but Guidoro's really a good guy.
[MISCHA]
Says you!
[LOUISE]
Huh?
Traitor! Enough!
[ELJUIA gasping]
I'll need you to tell Demetrio
that they fell into the sea.
[ELJUIA]
You're only joking. Aren't you?
This is why
short-tempered children
shouldn't have Warp Relics.
[MISCHA]
I am not a child!
Let's do this. Now.
[GUIDORO grunting]
[gasps]
[GUIDORO grunts]
[FELIX growls]
Guidoro, there's
no need for this!
Would everyone please
just calm down?!
[GUIDORO gasps]
[GRADIDO]
That's enough!
[GRADIDO] I humbly request that
you entrust these two to me.
[MISCHA, FELIX gasp]
I'm not an object to be given.
What are you talking
about, Gradido?
Demetrio!
What is it?
If you'll have me, I would
like to join the Ignauts.
I have looked after only myself
and my own for too long.
We cannot protect
this country divided.
Once the island is safe,
I'll join you in your fight.
[gasps] We would be
honored to have you.
Good. There's no erasing
the crimes you've committed.
[GUIDORO, LOUISE gasp]
That said,
I know the feeling of regret far
too well myself to condemn you.
[BOTH gasp]
When a Zoozian asks
to be entrusted with
a life that was forfeit,
we put both our honor and our
very own lives on the faith
that they can be redeemed.
I ask that you set your
hatred aside if you can.
[DEMETRIO]
Think you two better let it go.
It'd be a travesty to
let a speech that good
fall on deaf ears. It would also
be ignoring an order. Got it?
[gasps]
We can't fight this.
You don't give me orders. Hmph!
I can see I would be hard
pressed to find a better ally.
Thanks for the help.
My blade is yours.
Whatever the outcome may be,
I fight with you.
[explosion]
[gasps]
[ZOOZIAN 16A]
We're under attack!
[ZOOZIAN 8B]
Prepare for battle!
Loose formation, got it? We'll
close ranks when they land!
This island would be so
much easier to colonize
if I was able to
use the populace.
For the best though.
These Zoozians have been free
too long to make decent slaves.
[GUARD 16A groans]
[gasps] What? To arms!
That may well be the first thing
you've said about my people
that's actually true.
[LORD 14A] How did you
get onto my ship?!
If you leave now,
we'll let you return to your own
miserable lands in one piece.
Keep on making offers like that
and folks'll think
you've gotten soft.
No. You're clearly bluffing.
What can two men do
against all these troops?
[DEMETRIO] Actually, I think
you'd be surprised.
[LORD 14A gasps]
[LORD 14A]
What?!
[GUARDS groan]
[LOUISE yells]
[GUARDS groaning]
[LORD 14A whimpering]
That's that.
[IGNAUTS, ZOOZIANS cheer]
And don't come back, either!
[DEMETRIO] We'll make our
way south to the capital,
halting riots as we go.
Rather than leave
the north as is.
I'd like for you Zoozians
to stabilize it.
[GRADIDO]
Happy to.
We're already familiar with the
region. We can move out soon.
Look, I know this is a tough
request given the situation,
but--
You're asking us to minimize
bloodshed. I understand.
[DEMETRIO]
You know me well.
[GRADIDO]
Heh. If we don't show respect
for the sanctity of life,
then who else will?
Doesn't this seem a
little unfair to you?
I mean our first mission
was to do laundry.
No, but... there might
be an actual problem.
[SHUN]
Uh?
[CRUM]
Father! You're finally home!
[GRADIDO]
Yes. Good to be back.
Is that your kid?
He called him father.
[CRUM]
Uh?
Hey! He's your spitting image.
[whimpers]
Uh.
[GRADIDO] Crum, you don't
need to fear these people,
they're my trusted comrades.
Now say hello.
[SHUN]
Sorry for makin' him cry.
Well, we never were the
best at first impressions.
I mean yeah, you and Emilio
are pretty scary to look at.
That's quite hard to hear from
a man with the face of an ass.
Why don't you look me in
the eyes and say that?!
Because looking
at you is painful.
Oh, I'll show you
somethin' painful!
[CRUM wails]
[SHUN, EMILIO gasp]
He's terrified. Well done.
[EMILIO, SHUN gasp]
[CRUM]
Father, I-I can't!
Whoa there. If you want
to be strong someday,
you can't keep
crying like an infant.
I won't always be here
to take care of you.
[SHUN]
What's up?
Does it have to do with that
problem you mentioned?
I wanted to explain in private
to avoid causing any offense.
[DEMETRIO]
Explain away.
It's about sending Gradido
to unite the north.
He's a fine leader,
but it won't go smoothly.
[SHUN]
Huh?
What makes you think that?
[EMILIO] Too many Endra have
been raised to view Zoozians
as savages, scarcely
better than animals.
In an atmosphere this
fearful and chaotic,
regardless of intentions, a
Zoozian peacekeeping force
might very well be seen
as an invading army.
All it took was one
look at Ibelda,
and I was convinced
they were all savages.
[CRUM laughs]
[EMILIO] It's easy to form
prejudice from appearance
and rumors.
It's unfortunate but not
something we can ignore.
It's why I think our safest
option would be to send out
a coalition of both
Zoozians and Endra.
That really makes sense.
[EMILIO]
Yeah?
Though it's a pretty big
surprise to hear that from a guy
who used to say that peace
between us and the Zoozians
was totally impossible.
[EMILIO]
Shut up, you fool.
[SHUN]
What? You know it's true.
[EMILIO]
Be quiet!
Think I might just
steal your plan.
I'd like to help that father get
back to his son however I can.
[EMILIO]
Good. Please do.
[SHUN]
...I see... the light.
[ALICIA] Ahh. Wow,
I really needed this.
I can't remember the last
time I felt so relaxed.
[FALARION chirps]
Yes, it's important to take
time to cleanse and recharge.
I can second that,
even if we might be getting
close to the end of the world.
[MISCHA gasps, growls]
If the Warp Particles
keep disappearing,
I guess that places like
this'll disappear, too.
[chirps]
I wonder sometimes,
is there any way that
someone like me can help?
[LOUISE]
One way comes to mind.
Huh?
Something that no one
can do but you.
Are you serious?
What is it? Tell me!
[LOUISE]
It's obvious.
You need to get
married to Emilio
and help him restore
that Royal bloodline!
[ALICIA]
Ah!
That really is something
that no one's capable of
aside from Alicia.
No. What? Why me?!
Because you're the only girl
that the prince even looks at.
And the color of your heart
changes when you're near him.
I've seen it.
[FALARION chirps]
No it doesn't!
Or if it does that's just
because we've known
each other since we were kids!
That's all there is to it.
We're friends, okay?
Plus, it's super obvious
that he isn't into me.
I mean, he ditches me
every chance he gets.
Yeah, he does kinda do that.
So maybe you're more of
a nagging mother figure.
[yelps, groans]
[ELJUIA]
Louise.
What, I'm only
telling her straight.
[ALICIA] Honestly, I don't
even know how I feel.
[ELJUIA, LOUISE gasp]
I'm usually too busy worrying
to think about that stuff.
Like when I found out that
it was possible for him
to get trapped inside of a Warp
Relic. It scared me to death.
[chirps]
[ELJUIA]
There's no need to worry.
I haven't sensed even
the tiniest bit of hatred
from him recently.
[LOUISE] Why not talk to
him about how you feel?
[ALICIA]
Emilio has too much on his mind.
He's still trying to figure out
his purpose in the world.
And honestly, I need do
the same thing myself.
If I'm still at his side after
we've done what we need to do,
things will be more clear.
I'll know for sure how I feel.
And at that point,
I don't think I'll be scared
to tell him anymore.
I understand completely.
[ALICIA, LOUISE]
Uh?
You just described the way
I feel about Demetrio.
[MISCHA]
Huh?
[ELJUIA sighs]
[LOUISE] Oh, I didn't
know it was like that.
Romantic rival.
[ELJUIA]
I've been quiet for so long,
but I do want to tell him what
it means for our purposes
to be intertwined.
Someday, right?
Uh. Hey, worth a shot.
Hope you don't screw it up.
[laughs]
[CRUM cries]
[SHUN] If you want to be strong,
don't cry like a baby.
[gasps]
Hey.
[SHUN] I get it. If Gradido
goes on this mission,
you won't get to see
him for a while.
[CRUM]
Mm...
[EMILIO gasps]
[SHUN, CRUM]
Uh?!
[laughs]
Your dad know where you are?
Won't he be worried
that you're gone?
[CRUM] Please don't tell him
I was still crying, okay?
Sure. But you should tell
him what you're feeling.
[CRUM] I can't. I have
to act like I'm strong,
or he won't feel right
about leaving me behind.
Tough break.
[EMILIO]
It's not weak to have feelings.
[CRUM, SHUN]
Mm?
Your father isn't trying
to help us save the world
because he's a leader
among the Zoozians.
He's about to embark on
a very dangerous mission,
and he's doing it
because he has you.
So tell him if you're sad.
Tell him how much you
love him and admire him.
[CRUM] He'll just be ashamed
that I'm so weak.
Come on now,
I think you owe your old man a
little more credit than that.
[EMILIO]
He's your father. Talk to him.
[CRUM]
Okay.
[SHUN] Looks like I got
more fish than you!
[EMILIO]
Shut up.
[SHUN, CRUM laugh]
[GRADIDO] Crum! Home before
dusk. You know the rule.
[CRUM]
Sorry, lost track of time!
Our bad.
[GRADIDO]
Uh?
[CRUM]
Father.
I wanted to say... to say
good luck with your mission!
[gasps]
[CRUM] Mother and I will
take care of things
while you're gone. But...
we'll still miss you. So...
...come back as soon
as you can, 'kay?
[GRADIDO]
Spoken well, my son.
Uh!
For the sake of you and
your mother I'll do my best
to finish this task
as swiftly as possible.
As you are my pride, so
shall I strive to be yours.
[CRUM gasps, laughing]
[SHUN snoring]
[PASCAL]
It's time to call it a night.
We're heading out
early tomorrow.
I can't sleep.
I know just how you feel.
But if we try to rush things,
we'll only make mistakes.
[JOSEPH]
Right.
[knocking]
[PASCAL] Emilio? What brings
you here so late?
[EMILIO]
I need to ask you something.
I'll excuse myself.
[EMILIO]
Don't. You're welcome to stay.
[JOSEPH]
Mm?
So, Delzaine. You mentioned
there was something
you wanted to
ask him, right?
You're wishing you'd known
more about the king.
[EMILIO]
Yeah.
I see. Understand that
this is just a guess,
but I suspect that the king
may have been trying
to meet someone who
lives on the surface.
[EMILIO gasps]
This would have begun
a number of years
before your biological
father, Alzerm Langheim,
came into the throne.
Prince Delzaine was tasked
with unifying the north.
And I have reason to believe
that this is when
he found Babel.
Is there any chance it was
still operational at the time?
[PASCAL]
It's possible.
He was the first person to
reach it since the fall.
Do you have any idea what
he might've seen there?
Afraid not. I've scoured
the Royal Library
for documents from
that campaign,
but I came up empty-handed.
King Alzerm likely knew.
I don't suppose you
might remember anything
he said about it.
[EMILIO] No. I wouldn't
even know his face.
Unfortunately, Emilio
was only two years old
at the time of his
father's death.
None of us remember
being that young.
There are so many questions
that I should've asked before.
That's all right, it's never too
late to start learning more.
The Royal Library has a
great number of records
concerning King Alzerm.
But it's King Delzaine who I
really want to know more about.
I think I owe it to him and
myself to find out the truth.
If you'd like, I'd be
happy to start you off
by telling you everything
I know about him.
My experience is limited,
but I'd like to help as well.
Thank you both.
[GRADIDO] Well, I'll be sure to
report my progress up north.
Looking forward to it.
[GRADIDO] I know that it was you
who suggested that some Ignauts
accompany us.
You have my gratitude.
You're welcome.
[CRUM]
Father!
When I grow up,
I'm gonna join the
Ignauts just like you!
And when I do,
the two of us can travel
the world together!
I like that plan!
Tell ya what, kid,
you can be a future Ignaut
starting right this second!
[CRUM]
Thank you! Uh...
Uh. My name is Shun.
Shun Asanaga. And his name is...
...Emilio. Emilio Langheim.
I'm the son of King Delzaine.
[ALL gasp]
That explains a few things.
[GRADIDO]
It seems Demetrio found it.
Wait, what do you mean?
The flame of hope
for this country.
For now, it's small,
and flickering.
But soon it will be a
great beacon for all.
I thought you'd given up
on your fancy royal status.
I was planning to.
But if there's still good
that I can do with it,
I won't turn my back
on the people out there
who need my help.
[SHUN]
I see.
[CRUM]
Next Episode, "Return."