MAN: It’s over.
We have nowhere left to go.
This is it.
Our road ends here.
‐It was a foolish decision,
doomed from the start.
‐This is the end.
We must turn back.
‐There is a way.
Have faith.
I know that we will find it.
‐But, Princess‐‐
‐You mustn’t give up!
‐Princess.
‐[guffaws]
Princess Gale, this
is as far as you go!
Now, halt.
‐Don’t tell us, this
storm is your doing!
‐[snickers]
‐Behind you, Princess!
Look out!
‐Hah!
‐Give up, Princess!
Fall to your knees
and bow before me.
PRINCESS: I will never give up.
As long as I live, I
will gather my strength
and forge a path for
others to follow!
‐The princess!
‐Her Rainbow Chakra is ablaze!
‐My brothers, we must light
the flames of our chakra, too!
‐Right!
‐[inaudible].
‐Aaah!
Now!
[music playing]
‐[giggles]
All right!
Princess Gale, you rule!
Good sticks it to evil
once again! [laughs]
‐Hey!
What the heck do you think
you’re doing up there?
‐Hup, yike! [groans]
What’s the big idea?
‐Don’t play stupid with me.
You snuck in here
without paying,
you lousy little freeloader!
‐Wait, you’ve got it all wrong!
ere just getting
a little training in
while we watch the movie!
‐Training for what?
‐We have tickets.
‐Are you ninja from
the Leaf Village?
‐You bet we are!
You’re looking at
the next Hokage.
A super ninja, pal.
Oh, yeah, Naruto Uzumaki,
live and in the flesh!
[angry shouting]
‐Come, let’s push on.
Our fate lies
beyond the rainbow!
[angry shouting]
‐[sighs]
Kakashi Sensei is late.
‐So what else is new?
‐Aw, man, that
movie was so cool.
I don’t think I’ve ever been
so blown away in my life.
‐I don’t want to hear it!
You made such a
racket in there, we
didn’t get to see
the whole thing!
[sighs]
I wish we could’ve
stayed a little longer.
I could have watched
that handsome Omiji
who played Tsukekuro
all day long.
Oh, of course, he doesn’t
compare to you, Sasuke.
‐Man, I don’t know where you
got your taste in men, Sakura.
But it stinks.
‐Come again!
‐I’m sorry.
What was the question?
‐Humph!
‐[sighs]
I wonder if there’s
anyone like her out there.
I mean, where’s my
Princess Gale, you know?
If I could fight for a girl
like that, I’d be on cloud nine.
‐Whatever.
It was just a movie.
‐[sighs]
‐It’s funny.
I wonder why Kakashi
Sensei told us
we had to go see this
movie before he’d
give us our mission.
‐[gasps]
‐No way!
Was that the princess?
‐Ugh!
Agh!
[grunting]
‐Why, you!
‐Ugh!
‐Huh?
‐Rrrarh!
‐Heyah!
‐Don’t let her get away!
‐Not to worry, Princess Gale!
I could protect you!
‐Aah!
‐Get her!
‐Ugh!
‐Stay on her!
Don’t move!
We got you now.
‐We’ve finally captured her.
‐Feisty one.
Ow!
‐[grunts]
‐Huh?
‐Who are you?
Huh?
Ugh!
MAN: Where did the princess go?
‐Oh!
‐Oh, captain?
[men gasping]
‐Aarh!
MAN: Oh, dear.
‐Huh?
Kakashi Sensei!
‐What are you guys doing?
‐Killing time.
‐Gee, huh, I’m really
sorry about this.
‐Huh?
‐This is the gentleman who
hired us for our mission today.
NARUTO: Are you hurt, Princess?
This is crazy!
So, like, you are the real
Princess Gale, aren’t you?
I don’t believe this!
I just saw your
movie, and it totally
blew me out of the water!
"I’ll never give up."
It was so awesome.
First, you had me cheering.
Then I was crying.
Aakk!
Ugh!
I mean, after seeing the
movie, the feeling just
started to well up
inside of me! [panting]
I’ll never give up either!
I’m going to work my butt off.
And one day, I’ll
be the next Hokage.
Oh, right, you
probably don’t know.
The Hokage is the
highest ranking ninja
in the Hidden Leaf
Village where I come from.
Hey, lady, you really know
how to handle a horse.
No wonder you’re the Land
of Fire’s number 1 actress.
Ha!
And I know talent when I see it!
Ngeeh.
Hey, lady, aren’t we
going a little fast?
Look out!
‐Ugh!
‐Huh?
It’s Princess Gale!
‐Oh, wow!
It is her.
‐Princess Gale!
Princess Gale!
‐Oh, look, my name
isn’t Princess Gale, OK?
‐Yeah, that’s right!
You’re the actress
Yukie Fujikaze.
I’m your biggest fan!
Can I have your autograph?
‐Yeah, me, too!
‐Here, please!
orget it, guys.
I don’t do autographs.
‐Please.
‐Come on.
‐Hey, what about me?
Can I get one?
‐Please!
‐You’re a movie star!
Aw, come on!
Sign autograph!
‐Enough, already!
‐[groans]
‐I mean, come on!
What’s so special about
getting my autograph, huh?
You’re just going to
shove it in some drawer
and forget about it.
l it’s good for
is collecting dust.
They’re just a waste of time!
They’re useless!
What a joke!
‐Ugh, that was so rude.
Not like she is in
the movies, is she?
‐Her success went
right to her head.
KAKASHI: Our mission is to guard
Yukie Fujikaze, the actress
best known for her
role as Princess Gale.
‐Guard?
‐Well, maybe not guard
her so much as escort her.
‐The next Princess Gale
movie is the first one
that we’re shooting abroad.
And, uh, I don’t need to
tell you our leading lady
is a bit of a diva.
‐Sorry, uh, I do apologize.
‐I’ll tell you, these
Leaf Ninja are impressive.
Uh, they took care of those
stuntmen‐turned‐bodyguards
we hired was child’s play.
And those are some big fellows.
‐Oh, well, uh, thank you.
‐Oh, wow!
Look at those cliffs.
MAN: Uh, that’s the Rainbow
Glacier in the Land of Snow.
‐Hey, you played
the part of Buriken!
‐That’s where we’re all going to
shoot the scenes for the film’s
big climactic ending.
‐You’re Hidero!
You play Shishimaru!
‐Land of Snow?
Long way to go to shoot
some scene for a movie.
‐Yukie Fujikaze’s manager,
Sandayu, over here
recommended it.
Apparently, he tells
us this Rainbow Glacier
turns seven different colors
during the springtime.
‐No, that’s just an old legend.
The truth is, there isn’t any
spring in the Land of Snow.
‐What?
Not ever?
‐Does that mean it’s
winter all year long?
‐Mm‐hm.
You got it.
‐Kakashi, wasn’t it?
From what I hear, this
won’t be your first time
in the Land of Snow.
Is that true?
‐That was a long time ago.
MAN: They say that it’s
a very poor nation, too.
‐Huh!
[gasps]
‐You‐‐ you, Tsukekuro,
Omiji, you were great!
‐Actually, the story
is their former lord
had a thing for gadgets.
The guy squandered
everything the clan
had on mountains of
useless doodads and gizmos.
‐Yeah, well, I just hope
they’ve got central heating.
I’m not really all that
cut out for the cold.
‐Maybe you should run
for the hills, too.
Just like Yukie.
‐Oh, hey, come on, you guys.
That’s not even funny.
[men laughing]
‐So does that mean, Yukie‐‐ I
mean, she not always like this,
is she?
‐Hm.
‐Kind of, yeah.
Poor Yukie, huh, she wouldn’t
even know the meaning of words
like "dreams" or "aspirations."
DIRECTOR: But she’s never
been one to neglect her work.
I don’t know anything
about her personal life,
and I don’t need to.
As long as she’s giving her
all when the camera’s rolling,
I won’t have any complaints.
Say what you will, that
woman is a born actress.
ASST.
DIRECTOR: He’s right.
And anyway, she only
started running from the set
after she heard we were
going to the Land of Snow.
‐[panting]
Aah!
Ugh!
[panting]
Oh, all right, already.
‐[giggles]
Awesome!
‐What’s your name?
‐Naruto Uzumaki!
‐"Naruto Uzumaki," right?
‐Uh‐huh.
‐Gosh, lady, you
sure do smell nice.
[sighs]
Ow!
What the heck was that?
‐Pepper spray for stalkers.
‐Ugh!
‐You freak.
I mean, you’ve
got to be kidding.
Who would want to go
to the Land of Snow?
[piano music]
‐Ugh!
I finally found
you, Princess Gale!
‐I told you, kid.
I’m not the princess
of anything, OK?
‐What?
You think I don’t know that!
Do you really think you could
trample all over a kid’s dreams
like this?
I don’t care how high and
mighty an actress you are!
I’ll never forgive you!
‐An actress?
High and mighty?
[guffaws]
That’s a riot.
I can’t think of a worse
job than being an actor.
Only the lowest of the low would
want in on this profession.
‐Huh?
‐We’re handed lies
put down on paper
and breathe life into them.
It’s ridiculous.
‐Um, are you drunk?
‐Shut up!
Go bug someone else!
‐[gasps]
Ms. Yukie!
Our boat to the Land of
Snow is about to sail.
Please, we don’t have much time.
‐No, thank you.
‐Huh?
‐I’m bowing out as a princess.
‐Huh!
‐You, but‐‐
‐What on earth are
you talking about?
‐Ah, don’t worry.
It happens all the time, OK?
I mean, lead actresses
change from sequel to sequel.
Come on, directors change
every five minutes.
‐That’s enough!
You listen to me!
There is nobody on
this whole planet
who can play Princess Gale
other than you‐‐ nobody!
Besides, if you pull out
this late in the game,
you’ll never work in
this business again.
Do you understand me?
‐So?
Who cares?
‐Ms. Yukie?
MAN: Well, guess
there’s no other choice.
‐Huh?
MAN: So she has the hex crystal.
Splendid.
‐This film actress
Yukie, there’s
no question she’s
really Koyuki Kazahana.
‐I can hardly wait.
It was worth the 10 years
it took to find her.
‐Hah, taking care
of one little girl
ought to be a piece of cake.
‐She’s not alone.
She has Kakashi
Hatake as a bodyguard.
‐Kakashi Hatake?
‐Well, this should
be interesting.
In the end, it will
be a clash of fate.
[soft music]
‐Father?
Where are you?
Father?
‐Koyuki, come here.
Good.
Now, stand there.
What do you see?
‐I see you and me.
FATHER: If you look closely,
you’ll see the future.
‐[groans]
[knocks on door]
[door opens]
Uh.
SANDAYU: Ms. Yukie,
are you awake?
‐Sandayu, could you
get me some water?
My head won’t stop spinning.
This is going to
sound crazy, but it
feels like the room is swaying.
‐Actually, it’s, uh,
not all that crazy.
‐Huh?
[running footsteps]
Huh!
You have got to be kidding me!
‐I don’t know.
I don’t think I can
deal with this lady.
‐What are you talking
about, Naruto?
You have to deal with it.
You’ve just sworn
to protect her.
Come on, this is an
important mission.
‐Mission?
KAKASHI: Yes, an A‐rank one.
‐This is an A‐rank mission?
‐I don’t really
think our babysitting
a little pampered actress
will be all that difficult.
‐That’s not true, Sasuke.
Big celebrities are
targeted all the time.
Besides, it’s hard to
predict who’s after them.
Just be on your guard.
‐Light is set.
‐OK, we have speed!
‐Camera is rolling.
‐All right, folks!
I want to get this
on the first take!
ALL: Right!
‐OK, scene 23, cut 6, take 1.
‐And action!
‐Oh.
‐Huh?
‐Shishimaru!
Stay with me!
‐Uhh, I’m sorry.
I failed you, Princess.
Forgive me, I beg you.
‐How can you say that?
Without you at
our side, we never
would have found the courage
we needed to make it this far.
‐I only wish I’d seen beyond
the rainbow with you, Princess.
Uhh.
‐Shishimaru!
‐Whoa.
‐She’s amazing!
‐I don’t even feel like I’m
looking at the same person
anymore.
‐Oh, yes.
That’s Yukie for you.
‐Huh?
‐When the camera starts
to roll, she comes alive.
There isn’t another
actress on earth
who can match her brilliance.
‐[sobs]
Hold on a second, guys.
[men groan]
‐What’s wrong?
‐Sandayu, bring me my
drops so I can cry.
‐Right, right.
Oh, coming, coming.
I have the drops, the drops.
OK.
Now, let’s see.
Uh, one there and‐‐
‐‐‐and now, the other one.
‐Ready?
‐Ugh, they’re spilling over.
Come on, let’s do this.
h, for Pete’s sake!
Start with the close‐up.
‐Right.
ASST.
DIRECTOR: OK.
Scene 23, cut 6, take 2.
Action!
YUKIE: Shishimaru!
ASST.
DIRECTOR: Mr. Makino,
we’ve got a problem!
‐What is that?
‐When I woke up this morning,
I found this waiting for me.
We can’t get through!
What are we going to do?
‐This is it!
We’re changing everything!
‐Ha‐aah?
‐You moron!
Look, we’re standing on
the perfect spot to shoot!
It’s practically
begging us to film here!
‐Uh, ha‐aah?
‐Cherish this moment.
The movie gods are
smiling down on us!
Everyone, prepare to embark!
MAN: All right, yeah.
Clear this up.
Clear the area.
WOMAN: Let’s try and get
some last looks in, people.
[both yawning]
ASST.
DIRECTOR: All right,
people, we’re going to roll.
Stand by!
‐OK, scene 36, cut 22.
Action!
‐[guffaws]
So, Princess, you’ve arrived!
Well done!
‐It’s you, Mao!
‐Princess, please, stay back!
‐We’ll take care of him for you.
‐Did you honestly believe
these meager fools
would be a match
for me, Princess?
[growls]
Huh?
Is this in the scene?
‐Hey!
What do you think you’re doing?
‐Everyone, get back!
‐Welcome, friends,
to the Land of Snow.
‐You!
‐Greetings, Princess Koyuki.
I do hope you’re still carrying
around the hex crystal.
‐[gasps]
Princess Koyuki?
Huh!
‐You’re as good as
they say, Kakashi.
Unfortunately, it’s
not good enough.
KAKASHI: Naruto, Sasuke, Sakura.
‐Huh?
‐You three protect Yukie.
Everyone, get back to the ship!
‐Wha‐‐
‐Huh?
‐Fubuki, Mizore, I’ll
leave the princess to you.
‐Very well, then.
‐It’s been a long time, Kakashi.
I hope you’re not planning
to run like the last time.
‐Nadare Roga.
‐I don’t know what’s
in the script,
but I’ve always wanted
to be in the movies!
Don’t you worry, Princess.
Naruto Uzumaki’s
here to save you!
‐Ice Style, Tsubame Blizzard!
‐Fire Style, Fireball Jutsu!
‐Huh!
‐Hurry!
Back to the ship, everyone!
Yukie!
‐Princess!
‐Sandayu, what are you‐‐
‐Ice Prison!
‐Aaah!
‐Naruto!
Water Style, Water Dragon Jutsu!
[growls]
‐Keep that camera rolling
even if it kills you!
Show the resolve of
the cinematographer!
‐Sensei!
There’s something strange
about their armor!
‐Yeah, I know.
Just be careful.
It’s Chakra Armor created by the
ninja here in the Land of Snow.
‐Chakra Armor?
‐But it’s definitely a lot
stronger than it used to be.
NADARE: So you remember.
The armor increases the
chakra within the body,
strengthening a handful
of the more useful jutsu.
A chakra barrier gathers
around us as well,
able to deflect the
chakra of our adversaries.
As a result, ninjutsu and
genjutsu are rendered useless.
‐[grunts]
‐Ice Style, Dragon versus Tiger!
‐Water Style, Water Dragon!
‐Out of the way, little girl!
Ugh!
You little brat!
MIZORE (VOICEOVER):
What is this chakra?
‐Ugh!
‐Yukie, hurry!
Get to the ship already!
‐Princess!
‐Father!
‐What are you doing?
Get out of here!
‐Princess, please, we
must get to the ship.
‐No.
‐You’ve got to go now!
Your life is‐‐
‐I don’t care if I die!
I won’t‐‐ I won’t come
back to the Land of Snow!
‐We don’t have
time for this, OK?
Ugh!
Aagh!
Sakura!
‐Princess!
‐Huh?
‐Don’t be in such a hurry.
We’re not finished yet.
‐Ice Style, White Whale Jutsu!
[whale call]
‐OK, that was impressive.
Now, it’s my turn.
Naruto, get everyone
out of here!
Ice Style, White Whale Jutsu!
‐Still copying my moves, huh?
You’re not going to
settle this by doing that.
‐Settle the fight?
That’s not really what I was
aiming for at the moment.
‐What?
[whale call]
‐And cut!
‐Man, I hope we got all of that.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): 10 years.
It’s been a long time.
[door opens]
‐The ship pulled into
dock a moment ago.
KAKASHI: You’ve known all
along, Sandayu, haven’t you?
SANDAYU: Yes.
KAKASHI: Didn’t you
ever consider the risks
of what might happen if she
came back to the Land of Snow?
SANDAYU: You’re
right, of course.
But this was the
only way I could
think to get the
princess to return home.
‐[laughs]
Come on, Sandayu.
You don’t have to
keep calling her that.
I mean, she’s only royalty
on the big screen, right?
It’s not like she’s
really a princess.
SANDAYU: Actually, she is.
‐Huh?
‐Yukie Fujikaze
is only an alias.
We’re guarding Princess Koyuki
Kazahana, the rightful heir
to the Land of Snow’s throne.
[both gasp]
‐I first met her
a long time ago.
I was her aide when she was
still just a little girl.
I don’t blame her
for not remembering.
It was years ago.
‐So does that mean you are also
from the Land of Snow, Sandayu?
‐That’s right.
I served the princess’s
father, the former leader
of the clan, Lord
Sosetsu Kazahana.
The Land of Snow is
not a large nation,
but‐‐ but served as
a haven of peace.
Lord Sosetsu, he absolutely
adored the princess.
Ahh, those were idyllic times.
But 10 years ago, on that cursed
day, Lord Sosetsu’s younger
brother Doto hired a
group of Snow ninja
and instigated a revolt.
It was a coup d’etat.
The magnificent Kazahana
Castle burned to the ground.
And I feared the princess
had perished as well.
‐Keep your face hidden.
They could still find us!
SANDAYU (VOICEOVER): There was
no way we could defeat them.
We had to keep running.
We had to get away.
‐Father!
‐The day that I discovered
our beloved princess was still
alive, I was practically
beside myself with joy.
[sobs]
She was‐‐ she was alive
after all those years.
[sobs]
‐I should have died back then.
‐Huh?
‐[grunts]
‐You mustn’t say such
things, Princess.
We feared the worst.
You can’t imagine how
frantic we all were.
We never stopped
praying for your life.
PRINCESS: I’m alive,
but my heart is dead.
‐[gasps]
‐After that day, any tears
I had left all dried up.
‐And that’s how I came to be
the manager for Yukie Fujikaze.
I have bided my time
waiting for the day when
I could escort her
back to Land of Snow.
‐Uh!
So what are you saying then?
That all of this time
you’ve just been using us?
‐Uh, I apologize
for deceiving you.
But it was for the sake of
the Land of Snow’s people.
Princess Koyuki, confront Doto
and assume your rightful place
as the leader of our land!
I will sacrifice my
life without hesitation
in order to protect you.
I beg you!
Take up arms and
lead your people!
YUKIE: I don’t think so.
‐Huh?
‐You’ve got to be kidding.
‐But what about
what your people?
‐I couldn’t care
less about them.
Just forget it!
‐But, Princess.
‐Will you give it up already?
Don’t be dumb!
It doesn’t matter what you do.
You will never get
rid of Doto, OK?
‐[sobs]
‐So what?
He should just give up?
Quit being so heartless!
Can’t you see this poor man
has given his entire life
to the realization
of this dream?
You keep insulting
him like that,
and you’ll be dealing
with me, lady!
‐Naruto, I‐‐
‐Humph.
‐As long as there is
hope, one may dream.
And with those dreams,
the future comes.
I like it.
It’s the perfect theme for
our new Princess Gale movie.
‐Uh!
‐But, Mr. Makino,
you’re not really
going to continue filming with
everything that’s happened,
are you?
‐I told you.
The movie is evolving.
‐[gasps]
‐Just think about it.
How often do you get
the chance to make
a movie with a real princess?
We’re looking at the
chance of a lifetime here.
‐You’re right.
Think of the buzz.
Even the "Making
of" will be a hit!
We’re sitting on a
surefire blockbuster!
‐Hey!
KAKASHI: Unfortunately, there’s
only one course of action.
Now that Doto is on her trail,
running isn’t an option.
We have to fight.
It’s our only chance of
getting through this.
‐[gasps]
‐Kakashi Sensei.
‐OK!
Time to continue the mission!
The princess returns
to the Land of Snow
and shows that
creep who is boss!
YUKIE: Stop joking around!
‐Huh?
‐The movies aren’t
like real life.
There is no such thing as a
happy ending in this world!
‐Of course, there is!
If you’re willing
to fight for it!
‐Uh!
‐Normally, under
these circumstances,
I’d head back to the village
for a little bit of help.
But‐‐
‐It’s a waste of time.
We’re as fine as we can be.
It’s nothing we can’t handle.
‐[sobs]
Oh, thank you all.
‐That’s it then.
We’re going ahead
with this picture!
‐And you can bet this one
will have a happy ending!
NARUTO: That’s right!
[group sighing]
‐Hm?
SANDAYU: Our hideout
is not far from here.
It’s just beyond this cave.
Once we’ve finished
our shooting here,
we’ll pass through
to the other side.
Then my people can rest easier.
They’ll finally have
their princess back.
NARUTO: Boy, I can’t
see the exit at all.
‐Once upon a time, a
railroad ran through here.
‐Railroad?
‐It’s covered over with
pillars of ice by now.
But dig far enough
down, and you’ll
find the tracks
laying there still.
‐Ahh.
‐All right, people, let’s
get this show on the road.
‐Ugh, Mr. Makino, we’ve
got a bit of a problem.
‐What is it now?
‐Yukie has up and
vanished again!
‐What?
‐Huh?
‐[panting]
YUKIE (VOICEOVER): Forget it.
Absolutely not.
‐Fan out and look for her.
Radio in if she turns up.
TEAM: Got it!
‐[panting]
Ugh!
Aah!
SOSETSU (VOICEOVER): If you look
closely, you’ll see the future.
‐I can’t see anything.
‐Of course, you can.
When the spring comes, you will.
‐The spring?
YUKIE (VOICEOVER):
You’re a liar, Father.
There is no spring in this land.
[rustling]
‐Jeez, how many
times are you going
to run away from your fate?
Come on, everyone’s waiting.
‐Why?
Why do you always
come looking for me?
‐Because it’s my mission.
It doesn’t matter
how much you hate it,
I’ll keep coming after you.
Just try to hide.
I’m going to find you.
‐You can drag me back if you
like, but all I’m going to do
is act for the camera.
And that’s it, you got me?
‐Hah!
[train horn]
Huh?
[crowd gasping]
‐What is that?
‐Huh?
It’s chakra.
There’s chakra running through
the rails, melting the ice.
[gasps]
It must be him.
Everyone hurry!
You must get out of here!
You can’t let them find you!
’s not safe!
‐Sandayu?
‐Where are you going?
‐[panting]
‐It’s a train.
‐Train?
What do you mean a train?
[train horn]
‐Oh, that train!
‐It’s gaining on us!
‐Not, if I can help it!
‐We’ll never make it!
‐I’m not giving up, lady!
‐There’s no way you can do this!
‐Will you just shut up already?
‐Ah!
Uh, this is going
to be pointless!
Just give up!
NARUTO: This isn’t over!
‐[gasps]
‐I’ll be dead before
I’m going to give up,
even if you’re ready to call it
quits, I’m not giving up ever!
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on!
[music playing]
‐Ugh!
[gasping]
[laughing]
MAN (ON PA SYSTEM): It’s
been a long time, Koyuki.
‐[gasps]
I knew it.
It’s Doto.
‐It’s been 10 years.
Come now, don’t be shy.
Let’s get a look at that face.
Hm.
‐There you have it, men!
Our beloved Princess Koyuki
is here to watch over us!
With her at our side,
victory is ours!
[warriors cheer]
‐What the‐‐
‐Sandayu?
‐Hear me, Doto.
We’ve waited a long time for
this day of reckoning to come.
Sandayu Asama and
50 loyal warriors
stand before you to
avenge our great fallen
leader, Lord Sosetsu.
On this day, you
will breathe no more!
[warriors cheer]
‐Hm, I thought you destroyed
the last of the insurgents.
‐My apologies.
We’ll get rid of
them immediately.
‐No.
With men such as
these, there is little
that they can understand
other than total annihilation.
[warriors yelling]
[snickers]
[guffaws]
‐[gasping]
‐Sandayu.
‐Huh?
[train horn]
‐Hold it, Sasuke!
Don’t be hasty.
‐Awful.
PRINCESS: That’s what
comes of never giving up.
If they hadn’t stood up to Doto,
then none of this bloodshed
would have happened.
‐My Princess, please forgive me,
I‐‐ I never should have gotten
you involved in all of this.
[heaves]
It’s just that every
single one of us here,
we are able to keep believing
in spite of everything
because we knew you are alive.
When you were little,
uhh, and even now,
you have always been‐‐ [groans]
‐‐just as I, your loyal
Sandayu, believed, so, too, must
you believe in yourself.
You have always been our
purest hope, Princess.
Please do not waste
your tears on me.
Ahh.
‐You are such a fool, Sandayu.
I can’t cry.
You have my eye drops.
Are you all satisfied?
Let’s go back.
If you stay here, your
lives will be in jeopardy.
Let’s go home already.
NARUTO: Go home to where?
I thought this was
your home, wasn’t it?
What the heck do you
need to go back to?
Your place is here!
Now, face Doto and put
your house in order!
‐You know absolutely nothing.
Spring doesn’t come
to this country.
Our tears have frozen
over and our hearts
hardened with the cold.
SAKURA: But aren’t you the
only one with the power
to change that?
I mean, at least‐‐
at least, that’s
what Sandayu believed
anyway, wasn’t it?
‐I’ve had enough
of this nonsense.
‐Hey, hold on a minute!
‐Leave me alone already!
[motor whirs]
‐Huh?
‐Careful!
‐Sakura, where’s Naruto?
‐Huh?
Oh, you’re kidding
me, he didn’t!
‐Ugh, come on!
You didn’t think I’d let
you get away that easy?
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
DOTO: You’ve grown
quite beautiful, Koyuki.
Tell me, little princess, do you
have the hex crystal with you?
‐Yes.
‐Good.
It is the sole remaining
link to the Kazahana Clan
and the key to
opening its treasure.
‐The key to what?
‐When I wrested this land
from your father’s hands,
the Kazahana Clan’s
resources were all but gone.
I knew Sosetsu must have
hidden his riches somewhere.
I searched for a long time,
and finally, I found it.
It is hidden deep within
the Rainbow Glacier.
There’s a keyhole
there which can only
be opened by the hex crystal.
Once I have possession
over the Kazahana fortune,
our country can attain
military superiority
over the five great nations!
NARUTO: Not going to happen!
‐[gasps]
You!
‐How on earth did
you get in here?
‐Heh, never
underestimate a ninja!
[gasps]
Ugh!
‐My apologies.
As you can see, the little
runt was kind of a handful.
‐Well, he knows the
Multi Shadow Clone jutsu.
‐I’ll tell you, I don’t
know who this brat is,
but his level of chakra
is nothing to sniff at.
‐What do you think?
Maybe we should try that
contraption out on him?
‐Hm.
He would make for an
interesting test subject.
[zapping]
‐Ugh!
Aargh!
Agh!
‐What is that?
‐We’re cleansing
him of his chakra.
That device will
absorb any that’s
stored in his body and bind
it within a powerful barrier.
Once it’s been activated, it
cannot be broken or destroyed,
no matter what.
‐My strength, it’s
starting to slip away.
‐Not looking like much of
a ninja anymore, are you?
Just a little kid.
‐You dirty‐‐ ugh.
‐Now then, I’ll take the hex
crystal, if you don’t mind.
‐Oh.
Hm?
What is this?
‐Ugh!
‐This isn’t a game!
Do you think I don’t
know this is a fake?
‐No, that’s impossible!
[gasps]
Kakashi Hatake.
‐What?
‐Makes sense.
Kakashi’s a shrewd one.
I wouldn’t put it past him
to pull a bait‐and‐switch.
‐Don’t even worry about it.
We’ll have him
rounded up in no time.
DOTO: That won’t be necessary.
‐Huh?
‐Ugh!
‐Why even bother.
The man will show up
on his own soon enough.
Until then, we
just have to wait.
[chuckles]
[glass shatters]
[chains rattling]
‐Ugh!
[grunts]
[screams]
Ugh!
Uh!
[gasps]
Terrific.
I don’t have any power.
Guess I should have spent
a little more time working
on the Escape Jutsu.
[grunts]
These guys don’t know
who they’re dealing with.
A real ninja finds a way,
with or without his chakra.
[gate opens]
Hm?
[gate squeaks]
[thuds]
‐Serves you right.
‐Yeah?
You, too.
‐I know.
NARUTO: "No spring."
You said there was no spring.
What did you mean?
‐"You’ll see when
spring comes, Koyuki,"
my father used to say that.
YOUNG KOYUKI: Father,
what is spring?
SOSETSU: Oh, that’s right.
You’ve never felt
spring, have you, Koyuki?
‐Mm‐mm.
SOSETSU: Koyuki,
close your eyes.
Try to imagine yourself
surround with flowers.
There now, isn’t it beautiful?
Now, run through it
as fast as you can.
Well?
It makes you feel all warm
and happy, doesn’t it?
‐Mm‐hm.
‐That is spring.
And if you never give up, if
you believe in the future,
then spring is sure to come.
‐But this land has no spring.
My father died.
I fled from the Land of Snow.
And I stopped believing.
I was always running,
always lying to people.
But mostly, I was
just lying to myself.
My life has been
one big charade.
Becoming an actress was
about the only thing
I was cut out for in this world.
[chains rattling]
‐[grunts]
‐That’s not going to
change anything, you know?
‐[grunts]
Aah!
‐Told you.
In the end, all you
can do is give up.
‐[sighs]
I bet it’s a lot easier
once you’ve given up.
No one ever cared
about me before.
And I just try to
blow it off, you know.
But it was still pretty rough.
I used to think there was no
place in this world for me.
But‐‐ aagh!
‐[gasps]
‐[grunts]
But I still found friends.
I kept at it and didn’t give up.
And good things happened.
Aagh!
When you give up your dreams and
everything else, they’re gone!
Rrrh!
[grunts]
‐Stop!
‐Your father and‐‐
[grunts]
‐‐Sandayu.
[groans]
I’m going to show you
that they weren’t‐‐
[grunts]
‐‐wrong!
Rrrh!
Ugh!
‐Huh?
Naruto.
‐[grunting]
Aagh!
‐Uh!
‐[gasping]
Now, I’m just going
to get you out.
Ugh.
[panting]
[shrieking]
‐We’re under attack!
‐Hm, Kakashi.
So you’re here at last
and right on time.
[rumbling]
‐Huh?
Hey, when did he‐‐
[thumps]
‐Uh!
‐Heh, told them not to
underestimate a ninja.
‐Hm.
‐Rrh!
‐Hold it!
Hold it, Naruto!
It’s me.
‐Kakashi Sensei!
KAKASHI: Sorry to
keep you waiting.
You look all right, Princess.
‐Yeah.
You switched my hex crystal
for a fake without telling me,
didn’t you?
‐Yeah.
I apologize for that.
But I figured this
was what he was after.
‐All for this thing, huh?
[guard yells]
‐This place is
crawling with guards!
‐Sakura!
Sasuke!
‐This way.
[rumbling]
‐[chuckling]
‐Doto!
‐Well done, Koyuki.
‐Wha‐‐
‐[gasps]
‐Wait!
It can’t be.
‐This shouldn’t be a
surprise to any of you.
I mean, really, I’m
an actress, aren’t I?
DOTO: There you have it.
Another brilliant performance
by the great Yukie Fujikaze.
‐Yes, it was all an act.
Ugh!
‐[grunts]
‐I told you, didn’t I?
I’m an actress!
Uh!
‐You wretched‐‐
‐Aagh!
‐Princess!
‐Uhh, I always knew,
Naruto, that if I
ever return to this country,
I was going to die here.
At least, I could‐‐
‐[growls]
‐Don’t you do it!
Don’t you stop fighting!
‐Naruto, it’s only
thanks to you that I
could stop running
away here at the end.
‐No!
Because all you’re
doing is running away!
Don’t throw away
your life like this!
‐I’m sorry, Father, Sandayu.
‐Koyuki!
Aagh!
‐[chuckles]
You really thought
you could kill me,
did you with this little toy?
Humph.
[clinks]
‐That’s right.
It’s Chakra Armor,
our latest prototype.
‐Uhh.
[coughs]
‐Don’t you touch her with
those filthy hands of yours!
Ugh!
‐Naruto!
‐You’re wasting your time.
Every ounce of your chakra has
been completely sealed away.
Come, let us go, Koyuki,
beyond the rainbow.
‐No!
‐Naruto!
[crash]
‐Hm.
[chuckles]
[guffaws]
‐[grunts]
This ain’t over.
I’m not going to go!
Do you hear me?
[gasping]
You could run, but
you can’t hide.
I’ll follow you as
long as I have to.
Rrrharrh!
[motor noises]
Huh?
‐Hop on!
‐Huh.
‐This is it.
We’ve come here
after all, I guess.
‐Sakura, how close are they?
‐Hold on a sec.
I’ve got it!
20 degrees left in 5
seconds, 30 meters out.
You want to aim for that branch!
‐Right!
‐Give it up.
It’s useless.
Come on, don’t make me laugh.
‐Sakura Blizzard Jutsu!
Enjoy!
‐You’re dealing with a
ninja of the snow here.
It will take more than
that to bring us down.
‐You’re probably right.
‐Uh!
‐Lions Barrage!
‐[grunts]
‐Aagh!
‐Aargh!
‐What just happened?
‐Gosh, I’m not really sure.
Wait, you don’t
think that they‐‐
‐You really think
you’ve got a shot?
Maybe you ought to turn tail
and run, like the last time.
‐I don’t have a choice, do I?
At least, I could show you
one of my original techniques.
Lightning Blade!
‐Ice Style, Wolf Fang Avalanche!
[growls]
‐How did you‐‐
Almost had me there.
What?
‐Even without
ninjutsu and genjutsu,
a ninja always has taijutsu!
You rely too much on this armor!
‐I don’t see it.
The treasure, where is it?
‐It’s so warm.
What is this?
‐A heat generator?
This is the hidden treasure
of the Kazahana Clan?
NARUTO: Koyuki!
‐[grunts]
‐Naruto!
‐Rrrh!
Ice Style Black Dragon Blizzard!
‐Huh!
Naruto!
‐What’s the matter‐‐ I
hardly felt a thing there?
‐Naruto, that’s enough!
If you don’t stop,
he’s going to kill you!
NARUTO: Trust me.
If you just have a little
faith in me, I promise you,
I won’t lose!
‐How the‐‐ is it‐‐
is it possible
that the chakra is
leaking out somehow?
Hrrrh.
Rrrh!
Die!
‐Rrrh!
Chidori!
‐Agh!
‐Hah!
Did you really think
your pitiful little jutsu
would have an effect on me?
‐Naruto, his armor
has been fractured.
The rest is up to you.
Naruto!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Come
on, Nine‐Tailed Fox.
Where the heck are you
when I really need you!
[clangs]
Show some guts, will you?
[rumbling]
‐What is that?
Huh!
‐It’s payback time!
CLONES: With interest, pal!
‐Come on, you little
halfwit, quit!
Dragon Blizzard!
[roars]
It’s over.
This ridiculous
little farce is over!
[guffaws]
Huh?
NARUTO: Not yet, it’s not!
I told you already!
It ain’t over till justice
prevails and evil is wiped out!
‐Every good story’s got
to have a happy ending.
‐Naruto!
I believe in you!
You are by far the strongest
ninja I’ve ever known!
‐Yeah, I know.
‐I could have told you that!
‐Look, Rainbow Chakra!
It’s just like in the movie!
‐Take this!
Rasengan!
‐Aaah!
[cracking]
‐Huh?
What the‐‐
‐Wait a minute.
Could this be‐‐ we’re
making this movie 3D!
SOSETSU: Believe in the future.
If you do, the spring
will surely come.
What will you do when
it comes, Koyuki?
YOUNG KOYUKI: I’m going
to become a princess.
SOSETSU: Oh?
What sort of princess?
‐Um, let’s see.
One who is strong
and who is kind,
and most of all, one
who fights for justice.
SOSETSU: [laughs]
That’s some dream.
‐Did I‐‐ did I actually
say those things?
SOSETSU: Well, so long as
you believe in your dream
and never give up, one day,
you’ll be that princess.
You can see it, can’t you?
There’s a beautiful princess
standing right there
in front of you.
YOUNG KOYUKI: But I
have sort of a problem.
There’s something
else I want to be.
‐Really?
What’s that?
‐An actress.
SOSETSU: What?
[laughs]
‐[laughs]
Oh, yeah.
Now, that’s a happy ending.
[sighs]
THEME SONG: Oh, whoa,
oh, whoa, oh, oh.
Oh, whoa, oh, whoa, oh, oh.
Force of nature,
unrelenting, can never fall!
And it’s supersonic!
It will charge!
Invincible!
Here we go!
There’s always something
steering the path I lead.
There’s always someone ticking
and kicking inside of me.
I‐‐ I will never give up!
Oh, whoa, oh, whoa, oh, oh.
Ever changing and
evolving, life renewed.
From a fire, flies
a phoenix born into.
Here we go!
The days of darkness,
trawling the battlefields.
Remember your true friend, call
on and put your trust in me.
I‐‐ I will never give up.
I‐‐ I will never give up,
will never give up, yeah.
Like a hurricane,
like a hurricane.
Like jerks.
Hurricane, like a hurricane.
Lightning strikes.
In like a hurricane.
Oh, whoa, oh, whoa, oh, oh.
Oh, whoa, oh‐‐
YUKIE: That
generator wasn’t even
fully developed in the end.
SAKURA: I guess it will be
back to winter soon, huh?
YUKIE: Not really.
If we take what we know
and continue researching,
before you know it,
the Land of Snow
will be called the
Land of Spring.
‐Yeah, but it’s kind of a shame.
You’re such a big star.
Are you really going
to retire from acting?
YUKIE: Who said I was retiring?
BOTH: Huh?
‐Ruling over the Land
of Snow and acting?
I think I can handle both.
I mean, I’d have to be out
of my mind to give it up now.
‐Uh, that’s great.
‐Well, I’ll be seeing you.
‐That’s her!
‐There she is!
‐Princess, sign here!
‐Sure!
‐Can I have your autograph?
‐Would you please sign‐‐
KAKASHI: That is great.
She’s perfect.
‐Aaagh!
I’m so stupid.
I should have
gotten an autograph!
‐Don’t worry, I took care of it.
TEAM: Huh?
‐Whoa.
Aagh!
Oh, man, look at me.
Couldn’t you, at
least, have used
a better picture or something?
Haay.
DIRECTOR: And cut!
That’s a wrap.
ASSISTANT: Good stuff people!
Thanks a million.
Hey, let’s do lunch, seriously.
Nice working with you, buddy.
DIRECTOR: Isn’t that wonderful?