(electric zapping)
(thunder rumbling)
(sirens wailing)
(car horns honking)
(distant rumbling)
(people shouting)
[Man] What is it?
Quick, it's coming!
(people screaming)
Man, days like this never end.
Hmm.
(roaring)
This is no time to
dwell on the past!
Time to take care of business.
(announcer speaking
in foreign language)
I'll just forget the past!
It's easier!
(roaring)
(crashing)
You and I both bear mitamas!
That makes both of us monsters!
We were meant to do battle
with each other, Aragami!
I'm glad you came here!
As long as you exist,
I can be myself.
(crashing)
Finally, I can be myself!
Ha!
(exciting music)
(singing in foreign language)
(roaring)
(splashing)
(shouts)
Huh?
(explosion booms)
(gasps)
Ready, weapons?
Fire torpedo!
(torpedoes rushing)
(explosion booms)
Those idiots!
Oh my god, it just
disappeared, Admiral!
What?
That's not possible!
Check it again!
[Man] Yes, sir.
(eerie atmospheric music)
(chiming)
Huh?
What a monster.
That's right.
So now do you believe us?
I'm listening.
So, what can you tell me
about these terrible creatures?
[Sakura] Hey, everybody!
What is that?
[Sakura] We can use these charms
to destroy the Neo-Aragami.
But it's just paper!
She has the
authority of your CIA.
You're joking.
(chuckles) Just leave
this to the professionals.
(lights buzzing)
So, you really think
this will work, huh?
Corporal, the monitor, please.
That's quite all right.
My word.
You guys really have been
living in the Stone Age.
The first step, as you can see,
will be to set up our perimeter
using these giant charms.
The charms will
need to be placed
at these six points
around the Aragami.
Then, for step two, we
place the giant seal
in the center,
trapping the monster
inside of the perimeter!
You really expect to fight
that creature with banners?
(scoffs)
The United States navy
does not fight with voodoo.
It's not voodoo.
It's magic energy.
From the Kasamakato family.
For the third step...
We place the seal
there on the Aragami
to focus the power.
(giggles)
(alarm sounding)
(gasps)
Looks like a little
Stone Aged voodoo
might just be the thing
you need, Admiral.
So, how'd you like that?
A fiery sorceress.
If I understand the
situation correctly,
you've already sent destroyers
to intercept the
Aragami, haven't you?
Once the Aragami
has been trapped,
we go to step four and blast it.
Operation Fly Trap!
What a stupid name.
If we could fight this
thing out in the open
we wouldn't need
to use your voodoo.
The United States has a
lot to think about, Admiral.
Who knows why you found yourself
in the position you're in?
Perhaps it's impossible
for any country
to resist abusing its power
once it's gone
unchallenged for too long.
Or maybe it's decided that
insanity is the only choice
in an insane world.
Either way, it was a
mistake for you to research
the mitama so you could
develop a new weapon.
Now that your misguided
experiments have escaped
one by one, you've had to
turn to foreigners like us
to undo the turmoil
left in your wake.
We will help you destroy these
creatures you've created.
And we'll even help
you keep the true cause
behind this accident
from the public view,
but I hope you remember what
the TAC has done for you today
the next time you get the urge
to throw your power around
so unilaterally.
Or maybe in the future Japan
won't be there for you.
You need the Japanese,
if you want to bury this
mess without publicity.
However, first
we're going to need
your full cooperation to operate
freely within your borders.
(grunts)
This is hardly a
secret, young man.
You really think
these dames know how
to fight a battle?
Cut it out!
You bunch of amateurs!
And why don't you
leave the fighting
to the professionals?
Right?
(sighs)
Fine.
We will provide whatever
kind of assistance we can,
but the rest will
be up to you guys
and those destroyers of yours.
We'd better stop this gabbing.
Those Aragami are not
gonna wait around for us.
[Momiji] 16 years old.
[Kome] Are you
sure you should leave
those two along together?
What do you think I should do?
For starters,
you could make sure
you sit next to them, you idiot.
If you know so much
then why did you have to
break up with Yaegashi?
It's not the same thing!
Why isn't it?
Things were moving so damn fast.
We were talking
about having kids,
starting a family.
I wasn't sure I was
ready for all that.
What could be wrong
if you love each other?
That may be what
you believe now.
Huh?
But I doubt you will after
she steals your man away.
Uh, come again?
[Valencia] That's
the research facility
responsible for this.
They're the ones?
Be careful with that!
You're tearing it!
Will you watch it?
I can sense it.
Evil is near.
(chimes)
Is that?
No way!
(dramatic music)
Is that an Aragami?
This isn't good!
Huh, Valencia!
(screaming)
(yelps)
Valencia!
I'm okay.
Luckily Kusanagi rescued me.
Huh, Kusanagi?
You two go now!
Kusanagi!
You think you can handle this?
Of course I can!
You go!
Okay.
But don't take too long.
Follow me, Momiji.
Wait, I'm coming!
(tires squealing)
(screaming)
I...
[Valencia] Yes?
I want you to know
that I love him.
I love Kusanagi!
Huh?
Uh...
Well, there.
What else can I say?
(explosion booms) (shouting)
(roaring)
(crashing)
Oh, no.
Not another Aragami!
I think we can take it
out with a CO2 inhibitor.
[Kome] Right!
(tires squealing)
(engine revs)
(grunts)
Will you quit squishing me?
Well maybe you should
stop sitting there!
I think we've got him.
[Yoshiki] Let's
get a clear shot!
(grunts)
(thudding)
I've got you now, dough boy.
(tires squealing)
[Momiji] I must have
sounded like such an idiot.
(electric zapping)
(grunts)
There, got it.
Ooh, it's absolutely perfect!
You go girl.
All right, let's see
this Oriental witchcraft.
Kasamakato family, transfer
your power through this charm
to defeat the Neo-Aragami.
(alarm sounding)
(exciting music)
Deny their movements so
they may no longer rampage
through the city streets
of San Francisco.
(lasers zapping)
(bazooka fires)
(Aragami roaring)
Got him!
That CO2 inhibitor
really did the trick,
don't you think, Yaegashi?
- What?
(crashing)
You can go ahead and
give up any day now!
(roaring)
(crashing)
[Yoshiki] Are you all right?
Got him.
That is exactly
where I want him.
Why don't you go
take care of Momiji?
Kusanagi, let us handle this!
Nobody is gonna
tell me what to do!
(grunts)
You're such a show-off!
(electric zapping)
So.
What?
Look here.
(gasps)
This!
[Valencia] I found it on
the floor in the airport.
Really?
You love him.
Yes, I do.
But I need to know if you're
in love with Kusanagi, too!
Someone like me can't
afford to love anybody.
Because...
Of my mitama, you know?
Those strong emotions
might make me one of them
isn't that right?
[Momiji] I wonder if he's
afraid of the same thing.
(crashing)
(Momiji screaming)
Momiji!
(adventurous music)
(Aragami roaring)
[Kusanagi] You'll be
better off without me.
Sakura!
You men I swear!
You're never in the right
place at the right time!
What are you talking about?
Come on!
How can you be such a bonehead?
She's worried.
Go to her.
(roaring)
Take care of her, Kusanagi.
You dog.
I really hope you
like birdcages,
because you're sure
trapped inside one.
What...
What am I doing?
Momiji?
(whimpering)
(electric zapping)
The time has come.
I can build...
The perfect Aragami.
(explosion booms)
(alarm sounding)
That should do it!
Hey, that Oriental
magic ain't half bad!
Keep on truckin', cutie pie!
Take us up, captain.
I can't complain.
He's getting a bit better.
Okay, whatever you say.
And I'm the cutie pie, right?
- Huh?
Kome, are you all right?
Talk to me!
(explosion booms)
(both gasping)
Damn, so much for
those CO2 bullets!
What now?
What is it?
Kome!
Hold on.
I've got you.
[Kome] Thanks.
Damn, it's gaining on us!
I say we go out fighting!
When this is over?
You'll get me a ring,
won't you Yoshiki?
Uh...
Yeah!
Worth at least
three months salary!
(crashing)
(roaring)
(alarm sounding)
(sighs)
[Woman] Kome!
It's Ms. Takiochi!
So far so good.
It's time for step four!
It's up to Momiji now.
All right, let's get a move on!
Momiji! Momiji!
You here?
Kusanagi!
She's been kidnapped by Aragami!
What?
(electric zapping)
This place...
(heartbeat pumping)
(shrieks)
You do love her!
Thought so!
I'm envious, Kusanagi.
I don't have anyone.
For me
it's nothing but pain, but I
can't stop.
You're afraid.
I understand.
We're the same.
But you shouldn't
run from the future.
What future is there
with someone like me?
It doesn't matter!
That's Momiji's decision.
And she says she wants
to be with you, right?
So what more do
you need than that?
Where are we?
Where they make Aragami.
(Momiji screaming)
Momiji!
Strange.
Kusanagi!
(intense music)
(Momiji whimpering)
Kusanagi...
Momiji!
You here, Papa?
Papa?
Welcome home Valencia.
(cackling)
(gasps)
This is our birthday.
The day Aragami was born.
Papa.
We are the rulers now,
the era of humans has
already come to an end!
He's under their control.
My friends have already arrived!
You can't stop it now!
This is our world!
No!
[Papa] Now darling,
would you like to see
our birthday present?
All I have to do is attach
the special mitama to it
and watch it go.
No!
(cackling)
(grunts)
(shouting)
Let him go!
(laughing maniacally)
Did I hurt you?
(electrical zapping)
(Kusanagi screaming)
No, stop it!
(screaming)
I mimic the Kushinada
pulse, my dear.
That's why it hurts so bad.
Join me, and the pain stops.
I would never join you!
(screams)
No...
Papa...
Stop it! Stop it!
(laughing maniacally)
(screaming) (zapping)
Kusanagi!
(laughing maniacally)
Papa!
Listen, you let him go Papa!
Valencia?
You can be happy.
You won't be alone anymore.
What do you know?
What do you mean by that?
Eternal life, immortality.
You have these things.
That's why I took the mitama,
to be together.
No!
(emotional piano music)
All I wanted was
your attention, Papa.
That's why I agreed to
be your subject.
It was for you!
Oh, Valencia!
Being together was the
only happiness I wanted!
Valencia!
[Papa] Since when did you become
such a bad girl, Valencia?
You'll be an adult soon.
Don't you want to grow up happy?
Oh, Dad.
Honey, how could
you offend the mitama
after all it's done for you?
How could you be so ungrateful?
Stop!
I swear!
You're just like your mother!
Stupid girl
who hates the mitama!
Them nor none of you
have the right to live!
That's insane!
You choose the
mitama over your own
daughter?
(screaming)
I can't let myself die!
Not until I've held you
one more time, Momiji!
Kusanagi!
(roaring)
Momiji!
(laughing)
See the power of mitama?
That's how strong he is.
Hey, Valencia.
Get your mom over here!
I want to share this
with the entire family!
We can all join the
mitama together!
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
(laughing)
I'm sorry Papa.
(gunshot fires)
(screaming)
(gunshots firing)
Papa...
I did do the right
thing, didn't I?
This was the right thing?
(electrical humming)
(zapping)
(chiming)
(grunting)
- Valencia!
(crashing)
(explosion booms)
(glass shattering)
(sirens wailing)
[Bill] The United States
is forever in Japan's debt.
[Man] I thank you.
But I fear as long as there
are people who seek power
beyond their wisdom, we
will see more Aragami born
in the future.
You may be right.
By the way...
Hmm?
You know...
I'll never leave you, don't you?
Is that so?
Okay.
Huh?
Hey, wait up!
Kusanagi, what did
you mean by that?
That doesn't mean you can
take advantage, you know?
[Kusanagi] Hurry up, or
I'm gonna leave you here.
[Momiji] Where do
you think you're going?
(upbeat music)