(lightning crackling)
(sighs) Yes, I know.
Don't worry.
I'll be there even if it means
sneaking out of the office.
Okay, okay.
I'll talk to you later, huh?
What?
Can't say things like
that on an open line.
Someone might be listening.
I'll see you at Memorial Low, all right?
For Christ's sake, she hung up on me.
Damn it.
Why does she always do that to me?
Doesn't she know the stress I'm under?
Crap, I forgot to ask her
if it's a private hot spring or not.
Ah well, it's time to
pick Yaegashi up anyway.
(energetic music)
(woman singing in foreign language)
(man singing in foreign language)
(both singing in foreign language)
♪ Just love ♪
(singing in foreign language)
(machine beeping)
(suspenseful music)
(water splashing)
(birds chirping)
(soft music)
[Ryoko] This little oasis is the only
open air hot spring for miles.
Koume's grandfather built it himself.
[Momiji] You don't say!
[Koume] That's right.
I used to play soldier in
this very spot all the time
when I was a kid.
[Ryoko] I didn't see it on any maps
so we should have it all to ourselves.
[Koume] Oh no one
knows about this place.
[Sakura] Yeah it really is
out in the boonies, isn't it?
[Koume] It may sound idyllic,
but try growing up here.
Oh look, monkeys!
How cute!
Look at them up here.
Oh they're just ugly old monkeys.
What's so exciting about that?
(gasps) You've got to be kidding.
They're adorable.
She can't help it.
After all, all our friends
are monkeys you know.
Ha ha, very funny,
but I actually do know
how to speak monkey.
Aw, why don't you let hear me a little.
(whooping)
Oh, and how do you say one?
Kee!
And two?
Ah-kee!
Mhm?
Ah-kee-kee.
Valencia, go ahead and
take off your clothes
and put 'em in the basket.
Ooh that doesn't look very secure to me.
Are you sure?
Yeah well amazingly,
people used to trust total
strangers back in the old days.
[Woman] How strange.
That must be one of
seven mysteries of Japan.
[Woman] Gee, aren't we miss-know-it-all.
Would you tell us the other six?
Momiji, would you stop
playing around and hurry up?
[Momiji] Ohkey!
- Hello up there!
- Hello.
- May we join you?
- Of course.
- This water looks wonderful.
- Is it too hot?
No, I didn't think so.
Do you think the water's too hot?
Oh no, hot water is
good for these old bones.
Laziness will make a
woman weak, they say.
[Ryoko] You know, Ishida
said the same thing!
I must be getting soft.
(dial tone beeping)
You sure it's not too hot?
It's just right.
Miss Takeuchi, it's your cellphone!
Phone call!
I'll get it.
Careful, it's hot.
We wouldn't want you to wilt.
Yeah that's really funny.
How many times do I tell you, Valencia?
Swimsuits are not meant for hot springs.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
You can just blame it
on my American modesty.
Is that so?
Hi, who's calling?
[Yoshiki] Hello, it's Yaegashi!
Enjoying yourselves?
Yes we are.
Have you wrapped things up yet?
[Yoshiki] Yes, I think we'll
still be able to join you
by seven, if that's all right with you?
(dial tone beeping)
[Man] If she gabs any longer,
I'll blow the thing right now.
[Momoji] Those monkeys
sure are tame, aren't they?
No I think they're just
comfortable hanging around
someone who knows how
to speak their language.
What are you implying?
- Sure act innocent.
- Oh-key.
What you say you learned how to juggle?
[Yoshiki] Yes, and I'm looking forward
to showing off my talents
at the party tonight.
What a riot.
I can't wait.
(cellphone ringing)
Hello?
[Man] You're lucky you
didn't blab any longer.
Huh, who am I talking to?
[Man] I've placed a
bomb in the hot spring
your friends are bathing in right now.
[Ryoko] Is this a joke?
[Man] The bomb will
be activated the instant
the water hits a certain level.
Ah, if that level were to change, boom.
I don't believe one
word of this hogwash.
[Man] Fine, don't believe me.
Just thought you should know
the triggering device will be set
the instant that sweet
thing slips into the pool.
Stop!
Valencia.
(dramatic music)
No one, no one move a muscle.
[Koume] Did someone lose
their contacts or something?
Okay, listen up everyone.
Whatever you do, do not stand up.
Do you hear me?
I just received a call
claiming there's a bomb in the springs.
A bomb?
All the way out here?
Apparently it's activated
by the water level.
I don't know whether it's true or not,
but until we're absolutely sure, we'll...
Excuse me, does that include us?
Yes, I'm afraid you're going
to have to stay in the water.
In the water?
What about Momiji's bathing buddies?
(suspicious music)
Koume, can you catch them?
Why do I have to do everything?
Momiji, let's go.
Why me?
[Koume] They're your friends.
That's just great.
Say hi to your pals for me.
See you (mumbles).
(foreboding music)
Okay Momiji, reach under
water and grab their feet
so they can't see you coming.
It's impossible to catch
a wild monkey barehanded.
(foreboding music)
Key.
[Koume] You ready?
We're gonna grab them
on the count of three.
You got it?
Key.
One, two, and three.
Stay still, don't panic you stupid monkey.
Will you stay still?
Oh my.
Oh are you having trouble?
[Koume] How come yours is so tame, ow!
I don't know, just friends I guess.
Are you sure we can really
trust those two jokers?
Oh they're more serious than they look.
Don't worry about it.
So tell us, have you
learned anything so far?
Yes, I sure did.
The float is being used as a switch,
attached to a pack of explosives nearby.
He must be pretty confident
we can't disarm it
because it sure was easy to find.
So what do you think we can do about it?
Well I suppose, what??
Huh, what was that?
(explosion booming)
(foreboding music)
Close to the road.
What is it?
[Man] So do you still
think this is hogwash?
[Ryoko] What do you want?
[Man] Not a lot.
Just 50 million.
We aren't worth much, are we?
You hurt my feelings.
Oh I'm sorry.
I meant in US dollars.
Dollars?
What?
Can't you do multiplication?
What do you mean, that's
more than five billion yen.
We are so dead.
Oh yeah, that's about
what I'd go for these days.
You think so?
What are we, spare change?
She really doesn't know any.
The bag of unmarked hundred dollar bills
should be ready in three hours.
You'll hear from me in 10 minutes.
Hold on a minute.
- (telephone ringing)
- Hello.
This is Kunikida.
Ah, how's the vacation going?
What kind of bomb?
Wha, a bomb?
Are you sure?
I wonder what's going
to become of us now.
Oh Momiji, shit happens, life goes on.
What can you do?
Oh.
I wish Kusanagi were here.
(birds chirping)
(Momiji gasps)
Did someone call me?
(triumphant music)
Kusa.
Another one of your
monkey friends, Momiji?
You know I never let you
out of my sight, Momiji.
Greetings.
Now I'll need your help.
Sure, so where do you need me?
I'll need you in the hot spring.
Huh?
[Ryoko] To defuse that bomb,
I'll need someone who knows explosives
and that means Koume's more
use to me right now than you.
I'll do it,
but I don't want monkey
boy there seeing me naked.
This is no time for modesty, Koume.
I know that, but.
Ah I know, you can bring my bra
and undies over here for me.
I see.
Miss Takeuchi, while
you're at it, bring mine too.
What for?
You can't get out yet so you
won't be needing them until.
Okay, I'll bring them.
Oh are you still fighting?
They'll never last.
I give it about a week.
I heard that.
You guys don't need to gossip about me
when I'm standing right here.
[Ryoko] Koume, be careful.
You're disturbing the water.
I know that.
Will you please just
stop being such a nag?
(foreboding music)
Okay, ready.
Okay, she's ready, Kusanagi.
Valencia, keep an eye on the
float while we make the switch.
[Valencia] Okay.
Now it's entirely up to you Koume.
Be careful.
You know I will.
Ready to go?
I guess so.
You bet.
(clears throat)
Get in very slowly.
I need to time it.
[Mamoru] Sure thing.
(foreboding music)
You guys, be careful.
The water level's going down.
(suspenseful music)
Slow down, Koume.
(cellphone ringing)
Yeah?
[Man] I trust you have the money ready.
[Ryoko] We're preparing it now.
We should have it in time for the pick up.
How do we get it to you?
Hm, going right by the book, I see.
Keep communication open as
long as possible without
submitting to the culprit's demands?
There's no money, is there?
In that case, I'll settle for answers.
Answers, what do you mean?
What about the money?
[Man] Tell me what rare item was found
at the Ikebukuro station three years ago.
(keyboard clicking)
[Daitetsu] Did you get the data yet?
I need more time.
There's more data from
England than I expected.
Check Italy immediately after that.
Yeah, hello, Kunikida here.
I need a list of prime terrorist suspects
from the last 10 years.
I think it's the, a riddle.
What's going on?
What the hell is up with this guy?
You guys can work on
the riddle if you like,
but right now we need to defuse that bomb.
- Got ya.
- You all right?
Darling, please wake up.
What's wrong?
This heat's too much.
Quick, one of you go
and get me a cold towel.
[Ryoko] How's she doing?
She's not looking so good.
We need to get her out of
here as soon as possible.
I see.
What's the plan?
I'll think of something.
Just give me a minute.
I'm afraid we may have no choice,
but to leave this one to fate.
We have no plan, Koume,
so it just might come to that.
[Koume] If this were a public bath,
we'd just add cold water.
Add cold water.
Yeah, that's the easiest way
to bring down the temperature.
Why didn't I think
of that earlier, Koume?
I'll stop the hot water
and let in some cold.
(gunshots ringing)
(bamboo rustling)
Just don't miss, okay?
I'll do my best.
(gunshots ringing)
(water splashing)
Okay Koume, ready?
Just hurry, the water's
freezing over here.
[Ryoko] Ready, set, go.
(water splashing)
[Woman] Let's move
her near the cold water.
All right.
I got it, a square wheel.
And that's because?
I don't know, I just thought so.
You idiot, you can't just give an answer
like that without a reason.
Why not an ostrich doing the two-step
or a camel doing a handstand?
That makes just as much sense.
I don't need any of
your lip, you got it?
Don't you give me that face
and don't you even test me.
Will you two stop?
Your little lover's pack can wait a while.
Where did you get pack?
The word's pact.
You'd think you would know
how to speak your own native tongue.
When are you going to learn pronunciation?
Oh you're really one to talk.
You Yankees don't even know geology.
- You mean geography.
- Huh, what did you say?
It was nothing.
I can't tell anymore.
I'll have to get Koume.
Koume, Koume, where are you?
I'll call you back.
Koume, why are you changing now?
I have a hunch.
That bomb is set by remote.
They can't be far.
Not up here in the mountains.
Too much interference.
Where would you even begin to look?
There's an old abandoned cottage
about a 10 minutes' drive from here
so I thought I'd just go and clean it out.
Not with that slingshot, I hope.
Here you go.
Only you would take a gun
like this on vacation, Takeuchi.
(chuckles) See you.
Don't screw up.
(cellphone rings) Yes?
[Man] Not fair, you're
not playing by the rules.
What are you talking about?
[Man] Looks like I'm going
to have to impose a penalty.
[Ryoko] Hold on a minute, I
have an answer to your riddle.
Just hold on a minute.
Momiji, the answer.
(foreboding music)
A great big square wheel.
[Man] Wrong.
[Momiji] A sonic carrier pigeon?
A sonic carrier pigeon?
My dear, I thought you'd
try much harder on that.
(rock exploding)
What happened?
Your tub just sprang a leak.
Kusanagi, quick, close the hole.
What hole?
Over there, go and close it.
(dramatic music)
Looks like I saved the day, heh.
I think my heart just stopped.
(Koume grunts)
[Koume] Boy my legs are
gonna be sore tomorrow.
[Ryoko] What did you find out?
[Yoshiki] Nothing much I'm afraid.
I'm still working on it.
I don't care how trivial it is.
Just find me anything out of the ordinary.
[Yoshiki] All right, I'll try.
[Momiji] I never
thought I'd die this way.
(soft music)
Hey.
Have any ideas about the riddle yet?
No.
(Koume gasps)
Looks like this is the place all right.
(cellphone ringing)
Yes?
I was right, he's here.
I'm going inside.
[Ryoko] Whatever you do, don't kill him.
Gotcha.
(suspenseful music)
(gunshots ringing)
(glass shattering)
(dramatic music)
What was that?
I think it was gunfire.
[Ryoko] Koume.
Where the hell are you?
(suspenseful music)
Of all the luck.
Don't you know how to duck?
Her and her big gun.
[Ryoko] Hello?
It's me, I screwed up.
You killed him.
[Koume] Maybe just a little.
He might still be breathing,
but probably not for long.
Shit happens.
At least the timer hasn't gone off yet.
I might still be able to find something
around here that will help us.
No!
What did you do, Koume?
The timer's been activated.
But it wasn't me, I swear.
Oh, I wish I killed him.
- Still not connecting?
- No, the line's still busy.
What a time for her to
tie up the phone line.
Right when we learn how
to disarm this damn thing.
[Ryoko] Koume haven't
you found anything yet?
We're running out of time here.
This place is a total pig sty.
Is there a switch anywhere?
[Koume] How the hell should I know?
Hello, did I lose you?
Hello, Koume?
Koume, are you there?
[Koume] What a rotten
time for the battery to die.
Oh of all the luck, for crying out loud!
Kusanagi, how does it look?
I'd say we're pretty much screwed.
Mm, pretty much screwed?
Where did you learn to talk like that?
Huh?
You know, some girl I know.
Jeez, some guy I know named Girlo.
[Momiji] You idiot.
(cellphone ringing)
[Ryoko] Hello?
I finally got through.
Who were you talking to for so long?
We don't have time for all this.
The timer's started and I
don't know how to disarm it.
You'll be all right.
Calm down.
It only takes three minutes.
[Ryoko] We have two minutes 30 seconds.
Yeesh, then let's go.
Come on Koume.
Hurry up, Koume.
[Yoshiki] Next, cut the
blue and white striped wire
to bypass the extra battery.
Bypass?
What do you mean bypass?
We don't have the supplies
to do that, Yaegashi.
[Yoshiki] Oh yeah, right.
Cut the yellow wire in
the second panel then.
Yeah, that's right, the yellow one.
I think he's panicking.
We better get ready then.
(monkeys chattering)
[Together] Ah, monkeys!
Sakura, they're coming
towards the water.
They're coming.
Okay we have no choice
but to get out of the water
at the same time that they're getting in.
Kusanagi.
I can't leave, Momiji.
Now just go.
(dramatic music)
[Ryoko] I did it.
What's next?
There should be a green
wire around there somewhere.
That can't be right.
I've already cut all of those.
[Yoshiki] There has to be
another one there somewhere.
Look!
Stop yelling.
I'll find it.
It's not here.
I don't see it, I don't see it anywhere.
Calm down and look.
It has to be there.
(Sakura screams)
No way.
Could this be the right one?
That's it.
(water splashing)
(Ryoko sighs)
We did it.
[Mamoru] Momiji.
No, not yet.
Man am I sore.
Was it disarmed?
You bet it was.
Damn.
Don't die yet.
I have a question.
What's the answer to riddle you gave us?
Mask.
[Koume] Hey don't die.
What comes after mask?
Wake up!
Don't die, wake up!
(soft guitar music)
(Ryoko singing in foreign language)
(Daitetsu singing in foreign language)
(both singing in foreign language)
(Ryoko singing in foreign language)
(Daitetsu singing in foreign language)
(both singing in foreign language)
(Ryoko laughs and speaks
in foreign language)
(soft guitar music)
(woman singing in foreign language)
(man singing in foreign language)
(both singing in foreign language)
(woman singing in foreign language)
(man singing in foreign language)
(both singing in foreign language)
(lively music)