(thunder rumbling)
(traffic rumbling)
(siren blaring)
(trolley rattling)
(metal screeching)
- Huh?
- What's going on?
(bell ringing)
(crowd chattering)
(crowd murmuring)
[Man] You said this has
happened on all the routes?
[Man] Yeah, every
trolley in town is stopped.
Why do these things always
have to happen on my watch?
What the hell?
What is it?
(ominous music)
(vines squelching)
It's some sort of vine.
They sure grew fast.
(man shouting)
Huh?
Hey, hey where'd you go?
(machinery rattling)
Did you fall or something?
Stop screwing around.
(ground rumbling)
(rubble falling) (man gasping)
[Matsudaira] Is this the
incident in San Francisco?
[Kunikida] Yeah.
Now take a look at this.
[Matsudaira] It can't be.
(fan whirring)
[Kunikida] It just
doesn't make sense.
Susano-oh is still
in hibernation.
What could be causing this?
[Matsudaira] I can't explain it.
Could someone have
awakened Susano-oh?
[Matsudaira] I don't know.
But why in the States?
I don't know.
(tense music)
No, it can't be.
[Kunikida] What does
your intuition tell you?
[Matsudaira] I
wouldn't venture a guess,
not until I've
analyzed all the data.
God help us.
God help us all.
(computer beeping)
(horns honking)
Could it only have been
sleeping for two years?
Huh?
What?
(keyboard tapping)
That girl, it's her.
(building rumbling)
(Kunikida groaning)
Mitama Aragami.
(building rumbling)
("Eternal Truth" by Takada Band)
(singing in Japanese)
♪ Just love ♪
(computer beeping)
(gentle music)
Always toiling away,
hoping to put the power
of the Kushinada to good use.
(Momiji yelping)
Remember, you're really here
to serve Mr. Kusanagi, Momiji.
How's it going, anyway,
between you two lovebirds?
Come on, you can tell me.
Ms Matsudaira!
He's the reason you
study mitama so hard,
now isn't that right?
(Momiji giggling)
(birds chirping)
[Momiji] I'm afraid
he might have an affair.
(Matsudaira laughing)
I hardly see him at all anymore,
and even when we do go
out, he seems so distant.
Maybe he's bored of me.
I'm sure he's just
giving you your space,
so you can prepare for your
college entrance exams.
My husband was the same way
when I went to graduate school.
He just wanted me to
concentrate on my thesis.
I don't know.
Will you stop your worrying?
Momiji, I know Mr.
Kusanagi well enough
to know he'd never leave you.
- I'll be!
- Huh?
Kusanagi!
[Kusanagi] Why is it I
feel drawn to this place?
(gentle piano music)
(machinery beeping)
I'll see you later!
- [Matsudaira]
I'll let them know
as soon as I have
some hard evidence.
(telephone ringing)
(helicopter rotors whirring)
[Aide] Welcome, sir.
The media is waiting for you.
What emergency?
You need me?
Hello, Sugishita?
Just calm down and listen.
- But that can't be.
(siren wailing)
What happened?
[Sugishita] Apparently
something caused
the Terrestrial Administration
Center to collapse.
Mr. Kunikida was buried
beneath the rubble.
There no cause, as of yet.
(tense music)
[Yaegashi] Could this
be the work of terrorists?
[Sugishita] That's
certainly a possibility.
All we know at this point
is that the Terrestrial
Administration Center's
offices were attacked.
Have you contacted Momiji?
[Sugishita] No, not yet.
She's not in her office,
but I did leave a message
on her answering machine.
At this point, we're just
waiting on more data.
I just had a strange thought.
(footsteps tapping)
Sure is nice.
(fountain splashing)
I miss being together like this.
You do, is that so?
Kusanagi, you haven't
become bored with me?
Of course not.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
It's just that I
know that I like you,
but not if you like me.
Don't be silly.
So you do?
Well, I keep asking you
to go out with me, don't I?
(footsteps tapping)
(gentle piano music)
(Momiji sighing)
Hey, wait for me, you
big kidder, you. (Laughs)
I'll race you to the fountain.
Go!
I'm gonna beat you!
- Oh, no you won't.
(Momiji laughing)
(tires squealing)
Oh, Momiji?
(keypad beeping)
How long has it been?
Two years, at least.
It hasn't changed a
bit, if we're lucky.
[Momiji] Hurry, you slowpoke.
[Kusanagi] I'm telling
you, my room doesn't
need to be cleaned.
Oh yeah, we'll
just see about that.
(gentle music)
It's immaculate.
[Kusanagi] I told you, didn't I?
[Momiji] Well, that's no fun.
I'm sure we can find
something else to do.
[Momiji] We sure can.
(Kusanagi yelping)
(mattress creaking)
[Kusanagi] I'm sorry, I can't.
[Momiji] But, but why not?
[Kusanagi] You're
still just a kid.
[Momiji] No, I'm not.
Is that really the
way you see me?
You idiot!
(door rattling)
[Takeuchi] How's it going
over there, Mr. Sugishita?
[Sugishita] We're still
interviewing eyewitnesses,
but some of them reported
seeing a huge monster
break into the building
just before it collapsed.
[Takeuchi] Then it's
exactly as we feared.
I'm afraid so.
It's Aragami.
I'd have to disagree.
At least, it's not the same
Aragami we dealt with before.
How do you know that?
I didn't detect any change
whatsoever in Susano-oh.
(machinery beeping)
According to my work, all
Aragami activity ceased
when Susano-oh went dormant.
Everyone, that is,
except for Mr. Kusanagi.
As long as Susano-oh's soul
continues to remain dormant,
then there is absolutely no
way the Aragami could return.
But then what were all
of these people seeing?
I'm afraid that's not all.
The data on the Kushinada
has been stolen.
[Sugishita] Did
Kunikida tell you that?
Yes, he did.
Apparently this
thief went directly
for the host computer's
data access cable.
[Sugishita] Amazing,
an Aragami capable
of connecting to machines.
They seem to be
targeting the Kushinada.
We have to find
Momiji before they do.
No, no, she'll be fine as
long as she stays with Kusanagi.
(train rattling)
(siren wailing)
Hey, what's the big idea,
running into me like that?
Aren't you gonna apologize?
[Kusanagi] Bug off.
I'll teach you some manners.
(man grunting)
You'll pay for that!
(blows thudding)
(thugs groaning)
You monster, get away!
I don't think so.
(unearthly chiming)
(fabric ripping)
(muscles tearing)
Huh? (Thug gasping)
Who wants to go first?
(thug screaming)
You're right.
I am a monster.
Only a monster would be able
to make her this unhappy.
(melancholy piano music)
Don't come near me, not
unless you want to die!
You bear mitamas, yet
you are the only one
who never turned
into an Aragami.
What, who are you?
I understand more than you know.
Oh yeah?
I know how you feel, because...
(unearthly whistling)
(woman gasping)
You don't know me.
[Woman] We have to go, quick.
Momiji's in danger.
Wait, come back, stop!
- Slow down!
- Come on, it's an Aragami.
[Kusanagi] Aragami?
Who are you?
Stupid, he's just so stupid.
(water splashing)
(Momiji screaming)
(energy whirring)
An Aragami!
(tense music)
(Momiji panting)
(crowd shouting)
(blow thudding)
(Momiji screaming)
You shouldn't have done that.
(energy whirring)
Mitamas?
You're an Aragami, but how?
These creatures must be manmade.
How can that be?
What we found so far
is that the Aragami
that attacked Mr. Kunikida
was completely artificial,
except for the mitama.
Right, and if
all of that's true,
then that means there must be
a human being
behind all of this.
Then what about the mitama?
If that's true, then
not all the mitamas
were controlled
by the Susano-oh.
So where in the hell
did they come from?
(blow thudding)
(Aragami screeching)
Some mitamas were smuggled
out of Japan a long time ago.
What?
(water splashing)
(Aragami screaming)
It's been going
on for centuries.
Jewelry and other
Japanese artifacts
have always been
treasured exports.
Of course, many
of them contained
rare beads and
unusually shaped stones.
(claw slicing)
[Kusanagi] Let
me guess, mitamas.
(woman groaning)
Someone has been
transplanting the mitamas
into these artificial beings.
You can see the results.
Well, it ain't too pretty.
(water splashing)
Now where's he going?
(Aragami screeching)
(woman screaming)
You all right?
Hey!
(Kusanagi gasping)
Mitama, she's just like I am.
(guns firing)
It's true, they've returned.
Kusanagi?
Who's that?
How's he doing?
[Takeuchi] He'll be fine
once he gets some rest.
That's one strong old bastard
we've got lying in there.
Well, you don't seem worried.
Right now I'm more
concerned about those Aragami.
Yaegashi, do you know
where we can find Kome?
No, actually, uh...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I assumed you were
still together.
Where is Momiji, anyway?
Oh, don't worry about her.
She's in a very safe place.
[Momiji] Who was she, Kusanagi?
(Momiji shrieking)
(water splashing)
Wow, you sure have
developed, haven't you?
Damn it, Sakura,
you shouldn't do that,
especially when there are
Aragami lurking around.
I wonder what those monsters
would be after you for.
How long do you
intend to feel me up?
Like it?
I wonder why he
doesn't come for me.
He'd find a way to get
here if he truly did care.
Maybe he has a new girlfriend.
(Momiji gasping)
(Momiji sobbing)
(Momiji screaming)
(water bubbling)
(Momiji gasping)
You awake now?
Stop whining now, will you?
You do trust him, don't you?
But, but...
(building rumbling)
(Momiji gasping)
(building exploding)
(Sakura and Momiji screaming)
(tense music)
What is it?
Oh gross, it's all sticky.
(rubble falling)
(Aragami screeching)
[Bystander] You don't
see that every day.
- What is that?
- Monster!
What was that?
There's a giant Aragami
walking through the city?
Now Yaegashi, are you positive
that there's no way
to contact Kome?
I'm sure that the two of you
must've kept in touch somehow.
No, I haven't heard from her
since she switched divisions.
Damn you, why'd you
have to break up with her?
Things happen.
Come on, let's move.
(tires screeching)
(footsteps thudding)
(train horn blaring)
(metal screeching)
(train exploding)
[Announcer] Attention
please, all passengers.
We've just been notified
that a giant monster's
approaching the
westbound railway.
Please proceed to the exits
in a calm and orderly fashion.
Your tickets may be
refunded on your way out
by the nearest available teller.
Should you require assistance,
(crowd shouting)
A uniformed employee will
be by to help you shortly.
We apologize for
any inconvenience.
(glass shattering)
(crowd screaming)
(rubble falling)
(footsteps thudding)
(Aragami growling)
That's the guy we want.
You think so, huh?
(Sakura and Momiji screaming)
(glass shattering)
(carapaces creaking)
(Aragami screeching)
(rubble crashing)
- Please help us!
Momiji!
- This one's mine.
- What?
(woman shouting) (upbeat music)
(fabric tearing)
(wings creaking)
Well, I'll be god damned.
She's one too.
I can't help but like that.
(woman screaming)
(energy crackling)
(Sakura and Momiji screaming)
Why, you did come!
You two all right?
(tires squealing)
Here, look after them.
Come back!
(Kusanagi shouting)
(energy crackling)
There it is!
(blow thudding)
How do you like that trick, huh?
Not too bad.
Now it's my turn!
(Aragami creaking)
(woman gasping)
(claws slicing) (woman grunting)
Shit!
No! (Energy crackling)
(rubble crashing)
(Aragami screeching)
(energy crackling)
(woman panting)
- Not bad.
- Of course!
(rubble crashing)
Look who's coming.
(helicopter whirring)
Watch out, Kusanagi.
I'm taking care of this one.
Yes, the heavy artillery
has finally arrived.
Let's get 'em.
Why, it's Kome.
Ready!
(helicopter exploding)
(Aragami screaming)
Take that! (Laughs)
[Takeuchi] What
the hell is this?
[Sugishita] Why, it's
your new uniform, what else?
[Takeuchi] I think they're
just a tad bit too revealing.
[Sugishita] I like 'em.
Feminine yet practical, but
still says I mean business.
But you can't be serious.
Have mercy.
Come on, you'll get used to it.
It's not so bad.
[Takeuchi] Who picked
out these uniforms, anyway?
[Sugishita] Why,
I did, of course.
(group laughing) Didn't you know
I'm the new office director?
[Takeuchi] What, they
made you office director?
[Sugishita] Didn't you
see the sign on the door?
[Takeuchi] I'm going home.
Listen up, people.
I've just received
new information
regarding the origins
of the new Aragami.
It appears they were
derived from a plant
found only in North America.
Mr. Kunikida!
Well, you're looking better.
The problem is
that scientifically,
these Aragami
shouldn't even exist.
I don't care where
they come from.
Come and get us!
[Kusanagi] No, we're
going to get them.
(gasps) Kusanagi!
They're coming out
of San Francisco.
(group gasping)
Are you sure?
Someone has discovered
a way to combine
the power of the mitama
with biotechnology.
But before they can
harness its full power,
they had to steal the
data on the Kushinada.
[Kusanagi] And this
person can help us.
Hey!
You again?
She's just like me.
She was also implanted
without becoming an Aragami.
[Momiji] She has the Mitama.
I'm Valencia Thomas,
16, sign is Cancer.
Nice to meet you guys.
(laughs) Hello,
nice to meet you.
We cannot afford to have
another Aragami attack.
Then let's go to San Francisco.
(upbeat music)
San Francisco.
(airplane rumbling)
(singing in Japanese)