[grunting]
♪
Where's that traitor, Esta?
No need to get angry.
I am perfectly calm!
[RIT]
Good to know.
It's hard to believe
that she betrayed us.
Esta, a traitor?
You interrupted
my precious slumber
for a small thing like this?
Were this another,
then I simply would have
had her flogged for heresy.
-[sighs]
-And you!
I bet you're working
with that dirty rat
and trying to cover
for her, Lil' Miss Princess!
But think again!
Because I know exactly
what you all are up to!
[gurgling]
Red, are you sure about this?
Well, they did make
the first move.
So we better play
our cards now.
[LJUBO]
May I return to the inn?
I haven't had breakfast yet.
[LAVENDER] You're not
going anywhere!
Fine, we can talk.
Let's go inside.
We'll have some tea
and hash this out.
[TISSE] We didn't expect them
to figure it out this soon.
What are you
going to do, Red?
Fess up, Esta!
I won't budge
until I hear you say,
"I'm a dirty traitor.
Strike me down, Hero!"
To be quite frank, I'm insulted
by this accusation.
I was merely asked
to look into the identity
of Van's target.
Do you concur, Ljubo?
Technically, you're correct.
And Rit here
is a former adventurer
who now resides in Zoltan.
Seems like she is
a suitable candidate
for information.
Lavender.
What is it?
Here's my partner.
The guy who I've been
raving to you about.
[door opens]
[VAN] [gasps]
It's you!
The swordsman
who stole my shield!
Hold on! What are Gideon
and Danan doing here?
Somebody explain to me
what's going on.
Allies of the former Hero.
But yes,
what are you doing here?
Check this out, Ljubo.
My mark of battle!
What? Your arm!
I came here because I knew
it was the only place
with the information
I sought to acquire.
Those who fight
the Demon Lord's army
should have immense respect
for these two.
-[grunts]
-Respect, huh?
If what you say is all true,
then why did you attack me?
[grunts]
Huh?
Did you expect us to sit by
while you threatened
the lives of innocents?
[VAN]
Innocents?
We may have disbanded
the Hero's party,
but that won't stop us
from facing anything
that would bring suffering
to the people of Zoltan.
What are you saying?
Suffering?
I wanted to save those people,
rescue them
from their errant ways
and return them to a life
guided by their Blessings.
Look, Van.
You tried
to control their minds.
And you set the salt dragons
against the town.
Those are problems the Hero
should be putting a stop to,
not creating them
for his own gain.
I did what was right,
adhering to my Blessing's will.
For that is what
the Hero must do.
[RED]
And as the Guide I must say,
you and I are long overdue
for a conversation.
You're the Guide?
The Almighty has entrusted you
with that important task?
You keep the Hero
from being led astray,
through the divinity
of the Guide.
I do, and I've fulfilled
my role.
Which is why I'm out here now.
Fulfilled your role
to completion?
But how?
A role without purpose
would mean you have
nothing left to live for.
[RED] Yet here I stand,
living my life.
[gasps]
Stop manipulating my Van!
Lavender.
Rit, I will not let anyone
get in the way of my love!
None of us are trying
to confuse anyone, I swear.
Red included.
Spend time with him,
and you will understand.
You'll see just why I love him,
and the quiet life that we
share together in Zoltan.
[whimpering]
Aw!
I have no doubt this has been
a profound meeting
for all of us.
So I suggest we shelve
this matter for the time being.
Very good.
What do you say we agree
to postpone this discussion
for now and reconvene
at a later date?
Yeah, no use dragging this out
when neither side at the table
is thinking straight.
Huh?
♪
Are you sure about
letting them leave?
I feel like we should've
pushed them harder
while they were
caught off-guard.
Going at this heavy-handed
would've made them
more distrustful later on.
To change Van's mindset,
we have to handle it
delicately.
That calls for old-fashioned
diplomacy and negotiation,
not deception.
Sounds like a real plan.
I really hope
we can find a solution
that Van will accept.
Is that possible?
Who knows?
The kid's a Blessing
fundamentalist.
Maybe getting lectured
by the Guide is what he needs.
Which is why I thought
that he would listen to me,
and see where I'm coming from
if I gave him my view
on our Blessings.
[slurps]
This is really good.
I threw in a little mead
for fun.
[RED] [chuckles]
Nice!
Okay, so we have
a temporary reprieve.
What do we do next?
First things first,
we have to be smart
and think through our strategy.
We won't get many chances
to talk with him.
Van strikes me as someone
who doesn't take too long
to make a decision.
I'm sick of so much
talking and waiting,
when all I wanna do is
close the book on this mess.
[RED]
Stepping out for a bit.
[RUTI]
Welcome, Big Brother.
[RED]
Hope you're hungry.
[RUTI] You made
lunch for me? Thank you.
[RED]
They're just sandwiches.
I'm excited for dinner, too.
[chuckles]
Hm. Dinner will have to wait.
After this visit,
I think I should avoid
coming here for a little while.
But why?
Because of Lavender?
She's strong,
and surprisingly capable
of determining
a person's location.
There's no telling
when she'll figure out
where you are.
I see.
Also, we met Van's party.
[RUTI]
Oh.
♪
Are you all right?
What if this is
the Almighty's way
of telling us that
I'm not supposed
to live a normal life?
Could be.
Maybe Lord Demis is hoping
that the former Hero,
who cast her role aside,
will be championed
by the new holder.
Hm?
Don't worry.
We'll throw a wrench
in whatever plan
he has cooked up.
Everything will work out
just fine
if we keep you two
from fighting one-on-one.
[gasps]
So how does that
sound to you, Ruti?
Aw.
You really are something else.
[knocking on door]
[MEGRIA]
Ruti? Tisse?
-[gasps]
-[MEGRIA] Are you in?
[door creaking]
Oh, hi, Megria!
Please, come in.
[MEGRIA] Don't mind me,
I won't keep you!
Just thought
I'd share some news
with you two on my way by.
I do hope it's good news.
Get this!
That herb-hunt job you posted?
Well, we have a taker!
Someone accepted the post!
That's great!
We'll be able to grow
even more kinds of herbs.
Thanks for letting us know,
Megria.
[MEGRIA]
At your service!
What a coincidence!
I was about to head out
to the Adventurers' Guild,
actually.
Oh? Important business?
Have you had any interesting
hunts posted lately?
[MEGRIA]
Interesting how?
Well...
preferably something
that has travel
with a sprinkle of combat.
A sprinkle of combat here?
There aren't going
to be any jobs--
-[MEGRIA] Oh, great!
-[TISSE] You have something?
Some wild monsters
were spotted nearby,
and we don't have
near enough hands on deck
to deal with
a whole herd of them.
Tell me more about it.
[MEGRIA] Love to!
I'll give you all the details.
Come take a walk with me back
to the Adventurer's Guild, Red.
I'd like to formally request
that you take on the job.
[RED]
So, yeah.
After that,
I accepted the mission.
-[grunts]
-Sea bogies, huh?
-Those are rare.
-[Danan grunts]
Gosh, I absolutely
loathe those things.
Just the sight of them
is sickening.
I'm pretty sure
others would agree.
Most find their existence to be
psychologically draining.
That so?
I kill them on sight.
[RIT]
These things literally show up,
give off this aura
that messes with our heads,
and use it to drain
our life force.
[RED] The real kicker
is they mainly target
human children for consumption.
Guess we gotta take 'em out.
You read my mind.
There's a few of them nearby,
according to Megria.
We need to clear them out,
and fast.
-Okay.
-Hm.
Where does that leave Van?
I'll ask the boy wonder
himself to join me.
[ALL]
What?
Don't tell me you're gonna
fight alongside that punk?
Red, are you out of your mind?
Nothing matters more to him
than raising
his Blessing level,
even at the cost of lives.
There's no telling
what sort of problems
he could cause.
Actually, this just
might work out.
Think about it.
Lavender will be with him,
and she'll get to see what
Red and I are like together.
So, this might be
our best chance.
Lavender.
It would be nice to get
a better read on her abilities.
[DANAN]
Makes sense.
Get the enemy
to fight on our side
so we can learn about them.
Count me in, Red,
I'll back you guys up.
Rit's got me covered,
but thanks.
-[thuds]
-[gasps]
Where's the fun in asking me
to hold down the fort?
[RED]
Sorry, man.
[Danan exclaims]
-[DANAN] I hate it!
-Hm.
His over-the-top reaction
was remarkable
to witness firsthand.
Was it?
Is there something wrong?
My brother is out there
doing his best
while I'm stuck in here.
I hate it.
I wanna help, but I can't.
I know how you feel.
[waves crashing]
I'm glad you agreed
to help out.
I thought you'd refuse.
The Hero's duty
is to slay all evil.
[RED] The beach from our report
is just up ahead.
Are you ready, Van?
[VAN]
You need not ask.
The Hero is always
prepared to fight.
So for you,
fighting's just a part of life?
Isn't that true for all
living creatures, though?
Fighting is a way of life
so long
as we possess Blessings.
Hm.
Or so I think.
Enough with the thinking, Van!
Can we go now?
Indeed.
Gideon and I will take point
and engage the target,
won't we?
That's right.
And you two will use
spells for back up.
Roger that, Red.
Sorry, buddy,
but I don't take orders
from country bumpkins
like yourself!
[growling]
The beach isn't quite
crawling with them,
so that's a good sign.
I do see a group
hiding by the rocks.
[RIT]
Quite a few of them.
Cleaning up here
should be a cinch.
Nonetheless,
stay on your toes, Van.
Huh.
Why do you wield
a bronze sword?
Hm?
I'm no longer fighting
to save the world,
so I don't need
expensive equipment.
Perhaps. But as I said,
fighting is the way of life.
[RED]
Right.
And this bronze sword
is all I need to defend myself.
Hm.
Wielding an inferior weapon
is rather puzzling.
But surely it was
Lord Demis' will
that brought you before me.
To guide me
as the world's Hero.
No, I think that--
[LAVENDER]
Looks like we're caught.
[growling]
[RED]
Let's do this.
[gasps]
[growling]
[grunts]
[sea bogies whimpering]
-[groaning]
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
-[thumps]
Merely common beasts.
But the Hero
must slay all evil!
[grunts]
-[whimpering]
-[thuds]
Over here, uglies!
Huh.
Hm.
♪
[grunts]
Van, no!
Are you okay?
Gideon.
Just focus on the battle.
You're betting too much
on your Healing Hands
when you fight.
Have you tried defending?
Why waste time?
Offense is the best defense,
right?
[RED] None of that matters
if you're wounded.
I refuse to yield against evil.
That is how
the Hero must fight.
Adjusting your strategy
isn't yielding.
It's learning to adapt, Van.
-Huh?
-Here they come.
-Look alive.
-Yes.
[thuds]
[seagulls squawking]
[sighs]
All right.
Do you wanna tally up
the number of enemies
you killed?
Why?
You were keeping track,
weren't you?
I was not informed
there was any need to.
The Hero's role
is to slay all evil.
How many are irrelevant.
[RED] There were 45
sea bogies in total.
I killed 26, you 18,
and Rit got one.
[VAN]
What are you implying?
You didn't fight alone,
did you?
In a party, the number
of enemies you take down
is a good marker
of your contributions.
So what?
[RED] You're supposed to be
the Hero, the strongest.
You had better start
picking up the pace soon.
Hm.
The Blessing of the Guide
shows the Hero the way.
-Right.
-Meaning,
you can't call yourself
the true Hero
until you surpass me
in every way possible,
-right?
-[gasps]
[RED]
At least, that's what I argue.
Your thoughts?
Yes, I can see why you
would think that.
Van!
Why, you!
I only gave him my opinion.
Look, Van!
I think you're perfect
just the way you are!
[RED] A partner who accepts
everything about you,
including your weaknesses.
Seems like that'd
just ruin a person.
-Shut it!
-But I didn't say a thing.
Anyway, let us be off.
It is done.
[RIT]
Wait.
There are more
sea bogies around.
What do you mean, more?
Hm?
Okay, and what's the big deal
about a heap of sand?
No, it's tracks entering
and leaving the village.
The village?
That usually means
-missing children.
-[gasps]
[RIT] One of them may have
abducted a child earlier.
And the sea bogies we fought
sought more victims.
Then we must save the child!
Van. How skilled
are you at tracking?
Far from enough.
I did not acquire the skill.
It is unneeded for battle.
I guess it's a good thing
you have us with you.
We'll handle it.
With the help of my
Divine Blessing, of course.
Why the long face, Hero?
Hold your head up high,
and be grateful
that we are on the job.
Thank you.
You better stop teasing
my darling Van!
Don't listen to them!
You don't need
a tracking skill.
You have me, I can detect
all living creatures
wherever the wind blows!
[gasps]
♪
[RED] Sea bogies don't devour
children immediately.
They like to feed off
their fear for a while first.
Hope we're not too late.
I sense the creatures nearby.
I'll go ahead.
[grunts]
♪
[both grunt]
[gasps]
♪
Though I appreciate
the stealth,
you can relax.
The sea bogies are known
for their fairly poor hearing.
See any kids?
[RIT]
No, not from here.
[gasps]
[groans]
-Close!
-[RED] Two in front,
and three in the back.
[VAN]
I'll go!
-[Van grunts]
-[groaning]
-[slashing]
-[thuds]
-[groaning]
-[growls]
-[grunts]
[groaning]
-Are you hurt?
-Hardly.
Good. I'm glad.
Now, let's split up
and find the kid.
Huh.
[grunts]
Are you injured?
I'm Van the Hero.
-Here to save you.
-Huh?
A Hero?
-Really?
-Yes, it is I!
[gasping]
-[crying] Sir. Hero!
-[grunts]
Hey! Take your paws
off of him, now!
I said, get off!
Van, don't just sit there!
[FEMALE MOTHER 210A] Thank you
for bringing her home!
I and my family
will forever be in your debt!
Were it not for your help,
Sir Hero, our little girl.
She would be...
[crying]
No need to thank me.
-Mister Hero?
-Hm?
Thank you, sir,
for rescuing me!
Huh.
[ESTA]
Oh? Van, of all people?
So he can listen
to advice, then.
There, there.
It's like that sometimes.
I'm amazed you can get through
to Lavender, too, Rit.
Huh?
Well, see,
Lavender and I are...alike?
She's in love and so am I,
you know?
I can't do anything right.
-Don't say that.
-But it's true.
I had many talks
with Van and Lavender
during our travels.
Not once could I get them
to see my point of view
and change their ways.
But you two managed
to do just that
in such a short amount of time.
I tried my best, I suppose.
And I'm so glad you did!
None of this would
have happened
if it were not for you!
[ESTA]
Really?
Yes, of course!
Don't forget,
this whole saga began
because you sent me
to fetch Red!
And now here we stand today!
This is true.
You donned a mask
to conceal your identity!
But make no mistake,
my good friend.
I was in awe of your work!
Albert.
I didn't know you felt
that way about me.
Do you mean it?
I do!
What a pair.
You're being ridiculous!
Who, me?
No, wait!
By ridiculous,
I didn't mean to imply
that you're unfit
to be my partner!
I-It's just. I...
Say no more.
I still have a long way to go.
Don't worry! I can try harder!
No!
I mean, sure? Yes?
Help! Me!
[chuckles]
Reel in the sweetness, guys.
Honestly.
That's rich, coming from you.
-What do you mean?
Gosh!
-[laughing]
-Hm?
[YARANDRALA] You lovebirds
coo worse than they do!
-[RED] That's...
-[RIT] Not true.
Stay the path, Hero.
Never falter.