[TISSE]
Sorry to drop by so suddenly.
Don't be. We're happy
to help with anything.
Especially if it's urgent.
Do you remember
Cardinal Ljubo?
Yeah.
I think I saw him at the
Great Last Wall Fortress.
I hear he's looking for the
former demon lord's airship.
"Altra of the Water
dealt a crushing blow.
Masked Knight Escarlata
defeats army general,
forcing a retreat."
Makes me wonder who
this Knight is serving.
Perhaps the Church?
A mercenary.
Huh.
Hey. About what Tisse said.
How the Cardinal wants
control of the airship.
Is handing it over to
the Church the right call?
It's better for them
to put it to use,
than letting it rust
away in Zoltan.
Until they give us a reason
to keep it out of their hands,
I say we wait it out.
Fair enough.
Keeping Ruti safe.
Ensuring no one finds her
is our top priority.
♪
No sign of any cold mold.
[chuckling]
And the herbs are
growing nicely, too.
Yup. I've got your
advice to think for that.
Also, Tisse seems
to enjoy helping out.
I do. I never thought
doing farm work
with milady
would be this exciting!
Might be worth thinking up
a sales plan moving forward.
Let's start with my
apothecary shop.
How about I purchase
your first harvest?
All right.
Next, we spread the word.
Clinics and the
Merchants Guild.
Hmm. Traveling merchants
could make good customers.
Does this mean you'll
help us with sales?
Of course.
I'm a member of the
Merchants Guild, you know.
And not to mention
your masterful guide
to Zoltan easy living.
My Master Big Brother.
"Master Big Brother?" Hm?
A lovely phrase.
[chuckling]
[grunting]
[growling]
[RED]
Looking good, Danan!
Good enough!
But, throw me in a fight and
I'll be back to full strength.
Planning to leave Zoltan
once you're discharged?
I'll miss seeing you.
Tag along with me, Gideon!
Together we can annihilate
the demon lord's army!
Pass.
My new life is here with Rit,
running my apothecary shop.
Ah, well. Suit yourself.
Drinks, then? Before you go?
Why not? Although
there is one other thing
that I'd like to do
before I bid you goodbye.
What's that?
A spar.
♪
I want you to spar
with me, Gideon.
♪
[RIT]
And you said yes?
[RED]
Yeah.
He insisted he wanted
to before leaving Zoltan.
I'll have to train like crazy.
It's been a while.
Think you'll win?
The truth? No, not a chance.
His Blessing is Martial Artist.
It's pretty common.
But he adores his Blessing.
And it favors him right back.
Right.
Now consider me as the Guide.
I only have average skills
meant to protect a young Hero.
Kinda obvious how
this spar will turn out.
But you're still
going for it?
I am.
Huh.
Then do you want
to spar with me?
[gasps]
Come on, don't
give me that look.
It's not like we've
ever sparred.
If you're really worried,
just cast Merciful
before the fight.
Bet you're gonna use it
against Danan, anyway.
True.
The risk of scarring or
wounding my opponent is gone
if the spell is in effect.
Doesn't mean it
won't hurt all the same.
-Hm.
-Hmm?
Sorry, I can't.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[RED]
So rusty.
At this rate, I'll only end
up letting Danan down.
Here. Best to stay
hydrated while training.
Appreciated.
[YARANDRALA]
Red!
Huh?
Is it true you and Danan
are planning to spar?
Word gets around, I see.
You should have told me sooner.
I would be thrilled to help.
Please allow me
to train you
and help you brush up on
your combat skills.
That's very kind
of you to offer,
but I thought you
were a spirit mage.
Well, aside from
my magecraft,
I also founded the
Lotus-Style Staff Technique.
You're the founder? That style
is super famous everywhere!
And get this.
You know that book
detailing various
regions' military tactics?
The famous "One Hundred
Strategies, the Beauty of War?"
Authored by none
other than Yorondrala!
That's so amazing!
Well, sitting on my hands
as the years marched on
felt wasteful.
But back to more
pressing matters, you two.
What I think you
need right now, Red,
is to dig deep and
sharpen that mind of yours.
Rediscovering and honing your
past skills will not be easy.
This well of strength from
which you pull must be
different than what you've
relied upon in the past!
That makes sense.
The me from before
Zoltan is long gone now.
Which means I'll
have to train in a way
that plays to Red's strengths.
Now that's the spirit!
Then we should begin
your training camp at once!
- Training camp? - You grab
your bags too, dear Red!
♪
Did I keep you waiting?
Not at all.
I just got here.
[chuckles]
The two of you
were just waiting to
play out that tired
cliche, weren't you?
Go on. Just admit it.
Don't be shy.
Admit what?
Ruti just cares about me!
Did I keep you waiting?
Not at all.
I just got here.
-Did I keep you waiting?
-Not at all. I just got here.
Did I keep you wait--
Hate to interrupt,
but are you sure you can handle
training alongside m'lady?
You're talking to the guy
who taught Ruti swordplay.
Of course a teacher can keep
up with his favorite student.
Looking forward to
learning with you, big brother.
[DANAN] Training camps test the
mettle of one's character.
-It's the highest form of play.
-Huh?
[RED] Danan!
Discharged already?
Yeah. No way
I'm gonna sit back
while you guys
have all the fun.
Count me in on
the camping trip.
Figured as much.
You ready to head out?
All set.
[water flowing]
♪
Right, tense her up so that
just leaves the firewood.
[TISSE]
Done.
[panting]
Come now!
Be mindful of the ecosystem!
Break over!
Time for another firewood run!
He's not listening.
[RIT] First meal
of training camp
is Red's custom
training lunch!
[ALL gasping]
There's just one problem.
I don't think we have
enough for Danan.
Have mine instead.
Thanks, but I'm strong
enough to go without.
Please take it.
Even though hunger
is a new feeling for me,
I'd rather you have it.
Feel free to take
half of mine, m'lady.
Let me offer you
half of mine as well.
Half and half makes
one whole meal.
That doesn't seem fair.
Wait, wait. Try this.
[RED] Now we all grab
whatever we want.
[RUTI] Smart idea.
Sorry for the trouble.
But if you guys really insist,
thanks for the meal.
Don't mind if I do.
[chomps]
[chuckling]
Say something.
It's been quite
a while since the old
gang got together
like this, hasn't it?
Theodora's missing.
And we can't forget Ares.
Hm.
[DANAN]
That's true.
Oh right, I forgot to ask you.
Did you happen to
look at the newspaper?
Some hotshot mercenary
defeated Astra of the Water.
You mean the
Masked Knight, Escarlata?
That's gotta be Theodora.
Think, is there any other
knight on this continent
who can beat a general
of such high caliber?
And don't forget,
where she is, her right-hand
man's not far behind.
The knight with the
prosthetic right arm.
Can't be anyone
else but Albert.
[DANAN]
Oh him.
Still gotta
thank him for saving me.
After leaving Zoltan,
I plan to meet up with
Theodora first thing.
If she wants to finish
off the Water General
for good then, I'll
happily join her.
Hm?
In case you were unaware, I've
yet to sample the duck saute.
Gimme that.
[YARANDRALA]
Honestly, Danan!
-[grunts]
-[clanking]
[gasps]
[YARANDRALA, DANAN]
Ruti!
[DANAN]
Okay, time to fight.
♪
-Should we train too?
-Indeed.
There's something
else I want to do. Bye.
Wait for me.
♪
[water gushing]
I still feel exactly the same.
That's weird.
Why is it weird? I didn't
expect anything different.
You didn't?
Now I want to know
what you were expecting.
Wait.
Something smells nice.
Rit and Yarandrala's cooking,
maybe?
I think they're on
dinner duty tonight.
Should be good.
[sighs]
Your swordplay
makes your foe visible.
My foe?
That's right.
Each of your moves
tells me what kind of
enemy you're cutting down.
I do picture them, I guess.
Humans, and
elves, and monsters,
demons, all walks
of life fighting you.
I see them crystal clear.
Goes to show you how adaptable
your tactics are in combat.
Sparring with you
is all the fire I need.
Likewise.
♪
[water rushing]
[RIT] Hey you.
Need me to wash your back?
Huh?
Yes, please.
If you wouldn't mind.
Hm.
So training with
Danan today went well.
Really drove home
how strong he is.
Wouldn't be too far
off the mark to call him
the strongest human.
After Ruti, of course.
He is pretty impressive,
isn't he?
This isn't just another spar.
It's not for fun
or a deathmatch.
Winning or losing
isn't the point, either.
Then what is the point?
Danan's a warrior to the core.
Quiet life couldn't
be more different.
But there's strength
in easy living,
and I'll show him
that through our spar.
You two have been through
a lot together as friends.
I hope he understands.
Me too.
Fighters, keep still
while I cast Merciful.
This inhibits
wounds, but be aware
this spell does not
prevent pain, yes?
No hard feelings, okay, guys?
Begin!
♪
[grunts]
Martial art,
rampaging kick!
[grunts]
♪
Crap!
[slicing]
[grunting]
[grunts]
-[slicing]
-[thuds]
Martial art, pulverizing punch!
[grunts]
It really is just
a normal sword.
And I'm supposed to be
the stronger one between us.
But you saw through
every one of my moves,
and even made contact
with this simple blade.
[chuckling]
You know what,
Gideon? You're a fun.
There's never a dull
moment when you're around.
You have figured out
how to win, though.
I can see it in your eyes.
Nice catch.
I'm itching to see how
long you can keep this up.
You're managing to
block every hit from me
because you're
predicting them, aren't you?
Yeah, of course I am.
How else will I defend myself?
So all I gotta do to win
is use moves I wouldn't
normally rely on.
Holding back some is the key.
"Holding back". Huh.
That's your strategy?
The hell do you think I am?
We're sparring, so I'm
not swinging to kill you.
Just because I'm
not trying to kill you
doesn't mean that I won't fight
at my absolute peak!
I expect nothing less!
-[grunts]
-[clang]
Give it your all, Gideon!
So those eyes of yours
can see right through me
at my full strength?
Guess that means I'll
have to transcend my limits
and go above and beyond!
Then bring it!
I'll meet you blow for blow!
And prove what I've
gained from this life!
[grunts]
Ready, Gideon?
Ready, Danan!
♪
[grunts]
Ow. Stupid me
charging into a direct hit.
I'd be a goner if it wasn't
for Yarandrala's spell.
[chuckling]
I knew all along you were
a force to be reckoned with.
I just hope I didn't
disappoint you.
Not even close.
Can't say I totally
get this chill life thing.
So I thought fighting you might
help me wrap my head around it.
Fighting's the only language
I speak, and it's how I think.
And? Learn anything
about my lifestyle?
Not one thing.
But you know what, Gideon?
I mean, Red.
It is subtle, but
your swordplay
has a raw and
formidable strength.
You're the same tough
guy I've come to respect
who's just chosen a
different path to walk.
To your damnedest to
live happily ever after.
Easy living is strength, too.
Sure will. Thanks.
As for me, the thrill of
the battle is why I fight.
My desire is my
source of pride.
Your strength.
It's what I respect
most about you, Danan.
Relentless and free.
[chuckling]
All right.
It's my turn next, Danan.
[gasps]
Seriously? I get to spar with
the world's strongest hero?
Not even
my wildest dreams did I--
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
Come on! There's gotta be some
way I can still pull a wind.
[laughing]
I feel so bad for him.
Sorry.
♪
Long time no see, Albert.
It's been a while.
Are you back for good?
Talk about a nice surprise.
I arrived here today.
Mister Red and Miss Rit, I'm
glad to see that you're well.
Did I hear "Mister"?
That's a first.
Strange, I know.
Please, no reminders
of the man I once was.
Did Theodora come with you?
No, she's not here in Zoltan.
I came alone.
She's taken the
name of Escarlotta.
I have a message from her,
and an urgent one at that.
What message?
"Take heed that a new
Hero has appeared.
[ALBERT]
His name is Van of Flamberge.
He may make his way to Zoltan,
in order to take the former
demon lord's airship."
-[door creaks open]
-[indistinct chatter]
[VAN]
Such commotion.
[LAVENDER]
Looks lively, doesn't it?
Lavender, stay close to me.
Out of danger.
Will you keep me safe from
all the scary people?
Indeed.
No harm will come to you.
Goodness me!
When you say things like that,
I'd do anything for you!
[crashing]
Hey! Got something
funny to share with the bar?
You're giving me a good reason
to claim self-defense
here, pal!
[grunting]
Sorry, but you had it coming!
Need to keep my
Blessing from running wild,
or else the urges
just get worse!
[laughing]
Do any of his buddies
want to volunteer too?
Step right up,
don't be shy now.
You do want to avenge your
dead friend here, don't you?
[MALE RUFFIAN 205B]
Come on, hurry up and fight me!
A wrongdoer blessing.
[MALE RUFFIAN 205B]
Give you your life!
[slicing]
[thuds]
Be gone now, evil.
What is going on over here?
Nothing. Van just struck down
a very strange fellow.
Yes. This one murdered another
patron, so I killed him.
Start from the beginning, Van.
First, a reason for the fight.
Reason? Does a reason matter
in the grand scheme of things?
It'll shed light on your
motivation to kill outright.
You could have easily
captured him alive
before resorting to murder.
An interrogation
would be beneficial here.
What a curious statement.
You do realize he had
a wrongdoer blessing?
That doesn't deny
one's humanity.
People's lives involve
more than a blessing's urges.
Everyone has
their own free will.
You must never forget that.
You seem to
misunderstand the situation.
-Do I?
-Let me elaborate.
By no means am I implying that
your statements are incorrect.
I felt no hatred for that
beheaded corpse,
nor was preventing further
casualties here my priority.
The blade of the
hero is not meant
to satisfy personal ambition.
Above all else, Esta,
my battles are
offerings to the Almighty.
But why'd you kill him, Van?
[VAN] People with the
Wrongdoer Blessing
exist solely to be
executed by another.
His death by my
blade fulfilled the
role he was put
on this soil for.
In truth, I do feel stronger.
A strength achieved
in exchange for his life.
I offer love and
blessings to his sacrifice.
My blessing, which has
grown at the cost of his life,
will surely save
the world one day.
Do you hear yourself?
Words of a true hero.
Oh, not yet.
Even now, I stand
here before my party,
untested by the
demon lord's forces.
I am a hero in name only.
Hero Ruti's faith runs
deeper than mine.
Are we finished here?
If so, we should
head to Zoltan at once.