[LJUBO]
Apparently Zoltan's mountain
range houses
ancient elven ruins,
and that "girl" you seek is in
fact a weapon created there.
Read the report.
It has everything
you need to know.
She is not a
threat to humanity,
so our business
here is complete.
We'll return at once.
[VAN]
No, I will not.
Why's that?
You are aware that we must
live as our blessings
tell us to, yes?
Mine tells me to stay.
Hmm.
Far be it from me
to tell you otherwise.
I hope that your blessing will
encourage you to
begin a new journey.
[footsteps fading]
[VAN] My lord has
delivered me a revelation.
A trial that I must overcome.
[LAVENDER]
Trial?
To test my faith, no doubt.
My blessing's impulses, which
have guided me until now...
are utterly silent.
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
Perfect.
There's something to your
tea that eases the soul, Red.
Mighty high praise.
So, how's Van been holding up?
[cawing]
Ever since he came
back from your mission,
he's been distant.
He locks himself in
his room all day to pray.
He speaks much less now too.
-Huh!
-[sighs]
Leaving him to his
own devices is unwise.
Sir Ljubo and I take
turns checking up on him.
[TISSE]
Bad time?
[RIT]
Tisse, is something the matter?
I wanted your
opinion on something.
The Adventurer's Guild
received an urgent request
to search for a missing
child in the forest.
Milady and I would go,
but our hands are tied
as long as Van is here.
Other Adventurer's
aren't interested in taking
the mission because they doubt
there's foul play involved.
What should we do?
[ALBERT]
May I volunteer?
Huh?
-[RED] You sure?
-I am.
-I'll find the child.
-Albert.
Adventuring was
what I did best,
and I know my way
around those woods.
Trust me, this won't atone
for my unforgivable
behavior, I know that.
I'm doing this to help Zoltan.
It is my home.
Absolutely.
And nobody like
me is far from a Hero.
And that's fine, because
traveling alongside Esta
is all I ever want to do.
I am truly lucky.
[ALBERT] From here
on, I want to act in a way
that honors my
place at her side.
Well, you already have.
[both chuckle]
What is it?
Nothing. Just glad
we can trust Albert.
Oh, well, I-I suppose.
All the information we
have at the moment is here.
Good luck, Albert.
Thanks.
[birds chirping]
[footsteps approaching]
♪
[sighs]
Ah?
[wine dripping]
Waiter, fetch me another.
I'm empty over here.
Sir Ljubo drinking
again, I see.
Of course, I am.
Take a seat and join me.
[ESTA] Where's Van?
At the inn?
That boy? No, he ran
off on his own somewhere.
You've lost him?
Last I heard from him,
[LJUBO] he was following up
on a tip about a missing child.
He and Lavender went to search.
Huh!
Why does that boy resist
the teachings I offer him?
Why does he ignore
everything I say?
Dear lord, what's become
of my honorable Hero?
At least he can still be fixed.
Yes.
♪
Was it not the almighty himself
who brought the Hero to
me to be molded and primed?
[grunting]
[thudding]
Surprised to run
into an ogre out here.
And the child?
♪
[animal growling]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[ALBERT]
Sorry about that.
[groans]
Kurukururu!
-You meanie! Leave him alone!
-Just a scratch!
"Meanie", what a way to greet
the adventurer taking you home.
-Home?
-Yep.
Your parents have
been worried sick,
fearing the worst had happened.
Kurukururu's with me.
We were playing
when that ogre came.
You're safe now.
Did your friend here
keep an eye on you?
Uh-huh.
Kurukururu protected me.
But there's a
scarier one around.
But they were all afraid.
Of what?
[LAVENDER]
Found her!
Huh?
Hero.
How is she?
Faring well.
That is good news then.
[ALBERT]
Something feels off.
It's almost suffocating.
If that's all, I'll
take her home now.
Come with me.
[VAN] Not until we slay
the evil at fault.
The ogre?
It's dead.
Didn't that thing lure
the child into the forest?
It must be slain.
Wait!
Calm down and
sheathe your sword, Hero.
This is only a fairy
dragon, not a wicked fiend.
A fay being, not
unlike Lavender.
It's completely harmless.
You're using
me to beg for its life?
Albert, you have ten seconds.
If you are still in my
way, I will kill you.
Ah!
Leave now!
Run while I hold them off!
-You'll die!
-I said to go!
Ah!
Are you friends with
that fay creature?
I'm not.
I just met it.
And are you confident
you can best me in battle?
Not in the least.
So, why stand,
despite the inevitable?
"Why?"
That is a great question.
My feet won't stop
shaking, to be honest.
But I won't sit back
and watch while you
take an innocent life, Van.
I've no choice
but to stand tall.
What is this feeling?
Something deep down,
feeding my desire to witness
you laid low with one slash.
[screaming]
[breaks]
[thudding]
[rattles]
Lavender, find them.
Anything for you.
-[groans]
-Ah?
[groans]
Unhand me.
Don't kill it.
Why make such futile
effort for a mere fay?
I am part of the Hero's party.
And?
[sighs]
I wish to act in a
way to honor that.
Unhand me.
♪
Let go, let go, let go.
Let me go!
I am the one true Hero!
Damn you!
[thudding]
[grunts]
[rattles]
Van, no!
You fought well.
[ESTA]
Regenerate.
Albert, you are a champion.
I am truly proud to
call you my partner.
Esta, why defend a man
who conspires with the wicked?
-[thudding]
-Ah?
Van, do I look like I'm
in the mood to chat?
I am filled with rage!
[groans]
Why?
And to think
I admired you, Esta!
[VAN] Perhaps you've
made a grave mistake.
Ah!
You get away from him!
[thudding]
Ah!
If you're so angry,
stop fighting like a bitch!
And what happened
to you, Lavender?
I thought you were
resolved to never
show Van your unfettered mind.
Shut your mouth!
I hated you from the
moment I laid eyes upon you!
Dears, time to cool off.
[water dripping]
Give me a break.
Does a lonely archfay really
think she has the
power to stop me?
Careful, you'll ruin
that cute face of yours.
You are a fairy, are you not?
Just die!
♪
[thudding]
[LAVENDER]
Van!
[groans]
Healing hands.
[Van] The girl is finally
within my reach.
Soon, I'll do it.
♪
Will Mr. Adventurer be okay?
His wounds have totally healed.
Might look bad,
but he's just resting.
Thank goodness
the kid made it out.
You did good, Albert.
Do we know when
he might wake up?
[RED]
Anyone's guess.
He pushed himself past
his limits to deal with Van.
Give him some time
and he'll come to.
[ESTA]
Right.
It would have been
worse if you weren't there.
[sighs]
Had a hunch.
Couldn't shake
the peril in the air.
But Van is out of control.
[RUTI] The impulses of the
Hero's blessings are unmatched.
Normally, it wouldn't compel
you to submit to emotion.
Imagine how
aimless he must feel,
acting on a vague impulse.
Yeah, I know what
he's going through.
Knowing him, all
the inner turmoil
could be driving him insane.
My goal was to change his
thinking, not cause a meltdown.
This is not your fault.
It is mine.
Mine and those who
traveled with him.
Esta?
Let me go gather my
thoughts alone, Red.
[footsteps fading]
-Big Brother.
-Yeah.
[footsteps approaching]
When I clashed with Van,
for the first time in my
life, my anger took over.
Just seeing Albert on
the verge of death, I...
You couldn't hold
yourself back, right?
[ESTA]
I was terrified.
So, terrified of losing him.
Very thought drives a stake
into my heart even now.
Remember when I
tried to lay you low
to keep Rudy
fighting as our Hero?
I've changed so much
since, and it scares me.
One of these days I could
make a devastating choice.
I may lose myself again
and do something
beyond repair or apology.
It frightens me.
Are you going to cast
aside your feelings for him?
Ah!
No!
I can't do that.
I don't want to.
[RED]
Then don't, Esta.
Those emotions don't
come from your blessing,
but from deep
within your heart.
And I think that's really
worth something special.
[ESTA] Emotions that have
nothing to do with our blessings?
[chuckles]
One thing is for certain.
Meeting you people
has turned me
into a terrible woman of faith.
[Red chuckles]
[RIT] Red!
Esta!
[footsteps approaching]
[knocking]
Who's there?
[VAN]
Do you have a moment, Cardinal?
Van, my boy.
Don't be shy.
Door's open.
[door opens and creaks]
I am here to inform you
that I'm leaving Zoltan.
Is that so?
You've finally
come to understand.
Then let us prepare to depart.
Before that, I will make
for Undine's abode.
Undine?
[VAN] And I will
slaughter every last fay.
Esta, Gideon,
and everyone else
there will meet the same fate.
Are you mad?
Honestly-
Argh!
Surely that will lure the girl,
and then I will kill her, too.
If she hides, destroying
Zoltan should draw her out.
Oh, listen to this no longer.
You are the Almighty's chosen.
Now, act as such and
control yourself, Hero-
[groans]
Van.
[grunts]
Why?
[thudding]
The whisper of the
Hero's Blessing is no more.
With impulses silenced,
my Blessing is out of reach.
As such, I shall execute
the final urge I was given.
Starting with her, the
girl who bested me will fall,
and so will evil.
[footsteps fading]
Wait!
[grunts]
[sighs]
♪
[water gurgling]
[RED]
Van's on his way.
And Lavender will
no doubt be with him.
Even with my power, I
cannot stop her alone.
She's even stronger
than a water archfay?
Can you tell us exactly
what we're up against?
Despite everything,
it was not my intent
to out one of my kind.
Suppose it's far
too late for secrets.
[UNDINE] The being you call
Lavender is a calamity.
[RIT]
No way!
[UNDINE] Yes, she is
one of the archfay-Ketu,
avatars of power
and destruction,
inviting catastrophic disasters
since the time of
this planet's creation.
As civilization advanced,
the ancient elves and
dragons wiped out the Ketu,
leaving her the sole survivor.
It was my belief she had
sequestered herself
within a jungle.
Okay, so we've
barreled right past
legendary and
straight into mythical.
Any thoughts on a strategy?
A mythical archfay and
the ultimate champion
of mankind are on
their way as we speak.
No choice but to talk this out.
It's now or never.
Talk this out?
You don't seriously
believe that, do you?
It's gonna come to
blows at some point.
And whenever that
happens, we'll be ready.
Ready to talk down
an out of control Hero?
Yes.
Just think about it.
The unwavering
Hero we knew before
is now second
guessing his resolve.
Give me some time
and I can convince him.
Trust in Red, like I do.
And I'll back him up
if it comes down to it.
So please, let him
handle this, Tisse.
Guess, I'm in
if you two insist.
All right, shoot.
What crazy idea do
you have in store?
I'm gonna settle things
one on one with Van.
You want to fight
him all by yourself?
Sounds crazy, all right.
Maybe a little bit.
Anything could
happen, you know.
Call me crazy or just plain
stupid, but think I'll win.
♪
If all is decided,
I shall create a barrier
to minimize damage.
Would any of
you be willing to help?
More than happy to help.
I can lend a hand as well.
[UNDINE] Now, if there's someone
who can defend the village...
Don't worry, Mr. Crawly Wally
and I are on it.
[creature agrees]
Okay, looks like we're set.
Give it your all out there.
[ALL]
Alright!
[footsteps approaching]
[water waves crashing]
One more thing.
For good luck.
Thanks, Ruti.
[chuckles]
At long last...
I can reclaim my title
right after I kill you.
[water gurgling]
Be honest,
I will know if you lie
[Van]
she is the Hero, Ruti, yes?
This is my destiny set
forth by Lord Demis.
And in order to
fulfill that destiny,
I must first
slaughter that girl.
And when I inherit
the obsolete Hero's power,
I will save the
world as the true Hero.
[RED]
That's stretching it.
Ah!
You don't know what to
do with yourself anymore.
It's sad watching you create
meaning where there is none.
You are mistaken.
[RED]
Am I though?
What's your Hero's
Blessing telling you?
To slaughter the obsolete Hero!
Could it be that you
don't feel anything at all?
[gasps]
[grunts]
What have you done
to me, Guide bearer?
Do you know
how painful this is?
To feel doubts creeping
in, clouding your inner voice?
Everyone doubts themselves.
It's just a fact of life.
The Hero is above that!
I refuse to accept this!
[RUTI]
I did, so why can't you?
Accepted it over and over,
while fighting the army.
The entire time I was afraid.
Asking myself every day if
what I did was right or wrong.
And after my
brother left the party,
those feelings worsened.
Until I didn't know
what to think anymore.
At some point,
I shut myself off
from the people I could trust.
And yet, they're
helping me out now.
After all this time,
look at us now.
We've become an actual party.
Shut up!
A true Hero would
never waver from the role
assigned to him by the
almighty Lord Demis!
Quit running, Van!
Urgh!
If being the Hero is
what you want,
quit running from
the doubts you have.
Face them head on courageously.
Confront it?
That's right.
No matter how
painful things might get,
stand firm and
walk your own path.
That's what you call courage.
[VAN] A Hero is
completely immune to fear.
That alone is good enough.
[RED]
And as the Guide...
my job is to show you the way.
[thudding]
So, fight me.
With that sword.
Ugh!
[VAN]
The Bronze Blade?
[RED] This is a battle between
the Hero and the Guide.
Strike me down
where I stand, Van.
Do that and you'll
find your answer.
[VAN]
Very well.
Don't listen to that liar, Van!
Not another inch from you.
Move or die, Rit!
You heard what he said.
This is between Hero and Guide.
I'll tear out your tongue.
Any fool who gets
between me and my beloved
will beg for death
when I'm through!
Say what you will,
but my love is fighting too.
And I won't tolerate
anyone threatening him.
Fay, the Hero, even
the Almighty Demis.
And if you try
to interfere, you'll die.
♪
We stop our swords
at the last moment.
And the loser
will admit defeat.
Is that the outcome you wish?
Not today.
This ends when
one of us goes down.
A real fight.
"A real fight?"
Good, because I won't stop
until I unleash
this rage upon you!