[thuds]
Surrender.
You are the last hill giant
standing, Dantak.
We've left you alone,
so why attack us?
[VAN]
Because of your sloth.
[DANTAK] Nonsense.
On that, we can agree.
Monsters who won't kill?
Who just cower in their lairs?
You defy Lord Demis' will.
[DANTAK]
Who are you, boy?
Slayer of evil.
Van the Hero.
The Hero?
You're nothing but a child!
[slashing]
[blood splattering]
[VAN]
Begone now, evil.
Yay! Isn't he great?
-A maniac. Perfect.
-[squealing]
♪
-[fire crackling]
-[chuckles]
-Huh?
-Smells tasty, Esta.
Dinner ready?
[ESTA]
Care to join me, Tisse?
Where are the others?
[ESTA] Van and Lavender
went to hunt down monsters.
Cardinal Ljubo
is out like a light.
[chuckles]
Just us? Excellent.
[fire crackling]
♪
Remember when we used to sit
around campfires like this?
I do!
Those were good times.
But I don't recall you cooking
back then, Miss Theodora.
I picked it up recently.
An enjoyable skill, I've found.
Huh.
Seems to me you're
following in Red's footsteps.
I am.
I wish to be more like him.
Not only in making a meal,
but in supporting
and guiding a Hero.
However, all I've managed
to learn is how much I lack.
It's not you.
I would say it's more
an issue with your Hero.
Albert would be worried
to see you like this.
Huh?!
You have a point.
I fear I've caused him
enough trouble.
That's funny.
Whenever you come up,
he always speaks
about you with such pride,
that it makes me think
he's happy working
alongside you, specifically.
Stop. He can't be
that enthusiastic.
Oh, he is.
He also seemed
to miss you very much.
Does he really?
Albert misses me,
of all people?
Me?
-[Mr. Crawly Wally squeals]
-Hm.
I mean,
it's nice to hear, is all.
Very. I suppose
the feeling is mutual.
If I am afforded
the opportunity,
then I would like
to see him soon.
No! I misspoke!
[ESTA]
What am I even saying?
Please do not misunderstand.
I merely wish to reunite
with a good friend!
Yes, a good friend,
no more, and no less!
Thank you for the illuminating
discussion.
Well! A fine evening
for a drink, yes?
Indeed! Off to fetch water!
[cloth flutters]
[TISSE]
Someone's in love!
♪
-Huh!
-Piping hot curry buns,
the village specialty!
Eat! You three
must be starving!
-Go on. Don't be shy!
-[Rit chuckles]
[chuckles]
Three square meals
of curry a day.
-[RED] Shh.
-[chomps]
[munching]
[chuckles]
This aroma is absolutely
to die for.
And it's spicy!
Fried bread when the day's
only begun?
It feels a bit indulgent
for my taste.
Stuffed with curry, too.
Hence the name, curry bread.
-[FEMALE VILLAGER 208A] Wow!
-Huh.
[FEMALE VILLAGER 208B]
Look, look!
[FEMALE VILLAGER 208A]
That's amazing.
Where are they going?
My, oh, my.
There's a sight
you don't see every day.
A herd of Pegasi.
First time I've ever seen them
flying high over our village.
Almost like the herd's
fleeing for safety.
Hm.
Huh?
Something's coming.
[water gurgling]
[ESTA]
The Fairy King's gem.
That shield allows its wielder
to use mind control magic.
I trust you understand
its influence.
-[LAVENDER] Another lecture?
-Hm.
All you ever do is nag, lady!
That depends
on how one wields it.
If used as a beacon of light,
then it shall guide evildoers
onto the path of faith.
Forcing someone
to their knees in prayer
won't make them a believer.
That beacon should
be sealed away.
Van earned the shield, not you.
So how he uses it
is none of your concern.
[sighs]
♪
[children laughing]
Our only business here
is handing over an airship
to Sir Hero,
and they're throwing a party.
This event has me on edge.
Certainly there won't be
any issues
like our last encounter.
What more could a Hero want
than to celebrate in his honor?
-[indistinct chatter]
-Hm.
[MOGRIM]
All right! That should do it.
-[MIDO] Hey, Mogrim!
-Hm?
[chuckles]
How goes the missus?
[MOGRIM] Try as I might
to get her to rest,
she won't listen
to a word I say!
Got me all nervous!
Well, it's still early.
Make sure she slows down a bit.
And, of course, be there
for your wife, no matter what.
I got her covered there,
doc, no worries!
[all gulping]
[grunts]
Hey! How's the new gig going,
Godwin?
Starting to make a profit,
thanks to those little zoogs.
As it turns out,
those mushrooms in the forest
are in pretty high demand
around these parts
because of the fragrance.
So basically, you're loaded!
-Treat us to dinner!
-[GODWIN] What?
Why would I wanna
wine and dine you idiots?
Better yet,
why don't the two of you
buy me something?
No harm in helpin'
your friends,
don't be stingy!
-[laughing]
-Be a man, Godwin!
-You guys are morons! Shut it!
-[all laughing]
Takes one to know one, pal!
Would you boys
settle down and behave?
The kids are showing you
all up, look at them work!
-[ALL] Huh?
-[sighs]
Looking good over here!
-May I try?
-Huh.
[chomps]
Sir Hero's gonna love
all the nice stuff we have!
Mm-hmm. I bet he will.
No, they are not.
[VAN] What you have described
to me is called decadence.
It is not joy.
-Hm.
-[indistinct chatter]
[MALE VILLAGER 208A]
The Hero has returned!
Huh.
[indistinct chatter]
Excellent.
I hear you've
located the airship.
Yes.
Before that,
we would be most thrilled
to have you all join us
in a celebratory toast.
[FEMALE VILLAGER 208C]
Sir Hero!
[MALE VILLAGER 208B]
Congratulations, Sir!
This again?
What excessive revelry.
-Hm?
-Huh?
What he means is we
appreciate the thought, Mayor.
But due to prior commitments,
we must refrain.
[gasps]
I understand.
Forgive our arrogance
and complete failure
to take Sir Hero's obligations
into account.
The citizens of Zoltan
pray to Lord Demis
that Sir Hero finds
unwavering success.
Prayers from heretics
won't reach the Almighty.
-[MALE PRIEST 207A] Huh!
-[TORNED] Huh!
♪
Come now.
That was highly offensive.
Take it back, Van.
And apologize.
No. I will do neither.
I am the Hero,
who has undergone
training as a monk.
One of my tasks
is to guide heretics
onto the right path.
[TISSE]
What is he talking about?
The Divine Blessings
alone serve
as obvious proof of devotion
to Lord Demis.
Yet he calls us heretics?
-[stomach growling]
-[groans]
My stomach.
♪
Pardon me, but you do realize
you're being very insulting?
You declare us to be heretics,
but for what reason?
The fact that you live
such pointless,
indolent lives here.
According to scripture,
sloth is a mortal sin
that conflicts with our roles
granted by the Almighty.
You people must repent
and mend your ways.
The path before you is clear.
♪
[VAN] Take up arms against
the demonic troops!
"Demonic troops?"
"Take up arms?"
You must fight
alongside the Hero.
It is your sacred duty
to accept.
We have our land
and our livelihoods to protect!
Be rational!
Cast it aside.
This pedestrian backwater
is utterly worthless.
[indistinct chatter]
[TISSE]
Uh-oh.
Our grandparents
endured hardship
and put their lives on the line
to develop our home!
And yet you call it worthless?
Even as the Hero,
to say such a thing
is beyond rude!
Rude?
Etiquette describes
mortal norms.
I am speaking of the divine.
♪
Why do they deny me?
It's simple.
You just insulted their home
right in front of them.
Their Zoltan is dearly beloved.
They cherish
their peaceful lives here.
[sighs]
This is a nuisance.
[clangs]
Huh? What are you up to?
[ESTA]
Stop, Van!
[LAVENDER]
Do not get in Van's way.
Move aside!
Van's intentions are not
borne out of heroism,
but desperation!
Oh, I know what he's doing.
And I really don't care.
The way I see it,
anything Van does
is completely
within his rights.
Hm.
♪
[Esta and Mistorm grunting]
[MISTORM ]
Could it be?
This is sorcery!
[grunts]
Cardinal!
[cigar crackling]
-[exhales]
-[wind whooshing]
Failure can be a harsh teacher
in Van's education.
Anyway, the bodies
of a few small-town peasants
will not stain
the Hero's reputation,
if we're being
perfectly honest.
What?
[LAVENDER] No funny tricks
from you either, Tisse.
Any sudden moves,
and I'll kill you.
[groaning]
Behold.
The shield of the Fairy King.
It has the power to guide you
to the correct path
and save you.
Your denial of the Hero
for a life of idleness
has been judged by Lord Demis.
Now, let us fight
the demon lord's army together!
-[YARANDRALA] Thorn Bind!
-[rumbling]
What is this?
[YARANDRALA]
Van the Hero.
Is this truly necessary?
Who are you?
Your neighborhood
high elf residing in Zoltan.
[sighs]
What hero resorts
to mind control magic?
That is the work of a villain.
You dare liken me to a villain?
Who are you to speak
on right and wrong?
[thuds]
I the Hero, Van,
slayer of evil!
Stinger Weeds, unleash!
[rumbling]
[clanging]
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
♪
Hm.
[indistinct chatter]
-Party's over, we gotta run!
-Hurry, get to safety!
[grunts]
♪
Martial Art.
Destructive Comet Kick!
[thumps]
[screaming]
Close one.
Danan.
Gutsy of you
to take on a Hero alone.
I've got your back.
Do you know
what you're getting into?
Pretty obvious.
He can mend himself
as the Hero.
Why refuse to apply
Healing Hands?
Who's to say?
[YARANDRALA]
His body may be durable,
but not indestructible.
Two great evils!
But I am the Hero.
I will not succumb!
There's your answer.
This kid won't
stay down for good
because of the faith
he has in his Blessing.
Time to kick his butt
and take him down a peg.
Lord Demis,
I present to you
a Hero's fight.
Martial Art,
Fierce Tiger Claws! [echo]
Martial Art, Holy Blade!
[echo]
[grunts]
♪
[groans]
Just one hit.
[rumbling]
[thumps]
[groans]
[grunts]
It hurts.
But...a Hero must not yield.
[grunts]
Healing Hands Mastery. [echo]
Reflect.
[echo]
[grunting]
[groans]
[VAN]
Amazing.
I suffered immense pain
from that,
yet you still stand.
You are a worthy opponent
for the Hero.
Danan!
So you reflected
the injury right back?
Pretty low stunt if you ask me.
[VAN] That stunt
that allows me to heal
using my opponent's vitality,
with it, I can thwart
any dire situation at will.
No matter how great the evil,
the Hero will not give in.
What kind of Hero
passes his pain off to others?
Ain't nothin' heroic about it!
[spits]
The Almighty Lord Demis
designed me
with my role in mind.
Condemnation is
a rejection of His will.
There is no greater heresy.
Hm.
♪
[roaring]
Huh?!
[SALT DRAGON 208A] Murderer
of our fallen brethren.
Thief of our stolen treasure.
The time has come for you
to taste our wrath
and vengeance!
Those wicked dragons.
Have they come to rob me
of my shield?
[growling]
[YARANDRALA]
O, spirit of the mighty tree!
♪
[explosion]
My powers
are not a favorable match
against the salt dragons,
but...
Zoltan will be charred
at this rate!
-Yes! That is just what I fear!
-Now, fall!
Huh. Get lost!
O, spirit of the mighty tree!
[explosion]
This is such a shame.
The only shame
I see is standing
right in front of me,
not helping anyone!
I will not counter
the Lord's will.
If the salt dragons
do destroy this sinful land,
then no choice will remain.
Even the sloths of Zoltan
will join the war
in retaliation.
Okay, I've heard enough
of your crappy
sermons, little man.
I'm taking you down first!
[thumps]
[grunts]
Healing Hands Mastery.
Reflect.
[groans]
[explosion]
-[screams]
-[sword clangs]
[grunts]
Sorry we're late.
You're back!
Thought you were still gone.
-[grunts]
-[sword clanging]
[grunts]
-What was that?
-[shield whirring]
[chuckles]
[VAN]
Why, you...
[swords clanging]
[grunts]
♪
Huh.
Hm.
♪
[RED]
Here come the dragons.
Van's on my tail too, no doubt.
Hey, you. Nice work.
Without your threads,
Mr. Crawly Wally,
I never would've
made it in time.
[squealing]
Now, for the fun part.
Making sure his heroic efforts
aren't all for nothing.
-[growling]
-[grunts]
Just hear me out!
[growling]
♪
[SALT DRAGON 208A]
Immense bloodlust.
-The Hero.
-Huh.
[RED]
Listen carefully, okay?
Relax.
I ran here
so I could return this.
Yours to begin with, right?
-[thuds]
-Indeed.
The former demon lord entrusted
us with that treasure.
I knew it.
Then take it back.
♪
[SALT DRAGON 208A]
Beware of that Hero.
♪
It's kind of you
to offer a waring.
-But it's too late.
-Martial Art.
Holy Blade!
[rumbling]
[thudding]
[RED]
Oh, boy.
That's gonna give
travelers a headache.
Sorry, but you fail as a Hero.
Another heretic.
There!
[groaning]
[RED]
If you can't swing your blade,
you won't be
cutting anyone down.
[VAN]
How dare you? Release me!
All that work
to level your Blessing,
when you should've focused
on your sword.
The methods of men
have no merit.
It is nothing in the face
of my Divine Blessing!
[RED]
Got it.
So that's what makes you tick.
Explains why I could
lure you out of town
just like that,
away from the safety
of your party.
If my sword fails,
I have magic!
[grunts]
Good luck using
any magic at this range.
Is this some plot
to stall for time?
The Hero can fight
through nightfall
and not be out of breath!
Oh, we'll have this wrapped up
way before nightfall.
-Won't we?
-[gasps]
Oh!
[thumps]
[thudding]
[grunts]
Ow!
[groans]
[thuds]
Don't bother trying
to figure it out.
You'll forget me by tomorrow.
[blows]
His party will be here soon.
Let's get going
before they see us.
Hm.
[VAN]
So cold.
Ah. My death is imminent.
The Hero was defeated.
Then let it be so.
The only duty of the Hero
is to fight evil.
Not to win.
In the end, I did
what was asked of me.
But. Why must it be that girl?
If everything proceeds
according to Lord Demis' will,
then surely I met that
girl for a reason.
[ESTA]
He's losing consciousness!
[VAN]
I see.
♪
Healing Hands.
[gasps]
Look! He's alive!
Are you okay? I'm here!
I won't leave you alone
ever again!
[VAN]
Hm.
So this is part of my role.
Van?
I will kill that girl.
And at last I will be
the true Hero.
♪
[VAN]
The Lord is come!
[laughing]