[footsteps]
♪
-It's here.
-No way.
[KIGGITH]
What's so surprising?
-[BOTH] Huh.
-We knew
from eyewitness accounts
it was hidden
somewhere in this area.
Investigate it.
What, you mean now?
How do you expect us
to find anything?
It's pitch black out.
[KIGGITH] I didn't ask
for your opinion, did I?
-Get to it.
-Fine.
But before that, answer this.
What is it that has you so
worked up tonight, Kiggith?
That you'd ditch the hideout
we arranged for you?
[KIGGITH] Do you not hear
its claws against the ground?
[both gasp]
[chuckles]
Approaching near-silently,
with its fangs bared.
It's ready to pounce.
That's the stride of a spider.
-[birds chirping]
-[rooster crowing]
♪
[RUTI]
I go to sleep at night,
and wake up to sunrise.
The small joys in life.
♪
[grunting]
[grunts]
[creaking]
♪
[RUTI] Morning stretches
complete. Nice work.
The brightness
of the morning sun.
The satisfaction of exercise.
The gleam
of a freshly-cleaned home.
Simple pleasures I once thought
unnecessary as a Hero.
But I get to experience them
now thanks to "New Truth,"
the new Blessing
created within me.
Almighty Demis
had nothing to do with it.
Perhaps it's inaccurate
to call it his blessing,
but more a power
born of my free will.
At least,
that's what I believe.
[clatters]
Now this is the slow life.
Morning, Mr. Crawly Wawly.
[squawks]
Hm?
♪
[water gurgling]
[TISSE] The herb farm is really
coming along, isn't it?
Yep. But I couldn't have
done it without you, Tisse.
Are you sure about that?
Because I feel like
I haven't helped at all.
This is still very new
to me, you know.
That's why two heads
are better than one.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
An herb garden, huh?
I knew you were looking
to settle down,
but I never expected you
to think of something
like this.
Adventuring's the side gig.
But this project
will be my main job.
Growing and tending
herbs full-time.
You're putting in this work
to help Red, right?
[RUTI]
That's a big part of it, yeah.
But mostly, doing something
that didn't involve
swinging a sword around
seemed nice for a change.
[chuckles]
It does, doesn't it?
Um, about last night--
[TISSE]
Okay, time to get to work!
[gasps] Oh, look!
Figure it out, Mr. Crawly Wawly
[chittering]
Problem is the soil.
It's stone cold.
To the touch.
Why is that?
This might require
another pair of eyes, milady.
We should ask Red
to take a look.
[RED] Seems like there's
cold mold growing under there.
[RUTI]
Cold mold?
Like the stuff
that grows in caves?
Yeah.
It absorbs heat
from anything nearby.
Normally only the huge colonies
can cause problems
to adventurers,
but on farmland,
all it takes is a trace amount
for a disease to kick in.
What you'd expect
starting a farm.
-Things go wrong.
-Hm.
The good news is,
because you noticed it
and came to me immediately,
there's still time to fix this.
-[Ruti gasps]
-Ready to get to work?
Hm.
Whatever it takes
to save the herbs.
-Huh.
-[chitters]
♪
[RED]
Great work.
If the chemicals we sprayed
get rid of the cold mold,
the herbs should
recover in time.
[RUTI]
Hmph.
All we can do now is hope
for the herbs to pull through.
They will.
-Thanks to your help.
-Hm.
She's come a long way,
hasn't she?
[RED]
You said it.
Doing everything she can
to save those little guys
she's caring for.
To think we wouldn't have seen
this side of her as the Hero.
Because she's finally free
to live at her own pace.
So what about me?
[RED]
The two of them will be fine.
-[birds chirping]
-[rooster crowing]
[TISSE]
My name is Tisse.
A member
of the Assassins' Guild,
and an assassin
with a nefarious plan
to oversleep this morning.
Huh?
[gasps]
[screams]
[TISSE]
Um, good morning?
Good morning. Any plans today?
[TISSE]
Tending to the herbs, I guess.
I took care of that already.
Anything else?
♪
[TISSE]
Nothing in particular.
Well, that's good.
Because I want you
to accompany me today.
Accompany you for what?
[RUTI]
A very important task.
♪
[TISSE] Huh? Why are we having
breakfast like always?
[water splashing]
[TISSE]
And now we're taking a bath?
[RUTI]
Tisse.
[TISSE]
Um, yes?
You like baths.
[water splashing]
I...like 'em enough
to write my own
review book, sure.
[RUTI] My brother's cooking
is the best in the world,
isn't it?
[TISSE]
Very best, sure.
-[water splashing]
-So you get it.
[TISSE]
Get what?
Hook, line, and sinker.
[chuckles]
[TISSE] [gasps]
What is happening right now?
[indistinct chatter]
[TISSE]
An important task, huh?
Did you know?
My brother bought
my hairpin right here.
That's very nice of him!
It's cute!
Yep.
♪
[TISSE] [gasps]
Of course!
Hairpin is code for
"This is a crime scene, Tisse,
stay on your toes!"
I mean, got it!
I'm on the lookout!
Hm.
-[TISSE] Hm.
-[townswoman 204A screams]
-Hm.
-Runaway drake!
[squawking]
Guess I'll stop it.
No.
-I'll handle it.
-Wait.
Won't you make it
a bigger scene?
[thuds]
Now, sit, boy.
[whimpers]
[TOWNSMAN 204B]
Out of all the trainers
it's nearly killed,
she's the one it listens to?
She drew even more attention,
like I said.
♪
[RUTI]
The scenery here is pretty.
And it's always
so nice and breezy.
[TISSE]
It is very nice, yes.
[TISSE] So, is this where
the important task is?
[TISSE] [gasps]
Milady?
-[RUTI] You there.
-Hm? Huh?
[RUTI] There's a monster
lying dormant underground.
It needs to be dealt with.
[MALE FARMER 204A]
Huh? What was that, miss?
It's just a friendly warning,
from someone here to help.
[MALE FARMER 204A]
Huh?
-[gasps]
-[male farmer 204A grunts]
[male farmer 204A gasps]
[explosion]
[both shrieking]
So that's what she meant!
This earthworm would've
devoured any human in sight
after its hibernation!
-Hi-yah.
-[chopping]
-[thuds]
-[gasps]
Oh. Wow!
Pardon me, ma'am,
but are you Zoltan's
very own strongest
adventurer, Miss Ruti?
Anybody could've
executed that chop.
Think of me as your friendly
neighborhood adventurer.
You just split a man-eating
earthworm in two
with your bare hands.
[gasps]
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[TISSE]
From the farm to the theater.
What happened to the task?
The lead actor has gotten
some rave reviews lately.
This should be fun.
Says here the play's based
on the story
of a knight and a bandit
who fall for the same lady.
Stop it, both of you!
Haven't we been through
so much together?
Oh, it's getting good,
isn't it?
Isn't it?
-[gasps]
-[indistinct chatter]
[whimpering]
That sword has been cursed.
Toss it before
it's too late for you.
Come try and take it from me!
Ever since I got
my hands on this blade,
my acting's been
nothing short of divine!
Like, hell, I'm just gonna
throw all my dreams away!
[female actress 204A screams]
Possessed by a devil of arts.
He sacrificed his own lifespan
in exchange for this talent.
-[gasps]
-[indistinct chatter]
I'm your friendly
neighborhood adventurer.
Very ordinary.
Plot twist!
The rift between the bandit
and knight all started
because of a devil hiding
in the mix this whole time!
Huh?!
The play isn't over just yet!
Use this!
O, brave adventurer!
I beg you! Please rescue
the person I dearly love!
[both grunt]
-[male actor 204A grunts]
-[swords clanging]
[male actor 204A grunting]
And now she's drawing
even more attention.
This will be a play to remember
for everyone in the audience.
-[swords clanging]
-[male actor 204A groans]
[dog howling]
You sure gave out
a bunch of autographs.
I wasn't trying
to draw attention.
I hear rumors of a production
starring the Adventurer Ruti
that's premiering tomorrow.
Yay.
-[OPARARA] Order up!
-[chuckles]
[TISSE]
Can't be too surprised.
You're well-known
around Zoltan these days.
And it's not like
the attention is malicious.
I know. But today
was important to me.
What's so important
that you had me
tag along with you, anyway?
♪
[sighs]
[TISSE]
Oh. Not often do I see her,
look so down.
The day's not over yet.
We can turn this around.
-Can we?
-Yeah.
So, how are things lately?
Anything or anyone
bothering you?
Ooh, well, for starters,
I am a little worried
about how weird
you've been acting.
[RUTI]
It's hopeless.
Hey. Talk to me,
what's the matter?
[sighs]
Huh?
Something's been
on your mind lately,
but I don't know what it is.
Today was supposed to help you
decompress for a bit.
-[gasps]
-[RUTI] A day to relax,
A day where I treat you
to your favorite oden,
and you tell me whatever's
bothering you.
All of that, just for me?
[RUTI]
Yep. But it didn't go too well,
I think.
[TISSE] Everything
from the drake to the demon
seemed inconsequential
to someone as strong as her.
Causing a scene
was the last thing on her mind.
She acts funny sometimes.
Still...
You're a very nice person,
milady.
But all I do is make
a mess of things,
leaving you to clean
up the aftermath.
Is that what's been
bothering you today?
♪
I tried to be ordinary.
I used the most
ordinary skills.
I even said
I was very ordinary.
[TISSE] There's
your problem right there.
Really?
Cheer up! If you ask me,
you're much better off now.
Are you implying you thought
I was worse than this?
Huh?!
Let's just say I nearly
tore my hair out
when you tossed that knight
off the bridge.
Who?
[both laugh]
[TISSE]
Thank you very much, Miss Ruti.
No need to worry about me.
It'll all be over by morning.
-What are you doing?
-Huh.
[WOLF]
Airship's been looked over,
so we're finishing
up the report.
[paper rustling]
Omit any information on Tisse.
Redo the draft.
Sorry, Kiggith, but there's
no way that's happening.
Bottom line is,
it's important stuff.
If Tisse's here in Zoltan,
it could only mean
that the airship
belongs to the Hero Ruti.
And omitting
crucial information
would be an act of treachery
against Cardinal Ljubo.
[slashing]
[thudding]
[KIGGITH] I can't
have you reporting this.
Even if it means treachery
against the Church,
my score to settle with Tisse
is far more important.
♪
[crow cawing]
[paper rustling]
[KIGGITH]
Long have I waited for you,
my old enemy.
♪
Didn't expect you here.
Kiggith Viper.
[KIGGITH] Brings back
old memories of our days
training under Master
when I see you standing
beneath the moonlight.
Tisse Garland.
The Assassins' Guild
has only one way
of dealing with deserters.
Meaning you know
what comes next.
I trust you're aware of that?
[scoffs]
That bloodlust in your eyes.
No wonder our master saw
great potential in you.
Which means killing you now
would be a crying shame.
What are you implying?
[KIGGITH]
Come on.
Leave Zoltan behind
and join up with me.
You have what it takes
to work at my side, Tisse.
And what about the two men
who were with you?
I killed them.
Just like I'd kill anyone
who would dare stand
between me
and my greatest prey.
Well, that makes it
much easier for me
to cut you down
right here and now.
Traitors of the Guild
will not walk away unpunished.
Rousing words.
Yet all I see is a girl lacking
an assassin's
thirst for murder.
As your fellow student
and mentor,
I'll show you what it means
to be an assassin.
♪
[thuds]
-[slashing]
-[grunts]
♪
-[swords clanging]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
[laughing]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
♪
Not bad.
But how will you
deal with these?
[gasps]
♪
[rumbling]
[gasps]
-Huh.
-More where that came from.
Dodge them, and this airship
will get torn apart
piece by piece.
What good is the airship to you
if it's not in one piece?
That technique is reckless
and kills innocent bystanders.
Master forbade us
from using it!
See, that right there
is what I'm talking about!
You lack the thirst for murder.
Our Blessing grants us
the right to fight and kill
without any restraint.
That realization is why I left
the Assassins' Guild!
-[grunts]
-[explosions]
-[clinks]
-[gasps]
-[explosion]
[swords clanging]
[TISSE]
He's changed.
He used to be more faithful
to his Assassin's Blessing
than I was.
So why did he end up like this?
-Huh.
-Got you!
[explosions]
Huh?
[groans]
[groaning]
[thuds]
It's over.
Any last words before you die?
Wait.
You want answers, don't you?
I'm in the employ
of Cardinal Ljubo
of the Church.
Kill me,
and you're in the dark.
[gasps]
How could you spill
your client's name like that?
I'll tell you everything
I know.
I swear it on my life,
all right?
So, please,
just have mercy on me.
Ljubo wants to utilize...
[TISSE]
He refuses to uphold
even the most fundamental rules
of being an assassin.
This sniveling man is nothing
more than a dirty murderer!
[groaning]
Ah...
♪
[TISSE] Kiggith could only
adhere to his Blessing.
He had no will of his own.
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
Miss Ruti.
-[RUTI] Are you done here?
-[TISSE] Yes.
He was a rogue assassin
who deserted
the Assassins' Guild.
[RUTI]
I see.
[TISSE]
This isn't well known,
but the Guild
isn't as authoritarian
as people seem to think it is.
You're allowed
to turn down missions
you don't want to take.
You're even free to retire.
Through Blessings,
we walk as assassins,
and need sanctuary.
Somewhere we can
help each other.
That sanctuary,
and that organization,
is the Assassins' Guild.
Really? The reputation
makes the Guild seem scary.
Smart marketing, is all.
Even down to the rule
about declining
unreasonable missions.
Call it a strategy of sorts.
We can't be disciplined
if we have just cause.
We're all just doing everything
we can to live out our lives.
So you're not allowed
to murder without a reason?
No, of course not.
Think of the chaos we'd cause
if we killed left and right!
♪
At the end of the day,
it's still killing.
And I made you, a Hero,
help carry out
an assassination.
And is that why you wouldn't
talk to me about it, Tisse?
I know you want to live
a peaceful life here in Zoltan
more than anything! But me?
♪
My Blessing.
My fate being tied
to the cruel life
of an assassin.
I'm honestly not sure
I even have the right to stay
by your side anymore.
♪
Assassin or not,
you're still my close friend.
Stay by my side.
As you are.
And if it'd truly
make you happier,
you can always choose to become
a slow-life assassin.
What in the world
is a slow-life assassin?
Huh?
That's a funny thing to say.
No matter what happens,
I'll continue to support you
whenever you need it.
Who cares if we're Hero
and Assassin?
I'll do it because I want to.
[sniffles]
Miss Ruti.
[crying]
[RUTI]
Starting today,
let's open up
more to each other.
[TISSE]
Okay. You're right.
Thank you!
♪
[LJUBO] Huh. Unusually
shoddy work for Kiggith.
This doesn't even tell me
the airship's location.
He'll need to lead me
there in person.
Nevertheless,
this at least confirms
the airship's existence.
Summon Van back to me.
[MALE UNDERLING 204A]
Understood.
No, wait.
On second thought, I'll go.
[MALE UNDERLING 204A]
Need you go personally?
The trip to Zoltan will proceed
once I meet with Van.
[LJUBO] Noble aims
need time to cultivate,
and at long last,
mine has come to fruition.
[ESTA] The Church's warriors
can no longer keep up
with the way Van fights.
Our party is in shambles.
We should descend.
What reason is there to leave
if I can keep fighting?
Because if we don't leave now,
then they'll all die.
Is that a problem?
Are you serious?
Only the Hero is destined
to save the world.
Therefore, any sacrifices
made under the Hero's Blessing
are justified
for the greater good.
That's where you're wrong.
[MALE SOLDIER 204A]
Flare sighted!
Prepare to descend!
[VAN]
Cardinal Ljubo's orders?
At last, finally
my real adventure can begin.
Do you have no gentle
words of support
to send off
our fallen comrades?
[VAN]
Glance not behind, Hero.
From texts on Heroes of old,
and words I cherish most.
The Hero is a symbol of hope.
He need only march onward.
Wonderful words,
are they not, Esta?
♪
[TISSE]
Raise your arms for me.
Hm.
♪
The farm needs tending today,
which means...
Time to get some work done!
♪