♪
[door creaking]
[ALBERT] Huh.
Welcome back, Theodora.
I go by Esta now, Albert.
Esta, right.
Still getting used to that.
♪
[ALBERT] The former
demon lord's airship?
That's correct,
the very same vessel
Ruti took to Zoltan.
Should Van be granted clearance
to into the territory
and should he by chance run
into to Ruti while he's there,
I fear what would happen next.
Under no circumstances
can their paths cross.
Hmm.
Therefore, I ask you head
to Zoltan in my place.
Red must be informed
of these events.
You can count on me.
This new hero.
You think he's the real deal?
Mmm.
He was appraised by the saint.
Leadership from the Church
have recognized him, too.
So I would surmise
that he must be.
But he is nothing like Ruti.
All we can do is wait,
and see what becomes of him.
Then we wait.
Leave it to me, Esta.
I'll do whatever I can to help.
[chuckles]
[ESTA] Thank you, Albert.
I'm glad you're here with me.
♪
[door opens]
Good morning, Nao.
Good day to you, Red!
I'll take some of your
newest concoction, please!
The dragonshroom essence,
you mean?
That's the one!
One sip and I feel
on top of the world!
One sip, huh?
It's not every day you swing
by the shop this early, Nao.
Gotta be ready
to go for the festival!
If I waste time,
the day will slip
right by before I know it!
[chuckles]
I'll throw in an extra
for Mido and Gonz.
[NAO] Thanks, Red!
♪
All. Set.
[RED] Rit! Time to go!
[RIT] Coming!
[chuckles]
♪
Thanks for waiting!
How do I look?
Great!
The cape is a nice touch.
You look rather handsome
yourself in that coat!
You ready for the festival?
[chuckles] And what about
that one order from Zeff?
All packed. Right here.
Great! Let's go!
[indistinct chatter]
Wow. Everyone is so festive!
Today's the Drake Rider
and Saint Licinius's
Solstice Festival,
based on an Avalonian legend.
Even the famously
laid-back people of Zoltan
are out living it up
from sun-up to sundown.
[GONZ] Aye! Red!
[BOTH] Hmm?
[gurgling]
Wild party, huh?
[RED] Not sure
about that, Gonz.
Lively energy though!
Yeah, because I'm here!
Today is all about enjoying
the day off at the festival!
[laughs]
[gulping]
[Gonz laughs]
[GONZ] Tomorrow's about
sleeping off the hangover!
You're taking today
and tomorrow off?
[GONZ] Come on,
you gotta play hooky
-the day after a party!
-[gasps]
Yeah, you tell 'em, Gonz!
The Ultimate Man!
Ultimate?
It's all downhill from here
if I don't step in now,
as the adult.
-[munching]
-[RED] Tanta.
Can it wait 'til after I eat?
Real men will be up bright
and early for work tomorrow!
[TANTA] Boo, there's too much
to do today!
-Like, look at that!
-[BOTH] Huh.
[crowd cheering]
♪
[RIT] This is how
the Drake Rider
and Saint Licinius's
Solstice Festival
goes in Zoltan, huh?
[TANTA] Is it different
where you're from, Rit?
Way more formal
and stricter back in Loggervia.
Formal how?
[Rit chuckles]
[RIT]
The objective is the same.
The Drake Rider and Saint repel
the winter demons.
But it's great how each region
does it differently.
[TANTA] Well,
here we sing, dance,
and party like no tomorrow
to chase
the winter demons away!
It's the Zoltan way.
[GONZ] It really does a number
-on you.
-[all gasp]
No choice but to get wasted
and then sleep off
the crappy hangover!
He may have a point.
We do deserve a day off!
-Huh. Come on, Rit.
-[noisemaker honking]
[IN UNISON] Take the day off!
Take the day off!
-Take the day off!
-All right.
-I understand.
-[gasps]
Place will be a ghost town
by tomorrow anyway.
No work then. Guess you win.
[giggling] Yay!
-[IN UNISON] Yay!
-[gasps]
We want to take off, too.
Um, "we"?
Okay.
[squeaking]
[sighs]
Of course you guys do.
First Tanta, and now Tisse
and Ruti have gone rogue on me.
-Huh.
-You're enjoying this?
[chuckles]
A little bit.
[giggles]
♪
[Oparara grunting]
Refreshing, wouldn't you say?
As long as you're comfy.
-[groaning]
-Everything okay?
Are you ready to leave already,
Oparara?
Like hell! If that's a joke,
it ain't funny, Megria!
I'm just gettin' warmed up
is all, nothin' more!
Warmed up? In that case!
-[MEGRIA] Here.
-[screaming]
[steam whistling]
Hmm. Hmm.
That smells great.
[groaning]
♪
[sighs]
Here you go, I got you a drink.
Lifesaver!
[both gulping]
[BOTH] Aah!
[RED] Day off
for you two as well?
-Yep!
-[sighs]
Adventurers' Guild is closed!
Sounds mighty nice.
Working the festival.
Need to take the cart out
to feed folks, right?
I figured while my oden's busy
gettin' real tasty stewing
and simmering
in the pot
right about now... [inhales]
I'd do the same.
Came down to sweat it out
and detox.
[TISSE] Smart!
You can really bring out
the best flavors in oden
depending on how long
it's simmered.
-[squeaks]
-[WILLIAM] Hold it, you!
[LEON] Let me go!
I didn't do anything!
-[ALL] Hm?
-[WILLIAM] Hey!
I know for a fact you saw me
standing right there, kid!
I was here before you!
Quit cutting in line!
-Seriously?
-[scoffs]
-And what's going on here?
-[gasps]
[WILLIAM] This kid cut in line.
No! I was here first, you liar!
You're just trying to get
in front of me!
Oh, come on!
I could step right over you
if I wanted, shrimp!
Don't you dare mock me!
[screams]
-[gasps]
-Ugh.
Huh. [gasps]
-[LEON] Ademi.
-That sure would've been messy.
Huh?
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[ADEMI] Forgive him
for losing his cool there, sir.
[WILLIAM] Hm.
The thing is,
his Blessing awakened recently,
so he's still a bit unstable.
-[ADEMI] Now, apologize.
-[gasps]
[LEON] I'm sorry!
Don't be.
I got a little carried away,
too.
Can't blame a guy for his
Blessing's impulses, can I?
[RED] "Can't be blamed for your
Blessing's impulses," huh?
[RIT] Ademi's really grown up,
hasn't he?
He sure has.
[YARANDRALA] Red!
[BOTH] Huh?
Everyone! [laughs]
Who's that bouncy-yell-y person
over there?
-[YARANDRALA] Hello!
-[gasps]
[RED] Yarandrala!
-[RED] Over here!
-Hmm.
[YARANDRALA] Rit!
Huh.
[laughs]
The town's truly livened up
today!
[Red laughs]
Glad to hear you're having fun!
There are so many stalls set up
that I've never seen before!
Behold!
One said this sacred mask
was made by
a legendary great sage!
-[Yarandrala laughs]
-Just wondering,
but exactly how old
are you, again?
Huh? Huh.
Some might say I'm a lass
of around 50 years young!
-[laughs]
-Aw.
That's an elf joke.
♪
Come one, come all! Huh.
-[gasps]
-Hey, what's the deal, boss?
When were you gonna tell me
you hang around
a Kiramin elf, huh?
-A Kiramin elf?
-Yeah.
It's an elf thing.
We refer to one another
by the land we were born in.
So that makes me a Zoltan elf.
I'm amazed that
you can tell where she's from.
[OPARARA]
We just kinda know, okay?
Even among high elves,
Kiramin are somethin' special.
How do you expect
little old me,
a country bumpkin
from the middle of nowhere,
to talk to her?
I'm sweatin' buckets over here!
Oparara, was it?
Uh. Yes, ma'am!
[YARANDRALA]
While I do hail from Kiramin,
don't let that discourage you
from treating me
as you would anyone else.
Huh?
Act natural.
Yarandrala's an old friend
of mine from way back,
which makes us
all friends here.
Yeah, I guess you're right!
Since introductions
are out of the way,
I am eager to taste
some hearty oden!
Uh, well you've come
to the right place!
So! What'll it be, then?
How 'bout fresh octopus,
just in today?
Or fish balls!
I'll take an order of those.
Add some burdock, too.
I'll take the octopus
with egg, please.
You can make mine
the same as milady's dish.
And four orders of grilled
fish paste too, please.
And I think I'll have octopus,
the burdock, egg with fish
and squid ball,
beef tendon and radish.
And what else?
Throw in the fish cake,
seaweed, and jelly strings.
Oh, plus a cake pouch!
Did you add the whole menu?
Huh?
It all just sounded
so good, okay?
And for you, Yarandrala?
My turn next?
Your order sounds lovely.
Octopus and burdock for me.
Add some fish balls, too,
please.
Mm-hmm. Right away!
[OPARARA] Order up!
[IN UNISON] Let's eat!
Add this here and it'll taste
twice as good!
That's not a part of our order.
It's too expensive!
It's from the lady to my left.
-You ordered this?
-Sure did.
[RED] Wait, wait!
I'm the big brother here,
I can't have you paying for us.
You are talking to a hotshot
B-ranked adventurer.
My bag is more than
a little heavy, as you can see.
[RED] Is that
what I think it is?
Wasn't it you who told me
to live as I wanted?
Well, right now,
I want my brother and friends
to enjoy some yummy oden.
[chomps]
No way that's all hers.
-Step in, please.
-Hm?
I completely agree
with milady's decision.
Hmm.
Ha. [chomps]
♪
All right. Thank you, Ruti
[RUTI] Mhm.
[IN UNISON] Mmm!
[all laughing]
-[RED] Mm.
-[RIT] Oh.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
-[gasps]
-[YARANDRALA] Huh?
[Godwin groaning]
Huh? Now, now. Come here!
You are Zoltan's
representative, right?
-[MISTROM] Act like it!
-[groans] Mercy!
-[Godwin grunts]
-[YARANDRALA] A representative?
We stopped
by the zoogs' village
while gem-hunting,
and learned from their elder
they were struggling
due to a lack of trade.
Oh.
[RED] Godwin will be
handling that from now on.
Man, thanks for looking out
for your old pal.
I owe ya big-time, Red!
You just keep an eye out
for any monsters
that are on the way there.
Are you sure
this guy can be trusted?
What are you talking about?
Trust is my middle name!
He's a piece of work,
but he's capable, at least.
Put those skills of yours
to use.
They're depending on you
to make amends.
[chuckles] Huh?
Well, looks like it's time
for the grand finale.
Oh, let's see!
♪
[panting]
[grunting] Come on!
Follow the script!
You're supposed to be
good and dead by now!
[sobs]
Huh. Is that you,
my beloved lady warrior?
-Who's that?
-[RUTI] No idea.
Move! You're blocking my view!
-[Otto chuckles]
-He's staring right at you.
[RUTI] Hmm?
[TISSE] Hmm?
Isn't that the same guy
you threw off the bridge
on the way to Zoltan, milady?
-Oh!
-[OTTO] Huh!
-Doesn't ring a bell.
-Oh!
Otto is my name,
fair warrior-maiden!
Please remember it! [gasps]
Huh?
[RED] Hold on.
That you, Danan?
[thuds]
Long time no see!
-A very long time indeed!
-So.
I hear you'll be staying
in Zoltan for a while.
Huh?
What happened to your arm?
[DANAN] It's not a big deal.
It looks like a big deal!
Are you okay?
[DANAN] I'm fine.
If you ask me, it's not
the comeback I had in mind,
but the doc kept nagging me
about taking it slow.
[YARANDRALA] So much for that!
[DANAN]
This counts as taking it slow.
[Otto groans]
[gasps]
Cursed winter demon!
Show yourself, wretched fiend!
Whoops. I guess that's my cue
to get back in there.
♪
[crowd cheering]
[crowd applauding]
♪
[male villager 203A chuckles]
Man, I wish there was a way
to make some easy coin.
[WOLF] Hidden treasure
we could plunder, maybe.
[MALE VILLAGER 203A] Right?
[KAI] Now you're talking!
Say like, an airship?
-Huh.
-Get outta here,
keep dreaming, pal!
Worth a shot.
[all laughing]
♪
Hey, so.
Thanks for today.
I had a good time.
Hm?
Me too. It was fun.
[Ruti chuckles]
[RED] But, there's still
one thing left to do.
Huh?
[Ruti chuckles]
May I have this dance with you?
Dance with you?
Are you sure about this?
Hmm.
Can't remember
the last time I danced.
Maybe before your induction
to knighthood?
I won't be the best partner.
It's not about how good
you are at it.
It's about having fun
and just dancing.
Right?
[RUTI] Hmm...
♪
Right.
Is this okay?
What is it?
Am I really allowed
to feel such warmth?
Can I be this happy?
Of course you can, Ruti.
[gasps]
[RED] Everyone's able
to laugh and celebrate now
because of all the pain
you've endured to get us here.
Now it's your turn to be happy.
Only fair, don't you think?
[RUTI] Thank you.
Big brother.
[wind whooshing]
Would you like some wine?
No. Thank you.
-[wine gurgling]
-What's your assessment
of our hero?
Exceeding my expectations
in many ways.
Is he now?
Van's growth is proceeding
at a vastly rapid pace.
The records you gave to me
prove as much.
However, wouldn't that make
sending him to Zoltan
a waste of time
when we could focus elsewhere?
You speak as though
you've been to Zoltan yourself.
A brief venture
with little gained.
It has no economic
or historical significance.
It's a dead end.
Even if the demon lord's
airship is there,
what purpose
would it serve for Van?
An answer to ascertain, yes.
Information is of the essence.
Should the airship be found,
both your assistance
and knowledge will be required.
[LJUBO] I'm counting on you.
Don't forget that.
Escarlata.
The Festival went by so fast.
Good thing it'll be back
next year.
And will you be there with me?
'Course I will.
[RIT] And after that?
Then, too.
-[Rit giggles]
-[Red chuckles]
♪
Huh.
[gasps] Is that for me?
Go on, open it.
Huh?
Oh, Red.
[RED] Well, you know,
I couldn't get you
that blue sapphire
from the settlement,
but this is my way
of promising you
I'll get you that ring,
someday.
[chuckles] You picked out
an engagement necklace?
-Uh-huh.
-Hm.
-Huh?
-[RIT] Can you?
Oh. Yeah.
♪
Do you like it?
[RED] Hmm. I love it.
-You are beautiful.
-Huh.
Oh!
[RIT] No fair.
What's wrong?
You pick out
a beautiful necklace
for me to wear,
then you tell me to wait
for a ring as well?
I just...love you!
Hm.
I hope you know,
it's your fault for turning me
into a hopeless romantic.
You're not off the hook!
How can I fix it?
Here's an idea.
We will...sleep in together.
And I'm the unfair one?
♪
[KAI] There's no information
about the airship anywhere.
We need to turn up the heat.
Lay low for now.
It'll be much harder
to make a move otherwise.
[KAI] Huh?
Huh? Tisse!
-Hm.
-Let's go! [grunts]
[clanging]
Go after them.
-[squeaking]
-[Kai and Wolf panting]
This is ridiculous.
All that talk about laying low,
and then she pops in?
I know something's up
in this town.
[Kai grunts]
[groaning]
[KAI] What the heck
is all this?
♪
-Huh.
Hm.
Oh, crap. Huh?
♪
[gasps]
[Kai and Wolf panting]
♪
Are you...
[grunts]
[gasps]
♪