[RED] Now that we're all here,
let's go over it again
one more time.
[RED] Albert,
has the Church officially
recognized Van as the Hero?
[ALBERT] Yes. Van's Blessing
was appraised by the Church.
He's under
Cardinal Loo-bo's watch.
Therefore, he officially
operates as the Church's Hero.
It's hard to believe
there's another.
Well, Red?
[RED] If the Church
appraised him,
there's no reason
to doubt their assessment.
[RED] What I don't understand
is why he hasn't
shown up until now.
I don't either.
You know,
speaking of the Church,
remember when we visited
the Great Last Wall Fortress?
That's where we met
Theodora, isn't it?
Time flies.
If memory serves,
this was before my arrival.
[RIT] Which makes me wonder.
Do you think the Church
was aware of Van back then?
Two Heroes existing
at the same time is not normal.
If that were the case,
they would've acted.
But they did nothing at all.
So it makes more sense
to assume they didn't know.
[RED] Hmm.
[RUTI] Hmm.
[DANAN] Well! No point in
thinking about all that, right?
Come on. Didn't you say
that Van kid's on his way
to Zoltan right about now?
[chuckles]
[YARANDRALA] Tell us,
what all does the Church
know about Ruti?
Nothing, as far as I've heard.
In regard to
the former Hero's campaign,
they were unaware of it
to begin with.
Yeah. Because we were
making sure of that.
But Ruti took out
two of the generals,
and Theodora defeated one more.
[RED] The war with
the demon lord's army
is at a stalemate.
Safe to say Avalon
is at peace again,
more or less.
Honestly, Ruti's absence
shouldn't cause
too much of a problem.
But the appearance
of a new Hero
complicates things.
We're in a tight spot.
Say he finds out the Hero Ruti
walked away from battle.
I don't imagine he'll be happy.
[RIT] There has to be a way
to prevent them from meeting.
[DANAN] What about a disguise?
She'll just give herself away.
Milady sticks out too much.
-Hm.
-[chuckles]
I have a suggestion.
Van's only objective here
is to take the airship, yes?
In that case,
how about the three of you
depart Zoltan for a while
until matters settle down?
[ALL] Huh?
I recommend going
to a tourist destination.
And don't you worry,
I'll look after the herb farm.
Leave managing the shop to me.
Go relax! You deserve it!
I guess we're heading
out of town, you two.
Yep.
I will send word
if anything comes up.
Just in case,
I'll stay here, too.
Stay and you'll risk
running into the Cardinal.
[DANAN] Believe me,
I don't like it either.
But I've got a real bad feeling
about this situation.
Heck, even if I
do run into him,
I can say I got kicked out
of the Hero's party.
I've got a good reason
right here.
See, no arm!
You're stronger, Danan.
Stronger than
when you had both arms.
Huh? [laughs]
[RED] You are.
[DANAN] I am?
[RIT] Probably.
[DANAN] I am! [chuckles]
[birds chirping]
[RIT] Quiet town, isn't it?
[RUTI] Saint Durant Village.
[RED] Named after the man
who saved it from total ruin.
[RIT] This village
had a hero of their own
who shone on the battlefield?
[RED] Not even,
the guy was a lumberjack.
But he was unmatched.
[RUTI] Lumberjack.
[RED] When a horde
of hill giants attacked,
the initial settlers here
lost everything.
So Durant built homes
for them all in one night
and was celebrated as a savior.
Wow. He sounds incredible.
[ALL] Huh.
♪
[RIT] So this strapping fellow
is Durant?
[RUTI] "Durant the Hero."
"Many a hero
has killed a century
of foes before and after,
but only one hero
has ever built a century
of homes in one night.
Here he is in the process
of logging a big ol' tree.
Behold his glorious pectorals."
What do you think?
We've never come
to a tourist spot
-like this before.
-Nope!
I'm excited.
-[door bell jingles]
-[door opens]
[RIT] Wow.
Interesting, aren't they?
Apparently,
nobles and merchants
frequent the area.
This village
is a major trading hub.
Pardon me, but those items
are for display.
So, uh...
Gifts, anyone?
-Me!
-Please!
[GRAMPA LARRY] Here's your key
for the duration of your stay.
[RED] Thanks.
Well then, take care now.
-Let's check it out!
-Yeah.
[door unlocks]
[door opens]
[RED] Whoa!
[RIT] Whoa!
[RIT] All this to ourselves?
[RED] I like the ambiance.
[birds chirping]
-[grass rustling]
-[sighs]
Milady and the others.
They must've reached
the place by now.
Once this whole thing
dies down,
why don't we go
on a little trip ourselves?
[squeals]
[fire crackling]
[birds chirping]
Pretty.
Wonder what they mixed in
to get it to glow.
Lovely.
Hey, Red.
Do you wanna buy a few more
on the way home?
Yeah.
Yarandrala and Tisse
would love this.
And Mr. Crawly Wally, too.
[church bell tolls]
[ALL] Huh.
♪
Van the Hero.
Huh.
He should be getting
to Zoltan soon.
[RIT] I hope
he leaves just as quickly.
[RUTI] I know
better than anyone
how bad a Hero's urges
can become.
Even if he wants
to stay for a while,
his Hero's Blessing
won't let him.
♪
[fire crackling]
[RUTI] Let's enjoy
this moment while it lasts.
I couldn't agree more.
[RED] Hey. You want me
to make some milk and honey?
[RUTI] Yay!
♪
[bird screeching]
[RIT] The food there was great!
That weird leafy thing
was surprisingly sweet.
That's snakedrunk leaf.
From what I recall,
it's normally used
to treat indigestion.
My guess is
it grows around here.
-[Kate crying]
-[ALL] Huh.
[KATE] Ow.
[RIT] Oh, no!
Are you hurt, miss?
I'm fine.
[KATE] Ow.
Quick, the cottage.
-Hm.
[Kate groans]
[RED] Kate.
This is where it hurts, right?
[KATE] Yes.
Where's the village doctor at?
We don't have one.
That settles it, then.
I run an apothecary,
so while I'm not a doctor,
I know a thing or two
about illnesses and injuries.
Could you just answer
a few questions?
[KATE] Sure.
To start, have you experienced
strange symptoms lately?
Not that I recall, no.
Huh. Hold on, a few days ago,
I did cut my leg on accident.
[RED] Your leg?
[KATE] Yes.
[KATE] It happened during work.
I was a bit careless.
Is that when your limbs
started trembling, too?
Huh?
Well, I guess.
Now that you mention it.
[RIT] Did you
figure something out?
Think so.
Seems she was exposed
to poison from the cut.
Poison?
[RED] Magic can at least
suppress the pain,
but it won't
get rid of the toxins.
Hm?
[whimpering]
[KATE] What do I do?
Medicine.
Will that help Kate heal?
Yeah.
I can fix something up
with the herbs I have.
Does that sound good?
Yes! Thank you, sir!
I will need time
to put it together
with my Blending skill.
Ruti.
While I'm working here,
can I trust you
to pick up an herb
that I'm missing
for the concoction?
Sure. Just tell me
which one you need.
Snakedrunk leaf.
You mentioned it before.
The chef should be able
to tell you where it grows.
If I have that,
it'll be much easier for me
to replicate
the actual medicine's effects
without any difficulty.
On it.
[door opens]
Rit, you stay here
and take care of Kate.
Use your magic
to give her some pain relief.
Right.
[rain splattering]
♪
[sighs]
[rain splattering]
[door creaks open]
-[door shuts]
-Welcome back, Ruti. [gasps]
[RED] What happened to you?
Don't worry, I just
slipped down the valley.
Here. Found the herb.
Perfect! Thanks.
We should be
good to go with this!
[chuckles]
I'll have someone
escort her home!
[door opens]
[door shuts]
♪
[RED] You'll make
a full recovery,
but keep taking the medicine
as a precaution.
[KATE] I don't know
what I would've done
without your help!
[door creaks open]
-Huh?
[gasps]
[RED] What's with
all the people?
[indistinct chatter]
Since I didn't know
where she lived,
I asked around,
but they all just
tagged along.
[MALE VILLAGER 1]
Thanks for helping our Kate!
[MALE VILLAGER 2] This here's
the village's secret recipe!
[MALE VILLAGER 2]
Try it out sometime!
[FEMALE VILLAGER 1]
Take this, too!
[MALE VILLAGER 3]
And this!
[MALE VILLAGER 4]
Now, now! Don't be shy!
[Red chuckles]
Thank you all so much.
♪
[RED] I'm beat.
Doing okay out here, Red?
[breathing slowly]
♪
[both chuckle]
[RED] Dinner's ready!
[RIT] Yay!
[RUTI] Yay!
So, uh. What's on the menu?
A dish called curry.
It's a traditional dish
passed down
from Durant's homeland,
apparently.
That new recipe you got?
It sure does
have an intense color.
[Ruti sniffs]
Smells super strong, too.
So.
[RED] Rit. Why the getup?
What? We're on vacation!
And the floor down here
is pretty warm and toasty.
To be fair,
I did hear something
about this region being
a geothermal territory, so.
Uh?
What's your excuse?
Forgot my swimsuit.
[RED] That explains nothing!
[chuckles]
Know what? Never mind.
[RED] Let's eat.
[BOTH] Hm.
[Rit munches]
[Rit giggles]
These spices really have
a kick to them, don't they?
This is great!
Tastes even better on bread.
Delicious.
[RIT] Ah, I'm so nervous!
We haven't heard a peep, huh?
Almost feels wrong
to relax like this.
Us being there would
just cause more problems.
Let's trust the others
and wait.
♪
[RUTI] Seconds, please.
[birds chirping]
[clattering]
-Heya.
-Huh.
[ALBERT] Danan.
[DANAN] How's it looking?
They haven't arrived yet,
it seems.
[DANAN] I see.
[thuds]
Here you go. I brought gifts.
Thanks,
but what's the occasion?
[ALBERT] Wow.
This looks really good.
[DANAN] I made these, you know.
[gasps]
Oh, did you now?
[DANAN] Are you gonna eat?
Of course!
[gulps]
[munches]
Oh!
-It's not bad.
-What?
[ALBERT] No, I meant that
in a good way!
Listen up, Albert.
[whimpers]
Since I wasn't clear
the first time,
let me spell it out!
[whimpering]
[chuckles]
I seriously owe ya my life!
Thanks for the save!
[crying]
You're so very welcome!
[DANAN] We'll get along
just fine!
[ALBERT] We will!
[DANAN] Now, eat up!
[ALBERT] I will!
[waves crashing]
[VAN] Zoltan, at last.
We finally made it, Van!
-Yes!
-Hm.
It doesn't have the capacity
for the puny boat?
What a poor excuse for a port.
[pukes]
[VAN] Is something funny?
Just, I recall
a former comrade of mine
saying something similar.
[VAN] A former Hero, as well?
I would be honored
to meet them!
That is not possible.
How could I forget?
There is no time to spare
while the world
is on the brink.
And so the detours
will have to wait.
[LJUBO] Precisely, Van.
[Ljubo gagging]
[TISSE]
That's Van the Hero?
He's nothing like milady.
[indistinct chatter]
[VAN] Is our guide delayed?
Or, worst case,
he went and got himself killed
for taking a rather
unscrupulous offer.
Then what now?
Without their knowledge,
we're stuck here.
I propose we search
for the vessel ourselves.
[LJUBO] No,
nightfall is approaching.
We'll discuss our next steps
at the inn, Van.
Ugh!
♪
[RUTI] That's the end
of my turn.
[RIT] Nice!
Wyvern grandmaster!
[knocking on door]
Hold on, our friend's here.
-Our friend?
-Hmm?
[squealing]
[RED] Didn't expect him
to pay a visit.
[RIT] Clever spider, isn't he?
That's Mr. Crawly Wally.
Looks like
Van has arrived in Zoltan.
No major issues
for the time being.
Good to hear!
[squealing]
Huh.
[RIT] Huh?
You want to play
Wyvern Races, too?
[squealing]
[RED] He really can do it all.
[indistinct chatter]
♪
[TISSE] My name is Tisse.
I'm a member
of the Assassins' Guild.
And tonight, I'm deviously
blending in as a maid.
[TORNED] Welcome, hero!
It's a pleasure
to meet you, sir.
I'm Torned,
the mayor of this town.
[indistinct chatter]
[TORNED] Uh, sir?
Excuse him.
The Hero is recovering
from an exhausting trip.
[TORNED] The voyage, of course!
I'll return later
and leave him to recuperate,
for now.
I must say,
I don't approve
of this behavior.
If it is the airship
that upsets you,
then rest assured.
I have an idea.
[FEMALE MAID] Sir Hero,
this entrée
is our chef's specialty--
A Hero has no need
for your entrées!
[gasps]
[FEMALE MAID 206A]
Please forgive me!
Huh?
With me. Outside.
Yes, gladly!
I wanted to step out myself.
♪
[sighs]
[ESTA] I won't ask you
to be friendly,
but is it that hard
to tone down your displeasure
for the sake
of those around you?
Are we having
this discussion again?
I am beginning
to sincerely wonder
if you enjoy my nagging.
[VAN] Indeed I do!
I have much to learn
as the Hero still.
So talking to a wielder
of a high-level Blessing
inspires me.
[ESTA] Then why
haven't you listened
to a single word I've been
telling you since day one?
Others deserve
empathy and respect.
Inside that building are people
who organized this event
to celebrate your arrival.
Oh?
And who asked for them
to do that?
Who asked for them?
Can you not comprehend
their desire
to express their admiration,
their gratitude to you?
[VAN] The sole purpose
of a Hero
is to save its people,
because the Almighty
deemed it so.
There is no need
for admiration or gratitude.
You may see it that way,
but not everyone else does.
Don't you get it?
You are a symbol of courage
that moves people
to resist evil.
And in the future,
when the people
will look to you
to lead them to battle,
you must not ignore them.
Understand
and value their hearts.
I agree.
Granting people
the courage to fight
is a primary role of the Hero.
The masses
will march into battle
with the Hero
leading them forward.
And the masses will die.
What?
Such is the will
of the Almighty.
Naturally,
they will heed their call,
and courageously
perish one by one.
Admiration and gratitude
do not belong.
But Faith in the Almighty Demis
is paramount.
Truly, Van?
You would ask the people
who come to fight in your name
to simply die in battle?
Without any care
or remorse for their lives?
Yes.
The purest faith is martyrdom.
Emotions sully it.
That's my Hero! What a man!
-[door creaks open]
-Huh?
[LJUBO] Van.
We will be
leaving here tomorrow.
Huh?
[LJUBO] The people of Zoltan
can look into the airship.
In the meantime,
we shall do
what only we are capable of.
And what will we be doing?
It will require
some backtracking,
but there is an island
inhabited by a salt dragon.
Tomorrow,
we will exterminate it.
[VAN] What creature is this?
A dragon of stagnation
and destruction.
So a sworn enemy of the Hero?
A salt dragon
will not attack people
if they keep their distance.
Its presence
is largely innocuous.
Does it really need
to be exterminated?
I believe it
to be the perfect fodder
to strengthen Van's Blessing.
It's said the salt dragon
is in possession
of the Fairy King's
beloved treasure,
which it stole and hoards
for itself to this day.
Having it won't hurt us.
-Even so--
-Be at ease!
Killing monsters
and assuming the treasure
is morally correct.
The Church's scriptures
declare this to be true!
Do not make enemies
wherever you step.
You will come to regret it,
Van.
Eradicating agents of evil
is the Hero's duty.
So long as wicked
thrives in this world,
I will be its adversary.
Come. Join me inside
before the food gets cold.
I hear that seafood
pairs quite well
with Zoltan's wine.
[VAN] I'll return to the inn.
[LJUBO] The Almighty
created wine
for their followers to enjoy.
Bear in mind,
to refuse it
would be unfaithful.
-[VAN] Unfaithful, you say?
-Huh.
Must've imagined it.
[water gurgling]
[grunts]
♪
[thuds]
[SALT DRAGON] Have you come
to steal our treasure?
Have some shame,
you filthy thieves!
[grunts]
-[thumps]
-[grunts]
[LJUBO] Cheeky creature.
[SALT DRAGON]
Begone, humans!
[grunts]
[groans]
-[grunts]
-[roaring]
[VAN] I, Van the Hero,
slay all evil!
[roars]
♪
[chuckles]
[creaking]
[thuds]
[grunts]
Yay! You did it, Van!
Yes!
[VAN] I see.
[VAN] The Fairy King's shield.