[screaming]
Martial Art,
Swallow's Approach!
[grunting]
-[sword slashing]
-[grunting]
[gasps] Van!
Stay out of this, Lavender.
Foolish girl.
[groaning]
♪
[LAVENDER] You're in my way!
I'll kill you!
[screaming]
[swords clanking]
[grunting]
[LAVENDER (DEMON)]
Van. Van!
[electricity crackling]
Such power is beyond
what we feared.
We cannot let her
break free as she is!
So we must end this here!
[electricity crackling]
[rumbling]
[grunting]
[swords clanking]
[VAN] Lightning of Judgment!
[grunts]
[thumps]
[LAVENDER (DEMON)]
Don't touch him!
[RUTI] Sacred Shield.
♪
[screaming]
Martial Art, Great Whirlwind!
[wind gusting]
-[grunting]
-[sword shatters]
♪
[shattering]
[thudding]
[metal clanging]
Victory is mine!
Healing Hands Mastery:
Reflection!
[chuckles]
Sure took you long enough.
♪
[gasps]
-[slashing]
-[grunts]
[groaning]
[thuds]
[coin clinking]
Never call it early.
You held the power of the Hero?
Yeah.
Ruti infused the ornament
right before our duel.
Face the facts, Van,
ultimate skills can cancel
each other out.
♪
Deceit.
Wrong, you're fundamentally
mistaken there, Van.
[RED] On the surface,
you might have thought
this was a duel
between Guide and Hero.
But take all of that away,
and this was a fight
between two men.
Blessings alone weren't enough
to decide the outcome.
That's a small part
of what makes us who we are.
[trembling]
-Damn you.
-Embrace it, Van.
It was that emotion
that was making you waver.
You get it now?
[gasps]
Think back
to our mission together.
Didn't it feel like
you lost to me somehow?
You knew the kid
would have been a goner
without our help.
Because of your pride,
you felt undeserving
of the gratitude
she showed you.
For the first time
in your life,
you felt what
we call disappointment.
It feels...heavy.
Sure does,
now get some rest.
And we'll talk later.
[LAVENDER] Van, wake up!
Open your eyes, please!
[groaning]
[LAVENDER] Van!
[VAN] Lavender.
Where are we?
[door slides opens]
-Hey! Sleepyhead.
-[groans]
Sleepy-what?
Release me this instant,
you good for nothing bum!
Can't you see Van needs me?
A curse on you
for keeping us apart!
[grunting]
Keeping you from going
berserk, you mean.
Now just pipe down and deal
with it for a bit, okay?
[growling]
I'll deal with you, all right!
Desperate times
call for magical mending.
How do you feel?
Far less than heroic.
Sure does suck getting
your tail handed to you
by your sworn nemesis.
Is that your attempt
to humiliate me?
-[Red chuckles]
-[gasps]
[grunts] Tell me.
What became
of Albert and Ljubo?
Recovering from their wounds.
Albert's regained
consciousness,
while Cardinal Ljubo
is laid up in bed.
[LAVENDER] Curses!
[RED] Took a while before he
was treated for his injuries,
so he'll definitely
need more rest.
[sighs] Because of me.
[groans]
[gasps]
What now, princess?
I Think some fresh air
will do us good.
Guides and Heroes only, sorry.
Hurt Van again,
and it's over for you, bum!
As in, goodnight forever!
So say your prayers!
You hear me?
Say something!
[door closes]
[RED] How's your Blessing?
[VAN] It has returned to me.
I can feel
the impulse once more.
I have no desire
to see another in pain.
Good to hear.
[knife clinks]
♪
Considering you went
through some pretty heavy
emotional turmoil,
it must've made your Blessing
go berserk.
Turmoil? I see.
♪
Perhaps, disappointment
was a stranger to me
for so long.
[VAN] Am I now
unfit to be a Hero?
♪
[RED] Van, a Blessing by itself
doesn't turn you into the Hero.
Don't go around saying
you're the Hero,
act like one.
I do not understand.
Asking yourself what it means
to support and protect others.
Listening to guidance
when offered.
Wavering and worrying...
and yet always striving
to be a better person.
That's a Hero in my eyes.
♪
So then...what is my role?
Good question!
I'll be honest with you,
you're one ignorant guy.
You lack perspective,
and your sword's sorry.
Hey, I reject that!
Name one strategy you have
that isn't brute force.
One counter,
and you hit the ground!
[gasps]
[groans]
-[RED] Keep it up.
-Huh?
Don't change a thing.
Understand your emotions
and accept that you're human,
first and foremost.
That might make you
weaker in the moment.
But trusting your friends...
that gives purpose
to your sword.
Strength will return to you.
And that is when
you will be the truest Hero.
The truest Hero.
[RED] First off,
try listening to Esta's advice.
Talk to her about anything
on your mind,
not just about being a hero.
[VAN] After all I've done,
would she welcome me once more
as a travel companion?
So long as you desire
to be the Hero,
and learn from your mistakes,
you can lean on her
as your personal guide.
My guide?
She may not have the Blessing,
but that doesn't stop her
from looking after you.
And believe it or not,
no one in their right mind
would cast their lot
with a brat like you
if they didn't care.
Huh.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Wicked thing to say.
And yet, I do deserve it.
♪
Say, Gideon.
Would you join my party
if I asked you to?
Sorry, kiddo,
but I'm already Ruti's Guide.
And I don't plan
on teaming up with a new Hero.
What a shame.
If only our paths had crossed
before I awakened.
♪
Van...
when did your Blessing change?
How did you know?
While we fought the demonic
army on the battlefield,
you never made
a single appearance there.
Too busy living in a monastery?
Does nothing escape you?
Yes...the change.
Like Ljubo,
I had the Cardinal's Blessing.
Until, one day,
I awakened anew.
I believed it was a miracle
Lord Demis granted me.
I renounced it all.
To embrace my calling as Hero.
I see.
So you had to suddenly
change paths
and lead a completely
different lifestyle.
-That sounds rough.
-Very.
[RED] Your future's bright,
and all in your hands now.
[RED] Are you leaving soon?
[VAN] Of course I... Huh.
Hm. Wait.
On second thought, let me...
consult my party first.
♪
[sighs]
-[VAN] Lavender.
-Huh.
[LAVENDER] You're back!
No funny business, right?
Hm, I'm fine.
Really.
[gasps]
Lavender...you've been
faithfully by my side.
Thank you.
Huh.
[giggles]
Don't mention it.
♪
[birds chirping]
[knocking on door]
[ESTA] Pardon me.
How do you fare...Cardinal?
[sighs] Hand over
my drinks and cigars,
then ask me how I fare.
[chuckles]
You men of the cloth.
Van visited recently.
Came practically begging
for my forgiveness.
As if that wasn't enough,
he asked me to rejoin him.
[ESTA]
And what was your answer?
Acceptance, of course.
Troublesome as he can be,
no matter his sins,
that boy will save
the world one day.
My divine ambitions made real.
And all I'd need is a Hero.
[chuckles]
Even so, his words
of regret were most surprising.
Esta, you surely put him
up to it, didn't you?
No, I did nothing of the sort.
Van's had a true
change of heart.
He seems to be truly remorseful
for what he's done.
He even sought forgiveness
from Albert and the mayor.
♪
[ESTA] Imagine their surprise
to see him bow his head.
All thanks to that Gideon,
a divine addition to our party.
But a man can dream, can't he?
Theodora Dephilo?
-And who might that be?
-[Ljubo chuckles]
[LJUBO] You're a terrible liar.
[kids laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[FEMALE CHILD]
You're really good at this.
[yawns]
[MALE CHILD 207E]
Sir Eero!
Not another step,
you're scaring them!
What do you want?
♪
Their fear is my fault alone,
forgive me.
Please.
[gasps]
Your home, the lives you live.
If only I'd asked
about that earlier.
Huh.
Come pway wit us, eero!
[chuckles]
[VAN] Sure.
[Male Child 207E chuckles] Yay!
-Let's pway, Mister Eero!
-Huh?
[all laughing]
[TANTA] All right,
whose turn is it again?
[indistinct chatter]
[LAVENDER]
Ugh, this is torture!
Someone tell me
why Van has to go around
apologizing to people?
I mean, this was his idea,
Lavender.
Sure, but it's like
watching my darling
become a totally different
person before my eyes!
Are you falling
out of love with him?
Don't be ridiculous!
If anything, I love... Huh.
[groans]
This wasn't supposed to happen.
Guess what,
our mead is top notch.
Think booze will cheer you up?
Oh, you bet it will,
bring on the snacks, too!
Atta girl,
libations coming right up!
[chuckles]
[crickets chirping]
All done.
-[LAVENDER] Hey.
-Huh.
[RED] Oh, hey, what a surprise.
[LAVENDER] Just so you know,
I hate your guts.
And I'll never,
ever forgive you
for raising your sword
to Van, got it?
Well, he cut me first,
so we're even now.
[blowing raspberries]
-Take this!
-[grunts]
[sighs]
Huh.
Hm.
Wait, is this...
a blue sapphire?
As thanks
for looking after Van.
Huh.
[RED] How did you find this?
[LAVENDER]
Rit and I had some drinks,
and she mentioned
her good-for-nothing lover
needed some rock
for an engagement ring.
I could get my hands on gold
if I asked the fairies,
but if it's what you want.
How do you archfay do it?
Find the answer
at my altar, boy.
Sure, sure.
[scoffs]
Don't screw this up!
♪
[RIT] Huh?
[RIT] Where is that fairy?
[LAVENDER] Waiting for you!
[LAVENDER] Let's get drinking!
[RIT]
Someone's in a better mood!
♪
[sighs]
Hm.
[MOGRIM] Aw!
Seen my fair share
of sapphires,
but this one sure
takes the prize.
Her ring will sparkle like
the moonlight with this rock!
[RED] Really? [chuckles]
[MOGRIM] Not in a rush, right?
[RED] Nope.
Slide this way, Red.
I'm closin' up shop
for the day.
[Mogrim chuckles] Mink, dear!
Get my jeweler's tools for me!
Er, no, no, never mind!
Stay put, I got it!
What are you doing, pal,
don't be shy now!
[chuckles]
♪
[crickets chirping]
[crackling]
There.
Hey, Rit,
come on down for dinner!
[RIT] Okay!
[door opens and closes]
[sighs]
[RIT] Oh?
Did I miss an important date
or something?
You didn't, don't worry, Rit.
Huh?
Hm.
[clearing throat]
There's something
I wanna give you.
[gasps]
[Rit gasps]
[RIT] Is that a blue sapphire?
No, you didn't, Red.
-Listen!
-I'm listening?
If you don't mind, could you...
[gulps]
No.
I mean.
Huh?
My love.
May I have your hand
in marriage?
[gasps]
[RIT] Red.
I'm in love with you, Rit.
From the moment
I first saw you,
that fateful day in Loggervia.
♪
Even though
I may not be the hero,
and I'm far
from the knights or kings
that princesses deserve...
Rizlet.
I promise to make you
the happiest woman.
And promise to make you
breakfast every morning
until the day I die.
Nothing would make me happier.
[crying]
Hm.
♪
[RIT] I should be
the one asking you.
Darling, would you
please marry me?
Marry me because
my heart belongs to you.
Because even
when we grow into old
and wrinkly grandparents,
spending the rest
of my life with you
is all I can ever ask for.
[RED] Rit.
♪
[chuckles]
[RIT] Pinch me.
Am I dreaming?
[crying]
Red!
♪
[RED] I love you.
[ALL] Congratulations!
-[chuckles]
-Thanks a lot, everyone.
Look at you now, Sir Guide.
Together at last
with your beloved.
Glad I'm in Zoltan
to witness you thrive.
-How kind!
-So are we!
-Rit, dear.
-Huh?
My friend will have a lifetime
of happiness because of you.
So, thanks!
-[munching]
-[Danan gulping]
Who would have thought
that years later,
our friends would be engaged?
People change.
In fact, you've changed
some yourself.
[ESTA] Huh?
[chuckles] Any stories you can
share of Esta's former life?
I would love to hear them!
That does sound insightful.
[LAVENDER] Pass!
[DANAN] I'll fill you in.
[YARANDRALA] Apparently, our
Esta saw Ruti and the others
as threats back
when they first met.
[ESTA]
We are not talking about that!
[RUTI] Big Brother.
[ESTA] Albert, tell us more
about yourself instead!
We wanted to congratulate you.
You know...again.
[squeaks]
Tisse.
You two are absolutely
glowing together.
It's like a miracle
in front of me.
Oh, Ruti.
All worth it in the end,
to hear that from you.
Yep.
Suppose it's my turn next.
[TISSE] Next?
[DANAN] Come on, the kid
needs more meat than that!
Please don't,
I have no need for entrées!
[ALBERT] Good idea!
[LAVENDER]
Tasty mead, here I come!
[giggles]
[sighs]
Now let's plan mine.
[YARANDRALA] Looks like
you need to hustle, Esta.
[ESTA] Wait. What?
[RED] The Hero's journey
isn't an easy one.
I know that all too well.
Hm.
[RED] But, unlike Ruti,
Van desires not the slow life,
but to fight.
I don't have it in me
to tell him that he's wrong.
♪
[RED] Before he
goes on his way,
I think I'll continue
to play my part
in Van the Hero's story
a bit longer.
♪
[RED] Van.
[wind rustling]
-[wind whooshing]
-[birds chirping]