[sneezes]
[chuckles]
Here, drink this.
One sip should pick you
right up
and have you feeling
warm in no time.
Thank you.
♪
[fire sputtering]
-[Rit blowing]
-Funny...
Remember
when you used to drop by
for this very drink
back in Central?
Yeah.
It's the best.
You know, Gideon,
I am truly relieved
to see you safe
and healthy again.
Didn't mean to worry you,
by the way.
Mm-mm.
Now, now.
If anything, I was more
surprised to learn you two
are living together.
[giggling]
I do have a proposal.
Come with me.
Back to the Kingdom
of Kiramin.
We refuse.
[Rit and Red chuckles]
Allow me to explain.
[YARANDRALA]
As you know, Kiramin
is the biggest city-state
on the continent
of Avalon.
It lies
in the cold northern plains,
but magic keeps the weather
spring-like Kingdom-wide.
Most of all, while high elves
are by no means perfect,
we would never betray
our friends and allies.
Where is this coming from?
It never made sense to me!
How could they do
such a thing to you, Gideon?
Why were you banished
from the Hero's party
when you always worked
so hard for everyone?
[RED] I couldn't keep up
in battle anymore.
Even with my abilities,
it was inevitable.
[YARANDRALA]
"Inevitable"?!
You honestly
believe that drivel?!
The worth you bring
to the party
is not your only value!
I wanted to adventure with you
because you are my companion.
Even through difficult times,
I wanted to be
your pillar of support.
Disowning a member
of your own party,
because he has "stopped
being useful" to you.
I cannot accept that!
Look, I hear what
you're saying, Yarandrala.
I do.
And, Rit!
You are a Loggervian princess.
A hero who has
fought countless battles!
And yet, you were forced
to leave your home,
which you fought to protect.
You are kinda right.
Though I actually
left on my own volition.
Nobody was in the wrong
for that.
Be that as it may,
I wouldn't have let you set off
alone without support.
[RIT] Yarandrala.
We're very touched
by your concern,
but going back
with you to Kiramin
is not an option.
[YARANDRALA]
Why?!
[RIT] If we intend to spend
the rest of our days together,
we'd rather be nowhere
else than Zoltan.
[RED]
It's our home.
Originally, I came here
because I thought
nobody would recognize me.
But now, my closest friends
are the people
of this community.
[YARANDRALA] And if you
are betrayed yet again?
Then we'll accept it.
[Yarandala surprised]
[RED] Whenever I'm invited
out for drinks,
I always say I'm not interested
if Rit can't come along.
Friends will dig at me
about it, but then turn around
and plan a family
dinner party instead.
Little things like that
make it worth it, you know?
♪
Hey. You're more than welcome
to come by and stay a while
in Zoltan.
-Me?
-Yeah, why not?
Come see what all
of the fuss is about!
The Kingdom of Keramin
will suffice, thanks.
[sneezes]
Starting to get
a little chilly.
How about another cup of tea?
-I have a better idea.
-Tisse?
I know just the place
that'll warm us all right up.
[YARANDRALA]
Now this is bliss.
[RIT] Nothing like a hot spring
to end the day!
[RUTI] Yup.
Relaxing.
And look.
Pretty.
I am so proud of you,
dear Ruti.
Thanks.
Decent water temp,
sunset view by the pool.
Guess this warrants
a nice review.
I rate it a solid ninety-five.
Where did it lose
the five points?
For its convenience,
it's too far to walk here.
True.
Now that you mention it,
we'll be arriving
at the gem giants' settlement
soon.
Wonder what they look like.
Word has it they gain
their energy
from the gems they cut.
How is that?
My guess is it has something
to do with how the gem giants
sustain themselves.
Sorta like how eating
is for you and me.
So, like food?
Yum!
[chuckling]
Can't imagine.
These creatures
will have the stone
you and Red
have been searching for?
Yeah.
We're hoping to strike a deal.
The Zoltatian glass Red brought
for one blue sapphire stone.
The artistry and style
in Zoltatian glass
can't be found anywhere else,
so he thinks
the giants will see it
as a rare delicacy.
That stone is as good as yours!
[giggles]
Where are Red
and that Mogrim fellow?
Mogrim hates baths
to begin with,
and Red's being considerate
and using the annex bath.
What?! He's over there
all by himself?!
That just won't do!
[Rit] Yarandrala!
Where are you going?!
[YARANDRALA] No need
to be a stranger, Gideon.
[RIT] Wait!
Don't just rush in!
[YARANDRALA]
We're all friends here!
-Come in. Join us already.
-[Red screaming]
So, I've been meaning to ask,
are you okay with this?
With what?
Red and Rit will soon
be husband and wife, milady.
Oh.
Rit's a nice girl.
I know she'll treat
my brother well, Tisse.
To be completely honest,
I always thought
she was the kind of person
I wanted him to marry.
Okay.
So it doesn't seem to make
you at all lonely?
The thought
of them being married?
[RUTI] I couldn't possibly
marry my brother.
So if Rit turns out to be
a wonderful wife for him,
well... that's good enough
for me.
If you say so.
And, if we can't wed,
we can just be lovers, then.
[RUTI] My brother
is a giving person,
so there's enough room
for two.
Rit can be his number one wife,
while I can be the one
who loves my brother most.
[Ruti shocked]
Wonder how he's doing
over there.
[water splashing]
[Red screaming]
What? You tryin' to get
those two lovebirds
to move in
with you and Kiramin?
Of course!
Imagine how much happier
and safer they would be.
Ah... Don't make 'em mingle
with you lawless high elves
up yonder in the cold,
they're much better off staying
right where they are with us
dwarves in Zoltan!
[Mogrim, Yarandrala scoff]
[RIT] I guess there is some
truth about dwarves
and high elves
not getting along, huh?
[RED] You said it.
[YARANDRALA]
Are those the gem giants?
Something seems off.
[GIANT CHIEF 202A] I'm ashamed
to say we have nothing
to offer in terms
of hospitality.
But please, make
yourselves at home.
[RIT] Thank you.
[RED] We're interested
in trading for a gem.
And we can offer
this Zoltatian glass.
[GIANT CHIEF 202A]
It's beautiful.
Truly valuable
for us as a species.
However...
Unfortunately,
we cannot make that trade.
We have no gems
to offer in exchange.
Come back here!
[RED] Here you go.
-For me?
-Mm-hmm.
[GIANT BOY 202A]
Thanks, mister!
[Giant Boy 202A laughs]
Hey, hey!
Look what I got!
♪
Curious.
[RED]
We've got more glass.
It's not much but, please,
help yourselves.
[giggles]
We musn't.
[RED] Please,
forget the trade.
[RED] The gems
are nowhere in sight.
Chief, let us help you.
If this keeps up,
you will all starve to death.
Think of your people.
Please don't play
with their food, milady.
Don't worry.
I've got it.
This should bring
their smiles back.
Very well.
We are truly grateful
for receiving such a blessing
in these trying times.
Our human, dwarven,
and high-elven comrades.
We promise you
an unchanging friendship,
until the day our tribe
no longer stands.
Why would Demis
create these strange
biological functions?
You mean how
they gain their energy
from cutting through gems?
Yes.
The Almighty
created this world.
Every living being was surely
crafted with a purpose.
[RED] Well, by slaying
gem giants,
humans can retrieve
the leftover stones
as spoils of their victory.
I suppose you could say
they were meant to be enemies
to fight in order to develop
our Blessings.
[RUTI] If that's
the Almighty's design,
then conflict is unavoidable.
But monsters exist to be more
than just fodder for Blessings.
That's what I want
to believe.
Right.
So do I, Ruti.
It's been ages
since we last cut our fill.
You have our heartfelt thanks.
So, what exactly
happened to your home?
[sighs]
This troublesome beast
has overtaken our settlement.
[YARANDRALA] What sort?
A gem-consuming monster.
It's called a gem beast.
[RED] It eats gems?
Different from us,
all gems and minerals
that are within
close contact of the beast
are turned into lead.
[RIT] Really?
[MALE GIANT CHIEF 202A] Yes.
[GIANT CHIEF 202A]
See for yourself.
[YARANDRALA] It seems
imbued with a subtle magic.
[GIANT CHIEF 202A] And it grows
more poisonous with time.
[YARANDRALA] If the lead
has contaminated
the region's groundwater,
that explains the tainted soil.
[RUTI] And may be why
the zoogs' forest is weakened.
[RED] We need to stop this
before the damage spreads.
[RIT] But Red, we've never
heard of this monster before.
What is your plan?
[RED] Historical records
may hold our answer.
There was a warrior party.
If I recall, I read
they fought with a gem beast
in the era of wood elves.
[MOGRIM] Out with it, so
how did these warriors slay it?
[RED] Thing is,
they never did.
[MOGRIM] They lost?!
[RED] Most of the wood elves
in the battle died,
and only a handful of warriors
even managed to escape.
[TISSE] Are you saying no one
has ever slayed that monster?
Some of our own defenders
have fallen.
Fight, and you might not live.
[RED] Maybe.
But we'll fight anyway.
[MOGRIM] This oughta be
the southern mine
the chief of the gem giants
told us about.
[RIT] Look around
and you can see
plenty of gems still here.
[RUTI] The beast may
show up to consume them.
[RED]
The thing's huge, apparently.
Even in a place like this.
it could be hiding anywhere.
We've potions
to spare, at least.
[Mogrim]
Hmm... Curious rock you are.
[RED] Mogrim,
try to stay close!
[MOGRIM] Yeah, yeah!
♪
It's coming!
[loud explosion]
[flame sputtering, roaring]
[thunderous crashing]
[Red] Look.
Lead!
[rumbling]
♪
[thudding]
[roaring]
So that's the gem beast.
[Red] Ruti?!
[RUTI] Sacred Shield.
[glass shattering]
It's breaking.
[deafening explosion]
[RED] Ruti!
[sighs]
[roaring]
Now! Go, Thorn Bind!
[shouting]
[shattering]
[clanking]
[thudding]
[RED] We've gotta
find its weak point!
[clanking]
[swishing, thudding]
Soft landing
for something that big.
Given its size,
it could've made
the entire mountain crumble.
Is it propping up
its whole body with magic?
[RUTI] That's my spell.
[thudding]
[roaring]
My Thorn Bind?
[grunting loudly]
[Yarandrala] Impossible!
[RUTI] Sacred Shield.
[rapid firing]
[thudding]
Be careful.
Any magic we throw at it
is sent right on back.
Truly a troublesome beast,
indeed.
[roaring]
[flame roaring]
And it uses fire
and water magic all at once?
What is this Blessing?
Wait,
could the gem beast be...?
[RED] Using multiple
Blessings as a power-up.
That's why it can reflect
physical and magical attacks,
and support its massive weight.
In which case...
You don't mean...?
[roaring]
[explosion]
[RUTI] Go!
Sacred Shield!
[clattering]
Did ya get him?
-Nope.
-[RIT] What now, Red?
We cut down
its Blessing level.
Do that, and we win.
Then we need...
Medicine from the wild elves.
[RED] Yeah.
It's our only shot.
[RIT] The same tonic
we used on Ademi?
[RED] Right. But making
it drink this won't be as easy.
Leave that to me.
[RED] Good luck.
[YARANDRALA] Thanks.
[YARANDRALA] O origin of mana.
Ruler of all creation.
Great spirit
of the mighty tree!
[shattering]
[YARANDRALA] Gotcha!
[clinking]
[shattering]
[thudding, rumbling]
[RED] Without the use
of its Blessings,
this thing can't even stand?
[explosion]
Phew. Sure didn't expect
to mine this hefty beauty
inside the guts
of that gem beast.
Stroke of luck, right?
I'm glad you got
the earth crystal you came for.
Well, shucks!
Reckon my missus' childbirth
should go mighty smoothly
now that I've got
my mitts on this!
But on the other hand...
[sigh]
[RIT] Wow.
What a view!
[RED] Yeah.
[MOGRIM] Here I come, darling.
Daddy's home!
[Mogrim laughing]
[All chuckling]
About my offer.
Will nothing I say
convince you to leave?
Sorry.
But my home
is right here in Zoltan.
Where Rit and I can
settle down together.
[YARANDRALA] And you can
find that nowhere else?
For the first time in my life,
I'm living for myself.
That's wonderful.
Well, then! That's that,
so I might as well
get comfortable here.
Wait, you're staying?
My curiosity is piqued
by this place
that brings you joy.
That's great!
Welcome to Zoltan!
So, Ruti?
Is that okay?
Of course.
[RIT] Time to get
everyone together,
and throw a welcome party!
[MOGRIM] Hey!
I'm gettin' older by the day
down here!
[VAN] Ljubo.
I am strong enough
to combat the demonic army.
As this world's hero,
I must take my place
on the front lines now.
Dear boy,
you mustn't rush things.
We should plan everything out
and execute it flawlessly.
I've a new challenge prepared
for you that requires
your attention.
Head out with Esta and slay
the monster that awaits.
-Come in.
-[door opens]
-[LJUBO] Proceed.
-[UNDERLING 202A] Sire.
There have been reported
sightings of the former
demon lord's airship.
[VAN] And to where
does this vessel fly?
[UNDERLING 202A]
It was supposedly headed
for the remote town of Zoltan.
Right here.
Kiggith should have returned
from his scouting assignment
by now.
Find him and have him head
to Zoltan at once.
-[UNDERLING 202A] Sire.
-[door opens]
Ljubo-!
Build your strength
and level up
your Blessing for now.
As hero, that is paramount
above all else.
[LJUBO]
Precisely.
Adhere to our plan, Van.
Cull a few beasts with Esta
and wait for your time.
I will make sure Zoltan
is thoroughly investigated.
[Van pouts]
[LJUBO] Now.
No need to pout.
I'll draft up
a brand-new strategy
for you while you wait.
Great!