♪
[VAN] 'Tis my solemn vow
to obey your guidance.
And dedicate my whole being
to walking
the path of the Hero.
♪
For this, the will
of our Lord Demis.
Hey.
[gasps]
-Very good, I've found you.
-Huh.
♪
Ljubo. And a guest?
More than that.
Our newest comrade.
My name is Escarlata.
You may call me Esta.
Esta?
The masked knight
of those heroic tales?
Slayer of Demon-General Altra
of the Water?
You're Lady Esta?
Just Esta.
No need for formalities.
Very well, then.
I am Van of Flamberge.
Just call me Van.
Beg your pardon, but Flamberge?
Yes. The eighth prince
stands as the sole survivor
of the Demon Lord's invasion
against
the Kingdom of Flamberge.
A prince of fallen country
turned Hero.
This can only be the will
of the Almighty.
As our crossing of paths,
guided by Lord Demis,
my team is honored
to have you, Esta.
[ESTA]
The honor is all mine, Van.
Come. Introduce yourself.
[chuckles]
Lavender's the name!
Van's confidant
and close partner,
isn't that right?
With that,
our party is thus complete.
The tale we forge will be
one of triumph and victory
where the Hero prevails.
♪
[GODWIN] Go on now,
I told you where they are,
so can you please
cut me loose, lady?
Why should I?
So I can be without a guide
if your words prove false?
Keep your promises, at least.
[fire crackling]
[YARANDRALA] Is it really true
you know the Champion Rit?
How about the man with her?
[GODWIN] Sure, the three of us
are real close.
If that's the case,
do you mind escorting me
to where they reside?
Yeah, whatever you say.
But before that, how about you
and I have some alone time--
[grunts]
[groaning]
They always said
to mind the booze
and watch out for hot women,
so this is what my butt
gets for doing neither.
Less talking and more walking.
Yes, ma'am.
[growling]
[YARANDRALA]
Good day to you, sir!
We're adventurers,
come to meet old friends.
[MALE GUARD 9A]
Adventurers, eh?
[chuckles]
[growling]
Come right in!
Thank you.
[chuckles]
[GODWIN] [sighs] Tight security
you got here, Zoltan.
Hold on.
♪
-[chuckles]
-[grass rustling]
Hm.
[bird screeching]
[chuckles]
[RED]
You okay, Ruti?
[RUTI]
Fine!
♪
Someone's chipper.
Yep! This is a first
for me, after all.
[RED]
First?
My prior adventures
have always been for service.
I was the Hero then.
But this is the first time
I've taken a peaceful journey
with my brother as only myself.
Who knew...
a simple hike
through the mountains
could be so joyful.
Ruti.
[chuckles]
[RED] The four of us are headed
to the mountain range
called the
Wall at the World's End.
And unlike our travels
as a Hero's party,
there aren't any battles
in store for us today.
Just a lowkey, quiet trek.
[MOGRIM] What're you
standing around for?
-Hurry up!
-[RED] Okay!
Who votes for a quick break
after this?
-[RIT] Yeah!
-[RUTI] Sure!
♪
-[sighs]
-[MOGRIM] Listen, boy.
You're a mad bunch of kids
to want to hike the Wall
when there's so many others
who wouldn't scale those peaks
if their life depended on it.
Much less
for an engagement ring. [sips]
Whatever it takes to get
my hands on a blue sapphire.
It's the only stone
that matches
the color of Rit's eyes.
[MOGRIM]
Oh-ho?
They're rare stones,
but I'll bet the gem giants
probably have a supply.
And I hope that
they might sell me one.
I'll only give
an engagement ring once.
So it has to be perfect.
[giggles]
Do you really mean
all of that, Red?
Yeah, of course, I do!
Save it for the honeymoon,
ya lovebirds.
[RED]
You're one to talk, Mogrim!
You joined us for Mink, right?
Are you already married,
Mogrim?
Guess that news slipped
the old noggin!
My missus is pregnant, y'see.
[gasps]
Wonderful!
Wonderful, indeed!
The good doctor said
it might come down to surgery
and taking the child
out of her belly.
I'd do anything to ensure
my wife is comfortable
for the big day,
but all I'm good at
is hammering
and chipping away
with my tools.
Gave it some thought,
and figured I could carve her
a knife out of earth crystal.
Does it have
special properties?
Its blades are famous
for being so sharp
you don't even realize
you've been cut!
Reckon that should ease
her burden during the delivery.
Earth crystal
is hard to come by.
If we find the gem giants,
then we'll find
our sapphire and crystals.
I'm mighty grateful to you all
for allowing this old dreamer
to tag along with you.
Everyone here is thinking
of someone, I see.
-So am I.
-Huh?
[RUTI] My big brother
has traveled all over,
and faced countless dangers
for my sake.
You've been so selfless
and supportive,
and yet I've never once
offered the same to you.
So, now it's my turn.
I'll support you
each step of the way.
Counting on it.
[giggles]
[rustling]
Hang on.
Smells like some goblins
are afoot.
Ambushing unprotected travelers
for food and their valuables.
I would've liked
to avoid fighting,
but so much for that.
-Huh?
-[swords clanging]
[grunts]
[clanging]
[screaming]
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
-[slashing]
-[blood splattering]
How's the sword feel, boy?
My finest work, isn't it?
[Mogrim grunts]
-[thumps]
-[blood splattering]
[goblins groaning]
[thumps]
Hm?
[RIT]
That's all of them, right?
[RUTI] From what I can gather,
coast is clear for now.
-[MOGRIM] Hmm.
-[RED] What is it, Mogrim?
It was a long time ago now,
but I'm certain
I crafted this spear.
Did you?
So that means
whoever was the wielder
fell prey to the goblins.
[MOGRIM]
Hm.
[RED] This world
is rife with violence.
There isn't
a single person here
who can live
a life free of battle.
The Almighty Demis
grants a Divine Blessing
to all living things.
And the scales of power
tip in favor towards anyone
who battles and slays someone
who has a Blessing.
-I've been thinking.
-Huh?
I've rejected my old life
of endless fighting.
Was it wrong of me
to turn my back on that?
[RED] Ruti has the most
powerful Blessing of all.
The Blessing of the Hero.
Absolutely not.
Don't ever regret
choosing yourself, Ruti.
Your life is yours.
But...is it?
[electricity crackling]
[RUTI] Is me living my own life
really so wrong?
[SHISANDAN]
Indeed.
You must fulfill your duty
as the world's Hero.
The Almighty and all humanity
won't allow the Hero
to lead a peaceful life.
And if the Almighty
won't grant me my own life?
♪
[birds chirping]
[YARANDRALA]
This is their home?
[GODWIN]
Well, shucks, no one's in.
I guess those two
must've skipped work
to sneak out on a date.
[YARANDRALA]
A date to where?
How should I know where?
I held up my end of the deal,
so let me go!
[MALE GUARD 9A]
Hold it right there!
Thought you could slip by me?
[GODWIN]
Do I know you, sir?
Cut the act, Godwin!
Rumor had it you
broke out of prison,
but to have the gall
to waltz back here?
You're mistaken.
This fine gentleman is friends
with Rit and Red, you see.
[MALE GUARD 9A]
Don't make me laugh!
-He's a crook!
-[gasps]
This criminal attacked
our Champion Rit
with the help of demons!
He abducted the child
she and Red took
under their wing!
He's no friend!
-Is that so?
-[Godwin gasps]
[YARANDRALA]
Did you betray him as well?
O-Okay, so, we may have
gotten off to a rocky start,
but never in a million years
would I betray my friends!
[grunting]
[whimpering]
Hear me out, please!
-[grunts]
-[bangs]
Whoa, whoa, time out!
-[screams]
-[thumps]
-[GODWIN] Oh, my hero!
-[grunts]
Good grief. So what have you
gotten yourself into this time?
I'm the victim here, all right?
That scary Yarandrala woman
thinks I'm an enemy
of Red's for whatever reason!
Yarandrala?
Traitors must be
brought to justice.
O great monarch
of the forests of old!
The crown ruler of mana.
Origin of all life!
♪
[rumbling]
[roars]
♪
Huh.
[TISSE] Oh, boy, this escalated
super-fast, yep!
Hey, are you crazy?
What are trying to do,
wipe out the entire town
-with that thing?
-[TISSE] You're not helping!
[Godwin grunts]
If Zoltan is under attack,
it's my responsibility
as an adventurer
to protect my home!
[slashing]
♪
[TISSE]
Keep still.
-[thuds]
-[squeaking]
-[grunts]
-[MISTROM] O polar winds,
O life-stealing chill!
Blizzard!
-[wind whooshing]
-[creaking]
[gasps]
Hm.
About time you showed
your face, Granny,
er, I mean Lady Mistrom!
Someone we can trust?
She used to be Zoltan's mayor.
Even the Guild's brass think
she's something special.
Enough flattery,
I'm a retired old coot.
Look, there's more important
things to worry about.
-[shatters]
-I'll stop her.
Can I count on you
to cover for me?
Yes, of course.
♪
[shattering]
[thumps]
♪
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[clinks]
[groaning]
Tell me, who are you?
Red and Rit's ally
and close friend.
Do not lie.
Just ask them yourself
if you truly don't believe me.
They left for the Wall at the
World's End this morning.
Hm?
And why take a journey there?
Because Red is searching
for a gemstone
to engrave in the ring
he's giving to Rit.
A ring?
[gasps]
You mean an engagement ring?
I do.
[gasps]
♪
My.
So those two mean
to cement their bond.
Wonderful.
Quit your swooning and fix
this mess before you skip off.
♪
Are you sure
this is a good idea, lad?
What's wrong, Mogrim?
[MOGRIM]
Cute and fuzzy as they are,
zoogs are man-eating monsters!
-Hm?
-[gasps]
True, they can be a handful
and unpredictable at times,
but the four of us are safe.
I'm good friends
with their elder.
I shouldn't be too surprised
you've broken bread
with their leader.
You make friends
with anyone you meet.
These little guys are top-tier
experts about the Wall.
If anyone can find
the gem giants, it's them.
It's been far,
far too long, Red!
It has! How are you, Elder?
I know Zoltan is more than
a hop, skip and jump from here,
but you must stop by
every now and then!
Things have been
a bit hectic on my end.
I-I mean we've had
a hard time getting out.
[MALE ZOOG ELDER 201A]
As husband and wife?
We're engaged.
Soon to be married.
May your future together
and our friendship
continue to thrive
and be blessed.
You're too kind.
Oh, right.
Here's a home-cured ham
as a gift from us.
Oh, splendid!
Even more meat to go around
is most appreciated
indeed, yes!
If only we could understand
business etiquette
to barter with others!
Speaking of which,
we're hoping to do
some business
with the gem giants.
You wouldn't happen to know
where their settlement is,
do you, Elder?
[MALE ZOOG ELDER 201A]
Why, yes, I do
and would be happy to help.
But please,
promise to be careful.
Lately the temperament
of those fellows
has been quite unusual.
One could even say
they've become downright angry.
Why is that?
[MALE ZOOG ELDER 201A]
Can't say for sure,
so I'd advise you
and your party to take caution.
-[thudding]
-Got it.
-[crying]
-[all gasp]
What happened?
Poor thing fell from the tree!
Branch snapped right
underneath his tiny feet!
-Hush now, no need to fuss!
-[wailing loudly]
-[RUTI] Need help?
-No, we're quite all right.
There's no need
to fret, my dear!
[ZOOG BOY 201A] Oh, wow!
It doesn't hurt anymore!
-Thanks, miss!
-Something's off
about the trees here.
This trunk feels fragile,
which explains
why the branch snapped
and the trees look frail.
[MALE ZOOG ELDER 201A]
How can you tell?
Because I was listening
to the spirits,
though I can't say
for sure the cause.
Red? Can you make
some fertilizer?
Sure can.
I can cook something
with materials here.
Get to it!
It'll be a temporary solution,
but let's do what we can, okay?
What do you say, Elder?
Of course!
We would be most grateful
for your help!
♪
[snoring]
-[RIT] What's on your mind?
-[gasps]
Oh, Rit. Hey, there.
Any second thoughts
about this whole trip?
[sighs]
No, I was just thinking
about my sister's Blessing.
More specifically, I...
I was thinking about
her New Truth Blessing,
and how it's canceling out
the Hero's Blessing,
which tends to strip
one's will and individuality.
That's something
she always wanted.
The joys of life.
Snatched away from her
when she was so young.
Craving a home-cooked meal.
Even dreams, since she had
no need for food or rest.
I'm beginning to think
New Truth...
isn't something she received
from the Almighty.
What if the Blessing came
from within her,
and I'm just clueless
about why or how it happened?
[RIT]
Red.
It's all still a mystery to me.
But whatever happens,
I'll always choose Ruti's side,
no matter what.
Yeah.
And I'll be right there
with you.
Why did we stop?
Something's amiss
with the plant life
-in the area.
-Huh?
And the farther we travel,
the sicker they become.
Could the land's soil
be tainted?
-You can sense that?
-Indeed.
And I fear the root cause
may be found up
in the mountains.
-Hm.
-Let us rest here for tonight.
We'll set up camp
and restart our journey
come tomorrow morning.
[TISSE]
Understood.
[fire crackling]
-[YARANDRALA] Tell me.
-[TISSE] Hm?
What made you decide
for us to travel together?
It's easier to show you
where to go.
There was no need for you
to come all this way with me.
And there was no reason
for me not to.
To be honest,
I also want to see
the Wall's natural hot spring
that I've heard
so many good things about.
Is that all?
That's pretty much it.
Right.
[TISSE] My guess is
Yarandrala doesn't know
that Ruti is with Red and Rit.
When she learns that Ruti
is no longer the world's Hero,
I wonder how she'll react?
Um, can I ask you something?
[YARANDRALA]
You may.
[TISSE]
How did you end up becoming
one of the Hero's
party members?
You know my association
with the Hero?
I do.
After all, I am friends
with Red and Rit,
and one other person.
Then I'm not mistaken?
The man who goes
by Red is actually...
Gideon. Red is Gideon.
I suspected as much.
Good to get confirmation
after all of this time.
Thank goodness.
You're still alive.
Do you know the reason
why I joined their party?
It's not at all complicated.
My dear friend Gideon
was there,
and so I knew I had to be.
[TISSE]
Nothing more than that?
Indeed. Nothing more.
What other reason
could I possibly need
to lend aid
to a close companion?
[gasps]
[YARANDRALA] Saving the world
is an alluring adventure,
and helping people
who require my services
is a perfectly
charitable cause in itself.
But that wasn't reason
enough to gamble
on defeating the Demon Lord
with a party of six.
That's simply an absurd risk.
Do you think so?
[YARANDRALA]
Of course, I do.
Why intentionally fight with
so few people in your party?
The Hero carries the world
squarely on her shoulders.
If she were to fall,
it would spell certain doom
for those under her protection.
Leaving things up to her
is nonsense.
You're saying the Hero
doesn't need to keep fighting
if her defeat poses
much of a risk?
Ah.
I see now.
-Hm?
-[YARANDRALA] Don't you worry.
Gideon and I are
of the same mind about that,
though I am surprised.
Huh?
♪
Ruti's here, too, isn't she?
-So cold!
-Yeah!
Wanna bring back
the old special?
Sure!
[thuds]
-[MOGRIM] Hm?
-[RIT] Hm?
-[RED] Know what I think?
-Huh?
Live your life
the way you want to.
And if the Almighty
has something
to say about it, screw 'em.
Your big brother
has your back, Ruti.
Funny. You always know
the right things to say.
-[chuckles]
-[TISSE] Milady!
[gasps]
Tisse? Is that you?
♪
[YARANDRALA]
Oh, Gideon!
♪
-[thumps]
-[Owlbear 201A groans]
[thuds]
[groans]
[blood splattering]
[LJUBO]
Excellent work, Van.
What did you expect?
Van could kill off a horde
of these ugly monsters
in his sleep!
A shame we couldn't
arrive sooner than we did.
There wouldn't have
been any casualties.
-[VAN] Spare your pity, Esta.
-[gasps]
You have witnessed
fulfillment of the roles
-the Almighty has given.
-[ESTA] What?
[VAN] The Blessing this owlbear
was bound to make
is its fate
to attack this person.
And this person, in turn,
was fated to lose
his life to it.
They each had roles to play,
and they played them perfectly.
[ESTA] Is this truly what
you think of that dead man?
Yes.
For he lived and died all
according to Lord Demis' will.
So rejoice!
They deserve our utmost praise,
and not our remorse!
♪
And I...will grow stronger,
thanks to their sacrifice.
All to fulfill my role as Hero,
and purify this evil world!