♪
[giggles]
[ground rumbling]
[VAN]
I will grow stronger.
[sword slashing]
I will slaughter that girl.
♪
And...
[sword slashing]
...I will be the true Hero!
[birds chirping]
[RED] All right,
Straight to business, everyone.
Let's get to the bottom
of the Van situation.
Word from Esta came in...
Van and his party will be
returning to Zoltan shortly.
[ALBERT]
He has gained more confidence,
after hunting monsters
in the southern seas.
[scoffs]
So you mean he's raring to go.
[ALBERT] Apparently,
he's made a habit of declaring
he will kill Miss Ruti
with a smile.
That's not weird at all.
Well, any bright ideas
on how to kick that kid's butt?
Violence will only worsen
the situation.
Driving him out of Zoltan
without a fight would be best.
That's the idea.
So, I figured our best approach
is to plan ahead.
[YARANDRALA] Wow,
nice work on the portraits.
Who drew those?
-That'd be me.
-Tisse's very talented.
[squeaks]
Albert, so we are all clear,
can you go through
everyone once more?
Sure.
First, there's Van...
he was the eighth prince
of the kingdom of Flahmberge.
[ALBERT] And he was
raised in a monastery
from a very young age.
It seems that some royal
and noble families
deem raising their own children
as a mark of shame.
Yes, I remember hearing
something about that.
But I absolutely know
I'll be a doting parent!
Me, too,
anything for our kids.
I love that.
[laughs]
Anyway...
based on that information,
it's safe to say Van's zeal
comes from his upbringing.
Yeah, and then
when he got older,
he found himself
at the Great Last Wall,
claiming to be the true Hero.
That's right.
[ALBERT] And once the Church
recognized him as such,
he spent all his time
hunting monsters,
and raising
his Blessing's level.
Yep, that's the big issue.
We unfortunately learned
that many of his allies
have been lost on those hunts.
[YARANDRALA]
The Divine Blessing of the Hero
should not allow one
to abandon their party.
Van's Blessing comes
before his allies' welfare.
He may believe that
with all his heart.
Developing his skill
is paramount.
[RED] And that's what enables
him to leave them to die.
The more I hear,
the more pissed I am!
How can a guy like that
be the Hero?
Danan, let's settle down.
There you have it,
that is all we know about him.
[sighs]
He sure is something else.
What is this guy even thinking?
His world is tiny.
All that exists in it
is himself and the Almighty.
[RUTI] No parents,
friends or loved ones.
That's why he trusts
his beliefs unconditionally.
Unwavering, unshakeable.
Next, the other two.
Thanks to Mistorm, we learned
a bit about Lavender.
♪
[MISTORM]
Yes, I know her.
This is not
our first encounter.
I met her before
settling in Zoltan.
Granted, she looked
different back then.
But I could recognize
her mana anywhere.
When you say
she looked different,
what does that mean?
Exactly what I said.
She was a dark shadow
who harnessed lightning
to her very command.
Such strength is something
a retired woman cannot match.
Loathe as I am to admit it,
I can't fight her.
Therefore, can I trust you
to take care of her
in my stead?
[sighs]
Given the chance
of collateral damage,
we should try to avoid
fighting Lavender directly.
But, I cannot begin to imagine
how we could talk her down.
[sighs]
[wood scraping]
[RIT]
Let me try talking to her.
[gasps]
She's an unknown monster...
you know that, right?
Sure, but I'm the best person
for the job!
Because, just like her,
I'm in love, as well!
[gasps]
♪
What... What...
[gasps]
Hear me out!
I mean, I know Lavender
isn't exactly human per se,
but she and I are similar
because we're both
madly in love!
I figured I could use that
to negotiate.
-Negotiate?
-Just an idea!
I don't see anyone else
raising their hand around here!
Hmm.
Uh-uh.
It's worth a shot.
Danan, would you mind
looking after Rit, please?
Why me?
Wouldn't it be better
if you coupled up with her?
[RED] I need to have
a chat with Ljubo.
Oh, do you now?
Let me accompany you.
In that case,
you can count on me
to keep Rit safe and sound.
Then it's settled, thank you!
Cardinal Ljubo
was of the peasantry.
He managed to make
a name for himself
purely off his
Cardinal's Blessing.
[ALBERT] A man of excess
who won't hesitate to bribe,
embezzle,
or worse for his desires.
If he knows who you are,
how do you plan
to confront him?
[RED]
With a disguise.
Ruti, let's have you keep
a low profile in the meantime.
Can you back her up, Tisse?
[TISSE]
Yep.
[squeaks]
Don't forget, this is all
to protect Zoltan and Ruti!
[RED]
Do your best.
-[DANAN] Yeah!
-[RIT] Yeah!
[YARANDRALA]
Will do.
Thank you...really.
[giggles]
All done here,
nice work, everyone.
[RED]
Let's eat.
[DANAN]
Now that's what I like to hear!
[laughing]
♪
[door opens]
You okay, Tisse?
Hi, Red.
I'm...thinking.
Thinking about my
role in all of this.
What I can do
to prepare for Van.
Too anxious to relax, huh?
Kinda.
I've seen him.
He isn't just powerful,
but he's also
a terrible person, too.
My Blessing is warning me.
[TISSE] Telling me that
killing him won't be easy.
[squeaks]
It's hard to argue
against your Blessing
if that's how you really feel.
What do you make
of this situation?
The differences between them...
Van and Miss Ruti.
They share
the Blessing of the Hero.
Both of them.
But...even so,
their mindsets in battle
are extremely different.
[TISSE]
Mindsets?
[RED] Our Ruti
is an indomitable Hero,
one who won't succumb to any
foe she comes up against,
no matter how strong.
[TISSE]
And what about Van?
[RED] He probably doesn't
care about his foes at all.
Only about winning
with the ultimate attacks.
He's trying to be
an invincible Hero.
An indomitable Hero,
and an invincible one.
[RED] Ruti's mindset
is prepared to face
all kinds of foes,
for Van, it doesn't matter.
And if I had to bet on one,
it wouldn't be him.
I see what you mean.
My sword has
a surefire technique as well.
But relying on it too much
could one day cost me my life.
And that right there
is his weakness.
[RED] Basically, Van depends
totally on his Blessing,
while Ruti relies
only on herself.
On herself.
I think I understand
what makes them so different.
The source of her strength
is the guidance that you offer.
Don't know about that.
I just want to make sure Ruti
can stand on her own two feet.
She's very lucky
to have you as her guide.
I mean that, Red.
Maybe if Van had
someone like you,
he would've
turned out differently.
[TISSE] She's right,
his world really is a tiny one.
I feel a bit better
after talking to you.
[RED]
Good.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
Sir Ljubo...
Van may have raised
his Blessing's level,
but there's no guarantee
he can defeat that girl.
What point is there
in risking the Hero's life
all the way out here
for a foolish endeavor?
Regardless, we need as much
information as possible.
Gather what you can
about Van's attacker,
and report back to me.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
How marvelous,
an unhinged hero.
Who knows what havoc
he'll create next time?
I've said it before,
but let Red and his friends
handle the boy.
Until then, we must keep
the people calm,
or else all of Zoltan
will stir up a panic.
Yes, you're right,
good thinking, Mistorm.
[indistinct chatter]
♪
[footsteps]
[sighs]
Before you leave,
please meet my squire, Albert.
♪
At your service,
it is truly an honor.
Esta told me of you.
Do take care to be of use
to the Hero, Albert.
Absolutely.
Hero, how was your trip
on the airship?
It went well enough.
While the islands
in the southern seas
had many fiends for me to slay,
they were all perfect fodder
for my Blessing.
Yep, she won't know
what hit her!
[gasps]
♪
[grimacing]
The sooner I find that girl,
the better.
No, allow us to gather
information on the girl, Van.
Besides, you lack
the Tracking Skill
to find her yourself.
Rest, Van, and let us
handle this matter for you.
Remember,
you were severely injured.
[groaning]
[thumping]
[sighs]
[sighing]
Van...I'm here.
Forget those two,
you still have me!
[indistinct chatter]
What's this?
I spy a couple of bugs.
♪
[LAVENDER] I see you
buzzing around, you two!
[both gasping]
So much for laying low!
I oughta squash you
to the ground!
No doubt you could.
Word has it you're powerful,
even without Van.
[grunts]
Come again?
What's your true form?
That body of yours
can't fool my Blessing!
[RIT] Frail as you look,
you are far more violent
than you let on.
[groans]
You can't be bothered
by us lowly mortals.
So, why would you even
hide at all from them?
Flying around
as a small, little fairy?
♪
Does it have anything to do
with you being in love?
Going through all this trouble,
well aware of how terrifying
your true self is.
You've taken the
form of a typical fairy
in order to endear yourself
to a human boy.
One more word,
and I'll rip you apart, girl!
[screaming]
[electricity crackling]
Someone's dear to me, too!
And that's why I wanted
to talk to you about love!
[gasps]
♪
I'll start,
I'm Rizlet of Loggervia.
Just call me Rit.
Rit, okay, then.
And is that the man
you're in love with over there?
[gulping]
[giggles]
Gosh, no!
A completely different guy.
Yeah, I thought so.
Bet that lug hasn't seen
a trace of romance.
[RIT] Lying to Lavender
won't work in my favor.
Gotta bare my heart and hope
I find common ground.
Up north, in Loggervia,
I was princess of the Duchy.
♪
Wow, a princess, huh?
Spill it, is your lover
a prince or a knight
or someone else?
Whoa!
A knight from another land,
we live together now.
A commoner life in Zoltan.
Ooh, a forbidden elopement?
Good for you!
I mean, you gotta be willing
to sacrifice it all
for the sake of your love!
Right, I couldn't say it
better myself.
Always and forever,
I'll be with him,
'Til my final breath,
I swear to stay
right by his side.
You're a hit,
bring on the salad and mead!
[glass clanking]
[indistinct chatter]
[gasps]
♪
[RIT]
So, yeah...
The two of us
were separated for a while.
By the time we reunited,
we'd done some maturing.
And I fell for him anew.
[gulping]
Anew, huh?
What?
So, you didn't fall totally
in love with the guy
when you were still
in Low-ger-via?
I'm not saying that at all!
I loved the old Red,
too, just as much!
Oh, drop the act.
Love's got nothing to do
with maturity.
It's joyous and beautiful
and perfect just as it is!
What I wouldn't give to have
time stop the moment
I fell in love.
So not a single thing
would change, forever.
Anything less than that
is not true love!
Then you love Van
as he is, no question?
He's perfect,
like more mead would be!
[RIT]
She doesn't want him to change.
But that means she's not taking
his feelings into account.
♪
I'd crush this puny world
to dust to prove my love!
Because it's the very least
I can do for him.
But what if it's
your side that falls
instead of the other?
[growling]
[RIT]
I mean, the Demon Lord's army
has its share
of formidable foes.
Van being the Hero
doesn't guarantee victory.
You love him, and so you worry.
My Van remaining
the way he is comes first
before anything else.
And if that leads
to his death, then...
that's the day
I'll die with him.
[gasps]
My heart belongs to Van
until the moment I die.
I couldn't ask
for a more romantic ending.
Is that how you truly
view love?
You don't feel the same way?
♪
Lavender, I need a favor.
A favor...nice try, princess.
The only one I listen to
is my dear Van.
[RIT]
But this is for Van's own good.
Really?
Let's hear it, then.
Ask him to leave Zoltan,
only you can do it.
♪
[sighs]
You care about him, right?
One battle is not worth
risking his life.
There's so much more he can do
to raise his Blessing.
And I believe the Hero
has bigger things to fight for.
[LAVENDER]
You have a point there.
-[RIT] Yeah?
-But my answer is no.
[sighs]
Figured you'd say that.
[laughs]
[LAVENDER]
Oh, thank goodness!
If you'd insisted,
I would've had to kill you.
Well, that's not ideal.
[RIT]
Okay, before we leave...
[sighs]
[glass clanking]
...here's to many more
casual chats
with a hearty round of mead.
That isn't something
to toast about, silly.
-Bottom's up!
[gulping]
[fireworks bursting]
[indistinct chatter]
♪
Hustle...keep going!
[LJUBO]
Go, go!
C'mon, get past 'em!
[thumping]
Move it!
Pick up the pace...
wait, what?
Why'd you stop,
you stupid reptile?
Run, I say!
[grunting]
Screw the entire lot of you,
give me back my money!
This is a setup, a rigged race!
[groans]
-[RED] Cardinal Ljubo.
-[LJUBO] I'm on break.
Come back when I'm not busy.
[RED] But I think you'd like
what I have to say.
You'll leave here
a happier man.
[gasps]
[thumping]
Number 5's too fat.
This is Zoltan, my good sir.
You can't expect
fair play here.
Then how much
will you bet on him?
[coins clanking]
♪
[chuckles]
Red, are you sure about this?
If you lose, you'll never
bring him to the table.
It'll work, trust me.
[squeaks]
Ah!
[bell clanging]
[thumping]
[LJUBO] Splendid,
I never doubted the outcome!
But it was still riveting
to see her catch up from behind
and win by a nose!
And now that you have made
a killing, join me.
There's a restaurant
with the most excellent wine.
Bold of you to say so.
I'm quite particular
about my choice of drink.
♪
[sighs]
Oh, my...
I must admit, this product has
a pleasantly refreshing taste
that hits the tongue
like silk.
A subtle hint of fruit
that slowly overwhelms.
A fine, rich texture.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
My word!
Zesty, aren't you?
This wine feels wild
and pure and free,
like a noble lady
frolicking untamed
throughout the wood
and naked as the day
she was born!
Who would've expected
this bumpkin town
to possess quite a gem?
[YARANDRALA] Care to pair it
with this seafood dish?
♪
This plate has not a hint
of anything from the sea!
This is ground fish meat,
smoked and infused with herbs
and then roasted in olive oil.
[RED]
She's overdoing it.
Fish ground up
and paired with red wine?
What a primitive
establishment, honestly.
[munching]
[whimpering]
[LJUBO]
What in the Almighty's name!
[chomps]
This goes against
all conventional wisdom!
Such flavor!
[happy groan]
[RED] I'd like to discuss
something with you,
Cardinal Ljubo.
Of course, you do.
Back to business
already, I see.
So, what do you want?
[LJUBO]
Looking for a job?
This is regarding Sir Van.
Overlook his indiscretions,
will you?
You'll thank him one day
for delivering us from ruin.
Danger surrounds
the person Van seeks
to challenge in battle.
[gasps]
You know about the girl
who attacked Van?
Yes.
Speak,
who exactly is that girl?
An artifact from ancient elves.
Huh?
♪
[laughs]
[LJUBO]
Ridiculous.
All the ancient elves
left behind
is some absurd clockwork.
[RED] I know you find it
hard to believe.
But please, follow me.
♪
[door opens]
[gasps]
[LJUBO]
An ogre king?
♪
That writing
is Ancient Elven...
explain!
[RED] I hear this ogre king
was highly intelligent,
and even wielded a club.
It may have been
a biological weapon
created in ancient ruins.
[LJUBO]
What?
[RED] In the mountains
to the north of Zoltan,
there lies an elven monument
nearly buried in the wood.
It is supposedly home
to similar creations
as the ogre,
some of which look
remarkably humanoid.
[LJUBO] Then the girl
who attacked Van
is an Ancient Elven relic?
Small wonder she displayed
such terrifying strength.
She took down Van, after all.
[RED] There's a report from
the Thieves' Guild of Zoltan.
It backs up this theory.
It all makes sense.
The girl's sole purpose
is to protect
the Ancient Elven ruins.
♪
[RED]
Should the Demon Lord's army
ever reach Zoltan,
these weapons will crawl out
of the woodwork to fight them.
[LJUBO] So you want Van
to withdraw from this fight
for humanity's future, as well?
Yes.
Consider this,
if Sir Van or the girl
were to die in battle,
it will be a massive loss
for mankind.
Catastrophic.
In that case,
I'll strongly advise Van
to leave Zoltan right away.
Please do.
Make no mistake...
he might refuse.
Getting Van to obey has been
a rather vexing challenge
for me lately.
♪
Hmm.