[shimmering]
[RUOLONG] Takeshi from the
intruder’s team rushes at Viking
with reckless abandon!
This is for Mikan!
[grunts]
[yells]
[energy rushing]
-[clanging]
-[TAKESHI yelling]
[clattering]
[fire sizzling]
[RUOLONG] Well, this is
an unexpected turn of events!
For some reason,
the intruder team
has started
attacking each other!
What’ll happen next?
Could this be
some sort of strategy?
Uh...
I haven’t the slightest.
But speaking
of the intruders, I think
I’ve seen that girl before.
[TWIN STAR] Viking! Viking!
He’s our man!
Now it looks like Mammoth Viking
is having a performance battle
with the intruder team’s
mascot girl!
I don’t know
what to expect anymore!
I don’t know what’s going on,
but it’s funny!
My!
You’re such a big, handsome man!
Thankfully this guys’ brain
is in his biceps.
I’m counting on you, Suigin.
Why did you stop me?
♪
The pictures...
disappeared?
And they’ll never come back.
Do you honestly think
Mikan would be happy about this?
[shuddering]
They weren’t just yours.
They were a part of her, too.
Of her heart.
These memories were precious
reminders of your time together.
[sobbing]
I’m sorry. It’s just--
There’s no other way
to cure Mikan’s illness!
I have to win that money!
Do you think I want this?
I want to keep our memories,
but if I do, I’ll lose her
instead!
What do I do?
Take it.
Thanks, Suigin.
But, I-- I can’t use it.
You won’t have to.
Hang back.
Let me handle the rest.
[RUOLONG]
Looks like the intruder team's
finished their little spat.
The hammer kid is out,
and the red scarf is in!
[LAOLONG]
This is one wild final.
[RUOLONG]
According to the system,
red scarf is Suigin Riku.
Well, this is unexpected!
He hasn’t even finished
the beginner’s course!
Our new finalist is a complete
amateur, ladies and gents!
I know him! From before!
Uh-huh.
[MAMMOTH VIKING]
I think I’m being insulted!
You make me wait, and now you
want me to fight this loser?
I’ll rip his face asunder!
[charging attack yell]
If you don’t give it
everything you’ve got,
you don’t stand
a chance in hell!
[RUOLONG]
Newcomer Suigin is no match
for Mammoth Viking’s
overwhelming power!
I believe in you!
[frustrated sigh]
Really? This kid's hopeless.
[crashing, grunting]
[MAMMOTH VIKING]
Quit dodging and fight me!
You’re making it
too easy, newb!
[grunting]
[RUOLONG]
Suigin’s in real trouble now
thanks to Viking’s ice attack!
He’s struggling with all his
might, but he just can’t budge!
[gasping]
[RUOLONG] This doesn’t
look good for red scarf!
Viking moves in for the kill!
That’s what you get
for mocking me!
[laughs triumphantly]
No!
Well, kid.
“Ice” knowing ya!
-[energy surging]
-[pinging]
[giggling]
Holy crap!
[RUOLONG]
What an upset!
The mascot girl
from the intruder team
has just jumped
into the fray!
This finals match is
getting crazier every minute!
[LAOLONG] Strange. There’s no
registration data on her.
Then could this girl be...?
Phew! Thanks, Twin Star!
That was close!
You’re gonna owe me
big time for this later.
You’ve got strength, style,
and curves in all
the right places, lady!
You’d be the perfect wife
for the Mammoth Viking!
A wife?
Really?
Well, you’re right
about everything else.
But I doubt you’ll want
to tie the knot
once you’ve seen
the terror of my true form.
True form? You gonna let me see
the real goods or something?
[energy roaring]
[WEI]
Star.
That was it, huh?
How is that scary?
Not good, Star!
We chose the wrong form, Twin!
That’s not wrong, it’s adorable!
I can’t believe
how soft you are!
-Like a couple of marshmallows!
-[SHIN, WEI screaming]
-[MAMMOTH VIKING laughing]
-[SHIN] So gross, Twin!
Bounce! Bounce!
I don’t know which
one of you I like better!
Ew. This guy’s a freak.
Let them go!
What'd you do that for, brat?
Takeshi?
Guys should treat girls
with respect!
Sorry, Suigin.
But I can’t let you fight
my battles for me.
[exploding]
Okay, the monsters are gone now.
Takeshi, what’s the matter?
You aren’t hurt, are you?
Come on, talk to me.
I’m here, so there’s
nothing to be scared of.
You got guts, kid.
I like that.
Now you got to
the count of three
till I pummel your face in.
Three!
[yells]
[ice shattering]
[TAKESHI]
I wanted to be a hero.
To protect Mikan forever!
I won’t run from you!
I won’t hide like
a coward anymore!
Whatever happens,
I’m going to protect her!
Takeshi.
[RUOLONG] Despite his size,
Viking is a pretty small man!
He’s beating the little boy
without any remorse or honor!
[SHIN and WEI]
You’re really brave, Takeshi.
[TWIN STAR]
Thanks for protecting me.
Mikan’s a lucky girl.
You can let go now.
Huh?
Ah-ha!
I had a feeling about
that young lady.
Her ability to change form
at will means only one thing!
She isn’t a player at all.
She’s a Grave Beast!
[RUOLONG] Please tell me
you’re joking, sir!
A humanoid grave beast
is one of the highest level
familiars in all of
Grave Buster!
Who in the world
is this young man?
He’s so amateur, it hurts,
yet he controls a familiar?
Ridiculous!
Kinda.
[laughing]
Phoebe.
Uh-huh.
Don’t think I’m intimidated
by your little
transformation act, girly!
I know you’re tryin’
to mess with me,
and I’m calling your bluff!
Bring it!
[laughing]
-You asked for it.
-[shimmering]
[roaring]
[RUOLONG]
I don’t believe it!
The sexy mascot girl
has turned into a monster!
[LAOLONG] That’s the legendary
Twin-headed Jade Dragon.
I’m sure of it!
Why is it serving that amateur?
Wow.
[yells]
What the hell's going on?
This isn't sexy, or cute!
[fire exploding]
[energy radiating]
[MAMMOTH VIKING
yelling fearfully]
I-- I lost?
Impossible!
[shattering]
[LAOLONG] That’s it, folks!
The intruders win it all!
[crowd roaring, cheering]
I could never
thank you two enough!
Sure!
Give my regards to Mikan, okay?
Take care of Suigin,
okay, Dragon Lady?
And thanks again!
[SUIGIN]
Dragon Lady’s got a ring to it.
[cell phone ringing]
Oh, right.
[TWIN STAR]
Hey, Suigin.
Are you sure about this?
That was an awful lot
of money you gave up.
I’m a billion player,
I can go without.
Ten million’s a proverbial
drop in the bucket.
More importantly,
could you put some clothes on?
[TWIN STAR] I can’t until
I recharge the energy
I used saving your sorry butt!
All that real money, wasted.
Hmm?
Whatever!
Real?
[gasps]
I had no idea!
[energy blasting]
[RUOLONG] Any idea who that guy
could have been, Mr. Laolong?
Who knows?
The fact that he has
a Grave Beast
in tow might be a clue
to answering it.
[RUOLONG] You don’t think he’s--
The Collector’s--
[LAOLONG} Careful! You
shouldn’t say her name out loud!
That witch conquered this stage
without any resistance.
If she got wind of this,
well...
let’s just say calamity
would be the least
of our worries.