-[breeze blowing]
-[chains jangling]
This land may look barren,
but it’s a place where
dreams come true.
I have a dream for
the future of us Gold Hunters.
A time when ample
riches line our pockets.
[scratching]
-[pow]
-[pained cry]
[PHOEBE]
Quit trying to sound cool
-while you’re grabbing my ass!
-[groaning]
Ah!
You’re not our leader,
just a stupid pervert.
[groaning]
[BOTH sigh]
[chuckling]
Ample riches. So soft!
♪
[sheen sound]
You’re not the last guardian.
That title belongs to me!
[gunshot]
[sizzling]
[maniacal laughter]
[yelling]
-[gasping]
-[thudding]
[birds chirping]
[sighing]
[rattling]
Meow!
[gasp]
♪
Huh?
[sparkle]
-My wound...
-[ringing]
Uh!
[ringing]
[sigh]
[beep]
[MAN]
This Suigin Riku?
♪
[SUIGIN]
Yes. Who is this?
[chuckle]
[MAN]
I’m known by many names.
You can call me Temujin,
of Totems.
I’ll be waiting for you
in Grave Buster. Till then.
-[hangs up]
-Uh...
Wait! Don’t hang up yet!
Hello? What the hell?
Temujin...
-[ring]
-[gasp]
[beep]
[gasp]
[gasping]
No...
Rei!
[street noise]
[MALE PLAYER 1]
Check it out! I did it!
[MALE PLAYER 2]
You put in 200,000?!
[MALE PLAYER 1]
It’s a solid investment.
If you get the Divine Coins,
it could multiply
200 times over!
Hi, there!
Got room in your party, big boy?
There might be a spot.
Then, let’s go!
-Woo!
-Huh?
Fine then! I’ll deposit 500,000!
Keep talking like that,
and I might join you!
-[metal clinking]
-[breeze blowing]
Doesn’t look like our prey
wants to come out to play.
Well, we’re not going
after small fry.
I wouldn’t get enough exercise.
[sigh]
I’m beginning to think
you’re all talk.
I might go solo.
Calm down, we’re about
to catch some big quarry.
Just a little longer.
[sigh]
I’ll hold you to that.
-[FARIN] Hey.
-Hmm? What is it?
This is boring.
How long are we staying here?
Just a little longer!
In Grave Buster,
money is the ultimate power.
If we’ve got the dough,
the members of Precious
will notice us.
Then we’ll ride
the gravy train to easy street.
Keep that goal in sight,
friends.
All this waiting
will be worth it.
[sigh]
[siren blaring]
[running]
[BOTH]
Hmm?
Over there!
Competition.
[MAN]
Ah.
A fat duckie
and some ducklings.
Alright.
Ready? Let’s move!
[gasp]
Holy...
-crap!
-[sizzling]
-[whimpering]
-[sheen sound]
We’ve been ready, darling.
Yeah. That much is obvious...
♪
[SUIGIN]
New members of Grave Buster
must first complete the beginner
registration process.
If they pass the entrance exam,
they’re allowed to play.
All players that enter
must agree to these terms--
[RANSHOU]
Read something enough,
and the meaning
will become clear.
-You seem hard at work, Suigin.
-[giggle]
Ranshou?
Reading up on Grave Buster?
Mm-hmm.
Well, you’re in luck, my friend.
How’s that, exactly?
Behold.
This beauty is
actually a game freak.
And she participated
in the Closed Beta.
Oh.
Nice to meet ya.
[MAN yelling]
[groan]
D’ja see that?
Totally one-shotted him!
-[music]
-[coins rattle]
Ha! Guess that 200,000’s
already paying off!
-So cool!
-Money is power!
And we’ve got loads of it!
[giggle]
[PHOEBE]
Oh my!
-Are you a warrior?
-Huh?
That’s right!
-[sexy music]
-In that case, handsome,
would you mind doing me a favor?
-I’d be sure to reward you...
-[boing]
[BOTH moaning]
[BOTH]
Just name it!
Wait a second!
Doesn’t this seem suspicious?
[growl]
-[yelp, whimpering]
-[PHOEBE] We just found them.
Big, bountiful mounds
of amazing treasure.
Sadly, there are
tentacled monsters guarding it,
and I’m so afraid
they’re going to get me!
[MALE PLAYER 2]
This buxom babe...
And tentacles?
-[slithering]
-[moaning] No!
[BOTH moaning]
[PHOEBE] Don’t be shy, Farin!
Ask for their help.
Please, help us.
She’s a super cutie, too!
Oh boy!
That slightly cold
demeanor’s heating me up!
[PHOEBE] Great!
The treasure’s this way, boys.
-[BOTH] Okay!
-Hey! Don’t leave without me!
Wait!
[SUIGIN] Currently,
the ruler of Grave Buster
is someone called, “Dark Tiger.”
He heads an organization
known simply as, “Precious.”
Precious has an enormous
amount of wealth,
which it uses to
control the game world.
All the while stealing the money
and items of other players,
and gaining even more power.
[sigh]
But lately,
there are forces
fighting against them.
[GIRL]
Temujin of Totems?
You’re getting into
some dangerous territory!
-Uh...
-Totems is a powerful new group!
They’re challenging Precious
for supremacy in Grave Buster!
Temujin’s their leader,
and a total villain
who will do anything to win.
He’s known as
the Terrifying Devourer,
and he’ll take
whatever he wants!
[SUIGIN]
Whatever he wants?
-[magazine thuds]
-[gasp]
[grunting]
-[panting]
-[beep]
Terrifying Devourer?
♪
Devour her?!
[wailing]
Rei! No!
♪
[sigh]
-[hissing]
-Uh? Huh?
[energy humming]
[MAN]
Hello.
[door opens]
How do you like my home?
By all means,
make yourself comfortable.
If you need something,
say the word.
I’ll make sure that you get it.
I need to be set free!
Guess I should've seen
that one coming, huh?
[sigh]
Give it time.
[groaning, gasp]
Enough of my hospitality,
and you’ll be begging
to stay here forever.
[groan]
[grunting]
[sigh]
[MAN]
Feisty, aren’t you?
Fine by me.
It wouldn’t be fun
if you gave in quickly.
[laughing]
[sigh]
[grunt]
-[whimpering]
-[energy humming]
Alright, we’re here!
We are?
It just looks like
more rocks to me.
[MALE PLAYER 1]
Maybe they took off
after they saw our epic gear.
[MALE PLAYER 2]
Guess we’re done here.
-Oh!
-[groaning]
No, we’re still in danger!
The monsters are in
that abandoned mine!
Those creepy things
slimed all over us.
We barely escaped
with our lives!
[BOTH yelling]
Ha! Yeah, right.
Before we got away, they took
over 3,000,000 from us.
What? 3,000,000?!
[indistinct yelling]
[chuckle]
[metallic scrape, clank]
♪
[energy humming]
[MALE PLAYERS]
Huh?
[energy humming]
[ALL wailing]
[FEMALE PLAYER]
What? You’re kidding me!
[MALE PLAYER 1]
Hey? Sexy lady?
[MALE PLAYER 2] Little cutie!
Can you get rid of this barrier?
Get us outta here! Hurry!
-[bang]
-You horny idiots!
These two played
you like fiddles!
How dumb are you?!
[MALE PLAYER 2]
I don’t believe it!
[MALE PLAYER 1]
C’mon, let us out!
[FEMALE PLAYER]
I’ll report you to the admins!
Good grief.
Huh?
Isn’t that...?
[gasp]
Bro!
[breeze blowing]
[chuckle]
The heavens call!
The earth calls!
The people call!
-[ALL] Ooh...
-They demand
that I make my wealth!
-[groaning]
-I am he who lives
and dies for money!
-Ah...
-I’m known far and wide
as the Golden Ryouzaburou!
But you can call me...
[yells]
[air rushing]
[chuckling]
[grunt]
Wild Wolf.
♪
That’s my name!
[SUIGIN]
The Silver Guardian!