[shimmering]
♪
How many days has it been?
Feels like forever.
I dunno.
[MIKAN]
Takeshi.
You’ve been staring
at that console an awful lot.
Oh. Sorry. It’s just, if I make
enough money in this game,
maybe I could get out of
this town someday.
[laughs softly]
[MIKAN]
If you did, where would you go?
Wherever I could.
It’d be heaven compared to this.
Sounds great.
I’d like to go.
Well, I wouldn’t mind
taking you with me, Mikan.
We could go anywhere, together.
You’re sweet.
That means a lot.
Thanks.
[gasps softly]
[shimmering]
[door shuts]
[KOSHIRIKO]
Quit gawking, bimbo. Move it.
[heels clicking]
[grunts]
[HAKU]
The lovely Rei Riku.
We welcome you
as a member of Totems.
As a token of your initiation,
we present you
with this red console.
May it bring you fortune.
[shimmering]
[whimpers]
[soft chuckling]
[crowd murmuring]
[TAKESHI]
What? Why not?
Is it 'cause I’m a kid,
you don’t think I can
handle it in there?
That has absolutely
nothing to do with it.
I can't let you in
until you've paid
the fifty-thousand entry fee.
Fifty-thousand?
Ball's in your court, kid.
Fine.
[MALE FOREMAN] If you can’t pay
the damn fee, don’t fuss, brat.
Better not see you--
[FEMALE PARTICIPANT]
Pardon me, sir.
[MALE PARTICIPANT]
Could I get a flier?
Of course!
Take two if you like!
[wind rushing]
[paper flapping]
[gasps]
So high.
[SUIGIN]
Hey.
You wouldn’t happen to know
where Laolong
the matchmaker is, would ya?
[grunts]
[laughs]
[TAKESHI]
I might know.
[MALE CROWD MEMBER 1]
I came here to see a fight!
[MALE CROWD MEMBER 2]
Hurry up, would ya?
I’m Suigin, by the way.
Who're you?
I’m Takeshi.
And you can call me “pack mule."
My arms feel like noodles.
Why are we watching
from up here?
I didn’t come here to watch
the tournament, remember?
I just want to meet Laolong,
so it was pointless
to pay for a ticket.
Fifty-thousand isn’t
chump change, you know.
Did you forget
you’re a billion player,
or are you trying to hide
that fact for some reason?
[SUIGIN]
I’m just used to being frugal.
So, what’s your
business here, Takeshi?
I’m here to fight
and win this thing.
But I figured it was smarter
to wait and size up
the competition instead
of going in guns blazing.
Hey! Over there!
It’s Laolong!
That’s him on the right.
He’s in charge of all beginners’
courses in Grave Buster.
Let’s talk to him!
Let’s slow our roll, first.
Ladies and gentlemen,
kids of all ages!
Thank you for your patience!
What do you say we get
this final match underway?
[crowd cheering]
He’s a self-proclaimed
“Best Ice-user in the land!”
From the stormy seas,
Mammoth Viking!
And his opponent,
the “Number One Ice-user,"
Frost magician, Eeyuu!
The best
versus number one.
How exciting.
At least we know their egos
are on the same level.
[LAOLONG] This is it folks.
The winner of this icy bout
will walk away with ten million
in cold, hard cash!
With an added bonus
of this adorable
Ice Snow Leopard companion!
Ten million?
What a prize!
All right, ice-users,
let’s heat this place up!
Ready? Go!
You might as well give up,
little man.
Those prizes belong to me!
-[energy surging]
-[EEYUU chuckling]
Was that an attack,
or a tickle, old man?
[ice shattering]
[exploding]
[grunting]
You think this can stop me?
Damn! Guess that didn’t work.
-[EEYUU yelling]
-[ice shattering]
Looks like Mammoth
has gone animalistic
on the poor frost magician!
But he’s cool under pressure.
Look at his face!
-[EEYUU grunts]
-[ice shattering]
[EEYUU]
Keep coming.
Every step you take
brings you closer to your doom.
[chuckles]
I’ll be sure
to make it quick.
[shimmering]
No.
What are you doing?
-[ice shattering, crashing]
-[grunting]
[chuckling]
He’s definitely
planning something.
[TWIN STAR]
Huh? You can tell?
Who do you think’s
gonna win, Takeshi?
Neither one.
They don’t deserve it.
-[gasps]
The ten million in prizes
belongs to me!
[ALL yelling]
-[grunting]
-[shattering]
End of a line, gramps!
[SUIGIN yelling]
-[crashing]
[MAMMOTH VIKING grunting]
[RUOLONG]
I don’t believe my eyes!
It’s raining men!
[SUIGIN]
That hurt.
-[SUIGIN groaning]
-[shimmering]
-[gasps]
Sorry about that!
His book just started
glowing so suddenly!
[TAKESHI] I’m your opponent now.
Let’s do this.
Judges? What’s he on about?
Let's see.
According to the rule book,
if an intruder happens to
defeat one of
the original participants,
they have the right
to fight in their place.
Sounds crazy,
but this is totally legal!
Works for me.
[chuckles]
All right, I’ll just get these
intruders' IDs in the system.
Takeshi and Suigin Riku
are now designated
as the challenging team
for the final match!
Uh...
[humorless laugh]
Who the hell
thought up that rule?
Sorry to get you
caught up in this, Suigin.
But no matter what,
I have to win that ten million,
or this was all
just for nothing.
-[YOUNG MIKAN giggling]
-[BABY TAKESHI crying]
[TAKESHI]
Ever since we were little,
we were always together.
Me and Mikan.
[MIKAN] Here,
that’s your share, Takeshi!
All we have to do is use these
and we can make money, right?
[grunts]
Only if you win, silly.
I will! You’ll see!
[T-Rex roaring]
[MIKAN] You can’t keep running
from every monster.
The only way to get stronger
is to beat them.
Nuh-uh, there’s other ways.
This Paladin’s memoir lets you
increase your fighting power,
even if you don’t
fight anything!
Sounds fishy, if you ask me.
It’s true! It works!
Just look.
[camera shutter clicks]
[whirring]
[laughs]
If you put a photograph in,
you get stronger
little by little,
but you have to do it
daily for it to add up.
Oh.
At least now I know
the reason
you’ve been
sneaking photos of me
whenever you've got the chance.
No.
Not just of you.
Right. I believe that.
Fess up, I’m on
to your candid antics.
Sorry. It’s just that
I’m always with you.
You’re the only person
I can take pictures of.
Lemme see.
Come on.
Oh my.
Are you angry?
'Course not. Why would I be mad?
These memories are precious.
We should cherish them together.
And you’re just
as precious to me.
After all, we’re partners,
Takeshi.
[gasps]
[camera shutter clicks]
[TAKESHI]
Mikan, no!
You'll get better.
I'll make sure you do.
I’ll get you out of here
and into a better hospital.
I’ll go make some money,
just hold on till then!
[sobbing]
[MIKAN]
You dummy. Don’t worry about me.
Just get out of this town
for both of us.
[crowd roaring]
Hold on a little longer.
I’ll win, and we’ll leave
that place together.
Takeshi. That book.
[MAMMOTH VIKING laughing]
It doesn’t matter
if there’s two or ten of ya!
You won’t beat me!
And why’s that?
Intruders who qualify to fight
will have to take
a major penalty!
What did he say?
[RUOLONG] Regardless of
personal circumstances,
intruders will have the strength
of all their abilities
cut in half!
[laughing]
You see?
You screwed yourself.
There’s no way
you’ll be a match for me
with that puny amount of power!
But, I didn’t know that!
You barged in without
checking all the rules first?
Talk about doing something rash.
I don’t care!
I’m still winning
that ten million!
[grunts]
[energy surging]
[RUOLONG]
Oh, what’s this?
Apparently, Takeshi’s item
converts
photographs into
raw fighting power!
[MAMMOTH VIKING grunts]
Indeed, but with every attack,
the memories contained within
the photographs burn away.
That’s a hefty sacrifice.
He loses his memories?
I’ll lose everything I cherish,
if that’s what it takes.
[energy surging]
I'm saving Mikan.
Nothing you do will stop me!
The Silver
Guardian