[YUUKI] Long ago,
an all-powerful goddess
created this world.
Then, in order to create life,
she selflessly gave up her own.
This is how we came to be.
With her life force exhausted,
the goddess began her eternal
slumber in an imperial tomb.
Her death left behind a source
of unimaginable power.
The goddess’s name was Bango.
This is the myth of Creation
that has been passed down
through the ages.
[roaring]
[rocks tumbling]
-[SHIN, WEI shrieking]
-[SUIGIN yelling]
[SHIN]
Excuse us!
[WEI]
We’ll just hide in here, Star!
[SHIN] We’re guides,
not fighters, Twin.
[WEI]
We’ll leave the rest up to you.
Go get ’em, Star!
What can I do?
C’mon. Help me!
I’m Shin, by the way.
You can call me Wei!
[BOTH]
Together, we are Twin Star!
We’ll be right here,
cheering you on, Twin!
We’ll be right here
cheering you on, Star!
You’re running away?
What kind of guides are you?
[YUUKI (DEMON LORD)]
You won't escape, little man!
Would you stop
screaming everything?
It’s obnoxious!
My ears work fine!
Quite the attitude.
You might be tougher
than I thought, boy.
Very well!
Your worth will be tested!
We’ll see if you can be
a Tomb Guardian.
This stage has been
besieged by intruders.
You will help me ward them off
and protect the treasures!
That will be-- Huh?
Where'd he go?
[grunts]
[YUUKI (DEMON LORD)]
Hey! Wait!
You disrespectful
little brat!
Stop! I wasn’t done talking!
[SUIGIN]
Yeah. That’s why I’m leaving.
I guess you don’t want
to save Rei, then.
How disappointing.
If you don’t
pass the test, Suigin,
saving Rei will be
forever out of your reach.
What say you?
How’d you know that?
[energy rushing]
[shattering]
[explosions]
[PHOEBE]
Aw, what a shame. You missed.
Too far right.
No freakin’ way.
[PHOEBE]
Yes, freakin’ way.
Don’t lose your cool, Eeyuu.
Next shot will do it.
Try again.
Roger that.
Adjusting the firing angle.
Lock and load.
[chuckles]
We're ready to rock, Phoebs.
Five minutes
'til it’s recharged.
[PHOEBE]
Far too long.
Farin, be a dear and distract
it awhile, will you?
Roger!
[energy surging]
[grunts]
[energy rushing]
[exploding]
Great, just what I needed.
Hey. What’re you up to, Phoebe?
Why, the usual, of course.
What else?
Here we come.
[SUIGIN]
Holy crap.
That explosion.
What happened?
The tomb raiders attacked
sooner than expected.
[SUIGIN]
Tomb raiders?
As I was trying to say earlier,
you must fight them with me.
That’s the only way to prove
you are worthy of the moniker.
Enough!
Let’s get this over with.
Much better.
That’s what I like to hear.
Are you sure you’re prepared?
[scoffs]
Then let us begin!
-[grunts]
-[energy surging]
[SHOSTIA]
I am Shostia.
The spirit of
the desert incarnate.
[shimmering]
[grunts]
Excuse me, but...
would you happen
to be young Master Suigin?
Oh, uh...
yeah, that’s my name.
Finally!
I’ve been waiting for so long!
I can’t believe
you’re really here!
♪
[leaves rustling]
It should all come
back to you now!
The seal on your memories
is broken!
I’m so happy for you
I could cry!
I remember.
My grandpa.
This scarf was from him.
A gift from long ago.
He really was...
my grandfather.
[YUUKI (DEMON LORD) chuckling]
So, you finally remember,
Suigin, my boy?
That voice. Just who are you?
My Master!
[evil chuckling]
[YUUKI] Beloved grandson.
It’s been awhile.
Lookin’ good, Suigin.
[chuckles]
What?
[shimmering]
[gasping, whimpering]
[bubbling]
[water rushing]
[REI gasping]
[KOSHIRIKO]
Look who decided to wake up.
‘Bout time.
Who are you?
[KOSHIRIKO]
No time. Just put these on.
Time for purification.
Centipede Heart, let’s go!
[air whooshing]
[energy surging]
[centipedes twittering]
Alright now.
You know what to do, babies!
Take care of those pesky
guardians!
[SUIGIN]
You’re my gramps?
But, aren’t you... ancient?
And dead?
I can understand
your confusion, my boy,
so I’ll explain everything.
At times, I was
the genius game designer.
Others, I was the vice president
of God Grave Tech company
as well as the proud father
who raised the beautiful
Rei Riku.
But my true identity
has always been...
[water gushing]
Your grandfather,
the great Yuuki Riku!
[exploding]
[whimpering]
[exploding continues]
[yelling]
♪
[energy surging]
One more time!
Huh? Boo!
And it was just starting
to get good!
-[energy rushing]
-[centipedes twittering]
Centipedes?
You’re Phoebe’s, right?
Ah, yeah!
Also, I’m sure you’re wondering
how I’m here,
and it’s actually
quite simple.
This is the data I saved of
myself just before I died.
Now, do me a favor
and call me gramps again.
I love it! Pretty please?
This isn’t the time for that!
Young Master!
We need to get inside!
[SUIGIN yelling]
[PHOEBE]
They’re really going at it.
Let’s hurry up
and take care of this.
That treasure is waiting
for us to find it.
And get our hands on it.
So we can make
our dreams come true!
-[PHOEBE laughing]
-[EEYUU laughing]
Where are we?
The cockpit
of the Yuuki Thirty-Four.
The Guardian Giant
designed specifically for this
hidden level.
[shimmering]
[chuckles]
Unbelievable!
[explosions]
Finally!
[yelling]
[exploding]
[tomb cracking, thundering]
I did it!
The treasure’s ours!
[explosions]
What is that thing?
[energy shimmers]
[MERMAID 1] Gotta get you all
cleaned up!
[MERMAID 2]
Come on, little miss sensitive!
[mermaids giggling]
[gasps]
[MERMAID 2]
Are you having fun?
Please! No more!
[anguished cry]
The Silver Guardian!