[REI]
Stop, please!
My father would never
have left that much debt!
[MAN] Tell us your sob story
back at the office.
I’m not going anywhere!
Stop struggling!
Bastards!
[YUUKI] Suigin.
Use this inheritance well.
Now, you are the only one
who can protect Rei.
Hold it!
-Huh?
-Who's this?
Let her go.
Right now!
No, Suigin! Stay out of it!
Sorry, Rei. No can do!
[grunting]
[YUUKI]
Protect her from the enemy
and create a new future
for the both of you.
[MAN] Brat!
What the hell is your problem?
[YUUKI]
I’m counting on you.
[MAN] That's right.
Stay on the ground!
[YUUKI]
My grandson.
Make it stop!
Please, I’m begging you!
I’ll go wherever you want.
I’ll do anything you say,
just make him stop.
Huh. Now that’s
the right attitude.
Let's go! They get the point.
Time’s a wasting.
Hmm? All right.
Damn kid better have
learned his lesson.
[SUIGIN]
Wait...
Wait.
You don’t need to take her.
[grunts]
I'll pay her debt.
[shimmer]
[footsteps]
[MAN] You got
five hundred million? Right!
[SUIGIN] Just wait.
You’ll see!
This time, I will save her!
[FEMALE GAME VOICE]
I'm sorry.
It is not possible
to convert in-game currency
into real world currency.
[SUIGIN]
I have all of this money,
and it’s useless.
What's the point if I can’t
use it when it really matters?
[grunts]
[clattering]
Again.
I'm just completely...
[REI]
Suigin!
No! Come back!
I can’t thank you
enough for trying!
It made me happy beyond words.
Please, don’t forget that!
I promise to remember,
no matter where we end up,
you’ll be in my heart,
always and forever!
Thank you for being my friend!
-[SUIGIN shuddering]
-[REI laughing]
All right.
[MAN]
What a freakin' loser.
Yeah, but now he's got a taste
of the real world, thanks to us.
We did him a favor.
[jingling]
Huh?
What's wrong?
No freakin' way!
[glass jiggling]
Sui-- Suigin!
Rei!
[whoosh]
[MAN]
Is this kid for real?
The hell does he think
he’s gonna do?
Hey, knock it off!
Don’t you dare!
Suigin!
[SUIGIN]
Rei!
Please wait for me, okay?
I will, I promise!
Wherever you go, I’ll follow!
I swear I’ll save you,
even if it’s
the last thing I do!
Just wait for me!
Oh, Suigin!
Of course I’ll wait for you!
Forever, if that's
what it takes!
Because I believe
in you.
Okay?
Enough of this.
[yelling]
Eat my grill, loser.
-[yelling]
-[honking]
No, don’t!
Stay outta this!
[tires skidding]
-[clanging]
-[yelling]
-[tumbling, crashing]
-[grunting]
Suigin, no!
[MAN]
You think he's alive after that?
Not our freakin’ problem.
True enough.
[energy surging]
Ah! Who the hell are you?
Hey, where’d the poltergeist
come from?
[SILICON]
The name’s Silicon Totems.
Rei Riku. Come with me.
[heavy running breaths]
[grunting, groaning]
What did you do to Rei?
Answer me!
You must be Suigin.
Temujin sent me
with a message.
“I’ll be waiting for you
in Grave Buster.”
Huh?
My work here is done,
Suigin.
[energy rushing]
[exploding]
[fire sizzling]
[shuddering]
What now?
[siren wailing]
[phone pinging]
[SUIGIN grunts]
[scoffs]
Why won't it work?
Does it need to charge?
I don’t see any batteries.
[gentle snoring]
-[VOICES OVERLAPPING]
-[LING] My friend, Yuuki.
dedicated his life to creating
the best games in the world.
[REI] In fact, I’m not
his biological daughter.
[YUUKI] I raised Rei as my own,
and I am also your grandfather.
[SUIGIN]
Grandfather.
What is Grave Buster?
Just a game, or something else?
Who was that guy?
Where’d he take Rei?
I’m so lost.
What am I supposed to do?
-[shimmering]
-[SUIGIN gasping]
Where’d you come from?
Who are you?
You can call me
Twin Star, Master.
Okay. So, is there a reason
you’re in my bed?
You know the answer, meanie.
You called me here,
and like any good servant,
I do what I’m told.
Sorry, but, uh,
I think you may have
the wrong room, lady!
There’s no mistake.
You’re Suigin Riku.
My one and only Master.
Huh?
[shimmering]
[exploding]
[crashing]
[SUIGIN coughing]
Whoa.
Is this Grave Buster?
It’s huge!
[TWIN STAR moaning]
[SUIGIN]
What the...?
So weird. Why did she keep
calling me her master?
Who is she?
[gasps]
[yells]
-My eyes...
-are spinning, Star.
[SUIGIN]
Huh?
The hell?
[EEYUU]
I like this stage.
Nice and quiet.
[FARIN]
The sky's so big.
I think we’ve stumbled on
some kind of hidden stage.
So many tombs ripe
for the picking.
All right.
Let the grave robbing begin!
Somebody stop the world.
I wanna get off, Twin.
Don’t touch me there,
I’m really sensitive, Star.
Guess these weird things
are her true identity.
-[ALL yelling]
-[explosions]
[YUUKI (DEMON LORD)]
Who dares awaken me?
Holy crap!
What the hell is that?
[TWIN STAR]
Shinryou Academy.
A boarding school filled
to the brim
with the rich
and privileged.
But, among
the celebrity status kids,
one was always alone and worked
several jobs to get by.
Suigin Riku!
Gaming is his only talent.
And he doesn’t pay
anything for them!
After all, he’s broke.
Meanwhile, the Madonna
of the school
is the daughter of
world-renowned game designer,
Yuuki Riku.
The beautiful and
kind-hearted Rei Riku!
She’s loaded!
Despite sucking at the game,
she loves it
and plays it every night!
Get your beauty sleep,
darling!
One night, while
playing her game,
a mysterious masked
character appears
and saves her
from a horrific monster!
What a hero!
Maybe this was destiny!
A fated meeting between the two!
Sadly, the game was discontinued
and they thought they’d never
see each other again!
Then, on the last day
a strange monster appeared
and ruined everything!
Talk about heartbreaking!
But now, there’s a new, ultimate
game called Grave Buster.
Like it suggests,
it’s all about Grave Robbing.
Sounds like there
are a ton of secrets
to be found in there, huh?
Though, who knows
if that’s true.
Now, Suigin’s been left with an
inheritance of ten billion yen!
Lucky guy,
but what’s the reason?
And what’s to become
of poor Rei?
Everything’s about to get crazy!
Don’t you dare miss a minute
of the excitement!
The Silver Guardian!