[sirens]
[MAN ON POLICE COM] We’ve set up
a barricade around the building
and several blocks out.
-[cameras shutters clicking]
-No suspects identified yet.
We’re continuing
our investigation at this time.
Over.
-[footsteps]
-[fast running breaths]
[squealing]
What’s that guys deal?
Who knows?
[SUIGIN]
No. It’s a lie!
[RANSHOU]
I’m afraid not.
Yuuki Riku, vice president
of the God Grave Tech Company,
was murdered last night
in his office.
[SUIGIN]
But he’s...
[RANSHOU]
Yeah. Rei Riku’s father.
[gasping]
[SUIGIN]
No.
[fast running breaths]
[SUIGIN]
Rei!
[shimmering]
[MAKI]
Sorry, Rei already left.
[breathing heavily]
Okay, do you know
where she went?
Apparently there’s
a lot of paperwork
for the funeral arrangements.
So, people from
the company took her.
She said she’ll be gone
for a while.
I feel awful for her.
She loved her dad
more than anything.
[SUIGIN]
Poor Rei.
[FEMALE FOREMAN 1]
Such a tragedy.
[FEMALE FOREMAN 2]
To think her only
living relative would
end up like that.
[FEMALE FOREMAN 1]
I heard he left behind
an enormous amount of debt, too.
Poor little thing.
She’s got a tough road
ahead of her.
[LING]
My friend, Yuuki
dedicated his life
to creating the best games
in the world.
He sacrificed
his own happiness
so we could enjoy
the fruits of his labor.
Even now,
I can’t believe
a light as bright as his
was snuffed out
so early, and so cruelly.
Whatever the reason,
I can’t begin to imagine
what he could have done
to deserve such an end.
I vow that
the God Grave Tech company
will work around the clock
with law enforcement
to find the culprit
of this reprehensible crime,
and prosecute them to
the fullest extent of the law.
And to all our loyal fans,
I make this solemn promise:
we will do everything we can
to make sure his final game,
Grave Buster,
is a world-wide success
that can be enjoyed
for years to come.
[gasps]
Hey. Hold on.
Did I know him?
How?
[birds chirping]
[REI] Sorry for asking you
to come here.
I’m sure you had
better things to do.
You’re so busy.
Oh, please. It's no trouble...
at all.
Well, uh... I’m so sorry.
[REI]
Thank you. I’m fine now, really.
More importantly,
there’s something very special
that I’d like you have.
[SUIGIN]
For me?
[YUUKI]
In the event of my death,
please give this to Suigin Riku.
[SUIGIN]
It’s from your dad?
Hold on. Isn’t this...?
Yes, a Seabay.
He created this console
to play Grave Buster.
There’s never been
anything like it before.
[gasps]
Okay. Why did he want
me to have it?
[FEMALE GAME VOICE]
User identification commencing.
[shimmering]
Username: Suigin Riku.
Identification complete.
System starting.
I’m confused.
That makes two of us.
[BOTH sigh]
[gate clattering]
[SUIGIN] Wait. I still don’t get
why he left this for me.
[REI]
Me either.
I didn’t really know my dad.
In fact, I’m not
his biological daughter.
[gasps]
But, how is that...?
I was really young,
so I don’t remember.
All I know is he took me in
when I was a little girl.
We were close.
But, still,
he never told me about it.
I’m sorry, Suigin.
I’ve made things awkward.
No, not at all!
It’s totally fine!
[knocking]
[SECRETARY]
Miss Riku?
Yes?
Sorry, but you have
a guest outside.
Oh! Thanks, I’ll be right out.
Do you mind waiting for a bit?
[SUIGIN]
Not at all.
[grunts]
[sighs]
Right this way, miss.
[MAN]
Hello.
Didn't know Yuuki Riku’s
daughter was such a babe.
[evil chuckling]
[sighs]
[shimmering]
[FEMALE GAME VOICE]
Welcome to Grave Buster!
What the...?
[FEMALE GAME VOICE]
Your current saved wealth
is displayed here.
Observe.
[shimmer]
My what now?
[beeping]
[ching]
One, ten, hundred, thousand.
[exclaims]
Ten? Ten billion?
No way.
This has gotta be
some kinda glitch.
[shimmer]
[YUUKI]
Ahem.
[yells]
[YUUKI]
Ah, testing, testing.
[grunts]
Suigin, I hope this message
finds you well, my boy.
[SUIGIN]
Huh?
[YUUKI]
My name's Yuuki Riku.
I raised Rei as my own,
but I’m also your grandfather.
Although, it’s been so long,
I doubt you even remember me.
Grandfather? Really?
[whooshing]
[ELLE]
Mission complete.
All the countermeasures
are in place.
[LING]
I see. Well done.
[ELLE]
Unfortunately, he ate a bullet
before telling me
how to open the tomb.
[LING]
It can’t be helped.
We’ll just have to sort
through his estate
piece by piece.
[BASHIDA] There’s no need
to worry about that.
All of his assets
have been eliminated,
and his fake credit
has been sent off to collectors.
You know how vicious
they can be.
Such is the fate of all
who go against Precious.
Death and ruin.
That is the will of Dark Tiger.
And whatever our master decrees,
we will see done without fail.
[evil chuckling]
[YUUKI]
I’m sure you’re confused,
but there’s a reason I left
this inheritance to you.
I want you to use this money
to protect my dear Rei,
and ensure that the two of you
live happily ever after.
[gasps]
[yelps]
♪
I didn’t think it was possible
to be this happy!
Oh, stop, Rei!
What would Grandfather think?
On second thought,
my body is ready!
My body is so rea--
[YUUKI]
One more thing.
Rei and I are not
biologically related.
Her actual mother and father
were brutally murdered
by the enemy.
Her parents were
dear friends of mine.
Comrades, with a similar purpose
and iron resolve.
But the enemy got to them,
and eliminated them...
leaving Rei alone
without a guardian.
[YUUKI]
That day, I became her father.
I did what I could to raise her
and keep her out of harm’s way.
[SUIGIN]
Grandfather.
[REI]
Stop, please!
[MAN]
Not our fault.
Blame your old man
for leaving you this mess.
[REI] My father would never
have left that much debt!
Let go of me!
[MAN] Tell us your sob story
back at the office.
[REI]
I’m not going anywhere!
Stop struggling!
Bastards!
[grunts]
[YUUKI] Suigin.
Use this inheritance well.
Now you are the only one
who can protect Rei.
Hold it!
Who's this?
Let her go.
Right now!
[SUIGIN]
The Silver Guardian