[gasps]
They’re shutting it down
for good?
[wailing cry]
Meow!
[shimmering]
[bell chimes]
♪
It’s almost over.
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
Meow!
The world is ending for good.
And so are my adventures
with you, Rei.
[REI]
Father. What is this?
[YUUKI] I want you to hold onto
it for a while.
If something were to happen,
follow the instructions
inside it to the letter.
Nothing specific,
just... “something"?
Can you give me
a little more than that?
Nothing to worry about, dear.
Merely a precaution.
Dungeon Century was nothing
but a prototype.
It has served its purpose.
It’s time for my new creation
to take its place.
This will be the game
that truly changes the world.
A reality beyond reality.
A masterpiece.
Beyond reality?
Yes.
I realize it’s poor timing,
on my part,
now that you’ve found
a partner you like.
[gasps]
What?
Have you been spying on me?
Sorry.
You’re my precious daughter.
I was worried about you,
that’s all.
[REI]
Daddy, you’re the worst!
[YUUKI]
Yes, I know.
[chuckling]
Gwin!
[laughs]
Meow!
Meow.
-What’s his problem?
-Hush! He’ll hear you. Let's go.
I told him
he’d crash and burn.
Ranshou! Wait up!
[RANSHOU]
What’s wrong, Suigin?
I was under the impression
that you enjoyed
your nightly rendezvous.
[SUIGIN] Yeah, till the world
decided to end.
What’s that supposed to mean?
[chuckles] Come on, man.
Just because the game is ending
doesn’t mean it’s over.
All you need to do is get closer
to her outside of it.
[SUIGIN]
I can't.
She only knows the "me"
in-game, not the real me.
Hold on a second.
You love her, but you’ve
never actually met before?
[SUIGIN]
Can’t be helped.
We live in two completely
different worlds.
Meow!
[FEMALE STUDENT]
I hope he’ll be okay.
[RANSHOU] Don’t worry.
Even if the flames consume him,
I know he’ll rise again
from the ashes.
That’s just the kind of guy
Suigin is.
You’re such
a great friend to him.
[chuckles]
[SUIGIN]
Work.
-[shimmering]
-[laughter]
I need to get to work.
[car approaches]
[DRIVER]
I have your schedule, sir.
We need to be at the office
at 4 PM for
an executive meeting.
After that, President Ling needs
to go over the particulars
of the new game’s
announcement with you.
[YUUKI]
Hmm.
[typing]
[MAKI]
Rei, go to bed!
Staying up late every night
is murder for your complexion.
I’ll be okay.
Don’t worry.
[sighs, laughs] Well, don’t say
I didn’t warn you.
Sweet dreams, Maki.
[typing]
[bell chimes]
♪
[PLAYER 1]
This is bogus!
Why didn’t they make a public
statement about the shut-down?
This was so out of the blue!
[PLAYER 2] Especially after
all the time and money
I spent on this game.
[PLAYER 3]
Seriously!
[PLAYER 1] On another note,
did you hear the rumor?
Apparently they added
a new rare item.
There’s only one copy,
and if you find it,
it’ll grant you a wish.
You’re talking about
the Evening Song Flower, right?
[PLAYER 2]
If we found it,
we could wish
for the game to continue!
[PLAYER 1] Sure, that’ll happen.
Don’t be stupid.
[GAME PLAYERS chuckle]
[PLAYER 1] Still, I can’t
believe it’ll be over soon.
[PLAYER 2] Guess we’ll have to
go all-out until that happens.
[REI] Where are you?
C'mon, Gwin.
-[grunting]
-Meow!
[sighs]
[typing]
♪
This is one of the last times
I’ll get to play with you.
I hate it.
But there’s nothing
I can do to change it.
Meow!
Well, there you are, Gwin!
I’ve been waiting!
You must have been busy.
It’s okay. You’re here now.
We only have a week
before all of this ends for us.
So, until it does...
I say we enjoy every adventure
this game has to offer.
Let’s get going!
[laughs]
[SUIGIN] I see.
As far as she’s concerned...
this is just one game
among countless others.
And me?
I’m just one of her
many gaming buddies.
[SUIGIN]
But, is that really so bad?
Even now, in this game,
it’s just you and me.
In this place.
I’m able to be with you.
[rain pouring]
[REI]
Hey, Gwin.
Did you hear?
They just added a rare variant
of the Song Flower in-game.
No matter what happens,
I want to find it.
They call it
the Evening Song Flower.
Here.
Apparently it grows in one field
out of the whole game world.
I know we only have
a week left to play.
But I’d really like to find it,
if we could.
Uh.
Yes?
Are you saying you want to try?
You'll find it with me?
Oh! Oh, Gwin, you’re the best!
Thank you so much!
[whooping, laughing]
[water splashing]
[REI laughing]
[SUIGIN]
Together. With you.
[typing]
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Good evening, world!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
[MALE ANNOUNCER] We at
the God Grave Tech Company
proudly present
our latest creation!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
The ultimate
in massive-multiplayer
online entertainment!
[BOTH]
We call it, Grave Buster!
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
In Grave Buster,
each player will take
on the role of a grave robber.
Their goal: to loot the various
treasures within each stage.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] And to help
you with this endeavor,
we’re introducing
a new system.
Your ultimate strength
will be your financial strength!
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
The more players pay,
the more powerful
their characters
will eventually become!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Additionally, all players
who sign up will receive
a specially designed console
for free!
Seabay, the platform
of Grave Buster!
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Now, get out there
and raid some tombs!
[BOTH] And aim for supreme
financial power!
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
There are countless treasures
just waiting for you!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Only you can dig them up!
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A reality beyond reality!
[BOTH] That is the essence
of Grave Buster!
Looks like the announcement
went off without a hitch,
just as we expected.
We couldn’t have done it
without your genius.
The name Yuuki Riku will forever
be synonymous with game design.
Hmph.
This is only the beginning,
my friend.
Soon you’ll see my “vision.”
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Reality beyond reality!
[BOTH]
Grave Buster!
[birds chirping]
[grunts]
[REI]
Gwin! Over here!
[chuckling]
[SUIGIN]
The Silver Guardian.