Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 357A]
The Negative Ghosts have
lost in negativity?!
Now listen up. There's no one.
Not anyone in this entire world.
Who can defeat me in negativity!
Aaah!
What a terrible
source of self-esteem!
[ZOMBIE GENERAL LONGBEARD]
That's enough out of you,
Special Zombie Oars.
Bring him down!
Start with the feet!
[ZOMBIE GENERALS]
Huh?
[ZOMBIE GENERAL 357A]
What the...?
[ZOMBIE GENERAL 348B]
There he is! Above us!
Now Gum-Gum--though it's
not really rubber--Gatling!
Nami! I'm here to rescue you!
My love!
[LUFFY] "Blazing Knight Sanji!
Kick Down the Fake Wedding."
[MORIA]
Kushishishi!
You say you're
gonna kick my ass?
[LUFFY] Yep. That's right.
[MORIA] Well, even if
you do manage to beat me,
or even kill me,
it won't do any good.
The zombies will
lose their master,
but the shadows
won't return to you.
[LUFFY] Oh yeah?
That's right.
My power controls the
shadows. That's absolute.
So fair warning, if you
want the shadows back,
then there's only one solution.
You have to get the
commander of the shadows.
In other words me,
to issue them an order.
Because they aren't going
anywhere unless I say so.
[LUFFY] And that's all it's
gonna take to get them back?
Kushishishi!
You got it.
Pretty simple, huh?
You might even be
able to force me
to return them if you
kick my ass hard enough.
Well, I say that,
but with your power.
I doubt you can even
lay a finger on me.
[LUFFY] All right, then.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
[LUFFY] A shadow?
[MORIA]
Kushishishishi!
You have to go
through him first.
Consider him my double.
I call him the "Doppelman."
In the past, I was just
like you-overconfident
in my abilities and full
of unrealistic ambition.
But then I realized that the key
to victory is having underlings.
Real strong ones.
You suck doppel-guy.
Come on. Move it!
I'll never do anything
on my own again.
Without lifting a finger,
my minions will make me
the King of the Pirates!
The King of the Pirates
is gonna be me!
I seem to recall your
zombie making the same claim.
I'm gonna be the
King of the Pirates!
When there's such
an extreme difference
between the body and the shadow,
then the personality of
the shadow's original owner
lingers a bit more than usual.
But that sort of thing can't
last forever, you know.
It's only a matter of time
before all of your
memories will fade and Oars
becomes an obedient zombie
slave, just like the others.
No matter how strong
its will may be,
every zombie will bow
to me sooner or later.
I don't mind being
patient for a while.
I'll get my shadow back first!
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum...
Come, Brick Bat.
[LUFFY] ...Gatling!
Damn! These
things keep blocking me!
How am I supposed to punch him?
Haaaa...
Ow ow ow ow ow!!
Energetic, aren't you?
[LUFFY] Shut up, you!
Bring it!
Waaaaaaahhh!
Pound him! Crush
him! Rip him apart!
Okay, but let's watch
out for the salt!
Damn it!
I'm the only one
who can beat that girl,
but I can't do anything
with her minions around!
This was supposed to
be my chance to shine!
Stupid zombies!
[thinking] My ghosts took
care of the other pirates,
but this guy is a real pain!
[SANJI] I'm dumber
than a mackerel.
I should just die.
[FRANKY] I know, bro.
I wish a stray dog
would step on me!
[ZORO] I should
just crawl around
on the ground like
a worm, and eat dirt!
[PERONA] And what's with
that stupid explanation?
How the heck does
that even work?
I just naturally have
a negative personality!
What?
[PERONA thinking]
Not that it matters.
The wild zombies
will finish him off
one way or another, I'm sure.
[thinking] If I can hit a few
of them with some salt stars,
I can even the odds.
I gotta think of a
way to buy some time.
Wait, that's it!
Oh you got me.
All right, he's done for!
You idiot!
Don't open your mouth like that!
It might be another trick!
[ZOMBIE GORILLA]
Whoa, you're right!
Arrgh! He's probably
plotting something!
Humph! You can't trick us!
Salt...
[ZOMBIE KOALA]
How do you expect to hit us
with those when our
mouths are covered?
...Star! Star! Star!
Just kidding. Pepper Star!
[sneezing]
[USOPP] Eat this! Salt Star!
You cheater! No fair!
You're too gullible.
I'm the king of
sniping and lying.
[ZOMBIE PANDA] You got
lucky once, but that's it!
[ZOMBIE GORILLA] Don't get
cocky with me, human!
[ZOMBIE KOALA] Let's get him!
You're mine now!
Fire Bird Star!
[jeering]
[ZOMBIE CANINE] What a loser!
[USOPP] Oh no.
Make him pay!
[snickers]
What?
[panicked screams]
[ZOMBIE CANINE] Hot! Hot hot!
Guys! No! Wait!
Here goes!
[KUMACY] You can't.
Get outta the way!
I'll set you on fire too, bear!
Come back!
What's with this guy?
This isn't fun anymore!
Can't he just leave me alone
and go bother someone else?
I'm tired of fighting!
[USOPP] I'd give up,
if I were you!
For the record, I'm really
good at running, too!
Get rid of that guy
already, Kumacy!
No! Don't!
[KUMACY] Stop running!
[USOPP] No! You stop running!
And you, too, Ghost Girl!
[PERONA] Not until you stop!
[KUMACY] I won't let you lay
a finger on Mistress Perona!
[USOPP]
Whooooa!
For such a fluffy
stuffed animal,
that thing really packs
a punch, doesn't it?
He can't unzip his own zipper,
but he sure is good at
running and wrecking stuff.
[KUMACY] Now I'm angry.
[USOPP] What?
That was a compliment!
Gimme a break! Wait! This way!
[USOPP] Go away!
[USOPP] Leave me alone!
I mean, come back here!
I mean, don't hurt me!
I mean, you better
run, you bastard!
Wait, where'd you go?
Where'd you go?
[KUMACY] This is stupid!
[USOPP] No! Help!
Aaaah! Stop it! Leave me alone!
[USOPP] I can't help it!
He's chasing me!
[deafening footsteps]
Yay. I made it to the ocean!
I'm getting pumped!
I'ma be King of the Pirates!
You hear me? The king!
[OARS] Yeah!
[SANJI] And skip,
and skip, and skip.
Why, is that a Nami I see?
Get your hands off her!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Your knight has arrived.
[OARS] One. Two.
First we loosen up the arms.
One, two, three, four.
Stretch the legs, there we go.
Ahhh... Nice and loose.
Ah, I wonder why I'm so stiff?
Like my muscles haven't
moves in years, or something.
Hope I 'member how to swim.
Gonna be kinda bad
if I sink like a rock.
Here goes nothing!
This sucks! I'm drowning!
[HILDON] You just
came back to life
and you already
have a death wish!
What would've happened if
you drank that salt water?!
With your size a
little might not hurt,
but in case you missed
the memo-you're a zombie
and that means salt separates
your body and your shadow.
Ah water sure is wet.
[HILDON] Do you have any brains
in that thick skull of yours?
Do you have any? Shut up!
[sighs]
It's okay. Everything is--
Wait this is... a-a goddess!
No, wait a sec. I got confused.
This is definitely Nami.
Just calm down.
Man, that's crazy.
What a surprise.
It's just,
she was so beautiful,
for a sec there I thought I
rescued some goddess by mistake.
Phew!
Huh? A Princess?
No. It's that goddess.
Uh, wait, I mean,
it's Nami, just like before.
That's good.
I mean, princesses
are nice and all...
[ABSALOM] What the hell
is he mumbling about?
This moron is out of his mind.
Hey!
You're a member of that
pirate crew, aren't you?
It's an angel!
[ABSALOM] Oh, no,
it's just my bride.
My mistake. That scared me.
I know, right? I feel
you on that one, man!
I mean, it's like, the only
things that look good in white
are Nami and rice.
[ABSALOM] Amen, brother.
[ABSALOM] You might
say, one look at her
will stop you white
in your tracks. Get it?
So, uh what now?
Enough chit-chat!
Don't you try to
get friendly with me!
[SANJI] Hey! You almost
hit Nami with that!
Attacking me is one thing,
but show some damn courtesy
when there's a lady around!
Oh, by the way your shadow.
It's gone, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
One of the new
zombies we created
was strangely
attached to my bride.
It seems the will of
his shadow hadn't faded,
so he wasn't
obedient to us just yet.
You won't lay a
hand on this lady!
[ABSALOM] That must've
been your zombie.
How pathetic.
They didn't even bother
putting your shadow
in a Zombie General.
And since that's the case,
I'm assuming your fighting
skills are pretty weak.
Both of you are
overdressed weaklings
that run your mouths too much!
I'm one of the Mysterious Three!
All of the Zombie Generals
are under my command!
Do you really think you
stand a chance against me?
Who is that?
Oh, it's Nami again.
This is really
messing me up. Jeez.
Pay attention
to me, damn it!
[SANJI] But you know what, Nami?
You're even better
than all the goddesses
and princesses and
angels in the world.
Get away from my bride!
Listen. I'm already pissed
that you ruined my special day.
Just shut up and let me kick
your ass so I can kiss her!
Actually, you know what?
I'll be generous.
If you drag your sorry,
shadowless carcass out of
here right now and never
come back, I'll let you go.
The thing is,..
I'm really busy right now.
Your stupid captain's stupid
zombie went on a rampage
and smashed up
some of my best men.
But before I deal with that,
I'm kissing my damn bride,
and that's final!
You follow me?
I'm running very
low on patience.
I can't waste my time fighting
with some weakling like--
[SANJI] And you say
I talk too much, you creeper!
Master Absalom!
No way! He weighs
more than 600 pounds
and he got knocked
back just like that?
So this is the big,
bad invisible man Usopp
was talking about. Hmph!
[ABSALOM thinking]
What was with that kick?
Hogback made my body
into the perfect animal!
No human should be
able to do that to me!
Hands of the Dead!
[ABSALOM thinking] How did he
know what I was gonna do?
Damn it, who is this guy?
[SANJI] Basses Cote... Longe!
You're the guy
that showed up on the Sunny
and dragged your filthy tongue
all over Robin, aren't you?
Something is grabbing me.
And I heard you
were peeping on Nami
while she was naked
in the bath, too!
[ABSALOM] Hush, my darling!
Tendron! Flanchet! Quasi!
[thinking] This guy is just a
nobody! How is he so strong?
Cueue! Cuisseau! Jarret!
And why the hell is
Nami unconscious, huh?
You better not have
done anything weird to her!
[SANJI] You call
this crap a wedding?
You say that to my face again
and I'll pound you into
a croquette, you hear me?
I think I'd better
pull back for a second.
Invisi-skating.
Time for Usopp's Salt Balls.
[SANJI] There you are!
[ABSALOM] Augh!
What is this, salt?
[SANJI] Veau Shot!
[thinking] This bastard
doesn't even have a bounty!
What's going on here?
[SANJI] You say you're
running low on patience?
Well, I'm way
beyond that, buddy.
I'm so pissed off,
I'm about to explode!
He did!
[SANJI] And this is isn't
just about Nami, either. Oh no.
There's an issue.
A little something,
between the two of us.
That goes back a long way.
[ABSALOM] There's
an issue between us?
You sure about that?
[SANJI] Oh, I'm damn sure!
You bastard. You bastard!
[ABSALOM] But we just
met today, didn't we?
You must be mistaking
me for someone else.
[SANJI] There's no mistake.
You're the man who
stole my dream from me!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"A Clear-Clear History?
Sanji's Stolen Dream."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!