It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
I am a proud
Captain of the Navy!
I shall not let you pass!
Be it wood or steel,
I'll slash your ship in two!
Good luck with that one.
We won't stop 'til
we reach our goal
and I will cut down
anything in our way!
En garde!
I hate crooked swordplay.
Right Angle Flying Bird.
Three-Sword Style Bull Demon!
Bone Phoenix!
He cut right through it!
Bold Hooves!
No way!
He beat T-Bone!
He must've come from
one of the loose cars.
Gotta hand it to him
it takes a lot of guts
to keep going in
a storm like this.
But still, that's
not enough to stop us.
I'm sure the burden of
justice is a heavy one
but we've a few some
burdens of our own.
Hiss!
You put on a big show,
but you're all bark and no bite!
Go go, go, go, go!
You people are pathetic!
Nico Robin has you eating
right out of her hand!
She's betrayed every
person she's ever met,
and you're here risking
your life to save her?
You're beyond help!
It's time to die!
Three-Spot Decoupage!
Instead of making excuses
why don't you tell me
what you want written on
your gravestone, brother.
Here's my Ultimate Hammer!
Wow, some entrance.
What the hell have
you been doing?
Ow!
Well, as per usual, I've been
kicking ass-and what about you?
Been kicking ass.
It's gotten so noisy
all of a sudden.
I take it all of the escorts
for this mission have
been annihilated then?
Well, we weren't expecting much
from them to begin with.
So it's you, huh?
You're the bastards
who kidnapped Robin.
Be careful.
They use some
pretty weird moves.
And who is this?
Based on what Corgy said,
he's probably that
new recruit for CP9.
Name's Nero, he's
gone through training,
knows four of the powers.
Dammit!
You're in for it now, you
bastard!
Nobody does that to me
and gets away with it!
I'll show you why they call
me the genius of fighting!
Now prepare to die!
Huh?
Hey new guy.
Let me guess,
you must be Rob Lucci.
Sorry I didn't introduce myself.
Just give me a moment and
I'll kill this troublemaker.
Our orders were to
bring him in alive.
You've let your emotions get
the better of you, it seems.
Well, that just won't do.
I'll give you three seconds
to run for your life.
Three.
Run for my life?!
Run from who?
Two.
What?!
Stop kidding around, okay?!
It's not funny!
And one.
No! Don't do it!
I'll give you three
seconds to run for your life.
Three.
Run for my life?!
Run from who?
Two.
What?!
Stop kidding around, okay?!
It's not funny!
And one.
No! Don't do it!
Shave!
You're nothing more than an
incompetent piece of trash.
You call yourself CP9?
Don't make me laugh.
You have to master all Six
Powers to be one of us, rookie.
Kalifa.
Yes?
On our official report, state:
"The new guy was too weak.
He was therefore
deemed worthless."
Understood.
And these are the
agents of justice?
Can't tell which
side is evil, huh?
Just like all the other
Government officials.
You have some
extremely bad manners.
Just doing my job.
A-ha! I knew it!
My intuitive sense of
smell has never let me down!
Enough of this nonsense.
Take off that cloak!
Do it! Do it!
Do it!
Dammit!
This is it!
Ha-haaa!
Wait!
Hold on!
My name is Sniper King.
I'm the mysterious
hero from Sniper Island.
You got that?
Sniper King?
Let's settle down here!
You don't think you're gonna
get away with this, do you?!
Actually, I do!
You should never
underestimate a man
who is willing
to go the distance!
Lucci! Help!
I suppose there's no need to ask
what you're doing on
this train, intruder.
Judging by the way
you opened the door,
I know exactly the kind
of impatient people
we're dealing with.
Yeah.
Guess you'll have
to excuse my manners.
You've come to
rescue Nico Robin?
That is a mistake.
Oh?
Listen.
Her problem is one that's
beyond your comprehension.
You see, there are
some people in this world
who were just born
under a bad sign.
People who are, for the sake of
everyone else, better off dead.
What are you talking about?
For example.
Suppose there exists
a sleeping devil.
One that's capable of burning
the entire world to the ground.
And what if there was someone
with the ability
to wake that devil?
Even if this someone happened
to be an eight-year-old girl.
Don't you think
that for the lives
of every other living
being on this planet,
that girl should
be put to death?
Stop rambling and
get to the point.
What I just told you is the
true story of Nico Robin.
Her very first transgression.
And now, she's accumulated
an entire life of crime.
As far back as she can remember,
her very existence has
been nothing but a sin.
The only good she can
do this world would be
to forfeit her life
and disappear forever.
That's the misfortune
she carries with her.
She's cursed.
She has no choice but
to accept her fate and die.
Honestly, she should've
died over twenty years ago.
We're merely correcting
a wrong from the past.
It'll be better
for everyone else
when this is over
and she's dead.
Hey.
That's enough!
Bastard!
I don't wanna hear
another word out of you!
Pity.
Her death won't come nearly
as quickly as I would like.
Interrogations.
Torture.
Slowly.
Repeatedly.
The World Government is going
to keep her alive for years,
squeezing out all
of her knowledge,
experiences,
and intelligence.
She'll know agony
before she dies.
I'm not gonna let that happen!
Wait! Robin! Please!
Don't go in there!
No! Seriously!
That's a really, really,
really bad idea! Stop!
I said "Wait!"
not "Keep going!"
Robin!
There you are!
We're in deep trouble.
I'm so happy!
Are you okay?
Say something!
Why are you doing this?!
I went through all that trouble
to sneak in from the outside!
I even took out that
snoopy government guy!
So that's Nico Robin, huh?
I'd buy that.
Looks like the girl in the
wanted poster, that's for sure.
Lemme knock these guys
out then we'll escape!
We'll run away together and
leave all this behind us! 'Kay?
It's gonna be all right!
Usopp!
Robin! What are you doing?!
It seems that my words
mean nothing to you people.
Usopp!
Robin! What are you doing?!
It seems that my words
mean nothing to you people.
Franky! Quick!
Detach the third car!
Why? What are we gonna do?
Run.
We're gonna run?!
What the heck are
you talking about?
You too, Sanji!
Get ready!
This will be over in a flash!
Make sure that
Franky doesn't escape!
Right.
Sniper King Smoke Star!
What kind of a
stupid stunt is that?!
Come on!
I've got her!
Move it!
Put me down!
Let go!
All right!
Run!!!
Whoa!
Turn back!
What was that?
He wants us to turn back?
Is that so?
Well that's certainly a relief.
Right.
I suppose we should get ready
to turn this thing around then.
Yep!
Huh?
What?!
But we've already come so far!
No way!
What about Robin
and Usopp, Zoro?!
What are we gonna do?!
About what?
That idiot!
What in the hell
is he thinking?!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Why do you wanna turn back?
Answer us!
Yeah, tell us why!
You better give us a reason!
That's not what I meant!
I was telling that
giant frog that jumped
on the railway to turn back!
He came out of nowhere!
Gero! Gero! Gero!
It's Yokozuna!
Yokozuna?
No way!
Look out!
A giant frog's on the tracks!
Froggy!
Turn back!
Get out of the way!
Gero!
Look out!
Yes!
We did it!
We got Robin back!
You know I should be happy.
But I'm not really a big fan
of this "running away" stuff.
That smoke screen
was such a stupid idea
that it actually surprised them.
Whew!
Sniper King says,
"The plan that involves us
not fighting scary guys like
them is the best plan of all."
Doubtful.
Besides, that was too easy.
Yeah.
These guys aren't
like the others.
We shouldn't let our
guard down just yet.
What's that?
Those thorny whips again?
I've got them.
Now, Blueno.
Right.
Quick! Cut those things!
They're pulling us back!!
Whoa, these guys are powerful!
Did you actually think a
smoke screen would stop us?
Like I said,
that was way too easy.
Now remember, don't kill
any of the Straw Hats.
That was our agreement.
Hey, Sniper King.
Yeah?
Protect Robin with your life!
Got it?
What?
Right!
I'm gonna have to ask
you to let our car go!
What the hell?
His body's like a rock!
I told you, these guys
use some weird moves!
Concasser!
Now that was a
pretty powerful kick.
It almost broke
through the Iron Body.
Careful, Blueno.
Don't take him lightly.
He doesn't have a bounty on him,
but he's one of
their main fighters.
That martial art style is crazy
but they're still going down.
Whoa! Robin!
Hold on a sec!
Wait! What are you doing?!
Now Ocho Fleurs!
With a Clutch!
Long nose! Look out!
Hey! Robin, what are you doing?!
Didn't you hear me?
Stay out of my business!
Leave me alone!
It can't be.
Hey! Buddy! You
should learn to pay attention.
Eyebrows!
You Straw Hats are nuts!
None of you make any damn sense!
All of you are so stubborn,
especially when it has anything
to do with your friends!
Well, we've come this far.
So, you want to escape, huh?
Then here's your big chance!
Franky!
That was uncalled for.
Didn't expect that, did ya?
I don't understand
your intentions.
Why side with them
in the first place?
I couldn't take it anymore.
No matter what she said or did,
those two idiots weren't
gonna leave here without her.
That still doesn't explain
why you're butting in on this.
Ow!
Hey, listen!
Get outta here!
Don't worry about me!
I've got a plan!
When you meet up with Straw Hat,
find some way to get
back to Water 7, okay?!
Franky!
Hold on!
I'm not trying to escape!
I won't run!
Robin, what's wrong with you?
Cut it out!
There's no point in
trying to pretend anymore!
We know, okay?
We know what you did and
we came here to rescue you!
It doesn't matter if they
"Buster Call" us to
the ends of the world,
we'll fight them and win!
There's no reason for
you to keep obeying them
and throw your life away!
You're wrong.
If there's a Buster Call.
You'll be obliterated.
Stop it!
Let her go!
Robin, say something!
Robin, you're hiding
something, aren't you?
That's fine, have it your way.
But remember, a pirate
can't leave their crew
without the
captain's permission.
So believe in him.
Believe in Luffy!
On the next One Piece:
"The Judicial Island!
Full View of Enies Lobby!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!