Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy was sent flying
from the Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma.
After soaring
through the sky for hours,
he found himself in a kingdom
inhabited entirely by women.
Captured by the
pirate empress Hancock,
Luffy was forced into
combat with her sisters,
Marigold and Sandersonia,
who had both eaten
different Snake-Snake Fruits.
Why, of all
the insolent... Mari!
This is your chance
to finish him off!
I can't. Don't you understand?
He isn't mocking you, sister.
That man is... protecting us.
You'd rather die
than let people see this
thing on your back, right?
[LUFFY]
Hancock's Confession!
The Sisters' Abhorrent Past!
Well? Is it all clear now?
[MARIGOLD]
Are you all right, Sonia?
[SANDERSONIA]
Please forgive us, Hancock!
[MARIGOLD] We lost and
were rescued by our enemy!
Okay. What now? You next?
We're done.
I'm not in the mood to fight.
Really?
Is she okay? No cracks?
[LUFFY] So...
you're gonna fix 'em, right?
Make 'em normal again?
[HANCOCK] What?
You heard me.
You can make
'em normal, right?
Can't you?
It's not like they
did anything wrong!
They just told the truth!
C'mon! Please?
[HANCOCK] Of course I can.
I can easily reverse the
effects if I choose to do so.
But...
[HANCOCK] To be clear,
didn't you say you wanted
to go somewhere by ship?
[LUFFY] Yeah.
I gotta get back
and find my crew.
I see.
I have bad news.
You must decide.
I can either
return them to normal,
or help you to
reach your destination.
Choose one. Forget the other.
That's all I'm willing to do.
[chuckles]
Awful. Just awful.
[HANCOCK] You can't fool me.
[HANCOCK]
Now we'll see your true nature.
Good deal!
That's great!
Well, okay.
Go ahead and turn 'em back!
Seriously. Thank you!
That man...
He has such an
immensely powerful Haki,
but didn't hesitate
to save those he owes.
Incredible.
Sister.
Big sis?
[giggling]
[DAISY] It doesn't make sense.
The man defies us, then he
risks his life to protect us?
What a weirdo.
[RAN] There's no
question about that.
But unfortunately for him,
I doubt his kindness
will be enough
for the Snake Princess to
dismiss his rude behavior.
And it's even more unlikely
that she'll forgive the others.
[door creaks]
Hey, look, it's Margaret!
Sweetpea!
And Aphelandra!
Hey, everyone!
I was wondering where you went.
[NERINE] How wonderful!
She reversed the petrification!
I was so worried!
I just couldn't believe it
when you defended that man.
None of us could.
And then you were
turned to stone.
It was awful.
Stone? Huh?
What happened to us?
Most peculiar.
I have no recollection.
You can't remember a thing?
No.
I came to, and the man...
Well, he seemed so happy.
This is great!
I was really freaking out there!
I thought you guys
were gonna die!
[APHELANDRA]
Where did everyone go?
[SWEETPEA] Is the trial over?
Oh, hey, lady! Thanks!
[MARGARET] Snake Princess!
[SWEETPEA] We...
[APHELANDRA] Um...
[HANCOCK]
Continue to dedicate yourselves
to the protection of our nation.
That's... all I can remember.
[NERINE] It's fine!
[RAN] You're not the first
to have trouble remembering
after you've been
turned to stone.
Don't worry, I'll catch
you up on the details
of what happened later.
But what did happen?
And what did
she do with the man?
You really need to ask?
She just turned him to stone
and got on with her day.
[laughing]
Well I could be mistaken,
but it looked like they
took him to Kuja Castle.
What?!
[LUFFY] Hey, what'd
you say you want from me?
Ooh! Please tell me
you're gonna serve up
a big after-battle meal for us!
We're gonna get along
just fine if that's what it is!
So. What's the
best food around here?
Some kind of meat?
Just so you know,
I'm grateful for what you did.
Thank you.
Forget it!
It was nothin'! Really!
Feed me and we'll call it even.
If anyone had seen
what's on our backs,
it would've been the end of us.
We'd be cast out,
never to return.
[HANCOCK] You may enter.
[HANCOCK] I said come inside.
Where?
[HANCOCK] Behind the curtain.
[LUFFY] Oh! You've
got the food back there?
Here I co--!
Hey, where's the food?
And how come you
took your clothes off?
[HANCOCK] My! Astute
and charming, aren't you?
Look.
[HANCOCK] The mark on my back.
You... you said...
[HANCOCK] You said
that you'd seen it before.
I need to know.
Take a closer look.
Where have you seen it?
Do you know
what this mark means?
Answer me. Hurry up.
[HANCOCK]
This isn't pleasant, you know.
[LUFFY] It's not the same,
but it still reminds me
of the one I've seen before.
There's this friend of mine.
He's a fishman,
and his name is Hachi.
A fishman?
Yeah. He's got a mark
kind of like that one
on his forehead,
but it's different.
I've never seen one like yours.
[NYON] If he doesn't
nyo what it is, tell him.
Granny Nyon?
Why are you here?
Snake Princess. Be honest.
You nyo you can
trust him by nyow.
You've seen with your
own eyes he's a good man.
Go ahead, child.
Do not fear.
Your secret is safe.
You... You're the
nyotorious pirate
known as
Monkey D. Luffy, correct?
Yeah, that's me.
But how do you
know anything about me?
You do seem like a
decent enough young man,
despite your reputation.
Take a look at this newspaper.
Just a few days
before he arrived,
he caused an incident
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
an incident with
dire repercussions.
Nyot only did he oppose
the Celestial Dragons,
he punched one of them!
You... must be insane.
[NYON] By some miracle,
he was able to
escape the Central forces
they unleashed to capture him.
[NYON] And just as miraculous...
He traveled from
that faraway location
to here in a few short days.
Both of these things
are beyond my comprehension.
No. That's impossible.
I told you! Remember?
I got flung here.
Honestly! I don't
even know where we are.
I've never heard of it!
And I don't feel one bit bad
about knockin' out
that Celestial Dragon.
Does that newspaper even mention
what that bastard
did to my friend?
[HANCOCK] Then... it's true?
Are you telling me
that you actually struck
a Celestial Dragon?
[HANCOCK] I'm amazed.
I truly had no idea...
[HANCOCK] ...that there could
be such a wonderful fool
left in this world.
To challenge the World Nobles...
And risk your life...
You're just like he was.
[HANCOCK sobbing]
"He" who?
[HANCOCK] I will tell you
everything there is to know.
I can even tell you why your
fishman friend has that emblem.
And also what it means.
[LUFFY] Hachi's mark?
This brand is...
...the claw of the
Celestial Dragon.
The emblem of the World Nobles.
The Celestial Dragons brand it
upon those they take as slaves.
A marking to steal your humanity
and claim you as their property.
And they marked you?
You see,
the three of us were...
My sisters and I...
We were once slaves
of the World Nobles.
You guys were....
their slaves?
It happened when I
was twelve years old.
Okay! Starboard, clear!
Same here!
Port all clear, too!
[HANCOCK] Bow. All clear.
[HANCOCK] And visibility
is high. All is calm.
Careful you don't
fall in the ocean!
[laughing]
Don't make fun of me! Geez!
I'm a warrior now, aren't I?
Yeah, yeah.
Don't worry, we trust you.
[SANDERSONIA]
You tell 'em, Big Sis!
[MARIGOLD]
You know we believe in you!
You hungry?
I brought a snack out for you.
Hey, Hancock?
Sonia? Mari?
Where are you?!
[HANCOCK]
The three of us were abducted
from a Kuja pirate ship.
In broad daylight, no less.
And then we were sold.
From that point on,
we were submitted to
a hell we can never forget.
[HANCOCK] The first men
we ever encountered
were nothing but figures
of cruelty and horror.
Sonia! It'll be okay!
[HANCOCK] The memories
will always haunt us.
Hey, don't put
yourself through this!
I've heard enough! Really!
Please don't keep going!
It was all so awful.
Our world was
naught but despair.
And we prayed for
the mercy of death.
[LUFFY] Hey, c'mon.
But after four
years of that misery,
there came a night
that shocked even the
World Government to its core.
[HANCOCK] It was accepted
as a rule of the world
that no one would
ever dare challenge
the Celestial Dragons.
But on that fateful night,
there was a man
who scaled the Red Line
with his bare hands
and slipped into Marie Jois,
the holy land of the
Celestial Dragons.
This man
was an adventurer who
later led the Fishman Pirates.
Fisher Tiger.
He arrived
with the sole purpose
of releasing his fellow
fishmen who suffered as slaves.
He wreaked havoc
on the World Nobles
without reserve.
[RANDOM SLAVE 415A]
We're free! We're free!
[HANCOCK] Despite his
hatred for humans as a species,
he freed every one of us,
saving thousands of slaves
regardless of
who or what they were.
[HANCOCK] And so we fled,
more than willing to risk death.
[HANCOCK] We owe an
eternal debt to Fisher Tiger.
[HANCOCK] In the end,
Tiger unleashed an army.
Fishmen swarmed the oceans.
But they were cursed to wear
the Celestial Dragons'
mark of slavery.
[HANCOCK]
Tiger was relentlessly hunted
by the World Government.
So he brought
the fugitives together
to form the Pirates of the Sun
and sailed far
and wide across the seas.
[HANCOCK] In order to erase the
last trace of their bondage,
the former slaves
made a new brand
over the claw of
the Celestial Dragon...
...changing them
into a symbol of the sun.
[HANCOCK] There you have it.
By necessity, my brand
bears a similarity in design.
That's why you mistook it
for the symbol of
the Sun Pirates before.
Yeah. Guess so.
The mark on Hachi's
forehead does look like a sun.
Wait...
Does that mean Hachi
used to be a slave?
Possibly, although
not necessarily.
Not all of Tiger's
pirates were former slaves,
but they were all
branded with the symbol
to hide their comrades' past.
Which is why,
former slave or not,
it's safe to assume
that your friend
must've sailed with the
Sun Pirates at some point.
[NYON] Fisher Tiger has
been dead for some time nyow.
Upon his passing,
the Sun Pirates disbanded and
split into several factions.
Hold on.
When did you get
that wound on your head?
Huh? Oh, that.
Don't worry about it, okay?
[LUFFY] I knew he had a
pretty dark past, but jeez.
[MARIGOLD] Now that you
know the history of the mark,
I hope you can better
understand our position.
[LUFFY] Yeah. I think I get it.
[HANCOCK] It's sick--
The things that they
made us do as slaves.
They forced me to
eat the Love-Love Fruit.
And forced my sisters
to eat Snake-Snake Fruits
for their amusement.
Ironically, this allowed us to
hide our secret from the Kuja.
[HANCOCK] They praise our powers
because they misunderstand them.
But if you hadn't covered
Sandersonia's back in the arena,
the ugly truth
would be apparent to them.
I can't stand for
anyone to know of our past!
[HANCOCK] And I shall make
any sacrifice to ensure that!
Even if I must
deceive my own people,
I won't let
anyone control us again!
[HANCOCK]
I fear my own subjects.
I can't let anyone
come close to me,
or they might
know the truth.
[sobbing]
Sister...
Well on the
bright side of things,
it's been years
since you've displayed
even the most faint
affectation of an emotion.
But I welcome your tears
as they prove our sweet
Snake Princess' heart
has not frozen over.
You mock me.
You're the one who
left this nation behind!
That's neither here nor there!
Have you already forgotten
where you would be without me?
Yes, you escaped
the Celestial Dragons.
But you neglected to mention
that you didn't
know how to get home!
Tell me.
Would you have seen
Amazon Lily again
if I hadn't gone
to the outer seas?
You would
have starved to death
hiding in the cracks of the
Red Line if it wasn't for me!
[HANCOCK] A small kindness
you'll never let us forget.
What did you say?!
--Please, Granny.
I've watched
over the three of you
as though you were
my own daughters!
Yes, yes, we know you have.
[NYON] And you have the gall
to dismiss all I've done
for you as a "small kindness"?
Put me down!
Mari! Sonia!
[HANCOCK] I suppose...
...you find me repulsive
now that you know I was a slave?
Huh?
C'mon. Don't tell
me you're serious.
Really.
I told you I hate
the Celestial Dragons.
[HANCOCK]
I've decided I like you.
You said that
there was somewhere
you needed to go, yes?
Well...
My ship's at your command.
Name the place.
You mean it?
[laughing]
[NARRATOR] When the Kuja
Pirates hold a banquet,
Luffy is the
center of attention.
Margaret rescues him
from a sea of admirers
and takes him to Granny Nyon.
She reveals troubling news
about his brother Ace,
and Luffy is forced
to make a decision
that will change the
course of his destiny.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
Saving Ace!
The Next Stop: The Great Prison!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!