Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Negative Hollow!
What?
[USOPP] My name...
is Captain Usopp.
[PERONA] I don't get it!
Why don't my attacks
do anything to you?
I know I didn't miss
that time! What is this?
What kind of power have you got?
Power has nothing to do with it.
I just naturally have
a negative personality!
What?
[LUFFY] "The General Zombies
are Down in a Flash!
Oars Feels like an Adventure!"
The Negative Ghost's
power had no effect!
What kind of a
man is he, anyway?
[PERONA thinking] The Negative
Hollows don't work against him?
That doesn't make any sense!
This has to be
some kind of trick!
[USOPP thinking] Dammit!
Didn't they hear me?
I told them to take
out all these zombies!
I specifically asked for
help and they left anyway!
Even if I could somehow
manage to beat this girl,
with all these zombies around,
there's no way I'd make
it out of here alive!
Crap! Is this the end?
This is impossible!
No matter how I look
at it, it's impossible!
[NEGATIVE GHOSTS]
Horo horo horo horo!
That last one
must have been a dud.
With this final attack,
you'll lose every last
bit of your will to live.
Now. Quadruple Negative Attack!
Negative Hollows!
Holy crap!
He took all four ghosts at once!
All right!
For as long as
Thriller Bark has
floated on the sea.
There's never been a spirit
that couldn't be broken
by the Negative Ghosts!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 357A]
The Negative Ghosts
have lost in negativity!
[PERONA] Oh, Kumacy,
I'm sorry for everything.
Look, even Mistress Perona's
getting negative now!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 357B]
What the hell is this guy?
The patron saint of
pessimism or something?
It's freaking me out!
Now listen up.
There's no one, not
anyone in this entire world.
Who can defeat me in negativity!
Ahh! What a terrible
source of self-esteem!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 357C]
But for someone so pumped up,
he seems to have
gotten smaller somehow.
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 357D]
I think that's
because he's backing away.
Get back here!
Crap! They noticed!
Special Attack: Salt Star!
Hey, jerk!
My animal zombies are too cute
to die, so cut it out already!
Stay away from me,
all of you! Salt Star!
It's salt! Watch out!
[USOPP] Come on!
That's not fair at all!
Why'd I have
to call out, "Salt Star"?
[ZORO] I never
expected Usopp's pessimism
to come in handy during a fight.
Yeah, that was a close one!
If he hadn't have been there,
that would've been
the end for all of us!
[ZORO] Pretty scary power
she's got, that's for sure.
[SANJI] Hey.
I'm gonna run on ahead
and rescue Nami on my own.
[FRANKY] Gotcha.
Good luck! Go kick some ass!
[SANJI] Oh, I will.
I've got the power
of love on my side!
Nami-swaaaaaaaan!!
I won't let you get married!
You hear me?
[ZORO] Hey, uh...
Aren't we pretty high up
for him to jump like that?
[FRANKY] Maybe.
But don't forget: when
the adrenaline kicks in,
you won't feel the
pain until later.
Either way, let's get
to the top of that mansion!
[ZORO] Right!
[FRANKY] That's where
the skeleton guy is!
[BROOK panting]
[RYUMA] So this is how it ends.
Try to show a little
dignity in defeat, all right?
Nyhohoho.
You rise back up like
you're a phoenix or,
around here, a bit
more like a zombie.
No matter.
You won't be able
to stand much longer.
[RYUMA] I'll make sure you
stay down for good this time.
No more of these pointless
efforts to get your shadow back.
Now tell me.
What part of that
wretched excuse for a body
would you like me to sever
with my Arrow Notch Slash?
[BROOK] Shut up.
You don't know the first
thing about that technique!
You have no right
to even speak its name!
[BROOK] I used to serve in
my kingdom's Raider Squad.
The quick draw attack at which
I was most skilled
was originally
called the
"Requiem Lebanderole."
However, my
comdares-in-arms renamed it
in regard to my own
sword-fighting technique.
They called it: "Three Verse
Humming: Arrow Notch Slash."
Even if you share my
personality and my techniques.
You've forgotten my memories
and all the feelings
attached to them.
Which means you will
not use that name!
[RYUMA]
Nyohohohoho.
Well, if those
memories and feelings
make you the real thing, why
don't you do something about it?
Come. Take down the fake.
This will be your
last chance to do so.
Sword Technique:
Three Verse Humming...
[RYUMA] Arrow Notch Slash!
[RUMBAR PIRATE 357A]
Hey! Check it out!
Brook's head is shaped
just like Laboon's!
They're practically twins!
[RUMBAR PIRATE 357B]
What do you think, Laboon?
[BROOK thinking] Laboon.
[BROOK thinking]
More than anything else,
I just want to apologize to you.
[BROOK thinking] An apology
from the depths of my misery.
[BROOK] 50 long years
in these dark waters.
Drifting and drifting,
all for nothing.
[BROOK thinking] Scarcely alive,
but too afraid to die.
[BROOK] It's so lonely.
My life. So lonely.
I'm waiting.
Tell me where you'd
like me to start cutting.
Nyohohohoho!
[RYUMA] Well, while you're
making up your mind,
I think I'll start
with this afro.
Nyohohohoho!
[RYUMA] Well, while you're
making up your mind,
I think I'll start
with this afro.
Nyohohohoho!
Nyohohohohohaha!
What's going on?
The entire mansion is shaking!
[FRANKY] Whoa! What's up
with all this rumbling?
[ZORO] Don't know, don't care.
Probably just an earthquake.
[FRANKY] Is that the laboratory?
Look! There's
the skeleton guy!
Can you hear me?
Looks like you took
quite a beating.
But you're still alive,
aren't you? Say something!
Am I dreaming?
Why are you here?
[RYUMA] Nyohoho...
This won't do at all!
How dare you try to
interfere with our battle!
[ZORO] Not so fast.
[ZORO] Tell me... Are
you the legendary samurai
that slayed a dragon
in ancient times?
Heh! I've been
hoping to meet you.
[rumbling]
What the heck's
going on here?
This whole place is
shaking like crazy!
If I were to guess,
I'd say the ship's
probably been caught
in some strange ocean current.
At any rate,
whatever the hell it is,
I'm blaming everything on you.
Kushishishi!
Oh. Speaking of which.
You're probably not
here to chat, are you?
Just tell me what
you want already.
Oh, yeah.
I'm here because of that
crap you pulled earlier
when you took
my shadow with that lamp.
[LUFFY] I'm taking it back,
along with Zoro's,
Sanji's, and Brook's!
Oh and the old zombie
guy's, too! All of 'em!
My, you're a
greedy one, aren't you?
And how do you plan
on achieving all of that?
Obviously by kicking your ass.
Oh?
Kushishishishi!
[rumbling]
[loud crashing]
What the hell is going on?
I'm trying to give
the closing kiss!
It's kind of a big moment here!
[ZOMBIE GENERAL CAPED KNIGHT]
Master Absalom!
[ABSALOM] What is it?
What's with all this shaking?
[ZOMBIE GENERAL CAPED KNIGHT]
Thriller Bark has been caught up
in some strange current.
We're being thrown
around all over the place!
The whole island is shaking!
[ABSALOM] How did that happen?
[ZOMBIE GENERAL CAPED KNIGHT]
Well, probably because the
Special Zombie is moving
the rudder without permission.
[ABSALOM] What did you say?
[OARS] It's moving! It's moving!
Faster! Faster! Faster, faster,
faster, faster, faster!
Zombie Generals,
listen up! Move out!
Get out there, find Oars,
and stop him no matter what!
[ZOMBIE GENERALS]
Yes, sir!
[OARS] Faster, faster, faster!
[ZOMBIE GENERAL LONGBEARD]
Oars!
That's enough out of you,
Special Zombie Oars. Bring him
down! Start with the feet!
[ZOMBIE GENERALS]
Yeah!
[ZOMBIE GENERAL 357A]
What the?
[ZOMBIE GENERAL LONGBEARD]
He disappeared! Where'd he go?
[ZOMBIE GENERAL LONGBEARD] How
could something that big just...
[ZOMBIE GENERAL 348B ]
There's nowhere for him to hide!
[ZOMBIE GENERAL 348B]
There he is! Above us!
Now Gum-Gum--though it's
not really rubber--Gatling!
I'm tired of everybody getting
in the way of my fun time!
Annihilated?
You mean the entire group
that just left here?
[ZOMBIE 356A] Uh, yes sir. They
were squished flat. All of them.
[ABSALOM] But that's impossible!
Those guys are the strongest
Zombie Division on the island!
The Zombie Generals!
[ZOMBIE 356A] Yes. And he
took them out. Instantly.
That can't be.
Isn't Oars supposed
to be on our side?
Then why is he
revolting against us?
Zombies are
made to be obedient!
It's in their nature!
We can't let him keep up
all this rampaging around!
If we don't find
a way to stop him,
he'll sink the whole island!
Nami! I'm here to rescue you!
My love!
Is he one of the
Straw Hat Pirates?
Amazing!
He was able to fend
off Ryuma's attack!
I didn't know he was so strong!
[FRANKY] He's the Three-Sword
Style pirate swordsman
of the Straw Hats.
You better believe he's strong!
Looks like he's
itching for a fight.
If your pride will allow it,
I think he was planning
on getting your
shadow back for you.
What do you say?
[BROOK] My shadow?
Really? Yes! I beg of you!
Whatever you need to do!
Please get my shadow back!
I'd be ever so...
Enough, already!
Shut the hell up!
Aaaaaaa!
Hey! Skeleton guy!
[ZORO] That's a really
interesting looking katana
you've got there.
Nyohoho. You have good eyes.
Yes, this is indeed one
of the 21 legendary swords
of the highest grade.
A famed black blade with a
reverse-waved temper line.
It's known as the
Clear Autumn Wind, Shusui.
Consider yourself fortunate
to cast your eyes on it.
[ZORO] So it is one
of the legendary swords.
You're right, I am lucky.
Though I did expect you
to have a good blade,
being that you're
a samurai and all.
That settles it.
I'm gonna beat you and
take that sword as my own.
[BROOK] Ah!! Oh, you're so cool!
[SANJI] Nami, my love!
I won't ever leave your side,
no matter what happens!
[ABSALOM] Dammit!
I'm in the middle of an
important ceremony here!
Hey! Are you even
listening to me?
[SANJI] Why should I listen
to you? You're done for.
You've gone way beyond the
limitations of forgiveness.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Blazing Knight Sanji!
Kick Down the Fake Wedding!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!