[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention of
the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind
of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother
Ace, from execution.
Meanwhile on Marineford,
home of Navy HQ,
the epic war over Ace's
life between the Navy
and the Whitebeard
Pirates has begun!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
[KIZARU]
Huh?
[MARCO grunts]
[MARCO yells]
[KIZARU]
Hm. My fault.
I really should've known better.
If your boss was
that easy to kill,
you wouldn't be here
right now, would you?
[JOZU growls]
What the hell is he doing?
[JOZU yells]
Try blocking this one!
[AKAINU]
If we all left our posts...
...there'd be no one
here to do their job.
Great Eruption!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES gasp]
Sure like to be
flashy, don't they?
[WHITEBEARD grunts] Think I'll
have ya light the candles
for my next birthday,
ya magma punk.
I'd rather provide the
lighting for your funeral.
How 'bout it, old man?
[LUFFY]
"A Descendant of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.
Full Speed Ahead!"
[MARINES murmur]
[MARINES scream]
[OARS JR. roars]
How utterly repulsive.
Men are bothersome
enough at normal size.
Ah! Such a magnificent beast!
[cackles]
If I can just get my hands
on his dead body,
I'll have another giant zombie
that hopefully lasts longer
than the first one!
[DOFLAMINGO chuckles]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE A]
Make your way to the scaffold!
[MARINE AA]
Watch your backs!
The Giant Unit's moving out!
[LACROIX growls]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES groan]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE B]
Swallow your fear!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES gasping]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE C] They're
trying to head off Oars Jr.!
Time to live up to our duty!
[LACROIX]
He can't defeat us all!
That thing is impossibly huge!
He's at least twice as
big as a common Giant!
[MARINE BB]
Keep shooting!
He's a living creature!
Bullets should stop him!
[OARS JR. growls]
[SENGOKU] I can't say we were
expecting such a powerful beast.
[ACE whimpers]
[MARINE CC]
Shoot him! Fill him with lead!
[OARS JR. growls]
Oars! Don't do this!
You're an easy target for
them, please turn around!
Hang on, Ace!
I'm coming for you! [roars]
[GIANT MARINE A]
Ah, holy crap!
Kill that beast!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE AA]
Oars opened up a path
for us to get into the bay!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES gasping]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE BB]
Take the bay and then the plaza!
[STAINLESS panting]
Damn it all! Fall back!
Tighten up the defensive line
and don't let them
get to the plaza!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yell]
[MARINES yell]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE D yells]
[MARINE C]
Ah!
[groans]
[COBY whimpering]
I want to run, but I
don't know where to go!
Stand down or die, Navy!
[COBY gasps]
[YUKIMURA grunts]
Nobody needs you
getting in the way!
[COBY whimpering]
[COBY] Rear Admiral Yukimura,
slayer of a thousand men!
[YUKIMURA] I swear,
what the hell are you doing?
[COBY]
Huh?
We're at war here!
We don't have any
use for the weak!
[COBY grunts]
[whimpers]
[COBY] I'm useless.
I'm totally pathetic!
[LACROIX] I've never
had to crane my head up
to look at anyone!
[GIANT MARINE A]
Me neither!
Outta the way.
Ace is my friend and
he needs my help.
Don't try to stop me!
I don't take my orders
from you! Ah!
[OARS JR. growls]
[LACROIX screams]
[GIANT MARINES gasping]
[LACROIX groans]
Vice Admiral Lacroix!
[OARS JR. roars]
That Oars is just as
stubborn as he ever was.
Getting yourself killed
does not make you brave!
Don't stop me, Pops!
I won't stop!
'Cuz I don't wanna!
Not till I'm done!
Not till Ace is safe!
I wanna save my bro!
I wanna do it now, so
he doesn't hurt no more!
I know the feeling.
All right, men!
Help out the big guy!
Go cover Oars!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES]
Yeah!
[MARINE DD] How are we even
supposed to fight that thing?
He's too big!
[LONZ grunts]
[OARS JR. grunts]
[GIANT MARINE B] Don't worry,
Vice Admiral, I'll avenge you!
Ah!
[GIANT MARINE B grunting]
[OARS JR. growls]
[GIANT MARINE B groaning]
We can't do this alone!
We're all gonna have
to attack at once!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE F] Oars is
one hell of a distraction.
Let's make our move!
[HANCOCK]
Slave Arrow!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES groan]
Uh! Wait, what?
They're statues!
So! You're the
Pirate Empress, huh?
Uh... What did you do to me?
I'm crumbling!
[HANCOCK]
Perfume.
Femur!
[ALL groaning]
You psycho!
Why are you attacking
the Marines?
I may have agreed to
aid you in your fight
against Whitebeard's
crew, but I don't recall
making any promises
about collateral damage.
[MARINES growl]
[HANCOCK] Allies or foes,
all men are equally worthless.
Well, except for one.
[MARINES growls]
You can hate me if you want,
but you can't say that
I didn't keep my word.
You're nuts!
Uh. Won't you at least
take mercy on my beauty?
Uh. Uh. Why not?
[panting]
[ALL growl]
I'm comin', Ace!
[ACE gasping]
[MORIA laughs]
Yes! Right this way!
Huh?
[OARS JR. growls]
No, Oars!
Ah, damn it!
I'm gonna save you now, Ace.
Stop...
Nuthin' to fear!
Prepare yourself
for the Ursa Shock.
[ACE gasping]
[ALL groaning]
[COBY, HELMEPPO yell]
Stop!
Oars!
That's enough!
They won't let you reach me!
[ACE]
Hey, buddy...
[OARS JR.]
Huh?
[ACE] It's hard to tell
from all the way down here,
but I can't help but wonder...
Don't you get hot?
Just bein' closer
to the sun and all?
[OARS JR.]
I am hot.
[ACE]
I figured.
Hey y'know what?
We're gonna have to
get you some shade!
[ALL]
No, Captain Oars!
[OARS JR. grunts]
[SENGOKU]
Don't tell me he can still move.
Lovely!
He's every bit as resilient
as the other Oars!
[OARS JR.]
You made this?
Yeah, some folks I met in the
Wano Kingdom taught me how.
Try it on.
[PIRATE A]
Ace ruined two others
before he got that one right.
They burned to a crisp.
[PIRATE B]
That's what happens
when someone who's made
of fire weaves straw!
[PIRATES laugh]
Wow, it's nice and
cool under here!
Then it works!
I like the look!
[ACE whimpers]
[MARINE EE]
Aim and fire!
[ACE gasping]
Oars!
Run away, man!
You're an easy target now!
[OARS JR. groaning]
[OARS PIRATE A]
Hey, Captain Oars!
What're you doing
outside in the rain?
[OARS JR.]
Rain or shine, I'm doin' fine!
I don't get wet anymore!
Wow, I love this hat!
[OARS JR.]
I still can't reach him.
If I can't save you
at least I can take out
one of the Warlords!
[DOFLAMINGO]
Hm?
[OARS JR. roars]
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
[OARS JR. gronaing]
[DOFLAMINGO]
Why'd you stop?
Ace is right there!
[OARS JR.]
Ow, my foot...
[OARS PIRATE B]
Captain!
Hey, Captain!
You're gonna stay outside again?
[OARS JR.]
Why should I care?!
The snow's not gettin'
on my head.
In the heat or the cold,
this hat never gets old!
You're the best, Ace!
[OARS JR. groans]
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
Now that was fun.
[laughs]
Oars!
[OARS JR. groaning]
[MARINE N]
Wait, he's still moving?
[MARINE FF]
He's infiltrated the plaza!
[ACE whimpering]
Gotta go a little bit more.
[OARS JR.] Don't worry,
Ace, I can make it for sure!
[ACE whimpering]
That damn Doflamingo!
He knew I wanted Oars intact!
You don't cut the foot off
a corpse someone's claimed!
Doppelman!
[MARINES gasp]
Finish him!
Spiky Shadow Lizard!
[ACE]
No!
[OARS JR. groaning]
[ACE whimpering]
I made it, Ace.
I'm here to save you.
[ACE whimpers]
[OARS JR.]
Ace!
[NARRATOR]
After Oars Jr. risks his life
to pave the way forward,
the Whitebeard Pirates rush
for the execution platform.
However, just as
their resuce mission
begins to pick up momentum,
Sengoku employs a surprise
tactic that turns the tide
yet again.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Jusice for the Winners!
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!