[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[SANJI] Simmered
three nights and two days
to take off the bitter edge.
Nami and Robin,
my dears, just you wait.
This is a very special breakfast
for two very beautiful ladies.
[LUFFY]
"A Recipe Handed Down!
Sanji, the Iron Man of Curry!"
[USOPP] Damn, this fog is
too thick to see through.
I can't tell what's
right in front of us.
Luffy! Do you see anything?
[LUFFY]
Hm...
Wait a second. I think
I can see something now.
[USOPP gasps]
Hey, guys!
There's a giant ship
right in front of us!
Sanji, get to the helm!
Turn hard to starboard, now!
Ohh! Nami!
I made something just for you!
[SANJI yells]
[USOPP] Uh‐oh. This is bad,
you guys, real bad.
We're surrounded by
the Marines, aren't we?
[LUFFY]
Awesome!
[NAMI]
Think about it, though.
The Marines must be having
just as hard a time
with this fog as we are.
Exactly. It's probably
best for us to escape
under the cover of the fog.
[NAMI]
Yeah, you're right.
We'll keep heading forward.
Everyone keep quiet,
especially you, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Right!
Hm?
Hey, Nami.
Is that a kid standing up there?
A little kid.
What is he doing up there?
[gasps]
[yells]
Hold on!
Please, allow me.
[TAJIO yells]
He's coming around.
The smelling salts
seem to be working.
[gasps]
Where... am I?
Well, kid, you've ended up
on board the ship
of the Straw Hat pirates.
You're... pirates?
Sure are.
Don't you remember?
A little while ago, you fell
overboard off a Marine ship.
[gasps]
You stay back!
You're planning an attack
against the Marines, aren't you?
Pretty ungrateful,
considering we rescued him.
You can't blame him.
He's a Marine, after all.
[SANJI]
Here, eat something.
Keep it!
I don't need help from pirates.
Hah.
You have no interest
in eating something
prepared by a chef
on a pirate ship, huh?
You know, it's not like
it's poisoned or anything.
Give it a try.
You'll settle down once you have
a little something
in your stomach.
[gasps]
[TAJIO]
The soup does look amazing.
I can't imagine making a
consommé as clear as that.
[gasps]
[SANJI]
Hm.
[USOPP chuckles]
[LUFFY laughs]
[TAJIO]
Thanks, that was great!
No problem. You're welcome.
My name is Tajio.
I'm a probationary cook
for the Marines.
I'm Sanji, the chef.
Hah. Whadd'ya think,
pretty good, right?
Sanji, you're great!
You're too good to be
working on a run‐down
pirate ship like this.
You could do better.
[LUFFY]
What did you just say?!
This ship is not run down!
[USOPP]
Yeah, that's right!
This ship is from Syrup Village,
where I used to live!
[CHOPPER]
Was it a sweet village?
[USOPP] No, what are you
talking about? Anyway...
[CHOPPER]
I don't understand.
[NAMI]
Hey, hey, hey!
‐‐[CHOPPER] Why isn't it sweet?
‐‐Everyone just calm down,
will ya?
So, uh, earlier...
[TAJIO grunts]
[TAJIO yells]
[TAJIO] I spilled the curry that
was supposed to be for lunch.
[TAJIO]
I'm sorry!
[CHEF]
You make it then.
Huh?
You're the one who
spilled the curry, right?
Well, if you're
so sorry about it,
then you can be the one
to remake the curry.
And it had better be ready
in time for lunch.
Is that understood?
The chef was entirely
right, without question.
[LUFFY]
Yeah. I agree.
After that I worked really hard.
I tried to make it
again and again,
but it never turned out right.
Tajio, do you have
experience cooking?
It's only been six months now
since I started as
a probationary cook.
Well that's long enough
to learn something.
No, it isn't!
All I've gotten to do
on the ship so far
is wash dishes and
peel some things!
I haven't even
made any food yet!
What's worse...
This isn't any normal lunch
that the curry was cooked for.
All of the ships' captains
have a tradition.
They get together once a week
and have curry for lunch
and this is the week that
my ship was supposed to host.
They're used to great curry.
How is my dish going to measure
up to what they're expecting?
The curry of the Marines
certainly is famous.
I hear the chefs from each ship
are always competing
against each other
to see which one can
prepare the tastiest dish.
Ooh! Sounds delicious.
With six months in the galley,
you should have more
confidence than that.
But if you don't
think you can do it,
just go back to your chef
and apologize again.
[TAJIO]
No way.
I can't tell him that!
If I do then he'll
put me off the ship!
Do you have to cook on a
ship instead of on land?
[NAMI]
And why that particular ship?
Oh, well...
...it's, uh...
Have any of you ever
heard of the All Blue?
[TAJIO] There's the
East Blue, the West Blue,
the South Blue,
and the North Blue.
The All Blue is where
you can find every delicacy
from the four seas in one place.
For a cook,
it's a sea of treasures,
and I'd like to see it one day.
The older cooks all laugh it off
as a dream or a
myth or something,
but I still believe in it!
The All Blue is
out there somewhere!
Marine warships go everywhere,
so I have a good chance of
finding it by being on one.
So that's why... I can't afford
to be put off the ship.
Huh, that sounds familiar.
[NAMI]
Hmm...
I would really like us to get
out of here as soon as possible.
Yeah, if we're spotted,
they'll most likely fire at us,
and that would not
be a good situation.
[NAMI] However, we have to
do something about Tajio.
We should get him back
to his ship, right, Sanji?
Fine, I'll take the kid
back to his ship.
Hey, Luffy. Give us
a hand, will ya?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Gum‐Gum Mooring Line!
All right, Sanji.
I've got the other ship.
This fog'll probably clear up
when the afternoon comes.
We really can't risk
hanging around
any longer than that, all right?
Yeah, that's enough.
[NAMI] How much are you
planning to help him?
[SANJI]
I don't know what you mean.
I'm only going to have a look
at the galley of a Marine ship.
Sanji!
[SANJI]
Yeah.
[LUFFY] All right. You guys make
sure to hold on tight to me.
[TAJIO,SANJI yell]
[SANJI] Luffy, why did you
decide to come along with us?
How'd you plan on
getting back without me?
Fine. You just wait here
and behave yourself, got it?
Yeah, I got it.
This is the galley here.
All right.
I might as well have a look,
as long as I'm here.
Heh, heh.
This is expensive stuff.
That's the Marines for you.
And everything seems to
be in really good shape.
[thud]
What was that?
[TAJIO]
It came from the ship's pantry.
Whoo, that startled me.
[gasps] Luffy, what do you
think you're doing in here?
Exploring.
I was on an adventure.
A chance like this doesn't
come along every day, after all.
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY] So, I guess I'll go
explore somewhere else now!
You can do whatever you want,
but if the Marines find you,
I doubt they're gonna be nice.
Oh, and‐‐
whatever you've got stuffed
down your pants, leave it here.
‐‐[LUFFY grunts]
‐‐[SANJI] Apples, right?
This is the curry, or what's
left of it, at least.
I used to have your job
at a maritime restaurant.
[TAJIO]
Huh?
Yeah. The owner, Zeff,
never did seem to
want to teach me
anything either.
[SANJI]
Day in and day out,
all he ever let me do
was wash dishes.
[ZEFF]
Hey, you, brat.
Just working your hardest
isn't gonna be good enough
in this restaurant,
do you understand?
Just think about it all
for a little while.
Ask yourself why I would
let you into my kitchen
and then have you do
only chores for a year.
That's what Zeff told me
when I hated the kitchen
chores I'd been given.
Ah! Okay, now I get it.
Instead of teaching me,
chef wants me to absorb
his cooking skills.
Because cooking isn't
something that can be taught.
[TAJIO]
Hmm...
You know what?
I'm going to give it a try!
All right.
[TAJIO] Now I just have to
remember what it was Chef said!
[groans]
To make curry,
you basically combine
powder, broth,
vegetables, and seasonings,
and the curry powder needs
to be very delicately blended.
[SANJI]
From the aroma, it seems...
...they take ready‐made
curry powder and then add in
some freshly made garam masala.
[grunts, sneezes]
[TAJIO]
Hmm...
[CHEF] Only a lazy cook
will use an ingredient
that's sat around for days!
The longer ago it was made,
the less intense the flavor!
Ah! It's fresh garam masala!
[SANJI]
Well, it's a start, at least.
[LUFFY]
This is huge!
[MARINE A]
This fog is thick.
We won't be moving
for a little while.
[MARINE B] It'll probably
clear up around midday.
[MARINE B] Oh, yeah,
did you hear what happened
with the weekly luncheon?
[MARINE A]
Think so.
You talking about how that
probie cook has to make it?
[MARINE B]
I'm a little scared to find out
what kinda slop
he's gonna feed 'em!
[MARINE A]
Yeah, I'll say. Ha, ha, ha.
[sighs]
[TAJIO]
For the bullion, at least,
I should be able to use the
stuff that's already been made.
Now I'll prepare
the other ingredients.
For the first step,
I'm going to need to
cut up and brown this beef.
Hm?
[SANJI]
In some beef curries,
the beef flavor stays
locked within the meat
and is not allowed
to intrude upon
the flavor of the curry itself.
From the taste of
this recipe, however,
I can tell that the beef
is used to flavor the curry.
So, the meat's juices should be
dissolved in the broth.
In which case, the kid's
already messing things up
and he just got started.
[SANJI clears throat]
Something wrong?
Nah, kid.
I was just thinking that
cooking isn't something
you should rush through.
[gasps]
[CHEF] Everything in cooking
depends on preparation.
That's the most important part.
It's vital to take your time.
Always keep that in mind.
[TAJIO gasps]
[TAJIO]
Add garlic.
Ginger.
[TAJIO]
Turmeric, too.
Then you put in
some yogurt as well.
[TAJIO] That takes care
of the preparations.
Next, I need to start
sautéing the onion.
[SANJI]
Hm?
Uh...
[gasps]
[grunts]
As a chef, you have to know
that it's not appropriate
to smoke where food
is being prepared!
Earlier I said that
you were way too good
to be a cook on a pirate ship,
but now I take it back!
Well would you look at that.
It seems that I've
singed my hair.
[TAJIO grunts]
[door closes]
[gasps]
[CHEF] Now, begin by sautéing
the onions over a strong flame.
But keep them moving,
so they don't get scorched.
Once the onions are soft,
you lower the flame.
Stir slow and gentle,
and keep simmering them
over low heat until they're
a nice golden brown.
Got that, men?
That's what he meant.
Sanji was just warning me
about the heat level.
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
Wow! This is really high.
The view sure is a whole lot
different from way up here.
‐‐[MARINE C] Huh?
‐‐[LUFFY] Huh?
‐‐[MARINE C] Hey, who are you?
‐‐[LUFFY gasps]
It looks like they've seen me!
[MARINE C]
Hold it!
[LUFFY]
Uh‐oh, where am I goin'?
[LUFFY grunts]
[TAJIO]
Get the pork fat melted.
Then add in the flour.
[TAJIO]
Gently though.
No scorching.
[TAJIO]
Put the curry powder in...
...and add fresh garam masala
to enhance the flavor.
[TAJIO] Now, finally,
we put the ingredients together.
[TAJIO]
Add in the bullion...
...tomatoes...
Add the sautéed onions...
[TAJIO]
...and then the marinated beef.
[TAJIO gulps]
[TAJIO gasps]
[TAJIO gasping]
It's wrong.
[TAJIO]
It's so weak!
[whimpers]
I was right.
I couldn't do it after all.
[SANJI]
Hmm.
[gasps]
[TAJIO]
Subtle flavor.
Sanji!
Nice apple.
It sure is sweet.
[TAJIO]
Uh, Sanji?
[SANJI]
Hm?
[TAJIO]
Thank you so much!
What do you mean?
I haven't done anything
that requires thanks.
I was just looking
around, that's all.
Sanji, you said that
you were just stopping by
to look at a Marine galley,
but you were really trying
to teach me about cooking.
[SANJI] I told you, I don't know
what you're talking about.
[MARINE C]
Over there!
‐‐[SANJI] Huh?
‐‐He ran in that direction!
[LUFFY]
Sanji! Let's get goin'!
Luffy, you idiot.
[MARINE D]
Stop right there!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum Mooring Line!
All right! I got it!
[SANJI]
Tajio.
[TAJIO]
Huh?
[SANJI]
I think it's out there, too‐‐
the great All Blue!
[gasps]
Now, Sanji. Grab on!
[SANJI]
Right.
[LUFFY grunts]
[SANJI yells]
[TAJIO giggles]
Hey, Tajio,
there was a suspicious looking
man up here a second ago.
Did you see where he went?
Hm? I didn't see anything.
Maybe the fog was playing
tricks on your eyes.
[groans] Keep looking!
He has to be hiding
on the ship somewhere!
[MARINE D]
Find him!
[SANJI]
Damn you.
You did this on
purpose, didn't you?
[LUFFY]
I'm sorry.
[SANJI] Really? 'Cause
you don't look very sorry.
[LUFFY]
That's why I'm sorry.
[SANJI]
I'm going to fillet you!
Luffy, what's the matter?
[yells] Did you seriously damage
the Going Merry again, Luffy?!
Oh, yeah, about that,
I'm really sorry.
The Marines saw me so we kinda
had to hurry up and get back.
[chuckles]
[NAMI]
What?! The Marines saw you?
How could you let that happen?
[USOPP]
We got this ship from Kaya,
so it's really important
that we take care of it.
How many times do I
have to tell you that?
[NAMI] We can't just
stand around like this.
Usopp, Sanji, we're
leaving immediately.
[SANJI]
Yes, Nami, my love!
But I can't really
move at the moment.
[ROBIN chuckles]
[grunts] Serve the curry.
Yes, sir!
And now, I hope that
you enjoy your meal.
[CAPTAIN A] My goodness,
this is very good indeed.
[CAPTAIN B]
Yes, not too thick,
and the spices are
blended together perfectly.
[CAPTAIN C]
The meat is so tender
it almost melts in your mouth.
[CAPTAIN D]
Another bowl, right away.
[CHEF]
Tajio.
Yes, sir, Chef, sir?
Make certain that you
get everything cleaned up
in the kitchen.
Oh, yes. Yes, sir!
[TAJIO]
Sanji...
[SANJI]
I think it's out there, too‐‐
the great All Blue!
[TAJIO]
I'm going to work really hard.
And someday, I'll be as
good a cook as you, Sanji.
I promise!
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories
go racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...♪
[USOPP whistles, yells]
[USOPP] Wow! Fireworks
are great, aren't they?
They're just so pretty!
I'd like to set
some off sometime.
What? You mean you'll let me?
I can even set off
that huge one over there?
Now that I think
about it, though,
isn't that one a little too big?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"I Will Make it Bloom!
Usopp, the Man, and the
Eight‐Foot Shell."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!