[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
At the brink of war,
with nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other.
After parting with Ace,
Luffy and the rest of
the Straw Hat crew
continue their journey
through the vast desert.
They are heading
toward Yuba in hopes
of stopping the rebel army.
Whether they will
succeed is still unknown
as the setting sun
watches silently over them.
[LUFFY]
"Ruins and Lost Ways!
Vivi, Her Friends,
and the Country's Form!"
[LUFFY groans]
Looks like Luffy's back with us.
What?
[ZORO] Have you recovered
what's left of your sanity?
You are such a pain.
[LUFFY]
Where're the others?
[ZORO]
No idea.
[LUFFY] Huh? How can you
not know where they are?
[ZORO]
Pretty easily, actually.
[LUFFY]
Are you trying to be funny?
[ZORO laughs]
[LUFFY] You're laughing
at a time like this?
[ZORO]
Yes, I am.
[LUFFY]
Great. So we're lost again?
Yes, we're lost!
And guess whose fault that is!
Is it my fault?
[LUFFY yelling]
[VIVI]
What's he doing?
[NAMI]
He's freaking out again?
[SANJI]
How's he running on air?
He must've eaten another cactus.
He's gone crazy.
Jeez. Why can't he
stay out of trouble
for more than five minutes?
Chopper!
I don't think
he'll be much help.
Yeah, he's in pretty bad shape.
Well, up to you.
Why's it my job?
[NAMI] I seem to remember a
certain debt that you owe me.
[ZORO]
If you don't end up in hell,
I'll kick you down there myself.
Have fun, you two!
Right. Now, let's get going.
But don't you think that
we should wait for the others?
They can catch up by
following our footprints.
[NAMI] Knowing them, they
shouldn't have a hard time
finding us again,
and in the meantime,
we can find someplace to relax.
[USOPP]
Sounds good to me.
[VIVI] I hope that they
really will be all right.
[LUFFY yelling]
[ZORO] You moron!
Would you snap out of it?
Great.
Chopper, would you hurry
up and stick the fool
with a needle or something?
Uh... Yeah, okay.
Oh, great.
I guess I'll just do it myself.
You! Crocodile!
I'll kill you!
What's going on with you?
[LUFFY laughs]
I've got you now!
Just get it together, you idiot!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
Oh, crap.
[LUFFY]
Submarine!
[ZORO] I'm used to dealing
with him when he's being crazy,
but it never gets
any less annoying.
Well, here we go.
[LUFFY yelling]
[ZORO yelling]
[ZORO] How did I end up
following a captain like him
in the first place?
[LUFFY yelling]
[ZORO yelling]
Ow! [coughing]
This sand's hot! [coughs]
[screams]
What's going on here?
What in the world
happened to you two?
Hey, Zoro!
Hey! Hello?
Wake up!
Come on.
[ZORO coughing]
[ZORO]
Thanks for that.
So, what happened?
[ZORO]
Long story.
[CHOPPER]
Luffy's still stuck in the sand.
[ZORO] Let's just leave
him there for now.
Where're the others?
I don't know. When I woke up,
they had disappeared.
How considerate of them.
Oh, well.
We'll have to follow
their footprints
through the sand then.
[CHOPPER]
What footprints?
I know you!
You're that mean
jerk Crocodile, right?
It's time to wake up, moron!
Wait, where are the others at?
Welcome back.
Where did they all go,
and why aren't
we following them?
We fell behind
because we were trying
to take care of you!
[LUFFY] Chopper, you can track
stuff with your nose, right?
[CHOPPER]
That's what I'm trying to do.
But I can't smell
anything at all.
You don't know which way to go?
Can you tell which way
the wind's blowing from?
The wind's blowing
in from our left,
but that's about all I can tell.
Okay.
Since Chopper
can't smell anything,
we know they aren't
in that direction.
You don't know
what you're saying.
[ZORO] Fine, you can just stay
right there if you want to!
Come on, Chopper.
[CHOPPER]
Oh, okay.
[LUFFY]
Hey guys, wait for me!
You can't just leave me here!
[LUFFY]
So hot.
Is Luffy going to be all right?
It'll take a lot more
than cactus to kill him.
[CHOPPER]
Zoro?
What is it?
[CHOPPER] Is being a
pirate always like this?
Like what?
[CHOPPER] You know, climbing
mountains, crossing deserts.
I see what you mean.
Well, we aren't really
a normal pirate crew.
And then there's
our insane captain.
I'm wondering if maybe I
got on board the wrong ship.
What do you know?
I was just starting to think
the same thing myself.
[CHOPPER]
Hey.
[ZORO]
Yeah?
[CHOPPER] You were the
first out of everyone here
to join Luffy's crew,
isn't that right?
[ZORO] Yep, but the rest of
them came on pretty quickly
after that.
[CHOPPER] What made you
join in the first place?
[ZORO]
Why do you ask that?
[CHOPPER] I know I just joined,
but it seems like everyone
on the crew sort of
does their own thing
instead of really
working together.
Especially you.
[ZORO]
Yeah, that's pretty accurate.
I have my own reasons
for being here
and for joining the crew
in the first place.
It's like that for
the others, too.
None of us have the
same goals in mind
as Luffy does.
We all basically
do our own thing
for our own reasons.
It may seem a
little weird at times,
but it works for us, anyway.
It can look crazy,
like we have no idea
what teamwork is.
Especially when you
look at our captain.
He's a real handful.
Yeah, I'm with you on that one.
But still, what is
teamwork exactly
when you get right down to it?
Is it just about
protecting each other,
and helping each other out?
I guess most people
would say so,
but they're just
fooling themselves.
I think real teamwork
is about more than that
in the end.
It's about individuals
taking individual risks,
if you ask me.
You work together by
working separately.
You stand up and
risk your own life.
You do what you can
the best that you can
and then you turn to the others
and expect the same from them.
When you think about it
that way, what's so wrong
with everyone on the crew
having their own agenda?
You know?
But that's my opinion.
[CHOPPER]
I think I understand.
So that's what Usopp
meant when he said
"just do whatever you can."
[ZORO chuckles]
It sounds like a cop‐out
coming from him, though.
As for why I've stayed
on board with this crew?
Working beside him all
this time has ended up
giving me another
goal to work toward.
[CHOPPER]
So what's your new goal?
[ZORO] Sorry. I don't
know how to explain that.
[LUFFY]
Someplace shady! Finally!
Gum‐Gum...
[LUFFY]
Rocket!
[ZORO, CHOPPER yelling]
[LUFFY]
Ah! Nice and cool!
[laughing]
I should cut you in half!
Right, sorry about that!
Heh heh!
Hey, where's Chopper?
Oh! There he is!
What's Chopper doing out there?
He's a pretty weird guy, huh?
Yeah, this is my fault.
I'm sorry.
[ZORO] There's really no point
in talking to you sometimes,
you know that?
[yells]
[LUFFY] Hey, what's up
with this big hole here?
[ZORO] How should I
know that, you idiot?!
[LUFFY]
You okay down there?
[ZORO]
Dammit.
That really didn't feel good.
So where in the hell am I?
[ZORO]
What the‐‐?
Interesting.
What is something like this...
...doing underground?
[ZORO] What the hell are
you doing down here?
[LUFFY]
Lowered myself in.
[ZORO]
And what did you do that for?
[LUFFY]
Why not?
[ZORO] Why? Because
with you down here too,
we'll probably end up
getting separated
from Chopper.
And without his nose,
we're never gonna catch up
with Vivi and the others.
Nah, that shouldn't
be a problem.
[ZORO]
Why's that?
[LUFFY] Chopper's falling
down here, too.
[CHOPPER yells]
[LUFFY]
See?
Where am I?
Hey! Guys! Where are we?
[ZORO] I have no idea
what this place is.
All I know is that we're
definitely underground.
'Kay.
[NAMI]
I'm exhausted.
Why don't we take a break?
[SANJI]
Of course, Nami!
[NAMI]
Oh, come on, Usopp.
You really are pathetic.
[USOPP]
Easy for you to say!
You got to ride Eyelash!
I've been walking
the whole time!
Thanks for the ride, Eyelash.
Hey.
The other three.
How will they find us here?
We are up on top of a hill.
We should be visible,
even from a pretty long
distance away.
I hope you're right.
So, how long do we
have before we get there?
[VIVI]
Since we made it to these ruins,
we should be able to
get to Yuba by night
if we keep on walking.
Finally, we're getting close.
[SANJI] So these are ruins
of old buildings and stuff?
Yes, and they've been
sitting here for a long time,
I'd guess.
Civilization began
here on Alabasta
thousands of years ago.
Many kingdoms have risen
and fallen since that time,
and for many reasons.
Resettlement in search
of water, the occasional war.
Ruins of civilizations
like this one exist
throughout the country.
Many of them we know
almost nothing about.
[SANJI] And centuries
passed, one by one,
leading to the current
Alabasta kingdom.
An epic that always repeats.
Kingdoms rise and fall,
here one day, gone the next.
It's romantic.
Sanji!
Oh, um... My apologies.
Really, sorry, Vivi.
I was just babbling on.
Pay no attention to me.
[VIVI]
It's all right.
Actually, I've found myself
thinking the same thing lately.
What makes a country?
Not its ruler.
Even if the ruler dies,
the country's people
will keep on living.
Culture, faith.
Those can remain
the same even when
a country's rule changes.
So is it really necessary
to try and preserve
everything just as it is now?
What needs protecting?
And what do we let go of?
I've been thinking
about this ever since
the sand pirates and the town
with the fake rebel soldiers.
It's all just so
complicated now.
Oh, sorry!
I'm just babbling about this.
I'm sure these are
questions without answers.
But at least there's
one thing I do know:
what we need to do now.
Stop Baroque Works!
That organization is about
to cause a pointless war
with their malicious scheming.
They're trying to
destroy this country,
and we have to stop them.
No matter what the cost may be.
I don't care how difficult
it is or what the dangers are,
they absolutely
have to be stopped!
Crocodile will never
get what he wants.
Not while I'm alive.
[USOPP] Well, I guess we
should get going now, huh?
Usopp, are you sure
you're all right?
[USOPP] Oh, please!
Are you kidding me?
I'm feeling so strong
right now it almost hurts.
Liar.
My legs are shaking because
I've got so much energy!
You haven't seen
strong until you've seen
Captain Usopp in action!
I won't waver or
fall for one second!
[yelps]
[USOPP]
What did you do that for?!
[NAMI]
All right, we should get going.
[VIVI] What? Shouldn't we wait
for Luffy and the others?
[NAMI]
You're such a worrier.
Luffy is absolutely
determined to beat Crocodile.
Once he has his mind
set on something,
you can just let him
do his own thing.
You know that.
There, my eyes are adjusting.
From what I can tell,
we're in some
kind of giant dome.
[CHOPPER] Yeah, and I think
people used to live here, too.
[ZORO]
What?
[CHOPPER] These look like
ancient ruins or something.
[ZORO]
How can you tell that?
Look at this thing.
It's almost entirely covered
with rows of written characters.
I've seen something just
like this in a book before.
It's like an ancient alphabet.
[LUFFY] Who cares about
stupid stuff like that anyway?
The only thing I care
about is that it's cool
and shady in here.
So nice!
[ZORO]
Okay, let's say you're right.
But then, what's this place
doing underground?
[CHOPPER]
Well... I don't know why.
Was it built underground?
Or was it buried sometime
after it was built?
Either way, I get the
feeling that they're trying
to hide the building
for some reason.
Well, whoever made this place,
it must've taken them
a long time.
Whatever it is, it has
nothing to do with us,
so what's the point
in thinking about it?
Besides, at the moment we
need to be thinking about
how to get out of here.
Right, Captain?
[LUFFY]
But why? It's nice in here.
[ZORO]
Just get up already, will you?
[LUFFY]
No, I don't wanna!
Let's just stay in here a
little while longer, okay?
It's really, really hot outside!
All right, let's get going.
We've gotta hurry and
catch up with the others.
That hole's where Zoro
fell on his ass, right?
[ZORO]
Shut up!
[LUFFY]
Heh. Gum‐Gum...
Pistol!
[ZORO]
What are you trying to do?
Damn it, I just missed.
It's really hard to hit
a target that small.
[LUFFY yells]
There, I got it.
[LUFFY groaning]
[ZORO] And I say again,
what are you trying to do?
Why don't you just
grab the boulder
beside the hole?
[LUFFY coughs]
This is really starting
to bug me!
Gum‐Gum Gatling!
[LUFFY yelling]
[CHOPPER, ZORO yell]
Right, now that's better!
What are you doing,
you crazy idiot?
What're you gonna grab onto
now that you broke the boulder
up there?
[LUFFY]
Oh, calm down.
It's all right. I have an idea.
Chopper, you should
probably get little though.
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum!
Oh, I think I see
what he's doing.
Coming?
Accept it. We have to do this.
Here we go!
[LUFFY]
Spring!
Woo‐hoo!
Luffy, how are we going to land?
Don't know!
Oh, no!
[ZORO] Didn't I tell you
just to accept it?
[CHOPPER] Yeah, but you
didn't mention this part!
[LUFFY laughing]
Well, we're free now!
Hey, where did they go?
Ah! There they are!
[CHOPPER]
Yeah. That settles it.
I definitely chose
the wrong ship to join.
Yep, I know what
you mean, Chopper.
'Cause that's just
what I was thinking.
You're falling behind.
[USOPP grunts]
What happened to all
that strength and energy
you had, Captain Usopp?
[USOPP]
Oh, that?
I meant it in more of
a metaphorical sense,
not literally.
Well, hang in there.
Just a little bit longer.
[NAMI]
Still worried, huh?
[VIVI]
Oh, no.
It's written all over your face.
Yeah, I guess it is.
I'm sure they're okay, really.
I seriously doubt you'll
ever stop being a worrier.
But that isn't always
necessarily a bad thing.
[VIVI]
You know, you guys are amazing.
[NAMI]
Huh?
[VIVI] I've been thinking about
it ever since Little Garden.
You all seem to have so
much faith in one another.
How do you do that?
[NAMI]
How?
I guess it's not really
something I'm conscious of.
I've never really
thought about it before.
[VIVI]
That's what's so amazing.
That kind of unconditional
faith in others
is really difficult to come by.
[NAMI]
I can't say for sure,
but maybe we trust each
other because we all do
whatever we can
the best that we can.
A while back,
Luffy said something
on my home island that
makes a lot of sense now.
You're right, I don't know
how to use a sword,
you bastard!
I'm a terrible sailor.
I definitely can't cook.
And I can't even lie!
[USOPP]
Hey!
And without my
friends to help me,
I would've been dead
a long time ago!
[NAMI]
I remember those words well.
And I thought,
"Huh. This is something that
makes these pirates different.
This is how they are."
If you're alone,
your strength is limited.
There's only so much
that one person can do,
after all.
One isn't enough.
You need friends.
But at the same time,
it amounts to nothing
if those friends aren't
trying every bit as hard
as you to do what they can do.
Well, I don't know if
that was an answer.
It's great.
It's really hard to keep
your thoughts straight
in this heat! [laughs]
[VIVI] Actually, that
answered a lot. Really.
I wonder if that kind
of faith is part
of this country as well.
[LUFFY]
Zoro, Chopper, hurry!
Right.
He gets all of his energy
back now that it's starting
to cool off.
[ZORO]
What's up?
The wind changed.
I can smell...
[ZORO]
What?
I'm sure of it.
It's Nami's perfume.
Over there.
[ZORO]
Good work! Luffy!
We found Nami and the others!
In the sunset direction!
Really? Hey, you guys!
We're coming!
[ZORO]
Don't run off on your own!
We'll get separated again!
Slow down!
[VIVI] I've learned
so much just by knowing
this strange pirate crew.
Maybe.
Maybe these people can
help heal my country.
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[LUFFY]
Did we make it to Yuba?
I can't tell with all
this sand everywhere.
[VIVI]
Something's not right.
[ZORO]
This is horrible!
[SANJI] I thought this
was some kind of oasis.
[VIVI]
The sand is taking over!
The oasis has been swallowed up!
[CHOPPER]
And there isn't any water.
[NAMI] Well, the rebel army
doesn't seem to be here.
[VIVI]
I must stop the rebellion!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Spiders Café at 8 o'Clock!
The Enemy Leaders Gather!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!