Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
After being separated from Mr. 3
and Buggy in the
Starvation Hell.
Luffy and Bon Clay
continued to fight their way
to the lower levels.
[MAGELLAN]
Excluding Saldeath's,
I want all forces in the prison
down on Level 4, now!
[GUARD D] Yes, sir!
Of course, sir! Right away!
If Minotaurus fails us and
they do find the way down,
once they set foot
on this floor,
I will bury them
with my own hands.
That is a lot of smoke!
Don't tell me we have
to go down there?
Ugh! It's bad enough
up here on the ledge!
[BON CLAY] Alas, this is
the Burning Heat Hell
you so desired to visit.
And double alas, it lives up
to its name quite accurately.
Well, damn.
So, what's down there?
And, what're you
two doing here?
I thought you said you
were gonna break out!
Not you again, damn it!
I knew you'd change
your mind and come with me!
Screw you! I hope that
thing eats you alive!
Either way,
take this, you bastard!
My special weapon,
the Muggy Ball!
[mooing]
All right! Now, Gum-Gum!
Mallet Rifle!
[coughs]
[ALL] Yeah, we did it!
We really did it!
We beat the
monster cow thing from hell!
[LUFFY]
"All Forces Have Gathered!
The Battle on Level 4,
the Burning Heat Hell."
[HANCOCK] How much time is left
before they execute Ace?
[MOMONGA]
Twenty-nine hours.
It'll all be over
by 3 PM tomorrow.
That's the plan anyway.
Not that plans always go
the way they're supposed to.
Portgas D. Ace is safe,
for the time being.
We'll transfer him
in the morning.
[HANCOCK] Luffy, I pray that
you're safe more than anything.
That's all I want.
[BUGGY] All right, I'm gonna
ask you this one more time.
[LUFFY]
Heh?
After this,
do you still honestly
wanna go down to Level 4?
Yeah! I knew you
guys'd come with me.
There's no way you're
getting me down there.
I already feel like
my skin's melting off my bones.
What is it gonna take to make
you realize it is too damn hot?!
Does a boiling cauldron
of blood and fire
sound like a good time to you?!
What about "Burning Heat
Hell" don't you get?!
We are not going down there!
Aww, why?
It's pretty obvious!
We wanna go up,
not down! Up! Up!
Yeah, we're trying to escape
and that's up! Don't you get it?
Man, that is one really big
bloody booger I just picked.
You're not even listening!
[sighs] Just let 'em
run away, Straw Boy.
They clearly don't have the
balls to go one step further.
Hey, even my nose
is a damn ball!
Your what? Really?
That is weird.
Okay, we are getting
off topic here.
[laughing] How 'bout
you stop pulling my tail
and I'll get back to spinning?
[laughing]
We've got some
brilliant minds here.
Hey, is it just me
or does it look like
the ceiling is going up?
Ahh. Yeah, you're right, it is.
[BUGGY, BON CLAY]
Uh?
There's kind of a loud
rumbling too. And y'know,
this rushing sensation,
it sort of feels like--
The ceiling's not rising,
we're falling!
[ALL screaming]
Oh, no! My Muggy Ball
must've been so powerful
it caused the floor to collapse!
You wish! It was the force
of my Heavy Kick that did it!
You're both wrong!
It's 'cuz my punch was so strong
it sent out shock waves!
No, no, no.
My Wax-Wax power--Wait.
I guess it didn't really
do that much actually.
Then shut up!
[BUGGY screaming]
[ALL] We're falling
into hellfire! Help us!
[PRISONERS panting]
Please, don't do this, sir!
Please, don't kill us!
[PRISON GUARD A] You deserve
whatever happens to you.
That's the way justice works.
How many people have
begged you not to kill them?
It's over.
[PRISONER C] But, we deeply
regret what we've done!
[PRISONER A]
Yeah! We're sorry, honestly!
--No, please don't!
--[PRISONERS yelling]
[PRISONERS screaming]
[PRISONER A]
Ughh! It burns!
--I'm burning!
--[PRISONER C] Help me!
[PRISON GUARD B]
Keep moving! Lug that firewood!
[PRISONER H groans]
It's too hot. My body.
Even my guts are burning.
I'd rather die
than put up with this.
I'm running for it!
[PRISON GUARD C gasps, grunts]
Get out of my damn way!
I'm through with this!
[PRISONER I yells]
[PRISON GUARD D]
We've got a prisoner escaping!
[panting]
Hey! Move it!
[PRISON H grunts]
Go on, or you wanna get
thrown into the hellfire?
[groaning]
[PRISONER H]
I'm falling!
[PRISONER H screaming]
What the hell?
You can't just kill
other prisoners like that!
You want us to
execute you right here?
[gasps]
Your condition's been granted.
As for your end of the--
I'm aware of the deal.
I made a promise to you,
and I intend to live up to it.
[MARINE A]
Welcome back, sir!
It is very good to be back.
Show her to her quarters.
[MARINE A]
Yes, sir. This way.
I'll bring your dinner
immediately.
[HANCOCK] No need.
Reduce my servings from now on.
Uh. Are you certain about that?
How dare you question me.
Such insolence.
[grunts]
My apologies, madam.
[CAPTAIN A panting]
[CAPTAIN A]
Vice Admiral!
Yes, what now?
[CAPTAIN A]
We just received a report
that Red-Hair had
a run-in in the New World!
[MOMONGA] Shanks?
Are you sure about that one?
The timing doesn't
make much sense.
Who did they say he was
fighting? Not one of us?
[CAPTAIN A]
No, Kaido of the Four Emperors.
[grunts] Did you say Kaido?
That's correct, sir. Apparently,
Kaido was after White Beard.
I hear it was just a skirmish,
but Shanks intercepted him.
I can't say to what end, though.
[MOMONGA]
Bad tidings, but not unexpected.
These are
turbulent waters indeed.
And a brush like this
with the Four Emperors?
That's a deadly serious
circumstance beyond our control.
With Whitebeard safe,
he'll likely come after us.
I fear it may be all out war.
You think his response
will be that extreme, sir?
[MOMONGA]
Whitebeard's men make up
the strongest pirate
crew in the world.
He'd be facing the entire Navy,
including three Admirals,
and the Seven Warlords
of the Sea.
No matter who comes out on top,
this war will shape
the very course of history.
[MOMONGA]
Set sail for Marineford!
[CAPTAIN A]
Yes, sir!
What the hell's goin' on?
The entire upper brass
showed up here.
Magellan, Hannyabal,
and the Demon Guards.
I got a bad feelin'
somethin's about to go down.
[PRISONER GUARDS groaning]
[PRISON GUARD F]
This is murder.
[PRISON GUARD G]
Fasten your fireproof coat!
Straw Hat Luffy and the others
should be coming out this door.
No updates so far.
That's good. Maybe they already
got beaten by Minotaurus.
A true Warden should face
adversity instead of hiding.
Get your ugly mug out here!
[MAGELLAN screaming]
Could you warn me first?
It's too bright!
[HANNYABAL] When you inevitably
pass this seat on to me,
I'd appreciate it if you
made it more open, first.
[MAGELLAN] Shut up. This seat
was custom-made to my liking,
and I like it...
closed, private, and dark.
It's a metaphor for
how I feel about you.
[MAGELLAN grunts]
It's coming!
Huh?
[MAGELLAN farts]
[HANNYABAL]
Ew.
[toilet flushing]
Whaaaaaat?! It's a toilet!
That is gross!
[MAGELLAN]
I can hear you!
[HANNYABAL yelps]
Aww, if I had known
we were just gonna be
standing around and waiting
for them for this long,
then I would have gone hunting.
[MAGELLAN] Patience,
Mistress Sadie, please.
Oh, it doesn't bother me.
But my boys here.
They don't know
what patience is.
The only thing they know
is blood lust.
[PRISON GUARD J]
I have an update!
[HANNYABAL screams]
[PRISON GUARD J]
Straw Hat Luffy and the others
are now located inside
the Well Tower on Level 3.
Which means, we're unfortunately
unable to monitor them.
They've made it that far?!
If they pull this off,
all I have to do is lay
the blame on the warden
then I'll be--Ugh!
It's not fair!
I really wanna be warden!
Uh! I mean, I love your chair.
[MAGELLAN growls]
[MAGELLAN] It'd make our lives
a hell of a lot easier
if they simply plummeted
to their deaths from there.
The boiling Pool of Blood
is right beneath them.
They all have
Devil Fruit powers, after all.
They'd conveniently
sink like stones.
If I die here,
it's all your fault, Straw Hat!
I don't wanna go to Level 4,
it's hot enough already!
Speaking of hot, we're headed
for the Pool of Blood!
Man, this sucks!
[ALL screaming]
[PRISON GUARD K panting]
Warden Magellan! Another update!
[MAGELLAN]
Huh?
[PRISON GUARD K]
I'm afraid that Straw Hat Luffy
has already reached this level!
He didn't pass us!
How is that possible?!
He apparently fell down here
through the well.
[PRISON GUARDS chattering]
But the well leads directly
to the Pool of Blood.
How the hell are they alive?
From what I've gathered,
they used a massive piece
of the falling floor
to shield themselves
and leap to safety.
[MAGELLAN] The bastards
have luck on their side.
One more thing!
What now?
It stinks, Warden!
Ahem. I mean,
this situation, it stinks, huh.
--[MAGELLAN growls]
--[HANNYABAL yelps]
Well, sir.
The demon guard, Minotaurus,
also fell into the well
and apparently he's not moving.
Impossible! They defeated him?
[PRISON GUARD K]
It appears so.
[SADIE] The poor baby!
I won't believe it!
[SADIE whining]
[MAGELLAN]
Pull it together!
[SADIE gasps]
[MAGELLAN] You will follow
my orders carefully.
There are only two ways
to get out of Level 4
that don't include dying.
We have two staircases
they can take
that aren't currently protected
by security guards.
From this point forward,
we're splitting
our forces into three.
Hannyabal, I want you
in charge of this stairwell.
Block all access to Level 3.
Mistress Sadie, I want
you and the Demon Guards
to defend the stairwell
leading to Level 5.
No way! That sounds so boring!
I wanna punish those bad boys!
Surely my outfit makes
that clear enough to you!
[HANNYABAL] Maybe I'll just
let them slip past me
and have the Warden
take the blame.
Any objections?
Please, Warden!
Ohhh. Don't do that!
But I didn't complain this time!
You don't need to. I can sense
you plotting against me.
Oh, and once they're captured,
you're free to do
as you wish with them.
Ohh! Yes, sir!
I can get behind that idea.
And, as for the rest
of the guards,
I want you to pursue them
at all costs.
You bring them to me,
dead or alive!
[ALL]
Sir!
[SADIE squeals]
Almost dead works, too!
This ends right now. They have
toyed with me long enough.
We have a reputation to uphold.
The Burning Heat Hell
shall be their last stop.
But first...
[PRISON GUARD L] The warden's
about to unleash his power!
[growling]
[ALL gasping]
[whimpers]
[ALL]
You're dumping again?!
[MAGELLAN farts]
[BUGGY]
Damn it! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
The floor is
insanely hot in here!
[MR. 3] It's so hot my lungs
feel like they're full of fire!
[LUFFY] Faster we move, the
faster we get out of this place!
Now, which way should we go?
[laughing]
You guys sound
like babies! Whiny babies!
It's mind over matter! Just
pretend the fire's your friend!
Honestly, I can't really
blame you, though!
I do admit it's
a little steamy in here,
even compared to that desert.
Actually, maybe more
than just a little.
[BON CLAY groaning]
My friend the fire
might be turning on me.
[groaning]
Oh, crap!
Your blathering is worse
than the damn heat!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[sniffs]
[gasps] I know which way!
Follow me!
Hey! Where're you going?
[BON CLAY]
So hot!
We're aware of that!
Huh. Now where could our
little Straw Boy be leading us?
Of course, to the kitchen!
[laughing]
Good, because I'm famished!
Wait for me, old chum!
I'm not gonna lie,
food does sound good!
Kinda hoping for
some booze, too!
[MR. 3]
No! Wait a minute, Buggy!
[BUGGY grunts]
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
That food smells so good.
Hot, hot, hot, hot! Oh, boy, I
can't wait for yummy food time.
[PRISON GUARD M]
There he is!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Damn. There's a bunch of 'em.
All this heat's beatin' me down.
But I'll get my energy back
once I get some food in me!
Stop right there!
[LUFFY grunts]
[PRISON GUARDS yelping]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum!
[ALL gasping]
[yelps]
[LUFFY]
Fireworks!
[PRISON GUARDS screaming]
We have found
Straw Hat Luffy, sir!
Team A's locked
in battle with him now!
Team B has just arrived, too!
They've joined up with Team A
and they're closing in on him!
They don't seem to be
holding up too well, though.
[PRISON GUARD Q] Both teams are
requesting to send backup, sir!
What should we do?
[MAGELLAN growling]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum... Whip!
[PRISON GUARDS screaming]
[BON CLAY] A round and
around and around I go!
"Oh, Come My Way" Kenpo!
Memoirs of a Summer's Day!
[PRISON GUARDS screaming]
[PRISON GUARD K] A and B teams
have been wiped out!
C, D, and E have major losses!
[PRISON GUARD Q] Extra backup
from upstairs won't cut it!
They're too powerful for us!
We can't hold the position!
[MAGELLAN growling]
[MAGELLAN growls]
Oh, woe is me! If I only
I were Warden, I could fix this!
[screams]
[PRISON GUARDS chatter]
[growling]
[ALL gasp]
[whimpering]
[growling]
[BUGGY] What're you
freakin' out about, partner?
[MR. 3]
Open your eyes and take a look!
[BUGGY]
Heh?
[MR. 3] There's an ocean
of guards down there!
And think, this level is devoted
to the agony of the prisoners.
Yet, there's not a single guard
manning the fire torture pit.
[PRISONERS screaming]
[PRISON GUARD R]
Let's go! Get a move on!
The first thing we should do
is to check the staircases.
I've got a feeling
they ambushed us.
With all these guards,
they probably boxed us in
on this level.
[grunts]
But, if they've been waiting
on Level 4 this whole time,
that means they
just want Straw Hat!
We weren't even trying
to come down here!
Maybe not, but we are
still trying to break out
and they do know
our names and faces.
Still, there's something
even more troubling.
If they're sending this
many guards after us,
it's extremely likely
they're also sending
in the Impel Down all-stars
to put an end to this chaos.
And I'm not
just talking about
the other three
Demon Guards either.
Warden Magellan himself
might make an appearance,
and then, we're dead, my friend.
[LUFFY]
Get outta my way!
[yelling]
--[PRISON GUARDS yeling]
--Why don'tcha just give up?
Quit blockin' the food!
[LUFFY yelps]
[LUFFY]
Whoa! Freaked me out.
I thought it was a spear
or somethin' headin' at me.
What is that?
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY] Ah, geez, gross!
Is it jelly or poop?
[BON CLAY]
Huh?
Oh no, look!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[LUFFY grunting]
[BON CLAY screaming]
[MAGELLAN] It's time to put
an end to your buffoonery
once and for all, boy!
Who're you?
It's... Magellan!
[gasps]
I've got you now,
you criminal scum!
[NARRATOR]
Magellan finally reveals himself
and Luffy stands up to his
fearsome Venom-Venom power,
even knowing that a single touch
of the warden's deadly poison
could lead to his death.
When Bon Clay cowers before
the might of Magellan's hydra,
is it a show of weakness
or is the situation
truly hopeless after all?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Mighty Magellan!
Bon Clay Bugs Out."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!