[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
What happened to
our 100 million Berries?
Oh, that?
I already spent it all.
We needed to buy lots of
meat and booze for the party.
Spent it?
[loud banging noises]
Since the ship's
free, we'll be fine!
So no worries, right?
Hey, can I have some of
that money to go play with?
I'd sooner
take it to the grave!
Your allowance is revoked!
[LUFFY] A Girl in
Search of her Yagara!
Great Search
in the City of Water.
[YAGARA calling]
What?
[ABI]
Bluefin... What is it?
A dream?
[LUFFY] Thanks for giving me
this delicious
Water-Water candy!
It's awesome!
No problem!
I have the money,
why not share it?
With what's left over,
I wanna buy a medical book!
[LUFFY] Sounds good!
Hey, look!
Isn't that Straw Hat Luffy?
It sure is!
Hey! Everyone!
The town's hero is here!
[MALE CITIZEN 317A]
Great party!
[FEMALE CITIZEN 317A]
Everyone had a wonderful time!
[MALE CITIZEN 317B]
Thank you!
[MALE CITIZEN 317C]
Let's do it again!
Sure! Anytime!
"Anytime"?
Did you already
forget Nami's rage?
There, that should do it.
[CITIZEN 317B]
Really, that party was amazing!
[CITIZEN 317C] Yeah, I had a
blast! I'll never forget it!
Hey! Why don't we continue
the party over at my place?
[LUFFY] What? Really?
[CITIZEN 317D]
If that's the case,
then we should
do it at my house!
[ABI] Wait a sec.
[CITIZEN 317C] No, come to mine!
[ABI] Is that the pirate
Iceberg was talking about?
[CITIZEN 317D]
Who cares whose idea it was?
[ABI] I think it is!
Maybe he could help!
Abi! Wait!
You still need
to eat your breakfast!
[ABI'S MOM] Honey,
I know you're worried,
--but you need to stop!
--Abi, what are you--?
Abi...
We'll have it at
your place next time!
Let go!
No!
At my place,
the party'll never stop!
[CITIZEN 317C]
Like I'll let him go with you!
Straw Hat!
[ABI] Please, listen!
I need your help!
My dear, sweet yagara
has gone missing!
You have to help me find him!
You're a hero, right? Please!
[CITIZEN 317E] Isn't that Abi?
The girl from the photo studio?
Poor thing.
She's still out there
searching for him?
But it's been three days
since Aqua Laguna hit.
If she hasn't found him
by now, he's probably--
Yeah.
[CITIZEN 317F]
An old yagara like him,
surviving on his own
through that giant storm?
Bluefin's not just some
run-of-the-mill yagara,
understand?
He's got a lot of heart!
He'd never lose to
a wave like that, stupid!
What did you say?
Easy, easy.
Think about it, Abi.
You could be right.
He may have somehow been
able to survive the flooding
from Aqua Laguna.
But now, three days
have gone by since the storm.
So--
He's right.
You shouldn't involve Straw Hat
in a wild goose chase like this.
Besides, being
a citizen of Water 7,
surely you know that
tale of Tsui village.
That's where all the
yagara go when it's time--
Shut up! Shut up!
Listen!
I don't believe in a place
that no one has ever seen!
That's just a fairy tale!
Besides, he appeared
to me in a dream!
He said that he
wanted me to find him,
so I know he's out there
waiting for me!
I'll make a deal with you.
They say that pirates only
live for adventure and treasure.
Isn't that right?
Then here.
This is my entire fortune.
If you help me find him,
it's yours. All of it!
Whoa.
Your entire fortune, huh?
But only if you
help me find him.
Straw Hat, please.
Don't do it. Listen to me.
If you somehow end up
in the yagara's Tsui village,
you might not--
Shut up! Geez!
[CHOPPER] Scary!
I can't really
say I understand,
but you're right.
Once we spot a treasure,
a pirate won't be satisfied
until he's got it in his hand.
That's for sure.
[LUFFY] So if
I help you find him...
...you promise you'll give
me that treasure of yours?
That's right.
Sounds good!
Okay. Then it's a deal.
I'm Abi! Pleased to meet you!
Hey! I'm Luffy.
And this is my
crew's doctor, Chopper.
Hi!
A raccoon-dog!
And it talks!
Who're you calling
a raccoon dog?
[LUFFY] So what are
we looking for again?
Weren't you paying attention?
My yagara! His name's Bluefin!
Look.
[ABI] He has a blue fin
on the top of his head.
Bluefin has a blue fin.
Well, that's easy
enough to remember, huh?
Leave it to me!
[ABI and CHOPPER screaming]
What the--?
Why'd we start looking
for him way up here?
Because! Take a look!
You can see everything
in the city from this spot!
It's pretty handy, huh?
I'm scared!
Hurry! Get us down! Please!
Wait. Gimme a sec.
[LUFFY]
It's Zoro!
Zoro! Hey!
Up here! Up here!
Can you see me?
[ABI] He can't even
hear you from here!
[CHOPPER] We're gonna fall!
We're what?
[ABI and CHOPPER screaming]
That's fun! Ha!
Yeah, maybe for you it was!
Take this seriously!
[NAMI] Robin! What do
you think of this one?
[ROBIN] It's nice! Try it on!
Hey! Nami! Robin!
Over here!
Hey!
Hold on.
Maybe Robin can help.
A yagara with a blue fin
on his head, right?
I understand.
I'll see what I can do.
Ojos Fleur!
[screaming]
[CITIZENS screaming]
So, find him?
I'm afraid not.
I tried. Sorry.
t's okay.
Thanks for looking.
Come on, Abi. Let's go.
[LUFFY] Abi.
[LUFFY] See you later, Robin!
[ROBIN] Bye!
[ABI] That was really freaky.
[LUFFY] Well, freaky or not,
thanks to Robin,
at least we know that he
isn't anywhere on the streets.
Aren't you glad
she helped us out?
[CHOPPER] Hey Abi,
may I ask you a question?
[ABI] What is it?
[CHOPPER] What's this
"yagara Tsui village"
those guys were talking about?
[ABI] It's an old legend.
If a yagara is badly injured,
or suffering from an illness,
or maybe it's just
their time to go,
then supposedly,
they swim off to Tsui Village.
It's sort of like
the afterlife for them.
[ABI] But...
[CHOPPER] But?
[ABI] It's said that when a
human sees the Tsui village--
What happens?
The yagaras bring
them into that world,
never to return.
[CHOPPER screaming]
[ABI] It's just a fairy tale!
There's nothing to be afraid of!
[USOPP]
Hey, Captain.
Don't you think a skilled
sniper might come in handy
the next time you're in a fight?
I mean, you never know!
[USOPP] All right, that's good.
That's one more strategy.
Let's see, what else?
Gotcha!
Come on.
Damn it! Oh, no...
[ABI] Bluefin, where are you?
[CHOPPER] He's not here.
[LUFFY] You're right.
Let's look for him
in the backstreets.
[USOPP] I thought I was a goner!
[CHOPPER] Luffy! Over here!
This yagara said he
heard Bluefin's voice
right when he went missing!
On the night of the storm,
you heard a voice saying,
"Don't worry!
I'm on my way to help you!
So hang in there!"
And he said it was old man
Bluefin's for sure, you guys!
That's good, right?
I'll say!
Great! Thank you.
You're the best.
You're amazing!
You can understand
what yagaras are saying!
Stop it.
It's not a big deal.
You dummy!
Let's try searching
the neighborhood,
now that we have a clue,
we'll find him in no time!
[ABI, CHOPPER] Yeah!
[LITTLE GIRL laughing]
[LITTLE GIRL 317A]
Faster! Faster!
[DAD 317A] Hey! Calm down!
[ABI laughing (flashback)]
[ABI (flashback)]
Stop, that tickles!
[ABI laughing]
[ABI]
How is that? Any warmer?
Watch out!
You're going the wrong way!
[ABI] Dad, you can't
be serious, right?
Is Bluefin really blind?
[ABI'S DAD] Yeah.
A hundred years is
a long life for a yagara.
There's not much
I can do for him anymore.
[ABI] No way.
[ABI'S DAD] Bluefin's
been quite useful to us.
A good yagara.
But each day he seems
to get a little bit weaker.
I'm afraid that we should all
start preparing for the worst.
[ABI'S MOM] Poor thing.
I know you're right,
but how are we going
to explain it to Abi?
[ABI] No! I'm not going!
Not without Bluefin!
[ABI'S DAD] We can't take
refuge anywhere with him.
It's the same thing
we do every year.
You understand, right?
No! I won't leave him!
[ABI'S MOM] Our house is
in the middle of town, Abi.
We're too far inland for
Aqua Laguna to hurt him.
Oh, Bluefin...
We'll be back soon!
[ABI] I knew it.
Despite what they said,
he got swallowed up
by the storm.
[ABI] Or--
I don't know many
fish that drown.
We've got a deal, don't we?
I'll help you find him.
Come on now, you can't
give up on him just yet.
é/\That's right, Abi.
[LUFFY]
Save the crying for later.
I'm not crying! Let's go!
[LUFFY] Okay, then.
Right!
Let's go back to where
we started searching.
Maybe we missed something.
You never know!
What's this thing?
Wait!
This is Bluefin's!
It came from there.
[ABI] That's the entrance to
the underground water passage!
Here's more!
--[LUFFY] Hey! Bluefin!
--[ABI] Bluefin! Are you here?
--[CHOPPER] Bluefin! Hey!
--[ABI] Hey! Bluefin!
[ABI and CHOPPER]
Bluefin!
[LUFFY]
Where are you?
[CHOPPER]
Hey!
[ALL screaming]
[LUFFY panicking]
Get me out of the water!
Hurry! Somebody, help me!
[ABI] What's wrong?
It's shallow.
[LUFFY] We can't go any
further on a yagara, huh?
[ABI] It looks like there's
hardly any water at all
from here.
Either way,
let's keep going.
Yeah.
You wait here.
We'll be back soon.
See ya.
[YAGARA calling]
[LUFFY] What's this?
You mean there's a
town underneath the town?
That's kind of weird.
[ABI] Yeah.
The new buildings are
built over the old ones.
It's because of
the rising sea level.
At least, that's
what my dad told me.
What's that? Over there.
[LUFFY] Abi! Wait!
[ABI]
That's gotta be where he is!
[ABI] Soon we'll
be together again!
[ABI] I'm coming, Bluefin!
[ABI] What's this?
[ABI] I can't breathe!
[ABI] It hurts!
Help me! Bluefin!
I'm alive.
[ABI] Luffy! Chopper!
Are you all right?
[LUFFY coughing]
Thank goodness!
Where the heck...?
Hey. What's wrong, Abi?
[ABI] Luffy. Bluefin is here.
This is the same place
I saw in my dream!
Are you saying
we found Tsui village?
Of course not!
That's ridiculous!
That village doesn't exist!
There's no way
that Bluefin is dead!
You hear me?
The Tsui village is nothing
but a yagara fairy tale!
I knew it!
See, he's fine!
Come on, Bluefin!
Let's go home together, okay?
[BLUEFIN calling]
What did he say?
I'm sorry, Abi, but--
Why're you apologizing?
Listen! I've been
looking for you everywhere!
[ABI] Don't worry
about losing your scarf.
I can always
make you another one.
C'mon! Let's go back home!
[BLUEFIN calling]
Well, Chopper?
He said, "No. Sorry.
I can't do that."
Why not?
[CHOPPER] "With this,
I am now at peace."
[BLUEFIN calling]
"Thanks for everything, Abi."
No! Don't go!
Bluefin! No!
Please! Don't leave me!
I've been searching
for you everywhere!
I love you!
Wherever it is you're going,
please, take me with you!
Let go of me!
[BLUEFIN calling]
Bluefin!
[YAGARAS calling]
[YAGARA crying]
What's that?
It's crying.
[YAGARA crying]
His breathing's
a little weak,
but I think he's
gonna be all right!
Bluefin must have found him
and given him his scarf
to keep him warm.
It probably saved his life.
You're right.
That really is the scarf
I gave to Bluefin.
[CHOPPER] "Don't worry!
I'm on my way to help you!
So hang in there!"
He came down here
to save this baby.
That's why he
was in my dream.
[ABI] Here.
Keep it.
I didn't hold up
my end of the bargain.
Really, it's fine.
Thanks for everything, Luffy.
Because of you,
I was able to see
Bluefin one last time.
I'll always be
grateful for that.
And besides...
We were also able to
fulfill Bluefin's last wish
by saving this little baby.
I'm glad.
[LUFFY] Thanks!
Use that to feed the kid,
and make sure he
stays healthy and happy.
Thank you.
[CHOPPER] Hey, Luffy.
Do you really think that
place was the Tsui village?
[LUFFY] Who knows? It could be!
There are a lot of things we
don't know about in this world.
It was a nice place, though.
[AUNTIE] Listen up, everyone!
We've got a substitute!
[ZORO] Listen, I don't have
anything to do with this house.
Got it?
Why would I--
[AUNTIE] Here.
Take care of these kids for me.
[ZORO] Should I give
these two a--Wait!
What am I saying?
No way!
Have you heard
anything I've said?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
Mothers Are Strong!
Zoro's Hectic Household Chores.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!