Hey Chopper, did you
find any new herbs to use?
[CHOPPER] Mhmm! This place
has all sorts of neat stuff.
I got a good stock,
but I'm still in case
I missed something.
Which reminds me, I noticed
something weird a second ago.
There's a little groove
along the trail here.
I wonder what it is.
[USOPP] Oh, you're
right. That is weird.
Looks like a bicycle or
something came through here.
[LUFFY]
Well that's a letdown.
Just looks like a whole
lotta nothing out here.
[snores]
[AOKIJI] Hmm?
A raccoon dog?
See the antlers?!
I'm a reindeer!
[LUFFY]
I saw you fall! Are you hurt?
Who the heck is that?!
[ZORO]
What's going on?
[AOKIJI]
Do you mind? I was sleeping.
Did you hit my friend?!
Oh, man. That guy is huge!
I thought we were
alone on this island!
[gasps]
[CREW] Huh?
You know him?
This guy has Robin scared
out of her freakin' mind. Why?
He's a marine.
Navy Headquarters
Admiral Aokiji.
[CREW]
Admiral?!
Wait, you mean this
guy's an Admiral?!
That's one of the
highest ranks there is!
That's right.
There are only three
officers in the entire Navy
who currently hold
the position of Admiral.
Akainu, Aokiji, and Kizaru.
The only one who outranks
them is Fleet Admiral Sengoku,
the Navy's top official.
The man you see
standing before you
is one of the
three men known as
the World Government's
Ultimate Powerhouses.
But why the heck's
someone like this even here?
Shouldn't you be out
hunting some big-time pirates
with bazillion berry bounties
or somethin'?! G-Go away!
Huh?
Oh, my, my...
What? What is it?
Another very sexy lady
with super big bazongas.
Are you free tonight?
You watch your mouth,
you lanky jerk!
Hey! Focus! Pay attention!
Whoa, whoa, hold
on a second you guys!
Didn't you hear
what I just said?
I'm just out
taking a little stroll.
Don't get so worked up, okay?
I mean you guys are just,
you're like just
what-cha-ma-call-its, you know?
What?
What'd he say?
Hmmm...
[AOKIJI]
I forgot. Oh, well.
You're not making
any sense, you weirdo!
Robin, are you kidding?
You must be mistaking
him for someone else.
This doofus wouldn't
pass as a regular marine,
let alone an admiral!
Hey come on, you
shouldn't go around
judging people based
on their appearance.
The motto I've
always lived by
as a Marine is
Total Slovenly Justice.
Then our judgment was right!
Anyway, what I was saying.
Uh, excuse me a moment.
[AOKIJI] Being on my feet
too long makes me tired.
Yeah? Then maybe
you shouldn'ta been
sleeping standing up, ya' think?
What I was saying,
is that I have no
intention of capturing you
or anything like that,
so just take it easy.
I'm only here to confirm the
whereabouts of Nico Robin,
who hadn't been seen
since the Alabasta incident.
As we suspected,
she's been with you.
[SANJI] That is one
tall piece of apathy.
The only thing high-ranking
about him is his nerve.
I'll put some sort of report
together for headquarters later.
Now that you've added
another crewmember
who's got a price on her head,
your overall bounty has gone up.
100 million, plus 60 million,
plus 79 million equals...
[AOKIJI] Aww, screw it.
Some big-ass number.
Just do the damn math.
[LUFFY]
That's it! Gum-Gum...
[SANJI]
Hold on, Luffy!
[USOPP]
Stop it! Stop!
What are you guys
doing?! Let me go!
Why are you trying to
start a fight with this guy?
Are you crazy?!
He's one of the
strongest marines there is!
I'm not just
gonna stand around
while this jerk tries to
take Robin away from us!
[AOKIJI]
Take it easy!
I told you I'm not gonna
do anything, remember?
[LUFFY] Well, I am!
I'm kicking your ass!
[SANJI]
Stop it, dammit!
[USOPP]
Hold on! Just relax!
Huh?
Eh?
So you're really a marine?
I wish we'd known
that a lot sooner.
Hey, who are
all these people?
[SANJI]
Whoa! Are you guys okay?
[USOPP] I thought this
island was uninhabited.
Well, they're
probably castaways
that washed up
on the shore here.
There was a passenger liner
that was reported missing
about a month ago, last
seen somewhere in this area.
I'm guessing it sank,
and these are the survivors.
How are they, Chopper?
Some of them are injured,
but it doesn't appear to
be anything too serious.
I've got some medicine
that should fix them right up.
But the more
pressing matter is that
they haven't had
much to eat in days.
Their bodies are weak.
Sanji and Usopp went to see
if they could find some food.
They should be back soon.
[USOPP]
Hey! Sorry it took so long!
I can only imagine
how hungry you are!
Take it easy!
No need to wolf it down.
There's plenty more
where that came from.
Yeah! No wolf!
There's plenty!
Hey! Why are you
eating it? Cut it out!
Look, this island
may be deserted,
but you still could have found
food on your own, you know.
You're lucky we came
along when we did.
Their ship wrecked
in the Grand Line.
They're lucky
to be alive at all.
Not everyone was so fortunate.
We were the only ones on the
ship who made it to this island.
So what happened?
We were on our way home
from a gourmet tour of Pucci,
the city renowned
for its exquisite food.
When suddenly, our ship
collided with a giant frog
that was doing the front crawl,
and shattered it to pieces.
A giant frog doing the
front crawl? Seriously?!
Besides, frogs normally
do the breaststroke.
Awesome! I have
got to see this frog!
That sounds crazy.
It's the truth!
Yeah, that was Yokozuna.
Yokozuna?
After what seemed
like days of struggling,
we were finally able to
make it to this island.
It didn't take long to
deplete our food supply.
After one month, we were
on the brink of starvation.
Then, we spotted someone
approaching the island.
We rejoiced until we noticed
he was riding a
bicycle on the water.
Come on. That's even more
far-fetched than the frog!
Ah that was me, actually.
The only boat we spotted
after that was a pirate ship.
[NAMI]
That was us.
Well... That makes you one of
those, uh-uh those you know.
[SANJI and USOPP]
Spit it out, dammit!
Aw, man! I forgot!
Stop screwing us around, jerk!
Calm down, Luffy!
Get a hold of yourself!
Take it easy!
[AOKIJI]
Didn't you hear me?
I told you, I'm
just out on a stroll.
[LUFFY]
A stroll, huh?
Then go take your
stroll somewhere else!
Get out of here!
Why are you so angry at me?
[NAMI thinking] It's like
he's trying to pick a fight!
Okay. Whatever,
I'll leave, but before I do.
You guys should
gather your stuff
and get ready
to leave, too.
Fortunately, I know
of an inhabited island
that's not too far
away from this one.
You should go there and
ask them to help you out.
Hey! You guys!
Don't believe a word
he says, understand me?!
This jerk's a marine officer!
So what? Is that a problem?
[LUFFY]
Oh! That's right! I get it!
I guess that makes sense.
Normally, the marines
are your friends
and the pirates are
the bad guys, right?
Stop it! What's so funny?
Him! How is he
gonna help anybody?
I don't know!
Heck, I don't even
think he has a ship!
Other than ours, there isn't
another ship around anywhere!
Let's see...
There's no ship,
and nobody here seems to
have a Log Pose, either.
How in the world
are they supposed
to get to that island, anyway?
Oh, they'll be fine.
Nothing you say sounds
the least bit convincing.
It's true.
[ROBIN] He does have
the power to help them.
That should do it!
We loaded them up
with food and water.
It should be enough to
last them for quite a while.
Feels good to do a little
work from time to time.
Yeah, no doubt about that!
Hey, you know something?
You're not so bad!
What do you know?
They're hitting it off.
Okay, so now what?
Are you gonna
swim to that island
and drag these guys and
all their stuff behind you?
Don't be ridiculous.
All right, everybody stay back!
What is that thing?
It's some kind of monster!
I bet it's the guardian
of this part of the sea!
Hey, you! Run for it! Look out!
Get outta there! Gum-Gum...
Ice Age.
A devil fruit!
[LUFFY]
The sea! It's frozen!
This is the power of a
Navy Headquarters Admiral.
It'll stay like that
for at least a week.
Head out across the
sea in that direction.
And take your time.
You should reach the
island in about four days.
It's going to be a
little on the chilly side,
so be sure to bundle
up and stay warm.
Is this a dream?
[GENTLEMAN A] The sea has
become as hard as the ground!
We can finally cross it!
Now we'll be able to
get off of this island!
Thank you! Thanks so much!
[GENTLEMAN A] It's a miracle!
The marine granted us a miracle!
[GENTLEMAN A] All right then.
Time for us to get going.
[LUFFY] Right. I'm really
happy for you guys.
[NAMI]
Take care!
I guess there are all sorts
of different pirates, huh?
How can we ever thank you
for everything that
you've done for us?
Not only did you treat our sick
and injured but you shared your
food and water with us, as well!
Aw, don't worry about it!
Good things happen
to good people.
Just let fate take its course.
Make sure the
children don't catch cold.
Keep them bundled up tight.
At any rate, these
colder temperatures
should keep your
food fresh longer.
Thank you all very much.
We will never
forget your kindness!
Take care,
Straw Hat Pirates!
[NAMI]
Bye! Take care!
Be careful on your trip!
Safe journeys! Good-Bye!
That felt really good.
It feels like
winter just happened!
Check it out! I can skate!
Whoa! Awesome, Chopper!
Must be that
Winter Island blood.
[CHOPPER]
How about this one?
You guys should try it, too!
Man, it's cold!
I'm freezing!
Huh?
Hmm...
What is it?
[LUFFY]
How should I put this?
You're the spitting image
of your grandfather,
Monkey D. Luffy.
Or, maybe should I say
you're just as reckless
and hard to figure out.
You knew my grampa?!
Seriously? Luffy's?
Hey, Luffy! What's wrong?
You're sweating.
Uh, nothing! Really! I'm fine!
Your grandfather
helped me out once.
A long time ago.
That's why I'm here.
I wanted to see you
and Nico Robin together
with my own eyes.
On second thought, maybe
I should just kill you.
The government still doesn't
consider you a threat.
But I know enough
of your history
to see you're
a formidable crew.
You may be few in number,
but with the shrewd
rogues gathered here,
this crew will likely
be a problem later on.
Considering the circumstances
regarding your initial bounty,
the numerous daring
actions you've taken,
and the speed of
your overall progress.
I've fought outlaws
for most of my life,
but thinking about
how you'll turn out
scares the hell out of me.
Hey! Wait! Hold on a second!
You said you were just here
to check things out,
not to kill anyone!
[AOKIJI] One among you
I consider the most dangerous.
That would be you,
Nico Robin.
So despite everything,
you are here for Robin!
Now I'm really
gonna kick your ass!
The size of her bounty
isn't merely a reflection
of her strength and power,
it also represents
something else.
That would be
the level of threat
and danger that she poses
to the World Government.
That's why a
79-million-berry-bounty
was placed on her head at
the tender young age of 8.
I'm impressed you were able to
survive, especially as a child.
You managed to betray,
sidestep, and escape
from everyone in your past.
And then found a new
partner to make use of.
You survived in the underworld
by being quick to switch sides.
And now you've chosen this
crew as your next haven.
That's enough, jerk!
I'm not just gonna stand here
and let you speak
to a lady like that!
What kind of ridiculous grudge
are you holding against Robin?!
Stop it, Sanji!
I don't have
anything against her.
The only connection
we have between us
is that I let her escape
from me one time,
but that's about it.
It was a long time ago.
You will all learn soon enough
that protecting this
troublesome woman
leads to nothing but regret.
If you need proof,
consider this.
Every organization that
she's had something to do with
in the past has
been annihilated.
Not one single, solitary
member escaped, except for her.
Why is that, Nico Robin?
Shut up, you jerk!
The past doesn't matter!
That's right!
If it did, then
we wouldn't have
a dangerous former pirate
hunter guy or a degenerate,
conniving, ex-thief woman
on our crew, would we?!
Don't go overboard!
[SANJI] Who we are now is more
important than who we were!
[CHOPPER] That's right!
Robin is our friend!
Don't you dare say anything
bad about her, you hear me?!
I see. So these poor fools
don't suspect a thing.
Just get to the point!
If you want to arrest me,
then why not just
do it already?!
Trienta Fleurs!
No! Robin!
My, my, my!
Did something
I say strike a nerve?
That's too bad.
I must have overestimated how
reasonable a woman you were.
And clutch!
AAAH! He shattered
into a million pieces!
It didn't work! We're screwed!
Let's get out of here!
Everybody run for your lives!
AAAAAHHHH!
Now, now. That wasn't
a very nice thing to do.
Ice Saber!
I didn't wanna have
to kill you, but now.
[clank]
Slice Shoot!
Yeah!
I don't remember asking
for your help, cook.
Funny, I was gonna say the
same thing to you, moss head.
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
He's cold!
Ah-h! He froze 'em!
He froze 'em! Ah-h!!
He got all three
of them! At once!
He's freezing them solid!
I have to help quickly!
If they get frostbite,
their limbs will start to rot!
Usopp, what are you doing?!
We have to save them! Now!
I want to help! I'm trying to!
But I can't seem to move!
Did he freeze me, too?
No! You're just too
scared to move, coward!
Aaaaah!! Luffy!
Sanji! Zoro!
Hold on! We'll save you!
Robin! Run away!
You have some
very loyal friends.
But you will never
change, Nico Robin!
No! That's not true!
Robin! Get away
from him! Watch out!
I'm not who I--
Robin!
Aaaah!!
♪ ending song ♪
[USOPP]
Aaah!! Robin!
[CHOPPER]
She's frozen!
[AOKIJI]
Don't despair!
Her death will be
a benefit the world!
[ZORO]
What'd you say?!
[SANJI]
Bastard!
[LUFFY]
Everyone, wait!
[NAMI]
Luffy?
[LUFFY] Step back. I'm gonna
handle this guy on my own.
[AOKIJI] Fine by me, but
what about the-the, uhm...
What-cha-ma-call-it?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Duel Between Rubber
and Ice! Luffy vs Aokiji!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!