[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are
turning on each other.
After a long time away, Princess
Vivi has returned at last,
landing in the port
city of Nanohana,
accompanied by Luffy
and the Straw Hat crew.
While avoiding the
Baroque Works assassins,
the gang prepares to
travel across the desert
in order to stop the
rebel army from attacking.
However, they are
missing their captain.
Luffy rushed ahead of the
others in search of food
and found himself
lost outside the city.
[LUFFY] "The Heroes' Reunion!
His Name is Fire Fist Ace!"
[CITY FOLK chattering]
[sighs]
Oh hello there, young traveler.
I've never seen you
around before,
is this your first time here?
Would you care to take a look
at this solid gold apple?
I don't normally do this,
but I can usually tell when
someone has a discerning eye.
This apple's magic,
it's from an ancient ruin
and with just one bite you can
live for a thousand years.
Thanks, but no thanks.
I'm not really all
that interested in
living for a thousand years.
Just living today
is good enough.
[FRUIT SELLER gasps]
[FRUIT SELLER groans]
[FRUIT SELLER]
Huh?
[CHOPPER, USOPP gasp]
Solid gold, wow!
And live a thousand years?!
Really, you found it in
some ancient ruins? No way!
Oh yes, I sure did.
This is a legendary artifact
from an ancient land.
And after one bite, we can
really live that long?!
Of course, I would
never lie to a customer.
[CHOPPER, USOPP]
Amazing! That's so cool!
You men can certainly spot
a treasure, so I guess...
...for a one time price of
only a thousand Berries,
this apple is yours.
[BOTH]
For a thousand? That's all?!
Oh yeah! Solid‐‐
[BOTH groan]
Idiots!
Really, what are you thinking?
If I were you, I wouldn't
take his word for it.
[ASSISTANT gasps]
[USOPP]
Hey! Let go, Nami!
What are you doing?!
Put us down!
This is harassment!
We were just...
[NAMI] You two need to
quit wasting time and
look for Luffy with
the rest of us.
We're done shopping here,
so as soon as we find
the idiot, we're leaving.
Do you understand?
Okay, where would Luffy be?
He's got to be around
here somewhere.
[NAMI]
Shut up you two!
[CHOPPER]
Sorry...
Who is that?
[ACE] I just have one question.
Have you seen this guy?
Huh?
Hmm... His name's
Monkey D. Luffy?
‐‐[ZORO gasps]
‐‐[NAMI, USOPP, CHOPPER gasp]
[ACE] He might be in
town here somewhere.
I've been looking
for him for a while.
Well... I've never seen him.
If you want to find him,
then I would suggest
asking around that
restaurant over there.
The owner seems to know
everyone passing through.
[ACE]
Thank you, ma'am.
A restaurant? Huh.
Well, I was just starting to
feel a bit hungry anyway.
Who's that?
He sure looks like
he'd be really strong.
And why do ya think
he's looking for Luffy?
Maybe he's a bounty hunter.
He's not.
I'm sure of it.
The mark on his back.
[ALL]
Huh?
[ZORO]
I used to hunt pirates.
There's no way I
wouldn't recognize it.
[CHOPPER, USOPP, NAMI]
Hm...
Huh?
Oh no... is that her?
You've got to be kidding me!
Selling a sword like this
for 200,000 Berries
is nothing short of stealing!
Come on! Do you even have
a permit to sell these?
[groans] Yeah, it's her.
I didn't know you were
Zoro, and a pirate as well.
You lied...
You're just another liar!
You know there's no way I'm
going to allow someone like you
to leave town with such
a legendary sword.
Give it to me!
The Wado ichimonji!
Right now, damn it!
[yells]
I can't believe it.
What is that woman
doing out here?
You better never try to pull
another stunt like that again!
You understand me?
[yelps]
Hey Zoro, what are you doing?
Why are you hiding over here?
[ZORO] I swear, that woman
is nothing but trouble!
Damn it!
[SMOKER]
Hey, Tashigi.
[TASHIGI]
Captain Smoker!
Here.
Idiot small time pirates.
They made the mistake of
thinking that they could act
like hot‐shots on my watch,
so I was forced to
teach them a lesson.
Your dedication is inspiring.
Not a single pirate rogue will
ever escape with you around.
[SMOKER]
If you're done chattering,
have the Alabasta Royal Army
take care of these scum.
Yes sir!
So far I haven't heard anything
about Straw Hat Luffy
and the rest of them having
landed on this island.
But don't let your guard down.
They'll show up.
I'm sure of it.
That's Captain Smoker.
He's the Marine who caused us
a lot of trouble in Loguetown.
You mean‐‐
[USOPP] You think he and
his Marines followed us
all the way here from Loguetown?
Seems to be the case.
With him and that mystery man,
things could start to
get pretty ugly here.
Come on Luffy...
...show up!
[panting]
[LUFFY]
Uh, I'm so hungry...
[whines]
Well, it was fun!
Thanks a whole lot
for the food, old guy.
[chewing] Good food. Want more.
That little bit
wasn't enough food...
‐‐[STOMACH grumbles]
‐‐[LUFFY sighs]
[LUFFY] Where's the city?
Where's a restaurant?
Can't a guy get any food in
this stupid desert place!
[sighs]
[gasps]
Food!
[LUFFY]
I'm coming, food!
[ONLOOKERS gossiping]
What's going on? What happened?
Well... someone died.
Apparently he suddenly
dropped dead
right in the middle
of the restaurant.
He just died?!
[ONLOOKER B] Yeah, he just
up and keeled over
during a conversation
with the owner.
[ONLOOKER C]
He isn't from here.
We think he may have
accidentally eaten a
Desert Strawberry
while traveling,
not knowing what it was.
[ONLOOKER A] Uh, what is
a Desert Strawberry?
[ ONLOOKER C] There's a
species of poisonous spiders
that look like red strawberries
growing in the desert.
Anyone who eats one will
suddenly die a few days later.
The infection spreads throughout
the corpse, and it's contagious,
so no one can go near.
It's a quick but
unpleasant way to go.
[ONLOOKER B] You have to
be careful in the desert.
Anything you touch can kill you.
But just look at the way his
arm is still stuck up like that,
holding on to a bite of meat.
That's proof of just how swiftly
the Desert Strawberry acts.
It's an incredibly
deadly creature.
[ONLOOKERS whispering]
[ONLOOKERS scream]
[ONLOOKER A]
He came back to life!
[ACE]
Huh?
Um... are you all right?
‐‐[ONLOOKERS gasp]
‐‐[WOMAN screams]
[ACE sighs]
[ACE]
Sorry about that.
Fell asleep.
[ONLOOKERS]
You were asleep?!
That doesn't make sense!
You were right in the
middle of a conversation!
And now you're just eating
like nothing happened?!
Jeez, what's all the
commotion about, anyway?
[ONLOOKERS] We thought you had
dropped dead! Are you crazy?!
Does this restaurant of yours
do comedy skits or something?
Nope. That isn't
our thing, not here.
We're just glad that
you're all right.
[ONLOOKERS]
Damn it! Cut it out!
‐‐[ACE snores]
‐‐[ONLOOKERS chatter]
[ONLOOKER A] So it turns out
he wasn't dead after all?
[ONLOOKERS continue chattering]
[SMOKER]
Hm...
Yeah, I think that oughta do it.
Tell me, mister.
[OWNER]
What is it?
[ACE] Have you by any
chance seen this guy?
He's a pirate that
wears a straw hat.
[SMOKER]
You've got some nerve,
eating in the middle of
a public place like this.
Even for a Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates.
Hello Portgas D. Ace.
Huh? No way! Not the
Whitebeard Pirates?!
[ONLOOKER E] I knew I'd seen
that mark on his back before!
[ONLOOKER A]
You mean this weirdo is
one of the Whitebeard Pirates?
[ONLOOKER F] It's the mark
of the Whitebeard Pirates!
But what is he doing here?
[ONLOOKERS chatter]
[SMOKER]
I'm curious.
What's such a big shot pirate
doing in this country?
[ACE]
I'm looking for someone.
My little brother.
[LUFFY]
Give me food!
What's with this
weirdo city, anyway?
There's some strange non‐food
smell all over the place!
[gasps] There's one!
It's a restaurant!
[ACE] So... what do you
want from me now, Captain?
[SMOKER] I'd just like you
to come with me quietly.
No thanks, I think I'll pass.
Yeah... figured you'd say that.
[sighs]
[SMOKER] I'm here in
Alabasta trying to hunt down
another pirate at the moment.
To be honest, I have
no real interest in
capturing you right now.
[ACE]
Then just look the other way.
[SMOKER]
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Not as long as I'm a Marine,
and you're part of a
notorious pirate crew.
That's not much of
a reason, now is it.
How 'bout I give you one?
[LUFFY]
Give me food!
Gum‐Gum Rocket!
[SMOKER yells]
[ACE gasps]
[ONLOOKERS gasp]
[laughs]
Woo food! Now I can eat!
Finally! I'm starving!
I thought I was gonna die!
Old guy, gimme food.
Hurry, come on.
Food, food, food, food!
Now, now, now!
[LUFFY]
Amazing!
This is seriously the
best food I've ever tasted!
Uh, yes... thanks a lot.
But you see, sir...
It's just... well...
...you might want to
start running now.
Why is that?
The guy you sent flying
through the wall just now,
do you have any idea who he is?
Who sent someone flying?
You did.
Really? Who was he?
[LUFFY]
So...
...what's with all these holes?
Kind of a weird
decoration, you know?
So why'd you do it?
[ONLOOKERS]
You're the one who did it!
I did? Really?
[ACE groans]
Damn it.
So what the hell was that?
[SMOKER groans]
What just happened?
[ACE]
This is ridiculous!
Just look at this place!
[ACE]
Eh‐‐ Oh, hi there.
Many apologies for
disturbing your meal.
[ACE]
What kind of world‐class idiot
would do something like this?
[ONLOOKERS gasp, yell]
[grunts]
Ah!
[SMOKER]
Hm?
[LUFFY chewing]
Haha!
[gasps]
Hey Luf‐‐
[ACE yelps, groans]
[SMOKER]
Straw Hat!
I've been looking
for you, Straw Hat.
I thought you'd be here.
Seems I was correct.
Would you quit eating!
[LUFFY]
Isn't he...
[SMOKER]
Straw Hat Luffy.
You're finally here.
I already told you that you
couldn't make it
to the Grand Line
without beating
me first, didn't I?
[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY]
What's happening?!
[SMOKER]
I ate the Plume Plume Fruit,
so my body can be smoke
whenever I want.
Gum‐Gum Pistol!
[SMOKER]
Don't you see?
You've got to go through me
to get to the Grand Line.
I told you!
[LUFFY yells]
You're that smokey guy!
What're you doing in Alabasta?!
[growls]
[LUFFY]
Wait a sec!
Thanks a lot for the meal.
[ONLOOKERS]
Huh?
[SMOKER]
Stop, you!
[gasps]
[ACE]
Wait up Luffy! It's me!
Hold on a second!
Hey! Come back, Luffy!
They didn't pay...
[LUFFY]
This is bad!
My Gum‐Gum moves don't work
against this guy at all!
I just have to make
a run for it now!
Tashigi!
Yes sir! Would you
like a cool towel?
It's quite refreshing.
This desert kingdom
really is hot.
[SMOKER] Catch that guy!
It's Straw Hat!
Yes sir!
[LUFFY groans]
I've got him!
Huh?
[exhales]
[CITY FOLK gasp]
[SMOKER] Tashigi!
Gather the Marines at once!
Search every inch of this place
for the rest of his crew!
[TASHIGI]
Right! Come on!
They must have
devil fruit powers.
No way!
[TASHIGI]
The Straw Hat's crew is here.
That must mean...
[TASHIGI] Roronoa Zoro
is in the city somewhere!
[LUFFY groans]
White... snake!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY groans]
Why did you come to
this island, Straw Hat?
What are you after?
[LUFFY]
What am I after?
I just came here to beat up
some guy named Crocodile!
[SMOKER]
Crocodile?
[SMOKER] Tell me, how are
you and Crocodile connected?
[gasps]
[SMOKER]
He's gone.
Bastard thinks he can escape!
[gasps]
[SMOKER]
Straw Hat!
[VIVI]
Where could Luffy have gone?
He doesn't know
the island at all.
[SANJI]
Seriously.
A crew shouldn't have
to work this hard to
keep track of their captain.
Oh, Nami!
[USOPP]
This doesn't look good.
We could be in some
serious trouble
if we don't get
out of here soon.
[SANJI]
Trouble? Why's that?
'Cause the Marines are here.
Marines?
And also some mystery man.
Let's just find Luffy
as fast as possible and
get out of this town
as soon as we can.
‐‐[MEN shouting]
‐‐Hey, hide!
‐‐[NAMI] What for?
[CHOPPER]
Wh‐What was that?
It's the Marines.
Yeah, and they're
excited about something.
Don't let that
pirate escape, after him!
I'm sure it's nothing.
They're probably
chasing some idiot pirate
who's running crazy around town.
[OTHERS]
Some idiot pirate?!
‐‐[LUFFY yelling]
‐‐[MARINES yelling]
[ALL]
It's Luffy!
Oh hey, Zoro! What's up?
Oh, so that's where
you guys have been!
[ZORO] No, you moron!
Get rid of them first!
[MARINES yelling]
Well... they're coming!
What should we do now‐‐
[NAMI]
We've got to get going!
To the ship!
[LUFFY] Don't just
stand there, we gotta go!
[ALL]
Wait up!
[MARINE B]
Stop right there, pirates!
[SMOKER]
You can fall back now, men.
[MARINE B]
Captain!
That Straw Hat
is mine to finish!
Not good! Here he comes!
White Blow!
Not good!
Not good, not good, not good,
not good, not good, not good!
Heat Haze!
[gasps]
You again...
Hmph. Just give it up.
[gasps]
While you may have the
power of smoke, mine is fire.
A fight between the two
us would be pointless.
It would probably go on forever.
All right, looks like
the mystery man
has Devil Fruit powers.
Who is this guy anyway?
And why is he helping us?
That you, Ace?
You haven't changed
a bit, Luffy.
It is you! Really?
Wow, did you eat a
Devil Fruit or something?
[ACE]
Yeah! The Flame Flame Fruit.
[MARINE A] We'll secure the
perimeter, Captain Smoker.
Anyway, now's probably
not the time for chatting.
You guys get out of
here, I'll catch up.
Don't worry about these guys,
I've got 'em. Go on!
Let's go!
[USOPP]
Yeah! Coming!
[NAMI]
But, Luffy!
[SANJI]
Who is that guy back there?
There's one thing I don't get.
Why are you helping
the Straw Hat?
Heh. Can't a guy help out
his bungling kid brother?
Even you should
get that, Smoker.
He's your kid brother.
Interesting.
Oh please. How loving.
Now, move it.
I'm afraid I can't.
You understand.
[MARINES gasp]
[NAMI] Hold up, Luffy!
Tell us who that guy is!
[VIVI]
Do you know him from somewhere?
[LUFFY]
Heh! Yeah!
Heh, heh! He's my big brother!
[ALL]
Brother?!
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[LUFFY] Hey, guys!
This is my older brother, Ace.
[NAMI]
Your brother?
But he seems so... sensible.
[USOPP] I would have expected
him to be as reckless as Luffy.
[ZORO] He's a nice guy who
just cares about his brother.
[CHOPPER] Wow! Brothers
are really great, huh?
[SANJI]
Life's sure full of surprises.
[VIVI]
Come on, everyone.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Ace and Luffy! Hot Emotions
and Brotherly Bonds!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!