Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] In an attempt
to rescue his brother Ace,
Luffy enlisted the aid of
the Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock
to sneak onto
a Navy Vessel on course
to the government prison.
Impel Down.
Meanwhile, the other Straw Hats,
scattered around the globe
by Bartholomew Kuma,
face struggles of their own.
[SLAVER CAPTAIN] Tequila Wolf
is a nation of laborers.
[SLAVER 420G] Pull! Pull!
[SLAVES groan]
[SLAVER CAPTAIN] The people
we have constantly toiling away
to build this bridge
are criminals
from all over the world.
Either that, or they're
citizens of countries
that refused to ally
with the World Government.
[wheezes]
[SLAVER CAPTAIN]
In short, they're slaves.
How much longer
until the bridge is complete?
[SLAVER CAPTAIN]
I have no idea.
Now that you're here,
we're putting you to work.
So the only thing
you need to worry about
is making the bridge.
Hmph.
[USOPP]
Ooh! Is this thing edible?
I've never seen
this kind of fruit before.
[USOPP hollers]
[HERACLES] Usopp'n!
What the--?
Was that thing a plant?
And did it really
just try to eat me?
[HERACLES] Sure.
They are man-eating plants'n.
[USOPP yells]
Whoa!
[sighs]
[PLANT growls]
[USOPP yelling]
What the hell is this place?
[HERACLES] This is the
Swindling Forest, Glinston!
[USOPP] Help. Help! Help!
[LUFFY]
The Friends' Whereabouts!
A Negative Princess
and the King of Demons!
[LUFFY] I never knew
these Marine dudes
got such good grub to eat!
Though the stuff
Sanji cooks is way better.
[HANCOCK] Love-Love Beam!
[HANCOCK] I can't do it.
I can't stop thinking about
those women on Luffy's crew.
[HANCOCK] So. You're choosing
those two girls over me.
Is that it?
[LUFFY] You can't tie me down.
I'm a bad boy, missy.
You're better off without me.
Just tell me what it is
you don't like about me!
I promise I'll change for you!
Wait! Don't leave me!
I won't give up, no matter what!
[HANCOCK] Because...
[HANCOCK]
Even if there are two of them,
my love for Luffy
burns like the sun!
Aaah...
I can't eat another bite!
That was so good!
Quiet! Don't forget
you're a stowaway.
If you don't keep it down,
you'll be found!
[LUFFY laughing]
I never expected
such a beautiful woman
to burp and laugh like that.
Strangely enough,
I find it's sort of a turn-on.
But something's still fishy.
[STALKER] "Further investigation
will be needed on this issue."
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere, Luffy's
crew, who had been scattered
by Kuma
found themselves
facing more pressing matters.
[PERONA]
Nope, still angry. Still angry.
I'm still mad about this!
[PERONA]
Look, I know what I said.
"If I were to travel
anywhere in the world,
I would want to
go someplace dark and damp
with a creepy old castle.
And I would spend all my days
singing songs of curses."
But...
[grunts] Stupid Kuma!
I didn't know the castle
wouldn't have any maids!
No servants. Nothing cute.
No bagel sandwiches
and hot chocolate served to me
in bed every morning!
And to top it off, there isn't
a single stuffed animal here!
[crickets chirping]
[sobs]
Where in the heck
am I? Oh, Moria!
Oh, Kumacy. I miss you.
I wanna go back
to Thriller Bark and--
What was that?
[NEGATIVE GHOSTS]
Horo horo horo horo.
Yes, I knew it!
Someone else was
exiled here, just like me!
[PERONA]
Ooh! I hope it's someone cute!
Though I really shouldn't
expect too much.
Either way,
good-bye crushing loneliness!
♪
Uh...
[PERONA] No! Is that--? It is!
It's one of the Straw Hats!
Kuma must've beaten him
and launched him here.
Aaah...
[PERONA]
Also, he looks pretty dead.
[groans]
[screams]
[PERONA] He's got
all those bruises and stuff
and he's still alive?
Hm. It's only
a matter of time, I guess.
He'll be dead soon enough.
[PERONA] Serves you right!
[laughs]
[hoot, hoot]
[birds chirp]
[groans softly]
[snores lightly]
[ZORO] I'm alive.
But... where am I?
[ZORO] Huh?
[yells]
[screams]
[BOTH screaming]
[ZORO] Huh?
Hey, I know you.
[FRANKY] Retreat!
Negative Hollow!
[NEGATIVE GHOSTS]
Horo horo horo horo.
[ALL groan]
[NEGATIVE GHOSTS]
Horo horo horo.
[ZORO] I should just
crawl around on the ground
like a worm, and eat dirt!
[scoffs]
Where am I
and why are you here?
I could ask you the same thing!
Also, don't scream like that!
[grunts]
What did you do with my swords?
[PERONA] Oh, you won't
be getting those back.
[grunts] I'm warning you.
[grunts]
[scoffs]
This ought to slow you down.
Negative Hollow!
[NEGATIVE GHOST]
Horo horo horo horo.
[ZORO] I'm nothing but garbage.
Someone should throw me away.
Aaah.
[PERONA]
Ha! You're not so tough!
Or rather,
I'm just super awesome!
Heh!
[ZORO growls] How dare you!
Don't you growl at me like that!
It's not cute at all!
From now on,
you're going to be my servant.
Understand me?
[ZORO growls]
Now no more talking--
just be cute.
What the hell?
Stop that! This is not okay!
[ZORO]
No touching! No touching!
I won't be lonely ever again.
Crap! I can't even move!
What the--?
[giggles]
[gasps]
[screams]
This is gross!
[PERONA] Oh, Kumacy!
You freak! What did
you do to me? Get off!
[grunts]
[ZORO]
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
Lesson learned.
You're forgiven.
[yells]
[ZORO] You little--! I do
apologize--wait! Screw you!
I'll call you Mistress--
oh, like hell I will!
[ZORO] Okay, seriously.
Really sorry, here.
[laughs]
All right, I get it!
That's enough!
[ZORO] Ugh! Wasted too much
time here already!
I've gotta go back.
[PERONA]
Hey dummy, exit's that way.
[ZORO] Huh? Oh, gotcha.
[gasps] No, wait,
I shouldn't have told him that!
Where are you going?
You're not even walking
in the direction I pointed!
[grunts]
[PERONA] Hey!
Yeah, what is it?
Unless you tell me where
you hid my swords, I don't care.
Mmm...
[grunts]
Are you leaving now, or what?
It's none of your
damn business. Piss off.
[grunts lightly]
[PERONA laughs]
You won't get away
from me that easily.
Uh...
Because y'see, I've been
lonely far too long.
[ZORO yells]
[eerie music plays]
[SATANIC PRIEST] We call
upon you, our great lord!
We call upon you,
our great lord!
We pray to you, Oh Powerful One,
to rain terror
on our hateful enemies.
[SATANIC PRIEST] It is in your
name that we make this wish!
We call upon you,
Lord of Darkness!
We call upon you
to answer us! Come... Satan!
[SATANIC PRIEST]
Come Satan! Come Satan!
Grant the wish
of those who praise you!
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS]
Praise Satan! Praise Satan!
[thunder]
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS chatter]
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS gasping]
[groaning]
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS]
Is... is this the Devil?
Look. Our magic
incantation actually worked!
[SATANIC PRIEST] Ugh. What a
dreadful looking creature!
[SATAN WORSHIPPER 421B]
No kidding.
It's not of this world.
This is what we've waited for.
Our prayers are answered!
We'll have our revenge at last!
We don't have anything left.
The Long-Arm Tribe
took everything!
The bastards laid claim
to everything we hold dear!
Oh, great and powerful Satan.
Please grant us our wish!
[SATANIC PRIEST] In exchange,
we are prepared
to offer our souls up to you!
[SATAN WORSHIPPER 421E]
Leave them bloody
and begging for death!
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS] Praise
Satan, King of the Devils!
Praise Satan,
King of the Devils!
What is this place?
How far have I been carried away
from all of my dear friends?
More importantly, what in
the world has happened to them?
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS gasp]
Whatever their plight,
I must aid them!
I'll return to
meet the others at once!
Wait just a moment!
Please!
Don't go back to
Hell yet, Master Satan!
Quickly men,
we've got to stop him!
[SATAN WORSHIPPER 421G]
We need to offer him more!
But what could we possibly
offer Master Satan?
A sacrifice? Some blood?
[SATAN WORSHIPPER 421G]
What should we do?
I'll give up anything!
Anything to have
our wish come true!
[SATAN WORSHIPPERS wail]
[BROOK] What do I want?
Huh?
[gasps]
[BROOK exhales slowly]
[SATANIC BLONDE GIRL gasps]
[quavered exhales]
[BROOK] Pardon me.
Would you be so kind
as to show me your panties?
[SATANIC BLONDE GIRL gasps]
[SATANIC PRIEST] He...
he wants to see underwear!
Everyone show him
your underwear!
[BROOK] Uhm. I-I don't need to
see any man panties, thank you.
I--oh, uh--wow...!
[NARRATOR] And now
we return to the present,
where Luffy is steadily
speeding over the waves
to the Great Prison, Impel Down,
to rescue his brother Ace.
[STALKER] Something stinks and
I'm getting to the bottom of it!
[sighs]
I couldn't eat another bite!
That was so good!
[gasps] Quiet! Don't forget
you're a stowaway--
if you don't keep it down,
you'll be found!
[LUFFY laughing]
[knocking]
[MARINE 421A] Excuse me?
Is someone else
in your room with you?
Oh, damn it.
Lieutenant Stalker,
are you certain about this?
Yes, sir!
I just heard someone say,
"Whew! I couldn't
eat another bite!"
And I hardly think that the
Empress would say that, do you?
Hmmm...
He's right.
She'd never say that
and if she did,
I'll give myself a mohawk!
Same here!
[MARINES laugh]
Uhm. I couldn't
eat another bite!
[MARINES yell]
No way!
There, I'm finished for now.
Take these plates away.
Oh yes, and don't forget,
[HANCOCK] I require the same
amount five times every day.
[MARINES] That's a lot!
But if we give you that much,
how are we supposed to eat?
[HANCOCK] Frankly, I don't care
if you all starve to death.
[MARINES] That's awful!
But whatever, she's hot.
[NARRATOR] There are
now only six days left
until the public execution
of Portgas D. Ace.
[NARRATOR] With their
guard ships destroyed
at the hands of Whitebeard,
tensions at Navy
Headquarters are rising.
Famous marines
from all over the world
are gathering at
the harbor of Marineford,
prepared to battle
to the death, if need be.
[NARRATOR]
In the name of justice,
they ready their swords,
not for any mere battle,
but for war.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
in the Holy Land of Marie Jois.
[MARINES gulp]
[NARRATOR]
The Seven Warlords are summoned
for a meeting
to determine their roles
in the event
that Whitebeard attacks.
Ruffians that they are, however,
they have little taste
for the discussion.
[NARRATOR]
The mood in the room is tense
and all hopes for teamwork,
or any sort of organization,
are quickly put to rest.
[clanging]
[ACE breathes heavily]
Old man.
[GARP] Huh.
How can you still be alive
with all of those
horrific wounds?
Huh, Ace?
[GARP] Because of you,
Navy Headquarters is--
No. All of the
World Government is a mess.
[laughs]
Just... kill me.
Hm?
Do it. Kill me, now!
So you wanna die, huh?
You damned fool!
[GARP] Nothing can be done now.
Everything's in motion.
Even if you were
to die right now
that won't stop
Whitebeard from fighting.
There's nothing that can
stop that anymore, son.
Seems the Navy has made
the King of the Sea...
[ACE grunts]
[GARP] mad as hell!
[ACE grunts lightly]
[ACE snivels]
Father!
[NARRATOR] Before he can
reunite with his friends,
Luffy must make an urgent trip
to rescue his brother Ace.
To do so, he must
infiltrate the notoriously
well guarded prison, Impel Down.
But is there any hope
of making it in?
Let alone making it out
with an escaped prisoner.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece,
A Deadly Infiltration!
The Underwater Prison,
Impel Down!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!