[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[SANJI groaning]
[KUROOBI chuckles]
[USOPP]
If I don't fight with all I got,
then I don't deserve to be
on the same ship with them.
And I'll never be able
to face my friends again.
[USOPP]
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
[CHOO screams]
[SANJI]
Shoulder!
Chest!
Legs!
[CHOO]
What'd you say's is done?
This whole fight...
Alcohol lights on fire.
[CHOO screams]
[USOPP]
Usopp Hammer!
[USOPP] You see that loser‐‐
I beat your ass!
I don't have to lay
a finger on you.
You humans are so fragile
that I can kill you
just by playing around
with a little water.
That's the difference
between you and me.
[SANJI grunts]
[SANJI groans]
[SANJI gasping]
[gasps]
Arlong!
[BOTH]
It's Nami!
[ARLONG]
Hey Nami.
I was just teaching
one final lesson
to these pathetic
little pirates.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to kill you.
[LUFFY]
"Luffy at Full Power!
Nami's Determination
and The Straw Hat."
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[ARLONG]
Me?
You want to kill me?
[laughs] Haven't you
learned your lesson yet?
How many times have you
tried to kill me
in these last eight years?
[MEN gasp]
[ARLONG]
You've tried assassination,
poison, sneak attacks...
[ARLONG] You must be aware that
you mere humans can't kill me.
Now, listen. I won't put you
in the ground , Nami...
But you can't leave...
You will remain here...
with us...
...as our surveyor... forever.
But, as you know,
I'm quite good‐natured.
If possible I'd like you
to be our surveyor
of your own free will.
[ARLONG chuckles]
[ARLONG]
I'm giving you a choice.
I will not take pause in having
my fishmen kill every
living creature on this
island... except for you.
[NAMI gasps]
[ARLONG] But that's only if
you refuse to come back
to the Arlong Pirates and draw
sea charts as one of our own.
And if you decide
to come back with us,
I'll be kind and spare
the villagers their lives.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[ARLONG] But, I can't let
these ingrates live...
They must be made
an example of.
So there's only one question...
Will you come with me
and save the people
of Cocoyashi Village,
or be foolish and refuse
my request by fighting
alongside them?
It's your choice.
With them, you will be hopeless.
With them, you will die.
[ARLONG]
Nami...
Will you come and stand
by my side... or not?
The decision is yours.
[NAMI]
This isn't fair...
If I remain friends with
Luffy and the others,
everyone will be killed.
But if I go with Arlong,
everyone from the
village will be saved.
Their lives depend on my choice.
Not fair!
No matter what she chooses,
he'll never set her free!
[NAMI]
But...!
Luffy...
[NAMI]
...help me.
That's for Nami!
[NAMI]
I have to believe in him...
All right everyone...
We'll fight to
the death! Got it?
[VILLAGERS]
Yes!
[VILLAGERS shouting]
Well, then...
It looks like they've
made up their minds.
[NOJIKO]
Please live! Please live!
[ARLONG]
Hm?
What?!
All right...
Now just remove his leg weight.
I see... [grunting]
That's what you meant.
No way!
Luffy's alive!
[NAMI]
Uh?
Hey! Hang in there.
You can't give up now!
[LUFFY coughing]
[ZORO]
Thirty seconds!
That's all I got.
Zoro!
[SANJI grunts]
That'll be enough!
[ARLONG] There isn't
a fountain over there.
Could it be that rubber man?!
[ZORO]
Just stay back...
...you're not getting...
anywhere near him!
Ahh. Zoro.
I thought I told you
to never say that again.
Now prepare to die!
[SANJI] If I kick and break
that leg weight, he can fight.
Luffy, you're the only
one who can fight now!
[ARLONG] In the sea, one
with Devil Fruit powers
is supposed to lose even
the energy to struggle,
not to mention his
powers. He will die.
And if he's still alive, well,
that wouldn't be fair...
You okay?
Please say you're fine!
Sure... I'm fine.
You scared us!
Where'd your pinwheel go?
It was cool.
We've got bigger things
to worry about right now!
[ZORO] Wouldn't be fair?
This game hasn't been fair
from the moment we
started playing it.
Well, anyways.
If there's a hindrance,
I should be aware of it.
Correct?
[ZORO grunts]
[USOPP]
Egg Star!
I've got your back, Zoro!
Big Bro Usopp!
He's all right!
How brave! And he got
here just in time.
[USOPP]
Go on! Give it to him!
[VILLAGERS]
That's where you are?!
He's all right!
Hey, Nami! I beat one of their
leaders. Can you believe it?!
I wiped the smug
off his stupid face.
[laughs] Fishmen are so easy!
[ARLONG]
Hm?
No you... beat choo...
Heh. That's right!
And now that I'm back it's time
we finish this once and for all.
This is the end, Arlong!
[GEZNO] Think... Is there any
way you can free yourself?
Nope. Can't do it.
My energy is way too low...
[NOJIKO] Come on!
Come on! Come out!
[JOHNNY]
All right, Cook!
Now if they can just
set big bro Luffy free...
...the Fishmen will be
runnin' for their lives!
Go Zoro!
[YOSAKU] Take down Arlong
once and for all!
[USOPP]
Huh...?
Ha, ha. Okay!
We have to somehow
prevent Arlong
from getting into the sea...
I'll just keep him from
going anywhere!
[HACHI groans] I... won't
let you have your way...
[USOPP] Hey, Arlong!
I've got a present for you!
[ARLONG]
Huh?
Uh! What's he doin'?
He's so brave!
Usopp! Rubberband of Doom!
[ARLONG] You seem to keep
standing in my way...
I take it you wish
to die first, then.
I can take care of that.
Zoro! Now!
What do you think you're
doing, Usopp?!
[ZORO]
Now's my chance.
All I want is a piece
of that proud nose!
You fool!
It's a proud nose
because it's unbreakable.
If you were at full strength...
...you may have been able
to give it a little scratch.
[ZORO panting]
[ARLONG chuckles]
Ahh! No!
Look, over there!
[YOSAKU]
Hmm? Huh...?
That damn octopus is up!
[YOSAKU]
What's he doing?
[HACHI]
Uhh?! Seriously?!
I thought the rubber band
was gonna fly at me!
[VILLAGERS]
What?!
[USOPP]
[laughing] He saw what
I was aiming for!
But weren't you yelling
"Arlong," huh?
[ZORO pants]
Oh, great...
[HACHI]
We're not done, Zoro!
You may have put me down,
but it wasn't for good.
Cause I'm still alive,
and now I'm gonna finish
off your friend!
[ZORO gasps]
[ARLONG chuckles]
No need to be concerned‐‐
seeing as how you will
all be dead anyway.
[ZORO gasping]
[ZORO groans]
[ALL gasp]
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
Big bro!
[ARLONG chuckles]
[ZORO groans]
[SANJI] You've done enough,
Nojiko. Leave the rest to me!
[NOJIKO]
A fishman!
[SANJI] Watch out! I'll break
the rock with a kick!
[SANJI]
What?!
Octopus... Fritter Frenzy!
No!
[HACHI grunting]
[USOPP]
Zoro!
[ZORO grunting]
So, that's it, huh?
Way too easy...
[ARLONG]
What's with all these bandages?
Did you have a good fall?
[ZORO screams]
[ARLONG grunts]
[ARLONG]
What's this scar...?
[NAMI gasping]
[BOTH crying]
[USOPP whimpers]
[ARLONG] I can't believe
he's breathing...
How can he still be alive
with a body like this?
[ARLONG]
Is he dying already...?
Am I fighting a wounded man?
Either way, he's about to die...
He's going to die
right here and now!
[ZORO groaning]
[laughs]
[ARLONG]
Hm?
[ZORO]
If a person stays put...
...their wounds won't open up...
[ARLONG] Is that right? Do you
find your situation amusing?
[ZORO laughs]
[ZORO]
I'm not talking about me.
I'm talking about the Octo‐Man.
[ARLONG]
What?!
[ZORO] I thought I told you.
We'll win this game!
[HACHI groaning]
[SANJI]
That was too close.
[SANJI] You're the one
that made this complicated
in the first place!
[NOJIKO]
He did it!
[SANJI] It's time to take
care of that shark!
Hurry up, you idiot!
[LUFFY grunting]
Did they free you?
Yes!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY]
I'm back! Ha, ha!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
It's him!
Our hero's back!
[USOPP cheers]
[gasps] Luffy!
[ARLONG]
That rubber bastard...
You're... a bit late...
[LUFFY chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Zoro!
[ZORO grunts]
Hey! Hold on... what're you...
[LUFFY laughs]
[ZORO screams]
Let's switch!
[ALL] You idiot!!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum... Bell!
And whip!
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU gasp]
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum... Pistol!
Gatling!
Yes!
[ALL gasping]
[ARLONG]
Is that all you got?
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
It's not working!
Nope. Just a warm up.
[ZORO groans]
That idiot!
I'm gonna kill him!
[LUFFY grunting]
[ARLONG]
What a bunch of fools.
You think you can
actually beat me?
You were better off drowning
on the ocean floor.
[LUFFY]
No, I don't think so.
I like it up here.
Yep.
Do you not understand my anger?
I saw my brothers
crushed like worms.
[ARLONG]
You'll realize soon enough
that you should've quite
fighting a long time ago.
Do you think Luffy's
gonna be ok?
I mean Arlong doesn't
seem to be effected
by his attacks at all...
And more importantly,
just how far away do
you think Zoro flew?!
Luffy! I've got your back, pal!
[NAMI] No need to worry.
[SANJI] If he loses...
then we'll all... die.
[GENZO]
Yeah. We will.
[NOJIKO] If that happens, it's
the end of the East Blue, too...
Do you know what
the biggest difference
between you and me is?
The nose?
The jaw?
Umm...? What's he doing?
Uhh... I don't know.
Webbing!
[ARLONG growls]
Species!
[ALL gasping]
[LUFFY yelps]
[ARLONG grunting]
[LUFFY grunts]
[ARLONG yells]
[LUFFY gasps]
Oh, man! I bet that
had to be painful.
His teeth must be shattered.
[USOPP gasping]
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU screaming]
[JOHNNY, YOSUKA] He bit
through that stone pillar!
[LUFFY gasping]
[SANJI]
Wow...
If he bites you,
he won't just leave marks,
he'll bite right
through your bones!
[ARLONG] You see? This is
the inherent power of fishmen.
I feel sorry for you humans
having been created
with such limited power.
We've been on a different level
since the beginning of time.
You are inferior.
It only makes sense for
you to bow before me.
You're so weak.
Your presence on this
planet is deplorable.
Don't you think your time
has come to an end?
[chuckles] I'll show you...
...show you the real difference
between you and I...
Sure. Go ahead.
There's no way I'm
losing to a fishman.
Because...
...I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!
♪All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way♪
[LUFFY]
Hey! Where did Arlong go?
[NAMI]
The sea!
[LUFFY]
The sea?
Whoa! There's a shark!
[USOPP]
That's Arlong!
[LUFFY]
He ran away?
[SANJI]
This isn't good!
He gets even stronger
when he's in the water.
[USOPP]
Ahh! Watch out!
[LUFFY screams]
[STRAW HATS]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Explosion! Fishman Arlong's
Fierce Assault from the Sea!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!