Anyways. After this, where're
you folks headed off to?
Thanks, but there's no
reason for us to take the train
when we have our own ship.
We'll just follow the log.
I see. Well, in that case,
it's Water Seven for sure.
Water Seven, huh?
They got great shipyards.
You might say that's
their claim to fame.
When it comes to boats,
they're first class!
All right then it's settled!
We're gonna find the best
shipwright in Water Seven
and get him to join our crew!
[LUFFY] Nobody told me it
was gonna be this cool!
[USOPP]
Hmmm...
Should be okay to
anchor here, right?
Holy crap. If the Merry's
falling apart this easy,
we're lucky we
made it here at all!
[SHOP MAN A]
Here, take this.
Oh! A map!
Thanks for the help!
That'll be perfect.
We can head straight
to the shipyard soon
as we trade in our gold!
Well, you're not gonna hear
any complaints from me.
As long as the Merry gets
repaired, I'll be happy!
Yeah! Go Yagara!
[SHOP MAN A]
See you later!
Thanks for business
and have a safe trip!
[LUFFY] Downtown, full
speed ahead! Yahoo!
[LUFFY]
This is great! Hahahahaha!
You're the best, horse fish!
[USOPP] We might not be
traveling in style,
but I gotta admit,
this sure is handy!
I never thought riding
a fish would be so comfy!
[CHILD A]
Over here! Over here!
[CHILD B]
'Kay, here it comes!
[CHILD C]
No problem!
[CHILD D]
Oh no! It's too high!
[CHILD A]
Get ready!
[CHILD B]
Watch out!
[CHILD A]
I got it!
[CHILD C] Ah man, no fair!
You did that last time, too!
[CHILD D]
I was gonna get that one!
I wanna play, too!
[USOPP]
Ahhh...
I didn't think there'd be canals
running by people's houses, too!
They're everywhere!
[NAMI]
I'm trying to follow the map,
but I don't want
to miss anything!
Hey there, buddy!
[LUFFY]
Right back at 'cha!
Whatcha doing here?
Going sightseeing?
No, we're gonna have our
ship repaired at the shipyard!
[MAN A] I see! In that case,
you should probably go
to the backstreet
shopping district first!
[MAN B]
Checkmate.
[LUFFY]
Thanks!
Sure.
Backstreet shopping district.
Let's take the next right.
Oh! Hello, mademoiselle!
Would you like to have dinner?
Uh...
[sounds of a struggle]
[WOMAN A] Don't mind
him--it's nothing.
Men around here always
greet the ladies like
that when they
see one passing by.
[chuckles uncomfortably]
[WOMAN A]
Would you stop flirting
with girls for five minutes
and get some work done
for once in your life?!
[MAN C] Yes, darling,
you're the boss.
It's not that I don't
appreciate a warm welcome,
but these people are so
friendly, it's kinda weird.
[MAN D] Hey!
You with the long nose!
Huh?
[MAN D] Nothin'. I was
just saying hey, that's all.
You're lucky I'm down here!
Uh, we're about to
go against the flow.
Is that okay? We're not
supposed to go up, are we?
[NAMI] Wait, wrong way!
Go right! Right!
Awesome! You horse fish
can swim uphill, too?!
What can't you do?!
[LUFFY] Look! The canals go
on top of the buildings!
[NAMI]
Who cares?!
We're going the wrong way!
We need to go to
the shopping district!
Why? What's the rush?
You wanna see the rest
of the city, don't you?
[USOPP] Ahhh!! Look! Look!
Do something! Turn around!
[LUFFY laughs]
Oh yeah,
we're up pretty
high, aren't we?
[USOPP]
That not what I want to hear.
Faster!
This is fast enough, thank you!
Aaaaaahh!
Sorry!
[laughs]
Aaaaaahhh!! Help me!
We're falling, we're
falling, we're falling,
we're falling, we're falling,
we're falling, we're falling!
[NAMI] UGH!
Stop showing off!
Huh?
[MERCHANT MAN A] Best prices
in town! Check us out!
[MERCHANT MAN B]
Take a look over here!
I promise you won't regret it!
[MERCHANT MAN C] We're
starting our 50% off sale!
Don't miss it!
[MERCHANT MAN D]
We've got rare goods
for the distinguished customer!
[LUFFY] Ah! Oh man!
Check out all the stuff!
[NAMI] We ended up in the
shopping district after all!
Wait. You guys took
a shortcut, didn't you?
I'm sorry!
You're a lot smarter
than I gave you credit for!
[USOPP] This has gotta be the
biggest market I've ever seen!
[LUFFY] Uh-huh.
Whoa! Look!
That bull is huge!
[USOPP] Whoa! Should we move?
It's coming straight at us!
[USOPP]
That thing is scary!
[LUFFY]
You think he eats people?
[NAMI] I wonder if this
one is a "King"?
Huh? What's with them?
They're all wearing
masks. That's weird.
Wow. Neat. They're pretty.
They must be going to a party.
What's up? See something?
Freshly made water-water
octopus dumplings for sale!
Three water-water
croquettes, coming up!
I didn't know they sold food!
I'm hungry!
Let's buy everything!
Wait! Go back!
[USOPP] Hey, Luffy!
Where're you going?!
I dunno... Ask my ride!
[NAMI and USOPP]
Huh?
Hello, there!
How may I help you?
I see,so you
were hungry, too!
[MERCHANT LADY B]
Water-water meat
is the Yagara's favorite food.
Although we usually
cook it for humans.
Meat, huh?
I'll take ten please!
[MERCHANT LADY B]
They're so good that the cooks
from the Gourmet Town
come buy them in secret!
Bet you've never had
anything like it, huh?
So soft! Yummy!
Whoa, really? They're good?!
Let me try one, Luffy!
No way! I'm not sharing!
[USOPP]
Nami, he's being mean!
Make him share with me!
[NAMI]
More masks.
People all over town
are wearing them.
[USOPP]
Nami!
[NAMI] There's something
strange about this.
[USOPP]
Nami! Are you listening?!
[MAN F] Hey! Some pirates
are causing a ruckus at Dock #1!
[MAN G]
What?! That's not good!
[MAN H] Come on!
We'd better go check this out!
[PAULIE] Sorry, but you're
not making any sense.
[MIKAZUKI] Need me
to talk slow for you?
Hahahaha!
Soooooo you
repaired our ship.
Sooooo then I got to thinking.
And no matter
how I looked at it,
no matter how many times
I turned our little deal
around in my head,
I still felt like you
were charging me way too much.
You're interrupting our job.
[MIKAZUKI]
Here's the deal.
I'm not paying a single
berry for the work you did.
[MIKAZUKI CREW laughs]
[MIKAZUKI CREW A] Thanks for
the repairs, they were great!
[MIKAZUKI CREW B] So kind
of you to do them for free!
[ICEBERG] Mmwell... Kalifa.
You know what's going on?
[KALIFA] Yes, Mr. Iceberg.
Those pirates are
Dock 1 customers.
But now that the work's
done, they refuse to pay.
Sexual harassment.
Mmwell. Maybe it is.
[MIKAZUKI CREW laughs]
Listen, Sir, we take
our jobs very seriously.
It's not wise to mock
our shipwrights like that.
[MIKAZUKI CREW A]
Captain!
[CARPENTER A]
Oops. Sorry!
Hey jerk!
Watch where you
swing that thing!
You just knocked out our-- Ahh!
[KAKU]
Oops. Sorry.
Hey, you punks
trying to pick a fight?!
Who do you think you are?!
Oh yeah.
We haven't had a chance to
test fire that cannon, have we?
No. Not yet.
Damn you!
You won't get
away with this!
We'll be back! Just wait!
You're on shipwright turf.
This is what
happens when you try
to pull that pirate
crap around here.
[NAMI]
This is it.
As soon as we take
the water gate elevator,
we'll be at shipbuilding
island in no time.
What's this water gate thing?
[NAMI] It's that tower
right ahead of us.
[ELEVATOR GIRL A]
Attention everyone!
The elevator is ready to go.
Bulls and riders enter now!
[ELEVATOR GIRL A] Proceed in
an orderly fashion, please!
All aboard for
shipbuilding island
and downtown
Water Seven at this time!
Passengers should enter
the elevator quickly.
The gate will be closing
in only one minute!
Something crazy's gonna
happen, I just know it!
[LUFFY]
The gate closed! It's starting!
[USOPP] We're going up!
We're going up! We're going up!
I see! First you go in.
The gate shuts.
The water fills the elevator,
and then everybody
floats to the top!
I still don't get it
but it sure is awesome!
[NAMI] They really do use
water for everything here!
[SANJI]
Hey!
[mumbling]
Who you callin' Moss Head, jerk?
You awake?
Huh...?
You know where Robin went?
She's not on the ship.
Hmmm...
Oh, I remember.
She... uh... said she was
going out with Chopper.
What?
They were doing
some shopping, I think.
[SANJI]
What the hell?!
Does that mean I'm stuck
on this ship alone with you?!
That's gotta be the most
boring thing in the world!
[ZORO]
Yep. That's why I'm sleeping.
Fine. I need to do
our grocery shopping,
so I'm taking off, too.
Take good care of the
boat while I'm gone.
[snores]
Asleep already, huh?
Whatever.
Keep up the good work.
[LUFFY]
We made it!
So this is the best shipyard
in the whole world, huh?
It's even fancier than
the rest of the town!
[USOPP] They've got a lot
more ground to work with
than the residential
district, that's for sure.
Everything's huge! So cool!
Of course it's cool,
this place is the best!
It's great seeing
the fountain up close.
It really is
beautiful, isn't it?
[USOPP] There's a bunch
of people over there.
Think something's going
on at the shipyard?
[LUFFY] Let's go check
it out! Go, Yagara!
[WOMAN B]
Look! Over there!
It's Lucci!
He's so handsome!
[BUSYBODY MAN A]
Paulie's here today too, right?
[BUSYBODY MAN B] Who cares
about those guys, huh?!
Now Lulu, that's a real man.
Just look at that moustache!
[BUSYBODY MAN C]
Whatever!
Nobody's manlier than Tilestone!
[LUFFY]
Hey mister.
Hmm?
What's this crowd about?
Oh. It was just some
boneheaded pirates
trying to pick a fight
with the shipwrights again.
Y'know happens all the time.
But our guys sent
'em packing, like always.
Those pirates'll
never learn their lesson.
Whoa, that's nuts.
The shipwrights
can beat up pirates?
Ah, you must be tourists, huh?
The shipwrights are, well...
...they're like
celebrities to us.
In fact, you might say that
this crowd is their fan club.
We're always watching
the Galley-La Company.
They're strong.
They're skilled.
And they're the pride of
every citizen in Water Seven.
Wow. I can't wait to meet them!
[NAMI]
Hey, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Let's hurry up and get
the gold traded in, okay?
This is fun.
But it can wait 'til later.
[ROBIN]
It says that we're
in the backstreet
shopping district.
[CHOPPER] It seems awfully
crowded for a backstreet,
if you ask me.
Kinda neat that they have
places to walk around, though.
They must've put a lot of
thought into the town's design.
[CHOPPER]
Yeah.
Scary!!
[MAN I]
Would you look at that!
[MAN J]
What a beautiful woman!
She's gorgeous!
A real
once-in-a-lifetime beauty!
[CHOPPER]
Ugh...
This place is
full of Sanjis.
[chuckles]
[CHOPPER]
What is that guy selling?!
It looks creepy!
[ROBIN]
It's just a mask shop.
I noticed a lot of people
around town wearing them,
so they must buy
them from there.
It's something you wear?
I thought that was their face!
Wow that's a big relief!
[ROBIN]
It seems the people here
take the Sea Train
to San Faldo Island,
where they hold a
costume carnival every day.
[CHOPPER]
Huh? How do you know that?
We just got here!
[ROBIN] The people walking
by are talking about it.
[CHOPPER] Whoa and you
hear everything they say?
I can't help it.
Ever since I was young,
I've made it a habit
to keep a critical eye
and ear on my environment.
Wow, Robin that's cool.
[ROBIN]
Huh... Doctor.
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
[ROBIN] See that? I think
we found your bookstore.
Oh! Really?
Can we go inside now?!
[ROBIN chuckles]
Of course. Be my guest.
Today is the best day ever!
[BLUNO]
CP9.
Hey! What're you waiting for?!
[thinking] If I'm in my human
form maybe it'll be okay?
My! What a funny mask!
What's your costume?
Oh... uh... a human reindeer?
Hmm! Ahahaha! As long
as you're having fun, right?
Hey, wait.
Robin?
[CHOPPER]
Hello? Robin?!
Pity, I was hoping that we
could kill you in your sleep.
You bastards sure
got a lot of nerve.
Who are you?
♪ ending song ♪
[LUFFY] Did you see that?!
Usopp was flying!
[USOPP] Yeah! I mean what!
[LUFFY] Oh, but that Usopp
had a square nose, huh?
[USOPP] Round noses
are more manly.
[ICEBERG] Mmwell, you
must be Straw Hat Luffy.
My name's Iceberg.
[LUFFY] You're the
boss around here, right?!
Then repair our ship!
[ICEBERG]
Sure.
[USOPP] You're not even
gonna think about it first?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece :
"The Franky Family and Iceberg."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!