[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
You're all going to die!
You morons can't
challenge the entire world
and expect to win!
So long as that woman is
wanted by the World Government,
I'll chase her forever!
I want to live!
Jet...
...Gatling!
Luffy!
[MARINE 309L]
Whoa! Look at the tower!
Attention aboard all ships.
I have an urgent report!
[MARINE 309G]
Just now, Rob Lucci,
the most powerful agent of CP9,
was seen lying face-down and
lifeless near the first column.
I repeat--Rob Lucci
has just been defeated
by Straw Hat Luffy!
Yes!
It's over.
We should be okay now.
We're all going back together!
Robin!
[chuckles]
[LUFFY] From the Sea,
A Friend Arrives!
The Straw Hats
Share the Strongest Bond!
[MARINE 310B] What?
No way. Impossible!
But he was CP9!
And the agents they have now
are the strongest
the world has ever seen!
[MARINE 310B] Even among them,
Rob Lucci was the best!
These pirates are too powerful!
[USOPP]
He won! Luffy won!
Luffy. You had us worried.
You finally beat him.
Way to go!
Luffy!
Everybody head
to the escape ship!
We're getting out of here!
[GONBE]
Meow!
He did it!
[ZAMBAI] Way to go, Straw Hat!
[PAULIE] You morons!
Keep it down!
Everyone can hear us!
[ZAMBAI] Who cares?
We want him to know!
Hey! Those voices!
Whose are they?
Unknown!
They're coming
in from somewhere
through a
transponder snail, sir!
[ZAMBAI] All right, Big Bro!
[USOPP] What?
That voice...
[PAULIE] Stop it!
They still think
we're dead, remember?
You're gonna blow it!
[FRANKY] It's them.
They made it.
Aren't those the
pirates we shot down
on the shore
by the front gate?
It sounds like it.
But sir, we saw 'em.
They all fell
over the cliff, sir!
They couldn't have survived!
Big Bro!
[yelling]
[gasping]
[FRANKY FAMILY 310A]
Stop pushing, you idiot!
[FRANKY FAMILY 310B]
We're gonna fall!
[FRANKY FAMILY 310C]
The rope's gonna break!
[PAULIE] You morons!
Galley-La ropes
never break! Calm down!
Jeez. I told you
to keep it quiet!
[ZAMBAI] We're all okay!
Everybody made it!
[KIWI] That was close!
The giants...
They took all the
cannon fire for us!
Gero!
Gosh. They're a
stubborn bunch, huh?
Uh-huh!
But hey, at least they're alive!
Meow!
[MOZU] Sodom and Gomorrah
are okay, too!
That's great!
Look. It's not safe here.
Those battleships
will be coming back.
We need to get moving now!
Right! Listen up!
We've got our escape
plan all figured out.
Go! Don't worry about us!
Let's all leave
this place alive!
See you again soon!
Time to head out!
[KASHII] Move it!
You guys climb up first!
Hurry up!
Blood rushing to head.
Getting dizzy...
[PAULIE]
All right. Climb!
[FRANKY FAMILY] Yeah!
[KIWI] Come on, everybody!
Get moving!
[MOZU] I'm gonna fall!
[YOKOZUNA] Gero!
[LULU] Stop shoving!
You dummies!
I wasn't worried
about you at all!
They made it! They're alive!
I'm so happy
those idiots are okay!
[sobbing]
[ZORO] Agreed.
Good for them.
What a relief, huh?
But if you die here,
it won't matter.
Yeah, you're right.
Sir! Should we hurry
over to the main gate?
No. Later.
First things first.
What's wrong?
Move it! We've got
a duty to carry out!
[MARINES] Sir!
Ha! Bring it on!
I'll take all of ya out!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
[ZORO] Tiger Trap!
Oni Giri!
Phoenix!
All right! Cien Fleurs!
Our target is Straw Hat.
He's on the first column!
[MARINE 310G]
Right! Understood, sir!
But he's--
[MARINE 310G]
He doesn't seem to be moving!
Straw Hat Luffy is--
Sir, he--He appears
to be severely wounded!
[ZORO] What?
[USOPP] Luffy!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and get
the hell over here!
If we don't escape,
we're all gonna die!
What's wrong with you, dammit?
We're almost there!
Use your powers to
slingshot yourself over here!
I'll carry you
the rest of the way!
[USOPP] We're surrounded by sea
and battleships on all sides!
If we stay here,
we're going to be killed!
It seems the pirates
plan to escape
using the stolen escort ship.
[MOMONGA] Hm.
[USOPP] Luffy!
Answer me! Say something!
I--I can't--
My body won't--
What?
My body won't move.
It won't move?
Come on, don't be stupid!
You just beat Lucci,
didn't you?
[USOPP] And we
already saved Robin!
The only thing
left to do is run!
Try harder!
You can do it!
[NAMI] Usopp!
Let's take the ship to Luffy!
We'll grab him
and get outta here!
Everyone, move! Get onboard!
Fire!
No! That's our escape ship!
Those bastards!
Now it's hopeless!
We're completely surrounded!
That ship was our
only way outta here!
What are we gonna do?
Kokoro! Chimney! Gonbe! Chopper!
No. What now?
[yelling]
[SANJI] We made it!
Outta the way!
[NAMI] Thank goodness!
Sanji!
What the heck happened?
And where have you been?
Sorry.
There was something
I had to take care of.
Damn, this is bad.
We're pretty screwed right now.
I never thought
they'd attack us
as long as we
still had Robin here.
I was sure the bridge and
the ship would be safe--
That's far enough!
Surrender!
Release the old lady
and the little girl, or--
There's no time for any of that!
Mermaid Kick!
Fire.
[screaming]
[NAMI] Why does this
always happen to us?
[ONIGUMO] Corner them
at the second column!
Fire!
[SANJI] That was close!
Keep moving!
Fire.
[screaming]
[SANJI] Run!
[SANJI] Dammit!
They took out the bridge!
We're stuck on this column!
These bastards
have got us cornered!
[ZORO] There's
nothing else we can do!
We're surrounded!
[NAMI] Then this is
where we'll make our stand!
Let's fight!
[FRANKY] Don't be stupid!
They'll just keep
sending more and more
of those Captains at us!
[ONIGUMO] All ships!
Prepare to open fire
on the first column!
All cannons take aim!
Eliminate Straw Hat Luffy!
[USOPP] Luffy!
[ZORO] Luffy's in trouble!
We gotta do something!
Crap. This is bad.
[USOPP] Luffy!
No good.
At this distance,
all I can do is grab him
and throw him into the sea.
Bad news, you guys.
Straw Hat may have
won the fight,
but now, he's so
weak he can't get up!
He'll be killed!
[PAULIE] Straw Hat!
[FRANKY FAMILY]
No! Straw Hat!
[YOKOZUNA] Gero! Gero!
[FRANKY FAMILY]
Stand up, Straw Hat!
Come on! Stand up!
Pirate guy! Run!
Meow!
Luffy! Hurry!
Move it!
Dammit!
You've gotta do
something right now, Luffy!
[NAMI] Luffy!
[FRANKY] Straw Hat!
[FRANKY FAMILY]
Come on! You can do it!
[PAULIE] Straw Hat!
Gero! Gero!
No... I'm in trouble.
Luffy!
Get moving!
They're gonna kill you!
[KIWI and MOZU] Straw Hat!
[PAULIE] Get on your
feet and get outta there!
Now!
[FRANKY FAMILY]
Do something!
[USOPP] There it is again!
[USOPP] What?
Hey! You trying
to kill yourself?
Stop spacing out!
Now's not the time!
[USOPP]
Who's voice is this, anyway?
[USOPP] That's right!
It's the same voice
that I heard before!
What's going on here?
[PAULIE] Don't die on us!
What?
Those voices? It's my guys!
No!
That's not what
I'm talking about here!
I've heard it for a while.
Huh?
What?
Look below?
It's coming from over here.
"Below"?
[NAMI] Who's that?
What the hell? That voice.
It says "Look below!"
[CHIMNEY] Who does?
What are you talking about?
[MARINE 310T]
All ships, open fire
on the first column
and Straw Hat Luffy.
Commencing in five.
--[NAMI] No! Luffy!
-- [FRANKY FAMILY] Straw Hat!
[USOPP] You shouldn't have.
You really shouldn't have.
Jump in the sea!
[MARINE 310T] Four!
The sea!
[ZORO] Usopp?
Robin!
Can you still throw
Luffy into the sea?
Leave it to me!
[ZORO]
Are you trying to kill us?
What--
[ZORO] Jumping into the sea
won't help a damn thing!
[MARINE 310T] Three!
[USOPP] We're gonna be saved!
She came to rescue us!
Jump! It'll be okay!
We've still got
one more friend here!
[MARINE 310T] Two!
Chopper!
Did you see?
Yes!
Now. Cien Fleurs!
[MARINE 310T] One!
[ROBIN] Delphinium!
[LUFFY] I'm moving!
Is Robin doing this?
To the sea!
[USOPP]
Jump! Follow Luffy!
[NAMI and SANJI] Go!
[ZORO, CHOPPER, FRANKY]
Go!
[KOKORO, CHIMNEY, ROBIN]
To the sea!
All of the pirates are
jumping into the sea!
Ha!
There's no way those idiots
will survive in these waters!
They're done for!
[MARINE 310K]
Those Straw Hats are completely
out of their minds!
[VOICE]
Let's go back, everyone!
[MARINE 310T] Fire!
[VOICE] Back to
the seas of adventure!
[USOPP] Everyone!
Get on board the Merry!
Merry!
[MERRY]
I came to get you!
[ROBIN] Before now,
I have always been alone.
I never thought that
those words Saul said to me
would ever come true.
True friends.
I want to thank you all
from the bottom of my heart
for saving me.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Everyone Makes a Great Escape!
The Road to Victory
is for the Pirates!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!