[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[footsteps]
[LUFFY]
Come on, you guys!
Keep running!
[USOPP]
I-I-I don't think I can keep up!
I'm beat! No, wait,
don't leave me!
[LUFFY] Let's find the Going
Merry and get out of here!
[LUFFY] "Enter the
Hot-Blooded Special Forces!
Battle on the Bridge!"
[SHEPHERD]
Help.
--[MARINE A] Hey!
--[MARINE B] What do ya know?
Looks like the Straw Hats left
their pal Condoriano behind!
[SHEPHERD] For the last time,
I am not Condoriano!
I'm Major Shepherd,
an Inspector from HQ!
An Inspector?
I have to contact
them immediately
and tell them the incompetents
at Navarone allowed
pirates to escape.
Nice try, but you're
not fooling us!
You're one lying pirate who
won't escape, Condoriano!
Take him!
[SHEPHERD grunting]
[SHEPHERD] I'm special
Inspector Major Shepherd
--from HQ, you dolts!
--[MARINE B] Sure you are.
[SHEPHERD] You're all going
to be court-martialed for this!
Do you hear me?
Court-martialed!
[footsteps]
[USOPP]
What? What is it?
[yelps] Marines!
Over there, too!
And they're behind us!
We're trapped like
rats, you guys!
[LUFFY laughs]
It's about time things
got interesting.
What?
I wanna see if
Fortress Guy was right.
He said escape was impossible
and it would take a miracle.
It might.
The odds aren't in our favor,
that's for sure.
There's a thousand troops
stationed here.
You find this
interesting? Why, Luffy?
Because escape is
supposed to be impossible!
How is this interesting?!
[SANJI]
Forget it, Usopp.
You know how he is once he
gets an idea in his head.
[CAPTAIN A]
Unit 37 reporting!
[CAPTAIN B]
Unit 44 reporting!
[DRAKE]
Forward!
Capture the Straw Hats!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
He, he! Come on!
[USOPP screams]
[DRAKE]
After them! On the double!
[JONATHAN sighs]
[MARINE D]
Freeze, Pirates!
[MARINES groaning]
--[JONATHAN] Hm?
--Sir, look!
The Straw Hat captain!
Oh, great, a dead-end.
No, we can run along
this cliff here--
--[USOPP shouting]
--[gunshots]
[JONATHAN] So, you've finally
shown yourselves, eh?
[USOPP]
It's the base commander!
Jonathan. Oh, no.
Hey, Fortress Guy!
Why are you up there?
This is the balcony
to my office.
Now. Fire the cannons.
[CANNON GUY] Sir! If we
fire at the central tower,
won't that cause some kind of--.
You heard me! Fire!
[USOPP]
Agh! Luffy! Luffy!
My crew.
I rescued 'em. Whadaya think?
[JONATHAN]
Hm.
Sorry I beat your guys up.
But I told you I was gonna leave
when I wanted to, didn't I?
[JONATHAN]
Indeed.
Are you still planning to do
that, Straw Hat Luffy? Leave?
[LUFFY]
Yep! We're leavin' right now!
[JONATHAN laughs]
You're funny.
Do you actually think you
can escape from Navarone?
With your treasure?
You bet I do!
We're pirates!
You can't catch us.
[USOPP]
Run!
[LUFFY laughs]
They escaped!
Commander!
Don't fret!
We can still catch them!
Unit 21's waiting in Block 7.
If the pirates head down there,
we can take them down
once and for all!
No. Have Unit 21 withdraw
from Block 7 immediately.
But, sir, it's a dead-end,
perfect for an ambush!
Only if the Straw Hats
played by the book.
That kid didn't get
a 100-million-Berry bounty
on his head by
doing the obvious.
Besides, it would just
result in more injuries
and further damage to this base.
Navarone's seen enough of both.
Don't you agree, Sergeant?
[SERGEANT]
Yes, sir.
Instead of focusing
on where they might go,
let's focus on where
they will go.
Their ship is moored in Dock 88,
and it's only a matter of time
before those pirates reach it.
[DRAKE]
Stop them!
[SNAIL PHONE rings]
[JONATHAN]
Drake.
Sir!
[JONATHAN] I want you and your
men to break off your pursuit
and rush to Dock 88.
Set up an ambush there and
apprehend the Straw Hats.
Use of force is granted.
[DRAKE]
Yes, sir!
Sir?
Won't it take
Lieutenant Commander Drake
some time to reach Dock 88?
That's true.
There's only one way for
the Straw Hats to reach
Dock 88, and it's by
crossing this bridge.
We'll leave the Straw Gate
on the upper deck seemingly
unguarded to lure them across.
Yes, that should work.
We'll have troopers
concealed on both ends
to ambush the pirates
when they cross.
They don't need to stop them,
just slow them down.
That should buy us some time.
Good thinking.
[JONATHAN]
Now then.
Which unit should I send
to defend the bridge?
[JONATHAN] I guess there's
really only one unit who might
slow them down.
[UNIT 55 GUY A] ♪ We're 55,
and you better fear it! ♪
[UNIT 55 GUYS] ♪ We're 55,
[UNIT 55 GUY A] ♪ Or you're
gonna taste our fiery spirit! ♪
[UNIT 55 GUYS] ♪ Or you're
Aye-aye, sir!
[UNIT 55 CAPTAIN]
Slow down the pirates!
Understood!
We won't fail you, sir!
Commander, are you
sure you don't wanna
change your order
to "Shoot on sight?"
UNIT 55 GUYS] ♪ Then smash
your face and eat your guts! ♪
[UNIT 55 GUY A] ♪ We'll make you
wish you never were born! ♪
Yes, I'm sure.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Yes, ma'am?
[KOBATO]
The alarm? What's going on?
Jailbreak, ma'am.
It's those pirates.
We're under a code red situation
until they've been recaptured.
The brass thinks some
of them might be holed up
on the base somewhere.
Those morons!
Why couldn't they wait
until we were all together?
Now I'll bet Luffy and
the others are on their way
to the dock where the Going
Merry 's been impounded.
Then that means Luffy
must have rescued Zoro!
That's great news!
It would be if we knew
the layout of this fortress
or even had an escape plan.
Leave it to Luffy to
forget the important stuff.
I swear that guy is
so absentminded!
Yeah, but now we don't
have any choice.
We've got to get to that
dock, too, and quick.
You're right.
We've gotta get out of
here and meet up with
the others before it's too late.
The only problem is them.
In fact, Lieutenant Commander
Drake is sure one of the pirates
is disguised as a medlab doctor.
[MARINE E]
We have to search the premises!
Bloodthirsty pirates
could be in there with you!
[KOBATO gasps]
[MARINE E]
Dr. Kobato?
[BOTH gasp]
Bloodthirsty... in disguise...
You two!
[NAMI]
Umm... Yes, Dr. Kobato?
I guess we shoulda
told you this earlier,
but those pirates
they're looking for...
[NAMI, CHOPPER whimpering]
Don't you worry!
Everything will be okay!
We'll get you to safety!
You heard what those men said.
There are pirates
disguised as doctors!
And for all we know,
they could be nearby!
Um, yeah, about that.
They are nearby.
Because they're kinda us.
We're who they're looking for.
Don't you get it, doctor lady?
We're the pirates!
Look, you seem like
a nice person, and we're
sorry to put you through this!
We won't hurt you,
so don't scream!
All we want from you is
the location of the docks
so we can get back to our ship!
[whimpers]
[screams]
[KOBATO]
You're the pirates!
[KOBATO screams]
[NAMI, CHOPPER screaming]
--[MARINE E] That scream!
--[MARINE F] Dr. Kobato!
[knocking]
[MARINE E]
What happened?
[MARINE F]
Are you all right?
[MARINE E]
Something's wrong!
[MARINE F]
Let's knock it down!
[MARINE E, F grunting]
--[MARINE E] Hold on!
--[MARINE F] We're coming!
Doctor?
[MARINE E]
What the--?
Are you all right?
Miss, say something!
[MARINE E] They escaped
through the air ducts!
[CHOPPER whimpering]
Nurse, you're sure the
pirates went up there?
Uh, yes!
And if you hurry you
can probably catch them!
[KOBATO grunts]
Oh, you're awake.
[KOBATO gasps]
None of that!
I know you wanna
scream right now,
but I need you to promise to
stay quiet for a little bit.
[KOBATO]
Mm-hm.
[CHOPPER]
Nami!
We've gotta get out
of here right now!
You-- You were big.
But how?
Oh, what, that?
Here, I'll show you.
You see, I ate a
Devil fruit once,
and that's what gave me
the ability to transform.
[NAMI]
She really is a ditz.
Uh, look, we'd love to sit and
chat, and explain to you how
Chopper's powers work, but if
you haven't already noticed,
we're a little pressed for time.
It's okay.
What a strange day
this has become.
Well, we've gotta go.
It shouldn't take
those Marines too long
to realize we're
not in the ducts.
Uh, Mr. Deer, wait!
Hold on!
Even if you are a pirate
and a magical deer,
you're still the only
person who ever taught me
what it truly means
to be a doctor!
I would really like to
find a way to thank you.
Oh, that's okay, you
don't have to thank me!
And for the record,
I'm a reindeer!
Oh, gosh, I'm sorry.
Wait a minute, you two said
you needed to go to
the docks, didn't you?
[CHOPPER]
Yeah.
Well, I can show you the way
there if you'd like me to!
[NAMI]
You'll take us there?
But won't you get into
trouble for helping pirates?
They'll throw you
in the brig for sure
if anyone finds out about it.
Oh, yeah, right. Ah!
But in the event we get caught,
I'll just look real scared
and tell them that
you've taken me hostage!
Great!
I'm so glad
I could be of service!
[USOPP] I don't think
they can see us here, guys.
Careful. Fortress Guy's
probably just waiting
for us to stick our necks out.
Like you're doing right now?
Get down here!
[USOPP]
See that path down there?
Dock 88's on the
other side of it.
That's where they've got
the Going Merry stowed.
Yeah, but how do we
get across, though?
There's lots of guards.
What about up there?
Well, it looks crossable.
Yeah. It sure does.
But isn't it strange
there are no guards?
It's almost like they're
inviting us up there.
A trap, huh?
A trap?
Who cares? Let's just go for it.
I'm not scared.
What about you guys?
Worrying about annoying
stuff is annoying.
I say we do it.
If it really is a trap,
we'll just spring it.
Hey, Luffy!
Sanji! Zoro! Hey, wait!
Don't I have a say
in this? Fine!
If you guys get
caught in a trap,
I'm not gonna
rescue you, ya hear?
And without my help,
you're all gonna die!
Is that what you want?
Um, but, uh, if I
get caught in a trap,
you guys'll rescue me, right?
Please say yes!
Do you have any idea which
dock your ship was taken to?
There are actually
a number of docks here,
but they're scattered
all over the base.
[NAMI] Well, I can't be certain,
but judging from where our ship
touched down, I'd
have to guess a dock on
the western side of the base.
Oh.
Then I think I know
where your ship may be.
Dock 88.
What makes you
think that, Doctor?
Well,
due to recent budget cuts,
a lot of our docks
have been shut down,
including most on the
western side of the base.
However, Dock 88 is one of
the few docks on that side
that's still operational.
My father works there.
I'm sure that's
where your ship is.
[CHOPPER] Think that's where
Luffy and the others are headed?
We've got no way of knowing,
but I'd say it's a good bet.
Plus, thanks to all the
commotion they caused,
we've gotta take
advantage of it
and get while the gettin's good.
Well, Dr. Kobato, Dock 88 it is!
Lead on!
[ZORO]
Nobody here.
[LUFFY]
Great! That's perfect!
Let's get goin' then!
--[ZORO] Hey!
--[USOPP] Wait, you moron!
[SANJI]
He never learns!
Whoa! We're really high up!
That's a long way
to fall. Yikes!
[LUFFY panting]
All right!
There they are!
[screams]
See? I told ya, but you
wouldn't listen to me!
[whimpering]
Nice.
[ZORO]
Just as many behind us.
Looks like we're all
gonna get a little workout.
Listen up. We're getting
outta here, no matter what!
Please allow us to
introduce ourselves.
We're the legendary Unit 55,
and no pirates will ever
cross this bridge on our watch!
I already crossed once today,
but I guess you guys were
off the clock then, huh?
I'm gonna make you
eat those words, pirate!
♪ We're 55, and you
better fear it! ♪
[UNIT 55 GUYS] ♪ Or you're
gonna taste our fiery spirit! ♪
[LUFFY]
Whoa, that's catchy!
How's the rest of it go?
55, attack!
[UNIT 55 GUYS shouting]
Gum-Gum Gatling!
[UNIT 55 GUYS yelling]
[USOPP]
Zoro!
[ZORO]
Outta my way!
[USOPP]
On it!
[UNIT 55 GUYS groaning]
[USOPP]
Attaboy, Zoro!
Kick their ass!
Hope you're ready
for me, Straw Hat!
Those are neat!
How about a Gum-Gum...
[GUTS]
Now!
We sure fooled ya! Hah! Hah!
All we had to do was carefully
study your moves, Straw Hat!
What? That's cheating!
[UNIT 55 GUY I groans]
[UNIT 55 GUY J groans]
Scumbags!
Surrender, pirate!
It's over for you
and your friends!
Yeah, I don't think so, Tubby!
[USOPP]
Guys! What are ya doin'?
Quit fighting like a bunch
of scared little girls!
[USOPP whimpers]
--[UNIT 55 GUY L growls]
--[USOPP shrieking]
You're mine!
Wh-What the--?
How'd that little
sea shell stop my sword?
[USOPP]
Oh! An Impact dial!
--[UNIT 55 GUY L grunts]
--[USOPP shouts]
[UNIT 55 GUY N yells]
[ZORO]
There's no end to them!
Listen up, pirates,
and listen good!
We put the "N" in
"Navarone," see!
We're the special forces
unit that the other
special forces units
are scared of!
You should give up now!
And you should shut that dumb
yap of yours, chrome dome!
[SAPP grunts]
[SUMO GUY moans]
[SUMO GUY groans]
[SANJI]
Aw!
All right, who's next?
Huh?
--[LUFFY shouting]
--[UNIT 55 GUYS yelling]
[UNIT 55 GUY Q whimpering]
Ha, ha. Hey, those toys
of yours are pretty neat!
Now Gum-Gum...
[UNIT 55 GUY Q screams]
[GUTS whimpers]
[LUFFY]
...Bazooka!
[UNIT 55 GUYS shouting]
[LUFFY chuckles]
Now, men!
Grab a hold of his arms
before they're retracted!
[UNIT 55 GUYS screaming]
I'm not lettin' go
this time, Straw Hat!
You're stubborn, you!
Now, Gum-Gum...
Uh oh.
...Axe!
[UNIT 55 GUYS shouting]
[USOPP grunts]
[UNIT 55 GUYS yelling]
[LUFFY groans]
Moron. You never think about the
consequences, do you? Do you?!
[LUFFY]
I'm sorry.
[ZORO] Well, let's go.
Where's the dock?
Um, that way.
[SERGEANT]
Commander.
Part of the Straw Gate
bridge has just collapsed!
Unit 55 and the Straw Hat
pirates fell into the bay.
Luckily, Unit 55 is
reporting no casualties
and all members have
been accounted for.
[JONATHAN sighs]
[JONATHAN] I didn't think
they'd cause that much damage!
Still, they did do their job and
bought us the time we needed.
And it sounds like they gave
those Straw Hats
quite a surprise.
[DRAKE]
Commander!
We are in place at Dock 88
and ready to carry out
the capture operation!
We're ready for those
lousy Straw Hats, sir!
[JONATHAN]
Excellent.
They were just spotted passing
through the Straw Gate,
so they're en route and should
be arriving any minute now.
Now remember, these
pirates are crafty,
don't let your guard down.
[ZORO] Are you sure
it's this way, Usopp?
[USOPP] Yeah! Trust me!
It's just around the corner!
[MARINE G]
Sir?
Here they come!
Ready! Aim!
[yelps]
[KOBATO]
Medical emergency!
Let us through!
[KOBATO, NAMI yelling]
[SANJI]
Nami?
--Dressed as a nurse?
--[NAMI] What the--?
[LUFFY groaning]
[gasps] Luffy?
Hey.
A future lies before us
waiting to begin
Let's take to the wind!
and search the world for answers
to all the questions
in our minds
Exploring day and night we'll...
...live out our
dreams in paradise!
And that's why...
We're running, and running,
traveling along an open road
Never letting go of
what we came to do
We're here to see this through!
We can't lose, can't lose,
nothing on earth
can stop us now
'Cause we're not afraid
of our own destiny
We Dream and live
our lives free!
[ZORO] A few lousy flash
bombs won't stop me!
[SANJI] Really? I'm impressed,
three-sword Mary!
[ZORO] Well, I'm impressed
by your eyebrows!
[SANJI]
Bring it on, moss-head!
[ZORO]
You lousy cook!
[SANJI]
Lousy?
[USOPP]
This is no time to argue!
[DRAKE]
Mark my words!
You pirates will never
reach your ship!
[LUFFY]
I'm out of strength again.
On the next One Piece!
"Breaking Through the Siege!
The Going Merry is Recovered!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!