[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY]
Please help us... Call a doctor.
Our friend needs you.
I guess that I should
introduce myself.
My name is Dalton.
I'm the captain of
island security.
There's only one doctor here,
and she lives in a castle on
top of the tallest mountain.
Of all places, why does
she live there?!
Come on... Captain.
[USOPP]
I can't believe this...
Now our navigator's as
crazy as our captain.
[LUFFY] Hurry up, Sanji,
before Nami dies!
[SANJI grunts] Don't say
stuff like that, you idiot!
Do you want to jinx us?!
[shouts]
Look out!
[CHESS]
Oh! Wapol, come quickly.
What is it?
At last, we've returned home!
That's our homeland!
It's Drum Kingdom!
[LUFFY] "Are You Happy?
The Doctor Called Witch!"
[LUFFY gasps]
[NAMI whimpers]
What?
[SANJI]
Hm?
Hurry... Ala... ba...
Just rest. Never mind that.
We'll worry about
it later, okay?
She's not even worried
about her own life...
Just hang in there
a little longer, Nami.
Let's get going.
We have to make it to the
castle where the doctor lives,
and quickly.
Move it... you damn bunnies.
They're coming.
[SANJI]
Yeah.
Listen, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[SANJI] I don't want you
fighting these guys, all right?
‐‐[LUFFY] Why not?
‐‐[SANJI] Because...
Nami will be able to feel
every move you make.
She's too sick to be able to
handle something like that.
It would be too much.
[SANJI]
She could die.
[LUFFY grunts]
What?!
[roaring]
Jeez. Okay, then I won't
fight them at all!
But then...
[LUFFY grunts]
...what can I do?
Huh?!
[SANJI] Just dodge!
Dodge, dodge and run!
But don't retreat!
That's a little difficult!
[roaring]
[SANJI]
Flanchet... Shoot!
[LUFFY]
Dodging!
Damn. In this snow I can't
get my footing well enough
to land a solid kick.
[LAPIN CLAPIN growls]
[LUFFY yelps] They're
attacking all at once!
[SANJI] Head for the forest!
I'll cover you!
[LUFFY gasps]
[SANJI, LAPINS gruting]
[SANJI] Go left!
We'll head to the mountain.
[LUFFY]
Okay!
[SANJI] We need to get
rid of them somehow.
It would take us hours
to fight them all off,
but how do we shake 'em now?
For bunnies, these guys
are tough. We're in trouble.
[LAPIN E growls]
[SANJI]
Stop it!
What are you doing?
I told you not
to attack, you idiot!
Just leave them to me!
[LUFFY]
Sorry...
[SANJI] This is no time
to be screwing around!
[LUFFY] Sanji!
We can go up from here!
Right. Go on.
[LUFFY]
Wanna give me a lift?
[LAPINS growl]
Heh!
[LUFFY yelps]
[SANJI] Did you really
have to taunt them?!
[LUFFY]
Sorry!
[SANJI] Head for the
top of the mountain!
[USOPP] The snow's really
starting to pick up, huh?
[VIVI]
Nami... please just be okay.
[DALTON]
Tell me something...
Who are you guys?
Why do you ask that?
[DALTON] You're a group of
only six people traveling the
Grand Line on a
ship without a doctor.
Seems incredibly reckless.
In case you forgot,
we're pirates.
That's the reason you guys
were pointing all those
guns at us, remember?
Now, we may be a
small group, true,
but with the Brave Warrior
of the Sea onboard,
There's nothing to fear
from anyone or anything.
[DALTON]
Okay...
Even though we are very brave,
we are looking for someone
to be the ship's doctor.
In fact, I was really
hoping we'd find one
here on this island.
Of course,
what I wasn't expecting,
was that the doctor here would
be a witch living in a castle.
Well she's all we have.
You guys certainly seem
to be much different
than the pirates
we're used to.
[MRS. NEGI]
Hello, Dalton!
[USOPP]
Hm...? Egh!
[MRS. NEGI]
I was looking for you.
[DALTON]
Oh, what can I do for you?
[MRS. NEGI] I heard the
newcomers were looking for
Dr. Kureha.
[DALTON] Yes, but the sick
woman's friends had already
taken her up the mountain.
Oh, that's too bad.
Because I heard the doctor's
in Cocoaweed, right now.
[DALTON, VIVI, USOPP]
She's where?!
[USOPP] So Nami and the
others already passed her?!
[MAN A] Come on! We've had
enough of this crying already!
Just make him stop.
It's driving me nuts.
[OWNER]
Uh, yes... I'm sorry.
Hey, Tamachibi, what's wrong?
Are you hurt somewhere?
[OWNER] You need to stop crying
and tell me what's wrong.
You're upsetting the customers.
Tamachibi, say something!
If you don't stop crying,
you're going to go to your room.
[VILLAGERS mumbling]
[MAN B]
And look at that.
She's got that weird
monster with her again.
[gasps]
[TAMACHIBI cries]
[OWNER] That's it!
I've had enough of this!
[KUREHA]
Well, well...
Doesn't sound like a very
nice father in there.
If a child is crying
uncontrollably, chances are
something is wrong and
he doesn't know what.
[KUREHA cackles]
[KUREHA]
Stay there for now, Chopper.
[ALL gasp]
[KUREHA]
So sorry about that.
[OWNER]
It's... you.
So, are you kids... happy?
[KUREHA cackles]
[ALL yell]
[ALL]
Doctor Kureha!
[KUREHA] Anyone want my
secret to staying young?
[ALL]
No, were fine, thank you!
I can't believe she's really a
hundred and forty years old!
I'll have you know
I'm only 139.
[TAMACHIBI cries]
Shall I treat the boy?
Wait... what...? He's fine!
He isn't sick or hurt
or anything, really!
[KUREHA] Oh, well then.
Excuse me... doctor.
[gasp]
[KUREHA]
Let's go, Chopper.
Wait... Please come back!
I'm sorry. This is my mistake.
[USOPP, VIVI gasp]
[DALTON] I was aware that the
doctor had come into town
from the mountain
in the last few days.
But I assumed that she had
left and wouldn't be back
for quite some time.
[USOPP] Don't worry about it.
This isn't your fault.
The problem here is
how abnormally strong
Luffy and Sanji are.
Even if we go up the
mountain after them,
there's no way we'd be able
to catch up to them.
If we are able to find the
witch in this Cocoaweed place,
we just need to tell her
to get back up the mountain
as quickly as
she possibly can.
You're right... That's true.
We have no other choice.
[DALTON]
Forgive us.
[VIVI, USOPP]
Huh?
[DALTON] Forgive this land
for not having more doctors.
Don't say that. This isn't
something that you
need to be
apologizing for, Dalton.
[USOPP]
She's right about that.
[DALTON]
Let's hurry.
[TAMACHIBI groans]
[TAMACHIBI]
It's my hands... they hurt.
Your hands? All right...
how's this?
Ow, my leg!
You see? Now you've forgotten
all about your hands hurting.
What was that about?
What did you do to him?!
[KUREHA]
Are you happy?
You're happy. Good.
Now, stay nice and quiet.
Hey!
And you should calm down.
I only touched his leg,
and I did it very lightly.
[OWNER]
I heard a terrible noise!
He has pain in his
hands and legs.
He doesn't have a fever.
The swelling here on his leg is
from a purulent inflammation.
And it doesn't look good.
By now, the bone is
surely infected.
Chopper, bring me
some antibiotics.
Um, doctor? Is he all right?
The key to curing this disease
is treating it before
it can get too strong.
Don't worry. He'll live.
However he did almost die.
[OWNER]
What?! Almost died?!
[KUREHA] We're going to
do a little operation, okay?
[OWNER] Wait! Aren't you
going to use any anesthesia?
[KUREHA]
This is the anesthesia.
What the hell?!
[KUREHA]
Now, see how easy that was?
That's it for the treatment,
or the part you need
me for, anyway.
The rest is up to you.
Just make sure he rests and keep
his legs tightly bandaged.
Once they're bandaged,
keep them iced down.
Do you understand?
[OWNER]
Yes...
[KUREHA]
Now, about my fee.
I'm all out of trash
bags and toilet paper,
so I'm taking all of
those that you have,
along with all your
food and plum wine.
In addition to that, I'll be
taking 50 percent of this
restaurant's assets.
[gasps]
Chopper? Take it
all to the sled.
[OWNER]
This is outrageous!
You can't take half my assets!
Don't even think about giving
her all that; it's too much!
It's just crazy!
[CUSTOMERS shouting]
[CUSTOMER B] How dare you take
advantage of a sick person?!
[CUSTOMER E]
You should be ashamed!
[ALL] You aren't a real doctor
at all! You're just a witch!
[CHOPPER growls]
It's all right, Chopper.
They're just a bunch of
blabbering children.
[TAMACHIBI]
Old lady.
[OWNER gasps]
The pain... it's all better now.
Thanks so much!
[gasps]
Well, it looks like your son
just gave me a nice tip.
So I'll reduce my
fee to 49 percent.
[OWNER gasps] I'll pay
your price. Thank you.
[KUREHA]
Oh yeah... Hey, kid.
Huh?
This happiness you feel.
Don't you ever forget it.
‐‐[KUREHA cackles]
‐‐[TAMACHIBI] Okay!
[ZORO]
Burr...
It's freezing out here!
My whole body is
beginning to go numb.
I feel more like a popsicle
than a human at the moment.
Looks like I have a
lot more training to do.
But if I really concentrate,
I shouldn't be bothered by
even the coldest temperatures.
[ZORO] Hey, Karoo!
Want to come in with me?
It's a great way to get your
little bird body in shape!
[KAROO grumbles]
[KAROO shouts, whimpers]
[KAROO shouts]
[gasps] I didn't expect to
see this many fish here.
Well, I've got more to do.
[LUFFY grunts]
They coming?
[SANJI]
No. It doesn't look like it.
All right. I guess
we lost 'em, huh?
[SANJI]
Nope. We haven't yet.
[LUFFY]
They don't give up!
Why are they
jumpin' up and down?
[SANJI grunts]
[LUFFY] Maybe they're
grouchy cause they're hungry.
[SANJI]
I don't think so.
W‐Wait a second...
Don't tell me... Oh, no...
Dalton. You haven't
told us who you are yet.
Doesn't really seem like you're
just an ordinary villager.
You have this certain way of
speaking that makes me think
of a military officer.
[DALTON] You're correct.
I did serve this country.
Under our former tyrant, Wapol.
[BOTH gasp]
[WAPOL laughs]
[DALTON] I became the captain of
this country's security guard
long ago, during the time
that Wapol's father ruled here.
However, the time came
when the king died
and his rule was then handed
down to his son, Wapol.
When that happened,
this country changed.
[WAPOL] I have come up with
yet another brilliant new law!
I've decided that I'm going to
exile the country's doctors!
[CHESS]
What?
[KUROMARIMO]
Exile?
[DALTON]
The doctors?!
[WAPOL] Yes! I'll keep the
20 best doctors in the land,
and they will be my
private physicians.
I'll call them the Twenty MDs.
[CHESS]
The Twenty MDs?
[WAPOL]
That's right.
The Twenty MDs will be just for
me, and the rest will be exiled!
[KUROMARIMO] What a great idea,
Wapol! You're so smart.
[DALTON]
No! If you do this,
then who will the people go to
when they're sick or injured?
[WAPOL] Why should I
care about what happens
to those useless people?
If anyone needs a doctor, they
will have to grovel before me.
Anyone who disobeys me will be
refused any treatment at all.
This way, no one in the entire
country will dare defy me!
[WAPOL laughs] I'm such a
genius sometimes, it kills me!
[laughing continues]
[DALTON growls]
Wow, So from then on,
anyone who got sick had no
choice but to throw themselves
on Wapol's mercy and hope that
the Twenty MDs would treat them.
Yes and pay the excessive
medical fees.
So basically, Wapol was
ruling the country by taking
the citizens' lives
and health hostage?!
That's not ruling! What sort
of king would do that?!
That's tyranny.
[VIVI whimpers]
[DALTON]
It's just as I thought.
There can be no
mistaking it now.
[ZORO]
Burr...
Damn it! I got carried away
and swam for too long!
Where am I now?
And where's the ship?
This is great. I have no
way of telling where I am
with all this
snow everywhere.
[ZORO]
Huh?
Tsk.
[ZORO gasps]
I'm saved! Hey, old lady!
Sorry to bother you, but do you
think you could drop me off
at a village nearby
or something?
[ZORO]
Whoa!
What are you doing dressed
like that in this weather?
I've seen some weird old ladies
in my day but, but you, your‐‐
Huh? Uh...
Careful how you talk
to me, little boy.
[ZORO shouts]
At a hundred and
thirty‐nine years old,
I'm still young and strong.
Let's go, Chopper. That boy
is clearly some kind of freak.
[ZORO]
Come back here!
The hell was her problem?
Dumb old hag!
[whimpers]
That's cold!
I'll freeze to
death before long.
All right. I guess for now
I'll do some strength training
to get myself warmed up a bit.
[WAPOL laughs]
[WAPOL]
We've arrived at last!
After all this time,
I've returned to Drum Kingdom.
I'm finally home!
[WAPOL laughs]
[CHESS] Huh! Were they trying to
pretend to be a real military?
[KUROMARIMO] Bunch of
idiots and amateurs.
What were they thinking,
shooting at us like that?
[WAPOL]
Hm... Oh, my dear Drum Island.
Your towering majesty has
grown even more beautiful
in my absence!
Chess, is the castle all right?
Yes. It looks just as good as
when we left it. It's perfect.
[WAPOL laughs] What are we
waitin' for? Lets go home, boys.
I'm done being a pirate. Ha!
I'm going to be king again!
Onward, Robson!
[laughs]
[WAPOL] Huh? Robson move!
Why are you just standing here?
Hey! Get moving already!
[SUBORDINATE]
Wapol! We have a problem!
[WAPOL]
Hm. What's the matter now?
[SUBORDINATE]
The pirates...
The ones from the other day!
Their ship's over there!
[WAPOL]
What?!
Not them! What are the Straw Hat
Pirates doing in my country?!
How dare they come here
after pretending to not
even know about it!
[LUFFY]
Leave!
Does he not even care?!
I had a very painful recovery!
You! Go kill those
pirates now. I demand it!
[SUBORDINATE] Um, actually,
the ship is empty, sir.
Empty?
[SUBORDINATE]
We don't know where they went.
You want to be executed?
Our apologies, Wapol.
Please forgive him.
This man is just a
useless subordinate.
[WAPOL]
Hm.
Chess... Kuromarimo?
We took the liberty of
inspecting the footprints
that led away from the ship,
and we have some information.
Indeed.
It looks as if the footprints
were headed toward Big Horn.
Very good. That was
absolutely brilliant.
In that case, we're
headed on to Big Horn.
We'll stop there to fire a
salute to the restoration
of Drum Kingdom!
[pants]
[USOPP]
Wait. What are you telling us?
You mean the witch left this
town just a few moments ago?!
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me!
This is ridiculous!
She left after she made
my sickness all better.
[DALTON grunts]
[OWNER] If you're looking for
the doctor, she's already left.
We have to find her.
Can you tell us where she was
headed when she left here?
[CUSTOMER D]
I think I know.
I heard from somebody else that
she was headed for Gyasta.
Gyasta?
So where is that?
If we were going to
Gyasta from Big Horn,
we'd go in the
opposite direction
than we went to come here.
Oh great! We already passed her?
Ice skating is very
popular there.
[USOPP] What does that have
to do with anything?
‐‐Who cares about that?
‐‐[VIVI] Calm down, Usopp.
We need to get
going to that town.
At this point, we really don't
have any time to lose.
[USOPP]
Yeah, you're right.
[GUARD]
Dalton!
[GUARD grunting]
I found you at last!
Yes, guard. But I thought you
were standing watch today.
[GUARD groans]
What's the matter? I can tell
that you've been badly injured.
Tell me what went wrong.
Every watchman except for me.
They've all been killed, Dalton.
What?!
This thing...
This submarine sailboat...
it came out of nowhere,
and it attacked us.
They killed every one
of the watchmen.
We couldn't stop them.
Who are "they"?
I don't understand.
Please explain this.
Please Dalton!
You have to help us!
We aren't strong
enough to fight them!
You have to do something!
What's wrong?
It was them?
It was Wapol! Wapol and
his men. They came back!
[CUSTOMER A]
What did he say?!
[CUSTOMER B]
Wapol's back?!
[CUSTOMER C]
That can't be true!
[CUSTOMER D]
Why's he here?
Hey wait!
Dalton, wait!
[DALTON] I'm going to settle
this once and for all.
In the end, I don't know if it
can really be called justice.
I may be just as
guilty as you are,
but you're the one
who will be punished.
[DALTON] Just wait!
I'm coming for you, Wapol!
Those damn bunnies! Great!
They've done it now!
This isn't good.
Uh... Wait, what are
you talking about?
And what are the
bunnies doing?
[SANJI]
Okay. We gotta run, Luffy.
[LUFFY] We're running again?
Where to?
[SANJI] Anywhere.
As long as it's far away.
There's about to
be an avalanche!
♪If there is a treasure
out there to be found,
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big place,
the oceans are wide,
Dumb luck alone
won't help you find it,
Just give up, it's astronomical.
Even so.
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on,
The laughter behind our
backs, it keeps us strong
It's too bad 'cuz we're still
sailing forward, so bon voyage!
Just leave us alone!
It may be foolish
chasing impossible things,
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream,
the more ambition
I'm gonna need!
It may be foolish
travelin' on, but I know
That I just gotta fight!
The farther the sea,
the greater paradise
We're gonna find!
Don't give up,
just keep on trying,
And you'll see that
you're closer to...
The horizon of your dreams!♪
[USOPP] Where's the doctor?
Where is she?
[SANJI] Luffy, hurry! We need
to get as high up as we can!
[LUFFY shouts] The bunnies
are still following us!
[VIVI]
I wonder if Dalton is all right.
Can he take on Wapol and
his men all by himself?
[ZORO] Whoa! Look at that sword!
He's really good!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Dalton's Resolve! Wapol's
Corps Lands on the Island!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!