[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[JABRA]
Just like I promised.
I'll kill you quickly.
There won't be any pain.
It's too bad, really.
You were so much better
off when you were connected
to that green-haired
shepherd over there.
This is the end!
Please, don't kill him!
Keep your key! We don't need it!
[JABRA]
And now it's over!
[ZORO and NAMI]
Usopp!
Who the hell are you?
I'm the hunter.
I'm-- I'm sorry, Sanji. I--
I tried.
But I couldn't--
You're alive,
that's what matters.
Everyone has things
that they can do
and things that they can't.
Yeah, but--
Both of you.
Take a look outside.
Oh, no.
It's the Gates of Justice.
They're starting to open!
Robin.
[SANJI] If those gates open up
and Robin goes through them,
we won't have any
way to follow her.
She'll cross waters
infested with Sea Kings,
and beyond that is either
the undersea prison
or Navy Headquarters.
Everywhere on the other side
of those gates is
beyond our reach.
We'll lose her forever.
[NAMI] But I thought Luffy would
have caught up to her by now.
Let's teach her
a lesson, Funkfreed.
[ROBIN]
Luffy is just up ahead!
But don't kill her. Understood?
Ivory Dart!
Idiot! You, will never escape!
Don't underestimate me!
Now come along, you wench,
through the gates of dreams.
[SANJI]
Leave this guy's key to me.
Changing my opponent, huh?
Doesn't matter to me.
For now, I'm gonna stay here
and do what you can't do.
You need to do what I can't do.
[SANJI]
Think carefully.
Read the situation!
As long as we have you,
there's still a chance
we can save Robin!
You hear me, Usopp?
I want to live!
[USOPP]
What I can do?
[LUFFY]
As long as you have me,
there's a chance
we can save Robin?
How? What are you talking about?
And Shave.
Get outta here!
Right. C'mon, Usopp!
Ow, geez,
I'm still injured, y'know?
Just suck it up!
Staying here and getting
killed will hurt more!
That's a pretty good point!
Iron Body Kenpo!
Wolf Repel!
I thought you're supposed
to be some kind of hunter.
Guess you're nothin' but talk.
Wait! Now I get it!
Get what?
We can save Robin.
As long as I'm here
we can save her, dammit!
Whoa, okay.
Do you really have to get
so carried away about it?
[USOPP]
C'mon, let's go!
[NAMI]
Hey, wait up!
[USOPP] I've got it, I've got
it, we can save her!
[NAMI]
Will you shut up?
That's not exactly something
we want the wolf to hear!
Looks like I'll get
to kill them after all.
Damn. Direct hit.
Well that pissed me off.
Ten Finger Pistol!
[SANJI]
Troisieme-- Hache!
[JABRA]
Iron Body!
Do you think I even felt that?
This punk's got
some serious kicks.
That technique you guys use
to make your
body strong as iron?
Yeah, it's a really
big pain in my ass.
Tempest Kick Lone Wolf!
Basses Cote! Longe!
Tendron!
Flanchet! Quasil!
Queue! Cuisseau! Jarret!
Veau Shot!
Iron Body Kenpo!
How many times have
I gotta tell you?
Your kicks do nothin' to me!
Now that's real power.
That was my Iron Body
Kenpo Wolf Fang Stance.
I'm the only master of
the Six Powers that can
move around freely while
using the Iron Body technique.
[SANJI] You're tellin
me this like I care.
Deuxieme Hache!
That should've done the trick,
but he could be faking.
Is he actually stayin' down?
Nicely done.
I've been waitin' for
a worthy opponent.
And I finally found him.
[JABRA] Now if you don't
mind me askin' a favor.
Save Robin for me.
[SANJI]
What?
What're you talkin' about?
[JABRA] Nobody knows
this, but Robin is--
This is difficult for me to say,
but she's my
long-lost little sister.
She's what?
I had no idea.
I mean-- She never
said anything about
having an older brother before.
I'm not surprised
but it's the truth.
It's been more than twenty years
since we were separated.
I'll never forget that day.
It happened on a small
island in the West Blue.
The weather was sunny
and warm that day.
Robin and I were
having so much fun
just spending the day
together on the beach.
Big brother!
My sister and I were
the best of friends.
So naturally,
we always played together.
Look what I made!
We couldn't have possibly
been happier that day.
Little did we know
what was waiting for us.
I turned my back and
looked away for one second.
When a pirate crew
kidnapped my sister
and took her from me.
Robin! Bring back my sister!
And that was the
last time I saw her.
By the time that she
finally managed to escape
from the pirates--
Robin.
She was already
wanted by the law.
I blame myself for all this.
And that's why I'll do anything
to make sure she's safe,
but I can't help her now.
I'm not strong enough.
So please.
I'm on my knees begging you.
You have to save Robin!
[SANJI]
Sure, I can do that.
Leave it to me.
I'll just pick up this key here,
and then I'll be
off to save her.
You really think
I'd buy that crap?
My darling Robin is your
long-lost little sister?
Dumbass.
I'll have to kick you
twice as hard for that one.
[SPANDAM] I've dragged you
far beyond the reach
of any help or hope
and yet you keep
on trying to escape.
You stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid woman!
I'm completely
exhausted thanks to you.
Now get up and walk
on your own, you cow!
You are just determined
to keep making me repeat this:
There isn't even a microscopic
residue of hope left for you.
Sure, we might've
heard what could've been
a voice earlier, but I haven't
seen anyone, have you?
If there was anyone back there,
Lucci is probably killing
them right about now.
Get it?
[laughs]
[coughs]
Look what you've done to me!
I'm so exhausted I can't
even cackle without coughing!
You stupid, stupid,
stupid woman!
You're ruining everything!
Stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid woman!
Hasn't it sunk in yet?
You can fight as hard
as you possibly can,
but I am not going to
let you through those doors.
[LUFFY]
No. You're wrong.
'Cause no matter
how hard you fight,
I'm still gonna get past you!
I doubt that we'll
ever agree on this.
So there's no sense
in us discussing it.
And I don't have time
for talking anyway.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Stamp! Whip!
Spear!
Am I finally starting to make
an impression on you, wolf?
Hey, that's my key!
Well yeah,
you did give it to me.
You bastard.
Still want a fight, huh?
Iron Body Kenpo!
[SANJI]
Later!
[JABRA]
Get back here!
I'm the one who's supposed
to trick people
around here, dammit!
How dare you mock me
and steal my gimmick!
Shave!
Party Table!
Iron Body Kenpo!
Cuisseau Shoot!
Brochette!
Damn twerp. Now I'm pissed off.
If you wanna get hurt
that bad, I'll oblige you.
And the easiest way to do that
is to reveal to you
the true power of
my Iron Body Kenpo.
Iron Body Kenpo
Wolf Plantain Stance!
Wolf Hunt High-Speed Scratch!
[SANJI]
Crap!
Heavy Wolf Paw!
How's that Iron Body Punch feel?
Probably gonna ache for the rest
of your short, pathetic life.
Moon Walk!
Tempest Kick! Lupus Fall!
That was a pretty stupid
move you made back there,
trying to steal my key and
run off while I'm still alive.
I'm a wolf, you dolt.
I won't stop chasing you
until you're in my jaws.
[JABRA]
Still hanging in there, huh?
[SANJI]
I'm not going anywhere, pal.
I'm not about to
get killed, either.
And I'm not gonna forgive you.
[JABRA]
Forgive me?
Upset with the way
we've treated Robin?
Gettin' all emotional
will only clutter up
your mind during a fight.
Don't waste all of your
precious time pitying
that hopeless fool of a
woman when you should be busy
trying to think up a way
to get out of here alive.
[SANJI]
Watch your damn mouth, wolf.
You don't wanna see me mad.
I tend to overheat when I'm mad.
[JABRA] You aren't
gonna win this battle
by tossin' around threats.
It's pretty obvious how
badly injured you are.
Though I'm more than happy
to put you out of your misery.
Iron Body Kenpo Devil Wolf!
Go ahead and laugh it up.
It's the last
chance you'll have.
I don't get the point of this.
You tryin' to make me
dizzy from watching you?
What happened?
Why's his foot
all red like that?
The foot of the devil.
Diable Jambe.
The heat I generated
from all that spinning
will burn my kicks
straight through you.
[JABRA]
It's glowing!
[SANJI]
Ow! It burns!
The heat of its
destructive power burns
hotter than the flames of hell.
Ow! Hot, hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
I'm burning up!
Even my bones feel
like they're melting!
My Iron Body won't work!
How the hell could one
kick possibly do that?
Moron. You don't jump in the air
while you're fighting
a Six Powers Master.
Diable Jambe! Premiere Hache!
[JAMBRA]
Too bad! What a rookie mistake!
You got in a big hurry
to win and ya got sloppy.
So long, sucker!
Moonlight Ten Finger Pistol!
So you knocked one hand away.
Big deal!
If your other kick
could've landed in time,
you might've stopped my
Finger Pistol from hitting you.
Well I had no choice.
I had to get you close enough
to finish you off
with my last kick.
Diable Jambe!
Wait!
Flambage--
Shot!
God may have created food.
But the devil created spices.
If you think that kick was hot,
my heart was
burning even hotter.
[KAKU]
What are you talking about?
My attack has already begun!
[ZORO]
What?
[KAKU]
Giraffe Shower!
[ZORO]
There's too many of 'em. Damnit.
I can't block!
[KAKU] You're just beginning
to understand
the real, wild, destructive
strength of a giraffe.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Fierce Sword Attacks!
Zoro Vs. Kaku, Powerful
Sword Fighting Showdown!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!