Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the next
King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use
any means necessary
to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path
across the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Desperate to join the
ranks of Shiki the Golden Lion,
the Amigo Pirates
stormed Kansorn Island
to capture the pirate's
escaped giant beetle.
[COLT] You have only
two options here.
Give us the beetle or die.
[LUFFY]
Look, I already tried.
The beetle doesn't wanna
join a pirate crew.
So just leave him alone.
You got the wrong idea, idiot.
We're here to take
that beetle prisoner,
not make friends with him!
Eh?
[LUFFY grunting]
[AMIGO PIRATES scream]
[LARGO]
Mucho Needle Net!
[NAMI gasps]
Pointy!
[LUFFY groaning]
Luffy, no!
I admire your elastic nature,
but you must pay the price.
Comeuppance, senor!
[LUFFY] A Special Presentation
Related to the Movie.
The Fierce Onslaught
of the Amigo Pirates
[CHOPPER]
Come on! It's not fair!
She's unbeatable!
You've now won
69 games in a row.
You're like some sort
of prodigy, Robin.
Hm. I wonder.
This's a game of luck.
And nobody's that lucky.
[ROBIN]
Oh my. Is that so?
Then you're accusing me
of cheating, Franky?
Maybe so...
[bang]
[ALL gasp]
So loud! What was that noise?
[ROBIN] It came from
behind the mountain.
[BROOK] Do you think Nami
and the others are okay?
[FRANKY]
I guess catchin' that beetle
is tougher than they thought.
Instead of playin' cards, why
don't we go give 'em a hand?
[CHOPPER]
Yeah!
[ALL gasping]
His "big bro"?
They're related?
They don't look it.
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Dammit! What is this thing?
It keeps biting me! Stupid net!
[LARGO]
There's no point in fighting.
You can struggle
as much as you like,
but the more you do,
the tighter the net will get.
To suffocate at
such a young age.
What a cruel world.
A real tragedy.
[COLT whimpers]
[LARGO]
Correct me if I'm wrong, but,
you are the vice captain?
[LARGO]
Which makes you responsible
for this shameful situation.
[COLT]
I can explain!
The giant beetle we're
after is supposed to be
the guardian of
the island, right?
So, the plan was just
to give 'em a good scare.
Enough to get the beetle
to come to their rescue.
[COLT] But then that noisy
rubber poophead got in the way!
A giant beetle? How strange.
I thought we were looking
for a large needle.
Why would Shiki
need a giant needle?
You never listen
to what I tell you!
It's a grande beetle, okay?
Oh. Well then.
I wonder if the giant beetle
I happened to pass
on the way here is the
same one we're looking for.
[COLT, AMIGO PIRATES]
What?
[YOKO gasps]
Oh, no!
[YOKO]
You've gotta hide, Boss!
Boss! Can you hear me? Boss!
Where'd you see
the beetle, big bro?
[LARGO] I think it was
somewhere around there.
All right, then let's just--
[LARGO] Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Sure, we could saunter over
and capture the stupid
insect, but that's boring.
It'd be more fun to give
these yokels an ultimatum.
Hand over the beetle or die.
If I remember correctly,
that was your original plan.
Why squander your
only good idea? Ha ha!
That was before we knew
where the beetle was.
But, first off,
[LARGO] it might behoove us to
do away with these two ruffians
who've been glaring at us
with such hostility.
[LARGO]
I'll give you a choice.
Surrender yourselves to us now,
or die by my
Net-Net Fruit power.
Which would be muy malo.
Oh, such a tragic decision.
Ah. Well. I'll wallow in
your sorrow, swordsman.
[ZORO grunts]
108 Caliber Phoenix!
Yeah, nice try!
[LARGO]
How surprising!
And here I was about to nod off!
Mucho Sticky Net!
Huh? I can't cut it!
But that is not all.
Sticky Net Network!
[ZORO gasps]
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO]
What? Ugh, It's so damn sticky!
Tighter and tighter
and tighter it spins!
[ZORO]
Crap!
Aw, jeez, way to
not get captured!
And what does our next rival do?
[SANJI] I'm a first-class chef,
you weirdo bondage freak!
Ah. Then something boiling hot
seems appropriate, right Colt?
Sure!
Caliente!
I don't really see how
boiling your insides
is gonna help you that much.
[LARGO]
Well, that was certainly hot.
But, no pain no gain.
Million Boiling Net!
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI grunting]
[SANJI grunts]
[SANJI panting]
That's enough.
Screw you and all
your crappy nets.
[SANJI]
Just let my friends go already!
Such loyal friendship
does touch my heart.
Willing to sacrifice
his own life for them.
Now Mucho! Iron Net!
[SANJI]
What the?
You cheater!
Huh?
Oh come on.
Whoa, he just captured
all three of them!
These guys are the real deal.
[LARGO]
And there you have it.
To explain your
means of confinement.
The swordsman is in my
sticky net, but there's also,
[LARGO]
iron, hot water,
and my favorite.
A little fuego.
[LARGO yelps]
[LARGO cackles] I can transform
any type of matter I ingest
into a net. Anything at all.
My capture rate? 120%.
I'm sure you regret
challenging me.
But it is far too late
for second thoughts now.
Many apologies.
[LUFFY, ZORO, SANJI grunting]
[LARGO] So, I believe I'll
leave this next part to you.
Make me proud and
do your very worst.
[COLT] Right. You can
count on it, big bro.
You guys. Your attention please.
Coming from the East Blue,
I know your first reaction
is to run and hide.
So I'll appeal once again
to your sense of survival.
Just give us the beetle,
or we'll slaughter
every one of you.
[YOKO whimpers]
[COLT] Alright. I'm gonna
start picking you off
one by one from the end.
I'd recommend speaking up
if you don't wanna die.
[DOJO KIDS yelp]
That's enough!
--Huh?
[DOJO BOY]
Huh? Hey!
Yoko, no! Get back here!
Leave now, or I'll fight you!
Is that a Navy coat?
They're sure recruiting
'em young these days.
Oh, no. Senorita.
You threaten us
with a bamboo sword?
Is the weight of your
sorrow so great?
Shut up! I can beat you jerks
with any weapon I want!
No! Don't do it!
Shoot her.
[AMIGO PIRATES]
Right!
Yoko!
[YOKO yells]
Boss, no!
[BOSS growls]
[AMIGO PIRATES clamoring]
I'm gonna take a guess
that's Shiki's big beetle.
I didn't know it was that big.
And things were about
to get interesting, too.
[RED SHIRT]
Take 'em down, Boss!
[STRIPED SHIRT BOY]
You show those bad guys!
Yeahhh! Do it! Go crazy, bug!
[AMIGO PIRATES whimpering]
[AMIGO PIRATES yelping]
Shoot it down!
[AMIGO PIRATES scream]
[VILLAGERS cheer]
Awesome!
Careful, Boss!
Big Bro! How about some nets?
Such a letdown.
A thorough disappointment.
We were right on the cusp
of a dreadfully beautiful
and angelic inferno
fueled by despair.
Now I'll never hear the
symphony of their hopelessness.
Just use your damn nets!
Look at this annoying pest.
He's begging to be swatted.
[LARGO]
Mucho...
Burning...
...Net!
Ready and fire!
[YOKO whimpers]
[FABRE gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[LUFFY gasps]
[BOSS groans]
[YOKO]
Boss!
We got it!
[AMIGO PIRATES cheering]
Oh, Boss.
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
Man, I didn't think
anyone could beat Boss.
There's no other way.
C'mon. Please, Fabre.
The only way to save the
island is to let them take Boss!
You're the mayor!
Now make a decision!
Yoko. I'm sorry.
[YOKO]
What should I do?
Dad. What would you do?
I can't surrender!
[YOKO gasps]
I'm here, Boss.
Huh? Wait, where are you going?
[YOKO gasps]
Are you..?
[YOKO]
No! That's not what I want!
No!
[YOKO]
Boss!
Hey, Mayor Fabre!
What's Boss doing?
[FABRE gasps]
He must have--
He must have understood
our feelings.
He heard how scared
we were and now
he's trying to save us
by sacrificing himself.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[LUIGIA gasp]
[MITSUBOSHI gasps]
[MENDO growls]
Come back!
[BOSS growls]
Hey there. It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
You've got cuts and
bruises all over.
[YOKO]
But it'll be fine.
Just take it easy. I'll get
you fixed up, you'll see.
[BOSS groans]
[FABRE gasps]
I promise you can trust me.
[YOKO grunts]
No!
Music to my ears.
Sad, lovely music.
Thank you for
your grief, senorita.
That was too easy. But her
anguish made it worth it.
[LARGO]
Come in and get cozy.
[COLT laughs] With this
beetle in our clutches,
Shiki's gonna welcome us
into his crew with open arms!
Hey! Beetle!
Hold on!
[COLT, LARGO]
Huh?
[LUFFY grunting]
Wait!
I said stop!
I know you can hear me!
[YOKO gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[LUFFY panting]
Nice try, but you're not
takin' the easy way out.
Not with these bastards!
Ya hear me, beetle?
You're not goin' anywhere
until you fight me, damnit!
And don't act like
you don't remember!
You're can't back out
of our promise!
Really, pirate?
Hey, what's your problem?
He was just trying
to sacrifice himself!
Can't you see he was
trying to help us!
[LUFFY] Shut up! Shut up! I
don't give a damn about that!
All I want is to fight
that giant beetle!
[YOKO gasps]
[VILLAGERS]
Is that it?
Ugh. Jeez, he's hopeless.
Got a problem with that?
This is so awful!
[VILLAGERS]
Huh?
This can't be happening!
I want Boss to stay
here with me!
Aw, Yoko...
[YOKO sobbing]
You can't take him.
I won't let you.
He has to stay here!
There's nothing like
a crying little girl
to really open your
eyes. Put me down.
Huh?
[FABRE]
You're completely right, Yoko.
I'm sorry we were too scared to
make the right decision earlier.
[MITSUBOSHI]
We were dumb enough to think
we'd be better off
letting them take Boss.
[MENDO] I'm ashamed it
even crossed our minds.
Boss is like family to us
and we all love him!
As much as this island!
And... and... and...
And no way are we gonna let...
...scum like you lot...
[GROUP]
...take him from us!
[VILLAGERS cheer]
Oh, now this is just pathetic.
Some scrappy nina turns on the
waterworks and you go loco?
It's like a melodrama!
You make me sick!
[LARGO]
Death is their only option.
Underdogs ready to be put down.
So sad. Heh, heh, heh.
[YOKO gasps]
Wait. Is that?
[ALL gasp]
It's happening.
Boss is shedding his skin!
[BOSS growls]
Whoa!
[AMIGO PIRATES whimpering]
[LUFFY gasps]
[BOSS growls]
[LUFFY screams]
[ZORO, SANJI grunting]
[LUFFY groans]
[ALL gasp]
How funny is that?
That dumb beetle.
Killing his own allies!
[COLT chuckles]
[BOSS groans]
[YOKO gasps]
Boss!
What's wrong?
No, Boss!
This is awful!
It must've been too soon
for him to molt!
I do not claim to be
an entomologist.
But you didn't finish molting.
How heartbreaking.
You have my pity.
Your screaming and crying
won't do any good.
No one's gonna save
you whining peasants
now that we got
your guardian angel.
[LUFFY]
The fight's not over yet.
[COLT]
Eh?
[LARGO]
Que?
[LUFFY] You didn't risk
your life for nothing.
We'll save your friends, Boss.
We owe you that much.
Leave everything to us!
Well. The fun's over.
It's time to get serious.
[NARRATOR] In hopes of
saving the giant beetle
and protecting Little East Blue,
it's citizens follow
Nami's secret plan
and take to the island's
labyrinth-like caves.
Meanwhile, Luffy
chases after Largo,
but finds himself thwarthed
when Largo transforms
his entire body into a net.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece.
A Special Presentation
Related to the Movie:
The Battle is On!
Luffy vs. Largo.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!