Stop it, Saul!
You're scaring me!
Hope you're ready 'cause
if you make an enemy
outta me there's
gonna be hell to pay!
What's going on?
It's Vice Admiral Saul!
He ran away with Nico Olvia
and now he's attacking us!
He's lost his mind!
What's he doing on Ohara?
Hell if I know!
The whole island is done for!
They're gonna burn
it to the ground!
Don't give up yet!
Even if the library burns,
we can still save the books!
Throw them out the window
and drop them in the lake!
They're better off wet than
burned to ash! Hurry up!
Fire!
Come back! Don't do this!
It's not like you!
Get all the books
out of the library!
Don't give up on a single book!
Don't give up on
a single sentence!
These words have been passed
on for thousands of years!
They must reach the future!
Robin! Get the heck outta here!
The evacuation ship's
gonna leave without you!
Don't worry about me, just run!
Mommy!
Shoot him down!
C'mon! Go! Get moving!
Don't you remember
what your mom told you?
You must live, Robin!
Attention evacuees,
the ship is leaving!
Wait! Someone's coming!
It's her!
Isn't that the monster girl?
Yeah, it is!
Go away! You're creepy!
Hey! Now's not
the time for that!
No wait!
That kid's mother Olvia
was in the newspaper
just the other day!
That means she's the
daughter of a criminal!
You're right!
If we let her on the ship,
it might cause us trouble!
Just leave her!
Don't be ridiculous!
She's just a child!
Hurry up and help her!
Everyone stop!
Don't let that brat on board!
Huh?
She may be a child, but
she's still an archaeologist.
That means she's a criminal
like the rest of them!
A little girl like that?
If you say so, Chief.
See? I told you!
Good thing we didn't let her on!
Robin! Must be CP9.
Damn! I'll show them!
Chief! Vice Admiral Saul
is coming this way!
Is that so?
Then there was no
need to question Olvia
about him after all!
Fire! Now! Shoot him down!
Ice Block! Partisan!
Saul!
It's Kuzan!
You.
My my my. This just won't do.
If we let a former marine
stop the Buster Call,
we'd look like damn fools.
Kuzan, wake up.
You can't tell me
this nonsense is justice!
Pull back! Now!
You know this ain't right!
They're just making
an example out of Ohara!
Come on. Please.
You're better than this.
If it's for the good of
the world, it has to be done.
You can't deny
that those scholars
are breaking the law, can you?
I won't criticize
your sense of justice.
There are as many rights
and wrongs as there are
viewpoints in the world.
However, if you insist
on getting in our way,
I can't sit back and do nothing.
The evacuation
ship was blown up!
Wha--what happened?
Looked like cannon fire!
From one of our ships!
It was Vice Admiral Sakazuki!
That idiot.
If we're doing this,
we have to be thorough.
If even one of those scholars
had managed to sneak onboard
that ship then all
the sacrifices
we made today
would be in vain.
However small, we cannot
allow any evil to thrive.
Is this what you call justice?
Can you take pride
in something like this?
We went too far.
I would never do
something like that!
We gotta run, Robin!
This fella's way too
strong for me to fight!
Saul is escaping!
He's taking one of
the scholars with him!
Ice Time Capsule!
Oh no! Saul, are you okay?
Robin, you gotta
get out of here.
Don't look back, just go!
If you stay on
this island, you'll die!
Take my raft and go out to sea!
But what about you?
He's got me, little lady. I'm
afraid this is the end. Hurry!
No! Everybody
I care about is here!
Now you listen to me.
You may be lonely at first.
But one day,
you'll find true friends.
True friends?
Yeah, the sea's a vast
place, so I guarantee--
someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
No matter who you are,
ain't no one born into
this world to be alone!
It's time to go, Robin.
This is goodbye! When things
are bad, do like I taught cha.
You remember the
laugh, don'tcha?
Look out! He's behind you!
Dereshishishishi!
Now. Ice Time.
Saul, no!
Dereshishi...
Your friends are out there
at sea waiting for you, Robin.
All you gotta do is find them!
Share your life with them
and never let them go.
This is it. We're done for!
So this is the history
that mankind has chosen.
Shall we ever learn
the error of our ways?
Forgive me Robin.
I couldn't even leave you
with any parting words.
Neither as a scholar,
or a mother.
The Tree of Knowledge,
it's falling!
The concept of
"absolute justice"
can sometimes drive
a man to madness.
I've decided to let you escape.
I'm curious to see what
kind of flower will sprout
from the seed that
Saul protected.
You can bear a grudge against
whoever you like for this but
at least you're still alive.
However, I do suggest
you keep a low profile.
I've drawn a path for you
on the sea with my ice.
If you take the boat
and go straight ahead,
you'll reach land eventually.
Oh, one last thing.
I'm not your ally. If you do
cause any trouble,
I'll be the first
person to come after you.
My mom's here, can you help her?
No one will be saved.
If that pain is too
great for you to bear,
then you may join them.
This library is the
best in the world!
Do you like to read books?
Today is Robin's birthday!
Happy birthday
from us at the library!
Your mamma's a wonderful woman!
Ohara's a wonderful place!
And as surely as we
believe in the past,
we believe in the future
that you will inherit!
When you're feelin'
down, just laugh.
There ain't nothin'
a good laugh can't fix.
It seems awfully silly
to laugh when you're sad.
Don't knock it till you try it!
Dereshishishi! Dereshishishi!
Dereshishishi! Dereshi,,,
Dereshishishi!
Dereshishishi! Dereshishishi!
The sea's a vast place,
so I guarantee someday
you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
Survivors? No, I don't think so.
Hey!
Huh?
Come here, look at the lake!
What? That's insane!
How did all of
those books get here?
It can't be a coincidence!
Yeah, this is her!
That's definitely the girl!
Where did you find her?
Is she captured?
No, we were told to keep
watch for a suspicious girl.
We eventually found her
on a passenger ship
Northeast of Ohara.
Unfortunately,
she knew what we were after,
so she slipped away
before we could catch her.
She's got the devil's luck.
Back then, I'm sure
I saw her leaving Ohara.
The island was burning to ash,
but she somehow made it out
alone on a little rowboat!
Of course, I tried to chase
her but all of a sudden,
the helm of our boat got
stuck like it was frozen in ice!
Either way, Saul probably helped
her escape before he died.
A scholar with the ability
to read the Poneglyphs
is dangerous no matter
how young she may be.
I don't care what
methods you use.
If we don't capture
her immediately,
then this entire mission
will have been for nothing!
79 million Berries?
Why does an eight-year-old
child have such a high bounty?
They said she's one
of the devils of Ohara.
You know, those scholars who
were plotting to end the world.
Really?
I heard she sank six
Marine battleships, too.
She must have some
kind of weird power.
Well, that explains the bounty.
The government forces
and Navy leaders
are searching for her, too!
She probably wants to
carry out the same plan
as the scholars
that were executed.
If she's out for revenge,
then no one is safe!
We can't let a child
of the devil run wild!
Such a kind girl.
Thank you for helping me out.
Sure! I'm grateful
for any work I can get.
By the way, before
we have our dinner
some men are here to see you.
Don't let her get away!
Now, give me my money!
I told you where she
was hiding, didn't I?
She may be small,
but she still works hard.
What's wrong?
Having trouble sleeping?
We have to get up early tomorrow
to go to work, so rest well.
'Kay.
She's sweet but if
we keep her around,
we could get in serious trouble.
Besides, just
look at this bounty!
Honey, she isn't in her room!
Damn it!
She must've
overheard us talking!
Dereshishishi!
You're hungry? Sorry. Me too.
Seems we're both
wanted by the law, Robin.
I know all about you.
Work for me and I'll make
sure you never go hungry.
Captain!
The Marines are after us!
Where did Robin go?
Hand her over, damn it!
Hurry! That girl is bad luck!
A devil like you
shouldn't even exist!
What? Nico Robin's here?
Where at?
Hunt her down!
Turn her in to the government!
I can't believe it. A Poneglyph.
Stay away!
I have nothing to
sell to the likes of you!
Look, I'm 16. I'll do anything.
Please, just allow
me to join your group.
You betrayed me, you damn witch!
Nico Robin.
I'd like you to assist me.
I've been told you
can read Poneglyphs.
If you trigger a Buster Call,
everything will be destroyed.
That includes
all of Enies Lobby,
and most likely you as well.
Nonsense! What're you saying?
They wouldn't
kill a VIP like me!
I'm not falling for your bluff!
20 years ago, everything
was taken from me.
And many innocent
lives were lost.
With one push of a button,
they summoned a terrible demon.
Now it rears its head again.
Aiming its sights on the friends
I've searched so hard to find.
The more that I wish
for us to be together,
the more my ugly fate
bares its fangs at you!
Even now, no matter
how far we sail,
there's an enemy that
haunts me at every turn!
Because I'm facing the world,
and all of its darkness.
First it was Aokiji,
and now CP9.
I've dragged you into
my troubles twice already!
If it goes on and on like this,
no matter how kind you may be,
someday, you'll
see me as a burden.
Someday you'll be forced to
betray me and throw me away!
That's what I'm most afraid of!
Understand? That's why
I didn't want you to rescue me!
If that's the only
future I have,
I'd rather die
to save me the pain!
Robin.
I never knew.
I see. So that's it.
There you have it!
Yep! Right on the mark!
What a sorry case!
Even if you make friends,
all you can do is drag them
through the mud with you!
You can't win, pirates!
Look at this flag!
This symbol represents the
unity of over 170 nations.
A power that spans the
four seas and the Grand Line!
This is the world itself!
No matter how loud
your bark may be,
you can't stand up
to an enemy like that!
Just face it already!
Do you realize how
strong our organization is?
Do you realize how devoted
we are to capturing her?
If that's Robin's enemy,
then I know what to do.
Sniper King.
Hm?
Shoot down that flag.
Roger.
This my new weapon, a massive
slingshot by the name of Kabuto!
Behold its awesome power!
Special Attack Firebird Star!
No way.
Mission complete.
Now they've done it!
Those idiots!
You can't fire on a
government flag! That's crazy!
Those pirates just declared war
against the World Government!
You're all going to die!
You morons can't challenge the
entire world and expect to win!
Yeah?
Bring it on!
Robin!
There's still something
I want to hear you say!
Tell me you want to live!
Robin.
I can live?
Face it!
Your whole existence
is nothing but a crime!
The whole world's
against you Robin!
You can't be allowed to live!
I never dared to wish
for something like that.
The world had
denied me that hope.
I just want to die!
The sea's a vast place
so I guarantee--
someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
Believe in Luffy.
But now.
If I'm allowed to say my
wish--just this once. Then I--
I want to live!
Take me with you!
Take me away from here!
You guys!
You're so awesome--I love you!
Let's go!
When I was a kid,
I swore I'd gather a crew,
set out to sea,
and become a pirate.
A pirate, just like
the man who saved me.
And now, just as
he protected me,
I'll protect you, too, Robin!
You're one of us!
You're my friend!
I'm going to save
you no matter what!
Let's go!
On the next One Piece:
"Jump Towards The Falls!
Luffy's Feelings!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!