If you're prepared to
die, then that's fine.
Just come along with me.
We'll brave the storm.
On my sea train!
Whoa-hoa!
Awesome!
Its name is "Rocketman."
Comes with no guarantees,
so board at your own risk.
Rocketman!
Sounds fast!
Go ahead.
I just finished servicing it.
Water and coal has been loaded
and the steam's building up now.
Thanks for getting it
ready for us. We owe you one!
I wouldn't celebrate
yet, if I were you.
You might not
even survive the ride.
This was our failed prototype
before the Puffing Tom.
No matter how you tune it,
you can't control its speed.
In other words,
it's a runaway train.
That's fine!
It can go as fast as it wants!
Straw Hat!
Please, Straw Hat.
You guys gotta take us with you!
The people from Galley-La said
you were gonna take a
sea train to Enies Lobby!
Those government
bastards took Franky!
They took our bro away from us!
I'll give up my pride
if I can save him!
C'mon.
Hurry up!
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Now let's take off!
All right boys and girls.
Hold on tight,
so you don't fall off!
Now Departing Water
Seven for Enies Lobby!
Here comes Rocketman!
Yeah!
Full speed!
Let's go!
We'll get everything back!
What in the world is this place?
An underground canal!
Hey!
Luffy, you okay?
Water in my nose!
Duh!!!
What did you
expect would happen?!
Careful!
Whew!
Didn't see that one coming!
Aw, man!
This is getting exciting!
Hey, hey, hey!
Granny!
It feels a lot
like we're falling!
We're almost to the exit now.
Full speed ahead
until we fly outta here!
What?
No way!
You're kidding, right?!
All right!
There it is!
Time to move out, men!
Let's charge ahead, join
them, and get Franky back!
Yeah!!!
Sodom! Gomorrah! Jump!
Huh?!
Straw Hat!
The entire Franky Family
thanks you for helping us!
We'll never forget it!
Fire the connection cannons!
Cool!
Hey, nice job!
Pretty high-grade
bulls you've got there!
Awesome!
Dammit!
Those stupid bastards!
You idiots!
You gotta be more careful!
Thanks for the help!
What a cheerful bunch of guys.
Hey, monster granny!
So is this that fastest
that Rocketman can go?
It's not very fast at all!
Just hold your horses.
Things'll change once
we hit the railway.
Railway?
Where is it?
I don't see it anywhere.
Looks like it
drifted a bit, huh?
Listen I know these sea trains
like the back of my hand.
I'll find that railway,
no problem!
Found ya!
Let's go!
Attention!
This train will soon
be on the railway.
Once we are, our acceleration
will increase exponentially!
Find something to hold on to
so we can keep the
injuries to a minimum.
"A minimum"?
We'll be injured regardless?
Damn!
I missed it!
No worries!
We're just getting started!
Listen, you!
Behave yourself!
Whoa!
That was close, Granny!
A little to the right!
Meow!
Don't you worry!
I'll get it next time!
You'll see!
Chimney!
Gonbe!
No!
I left you with Iceberg!
Meow! Meow!
How could this have happened?!
Get down from there
and come inside!
You'll be blown away out there!
We're fine! We're fine!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, WHOA!
Chimney!
I'm gonna fall!
Whatever you do, don't let go!
I'm flying!
Meow!
Wait!
Hold on a second, okay?
Let me slow down!
Oh, no!
I forgot!
No brakes!
We can't stop!
Whoa, what the heck?
Hey, that kind
of looks like fun!
Look, it's the Straw Hat guy!
Hi!
Meow!
Hurry!
Grab those two
and bring them inside!
Once this train hits the
railway, they'll be blown away!
Right!
Yes!
All right!
They got onto the railway!
What?!
No way!
Here! Let me take a look!
Yes, you're right!
I see I see!
Just what you'd expect
from Ms. Kokoro!
She's something else, isn't she?
Indeed!
I must admit.
For a while there, I wasn't
sure what was going to happen!
I know what you mean!
With this storm and those waves,
it must have been nearly
impossible to find the railway!
Exactly!
Quite right!
I can't imagine what
it must've been like to--
For sure! For sure!
Just look at--
Don't mind if I do!
Yes, I see!
She's something else, all right!
Yes, no doubt!
Hey, listen.
Don't you think we should let
Iceberg know what's going on?
Absolutely!
I bet the old guy's worried
himself sick about all of this!
Right!
One of us should tell him then!
Rock!
Paper!
Hey, there's no need to trouble
yourself over him, either.
If he can survive being
hit by a sea train,
then I'm sure he'll be okay.
So did you hear the news?
They're talking
about it all over.
"Tom's violent apprentice,
Cutty Flam, is dead."
He was hit by the sea train.
Iceberg, listen.
I know you can do it.
You're the first
apprentice of Tom,
the greatest shipwright
the world has ever known.
If anybody can do it, you can.
Hey, Kokoro.
One of these days
let's share a drink.
You know, when we actually
have something to drink to.
Yeah.
Tom, I won't let you down.
I'll watch over your dreams.
I'll protect everything.
Not only this town but
these blueprints, as well!
There's a visitor, sir.
He said he's a friend
from years back.
Do you know anyone
named "Cutty Flam"?
Franky?
Shall I show him in, sir?
No.
Turn him away.
You sure picked a
roundabout way of meeting me.
Mwell, maybe, but anyway,
what's up with that strange
looking body of yours?
Screw you!
The sea train mangled my body,
so in order to stay alive
I rebuilt it using
some iron scraps.
But that's not the issue!
I've heard that your
company has been contracted
to build ships for
the World Government!
I won't tolerate you doing
anything to help them!
How could you?
They took Tom away!
And the weapons that
caused the whole incident.
Have you forgotten
who made those?!
I'm sure you have plenty of
things you want to say to me,
but I have a few as well.
I still haven't forgiven you.
Four years isn't nearly
enough time for that.
I'm surprised you
even have the nerve
to show your face around
here after what happened!
What'd you say?!
The government told me
that you died in an
accident on the railway.
You never came back so
I believed it to be true.
Even if Tom forgave you,
remember this:
It doesn't mean for a
second that I'm going to.
What's with all the secrecy?
Something going on?
Hey, what're these?
The blueprints for
that old battleship?
Don't call yourself
Cutty Flam anymore.
It's only a matter of time
before the
government targets me.
Now listen carefully.
I want you to take these
and leave this island, Franky.
Why should I?
The "Cutty Flam" from
Tom's Workers is dead.
As long as you don't
use that name anymore,
then there'll be no
connection between us.
Additionally, if you
leave the island,
the whereabouts of the
blueprints will vanish.
Hey, hold on a second!
What happens if the
government comes after you
and you don't have them?!
I've said what I came to say.
What the--?
Hey, Iceberg!
We shouldn't see
each other again.
Wait! Hold on!
Listen to me.
Do you want to end up
the same way that Tom did?
Hang on to the blueprints.
If you're threatened
and your life is in danger,
just hand them over!
And if you don't wanna do that,
you can burn them
right before their eyes!
If you were me,
would you do that?
Tom had achieved so
many wonderful things.
But he gave up everything
to keep these blueprints
hidden from the world.
As long as the risk remains
that a woman named Nico Robin
can figure out how to restore
the weapon then the world
needs these blueprints
to be able to fight back!
If I continue to keep them
with me even if they
threaten my life, I won't hand
them over to the government!
Are you sure?
You know me--what if
I decide to build it?
Do you really think
that you can trust me?
I'm giving them to you.
Doesn't that answer
your question?
We never change, do we?
Every time we meet
face to face,
we yell and argue
with each other.
I won't forgive you, and you may
feel the same way about me, too.
Franky, I'm, I'm really--
I'm so glad that
you're still alive.
You listen to me!
I'm not gonna leave this island!
You got that, Ice-for-brains?!
I'm gonna do whatever
the hell I wanna do!
You think I'm gonna
do what you tell me?
I'd rather die!
Understand?!
Dammit, Flunky!
Why can't you get it through
that thick head of yours?!
This is to protect
the blueprints!
Shut it!
It's you who doesn't get it!
I'm not gonna leave this island!
No matter what!
Why the hell am I
thinking about
Ice-for-brains at a
time like this?!
Where is he?
Where the hell is Iceberg?
He's dead.
I thought I was a goner!
You almost were!
I said "If you
don't come inside,
you're gonna get blown away!"
Whew!
That speed was crazy!
Told ya!
He's right!! That was rough!!
Hurt my back.
Hold on a second.
There're a few more people
in here than there should be.
Yeah?
Who do you mean?
He means you!
I mean you, too!
I decided to
come along with you.
I tried but no matter
what I said or did,
I couldn't stop you.
And the enemy that
you'd go through all of this
to rescue your friend from
is the exact same one
that tried to kill Iceberg.
I've got a word or two of my own
I wanna say to those bastards!
Yeah!!
You're not the only one!!
We figured that if we snuck
onto the train and followed you,
we'd be right behind
you when things
went down with those
no good assassins!!
So here we are.
Seems our hunch was right.
Let us join you.
We wanna avenge Iceberg.
Sounds like we all
have a common enemy!
They're the same ones that
kidnapped our bro Franky!
Yeah, he's right!
No point in playing dumb,
we know exactly who they are!
Hey, Galley-La!
If anything happens to him,
it's gonna be on your shoulders!
Can it!
Iceberg's the one that's
endured the most here!
Hey!!
What the heck are
they talking about?!
Come on!!
There's something you're
not telling us, Paulie!!
Yeah. It's time to come clean.
Tell us everything.
We need answers.
You know who
the true culprit is.
We're not stupid, you know.
We've got a pretty
good idea who it is.
You're not gonna surprise us.
Well, I guess the story
about them disappearing
was too convenient.
Fine I'll tell you.
The true identities
of those masked men
are Lucci, Kaku, Kalifa,
and Blueno from the bar.
It was them. They're the ones
who tried to kill Iceberg.
Are you trying to tell me you
never even thought of them?!
You said they went
back to their hometowns!
Come on! You believed that?!
We... We thought it was Michael
and Hoychael from
the backstreet district!
Right!! Right!!
Who the hell are they?!
What?
You're kidding!
You've never heard of them?
They're pretty famous
in the backstreets!
Right!! Right!!
Why would half the foremen
leave in the middle of a crisis!
Didn't--
Whew! That really hit the spot!
Man, I was starving!
Right.
So even though we
got in a few fights
back in town with
both the Franky Family.
And with the
Galley-La shipwrights,
the enemy we're all going
after here is one and the same.
Now the strongest one,
the toughest out of all of them,
is definitely that pigeon guy.
He's mine.
I'm gonna beat
the crap out of him.
Luffy's right.
This is a battle to get
back what those four goons
from the World
Government took from us.
So we either reach them in time
or all of this will
be for nothing.
Granny!
Look!
It's Aqua Laguna!
Meow!
Oh?
It's here already?
Hey, let me take a look!
Oh, no!
Hey!
Shouldn't you be in the
engine room right now?
You've gotta find some way
to dodge that gigantic wave!
Rocketman can't be
controlled, remember?
We can't adjust the
speed, use the brakes,
or change our course.
My job ended as soon as
I got us up on the railway.
The train's lined up on the
tracks, running at full speed,
and there's nothing
anybody can do to stop it.
No.
Hey!
If we don't do something,
and fast this train's gonna...
Everybody on this train
has the exact same goal.
There's no point in
fighting separately.
Yeah.
He's right.
From this point forward,
we fight as one!
There are two more of
my crew on that other train.
Once we've caught up to them,
our fighting force
will be even stronger.
Listen up!
We're not gonna let
that big wave beat us!
We will achieve our goal!
Let's go!!!
Yeah!
Hey, look!
That wave is freakin' huge!
Amazing!
If we don't do something,
it's gonna swamp Rocketman!
Everybody hang on to something!
Are we gonna die?
All right, Captain.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
"Do this"?
What are you guys gonna do?
We're gonna fire a cannon!
On the next One Piece:
"Smash the Wave!
Luffy and Zoro Use
the Strongest Combo!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!