[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[SPANDAM] I admit, it was
scary for a while there,
but I finally made it.
Once I step through those gates,
I'll be the government's hero.
No, I will be a hero
to the entire world!
[FRANKY]
Lucci, huh?
He givin' you a hard
time, or something?
By the way, I brought
you two keys.
Though I guess Robin's not here.
Should I lend you a hand?
No.
Leave this guy to me.
You should go after Robin.
You can get to the
Gates of Justice
through that door
behind the pigeon guy.
Robin left a while back,
so we're running out of time.
Keep going and don't look back.
You can super
count on me, brother.
Thank you for waiting.
[KAKU]
Never mind the neck.
If I can control the
reach of all four limbs,
my blades will be unstoppable!
[KAKU] Perhaps you were so
distracted by my Giraffe Powers,
that you forgot I'm a master
of the Four Sword Style!
You've done well thus far,
but this battle is over now!
[ZORO] Even if you have
the power of a wild animal.
Even if you can attack with
that long neck of yours.
Even if you can use
the Four-Sword Style.
What?
He deflected all four blades?
None of those
things will give you
the strength it
takes to defeat me!
You're all talk.
If you think you
can take me down,
then let's see what you've got!
Three-Sword Style.
Leopard Spinning--
[KAKU]
Is he flying at me?
[ZORO]
Shot!
[KAKU]
Impossible!
I thought for sure he missed me!
[KAKU]
What was that?
[KAKU] Did he somehow predict
which way I would dodge?
Oh, come on.
Don't look so surprised.
The way you fight,
I find it hard to believe
this is the first time you've
been touched by a blade.
Well, it seems you have
a little something
to back up your boast.
I won't underestimate you again.
But I'm afraid that one hit
is the best you're going to do.
I have four swords,
Six Powers and the
immeasurable strength
of a giraffe on my side.
That's an equation for victory
if I've ever heard one.
So don't blink!
This'll be over in a flash!
Tempest Kick Shuriken!
Now, Giraffe Blast!
[ZORO]
Dammit!
My neck's like a whip. Whiplash!
Even faster! Fierce Smash!
[KAKU]
How do you like this?
Still think you can defeat me?
And now for a taste
of my Four-Sword Style.
Prepare yourself.
[KAKU]
Fury Slash!
Here I come.
[ZORO]
Damn, I can barely keep up!
[KAKU]
Hey, what's wrong?
All you're doing is
blocking! Give it up!
You don't have what
it takes to beat me!
[KAKU]
You pirates were sorely mistaken
if you thought you could defy
the World Government
and survive.
In the name of justice,
a mistake that severe can
only be punished by death!
The same goes for Nico Robin!
[ZORO]
You bastard.
[KAKU]
What the hell was that?
He looked like a demon;
a god of war, with
three faces, and six arms!
That can't be possible.
Was I seeing things?
Your mouth just
crossed the line.
Now you're gonna pay,
you arrogant freak.
Oh, did I offend you?
Well, if you're tired
of hearing me talk,
I'll just end this now
with the same move
that crippled this tower.
This will be over in an instant
when I slice you in two!
It's the end of the line!
There's nowhere to run!
This time, I'll make my attack
twice as powerful as before!
Yeah, you're right.
It is the end of the line.
For you, at least.
Demon Aura Nine-Sword
Style Asura!
It's that demon I saw before!
Is he making that illusion
with his strength of will alone?
Nice try, but you're too late!
Is it too late for me?
Or for you?
[KAKU] Unless you
somehow manage to dodge
this Tempest Kick,
then nothing has changed!
You're all talk!
Sky Slicer!
That's impossible!
He slashed it into mist!
[ZORO]
You did well.
I commend you!
Suffering is welcome
on the path to bloodshed!
[ZORO]
Asura Silver Mist!
I got a message for you,
from your other boss
over at Galley-La.
[PAULIE]
When you see 'em,
I want you to pass
on a message for me.
He said.
"You're all fired."
How could you do this?
You tricked me!
I thought you were my friends!
Paulie. I see.
Fired, huh?
Too bad. It'll be tough.
Assassination
skills don't really
come in handy in
other lines of work.
You can always get
a job at the zoo.
Nice. That's a good one.
Sorry.
[running footsteps]
Hey, Moss Head!
Did you get a key?
[ZORO]
Yeah. Just now.
Got it right here.
That's good news.
Seems like you two might have
overdone it a bit, though.
Tower isn't looking so good.
You think it's safe?
[ZORO]
Safe enough.
Who cares, anyway?
That's not important right now.
There you go.
That was the last one.
Now we have all of the keys.
Yeah.
We'd better hurry
and get them to Robin.
[ZAMBAI ]
Run! Full speed!
Don't stop!
Keep moving no matter what!
We need to save ourselves
and just trust that Bro and
the Straw Hats will be safe!
We're all gonna make it!
Gero!
[ZAMBAI]
So run for your lives!
Even if we break our legs
the Franky Family
ain't stopping!
Yeah!
[FRANK FAMILY]
Go! You can do it!
We're counting on you, giants!
[KASHII]
Listen, guys.
If you're just gonna ride,
then try to keep it down!
[OIMO]
Oi, I agree! Enough, already!
[ZAMBAI] Forward! Go,
in the name of Elbath!
[OIMO and KASHII]
Shut up!
Granny, hurry! Faster, faster!
Chimney, I'm an old woman!
Gimme a break, here!
Seriously, I'm gonna have
to refuel to keep this up!
Whoa! Granny!
He's gonna fall!
Pull him up! Pull him up!
[KOKORO]
Geez!
You sure are demanding today.
[CHIMNEY]
Granny!
[KOKORO]
I know, I know! "Hurry! Hurry!"
[SPANDAM]
Finally!
The bridge is connected!
Hahahahahaha!
I can't stop laughing!
Hey! Gate Guards!
[MARINE]
Is everything ready or what?
Yes, sir!
Everything is in order!
We're awaiting your
arrival by the third column.
That's not what I meant!
The crew should come
out to salute me!
Their hero,
Chief Spandam, has arrived!
[MARINE]
Oh, uh, yes sir!
We'll be right out!
[SPANDAM]
Idiots.
They can't do anything right!
Look, Nico Robin. There it is!
That little gate's
the real entrance.
Just a few more steps
and we're there.
Once you pass through it,
you'll be crossing the border
between heaven and hell.
There's no turning back!
And the moment
I drag you past it,
my name will be
engraved in history!
Hey-hey-hey there, witch!
Where do you think you're going?
I know you may not believe me,
but I do feel a
bit sorry for you.
Too bad I've got
no say in the matter.
There's no reason
for you to live.
Your death awaits.
You bitch!
[ROBIN]
I don't want to die!
I want to live!
[SPANDAM]
Stop delaying the inevitable!
You're wasting time! Get up!
Damn it all. She won't budge.
What's going on here?
You're kidding me!
She's holding on to
the bridge with her teeth?
She just doesn't know
when to give up, does she?
How annoying!
Why the hell are you
so desperate to live?
Don't be so damn greedy!
Listen to me!
You're a criminal, understand?
The only way you can make
the world a better
place is by dying!
Why must you be
such an annoyance
all the way to the bitter end?
[ROBIN] I never thought
I would be so afraid of death.
I want to live! Please! Save me!
Luffy!
Finger Pistol!
I told you, that won't work!
[LUCCI]
Yellow Lotus!
[FRANKY]
Straw Hat!
No. Wait.
I can't worry about him.
My only concern
is getting through
those doors, and fast!
It's no use.
There's no way you'll
ever get past me.
We'll just have to see
about that, won't we?
Have some Strong--
Iron Body.
Hammer!
No way.
He didn't even flinch!
That same punch sent that
"Chapapa" freak flying!
Ah, I see.
You beat Fukurou along the way?
Sorry to break it to you,
but my power level
is five times his.
Still, I'm impressed you
defeated Fukurou.
Bringing down any agent of CP9
requires super-human strength.
[FRANKY]
Whoa.
This guy's in a completely
different league!
Now. You die.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
What the hell? What happened?
And what's with all that steam?
[LUFFY]
Second Gear.
I can't keep my
body like this for long.
But I'll damn sure stop him,
so you go on ahead, and hurry!
Robin's waiting!
Right! You got it!
I have no idea
what you're doing,
but keep it up and finish him!
[LUCCI]
I said you'll never get past me.
Didn't I?
Another guy with
Devil Fruit Powers?
[LUCCI]
First thing's first.
Time to die, Franky.
Jet Whip!
[LUCCI]
Have you forgotten something?
Back in the Galley-La building,
this is the form I was in
when I defeated
you with a single blow.
Yeah. Sure.
But I was real hungry that day.
[LUCCI]
Shave! Finger Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Jet Bazooka!
Franky! You gotta save her!
Just super leave it to me!
[SPANDAM]
Stupid woman!
Don't you get it?
This is useless!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
There's no hope for you
so just give it up now!
[ROBIN]
I'm not going anywhere!
They're coming!
They're all coming to rescue me!
[SPANDAM] Ahahahaha!
Watch carefully, men,
because you're about
to witness the first step
of a hero that is destined
to go down in history!
[MARINE]
Chief!
[SPANDAM]
Over there!
[MARINE]
What?
[SPANDAM]
Over where?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Spandam Frightened!
The Hero on the Tower of Law."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!