[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other instead.
To end the chaos, Luffy and
his crew make their way
towards the green
city of Erumalu
and head for the Yuba oasis,
home of the desert insurgents.
[LUFFY] "Rebel Warrior Koza!
The Dream Vowed to Vivi!"
[USOPP]
Gah!
What are you doing?!
Ah!
Stop spilling all
the water! You slob!
What's the big deal?
Ace brought plenty of
water for everybody.
Well, we still gotta
conserve all our supplies!
Stop hogging all the
water for yourself!
Why's it okay if Sanji does?
This is for Nami, so if she
gets thirsty or dehydrated
and cries out for water,
I'll be there to rescue her!
Nami, Vivi!
You care for some refreshment?
Hey, gimme me some!
No thank you.
[USOPP]
Come on now.
You're spilling it
all over the place.
Hey. You want some water?
No thank you. I'll be just fine.
[ALL shouting]
Hey, Vivi.
Can you tell me some more
about this rebel army?
Yes, I probably should fill
you in before we get there.
[LUFFY, SANJI, USOPP shouting]
It started 11 years ago.
[KOZA]
See ya, Vivi!
I hope you grow up to
become a great princess!
[KOZA]
We‐We need help!
Our village has dried up!
How can you sit there
and do nothing?!
Weather is beyond
my control as king.
I cannot command nature.
It is beyond any man's power.
There's nothing I can do.
[KOZA] My dad always told me
the king's power is limitless‐‐
he can do anything he wishes!
My abilities exist only
in the realm of men.
I'm not some kind of god‐‐
[MESSENGER]
Your Highness!
This boy's father's
come to the palace!
[TOTO] My deepest apologizes,
Your Majesty! It's my fault.
Forgive my stupid son, Sire!
Place the punishment
for his actions on me!
I'll accept any penalties!
It's my fault!
Please, I beg of you!
What were you thinking?
How dare you!
You're stupid, insolent,
thoughtless...
An idiot!
Your name is Toto, is it not?
Yes!
[COBRA] I will officially grant
temporary sanctuary
to any villagers who are
suffering due to the crisis
caused by this drought.
You're welcome to live here.
Alubarna is a fine place for
you to plan for your future.
[TOTO] Oh, we appreciate
your benevolence, King!
Thank you, Sire!
Whatever! I don't wanna
live in this stupid capital!
Is that the best you
can do for us?!
[TOTO]
Wait, Koza! Get back here!
Mr. Toto.
[TOTO]
Yes, Sire! As you say!
[COBRA]
Your son's comments
represent the people's
frustrations.
He's a good boy.
He cares for those who suffer.
That is why he is
acting in such a way.
Hey there, crybaby.
What did you say to me, midget?
Midget?
[IGARAM]
King Cobra.
Igaram, what's the matter?
[IGARAM]
With all due respect,
it's unrealistic to think
we can support them all,
not without exhausting
our funds, Sire.
[COBRA]
You fool!
We will bear the burden of
this crisis with our people.
Their pleas will not be ignored.
I understand. As you wish.
[MESSENGER]
It's terrible.
Your Majesty!
It's Princess Vivi!
I fought with that boy,
and got beaten.
‐‐Vivi!
‐‐Ah! Princess Vivi!
How dare a commoner
lay even a finger
on a member of this
esteemed house.
That boy's dead!
No! Wait! Igaram,
you must calm down!
[TOTO] Your Majesty,
my deepest apologies!
Please, Sire, kill me instead!
[COBRA]
You're both idiots!
You fools. It was a
children's quarrel!
Hey, you, come!
Fresh fruit, cheap!
Vases. Cheap vases! We got...
Here you go, kiddo.
Here's that camel's
hump kabob you wanted.
[KIDS laughing]
Fruit on sale!
[RUNNING BOY]
Fight! Fight!
[KIDS shouting]
Teach that snotty princess
a lesson! Take her down!
[KID C, KID D]
Go, Vivi! Beat him.
Shut up, traitors!
Don't ya know we're supposed
to cheer for Koza?!
I become your leader when I
beat you, that's the deal!
[KOZA] I'd never lose
a fight to you, midget!
I've never lost a fight.
Especially to a dumb girl!
Is that right?
[KIDS yelling]
[KID A, KID B]
You can do it, Koza! Fight!
[KID C, KID D]
Go, Princess, go!!
All right, you guys, listen up!
As of today, Princess
Vivi will be vice‐leader
of the Sand‐Sand Clan!
Does anyone have a
problem with that?!
[KIDS]
No!
[COBRA]
Look, Igaram.
Vivi has made some new friends.
Yes, Sire.
That is the most
important thing to have
if she's to rule
Alabasta in my stead.
The people must follow her.
[chuckles]
[VIVI]
Toto! Ma'am!
Good morning! Where's Leader?
Oh, good morning!
If you're looking for
Koza, he already left.
I assume he's at the usual spot.
See ya later!
Hey, Vivi! You coming for lunch?
Yes, please!
Thank you very much!
What a strange
country we live in.
The princess mingling
with commoners like us,
who would've ever thought?
A sign of peaceful times.
[TOTO]
And will you be joining us?
No, no, that's quite all right.
I packed a lunch today. Bye!
[COBRA]
Shh!
Your Majesty! What are
you doing here?!
Cobra! My lord! Ugh...
I asked you not to
follow me again.
Yeah, it's just,
I wanted to make sure my
precious daughter's okay.
[growls]
Go home, Sire!
I can't babysit you
and Princess Vivi, too!
What?!
Go home! You heard me!
What a sweet story, Vivi.
[USOPP]
Luffy, stop it!
You gimme that water
back right this minute!
Just wait. I haven't gotten
to the best part yet.
[BAD GUYS laughing]
Hello, Princess!
You lost, little girl?
We'll help you out.
Protect her, Sand‐Sand Clan!
[KIDS yelling]
[BAD GUY A] What the hell's
wrong with these kids?!
They won't give up!
Leader! Guys!
Vivi! Get going!
We're trying to hold these
guys off for you! Go!
Vivi, get outta here right now!
Yeah, you gotta run, now!
I can't... Leader!
[BAD GUY A laughs]
We're not here to kill you.
We just wanna kidnap you for
a ransom from your father,
but these other kids...
Damn!
Okay. Now just come with
us quietly, Princess Vivi.
[BOTH laugh]
[KOZA]
Step back!
Protect her to the death,
Sand‐Sand Clan!
[KIDS yelling]
Ah! What the heck is that?!
It looks like a tail!
Hello there. Don't be
shy. Come on... out!
[USOPP screams]
It's huge!
[USOPP screaming]
Vivi, please continue
telling the story.
I'm getting hooked on your
adventures with Koza.
All right.
See, Koza had a strong heart
that burned as
bright as the sun.
But I worried that
his compassion
would one day be
used against him.
[KOZA]
Don't give up!
We're not beat yet.
Keep fighting!
[KIDS shouting]
[VIVI gasps]
[BAD GUY C laughs]
Stupid kids. Lookie here.
Oh, crap! Another one?!
[BAD GUY C screams]
Ah! Damn it! She's getting away!
Well, lookie there!
She's in the ruins!
Let's get 'em!
[KIDS yelling]
Move it!
What happened?
[KIDS groaning]
Hey. Boy, what happened to you?
Hey, kid. Where's princess Vivi?
Vivi got kidnapped by three men.
Oh, no!
Bad guys. Went in the old ruins.
Koza followed them in there.
He's trying to save
the vice‐leader.
Oh, yeah?
[BAD GUY B]
Oh, Princess!
Where did you go, little girl?!
Let's play a game.
[BAD GUY C] Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
[BAD GUY B] Yeah! Come out,
come out wherever you are.
Little Vivi!
You can stop hiding!
We aren't gonna hurt you!
Found ya, little princess!
There you are, girl.
Don't go and run off
again on me now!
[KOZA]
Gotcha!
[gasps] Leader!
Vivi, are you okay?!
[VIVI]
Yes. I'm fine. Just‐‐
Stay down, punk, unless
you want another beating!
I'll never surrender the
princess, you got that?!
Hey, kid, shut your damn mouth
and hand over my meal ticket.
I'm done playing games
with you little brats.
[VIVI]
It's a sword.
Let's run! Koza!
Don't worry, Princess,
he's harmless.
Huh?!
[KOZA] Protect her to the
death, Sand‐Sand Clan!
Leader! Please stop it!
I'm warning you.
[BAD GUY A laughing]
[screams]
[yells]
[laughs]
[groaning]
[VIVI]
Leader!
[BAD GUY B]
No way.
That damn little kid managed
to knock out our boss!
How dare he.
It's time to make
that little brat pay.
You. You're dead, boy!
[COBRA, IGARAM yell]
[COBRA]
Take that, bastards!
Papa! Igaram!
‐‐Princess Vivi! Are you okay?
‐‐How dare you punks!
You desert garbage dare
to kidnap my daughter?
You dirty swine!
[CHAKA] We took care
of the others, Sire.
Chaka! Pell? My friends,
why are you two here?
[CHAKA]
That's funny.
We were going to ask
you the same question.
[PELL] What would drive a king
to travel so far from home?
These areas are a haven
for many bandits.
It's not a place for royalty.
Igaram! Koza's hurt!
Yes. He needs immediate
medical attention.
The others are also
in dire need.
Pell! Chaka!
Arrange help at once!
[CHAKA, PELL]
Sir!
You children acted very brave.
[COBRA]
What's wrong, Vivi?
Why are you so distant, child?
[VIVI]
I was... just so scared.
[KOZA]
I was scared too.
They were so much bigger
and stronger than us,
and armed to the teeth.
[VIVI]
It's not that...
It's just...
Leader, you told them to
protect me... to the death.
Protect her to the death,
Sand‐Sand Clan.
Don't give your life
to save mine, Leader.
[IGARAM]
Poor Vivi.
Her greatest fear is
losing her friends.
[COBRA] Vivi may be a little
girl, but she's also a princess.
Koza, the full measure
of gratitude I owe you
cannot be expressed,
so I will simply say...
Thank you.
But Vivi is one of my friends.
I would do that for all of them.
I see.
Then I'm certain the next
generation of Alabasta's people
will be in good hands.
Do you love this country?
Yes. This is my home!
Mine as well!
[IGARAM]
Excuse me.
Ma, ma, maaa!
There is an important matter
that concerns me greatly.
[COBRA]
What's that?
[IGARAM] Those who are to lead
their countrymen must be able
to make life and death
decisions without hesitation.
Vivi is far too tenderhearted
for such crushing
responsibility.
Sir Igaram.
Sire?
Just relax.
Because as I see it,
Alabasta is safe.
[IGARAM] Your Majesty,
it is my greatest desire
to serve you until my death.
Yuba?
Exactly!
And that news comes directly
from your dad to mine
so you know it's true.
Oh, wow! That's great!
Your dad asked mine
to start a town.
He said it would be built
at the Yuba Oasis!
That's considered the
crossroads of Alabasta,
where every merchant and
traveler must pass through.
It's the perfect location!
You just wait
until it's finished.
This town will bring
good fortune and joy
to so many people.
Amazing!
And that's not even
the best part!
My dad is going to be the
mayor of the whole thing!
You're going too, Koza?
Of course!
But my dad wants me to
stay here in the capital.
He says life will be too hard.
But I just gotta be where all
the action is! And live it!
I wanna help build the city
with my own two hands.
Alabasta will need the
city of Yuba to survive.
We're counting on you, Toto.
Yes, yes, Your Majesty!
We'll make Yuba a great
city for Alabasta.
So long, my princess.
We won't see you for a while.
As soon as Yuba's up and
running, stop by, Princess.
Yes. Of course I will.
It's gonna be the
best town ever!
When it's up and running,
I'll personally give
ya the grand tour!
[CARAVAN LEADER]
Let's move out!
See ya, Vivi!
I hope ya grow up to
become a great princess!
Okay!
[TOTO]
Koza, stop being so arrogant.
[KOZA]
Oww!
Koza is correct about Yuba.
This new city will bring great
prosperity to the kingdom.
So, Koza went with his father
to found the city of Yuba.
Does this have something
to do with the rebel army?
Uh‐huh. That's right.
We're heading toward
the oasis of Yuba.
That's where the
rebel army is stationed.
The leader of the rebel
insurgents is named...
...Koza.
So that means‐‐!
[VIVI]
Mh‐hm.
It's the same boy
from the story.
Nami, look! I managed to
save you the best part!
[NAMI, VIVI scream]
This desert shrimp is so good!
It's not shrimp!
It's a scorpion!
[LUFFY]
Ugh... I'm so full.
You guys are a buncha
inconsiderate jerks!
Let's go, Eyelash!
Whoa. Why is she so angry?
[USOPP, ZORO, CHOPPER]
Uhhh... Uhh‐uh.
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[USOPP] Ace doesn't seem like
the wanted criminal type, huh?
[NAMI] Yet, every single
pirate the world over
fears the name "Fire Fist Ace."
[VIVI] Ace is chasing some
pirate named Blackbeard!
I wonder what he's like.
[SANJI] I heard that only one
person has defeated Blackbeard.
[ZORO] Yeah, Scorpion.
He's a bounty hunter.
[CHOPPER] Wow, Scorpion
must be really strong!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Showdown in a Heat Haze!
Ace vs. the Gallant Scorpion."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!