[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
The sea!
[ZORO] Usopp?
[USOPP] We're gonna be saved!
She came to rescue us!
Jump! It'll be okay!
We've still got
one more friend here!
Chopper! Did you see?
Yes!
Now. Cien Fleurs!
[ROBIN] Delphinium!
[LUFFY] I'm moving!
Is Robin doing this?
To the sea!
[USOPP]
Jump! Follow Luffy!
[NAMI, SANJI] Go!
[ZORO, CHOPPER, FRANKY]
Go!
[KOKORO, CHIMNEY, ROBIN]
To the sea!
All of the pirates
are jumping into the sea!
Ha!
There's no way
that they'll survive.
Those idiots are done for!
[MERRY]
Let's go back, everyone!
[MARINE 310T] Fire!
[MERRY] Back to
the seas of adventure!
[USOPP] Everyone!
Get onboard the Merry!
Merry!
[LUFFY]
Everyone Makes a Great Escape!
The Road to Victory
is for the Pirates!
[MARINE 311A]
What are they thinking?
If they jump in the ocean,
they're just gonna drown!
And they have
Devil Fruit users
with them, as well.
It's suicide!
Hold on.
Look at that!
Is that their ship?
[MARINE 311B]
It's gotta be!
See? It even has
Straw Hat's pirate flag on it!
[MARINE 311C]
How the hell did it sneak past
all our battleships?
I dunno who you are, pal,
but I sure owe you one.
This is weird.
What's going on, Sanji?
Something wrong?
Not wrong, just strange.
The rope ladder
got dropped down,
but it doesn't look
like anyone's here.
[NAMI] What?
[CHIMNEY] Yay!
[GONBE] Meow!
[USOPP] Merry!
[FRANKY] Seriously, can't
you swim on your own, brother?
Alrighty, up you go!
Hope you enjoyed the ride!
[SANJI]
Robin! Yoohoo!
Leap into my arms, darling!
Over here!
We're on the Merry!
We're back on the Merry!
I love you, Merry!
I love you so much!
Thank you!
[USOPP] Merry...
My sweet Merry is still alive!
[USOPP] I don't understand!
How did she make it here? How?
[CHOPPER] I wish--
I wish I could give
you a hug, Merry,
but I can't move!
This doesn't make sense.
I saw this ship
drop into the ocean myself!
The question is,
who sailed it here?
We'll figure it out later.
Just get us out of here.
Right. Let me think.
[ZORO] Everyone ready?
[NAMI] Sanji, get up!
What're you doing?
[SANJI] Whatever you
want me to do, Nami sweet!
That was a close one!
I thought those battleships
were gonna blow me up for sure!
[LUFFY] Hey, Robin!
You saved me! Thanks a--
From now on,
leave everything to us!
[ROBIN]
Luffy, everyone, thank you.
Sure.
[GONBE] Meow! Meow!
Don't worry 'bout it.
That's nice,
but save the sappy stuff
til after we escape, okay?
[SANJI] You take that back,
you heartless bastard!
[CHOPPER] Yeah, you bastard!
[ZORO] If we sit around, we're
just gonna end up dead, stupid!
[SANJI] I don't care!
Apologize to Robin!
[CHOPPER] Yeah!
That's enough--
Both of you, stop!
Hey, wait.
Chopper! You're moving again.
Now that you mention it,
I guess I am moving!
I was afraid
I'd never get better!
Now apologize to Robin already!
Give up yet?
[ZORO] No! Never!
Okay! Let's go!
You guys ready to move?
[ALL] Yeah!
[SPANDAM] Pull it
together, you idiots!
Are you gonna just stand
there and let them get away?
If they're gonna
escape anyway,
we might as well
blow up Nico Robin, too!
But--But we're supposed to
capture her alive, sir!
[SPANDAM] Tragic, I know,
but that's what
Aokiji said to do.
Now all ships prepare to fire!
Admiral Aokiji said that?
All right, men! Take aim!
[MARINE 311D]
All ships, prepare to fire!
Repeat, prepare to fire!
[SPANDAM] Okay, so I lied,
but that's better than
letting them get away!
I'll make them pay
for what they've done!
[SPANDAM] Can't you load
those cannonballs any faster?
Do you want them to get away?
[FRANKY] So Spandam's
still alive, huh?
That sucks.
[USOPP] They're gonna fire!
[NAMI] Catch the wind
from starboard and head east!
[ZORO] We can't!
We're completely surrounded!
[USOPP]
All those big, scary cannons
and they're
aimed straight at us!
At this range,
with that many ships,
there's no way
they're gonna miss.
[MARINE 311D] Fire!
[USOPP screaming]
[USOPP] Help!
[USOPP] Wait, are they
firing at each other?
Their aim can't be that bad.
[DOBERMAN] What was that?
Where the hell are you aiming?
Something's wrong!
It's like the cannons
just did that on their own!
Don't make such stupid excuses!
[MARINE 311E]
Change course!
[MARINE 311F]
We can't! It's too late!
[yelling]
[MARINE 311G]
They're coming straight at us!
We're gonna crash!
[panicked yelling]
This is madness!
What the hell is going on here?
Look over there, sir!
[MARINE 311H]
The Gates of Justice
are closing for some reason!
[MARINE 311I] The gate can't
block the current anymore!
With these whirlpools around,
we won't be able
to control the rudder!
[MARINE 311H] So that's
why our aim was so bad.
[CAPTAIN 311A]
Don't get sucked in!
Ugh, this day keeps
going from bad to worse!
[MARINE 311J]
Put out the fire! Quick!
[MARINE 311K]
We're gonna have to jump ship!
We're finished!
Those damn fools!
Why did they close the gate?
Hurry the hell up
and open it again!
[MARINE 311H]
We can't, sir.
The operation lever is
on the Bridge of Hesitation.
It wasn't our fault!
[SANJI] That turned out
better than I thought!
Sanji!
Is that what you did
while you were gone?
[SANJI] Mm-hmm.
I figured it'd take
more than just guts
to get out of here alive.
Bingo!
You're like
my hero forever, Sanji!
Are you a genius or what?
It's a little early
to be kissing his ass.
These whirlpools
are a problem for us, too!
[USOPP] Oh great,
thanks a lot, Sanji!
Would you shut up?
It's not a problem.
[NAMI] As long
as we're together,
there's no sea that the
Going Merry can't cross, right?
[SANJI] You're so cool, Nami!
[USOPP] That's right!
Go for it, Navigator!
[NAMI] Just hold them off
while I find a path for us!
[CHOPPER, USOPP, SANJI, ZORO]
No problem!
[ZORO] One-Sword Style...
...Thirty-six Caliber Phoenix!
Since I lost a sword,
I can't do a full 108 Phoenix.
Why don't you
go cry about it?
--I'm gonna make you cry!
--Hey guys,
here they come again!
[SANJI] Collier Shoot!
[ROBIN]
Cien Fleurs! Defense!
[FRANKY] We don't want 'em!
Take 'em back!
It's my turn!
Triple... Flame... Stars!
I sure hope the guys
are okay up there.
Me, too.
Meow!
[NAMI] It's fine, Chopper.
After all we've been through,
they won't lose now.
Just focus on
steering the ship, okay?
Uh, right.
Yah!
[SPANDAM] Damn it!
Why do you idiots keep missing?
It's right there!
We've got like a million cannons
firing at that stupid thing!
It's just one little ship!
[ZORO]
They're coming your way, Usopp!
[USOPP] I got it!
No, wait, I missed one!
Sanji, help!
[SANJI] Basses Côte!
Ah, guys!
Save some for me!
I wanna fight 'em, too!
Oh really?
Are you gonna
squirm them to death?
[SANJI] Hate to break
it to you Captain,
but I think this one
is our battle.
Take a nap!
We'll be done soon!
[LUFFY] You go take a nap!
I'm gonna beat
these guys, you'll see!
I just gotta get there!
I'll give a medal to
anyone who can hit them!
One shot is all it takes!
All ships, concentrate
attacks on their back deck!
Damn it, Luffy,
get out of the way!
[CAPTAIN 311D] Fire!
Shut up, Zoro!
You can't tell me what to do!
You ready?
Let's go!
[MARINE 311L] Uh-oh!
I think they're coming back!
You never let us down,
huh Captain?
I guess we needed you after all!
You people are monsters!
Uh-huh!
[NAMI] I've got it.
The path to victory!
[NAMI]
Chopper, helm hard to port!
9 o'clock!
[CHOPPER] All right, you got it!
[MARINE 311M] They're pulling
towards the waterfall!
What should we do?
[SPANDAM] Just shoot them!
What the hell do you think?
How hard can it be?
Sink that damn ship!
[MARINE 311M]
They're riding the current
of the whirlpool!
It's no use!
We can't keep up!
All right!
I get to be useful, too!
You can do it,
reindeer dude!
Meow!
Let's go!
Full speed ahead!
[SPANDAM] Damn it!
Damn it! Those bastards!
[SPANDAM] I have the
power of Enies Lobby--
The power of CP9!
[SPANDAM] I even had the
power of a Buster Call!
They practically burned
the whole island down!
And yet,
even after all that,
even after all I've done,
I can't take a single woman away
from a tiny band of riffraff!
It's not fair!
[SPANDAM muffled screaming]
[CAPTAIN 311E] Chief Spandam!
[SPANDAM] You get to play a part
in the rebirth of this world!
Isn't that enough for you,
you insolent witch?
[SPANDAM] There's no hope for
you, so just give it up now!
[SPANDAM]
Sad enough to make you cry, huh?
[laughing]
[SPANDAM] Help me!
Please, someone help me!
[ROBIN] Clutch!
Hey! Chief Spandam!
Are you okay?
[CHIMNEY]
Yeah! Go!
--Yeah! Go!
--Well...
--I guess that settles that.
All right, Franky.
It's time to do your thing!
[FRANKY] You got it!
Get ready kids,
'cause this is gonna be wild.
[CAPTAIN 311F]
Block their path!
Don't let them get
out of the whirlpools!
Just so you know,
this might bang up
your ship a bit.
Sorry 'bout that.
Coup de Vent!
Wait, what?
The pirate ship is flying?
[MARINE 311N] How are
we supposed to top that?
[MARINE 311O] Our cannons
can't reach that high!
If you think the Merry's
an ordinary ship,
then you're wrong!
She's flown through the air once
and she can do it
again no problem!
Special attack--
Super Smoke Star!
[MARINE 311O]
It's a smokescreen!
[USOPP laughing]
Damn pirates!
Go! Don't let them get away!
We can't, sir!
It's taking all we've got
just to stay afloat!
We gotta get out
of this whirlpool first!
Maintain fire! Don't stop!
[ZORO] Hmph.
[ZAMBAI] Looks like the
Straw Hats are safe and sound!
Good!
Now let's get
the hell outta here!
All of your men
are onboard, right?
Of course!
We packed the injured
people into the cars,
so they're nice
and snug right now!
Okay!
It's gonna be a rough ride for
you folks outside the train,
so you better hang on tight!
It's all over.
We're still alive.
Yeah.
We survived the Buster Call.
It's strange,
watching their island burn
from the fire
of their own ships.
[LULU] But now that
Enies Lobby is gone,
maybe the Govnerment won't get
in our business quite as much.
That should be good for Iceberg.
[TILESTONE] I hope you're right.
[PAULIE]
Hey! Hey! Stay out!
Get away from me!
We never would've made it
without your ropes!
I didn't know you were
such a hero, Paulie!
If there's anything
we can do to repay you,
just say it, okay?
Yeah?
You can start by getting
your hands offa me!
He's so innocent!
Isn't it the cutest thing?
It just makes
you wanna cuddle him!
That's enough, you perverts!
[KIWI] Aw, are you
having a hard time?
[MOZU] You poor thing!
We'll take care of you!
[PAULIE] I'm beggin you,
please, have mercy!
[cheering]
[ZAMBAI] Let's go, Puffing Tom!
We're heading home!
[DOBERMAN] I didn't
realize you were here, sir.
We haven't given up
the chase yet.
[DOBERMAN] I swear
it won't end like this!
[MOMONGA] We must maintain
our dignity as the Navy--
No, as the World Government!
[STRAWBERRY] We'll bring down
the Straw Hats at any cost!
Nico Robin is in
the palm of our hand.
We can't let her escape
again after all we've done!
[ONIGUMO] Admiral, allow us
to call in reinforcements
and we'll overtake them
as quickly as possible!
[AOKIJI] Don't bother.
[ONIGUMO]
But sir--
The force that we command
with a Buster Call
is as powerful as an
entire nation's military.
And yet, look at
the state of our fleet.
Look at Enies Lobby,
burning to the ground.
The situation
is obvious, isn't it?
The day is lost, men.
We've been utterly defeated.
[KOKORO] You sure you wanna sit
up on top of that sheep head?
[LUFFY] Of course I do.
That's the Captain's seat.
[KOKORO] Well, there you go.
Careful not to fall.
[KOKORO laughs]
Sure.
Thanks for the help, Monster
Granny, you're the best.
And thank you, Merry.
We never would've
made it if you weren't there.
[LUFFY] I was pretty
surprised when you showed up,
but when I think about it,
you've always been
there to protect us.
We've always counted on you.
Anyway, I'm just
happy you've been
part of the team, Merry.
You're a good friend to have.
[FRANKY] I don't
mean to spoil the mood,
but damn, you guys did
some crazy stuff back there.
[FRANKY] I don't
think the government's
gonna let you off that easy
after you burned
down their flag.
[LUFFY] Eh, whatever.
It doesn't feel
like a big deal to me.
The only reason
I did any of that
was 'cause they took our
friend and I wanted her back.
And we couldn't
have done what we did
without your help,
so thanks a lot.
Well, like you said, it
wasn't really that big o' deal.
I just did what I had to do.
[LUFFY] The point is
we're all together,
we're coming back in one piece,
and this fight was our victory!
[ALL] Yeah!
[LUFFY] Merry.
Merry.
Merry!
Your name is the Going Merry,
and you're one of us,
once and for all!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Thank You, Merry!
Snow Falls over the Parting Sea.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!