Armée de l'Air
Power Shoot!
[STRAW HAT PIRATES]
All right!
[PORCHE]
No way!
AAAAHHH!!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Goal! Goal! Goal!
Our new champions are
the Straw Hat Pirates!
Shelly!
Huh?
Hahahaha...
[ITOMIMIZU]
What a turn of events!
The captain of the Straw
Hats has chosen Shelly,
a horse that Captain Foxy
picked up on a whim
after coming to this island!
Is this pure genius
or just plain idiocy?!
[LUFFY]
There you go, Stilts Guy.
Now you have your horse
back once and for all.
[TONJIT]
How can I thank you?
[LUFFY] Seeing you
together is thanks enough.
This means so much.
Really, thank you.
[sighs]
Well, I guess
I can't blame him.
Yeah. That's totally
what I would've done.
[laughs]
Good girl!
[LUFFY]
I know you can take it.
After all, you're
a man, right?
You bet I am!
[chuckle]
That's our Chopper.
Leave it to me little
pal. You'll be just fine.
If you're Chopper's
last hope. He's screwed.
Eh-heh!
I wonder what the
next game is going to be.
Hmph! Whatever it is,
I'm ready for it.
[chuckles]
We're gonna have Chopper
back on the crew in no time!
[sounds of construction]
[concerned neighing]
Shelly don't worry, girl,
our friends will be just fine.
All we can do is cheer them on.
Two fried squids and
a sausage on a stick.
You got it!
[CARPENTER A]
We're still missing
six support pillars over here!
[CARPENTER B]
Hurry it up!
[CARPENTER C]
Hey!
Where'd you
guys put my tools?!
This next game sounds
like fun, don't you think?
[NAMI] Fun? That's
kind of insensitive.
Put yourself in Chopper's
shoes for a second.
Poor little guy.
I didn't think of
that. My apologies.
Well, no big deal.
It's these idiots that could
use some sensitivity training.
Aaaaahh!
Hello! You're
both so lovely!
You two ready
for the match?
What're you
eating now, Luffy?
It's a long kiwi.
That old horse
guy gave it to me.
Actually tastes
pretty good!
[LUFFY]
You can't have it.
I don't want it!
Mellorine!
[ITOMIMIZU] It's
time for Round 3,
the "Run Roller Round"
roller skating race!
Say that three times fast!
At any rate, it's a
head-to-head race
on an outdoor track.
As always, the rules are simple!
At the sound of
the first whistle,
each team's point
getter will start skating
around the track.
20 seconds later,
the second whistle will blow
and the team defenders
will follow suit.
The defenders can try to
hinder the opposing team
or support their point
getter. Anything goes!
Assuming that the point getters
aren't injured or disqualified,
the race will continue
for five minutes.
At the end of that time,
the team whose point
getter is in the lead wins
so as little as an inch
can mean victory or defeat!
Naturally, yours truly
will be providing
the play-by-play from my
special "birds nest view"
right next to
the starting line.
Now, it's time for
our two talented teams
to take to the track!
All right guys, no
matter how bad they cheat,
we gotta get Chopper
back this time! You ready?
[STRAW HAT PIRATES]
Yeah!
[ITOMIMIZU] And here
come the Straw Hat Dangers
making a grand entrance
with a roaring battle cry!
Feh-feh-feh!
And on this end, their
all-powerful opponents,
the indomitable Foxy Devils!
First up is the
team's playmaker, Porche!
Next is the stunningly
speedy Chiqicheetah,
the defensive dynamo Masshikaku,
the fighting fishman
Jube, and Girarin!
Oh, and last but not least,
we have Foxy as
the head coach
and Hamburg as
the team manager!
That's a mighty lineup
if I've ever seen one!
[sniff, sniff]
Hey, what're you doing?
Whoa! What is
Chiqicheetah up to?
Is he intimidating Luffy
before the start of the match?!
What's with this weirdo?
He's kinda creepin' me out.
Feh-feh-feh-feh!
His feet are indeed
a thing of wonder,
but his nose is
impressive too!
You ate something
pungent, didn't you?
Huh?
Haha! Uh-oh Luffy,
looks like he's onto you!
That's what you get for
eating that old man's cheese!
[LUFFY]
Oh! Is that why?
That was a joke!
Jeez, learn some
manners, will ya?
Shoo shoo!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Eh.. Ha ha... Wow...
Okay, I don't know
what that was about...
But anyway, now
that that's done with,
let's get back to the rules!
In addition to the
defenders and point getters,
each team also has a
coach and a manager
but unlike the
other players,
they're limited
to the sidelines.
The teams must change
point getters every round,
and each player can
only be point getter once!
But wait!
Since the manager
and coach can't play,
that means you need
at least seven members
which makes the
Straw Hats one man short!
Whatever shall they do?!
That's a shame!
But hey, since I'm
such a generous guy,
I'll let one of you sorry
saps be the point getter twice.
If your pride will
allow it, of course.
Feh-feh-feh-feh...!
I've had about
enough of that laugh.
[PIRATE VOICE A] We love
you, Boss! You're the best!
[PIRATE VOICE B]
So kind!
Your generosity has
moved me to tears!
[PIRATE VOICE C]
You're a real man!
Aw! Feh-feh-feh! You guys!
[NAMI]
Can you believe this guy?
He's actually taking
this crap seriously.
[USOPP] Anything to
feed his ego, right?
[SANJI]
We gotta hurry up
and put this guy
out of his misery.
Oh no! Don't sink,
boss! We need you!
Puh-puh-puh...!
But annoying as he is,
we kinda have to take
him up on his offer, right?
Hey, as long as it
helps us beat him faster,
I'm not complaining!
We're fighting
for Chopper's sake.
This is no time to
get hung up on pride.
Hmm?
Huh?
You're on, Split Head.
We've got ourselves a
match now! Get ready!
Ha! You're too naïve, boy.
Do you want to know
why I made you an offer
that puts me at a
disadvantage? Simple.
'Cause we're awesome.
[LUFFY] All right!
Let's get Chopper back!
Yeah!
[PORCHE]
Boss, no!
[ITOMIMIZU]
And there you have it.
Both captains have
agreed to amend the rules!
Now, as soon as
the Straw Hat Dangers
select a point getter for
each round we can begin!
Hhhh... All right, Since
we've got five rounds,
our best bet is to put
our strongest scorers
in rounds 1, 3, and 5.
Question is, who do we
want to start out with?
Put me in two rounds,
okay? Please? Please?
I'll think about it,
if you shut up and
leave me alone for a sec.
Since he's so full of energy,
I'll put Luffy as point
getter in round one,
then again in round five.
Yeah!
I probably shouldn't expect
much from Nami and Usopp.
Hey, Robin?
Looks like it's best
to put you in Round 3.
That okay?
Sure. You seem to understand
this better than anyone else.
Thank you.
Ah, but wait what if the
other team has the same idea?
[thinking]
Okay, new plan.
[LUFFY]
Okay, come on! Hurry up!
All right, I'm done!
Luffy has rounds 1 and 5.
Nami has 2. Usopp has 3
and Robin has been moved to 4.
Hey, hold on a sec.
Why do you get to make
all these big decisions
without asking me?
Huh? 'Cause the coach
makes all the decisions,
not the manager.
And I'm the coach.
And why do you get to
have the awesome job,
while I get stuck following
your stupid orders?!
Obviously because I'm a genius
and your brain is so rotten
you're growing
mold on your head.
If you think you're a genius,
then your ego is as
twisted as your eyebrows.
What?!
By the way,
there's one more
very important rule
we need to go over.
[NAMI]
Knock it off! I can't hear him!
[ITOMIMIZU] If any of
the racers go in reverse,
or leave the course
for whatever reason,
they will be immediately
disqualified from the game.
Starting before the whistle
means disqualification, as well!
Okay, looks like
everything is finally set!
In the first round...
Oh! Coming on
strong from the start!
It's Straw Hat Luffy
versus our very own Porche!
The anticipation is killing me.
So without further ado,
let's get this thing started!
[PIRATE VOICE D]
Man, talk about exciting!
[PIRATE VOICE E]
No kidding!
This is my favorite event!
[PIRATE VOICE C]
Yeah, mine too!
Go Porche!
Beat that rubber
dude senseless!
Hahaha! Hey, look!
[gasp]
You're kidding me.
No way.
Whoa, this
is kinda hard.
Please, somebody tell
me I'm seeing things!
No, don't make me look!
I'm scared! Make it go away!
[CROWD jeers]
[ITOMIMIZU]
Now this is unexpected!
Straw Hat doesn't
know how to skate!
And according to the roster,
he's scheduled to play
point getter in two rounds!
Is the game over
before it's even started?
Feh-feh-feh!
You can race as many
times as you like, kid!
Now what're we gonna do?
Wait a second if we
can't count on Luffy,
then that means
everyone's gonna expect me
to win the third round!
[CROWD jeers]
[ITOMIMIZU] Both teams
have finally made it
to the starting line,
but I'm beginning
to wonder if this is
going to be much of a race.
At any rate, let's see
what happens, shall we?
Why'd you ask to
be in two rounds
if you don't even
know how to skate?!
It's not my fault,
that was before
I found out that skating
is the hardest
thing in the world!
We're doomed!
It's all over now!
Don't give up just yet.
It's our job to
pick up the slack.
Come on guys, let's go!
Point Getters to the track!
What?! Not you again!
If you pull any more stunts
you're getting a
boot to the face!
Feh-feh-fe!
We don't need
"stunts" this time.
We could beat you with both
hands tied behind our backs!
[ITOMIMIZU]
It's time for the third game!
The Run Roller Round!
Will Porche breeze
through to an easy victory,
or will the rookie
skater Straw Hat
make a miraculous
improvement?!
[REFEREE]
On your marks! Get set.
[whistle blow]
[ITOMIMIZU]
And she's off!
Porche tears down the
track with spectacular speed!
Now, let's check in on
our challenger, Luffy!
Oh! He's flat on his face!
He didn't even make it
across the starting line!
Certainly is
hard-headed, isn't he?
You, stupid shoes!
[ITOMIMIZU] Whoa, now!
Removing your skates
will result in instant
disqualification!
Crap!
If I make it over there,
I can grab the railing!
Well! Not much of a race!
[whistle blow]
[ITOMIMIZU]
Twenty seconds have passed!
It's time to let
the defenders loose!
[MASSHIKAKU]
Masshikaku!
Hey! He's about
to get pinned!
Somebody, help him!
Not me!!
[MASSHIKAKU]
Huh? That's weird.
Huh?
Gum-Gum Balloon?!
That's it! Let's go, Usopp!
What?!
Hey!
Listen Luffy, you have to
keep holding your breath!
We're gonna roll you all
the way around the track!
Whatever works.
Cien Fleurs! Delphinium!
[NAMI]
Huh?
Wow, thanks Robin!
She's rolling him with her arms!
Awesome!
[ITOMIMIZU]
What incredible speed!
You can hardly
call it skating,
but he's definitely
catching up to Porche!
Oh no! Flower Shuriken!
Uh-oh!
Amazing!
This is certainly the
most bizarre comeback
I've ever seen! But wait!
The Foxy Devils
have lined up
some powerful defense!
[MASSHIKAKU]
I am a wall.
Huh?
[ITOMIMIZU] Oh! But a
fancy flying maneuver
sends him sailing
over Masshikaku!
It's only a matter of time
before he catches up to Porche!
All right, Robin! Nice!
[GIRARIN]
Not so fast.
Killer Sword Festival!
[ITOMIMIZU]
What a turn of events!
Straw Hat Luffy has soared
his way out of bounds!
Oh no.
Was that a sword?!
Luffy, are you okay?!
[GIRARIN]
These things? Don't worry.
Here, look. It's fine.
They're nothing but show!
I... I don't feel so good.
You can come down now.
[thinking]
This is bad.
Since we can't count on Luffy,
that means me, Robin,
and Usopp all have to win.
At this rate, Chopper might
not be the only one we lose!
[whistle blow]
[ITOMIMIZU] As expected,
the winner of the first round
is the lovely Porche!
As you know,
that means one point
for the Foxy Devils!
[LUFFY]
I hate skating!!
Shut up and
get down here!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Now let's move right along!
In the second round match-up,
the Straw Hat's point getter
is Nami, the
nefarious navigator!
She'll be up against
the king of defense.
Masshikaku, everyone's
favorite human wall!
Don't worry about losing,
just focus on the match!
Round #2! On your
marks, get set.
[whistle blow]
[ITOMIMIZU]
And they're off!
Or at least Nami is,
Masshikaku on the other hand.
Well, to put it nicely,
let's say he's taking his time.
It looks like the
heartless witch
might be able to win without
any conniving this time!
Am I missing something?
Why's he so slow?
[thinking]
It's too quiet what's going on?
Is this some kind of trick?
[USOPP] Forget about him,
Nami! Just keep moving!
Right!
[whistle blow]
[ITOMIMIZU]
And there's the second whistle!
Let's see what we can do.
Wait. Why aren't they moving?
Heh heh heh heh...
If you think you can get
past us, then be my guest!
[GIRARIN] You wanna
step up to these babies?
Little late to be
making a roadblock.
We're the ones in
the lead this time.
If you guys don't
move, then I will!
Take it easy Luffy,
we got this one!
Look how slow he is.
There's no way Nami's
gonna lose against that guy!
Huh?
Hmph... Is that what you think?
Hmm?
Flower Hypnosis!
[motorized skate noises]
What happened?
We didn't just fall
asleep on the track, did we?
I'm not sure.
[USOPP]
Luffy! Guys! Wake up!
But they're in the same
place as before, right?
Yeah.
[CHOPPER] Nami! Hurry!
You're about to lose the race!
You gotta get moving now!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Four!
Why would I...
[ITOMIMIZU]
Three! Two! One!
[whistle blow]
[ITOMIZMIZU] The Foxy Devils
win two rounds in a row!
One more and it's all
over for the Dangers!
That can't be.
He's in the same spot,
but that's only cause
he did a whole lap.
Snooze you lose!
It sucks to be you, huh?
Feh-feh-feh!
Can't believe we beat
'em with Masshikaku!
Puh-puh-puh...
Are you kidding?!
[ITOMIMIZU] Unless the
Straw Hats can pull it
together fast, things could
be over for them in a flash!
With a two point deficit,
everything is riding
on the next round!
Will Usopp's
aerodynamic nose give him
the edge he needs
to beat Chiqicheetah?
But I'm aller--
[STRAW HAT PIRATES]
Don't you dare try to tell us
you're allergic
to roller skates!
[thinking] How can I beat a
guy with "cheetah" in his name?
Heck, he might even be a
cheetah, now that I look at him.
[LUFFY]
Ow!
That's all wrong.
Try to lower your
stance a little.
You gotta use your
hips when you move.
I never figured you
for a skater! Wow!
[ZORO] I'm not. I just
watched other people do it.
[thinking] I can't rely
on Luffy for this one.
What I need is a strategy!
[ZORO]
Spread them out a little.
[LUFFY]
Huh. Like this?
Ow!
[ZORO]
Not even close.
[LUFFY]
Like this? Ow!
[ZORO]
No!
[LUFFY]
Like this? Ow!
[ZORO]
No! Listen to me, damn it!
[whistle blow]
On your marks! Get set.
[USOPP thinking]
I got nothing! Well, whatever!
I can go faster than a cheetah
if I try really hard, right?!
Ah ha! I'm in the
lead! It worked!
AHHHH!!!
So fast!
Eh-heh! Your little friend
might as well give up now
and save himself the effort.
Chiqicheetah doesn't even
need our help, ya know.
[USOPP] This is hopeless!
What am I supposed to do?!
No way! He already
finished a whole lap?!
Maybe you guys should
just sit back and relax too!
It's not over
'til it's over, okay?
[ITOMIMIZU]
That's twenty seconds!
It's time for
the defense to go!
Come on, Robin!
Right.
Well, good luck.
Here he comes!
I gotta do something!
He's gonna lap me!
How do you like this?!
No way!
Oh!
There you go. Now keep
it up, just like I said.
Look! He's almost there!
C'mon kid, you can do it!
That's it! C'mon! Go!
Grrr!
[CROWD cheers]
Huh? Is he?
Yeah! Usopp,
you're gonna win this!
[LUFFY] Hang on,
Chopper, we'll get you back!
♪ ending song ♪
[ITOMIMIZU] Luffy has
finally found his footing!
[LUFFY] Yeah! There's
no stopping me now!
[USOPP] But you
can't even turn corners!
[ZORO] Hey coach,
why don't you try doing
something useful for once?
[SANJI] Why's it my
job all of a sudden?
Oh, wait, but now
that I think about it,
I might actually have a plan!
[ROBIN] I hope it works,
since I'm racing next.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"A Seriously Heated Race!
Into the Final Round!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!