[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other.
After arriving in the Alabasta
port town of Nanohana,
Luffy was reunited with
his older brother, Ace.
Ace demonstrated the power
of the Flame Flame Fruit.
And now with him by their side,
the Straw Hat Pirates
follow the Sandora River
upstream towards Yuba.
[LUFFY]
"Erumalu, the City of Green
and the Kung Fu Dugongs!"
Hold it!
What business do you have here?!
[CITIZEN A]
We have to see the king!
We're dying out here.
How much longer can
this war go on?
Between the war and the drought,
there's nothing to eat.
Our crops and
livestock are dead!
My baby needs milk!
There must be some in
the palace! Let us in!
[GUARD A]
Stop pushing!
[GUARD B] Sorry, but we
can't let you through!
Stop pushing! Stay back!
[BOY crying]
[CITIZEN C]
Are you gonna just stand there?!
[CITIZEN D]
And do nothing?!
[CITIZEN E]
And you call yourself a king?!
Shut up! How dare you
insult His Royal Highness!
They have every right!
All of them!
I'm sorry.
You've all had to put up
with unbearable suffering
because of my lack of strength,
and for that, I apologize.
Those who wish to speak,
please, come inside the palace.
Tell me of your qualms,
and I will listen.
The only thing I can promise is
that I will share your suffering
as if it were my own.
I ask that you endure
a little more.
Mark my words, though,
I will return peace
to this kingdom,
even if it takes
my life to do so.
[VIVI] Father, this is
an obvious set‐up!
It's clear that someone
is trying to throw you
and this kingdom into ruin!
[COBRA] I hope you're
all right, my dear.
I wonder where you are right now
and what you're doing at
this very moment, Vivi.
[SANJI] The tea's ready.
Come on up to the kitchen.
Thanks, Sanji.
I'll be right there.
[USOPP]
Ahoy there, maties!
It is me, Captain
Rice Ball Usopp!
Yeah. And who might you be, huh?
I am Ricey the Rice Man!
Quit playin' with our food,
you damn numbskulls!
If you've got free
time, wash dishes!
I could use some help since I
still have to pack all the food
for the hike to Yuba!
Let me know if I can help.
No. You're our guest,
so just sit back and relax.
Thanks, though.
[ACE]
All right.
[SANJI]
That's mop water, you idiots!
We just swabbed
the deck with it!
Ah! What a nice breeze!
[VIVI] Nami, if you don't mind,
I'd like to stop the ship here.
It'll just be for a moment.
Stop? What for?
I have a very important
mission for Karoo.
Karoo?
Karoo, I need you to
go to Alubarna Palace
and deliver this
letter to my father.
It contains everything uncovered
by Igaram and myself.
The details of Crocodile's
nefarious plans
for this country are in here.
Also, it lets him know
that I've returned to
Alabasta safe and sound
and in the company
of brave friends
willing to help us
in our struggle.
Well, then. Can you do
this for me, Karoo?
[squawks]
Now, be careful to conserve
your water, 'kay?
[KAROO squawks]
Good luck! You can do it, Duck!
Go let my father know, Karoo.
There's hope for this
kingdom at last!
[squawks]
[VIVI] I said "conserve,"
not "consume"!
Thank you. And good luck.
Well, I did know that Crocodile
was here in Alabasta...
...but him trying to
steal a kingdom?
That sounds like a bad joke.
Because why would a pirate
drop anchor in one spot
and settle down?
Crocodile trying to usurp
the throne of Alabasta
doesn't make sense.
[LUFFY]
All right! Let's set sail!
[USOPP]
Hold on!
[ACE] You know, there
could be another side
to this takeover thing.
Huh?
Like some sort of deeper
goal or something.
[CROCODILE]
Alabasta, the kingdom of sand.
Even if you can build
cities atop the dunes
and they manage to stand
for a thousand years,
the desert will still be filled
with the stench of death.
Death is a constant and this
land has embraced its shadow
since its inception.
I just got a report.
It's about the Billions' ships
stationed in Nanohana.
They were destroyed by someone
and all hands are reported lost.
Of course, I'm having all of
this verified as we speak.
[CROCODILE]
No great loss.
We have more replacements
for the Billions
than we'll ever need.
A single drop of water spilled
in the desert is insignificant
and no obstacle for my plan.
However, if anyone who
would dare defy me
has appeared in this land...
...crush them underfoot.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Understood.
I've already dispatched
the lizard runners
to contact our other agents.
[CROCODILE]
Excellent.
[LUFFY]
We're finally here!
[CHOPPER] Wow, so we're
going into the desert?
Does anyone know how
hot it's supposed to get?
[NAMI] Over a hundred
degrees in the daytime!
[CHOPPER] What?! Please
tell me you're joking!
Ah! Nami, what happened?!
Where's your dancer outfit?!
Ah! You, too?! Vivi,
why are you wearing that?!
Because any exposed skin
will get sunburned.
You have to cover
up in the desert.
But... those outfits...
were so sexy...
[VIVI]
Put these on, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Oh, thank you.
[ZORO]
Time to drop anchor.
[USOPP]
Right.
[splash]
[LUFFY]
Yuba, here we come!
[ZORO]
Huh?
What are those?
[DUGONGS yell]
Turtles?
No, I think they're seals.
Kung Fu Dugongs!
[grunting]
[CHOPPER]
"If you wanna come ashore,
you'll have to beat me first,
but I doubt that'll happen,
you buncha cowards!"
He says.
[USOPP]
Ha.
Nobody calls me a coward
and gets away with it.
Here comes the pain!
[VIVI]
Usopp! No, wait!
Kung Fu Dugongs
are really strong!
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY]
See! They're not too tough!
[VIVI]
That's bad, too!
[LUFFY]
Huh? What the‐‐?
It's one of their rules.
If they lose a kung fu match,
they become the winner's pupil.
You don't say...
They think you're
their master now!
Right! Everyone, after me!
Now, punch!
No! Like this!
Yeah! Now... harder!
And now... left!
Left! Right!
Yeah!
Right! All set?!
Let's go to Yuba!
Hey, wait a minute!
You're not bringing
them with us!
Luffy, you can't!
They're water creatures;
they won't make it.
[BOTH]
But they're so cute...
[NAMI] It's gonna break my
heart to say no to them,
but we can't let
them come along.
[VIVI] I agree, but how are we
supposed to get them to stay?
I know!
Hm... let's see.
Where was that thing?
[SANJI]
What are you doing?
[CHOPPER]
Here!
You can have this, but only
if you guys stay here, okay?
[CHOPPER screams]
[CHOPPER]
Somebody! Help me!
Chopper!
[LUFFY] Hope all you guys
enjoy the food! See ya!
"All you guys." "Food."
Now do you get it?
No. They said they
wanted to go with us,
so why couldn't we let 'em?
We don't have enough
food and water
to take care of
a group that big!
Moron!
Honestly, I don't know
what we would've done
if Chopper hadn't
persuaded them to stay.
[CHOPPER]
Yeah!
They kept saying, "Where you
go, we'll follow, Master!"
They really would have, too,
if I hadn't given
them that food!
[SANJI] And now our food
supply's gotten a lot smaller.
Thanks, Luffy, thanks.
He's a handful.
[SANJI]
You're tellin' me.
[ZORO]
Hm?
[USOPP]
Huh?
[SANJI]
What's this?
[LUFFY]
Are we in Yuba already?
No. This is Erumalu.
It was known far and wide
as the "City of Green."
It was green?
Take a good look
around, everyone.
This is what Baroque Works
has been doing to my country.
The people of Alabasta, this is
what they've had to go through.
[LUFFY] Wow! There's nothing
here at all anymore, huh?
[VIVI]
No.
It's nothing but
a ghost town now.
But up until a few short years
ago, it was a thriving city
full of gardens, palm trees,
and lush greenery.
[ZORO]
This place? Hm.
[VIVI]
Rain was always scarce here,
but by saving every last drop
of water and using it wisely,
the city was able to make
the foliage flourish.
Unfortunately, that stopped
when the rain did.
Not a single drop
of water has fallen
in any part of this country
for three years now.
Three years?!
Wow, that long?
But wait, even without rain,
there was still the river
as another water source.
And it's close.
Why couldn't they just pipe
the water in from over there?
Well, the answer to
that is just up ahead.
[USOPP]
Hm?
[VIVI] Even though it's
a desert kingdom,
never in a thousands of years
of Alabasta's history
has the rain ever
stopped completely.
However, there was one
place in the country
where the rain fell more than
usual, much more in fact.
Alubarna, the capital.
The city where the
king's palace is located.
[VIVI] The people of the land
called it the "King's Miracle."
At least, they did until
one particular day.
[SAILOR]
Get that cargo unloaded!
We've got a schedule to keep!
[STRIPED SHIRT]
We're losing it!
Watch out!
[CITIZEN I] What happened?!
Is everyone all right?!
Damn it. What are we
supposed to do now?
It's a delivery for the king.
What's he gonna do when
it doesn't arrive on time?
[CITIZEN J] This green
powder's for the king?
What is it?
[BILLIONS A]
How the hell should we know?!
We're only following
your king's orders.
[BILLIONS B]
We're just couriers!
Run!
[CITIZEN K]
Wait a minute. Could this be...?
[NAMI]
Dance Powder?
Oh, so you've heard of it?
Yes.
I sure have. It summons rain.
A powder can?
[NAMI] I've only heard
stories about it,
but apparently, dance powder
was created by a researcher
in a country where
it never rained.
Burning it creates a misty
smoke which rises into the sky.
Once it reaches the clouds,
it causes them to rain.
In essence, it gives
you the ability
to create rain on the spot.
[LUFFY] Oh! I know what
you're talkin' about!
I've seen that stuff before!
I ate some a while back!
It tasted pretty gross,
though! Yuck!
You ate dance powder?
[ZORO] It's not even food;
it's for makin' rain.
Hey! I'm not lying!
I'm telling the truth!
I did eat it, and it
tasted so gross...
Hang on! I don't get it.
Wouldn't that stuff be perfect
for a desert country like this?
You'd think so.
In fact, as its name suggests,
the country that
developed dance powder
was happy enough to dance.
It got lots of rain.
But there was a catch:
Its neighboring country
had a drought.
Let me explain how it works.
Now...
The mist from the
burned dance powder
targets small clouds that
aren't ready to rain yet.
It artificially matures them
into full rain clouds.
Those clouds would
have naturally grown
into rain clouds,
but when they were
further downwind...
[USOPP]
Oh, I get it!
It steals all the rain that
would've normally gone
to a neighboring country!
That musta caused
some big problems!
[NAMI]
Oh, it did.
A war broke out between
the two countries.
Ever since then,
the World Government has
instituted a worldwide ban
on the production and
possession of dance powder.
[USOPP] Even so, some of it
managed to show up here, huh.
When it happened,
the country had been
experiencing strange weather.
There had been no rain.
Not a single drop had fallen
anywhere except one place,
and that was the capital.
[CITIZEN L] No wonder we
haven't had any rain in ages!
The king stole it for the
capital using this dance powder!
[CITIZEN M] So Alubarna's rain
wasn't a miracle at all!
It was a sham!
[CITIZEN N] Yeah! One that's
left us parched and starving!
This is all King Cobra's fault!
Vivi! That means your
dad is the bad guy here!
No! You idiot! He was framed!
[LUFFY]
Ow! Ow!
[SANJI] Her sweet dear old dad
would never do such a thing,
you got it?
Of course. My father didn't
have anything to do with it.
He was innocent.
Unfortunately, a large
amount of dance powder
was discovered inside his
palace shortly thereafter.
[ZORO]
Huh.
They even had people
working inside the palace.
[SANJI]
So... what is this? A road?
No. It used to be a large canal.
It piped in fresh water
from the Sandora River.
Until someone destroyed it.
Now do you see what happened?
With its canal gone,
the City of Green lost its only
remaining source of fresh water.
The people here
waited and prayed,
but sadly, rain never came.
[clatter]
[NAMI]
Wow.
Something like that and
the dance powder incident
would really make people
distrust their king.
[ZORO] That's exactly what
Crocodile planned, I bet.
[VIVI]
With no more water,
fighting began to
break out in Erumalu.
To escape the violence here,
there was only one thing the
exhausted citizens could do.
They abandoned the city
and left for other oases
in search of water.
And then...
[VIVI] ...the City of
Green withered away.
[howling]
What... is that?
Is it the rebels?
Or more of those creeps from
Baroque Works. Oh, no!
No. It's just wind.
Sounds like a voice, right?
Oh, man. It's coming
from all directions!
This isn't good!
Ace, what are we gonna do?!
There's no danger.
It's just the wind blowing
around the town
and echoing off
the old buildings.
It's like...
It's like the city of
Erumalu is wailing
over what's happened to it.
[NAMI]
Watch out!
[gasps]
[USOPP]
Whoa!
What's the deal with
that freaky wind?
Someone's collapsed!
Wait, you mean there are still
people living in this city?!
[VIVI]
What did my father...
...and all of the
other good people...
...what did they ever do?
They don't deserve this.
It's hard enough to
live in the desert.
Every day, it's a struggle
just to survive.
Somehow the people of Alabasta
found a way to do it
and they led happy lives!
But Crocodile
destroyed those lives!
What gives him the right
to do that?! What?!
All the while, as one
of the Seven Warlords,
he passes himself off
as a hero of the people!
They don't know what
he's really doing!
No one realizes that
he's actually deceiving
the entire country,
even as they cheer him on!
[CROWD]
Crocodile! Crocodile!
I can't! I can't let
him get away with this!
[LUFFY yells]
Oh, well... Hope that
made him feel better.
[LUFFY]
Vivi!
Let's get movin', 'kay?
I'm itchin' to do this!
[NAMI]
He's right. Let's get to Yuba.
That's where the rebel
army is, right? Yuba?
Yes, I have to stop them.
I'm going to persuade
their leader.
How so?
I'll tell the rebel
leader the truth,
that all of this is
Crocodile's doing,
and have him stop all of
this pointless bloodshed.
Let's go.
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[CHOPPER] I can't go on!
I can't take this heat!
[USOPP]
Take off that animal suit.
[CHOPPER] You jerk! Are you
making fun of reindeer?!
[SANJI] What in the world is
Luffy doing over there?
[USOPP]
He's riding a camel!
[NAMI] Yeah, and something's
chasing him, too!
[ZORO]
Damn it.
How does he always manage
to attract trouble like this?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Adventure in the
Country of Sand!
The Monsters that Live
in the Scorching Land!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!