Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use
any means necessary
to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] In search of
a ship-coating craftsman
to help them reach Fishman
Island, the Straw Hat crew
landed on the
Sabaody Archipelago.
This mission led them
to Rayleigh, a craftsman
and former vice-captain
of the Roger Pirates.
The Straw Hat crew
tried to lay low
while Rayleigh
modified the Sunny,
but they were ambushed
by a cyborg that bore
a suspicious resemblance
to Bartholomew Kuma.
[SANJI]
Diable Jambe!
Flambe Shot!
[ZORO]
Demon Aura.
Nine-Sword Style.
Asura!
[LUFFY]
Third gear!
Here goes!
Giant rifle!
[panting]
[LUFFY sighs]
We need to get some rest.
I was up for a fight, but that
guy was way too much for me.
I'm exhausted.
[NARRATOR] Overwhelmed and
tired, they attempted to escape,
only to be ambushed by
Sentomaru of the Marines
and another Pacifista.
[ALL scream]
[LUFFY pants]
We can't win.
Let's run, but not all together.
We need to split up!
[SENTOMARU]
They're splitting into groups!
Go after them, PX-1!
Now Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
[SENTOMARU]
Hoisa!
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
[ZORO groans]
[USOPP]
Zoro!
[LUFFY gasps]
[USOPP] Who-who are
you? Or what are you?
Whatever! Just get the
hell away from Zoro!
[BROOK]
Oh, no, no, Zoro!
He got hit by one of
those laser beams!
Kizaru?
[NARRATOR] When it seemed
things couldn't get any worse,
Navy Admiral Kizaru appeared,
thrusting the Straw Hats
into the most desperate
situation they've ever faced.
[LUFFY]
Admiral Kizaru's Fierce Assault.
The Straw Hats
Face Certain Death!
[KID panting]
[LAW]
Get ready.
[MARINES scream]
[KID grunts]
[KILLER yells]
[BEPO yelling]
[BEPO groans]
Uh. I'll just stay down.
[KID]
Hey! Warlord!
Let's go for another spin.
It's time you got your
ass handed to you.
[KID grunting]
[KILLER]
Kid!
[KID]
Repel!
[KID panting]
[KID laughs]
No one's ever stood up
and walked away
after that attack.
[KID laughing]
We just took down one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
[KID PIRATES]
Yeah!
[LAW] That's all it took
to bring Kuma down?
Seems a bit too easy.
[KID gasps]
What the hell?
He's a machine. He's--
The damn thing's a cyborg!
[KID grunts]
Funny, I don't remember
asking for help.
[LAW] If you could see
past your own fat head,
you'd realize how
screwed you are.
What?
Ya think ya could take down
a real Warlord that easy?
What do you mean by real?
[LAW] We can discuss it later.
We've got a few more guests.
Capture them!
[MARINES yelling]
[BEPO yells]
[MARINE 404A groans]
[MARINES gasp]
A polar bear?
[BEPO]
Aah, ho.
[MARINES]
Huh?
[BEPO]
Hah, waaaah ho!
[MARINES]
Uh...?
[JEAN BART grunts]
[BEPO]
I had that, you know?
Alright, Trafalgar.
You gonna explain now?
If he isn't a Warlord,
what is he?
[BOTH grunt]
Great, what is it this time?
Zoro!
Crap! He shoots beams too?!
How're we supposed
to beat these guys?
[FRANKY] At point blank
like that, he's done for!
Zoro's in trouble!
Come on, do something, guys!
[USOPP whimpering]
Usopp! Please!
[USOPP gasps]
Get away from him!
Back up or else!
Take this!
What?! What the hell?!
Why? What is this?!
What's happening?!
I can't hit him!
[BROOK yells]
I-I can't stab him!
What the-- What can we do?
Keep trying! Dammit!
Get back! Move your
foot! I mean it!
Leave him alone!
Step away from our friend!
You're wasting your time.
I ate the Glint-Glint Fruit
and now I'm made of light.
It's a Logia, you see.
He's made of light?
[NAMI] This is a nightmare.
There's nothing we can do.
Zoro! Try to run away! Hurry!
[ZORO]
I can't move. I'm too weak.
[SANJI] It's no use!
The bastard's worn out,
he can't save himself!
Now Veinte Fleurs!
[KIZARU]
Huh?
[USOPP]
Yes! Awesome work, Robin!
[BROOK gasps]
[ZORO grunts]
He just shifted in place!
Unbelievable.
[ROBIN grunts]
It's cute how your
friends want to save you.
But you're far beyond help now.
[KIZARU]
Well then...
Time to die.
[ZORO groans]
You picked some time
to come out of hiding.
[KIZARU]
You sure you want to do this,
Dark King Rayleigh?
Don't go picking these
buds before they sprout.
Their era is only
just beginning.
And I wanna see
what they do with it.
Rayleigh!
The geezer saved Zoro.
[NAMI sighs]
[SANJI panting]
I was so scared!
[ROBIN sighs]
[SENTOMARU] So that guy is
the Dark King? Interesting.
[KIZARU] I'd heard rumors
you were somewhere
on the archipelago but I chalked
them up as ghost stories.
Yet here you are,
sticking your neck out
for these rookies.
You just can't shake those
instincts, can you, Rayleigh?
Once a pirate, always a pirate.
[RAYLEIGH] I'd be more than
happy to retire in peace
and live out the quiet life,
but it's a little tough to do
when the Navy keeps hanging
wanted posters of me.
[KIZARU] You were a member
of the Roger Pirates, Rayleigh.
Do you really think your
crimes can be forgotten?
But if we were to make
an honest attempt
at capturing you, that
would require some serious
preparation on our part.
[USOPP sighs]
Wow, I'm so relieved!
That old man has
really got some power.
All of our attacks
went through him
as if he were a ghost.
But, when Rayleigh
attacked, it hit.
[RAYLEIGH] Why don't you
just look the other way
and let these kids go?
What's the harm?
C'mon, what reality
are you living in?
You know there's no way I
can just let them off the hook.
Not when we have to answer
to the Celestial Dragons.
Navy HQ's gotta keep them
happy and that won't do it.
I'd appreciate it if
you don't interfere.
Hey, Usopp! You guys!
[KIZARU]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Grab Zoro and get outta there!
[USOPP]
Let's go, Brook!
[BROOK]
Right!
Everyone start running
and look after yourselves!
[LUFFY]
We can't win this one!
We're too weak!
Get moving!
He knows when he's beat.
Well, ain't that a pain.
[NAMI]
Franky, c'mon!
Not before I let loose
one final attack
with all of my cola energy!
Coup de Vent!
[FRANKY] How'd that feel,
ya mechanical ass?!
Now hurry, run!
[CHOPPER, ROBIN panting]
Hey, old man! Thanks a lot!
Sure thing! And best
of luck to you!
[KIZARU]
Sacred Yata Mirror.
[USOPP]
I can't see!
I don't think he's
trying to help us see!
[RAYLEIGH grunts]
You're stayin' put.
Feels good to hold
a blade again.
Ama no Murakumo.
Sword!
This is disappointing.
I was expecting a laid back,
hassle free, island excursion.
Life is nothing but a series
of surprises, Kizaru.
[BROOK] That light
from before. It's gone!
[USOPP] I guess the
old man saved us again!
[BROOK yelping]
I was so scared!
It appears he's the
Dark King after all.
I've never seen anyone put
Uncle through a fight like that.
We were so close to closing the
book on Roronoa's days of crime.
[SENTOMARU]
PX-1! Finish Roronoa off first!
He's barely alive!
Crap, this is bad. Hey, Franky!
Do me a favor and
keep Nami safe, okay?
Just keep on running!
[FRANKY] We'll be fine! You
take care of yourself, okay?
[NAMI]
What're you doing, Sanji?
[SANJI]
I've gotta help Usopp and Zoro!
[USOPP panting]
[ZORO] Put me down.
[USOPP] Huh?
Just leave me. Save yourself.
Aw, don't be a moron!
Right now, you're even more
weak and useless than I am!
We're getting out
of here together!
Those were Luffy's orders
and I'm stickin' to 'em!
Huh? Wait, do I hear--
[BROOK, USOPP scream]
[USOPP, BROOK whimpering]
[BROOK]
C'mon, hurry up, Usopp!
You go on without me!
It's fine. I'll hold him back!
No, don't do it, Brook!
You dont' know how strong
he is, he'll rip you apart!
[BROOK]
Never fear! Run on, my friend!
This is what must be done!
There comes a time
when a man must put
everything on the line!
[BROOK yells]
[BROOK groaning]
No bones about it,
that was pretty pointless.
Brook, no!
[USOPP screams]
[USOPP]
Go away, leave me alone!
[SANJI panting]
Get the hell away from them,
you stupid cyborg!
[SANJI]
Hyah!
Sanji!
[SANJI groans]
Ow, my leg!
[SANJI grunting]
[USOPP] Move, Sanji!
He's gonna shoot you!
Moron! Why aren't you running?
[USOPP screams]
[panting]
[RAYLEIGH]
Huh?
Even if you distract
me, my subordinates
are quite capable on their own.
[RAYLEIGH growls]
[SANJI grunts, panting]
[USOPP panting, coughing]
I dropped you! I'm sorry,
Zoro! It was an accident!
Hey, jerk, who said
I was done with you?
[SANJI grunting]
Dammit! Stop and fight me!
Looks like they're
in trouble over there.
[SENTOMARU] You've got
plenty of trouble yourself.
But just to be fair,
I won't use my battleaxe
on you this time.
[SENTOMARU]
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
[LUFFY screams]
Luffy! Why?
How can his attacks work on him
when Luffy's made of rubber?
What the hell?
Chopper! We have to keep moving!
[USOPP]
Sanji!
[CHOPPER, ROBIN gasp]
[USOPP groans]
[LUFFY groaning]
Everybody's gonna die!
[ROBIN]
No, Chopper! It's too dangerous!
Get the hell away
from my friends!
Now rumble ball!
[CHOPPER roaring]
[BOTH gasp]
It's Chopper!
I like little Chopper better!
What exactly am I looking at?
[CHOPPER roaring]
It's even worse than
what the others told me.
[CHOPPER growling]
That's an interesting
power you've got there.
It's too bad you don't seem
to have any control over it.
[CHOPPER growling]
[ROBIN]
Luffy! C'mon!
[CHOPPER growling]
[USOPP pants]
This is what it's come to?
Even if he beats him, then what?
[beeping]
[CHOPPER roars]
[USOPP] I don't know what's
going on, but he seems confused.
Now's our chance!
[USOPP]
Sanji, Brook...
Get up. Snap out of it!
Chopper bought us
some time! We gotta move!
You wanna live, right?
[USOPP gasps]
Hey! You're blowin' our chance!
Brook! Sanji!
[USOPP whimpers]
[KUMA]
Stand down, PX-1.
[BROOK gasps]
[USOPP, BROOK scream]
[USOPP]
Not another one!
This is officially too much.
I can't take it!
Just how many of these guys
are there? It isn't fair!
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO]
It's him. It's the real Kuma.
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO groaning]
[ZORO panting]
[SANJI] What in the
hell happened here?
[ZORO grunts]
What happened here?
Nothing at all.
[KUMA]
I see you survived, Roronoa.
Just barely.
I've got your mercy
to thank for that.
What're you doing, Zoro?
This is no time to talk
to the enemy. Let's go!
[KUMA]
If you could take a vacation,
where is it you'd like to go?
Hey, Zoro. C'mon!
Let's get out of
here while we can!
Huh?
Where did-- Hey, Zoro?
Is he gone?
[SANJI grunting]
[USOPP] Zoro! Oh man,
oh man, this is bad!
No.
What happened? Where is he?
[ROBIN gasps]
Zoro...
Zoro... He just disappeared.
[LUFFY]
It's over. They're all gone.
Brook, Franky, Robin, Chopper,
Sanji, Usopp, Nami, Zoro...
What's wrong with me?
I couldn't save a single
one of my friends!
On the next One Piece.
"Eliminated Friends - The Final
Day of the Straw Hat Crew."