[FRANKY]
Huh?
Show yourself!
What fool would dare to
oppose the Franky Family?!
Give us our money back!
[FRANKY] "Give us our
money back," you say?
Hmm, does that mean
you're one of the Straw Hats?
That's right, bro!
He totally is!
I was expecting all of the Straw
Hat crew to be really strong,
but this one's not at all!
Hahahaha!
Yeah, he's a complete weakling!
What a joke!
Mind your own damn business!
[FRANKY]
Whoops!
You've got some guts
trying to take back
the money all by yourself.
But I'm afraid
I can't let you have it.
Give it back.
We need the money...
...to fix the Merry!
Her scars are deep.
That's our money.
It's to heal her wounds,
understand me?!
You can't have it!
Give it back to me right now!
[LUFFY]
[FRANKY]
Hahahaha!
What are you so
worked up about?
Seems like you love
your ship quite a bit.
[chuckles]
No matter.
Whatever condition she's in,
this money belongs
to us now. Understand?
Damn you.
[FRANKY]
Unfortunately, in this world,
stealing from pirates isn't
really seen as a crime.
Besides, this is
probably dirty money
you swiped somewhere
along the way here.
[chuckles]
Just let us have it.
[FRANKY] Maybe you could
beg the Navy for help.
Nah, they'd just arrest you.
[chuckles]
Too bad for Straw Hat Luffy.
He's got himself a
useless crony who can't even
handle the simple task
of guarding a little money.
Such a shame.
[FRANKY]
All right, boys!
Show him all the hospitalities
of The Franky House
while I'm gone.
No time like the present
to start shopping
with this pile of money.
[chuckles]
Man! This is gonna be great!
Hold it! Special
Attack Exploding Star!
[gasps]
[FRANKY] Remember my name,
long-nosed boy. It's Franky.
If you wanna leave
this city alive,
I'd suggest you
never cross me.
Hey! What are you
guys doing?! Let go!
Hahahaha!
You call this little
kid's toy a weapon?
Hahahaha!
[FRANKY]
See ya later, Long-Nose.
Thanks again for the
200 million Berries.
[USOPP]
No! Wait! Give it back!
Give back the Merry!
You hear me?! Give it back!
No! Give it back!
[laughter]
Give it back!
[jeers and laughter]
No! Please!
Give it back!!
[NAMI] I need to wait here
until Robin comes back.
If I march in with
the others right now,
I'll just be in the way.
It'll be scary, too.
For now the best thing
I can do is stay here,
guard the money and
protect the Merry.
Don't let me down, guys.
I'm counting on you!
[SANJI]
Stop Stop!!
If I remember correctly.
This is the place
Nami was talking about.
[NAMI] Look. This is the
backstreet shopping district.
You go up this canal,
turn, then here!
Usopp is right here!
[CHOPPER]
Got it.
[SANJI] Nami, where are those
dismantlers you mentioned?
The Franky Family. Show me.
[CHOPPER]
Hey, Usopp!
[SANJI]
I guess he left.
[ZORO]
Are you sure?
Maybe you just screwed
up the directions.
[SANJI] I'm not you, moron!
Shut your hole!
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
What'd you say?
Look at this!
It's blood! See?
That idiot,
I guess he walked off
somewhere on his own.
Wait, you don't think that he--
Usopp, no.
[LUFFY]
Aaaaaaaaaaaa...
Huh?
...aaaaaaaaa!
Luffy!
Help! I'm drowning!
[coughing]
[SANJI]
What are you doing?
And where the hell
did you fall from?
[LUFFY] The shipyard. I was
trying to jump around
like that carpenter
to look for Usopp.
[CHOPPER]
Are you all right?
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
Oh, that's right!
I almost forgot!
We've got a terrible problem!
Usopp was abducted
and so was the money!
We know. That's why
we're here. Come on.
We were just about to
head over to the hideout
of the guys that did it.
I'll bet that's where we'll
find Usopp and the money.
[SANJI] Maybe he felt
responsible about what
happened and went
to settle the matter
with the Franky
Family on his own.
[CORGY] All right then.
We'll be leaving now.
That man is
seriously stubborn!
It's infuriating!
We don't even know
if he has it or not,
yet they keep
sending me out here.
Over and over again.
I wish those people would put
themselves in my shoes for once.
[knocking]
It's Kalifa.
[ICEBERG]
Mwell, come in.
You must be worn out, Sir.
Would you like
something to drink?
[ICEBERG]
I would. Thank you.
Maybe some tea.
[KALIFA]
I've already prepared it.
Mwell, I'd expect
nothing less from you.
Thank you. I'm grateful.
Poor Mr. Corgy is always so
angry when he leaves, isn't he?
What in the world does he
come here to talk about?
[ICEBERG]
Oh, that.
Those he represents
want something I have,
and they keep
making various offers.
It must be something of
great importance then, isn't it?
Mwell, maybe so,
though I always deny
knowing anything about it.
They really are tiresome people.
[LUFFY]
Is he breathing, Chopper?
[CHOPPER] He's unconscious
but yes, he's breathing.
He'll live. I can save him.
You wait out here for us.
'Kay, Usopp?
[LUFFY]
We're gonna go level
that stupid house
to the ground.
[cheering]
[FAMILY A] Hey! Somebody
go buy some more food!
[FAMILY B] Yeah!
We've got the money!
[FAMILY C] Get some more
booze while you're at it!
When it comes to painting,
I'm in a league of my own!
So, what do you think?
M-My goggles!
You got them back
from that creep for me!
Thank you so much!
Well! Let me tell you about
the time that I, Usopp,
bravely fought off vicious
sea kings in the Calm Belt,
young Chopper.
Big ones, too! Huge!
Be warned! Captain Usopp
has an army! 8000 men!
[USOPP]
They took all of the money.
How can I face the
others now, Nami?
All right, guys, it's
time to kick their asses.
All of them!
[KIDROCK]
That's it! Show 'em!
Looks like you
lose this round!
Losers get to go
pick up more booze!
Buy all the food they
have in the shop, too!
It's not like we
don't have the money!
[laughter]
Be right back.
And when I am,
I'm gonna win every hand.
Just you wait!
Hmm?
Ahh!
[RAZ-BERET] What was that?
What happened?!
Who the hell are those guys?
You jerks! You got a death wish?
I recognize them!
It's that pirate.
Straw Hat Luffy!
Ha ha ha!
So you came here to get
your money back, did ya?
Bad move.
Just take a
look around you.
Do you really think the four
of you are enough
to handle all of us?
Ha ha ha!
But, since you're here,
we might as well
take those big bounties
you've got on your heads.
He's the captain of
that long-nosed weakling
we took care of earlier.
[laughter]
With that pitiful excuse
for a pirate on his crew,
he can't possibly
be that strong.
Let's go! C'mon, shrimp!
Now, Gum Gum...
Huh?
What do you
think you're doing?
Hahaha!
Are you punching him?
Not even a bombardment
from battleship cannons
can put a dent in that armor.
Hahaha! What a joke!
If you're just
gonna play around,
then I'll go ahead
and end this right now.
And Cannon!
[cries of surprise]
[POLKA-HAT] He punched
a hole right through it!
[ZAMBAI]
Hey!
Hold on! W-Wait a
second, you guys!
Let's talk about this first!
[ZAMBAI]
Okay? Guys?
Okay, guys,
fire the cannons!
Now, Three-Sword
Style Kara Suma...
...Raven Hunt!
What?! Impossible!
Those cannonballs
are made of iron!
The cannons, too?!
[GOLDILOCKS]
Holy crap!
These guys are
seriously bad news!
[PURPLE SHIRT]
Let's get out of here!
Everybody run
for the back door!
You guys started this fight.
It's kind of pathetic to
run from it like cowards.
Party Table...
...Kick Course!
We... We can't make
it to the backdoor!
Windows! Use the windows!
[CHOPPER]
Rumble!
Horn Point!
Roseo Colonnade!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, you guys!
It's the money, right?
You just want the money back?
The 200 million berries the
long-nosed guy had? Is that it?
I'm sorry to be
the one to tell you,
but that pile of money
isn't here anymore.
Franky, the family
boss, took all of it
and went out on
a shopping spree!
And since he's buying
something on the black market,
we don't have any idea
where he might be
or even how to find him!
So, no matter how much
of a rampage you go on,
that 200 million
won't be coming back!
So why don't you an--
Zambai!
Shut up. That's
enough out of you.
This has nothing to
do with the money.
Damn straight.
It's too late for that.
Not even your bones will
be left when we're done.
Not even our bones?!
What's the matter with you?
Acting like a
bunch of cowards!
We're the Franky Family!
We're the ones who do all the
bone breaking around here!
Got it? Never
forget who you are!
Okay, brothers!
Let's show 'em the specialty
of The Franky House!
Now! Fire the
Anything Shot Cannon!
[BEARDFACE]
Here they come! Attack!
[SORBO]
Don't let up!
Keep firing until there's
nothing left to shoot!
[GIANT SPIKE] Come on!
There're only four of them!
[CITIZENS]
Huh?
[FRANKY]
[CITIZEN C]
What was that? Fireworks?
[CITIZEN D]
Sounds like it's coming
from out toward
The Franky House.
Them again?
What trouble are
they up to this time?
I know, right?
Hey! Quiet, they're
gonna hear us!
[MOZU]
Oh, boy.
Sounds like they're
getting a little carried away.
[KIWI]
When those boys party.
They really don't show
any restraint, now do they?
[FRANKY] No big deal. It's not
like they do it all the time.
It's a nice day. Hahaha!
[SANJI]
Should we go after Franky?
And start looking where?
Ah, man, looks like these idiots
really didn't know
where he took the money.
[SANJI]
And if we do find him.
If he spent it, then
there's no getting it back.
What now? Even if we
wait around for him,
he might not be
back for quite a while.
Okay! The first aid
treatment is all done!
We need to take him
back on a stretcher,
so I could use
some help over here!
Hanging around here
won't do any good.
Let's head back to
the ship for now.
We left Nami there
all by herself
and Robin's still missing.
The ship's a problem, too.
[ZORO]
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
I've made a decision.
Huh?
About the ship.
It's time to part
ways with the Merry.
We'll say goodbye
to her here.
♪ ending song ♪
[USOPP] Hey, you're
taking this joke too far!
[LUFFY] It's not a joke.
We're leaving the Merry behind.
[USOPP] Don't be
ridiculous! You're lying!
[NAMI]
Usopp, please.
[LUFFY]
She can't be fixed anymore!
She's gonna sink!
Understand?
[NAMI]
Luffy!
[USOPP] I don't care what
you say, I won't abandon her!
You hear me?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece :
"Big Fight Under the Moon!
The Pirate Flag
Flutters with Sorrow!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!