Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
I'll have a
"Rainbow Rock", please.
That's an excellent choice.
This is the life!
Who would have ever thought
that when we sailed
through the Florian Triangle
that we would end up in a
fabulous place like this?
[NAMI]
Right?
I'm so glad that you
find our accommodations
to your liking.
On Spa Island, we proudly
boast 10 heated swimming pools,
three simulated river pools,
and pools dedicated to diving.
We also have
waterfalls for meditation,
cola baths, milk baths,
you name it!
There are more than 50
varieties of spas available.
For those who
enjoy playing games,
we have in-pool table tennis
as well as an in-pool casino.
As for food, our
restaurant has top chefs
providing delicious cuisine
from all over the world
in gigantic proportions.
Our top priority is
the pleasure of our guests.
And I, Doran,
the proprietor here,
find my own pleasure
making sure this happens.
On occasion, some guests
are lucky enough
to witness rainbows
and candy rain
at our establishment as well.
Oh yeah!
I've heard of that!
It's some kind of
natural occurrence
people call "the Gem
of the Ocean", right?
But there hasn't
been a confirmed sighting
of that phenomenon
in quite some time.
Which is why I noted that
the guests who do see them
are considered quite lucky.
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
I think we're about to be
some of those lucky guests.
Girugiru!
Oh, surely you jest.
It's hard to believe
you made this place
way out here yourself.
That must have
been quite a task.
Girugirugiru!
It was,
but when you bring in over
10 billion berries a year
in profits and become an
officially recognized resort
by the World Government,
it makes it all worthwhile.
We also have a highly
sophisticated security team
so civilians can
enjoy themselves
without a care in the world.
It truly is a paradise.
Over 10 billion
berries a year?
And of course pirates
can relax here, as well.
Girugirugiru!
We do appreciate that.
Certainly, madam.
Just thought I'd
make note of it.
Pirates, civilians,
it doesn't matter.
As long as you're
a paying customer,
consider yourself
safe here in our care.
Girugirugiru!
A man after your own heart.
Wouldn't you agree?
Over 10 billion berries!
Berries, berries, berries!
[LUFFY]
The Slow-Slow Menace!
"Silver Fox" Foxy Returns!
[LUFFY]
Ready? Go!
[giggling]
What in the heck is this?
Whoa, it's candy!
It's raining candy!
It's just that one cloud!
And looks like
it's only falling on us!
We're so super lucky!
Super lucky!
That's too much!
[shouting and laughing]
[laughing]
[GIRL] What a bunch of
dummies! You're funny!
[USOPP]
Hey! What is that?
Oh, you mean this guy?
That's Nukki,
he's a sea raccoon.
He can transform into anything.
[NUKKI]
Nukki!
--That's awesome!
He just said that this
girl's name is Rina.
It's a talking raccoon-dog!
I am not a raccoon-dog!
I'm a reindeer!
You have a raccoon.
Can't you tell?
[RINA'S stomach growling]
It sounds like you're hungry.
Uh, yeah.
[LUFFY]
How about this?
It's the official meal
of a pirate captain!
Pirate?
You mean you guys are--
The name's Luffy.
And I'm the man who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
And I'm Chopper!
Ship's doctor!
Captain Usopp here!
The ship's sniper!
So even silly
people can be pirates!
I thought all
pirates were scary!
It's nice to meet you!
And thanks for the food!
Hey, what's wrong?
I wonder if my
big sister wants some.
[LUFFY, CHOPPER, USOPP]
Big sister?
[RINA]
Hey, Sayo!
Some appetite, huh?
This little guy
will eat anything!
Well, of course!
Sea raccoons are omnivores.
Does that include this?
--As if!
What in the hell is that?
[SANJI] Wait! You're saying
it can change into anything?
[LUFFY]
Pretty much.
Make yourself beautiful!
The hottest, sexiest thing ever!
[NUKKI]
Nukki! Nukki!
[SANJI] I really walked right
into that one, didn't I?
No, I mean like
that girl over there!
Turn into Nami for me!
[groaning]
[SANJI]
Too small!
What an idiot!
How could I be so--
Even though she's tiny,
she's still Nami!
Nami-swan!
[NAMI]
Moron!
You see?
I told you they're
a bunch of weirdoes!
Do you wanna go, sis?
Thanks for the food!
We appreciate it!
No problem.
You're leaving?
Yes. Thank you again
for all your kindness.
[CHOPPER]
Sanji, are you all right?
Goodbye, Luffy!
Thanks again
for the food and fun!
Aw, do you have to leave
so soon, little sea raccoon?
You're hopeless.
[FOXY]
Fehfehfehfeh!
[FOXY] I've been looking
everywhere for you two.
Fehfehfehfeh!
[HAMBURG]
Pupupupu!
Don't you ever give up?
I can't believe I had
to chase you two brats
all the way out here.
You really gave
me the run-around.
Now, if you come
along quietly...
Hold on a second.
There seem to be some
other familiar faces here.
[FOXY] So this is where you've
been, my dear old rival!
Straw Hat Luffy!
It's been a long time!
Do I know you?
[FOXY] "Do I know you?"
He doesn't remember me!
It's okay, boss!
Don't be sad!
[HAMBURG]
Pupupupu!
Hey, hold on a second.
[LUFFY] You're the guy
Zoro and Sanji beat up!
[FOXY] He's doing it on purpose!
Playing with my mind!
It'll be okay, Boss!
Fine! Let me remind you, then!
You ended my
undefeated winning streak.
You stole my pirate flag.
I challenged you
to a Davy Back fight!
Does any of this ring a bell?
Oh! I remember now!
Stupid splithead guy!
Dammit! That's Silver Fox Foxy!
Hey. Be careful, Luffy.
I remember him shooting
some kinda weird beams.
Beams, huh?
[SANJI] True, but we already
know how to avoid them.
It shouldn't be a problem.
Fehfehfehfeh!
I've got a new trick
or two up my sleeve!
Observe!
Is that made of mirrors?
[PORCHE]
High Speed Rotation Mirror Ball!
[FOXY] Followed by
the new Slow-Slow Beam!
That's gotta be
against the rules!
[USOPP]
I... hate... that... beam!
Dammit!
[FOXY]
Fehfehfehfeh!
[FOXY] Anyone caught in the
path of my Slow-Slow Beam
will remain under its
effects for thirty seconds.
I'll take that.
[FOXY]
Fehfehfehfeh!
So, do you remember me now,
Straw Hat Luffy?
[FOXY]
Fehfehfehfeh!
In about ten seconds,
you'll drop like rocks.
Now nine!
Now eight!
[FOXY]
And seven!
My, what a
glorious bath that was!
My skin's sparkling
and squeaky clean!
Well, it would be
if I had any skin!
Yohohohoho!
[FRANKY] What the heck
are you guys doing?
[LUFFY]
Franky! Brook!
Kick those guy's asses!
[FRANKY]
Weapons Left!
[RANDOM SPA GOER 382A]
What's going on?
[screaming]
[NUKKI]
Nukki?
It's Luffy!
[ROBIN]
Cien Fleur!
[SANJI]
Thanks, Robin!
[USOPP]
You saved us!
Is everyone
all right down there?
Oh, goodness!
You had me worried!
[RINA]
How did you do that, Luffy?
Well, see...
I'm kinda made of rubber.
Plus, there's no way
I'd ever lose to splithead.
It would seem you've
added two new members
to your crew,
haven't you, Straw Hat?
Boss, look at that!
It's a living skeleton!
[FOXY] This isn't over yet,
you bastards!
Mirror Ball, round two!
[FOXY] Idiot, what are you
doing? Close the door!
Now Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
[screaming]
[MALE SPA ATTENDANT 382A]
Everyone, remain calm!
What the heck
is going on, huh?
[NAMI] Listen, I have something
I'd like to ask the two of you.
[SAYO]
What is it?
[NAMI]
The thing you're holding.
That's what Foxy
was after, wasn't it?
Your notebook.
[RINA]
Foxy?
[NAMI]
That pirate we just beat.
He doesn't like us, but I don't
think that we were his target.
So that must mean--
You girls are hiding
something important
in that notebook.
I'm right, aren't I?
Yeah, you're right.
The notebook has
special instructions
on how to make a gem!
Whoa! Did you say "make a gem"?
Rina, wait!
It's okay.
Just leave everything to me.
I know these people are
pirates, but they're different.
I think we can
put our trust in them.
And they're strong!
If you and I try
to handle this alone,
I'm starting to think we won't
be able to pull it off at all!
[RINA]
Here.
This is our daddy's notebook.
Oh, wow! Check it out!
They're scientific formulas!
Our daddy was an inventor.
Those are all his formulas.
Plus the directions for making
that gem I told you about.
Do you two actually know
what all this stuff means?
Sayo knows how to read it!
I don't know
what any of it means.
[NAMI]
That's amazing, Sayo!
Hey, wait.
There's also a sea chart
mapped inside here.
[USOPP] That steam
thing looks important.
[RINA]
That's the secret memo.
I think it's a hint as
to how the gem is made.
[NAMI]
Yeah? Seriously?
[RINA] The stuff in the
notebook is supposed to be
99% of everything
you need to make it.
[USOPP] So this little map
is a clue to the other 1%?
[SAYO]
That's right.
I'm betting that this
steam stands for a spa,
which means that this
"X" is somewhere here
on Spa Island.
Mmm-hmm.
That's just what
we were thinking,
which is why we snuck
onto the island.
Nice! Way to go!
[SAYO] But we've
searched everywhere
and haven't found anything.
Not even a clue as to what
or where that "X" could be.
It's hard to believe that
with all the other information,
the only way to make it work
is with some mysterious clue.
Well Foxy followed
them all the way out here
to find that clue, didn't he?
If he went to that much
trouble, it's gotta be real!
[RINA]
It might be a fake.
Rina.
In fact, I'm positive
this thing's a fake.
Dad doesn't know
how to make a gem.
What did you say?
Our daddy was a
moron and a big liar!
He was such an idiot!
I hate him!
He never did anything right!
And this's the same!
[RINA]
Daddy!
[SAYO]
Welcome back!
[RINA'S DAD]
Sayo! Rina!
Thank goodness you're here.
It's terrible news!
What is?
This Golden Horned-Beetle,
that's what!
According to legends,
when this thing appears,
the village of the one that
found it will be destroyed!
This is awful!
[RINA]
Daddy, look.
The gold is rubbing off.
[screams]
[BRATTY BOY 382A]
He totally fell for it!
[BRATTY BOY 382B]
Ha! That moron!
[RINA]
Scram!
What a bunch of stupid jerks!
The beetle was a fake!
What a relief!
It's fake!
That means the village
won't be destroyed!
It was a lie!
Isn't that wonderful?
[RINA] Dad loved our village and
he was proud to live there.
[RINA] Because that was the
place our mom was born.
[RINA'S DAD]
This research I'm doing
might save all the people
of this village someday.
Everyone will be able to live
their lives as they please
without a care in the world.
So what's the research about?
How can it help?
I'll tell you!
It's a way to create gems!
[laughing]
But that's impossible.
Gems aren't just
something you "make".
They're things you find.
[laughing]
Your old man
sounds really funny!
He's not funny!
He's an awful scientist
and an awful dad!
[RINA] Three years ago, he left
home to do some research,
but he never came back.
[RINA] He abandoned us,
just like that.
So we lived there together.
Just the two of us.
People made fun of us,
but we ignored them
and made the best of things.
I couldn't help but think,
"Daddy isn't here anymore.
He must have died."
[RINA]
And then, one month ago...
[RINA] Nukki came back
to us out of nowhere
with that notebook
in his mouth.
[RINA] We found a letter
folded up and stuck inside.
You know what it said?
It said, "Dear daughters,
please complete the research
that I began".
[RINA] Isn't that
the dumbest thing?
He left us to go who
knows where to study this,
and he never came back!
And now we're here risking our
lives to do the same thing
because he asked us to!
I hate that stupid man!
He left us behind to go chase
some crazy dream he has!
I bet this map is just
as fake as that gem is!
Why is the last part a clue?
It's like some
sort of lame test!
Man, your dad's a
pretty funny guy, huh?
Gem making
sounds pretty cool.
I really wanna see one.
What?
But... Wait.
Were you even listening
to what I was saying?
[ZORO]
Ah! Here you are!
Just waking up, eh, Zoro?
[RINA]
I'm talking to you!
If it's so stupid,
why are you here looking
for it in the first place?
I'm not looking for it!
My sister is!
I'm only here as her bodyguard!
Wait, you're her bodyguard?
[RINA]
Yeah.
Big sis says she'll keep
looking for the secret
and find it no matter what,
so I'm here to protect her.
Got it?
Hey, what's
going on over here?
[SAYO]
No, it's true!
There is a way
to create that gem!
No matter what you say,
I believe him.
Big sister...
Listen.
Everyone, please save--
[SAYO screams]
[RINA] No!
Sayo! Where are you?
[DORAN]
Girugirugiru!
I have the girl.
Now...
If you want to see her again,
you'll do just as I say.
Is that Doran?
[CHOPPER]
Who the heck is Doran?
The owner and
proprietor of this place.
What the hell is he doing?
[DORAN]
Girugirugirugiru!
All of you are going
to search for that secret
in the notebook for me.
If you find it,
I'll give back the girl.
[DORAN]
Girugirugirugirugiru!
Holy crap on a stick!
Foxy wasn't the
only one after it!
Luffy! What are we gonna do?
[SAYO] Rina, please!
Finish the research!
Don't let Dad's dream
fall into the hands
of that stupid jerk!
[RINA] Dad's research
was nothing but lies!
I can't believe he took Sayo
over this stupid notebook!
Luffy, please, save her!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"The Great
Scramble for Treasure!
Collapse, Spa Island!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!