[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[LUFFY laughs]
Gum-Gum Balloon!
[grunts]
Nami?
We've been had!
My treasure!
[LUFFY]
"The Pirate Ship Disappears!
Fortress Battle, Round #2!"
[DRAKE]
They're getting away!
All ships full speed!
Now!
[NAVIGATOR]
But, sir!
With all due respect,
we're in shallow waters!
If we sail headlong
into that smoke,
we run the risk of
hitting the reef!
[DRAKE]
I said full speed ahead!
[NAVIGATOR]
But, sir!
Do you know what's
going to happen if we let
those pirates escape from us?
This fortress and everyone
who serves here will become the
laughingstock of the Marines,
we'll be synonymous
with failure!
[NAVIGATOR]
We will?
You really think so, Lieutenant?
[DRAKE]
I know so!
And in fact, I'm sure this will
be the last straw for Navarone!
Those bigwigs at HQ have
been waiting for an excuse
to shut us down
once and for all!
Do you understand me, sailor?!
[NAVIGATOR grumbles]
[DRAKE]
So tell me!
Are you going to allow that
to happen to Navarone?
No, sir!
Attention, all ships!
Full speed ahead!
Sail through the Sea Gate!
[LUFFY laughing]
Whoa!
The open sea! Keep her
on a straight course, guys!
[NAMI]
No, turn around!
Huh?
We can't leave yet!
Full reverse!
Don't just stand there!
Those lousy Marines
stole all our gold!
Turn us around! We have to go
back to the fortress right now!
Are you nuts?
Maybe you didn't notice,
Nami, but we almost got killed
breaking out of that place!
Zoro's right!
You're completely nuts!
I'm quite sane right now, thank
you! Look, what's the point
in escaping if it's without
all our hard-earned gold?
Wow, whenever money's involved,
Nami gets really serious.
I love that side of Nami, too!
But we're so close to
that big hole we made!
All we gotta do is just
sail through it ya know.
[NAMI] Hey, aren't we
supposed to be pirates?
[LUFFY]
Mm-hm.
Well, have you ever heard of
pirates leaving gold behind?
Wouldn't that be the worst
thing a pirate could do?
Yeah, I guess.
So, it's decided then!
Let's get our treasure!
Crew, make a U-turn and take us
back to the fortress
on the double!
--[CHOPPER] Got it!
-- [SANJI] Aye!
Anything for you, Captain Nami!
[CHOPPER]
Right rudder, full!
[SANJI]
U-Turn!
Hold on, you guys!
What are they doing?
Hey! Be careful!
[NAMI] That's it, guys!
Just keep it up!
[bells clanging]
[gasps]
Sound the alarm bell!
Much louder!
With all this smoke, it's the
only way we can avoid collisions
with our fellow ships!
[bells clanging]
[LUFFY]
You hear that?
Please be quiet, Luffy!
Sounds like wind chimes.
They're alarm bells. You use
them to signal your location
to other ships when
you're in a fog!
[bells continue clanging]
And those sound like they're
coming straight toward us!
How was that, Nami? Should we
keep her on a rightward course?
[NAMI]
No! Left rudder, full!
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[NAMI] If we don't, we're
gonna crash into that big ship
that's headed right for us!
Anything for you,
my sweet thing!
[bells continue clanging]
[USOPP yelps]
[gasps]
[NAMI]
We're gonna crash!
Hah, that sure was close.
To think we almost died without
ever laying eyes
on our gold again...
How do things look up ahead?
Is the coast clear?
[bells clanging rapidly]
Uh, oh!
[LUFFY] Sounds like a lot
more than last time!
I see one, two, oh, no!
There's a whole flotilla
of ships bearing down on us!
We're dead meat!
So, Nami?
What'll it be, my sweet?
Left rudder or right rudder?
--[NAMI] Left! Quickly!
--[BOTH] Huh?
If we don't we're gonna
get smashed to pieces!
[NAMI, USOPP, and ZORO groan]
What's going on out there?
I don't know! Just do
what Nami says, Chopper!
She's the best
navigator in the world!
Ah! I don't think
we're gonna make it!
[gasps]
[whimpering]
We... We made it.
Keep her headed straight, guys!
We can't keep sailing
blind like this!
It's too dangerous here! We've
gotta get out of this smoke!
Won't they spot us if we do?
Yeah! We'll be sitting ducks
once we leave this smoke!
Those ships'll take
aim and then boom!
They'll blast us to
the bottom of the ocean
and we'll be fish food!
I can't die yet.
[NAMI]
Do you have any better ideas?
--Miss Navigator...
--[NAMI] Huh?
I was able to do a
little bit of research.
It turns out that this fortress
used to station quite a lot more
troops and warships
than it currently does.
Uh...
Well, thank you for sharing,
but this is not the time for
a stupid history lesson, Robin!
[ROBIN] It seems that this
fortress has been a victim of
military downsizing. As a
result, many of its areas
have been shut down,
and there are plenty
of unused docks around the base.
Plenty of unused docks, huh?
That's great! Wow! Thanks,
Robin! You're a lifesaver!
Okay guys, here's the plan!
We're going to hide the Merry
in one of those old docks!
[USOPP] Uh? How do we
even know where to find one?
[NAMI] Just follow my
orders and this map!
[DRAKE]
What the...?
[grunts]
You there, call the
cannoneers at the sea gate!
Ask if the Straw Hat
ship passed through!
Yes, sir!
Sea Gate cannons! This is
Drake's flagship calling!
Have any of you spotted
the Straw Hats' ship?
What?
Sir! They say
the only ship that's
passed through the
sea gate is ours!
Just us?
Where are they?
They couldn't have snuck past
the canonneers sight unseen!
And then somehow sailed
off beyond the horizon
in such a short amount of time?
No, that would be impossible.
[SNAIL PHONE rings]
Huh?
I'm sorry Commander,
but it looks like the
pirates escaped, Sir.
We lost sight of them
when they hit the open sea.
I don't know how to explain it!
It's like they completely
vanished into thin air!
[JONATHAN]
Just as I thought.
[DRAKE]
Sir?
[JONATHAN] Never mind. You
and your men did well, Drake.
Now come on back to port. I'll
share with you my plan on how
we're going to catch
the Straw Hats.
They haven't gotten
away from us just yet.
Nor will they even try
while we still have what
they hold most dear
in this fortress.
[SHEPHERD] Unhand me this
instant or you'll be
court-martialed for insulting
a superior officer!
[GUARD A] Hear that?
He's gonna court-martial us!
[GUARD B]
Drop the act.
You two! Let that man go!
[[GUARD A, GUARD B]
Huh?
[GUARD A, GUARD B gasping]
Please accept
our apologies, Major!
[GUARD A, GUARD B gasping]
[SHEPHERD]
Finally figured it out, huh?
That I'm not some mangy pirate,
but a Special Inspector.
I'm Major Shepherd!
[JONATHAN]
Hmm...
You Straw Hats are probably
holed up somewhere around here.
Well in that case,
let the games continue.
All I need to do now
is sit back and wait.
You'll reveal yourselves.
[MARINE B] Man, searchin' for
those pirates is wearin' me out.
Well, this delicious food
should give us some energy,
and then it's back to searching.
Wait! This doesn't taste
anything like the food
from this morning!
You're right! Compared to the
eats we had this morning,
this stuff tastes like dirt!
Hey! Just what are you
cooks trying to pull here?
Give us some of the good grub!
[MARINES] Give us good grub!
Give us good grub!
Jessica! Do you hear that?
The soldiers are
complaining about the food!
What do we do?
Jessica, please. You have to
let us use his recipes.
No way.
How dare you even suggest
such a thing in this kitchen.
[VICE HEAD CHEF]
Please, hear me out!
It's true that he was a pirate,
but he was still
an excellent cook!
His food tantalized the palates
of the soldiers who ate here.
Isn't that the goal of each and
every one of us in the kitchen?
The troops loved his cooking!
In fact, it's his food they're
asking for right now, Jessica!
So, what's it gonna be?
Please say yes!
We're begging you, Jessica!
[COOKS]
Please, Jessica!
[COOKS gasping]
All right, listen up!
We're going to learn how to
make food just as delicious
and mouth-watering
as the pirate's was.
But as for today, we're
going to swallow our pride
and use his recipes
to feed our troops!
And you're right.
He wasn't a pirate when he
was working in this kitchen.
He was a cook.
[JESSICA] And he knew the most
important thing was to satisfy
the people eating his food!
[COOKS]
Jessica!
[JESSICA] What are you
standing around for?
We've got men to feed!
[COOKS]
Yeah!
[USOPP]
Well? What do we do now, guys?
[ZORO] If you ask me, I think
we should just head back to the
gate and make a break for
it while we still can.
You've got a point there.
The Marines mean business.
It's too bad we have to
leave the gold behind,
but our lives
are more important.
You're the captain, Luffy.
What do you think?
We need to get our gold, but
I need something to eat first!
I heard ya. Gimme a sec
and I'll whip something up.
Um, the storerooms
looked kinda empty.
[SANJI]
There's gotta be something
left to eat around here.
Just so I understand you
correctly, you guys are okay
with us leaving this
place without our gold?
[CHOPPER, ZORO, LUFFY, USOPP]
Mm-hmm.
Well, that's too bad,
'cause you know,
pirate treasure is
always divided up.
Even after
splitting up the loot,
we'd all have more gold than
we'd know what to do with.
Just think of all the
stuff we could have bought.
Hey, wait! I wanna go
and buy some stuff!
[NAMI]
Like what?
Ooh, I'll tell you what I
wanna buy! A big gold statue!
Ooh, Nami, over here!
I wanna buy a bunch
of new medical books!
Ones that that'll
teach me all about
the latest medical
procedures and operations!
New pots, frying pans,
silverware, giant mousetrap...
Wow, even after all that,
there'll still be
a lot left over.
I could buy lotsa booze.
--[NAMI] Right.
--[ALL] Uh-huh.
But first, I take an
extra cut: 80 percent!
[ALL]
Are you nuts?!
It's not for me.
Oh, yeah? Then who? And why
should they receive a bigger
share than the rest of us, huh?!
It's for a special lady.
We're going to set aside
the gold to pay for the
repairs we need to make.
A lady? Oh, wait,
you mean the Merry?
[NAMI]
That's right.
Isn't it about time we paid her
back for all she's done for us?
Well, come to think of it,
the Going Merry has carried us
for a long time now, hasn't she?
Ever since I joined up and left
my village in the East Blue.
[MERRY]
It's a slightly older model,
but I personally designed
it and she sails like a dream.
She has a carvel-make caravel
with lateen sails and
a central stern rudder.
She's a fine ship
and her name...
...is the Going Merry!
Get on already!
Huh?
We're friends, right? So get on.
[USOPP] This is it.
I'm really a pirate captain now!
[LUFFY] Don't be stupid,
Usopp! I'm the captain!
[ZORO, NAMI, LUFFY laughing]
We've had so many adventures.
Lots of good times and
made so many memories.
And me? I'm finally
gonna leave this island.
[NAMI]
I'm going now, o-okay?
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI]
I'm off.
Hey, don't forget. The Merry
was also with us when we crossed
that crazy Reverse Mountain,
and burst into the Grand Line.
I've gotta be dreaming!
It's impossible.
The ocean really is
flowing up the mountain!
[SANJI, USOPP]
We made it!
[LUFFY]
Whoa!
Look how high we are!
We're in the clouds!
Woo-hoo!
[LUFFY]
This is insane!
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
I can see it!
This is the greatest
sea in the whole world!
The Grand Line!
Somewhere out there
the One Piece is waiting!
And we're gonna find it!
Let's go!
Don't forget sky island.
Trust me.
I'm a navigator, aren't I?
[SANJI]
Thank you, Nami!
All right, gang!
Nami's leadin' the way!
[LUFFY, CHOPPER, USOPP, ZORO]
Yeah!
[LUFFY]
We're flying!
Yeah! We're headed to the sky!
Nami! Good job!
I think I love you!
Yeah, I even risked
my life to save it
when it was carried
to Upper Yard!
[CHOPPER whimpers]
[screams]
[CHOPPER]
Stop it! Please!
Just stop burning the ship!
This is gonna hurt.
[CHOPPER yells]
Yeah, then that mysterious
someone fixed the ship for us.
[thud]
I saw somebody, I swear!
When you think about it,
this ship's gone
through a lot for us.
And that's exactly why
we need to give her
some tender, loving care.
[USOPP] Good idea!
The Going Merry's Great Repair!
[LUFFY]
Let's do it!
It's settled! And since we don't
know how much the repairs'll be,
we'll just hold off dividing
up the treasure until we do.
[SANJI] Those goons took all
the food from the storeroom,
but lucky for us,
they didn't touch the fridge.
Here. Dig in.
Huh. I've been wondering
how much longer
Usopp's half-ass
repairs were gonna last.
Hey, I'm a sniper,
not a shipwright!
But yeah, Mechao
said the same thing.
It needs professional repairs.
Yeah, right. It's time we took
the Merry to a real shipyard,
and got some honest-to-
goodness shipwrights
to give her the
repairs she needs.
So, there are people who can
fix ships better than Usopp?
Yep! Sometimes when you
need a job done right,
you've gotta go see
a professional!
[LUFFY]
That's it!
We've gotta get a
shipwright for our crew!
Our journey's far
from over, right?
[USOPP, ZORO, NAMI, CHOPPER]
Mm.
[LUFFY] We really need
someone with those skills.
[USOPP, ZORO, NAMI, CHOPPER]
Mm-hmm.
And the Merry
isn't just our ship!
She's our home, too!
So let's go find us a shipwright
who can keep the Merry safe!
Well, I'm impressed.
Whoa. He got to the point.
That's pretty rare.
Well, that sounds really good
to me, Luffy! Let's go do it!
Uh... That's what I just said!
I just hope we can
find somebody good!
We should get a musician, too!
Let's forget that one.
The shipwright's a great idea,
but haven't you all
forgotten something?
[CHOPPER, LUFFY, USOPP, ZORO]
What's that?
[NAMI] We have to get
our gold back first!
[LUFFY]
Oh, yeah, right.
Well, do we have any idea
where they may have taken it?
[USOPP]
To a vault, I bet.
Well, duh, genius! Where else?
The problem is we have no clue
where that vault may be!
[USOPP]
Hey, you don't hafta be rude!
I'd say here.
It's just a guess, of course,
but if I were going to hide gold
inside Navarone,
this multi-lock storage vault
seems like it would
be the ideal place.
You're so smart!
You're right! That does seem
like the most obvious place!
All right, guys!
Let's go bust into that vault
and get our gold back!
But what do we do
about the Merry?
We can't just leave her here!
She's sure to get
spotted eventually!
"Hide a tree in a forest
and hide a big ship
among big ships!"
[NAMI, SANJI, USOPP sighing]
So, that's your big plan?
I think I liked you better
when you weren't so serious.
I don't know if it'll help
or not, but we are at a dock
where ships used to be
constructed and repaired.
When we sailed in just now,
I couldn't help but notice
an abundance of abandoned
materials lying around.
Ya don't say! Well,
that gives me a great idea!
[USOPP whispering]
[USOPP]
Well?
[ALL]
Yeah!
[hammering]
[USOPP sighs]
[USOPP]
Well... Whaddaya think, guys?
Not bad if I do say so myself!
At least we don't have to worry
about the Merry getting
stolen again, right?
[ZORO] Gluing paper all over
the ship to disguise it...
What a great idea.
[SANJI]
I don't know, guys.
It looks like
a three-year-old did it.
You think that's gonna
fool anyone for very long?
Yeah, of course it will!
It looks just like one of
the Marine's warships,
no doubt about it!
--It sure does!
--You're nuts!
Great!
Now all we have to do
is get our treasure back!
Operation Gold Recovery
commences at midnight! Got it?
[ALL]
Got it!
[CHOPPER]
Um, why don't we go right now?
[LUFFY] Well, 'cause
super-secret missions are
always better at midnight!
[CHOPPER]
Oh, I get it now!
[USOPP]
Um, you guys are joking, right?
A future lies before us
waiting to begin
Let's take to the wind!
and search the world for answers
to all the questions
in our minds
Exploring day and night we'll...
...live out our
dreams in paradise!
And that's why...
We're running, and running,
traveling along an open road
Never letting go of
what we came to do
We're here to see this through!
We can't lose, can't lose,
nothing on earth
can stop us now
'Cause we're not afraid
of our own destiny
We Dream and live
our lives free!
[USOPP] Now we don't have to
worry about the Merry, but wait!
Hold on, you guys!
Are we just gonna go like this?
Jeez! Seven people running
around will stand out too much!
Here, I'll tell you
my super-secret plan!
On the next One Piece!
[LUFFY]
Hey, I do this part!
On the next One Piece!
"The Gold and Waver
Recovery Operations!"
[USOPP] I'm gonna be
a heroic warrior of the sea!
[LUFFY]
You, too?!