[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[VIVI, NAMI roar]
[MISS VALENTINE shrieks]
[NAMI]
That was really hot...!
Couldn't you have
thought up another plan?
[MR. 5]
Huh?
[MR. 3 laughs]
[MR. 3] Let's play a little
game of hide and seek...
Can you figure out
which one's me?
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum... Stamp!
[MR. 3]
Ugh!
[groans]
But... how... did you know...?
Instinct.
[LUFFY] "Farewell, Giant Island!
Head for Alabasta."
[BROGGY sobs]
[LUFFY]
Whoa, look at that...!
His tears are making a rainbow!
[BROGGY sobbing]
With all this crying,
we'll drown here.
It's practically a waterfall.
So sad... Master... Broggy!
Huh?!
Dorry... you're... alive!
[DORRY] I must have
lost consciousness...
[pants]
[SANJI]
Mr. 0...
I've heard that name
somewhere before...
Wasn't that the
name of the boss guy
that Vivi was so frightened of?
Which would mean...
...that the person
who is on the other end
of this transponder snail...
[SANJI] ...is one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
It's been a long time since
I issued your orders Mr. 3...
What's happening on that island?
[SANJI] All right,
so I guess this Mr. 3 character
is the owner of this
transponder snail.
I think I have
this figured out now.
This little place here
is an enemy hideout,
and someone named Mr. 3
was ordered by someone
named Mr. 0 to come to
this island and kill Vivi.
Damn it...
What was I thinking...?
This was no time for me to
be out on a hunting trip...!
I hope that
they're all still okay.
Shit...
[MR. 0] Well, are you
going to answer me?
When I ask a question,
I expect an answer...
Have you eliminated Princess
Vivi and the Straw Hats
as you were ordered?
Oh, yeah, the mission
was successful.
I eliminated all those
pesky brats like you said to.
Your secret is
completely protected,
so there's no need to keep
going after them anymore.
I see... so...
As we speak, the Unluckies
are headed your way
in order to confirm the
success of your mission
and to deliver
a certain package.
The Unluckies. Of course...
And a package?
It's an Eternal Pose that will
point you to Alabasta Kingdom.
Once that arrives,
you and Miss Golden Week
will head for Alabasta.
It's time for the
next phase of the plan.
We are about to
begin embarking upon
our most important
operation to date...
Details will follow
after you reach Alabasta.
Wait for my orders.
[SANJI]
Huh?
What the...
What are those...
Mr. 3...! What was that?!
Oh, uh...
It's nothing... really.
What the hell is that?
[SANJI]
Hmm?
So I guess you're trying
to kill me, huh...?
Well, monkey, bring it on.
All right, you... What now...?
So what are you gonna do now,
you oversized chicken?!
Hey...
What's going on...?
Answer me, Mr. 3...
Hey...! Well... nothing...
It's just...
...that damn Straw Hat
was still alive.
It's okay, though.
I finished him off real good.
No need to worry.
[MR. 0] What do you mean
he was still alive...?
I believe that just a moment ago
you said that your mission
was completed successfully...
Isn't that correct?
[SANJI]
Yes, that is what I said...
I mean, I absolutely thought
that it was completed then.
But that Straw Hat guy,
he's really a lot tougher
than you'd expect...
So let me see if I understand...
The report you gave
me was a complete lie?
Well, yeah,
when you put it that way,
I guess the report
wasn't the truth,
But now, I've gotten rid
of that Straw Hat for sure,
so there's no need for you
to send anyone else after him
or the others...
[MR. 0]
Very well...
Take the pose and head straight
to Alabasta from
there immediately.
Do you understand me?
[NAMI]
But how are you still alive?
The weapons...
They saved me...
[USOPP]
Weapons?
Oh, yeah!
That makes sense!
Not even weapons
that were made in Elbaf
could hold up after
a hundred years
of giants dueling
to the death with 'em!
They must be dull by now!
[sighs]
Now, that's a relief...
[chuckles]
It's a miracle, really!
[BROGGY sobs]
[DORRY]
Broggy, would you let go...?
I'm a little sore, here.
I'm so glad you're
still alive, Dorry...
It's amazing!
Gya, ba, ba, ba!
Gya, gya, gya, gya!
[ZORO]
Come on, this wasn't a miracle.
The fact that those
weapons are even intact
after a century of fighting
is the miraculous part.
They should be scrap by now.
I'm surprised
they lasted this long.
What a day this was...
Thank you, God of Elbaf,
for this wonderful day!
Oh, is that true, Broggy?
You're saying that fighting
me while I was injured,
cutting me down, and knocking
me out was all wonderful.
Don't be an idiot, Dorry.
That's not what I'm saying,
and you know it.
Would you keep your
hands off my wounds?
Gya, gya, gya, gya!
Gya, ba, ba, ba!
[DORRY] You try doing that
again and see how far you get!
Yeah?! I could take
you down in a heartbeat!
[BROGGY growls]
Yeah...!
[laughs]
Duel...! Fight!
You two are fighting
again, already?!
[MR. 0] We will have
no more radio contact
from now on, understand?
If Marines were to catch on
to what we're doing,
that would be most unfortunate.
From this point on, all of my
orders will be sent via letter,
following the usual protocol.
That will be all, Mr. 3...
Good luck on your mission.
[MR. 0]
Miss All Sunday.
Yes, sir?
[MR. 0]
I want you to send Mr. 2
to Little Garden immediately.
Huh?
Mr. 3 is on his way from
Little Garden to Alabasta.
I want you to see
that he is eliminated...
Perhaps that might be...
a little extreme, Crocodile.
[MR. 0] We still have plenty
of agents to spare.
Are you arguing with me,
Miss All Sunday?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
No...
I'll make the
arrangements at once.
Consider it done.
[MR. 0]
Hmm...
Well, he finally hung up...
Now... I wonder
who these guys were...
They sure are funny looking.
What's this?
[BROGGY]
Gya, ba, ba, ba, ba!
Gya, gya, gya, gya!
We've been fighting so long
that we'd completely forgotten
about the bounties
that were put on our heads.
It has been a long time.
But I'm the whole reason
that the Baroque Works agents
came here in the first place...
It's my fault.
None of that anymore... Okay...?
Yeah, come on, Vivi.
Why are you so sad?
Here, have a rice cracker.
[NAMI] Uh, guys,
where did you get those?
[LUFFY] I know!
Let's have a rice cracker party!
Rice crackers aren't
that exciting, though.
[LUFFY] Sure they are!
We can even toast with them.
You see...?
Nobody's blaming you.
[LUFFY]
Cheers!
[USOPP]
Hey, Luffy, don't do that!
You can't just go
wasting food like that.
Seriously,
you should know better.
[LUFFY]
Hey, what are you doing?!
Who said you could
have my cracker?
Give it here!
[USOPP]
It's done! It's mine now!
[LUFFY]
No, it's not!
What's with you?
[NAMI]
Nothing... Just a bug bite.
All right, I still can't believe
we have to wait here a year
just for the Log Pose to reset.
I know...
It's definitely something
we should be worried about!
All of you helped save us
from those other guys.
If we can, we would really
like to return the favor.
Well, maybe you guys could do
something about our Log Pose,
so we won't be stuck here.
Huh...
I'm afraid the Log Pose
is the one thing
that we can't help you with.
[SANJI]
Ahhh!
Nami, dear! Vivi, my love!
And all the rest of you!
Hey...! Sanji!
You're all still okay...!
I'm so happy, so happy!
Of course, he's happy,
the big useless jerk...!
He shows up after we've
taken care of everything!
[laughs]
[shrieks]
[SANJI]
What the hell is going on?!
Is one of you guys Mr. 3?
Wait... and just how do you
know about Mr. 3 anyway?
Nami...
You look absolutely
amazing in that outfit!
[NAMI]
Say that again.
[SANJI]
Now, Nami...
If you stand around dressed like
that all day, you'll catch cold.
Here... Take my coat...
Oh, thank you...
[SANJI]
So, I've been a little busy.
I just finished talking
to that Mr. 0 guy over
a transponder snail.
Mr. 0?!
[SANJI]
Yeah, that guy...
I was talking to him in
this weird hideout place
I found in the jungle.
He thought I was
some guy called Mr. 3,
and I thought it would be a
good idea to let him believe it.
And since I had him on the line,
I went ahead and told him
that we were all dead.
[gasps]
So he thinks he doesn't have to
send people after us anymore.
So you're saying
that we're finally free
of people chasing us now that
we can't go anywhere anyway?
Oh... That is just perfect...
We can't go? Why?
Is there still something we
need to take care of here?
That's a real shame
after I managed
to get hold of this thing.
Uh... what...?
An Eternal Pose to
Alabasta...! All right!
Now, we can set sail! Woo‐hoo!
[NAMI]
Yes! Good job!
I knew something would happen!
Ohh...! Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, Sanji!
I was getting really
worried, thank you!
No, no!
It was all my pleasure.
I'm just glad I could
make you happy, Vivi.
[LUFFY]
All right, everyone!
Now we're having
a rice cracker party!
No way. Look, Luffy,
we don't have
enough left for a party.
There's only three.
[LUFFY]
What?!
It doesn't matter.
We don't have time
for that anyway.
Come on now, Captain.
We don't have time
to be sitting here.
Zoro! Hold on a sec.
So, uh, you forget
about our hunting contest?
[ZORO] Nope. Hate to
tell you this, but you lost.
I caught a rhino
that was this big.
That doesn't sound very tasty,
but I guess you can eat it.
Sounds just fine to me.
[BROGGY]
Hunting contest?
[DORRY]
Something about that
sounds familiar somehow.
[DORRY]
Hmm...
'Kay... Giant old guys,
it's really been
a lot of fun, but we gotta go.
[BROGGY]
Hm?
[DORRY]
Hmm?
Of course... Right...
We can tell you
need to get going.
It's too bad that you
have to leave so soon.
I hope you get to
your homeland in time.
Me too. Thank you.
[LUFFY] See ya...!
Try not to die anymore, okay?
Quaaaack!
Master...
I'm going to go
visit Elbaf someday!
You just wait and see.
My catch is much
bigger than yours.
[ZORO]
Hmph! You wish.
Our friends are setting sail.
That's right, and
we can't just sit here,
not when there's a monster
waiting for them in the sea.
So, Dorry,
how are your wounds doing?
These...? I think
I can live with them.
It's safe to say that our
weapons are about worn through.
Any regrets?
[BROGGY]
It's difficult to give up...
I've fought with this axe for
more than a hundred years,
but if it's a sacrifice for our
friends, then it's worth it.
Yeah, I agree...
[ZORO] See, I told you mine
was bigger than yours.
I win!
You should look closer!
My lizard is much bigger!
[ZORO] What, are you
blind or something...?
My rhino is obviously
so much larger
than your stupid lizard is.
It doesn't really matter...
They both look yummy.
[ZORO, SANJI]
Just shut up, Luffy!
[ZORO]
Yours doesn't even have horns...
[SANJI] What does that
have to do with anything...?
[ZORO]
Size! Yours is puny...
Children, how long
are you going to fight...?
We don't need all of it, anyway,
just cut up what we do need, so
we can get out of here, already.
Right...! Of course, Nami!
Hey, Usopp! Would you tell him
that I'm clearly the winner?
No, I really don't care.
Can't you just agree it's a tie?
I don't believe in ties.
I fight to win.
Just hurry up, you two!
[shuddering]
[SANJI]
Yeah!
[LUFFY]
Set sail!
[NAMI] The giants said that
going straight would take us
to the western end
of the island...
[LUFFY]
Hey! Couldn't you guys
have gotten any
more meat on board?
[ZORO]
Yeah, right.
[SANJI] We can't possibly
preserve any more than this.
It would just spoil
before we could eat it
[NAMI] Are you actively
trying to sink the ship?
Hey! Look at that;
it's the giants!
They must have come
down here to say goodbye.
[BROGGY] A great danger
still lies ahead of you.
[DORRY] It is an obstacle that
has always been here.
Trying to prevent people from
reaching the next island.
[NAMI]
Uhh...
Everyone of you
fought like true warriors
in order to protect
the pride of our duel...
And because you
were willing to do that,
no matter what
enemy you may face...
We will never let them
destroy your pride, friends.
You must have faith in
what we say. Go straight...
No matter what happens,
keep going straight.
Understand?
Yeah, got it...
What was that about?
I don't get it.
What'd he say?
No matter what happens,
we just go straight!
This is goodbye.
Let's meet again someday.
Absolutely.
Look! Over there!
Hello, Island‐Eater.
You will open the path...
In the name of Elbaf,
you will open it!
[roars]
[CREW screaming]
Quaaack!
It's a monster!
What the heck is
that guy? A goldfish?
It's a... giant goldfish?
Usopp, hey!
Start working the rudder
or we're gonna be eaten!
Hurry it up!
Yeah... I know but,
we have to go straight ahead...
Isn't that right, Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Mm‐hmm.
We sure do.
Don't be a moron, Luffy!
This isn't going to be anything
like what happened with Laboon.
Yeah, I know...
Now, calm down...
Here... I'll let you
have the last rice cracker.
I don't want a cracker!
If we don't turn the
ship around right now,
that thing is gonna eat us.
Quaaack!
Nami, just give it up.
Luffy! You really sure
we can trust
those little pals of yours?
[LUFFY]
Yup!
Are we actually
going to willingly
head straight into
that beast's belly?!
Uh‐huh! It's too
late to turn now!
You've sure gotten a
lot bigger, Island‐Eater...
Filthy goldfish.
And his size isn't
the only surprising
thing about him, either.
There's also the dung
that he produces
after he devours a island.
The size of that stuff
is quite impressive...
I recall one specimen that's
known as Nothing At All Island.
[DORRY]
Gya, gya, gya, gya!
Yes... We landed
on it a long time ago
and thought it was real
land we were standing on.
I'm beginning
to feel nostalgic...
Watching them sail in,
I remember my old
adventurous days.
[DORRY] The only thing that we
can't pierce with this weapon,
is the great bloodstained snake.
[BROGGY]
Together our weapons
form the most powerful
weapon Elbaf can offer.
The giant spear...
Just go straight...!
Go straight!
What does it matter...?!
We've already been eaten here!
Straight, okay?!
Just keep going!
[LUFFY laughs]
[BROGGY, DORRY]
Hokoku!
♪If there is a treasure
out there to be found,
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big place,
the oceans are wide,
Dumb luck alone
won't help you find it,
Just give up, it's astronomical.
Even so.
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on,
The laughter behind our
backs, it keeps us strong
It's too bad 'cuz we're still
sailing forward, so bon voyage!
Just leave us alone!
It may be foolish
chasing impossible things,
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream,
the more ambition
I'm gonna need!
It may be foolish
travelin' on, but I know
That I just gotta fight!
The farther the sea,
the greater paradise
We're gonna find!
Don't give up,
just keep on trying,
And you'll see that
you're closer to...
The horizon of your dreams!♪
[NAMI] For some reason
I feel really tired.
[VIVI]
What? Are you all right?
Everyone hurry!
Nami has a bad fever!
[SANJI]
What?! Is Nami gonna die?
[VIVI] We have to find
an island with a doctor now!
[USOPP] But don't we need
to hurry to Alabasta?
[VIVI]
Taking care of Nami comes first!
[SANJI]
Yeah, well said, Vivi!
[ZORO]
What's that?
[LUFFY]
Do you see a doctor?
On the next One Piece:
"Nami's Sick? Beyond
the Snow Falling on the Sea!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!