[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR]
Aboard the Going Merry,
Nami's group traversed
the treacherous milky road.
Their goal: to rendezvous on
the other side of the island
with the rest of the Straw Hats
and make their escape.
All the while, the
Shandorians blazed a path
to God's Shrine,
eager to destroy Eneru.
But they were blocked
by the Priest Shura,
birthing an epic battle of
entitlement versus honor
as Shura faced Wyper.
--[WYPER groans]
--[SHURA gasps]
Why did you throw away
your shield and weapon?
Are you insane?
No, he wouldn't dare.
[SHURA grunts]
Take it. If all you want's
a shoulder, it's yours.
An Impact Dial?
But that can't kill me!
[WYPER chuckles]
No, ten times that power!
Reject Dial!
Wyper! What were you thinking?
Just try using that
Reject Dial again!
You'll blow your body to pieces!
It's my body, isn't it?
I warned you we'd have to
take risks if we wanted victory!
[WYPER] We'll never beat
them if we aren't willing
to make sacrifices! Understand?
I'm going ahead!
Hah! Fine, then!
Do whatever you want!
[KAMAKIRI] Just don't forget
to pray for our safety.
Okay, men! Let's be careful!
We'll meet at God's Shrine!
[NARRATOR] Following
Shura's vicious defeat at
the hands of Wyper,
only 80 now remain in
the survivial game
of The Upper Yard.
Perhaps they
lacked divine protection.
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] As the four members
of Luffy's exploration team
know precisely the location
of the gold this island
has kept secret for 400 years,
they set their sights on it
and head south from
the sacrificial altar.
South. I mean.
Straight, uh, directly
south, or down.
Opposite of north.
Or, uh... Whatever.
[FUZA caws]
[LUFFY] "Fierce Midair Battle!
Pirate Zoro vs. Warrior Braham!"
[LUFFY hums]
♪ Islands in the east-- ♪
--[WYPER] Hold it!
--[LUFFY] What is it now?
[WYPER]
One last thing.
I'm through wasting any
more of my words on you.
So I'm gonna destroy you.
I see.
If you wanna fight,
you just have to say so.
[knuckles pop]
[CHOPPER screams]
[ZORO] Both the priests
and those guerillas all have
powers that I can't hold up to.
So a close quarters fight
doesn't mean much.
Guess I'll have to back up.
And if I have to
take 'em down at a distance,
I think I have
a move that'll work.
[ZORO]
Hawk Wave!
[ZORO] Well, it works on your
basic glass-jawed fighters,
but against a real guy? Hm.
[growls]
[BUZZARD caws]
It needs some work.
But I think after
a few tests, it'll be ready.
[ZORO]
The Flying Blade attack.
[CHOPPER screams]
[screaming continues]
[DIVINE WARRIORS laugh]
[CHOPPER wails]
[CHOPPER yelling]
Shandorians!
Divine warriors!
[yelling]
[CHOPPER sobbing]
[grunting]
[CHOPPER screams]
I would have been better
off eaten alive at the altar!
[sobs]
[CHOPPER screaming
[distant explosions
[ROBIN]
Huh.
Sounds like the island is
having it's fair share of drama.
I bet these homes were
built so far out from the city
in the hopes of greater
longevity with crops.
But it looks like all this
brush swallowed up
the mortar and brick.
I hope the city's still there.
[DIVINE WARRIOR D bleats]
[DIVINE WARRIOR D]
What are you doing here, woman?
You should be aware
that this is the path
to God's Shrine! Proceeding any
further would be insolent!
[bleats]
[ROBIN]
Would you get down?
Do you even have a clue as
to the archaeological
significance of these ruins?
They're priceless.
[growls]
How dare you talk back!
[ROBIN]
What are you doing here anyway?
You have some kind
of business with me?
[DIVINE WARRIOR D] Hmph!
Yes, simple business, actually.
I've been charged by God
to eliminate any Shandorians
or Blue Sea people
I find with my Axe Dial!
Heh. Seis Fleurs!
[gasps]
And with a twist.
[groans]
[bones cracking]
Such a lack of respect.
[growls]
[SHANDORIAN D]
And you call yourself divine?
These guys are gonna
be the end of us.
So far, they've managed
to kill a lot more of us
than we have of them.
[ZORO]
South should be to the right,
so if I keep to the right,
I should find it.
That's one of
those Blue Sea People
Wyper was talking about.
Better go take him out.
[yelling]
[ZORO]
A guerilla!
And he looks pissed.
[yells]
Die!
What's your problem?
You fellas have some serious
anger management issues.
[DIVINE WARRIOR F
bleats, whimpers]
[DIVINE WARRIOR F]
P-Please, no! I surrender!
I give up! I lose, you win.
Just, please, don't kill me!
I-I want to--
--[gunshot]
--[screams]
[ZORO]
Not again.
Listen, nutcase.
If you're not a Priest, then go
find another goat to shoot!
I'm in a hurry here!
[BRAHAM grunts]
[yells]
[ZORO growls]
All right. What's the deal
with these glowing pistols?
[gasps]
Where'd he go?
Couldn't have gotten far.
[ZORO grunts]
[BRAHAM growls]
[ZORO groans]
You put up a good fight.
I'm almost sorry I
underestimated you.
Well, thanks, pal.
But I should apologize to you.
I took you for a loser.
[yelling]
[grunting]
[distant gunfire, explosions
[engine revving
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO]
He never moved his feet!
[ZORO grunts] Pagaya said
there were different types
of Dials up here.
I wonder if this guy has one
or two stuck to his shoes.
'Cause when he moves,
gusts of wind shoot
from his feet.
[ZORO]
What else could it be?
And those pistols of his
flash as bright as the sun,
blinding me every time he fires.
Where is he now?
--[leaves rustle]
--[gunshot]
[gasps]
[ZORO]
Tiger...
He's using all three?
[ZORO]
...Trap!
[ZORO grunts]
Aren't you a hot shot?
[BRAHAM grunts]
[ZORO yells]
Hah. This Blue Sea idiot
has no clue about using Dials.
[BRAHAM]
He doesn't even stand a chance.
Hey! Guess what this is!
Oh, no!
[BRAHAM]
It's called a Milky Dial!
[ZORO whimpers]
You know, aerial combat
isn't just leaping around
out of desperation.
That looks big.
[ZORO] A ton of wood,
and these things would make
for a killer barbeque.
[ZORO groans]
[ZORO pants]
That was stupid.
Wh-What's wrong with me?
[ZORO] This guy's
already faster than me,
and I hang myself
out like an easy target.
Ugh. And I got
a bullet in my leg.
Agh. Genius.
Gotta be something I can do
about those flashing pistols.
Hold on.
Those guns of yours
are pretty nice accessories.
But too bad for you.
I found my lucky goggles.
Which means
your little blinding trick...
...won't work on me anymore.
You might as well give up.
[BRAHAM] Those just
look like regular goggles.
[ZORO gasps]
He found me out!
Not a big fan of
my flash guns are you?
Being a swordsman, you
need close quarters to fight,
which I won't give you.
I don't understand your
reasons for being here
and I don't care.
But I will say that your mere
presence defines you as
an enemy of the Shandorians.
Now I'm telling you,
surrender or die.
Which might happen sooner
if we keep standing here.
That leg of yours
isn't getting any better.
Doesn't hurt too bad.
Barely made a dent.
[ZORO] Getting shot while
I made smug comments about
some big dead eel proves
I'm lacking in concentration.
All right.
Guess I found the perfect
situation to test
that technique again.
[ZORO]
Let's give it a try.
[BRAHAM grunts]
[ZORO groans]
[grunts]
[BRAHAM]
Hmph!
Think you can run away?
[ZORO]
Sight.
Sound. Smell.
Taste. Touch. And thought.
These six roots ground us all by
way of good, evil, and peace.
What are you talking about?
[ZORO] And of course, each can
either be pure or impure.
These are the
36 earthly desires.
[BRAHAM]
Hmph.
Listen up, I have
the barrel of a cannon
aimed directly at your head.
And all you have
are a couple of pistols.
In both distance and power,
my weapon's superior.
You've done very well.
But you're still gonna die.
[BRAHAM]
Hmph.
What cannon?
You're outta your mind.
All I see are three swords.
Have you ever seen
a Flying Blade Attack?
[BRAHAM]
Attack this!
[yells]
[ZORO]
Single sword style.
[BRAHAM yells]
[ZORO]
Thirty-six caliber phoenix!
[BRAHAM groans]
[BRAHAM grunts]
[ZORO]
That looked uncomfortable.
Nothing personal,
being natural enemies and, all.
But you're in the dirt 'cause
I hate being told what to do.
No other reason.
I'll survive. You watch.
[whistling]
[explosion]
[SHANDORIAN Y yells]
[distant gunfire, explosions
[GEDATSU]
Hmph!
[GEDATSU growls]
[CHOPPER]
Where am I?
[GEDATSU]
Hm?
[CHOPPER] I've lost
all sense of direction.
The trees are too tall
for me to see the sun.
Help!
Luffy! Zoro! Robin!
Please find me!
I don't wanna be left on this
stinking island just to die
and turn into food
for gigantic bugs.
And if I do die, will there even
be a doctor waiting for me?
Wait, it doesn't matter.
When you're dead, you're dead,
and no doctor can save you.
But I don't wanna die!
Now I'm stuck in this awful
place, thinking about death
and doctors, and wondering: Why
couldn't I be something else?
Like a dentist.
Dentist would be nice.
Poke peoples teeth.
Make them feel better.
No giant sky sharks and
winged people trying to kill me.
At least I got my stick.
Wait. Maybe I've already died
and gone to Heaven.
[gasps]
These look like ruins.
We were supposed
to meet at ruins!
[laughs] Maybe they're
already here waiting for me!
Or maybe I was
so fast I beat them!
I'm so impressed with
my shrewd navigational skills,
they led me to just
the right place.
This is awesome!
[laughs] I'm right!
I'm the first one here!
[GEDATSU growling]
[GEDATSU]
A raccoon-dog?
[WYPER growls]
Gum Gum...
...Balloon!
[grunts, sighs]
You'll never be able
to hurt me with that thing.
Gum Gum...
[LUFFY]
...Balloon!
[LUFFY chuckles]
[USOPP whimpers]
[NAMI gasps]
[SANJI growls]
[yells]
You bastard!
[NAMI]
Sanji!
[USOPP]
[screams]
Sanji!
[USOPP whimpers]
[NAMI]
Sanji?!
No, Sanji! Get up, please!
[PIERRE whimpers, screams]
This is bad! This is really bad!
Sanji!
[ENERU chuckles]
I... I can't even
hear his heart beating.
It can't be!
[ENERU chuckles]
[ENERU laughs]
What a foolishly angry man.
If I'd come here today
and brought with me pain
and destruction, it would have
been the first thing you felt.
[GAN FALL]
Then why are you here, Eneru?
[ENERU laughs]
I expected a warmer hello.
It has been six years
now, my former God...
...Gan Fall.
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[NAMI]
I can't believe Sanji's dead.
[USOPP] Why am I stuck here with
you and the useless old man!
I can't count on either of you!
[NAMI]
Hey, that's my line.
[WYPER]
I'm taking you out, Straw Hats!
[LUFFY]
Excellent!
You mean for dinner?
What kinda place? Fancy?
[WYPER] Don't mock me,
you slithery pest!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Roaring Burn Bazooka!
Luffy vs. War Demon Wyper!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!