[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[ROSHIO] Looks like that's
the last of your cash.
But if you wanted to...
...I'd let you raise with, say
your clothes.
[MEDDLER B] You're lucky
and you don't even know it.
[MEDDLER A]
Playing with Roshio,
even if you would
have won the hand,
trust me, you would
have lost something else.
[ROSHIO] I suppose
that about wraps it up.
Let it go, buddy.
I won the lot fair and
square and you know it.
[BELLAMY]
Don't think so.
You cheated this entire hand,
didn't you?
I never cheat.
You're a liar.
You lie.
I watched every
deceitful move you made.
[ROSHIO] You better watch you
mouth in this place, loser!
Sarquiss?
Hey, Sarquiss!
[SARQUISS]
Hmm?
What is it?
[BELLAMY]
This guy was cheating just now.
You saw the whole
thing, didn't you?
[SARQUISS]
You bet I did.
Every rotten little move.
He cheated straight through.
I say we do something
about this guy.
Make an example out of him.
You have no idea
who you're dealing with!
[giggles]
[LUFFY]
"Quit Dreaming!
Mock Town,
the Town Of Ridicule!"
You see anything, Usopp?
Nothing.
Just the sky and the sea.
I thought that
Jaya Island wasn't too far
from where we were.
[NAMI]
It shouldn't be.
And with the weather
being so clear.
We should have spotted
the coastline over an hour ago.
I'm gonna like Jaya
if it's as warm as it is now.
I'm finally getting
to work on my tan.
Spring weather's the best.
It looks like the seagulls
are enjoying it too.
They've been shot!
Looks like we'll be
eating good tonight.
I don't think they could
have been shot, Chopper.
I didn't hear any gunfire.
I found a bullet!
And judging from the trajectory
it came from that way!
[NAMI]
Are you saying the shots
came from an island we
can't even see yet?
That's impossible, Chopper.
But I saw it happen
with my own eyes!
[laughs]
A tuna had a better
chance at killing them.
No sniper or gun
has that kind of range.
They were probably shot before
and just happened to fall now.
Hey, Sanji!
Look!
We found our dinner!
[OGRE]
Poor creature.
He must have suffered.
I wasn't able to get an
instant kill on one of them.
But that's what
fate haled for him.
All the events of his life
destined him to this outcome,
so I can't blame myself.
[BURGESS]
Hey, jerk!
Do you know who I am?
No! Get lost.
Ha!
I'll tell ya!
I'm the greatest fighting
champion ever!
[LUFFY]
Haha! Awesome!
Check it out,
this town looks great!
Is it just me or does this
place look like a resort?
It sure does!
Hurry up and dock!
It does look promising.
Maybe we can even
stay here awhile.
[USOPP]
Hmm?
[USOPP] Either I'm
starting to hallucinate
or the harbor over there
is full of pirate ships.
[NAMI]
Don't be silly, Usopp!
Since when can pirates
dock their ships in a harbor
without being run out of town.
[USOPP chuckles]
You're right. It must be a joke.
Someone help!
He's gonna kill me!
What the heck's going
on with this crazy town?
[BURGESS laughs]
What a pathetic little weakling!
[DRUNK] Hu‐ho! Mister you picked
the wrong guy to beat up.
Look at that emblem.
He's in Roshio's gang.
You have heard of Roshio, right?
You know, the executioner whose
bounty is 42 million Berries!
The man is psychotic,
you better watch your back!
[CUSTOMER A]
That guy is full of it.
We watched that
entire game ourselves.
No one cheated.
I still can't believe
he was able
to beat up Roshio so easily.
Don't you know?
That's Bellamy.
[CUSTOMER B]
What? That's Bellamy?
The one with the 55 million
bounty on his head?
Captain!
I can't believe it!
Who did this to him?
[UNDERLING B] We need
to get him to a doctor! Hurry!
[UNDERLING C]
Hang in there, Captain!
We'll get ya' fixed up!
Now this looks
like my kind of town.
[ZORO] We'll have
no problem fitting in here.
There's no way.
Do you think those
two can last an hour
without getting
into any trouble?
Well, by the
looks of this place,
I'd say 15 minutes
is a generous assumption.
You really think so?
I'd better save them!
Nami!
[NAMI]
Luffy! Zoro!
Wait for me!
I'm coming too!
There she goes.
Don't worry.
I'm sure she'll be fine
with those two protecting her.
[SANJI] I'm the only
one who can protect Nami.
[USOPP]
Not today!
Nami will be safe and
sound with Luffy and Zoro!
But if you leave, then what
are we supposed to do
‐‐if the ship is attacked?
‐‐Please don't leave!
Who's gonna protect us?
Fine, I'll stay behind.
Let me go!
Ha.
I guess I'll whip up some tea
and hold down the fort then.
Where did Robin go?
Huh?
I don't know.
[USOPP]
Sanji, about that tea.
[SANJI]
Make it yourself.
I got my tough face on
so if anybody messes with‐‐
[NAMI]
No fighting!
Promise me!
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
I promise.
Good. This is serious
business you two.
‐‐Good.
‐‐Great.
[NAMI]
Gee, thanks for the support!
Look, if one of you
causes trouble here,
we'll have to get
out of this town.
And if that happens,
then we'll never know how to
get to the sky island, right?
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
Whoa. He's messed up.
[LUFFY] Looks like
he fell off his horse.
[ZORO]
That's gotta hurt.
[LUFFY]
Looks like he's in pain too.
[ZORO]
No doubt.
Hey. Sorry to bother you.
But will you help me up?
[ZORO] What, are you not
in the mood to help yourself?
Luffy. Give me a hand.
Sure.
Up you go!
[DOC Q]
Hey, would ya look at that!
I'm on my horse again.
I was a sickly child growing
up and never got better.
Now let's get out
of here, Stronger.
[LUFFY, ZORO]
The horse too?
[ZORO] We should put them
out of their misery.
[DOC Q]
Thanks again, pal.
Ya know I don't
have enough money
for a reward these days,
but care for an apple?
[ZORO]
Do you take us for idiots?
We'd never trust food
from someone like you.
Hey, look! Apples!
Luffy!
What the? What happened?
[CLERK] Some guys
took a few apples
from that freak on the horse,
and when they bit into
them, they exploded!
Oh no! Luffy! Spit it out!
Spit out the apple you just ate!
I already swallowed it!
What the hell'd you do that for?
[laughs]
No worries.
The boy isn't hurt.
[MAN C]
What happened?
[MAN D] I don't know,
but the inside's destroyed.
[DOC Q] If you had
eaten the bad one,
you would have died
on the first bite.
Heh! You're lucky.
[ONLOOKER A]
What is all this?
[ONLOOKER B]
It's Roshio's grave now.
[ONLOOKER A] It looks like
a war broke out here.
Did they fire a cannon into
the middle of town or something?
[ONLOOKER B]
Who knows?
Even the people who were
there and saw what happened
said they couldn't tell
exactly what was going on.
About the only thing
everyone knows for certain
is that Bellamy had
something to do with this.
[ONLOOKER A]
Bellamy the Hyena?
I think it's pretty obvious
that he's using the power
of one of the devil's fruits.
[NAMI]
What's the deal with this town?
I don't know.
Who really cares?
You should care
seeing as you were
almost killed for no reason.
Well that was bound to
happen sooner or later.
Have you lost your mind?
[BURGESS roars]
[laughs]
Oh great, look who's back.
How many victims
has he racked up now?
[MAN E] It's not like he's
a famous fugitive or anything.
Who do you think he is?
I don't care, and to be honest,
I don't want to know.
If that meathead wants
to be the fighting champion,
then go ahead and let him.
Fighting champion?
Hey, don't even
think about it you two!
Dammit.
I'm starting to wonder
if we can find any
useful information here.
[ZORO]
How about this place?
[LUFFY]
Uh, seems pretty quiet to me.
You can say that again.
This place is gorgeous!
To think such an oasis exists
in the middle of
this disgusting town.
[ZORO]
It's built above the water.
[LUFFY] That's great,
but there's no one here.
Although I can smell
that someone's cooking.
Excuse me!
Excuse me! I'm gonna have to
ask you all to leave please.
See, the entire hotel has been
rented out by Mr. Bellamy
and his guests,
and he's asked that we
tell other guests like
yourselves to go somewhere else.
So, uh, you must understand that
I have no say in the matter.
So, one man rented
out this entire place?
If Mr. Bellamy sees you here,
he'll have my head
removed from my body,
so please leave for my sake.
[LUFFY]
C'mon, I'm sure he won't mind.
Who is this Bellamy anyway?
[SARQUISS]
What's going on in here?
Who are these scumbags and what
are they doing in our hotel?
Mr. Sarquiss!
Welcome back!
I told them to leave,
but they won't listen!
I really don't care.
Just get rid of them!
We're paying a lot of money
to have this place to ourselves.
She's right.
Now get out of here
before I throw you out.
Hey, guys, would you
mind if I beat him up?
Luffy!
Ha! You're going to beat me up?
[laughs]
Hilarious!
Seriously though,
those are rags you're wearing.
Here.
Go buy some new rags so you
don't look like an orphan.
[LILY] Sarquiss,
you're wasting your money
by tossing it to
this bunch of losers.
[SARQUISS]
No kidding.
I should have just flushed it
down along with my lunch.
I'll take free money!
Let's go.
These jerks can't help us.
[LUFFY]
I can walk on my own, you know.
See you around.
[EDDY]
Sarquiss. Lily.
Just leave well enough alone.
[SARQUISS] Eddy,
we've been looking for you.
You know that
trash you ran into?
Seems that they've been doing
pretty well for themselves.
Look.
Not bad,
but they're nothing compared
to you and Bellamy.
Here.
But for ordinary scum
they can hold their own.
They still don't stand
a chance of surviving the
transition into the new era.
Wow.
His bounty is 30 million,
for such a little puke.
I'm sure Bellamy
will want to see this.
Man, that really pisses me off!
[TERRY]
That's a shame.
Cause you know.
Mock Town's economy depends
on pirates throwing money around
to show off power they
may or may not have.
What, so poor pirates aren't
allowed on the island?
Looks like there's
no way of calming you down.
Here.
This one's on the house.
Huh?
[TERRY]
Tough guys and degenerates
are our clientele here,
so trouble isn't hard to find.
You aren't gonna make it in this
town if ya let it bother ya.
You have to play it
safe when you can.
Here you go.
This whole town's
a real dump, ya know?
Of course, that's how
most level‐headed people
would think of it.
But unfortunately for you,
level‐headed people
are rare in these parts.
The wanted posters won't be on
the walls for a couple of days,
so you may want to skip town
sooner rather than later.
A couple days.
That doesn't give us much time.
Now here's a question.
‐‐Hey, fatso!
‐‐[BLACKBEARD] Hey, barkeep!
[TERRY]
Huh?
What's wrong?
‐‐[BLACKBEARD] This cherry pie
‐‐[LUFFY] This cherry pie
‐‐tastes friggin' delicious!
‐‐tastes friggin' horrible!
‐‐Huh?
‐‐Hm?
‐‐This is one of the
‐‐worst drinks I've ever tasted!
‐‐best drinks I've ever tasted!
I think there
may be something wrong
with your taste buds, kid.
I think there's somethin' wrong
with your big fat head.
Well, I'm not
the cook in this joint,
so I don't care
what you have to say.
Got it?
Hey, barkeep!
I'll take 50 steaks to go!
And I'll take 51 of those
delicious cherry pies to go.
Wait, make that 52 steaks!
[BLACKBEARD]
Better make that 53 pies.
[LUFFY]
Fifty‐four steaks!
[BLACKBEARD]
Fifty‐five pies!
[LUFFY]
Sixty steaks!
[BLACKBEARD]
Seventy pies!
[LUFFY]
Eighty!
[BLACKBEARD]
A hundred!
I'm gonna beat the
living crap out of you!
Do you two even
have the slightest idea
what you're fighting about?
Luffy, you promised, remember?
Besides, we don't have enough
money to buy dozens of steaks!
We aren't here to shop!
So then, are you a pirate?
Yeah. That's right.
How big's your bounty?
Thirty million.
Thirty million? For you?
I wouldn't believe it
even if I collected it!
Are you calling me
a liar you fat, hairy ape?
[ZORO]
Enough!
[TERRY]
We've got rules in this place,
and one of 'em's no fighting.
Here's your 50 cherry pies.
Now please, just walk away.
[BELLAMY] I'm looking for a
pirate that wears a straw hat.
[LUFFY]
Hmm?
[CUSTOMER A]
It's Bellamy!
Heh.
So you must
be Straw Hat Luffy,
worth a cool 30 million.
Who's this guy?
Looks like he has a bone
to pick with you, Luffy.
That must be that Bellamy guy
that rented out
the hotel we were at.
Did you hear that?
The kid's worth 30 million.
[CUSTOMER C]
No way.
[CUSTOMER B]
Tell me about it.
How come everyone
I meet in this town is so tall?
I'll take a glass
from the top shelf
and give the kid
whatever he wants.
Right.
[SARQUISS]
Look at this place.
This joint is packed solid!
[LILY]
This place is disgusting.
It smells like vomit.
[RIVERS] All you can
get here is cheap rum.
Look, Zoro.
It's those guys from earlier.
You'd be in a lot less pain
if you'd just offered
us your seats.
Pathetic harbor trash.
[CUSTOMER D]
It's him! "Big Knife" Sarquiss!
[CUSTOMER E] How much you wanna
bet he's looking for a fight?
[CUSTOMER D]
Oh great.
The whole gang is here.
There's no way that they stopped
in just for a bite to eat.
Drop it, man.
It has nothing to do with us.
What's Bellamy up to?
[SARQUISS]
The usual fun.
[BELLAMY]
Cheers.
Hey, thanks for the drink, pal!
You know what?
You're all right.
[gasps]
[CUSTOMER F]
He did it!
[laughs]
Brilliant move, Bellamy!
Just brilliant!
[laughs]
Huh?
What are you doing, punk?
[ZORO] That's the question
you should be asking yourself.
Zoro! Don't do it!
We still need to get
some information from‐‐
Quiet! If this guy wants
a fight, I'll give it to him.
[BELLAMY] So that's all
you've got for backup?
[laughs]
Now, are you ready
to take me on or not?
Heh...
[CUSTOMER G]
No way!
The kid just challenged Bellamy!
[CUSTOMER I]
He'll be slaughtered!
[laughs]
You've got it all wrong, kid.
This isn't a fight.
It's a test.
Now come on.
Let's see how strong you are.
Luffy, hold on!
Mister, we're trying
to get to the sky island.
Do you know anything about that?
Did she just say "sky island"?
She's crazy.
[NAMI] Like I was saying, if you
know how to get to sky island...
[laughter]
Did she say
what I think she said?
Sky island? What an idiot!
What the...
You can look at the
Log Pose yourself!
It's pointed at the sky,
plain as day!
[CUSTOMER I]
Hey, check it out!
Do I look like the Log Pose now?
[CUSTOMER J] No one trusts
those things anymore!
They break if you breathe wrong!
[laughs]
You got me there, kid.
I can't believe you
guys are putting hope
into such a ridiculous legend
like an island in the sky.
Especially considering
how little you know.
Like, of the thousands
of weird currents cutting
through the Grand Line,
one of the weirdest is
called the Knock‐Up Stream.
Looks to me like
this is the first
you've ever heard about it.
Any ship that gets caught
in the Knock‐Up Stream
is catapulted into the sky,
and later slams back
into the ocean.
Years ago, a bunch
of ignorant sailors saw
ships falling from the sky
and assumed there must be
an island up there somewhere.
In their minds, how else could
a ship get up that high? Ha!
Ridiculous!
Anything that seems supernatural
always has a
rational explanation.
Anything a man can dream
will eventually be explained,
and let me tell ya,
the truth will hurt.
What a shame.
Look.
I was gonna let you join my crew
if you'd passed the
test of the new era.
But it seems like
you're a lost cause.
Thing is, the time of
pirate's dreams are over!
The City of Gold, the Emerald
Ruins, and the great One Piece!
The fools who dream of
these fictional treasures
don't notice the real
treasures that surround them!
In this age of oceans, the very
men who are brave enough
and capable of
navigating currents end up
chasing these ridiculous
dreams and die in the process!
Whenever people speak of these
dead idiots they always say,
"He was happy because
he died living his dreams."
Ha!
No, he died because
he was a fool!
So when I see people
chasing dreams of One Piece,
I get disgusted!
[NAMI]
Luffy!
[BELLAMY] You're a weak pirate,
just like they were,
and as long as you're hacking
around, you'll make us,
the real pirates,
look like trash.
[CUSTOMER K chuckles]
Get out of here,
you scrawny punk!
You're killing our buzz!
Way to go, Bellamy!
Get lost, you wimp!
[CUSTOMER N]
Put him in a body bag, Bellamy!
Yeah!
[laughs]
Bellamy, give
these people what they want!
Tear into them!
[BELLAMY chuckles]
I'd be more than
happy to entertain.
Yeah.
Luffy! Zoro!
Forget about all that
pacifist crap I was talking
about earlier and
take this jerk out!
[LUFFY]
Zoro.
No matter what happens,
don't fight back.
[laughs]
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...♪
[NAMI] Hey! Why are you letting
them beat you like that?
[USOPP]
Men can make dumb decisions
inside their masculine heads.
[NAMI] And I suppose somehow,
they believe that dying
is going to prove them right
and vindicate them!
We can always leave them behind.
[USOPP] I think I'd still rather
have Luffy as Captain over you.
Sorry.
[NAMI]
Jerk.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Distinguished Pirates!
A Man Who Talks of Dreams and
The King of Undersea Search!"
I'm gonna be the
King of the Pirates!