Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of
pirates go to battle
across the seas in
search of the One Piece,
the legendary
treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles.
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
The Straw Hat crew,
needing their ship coated before
their journey to Fishman Island,
landed on the
Sabaody Archipelago
in search of a
coating mechanic.
Little did they know
the man they were looking for,
was once the vice-captain
of the Roger Pirates.
After finding him,
they were ambushed by Sentomaru
of the Marine Science Unit.
[SENTOMARU]
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
Luffy!
[NARRATOR]
To make matters worse,
they were also pitted against
the Marine Admiral Kizaru,
who proved too deadly a foe
for the exhausted Straw Hats.
[KIZARU] Well, you'll have
plenty time to rest up now.
Zoro!
]Are you sure you want to do
this, Dark King Rayleigh?
Don't go pickin' these
buds before they sprout.
Their era's only just beginning.
And I wanna see
what they do with it.
Rayleigh!
[NARRATOR]
Thanks to Rayleigh's help,
the crew made a hasty retreat.
But before they
could celebrate,
they were stopped dead in their
tracks by Bartholomew Kuma,
a Warlord of the Sea.
[KUMA]
You and I...
We'll never meet again.
Farewell, Straw Hat.
[LUFFY moans]
[NARRATOR] And so the Straw Hat
crew disappeared from Sabaody,
suffering absolute defeat.
[LUFFY] Landing! The All-Female
Island, Amazon Lily!
[DUVAL] Damn it, if I
could just wink right.
I'd be even more handsome!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
Cah-lick.
[FISH RIDER 386A]
Good news, Duval, we found it!
It's at a bay by Grove 41!
[DUVAL]
I got it! I'll be right there!
All right men, listen up.
The pride of the Rosy Life
Riders is on the line here!
We can't lose!
[FISH RIDERS]
Yes, sir!
Grove 41! Now c'mon,
Motobalo! Go!
[DUVAL] I wonder what those
shockwaves were about.
They shook
the whole archipelago.
I hope the young master
and his friends are all right.
[SHALRIA] What do you mean,
you haven't caught them?
[MARINE OFFICER 408A]
Admiral Kizaru is pursuing
them as we speak, so I'm
sure it's only a matter of time
until they're captured, ma'am!
You bunch of useless dogs!
[SHALRIA]
Not only did you allow them
to do this to my
father and brother,
you also let every last
one of our slaves escape!
And yet I must
save my contempt
for the pirates who made
a mockery of our bloodline!
When you catch those heathens,
I'll show them
a true living hell.
Until they beg for
death on their knees!
[FISH RIDER 386A]
Hey Duval-- I mean, handsome.
What do you think's
taking the Straw Hats so long?
Maybe those guys
are still chasing 'em.
I heard things are a
mess at the port right now.
Yeah, I saw it from
the air myself.
Pirates and Marines
were fighting like crazy.
Hope they didn't
get caught in that.
[DUVAL]
Stay sharp!
With all of those idiots
running wild all over Sabaody,
who knows if their
ship will be safe.
That's why we gotta guard
it with our very lives!
Until the coating craftsman
shows up and takes over,
don't budge an inch!
[DUVAL]
You got that, Rosy Life Riders?
[FISH RIDERS]
Roger, Captain Handsome!
[CAMIE] I have a bad feeling
about this all of a sudden.
I sure hope Luffy-chin and
his friends are okay out there.
[PAPPAGU] Come on, Camie!
Don't say stuff like that!
You're just gonna
stress everybody out!
[CAMIE]
Yeah, but--
[HACHI] The Straw Hats
are tough, you know that.
There's nothing
to worry about.
I hope you're right.
[PAPPAGU]
Knock it off, Camie!
You're scaring me
over nothing here!
Straw Hat might
not be the brightest,
but he won't
lose in a fight!
You've seen how
strong that guy is!
[SHAKKY] But not
stronger than an Admiral.
I'm not saying
that they'll lose.
But this will take
more than just strength.
[SHAKKY] The seas ahead
will be rough for them.
Filled with waves
the likes of which
have never been seen before.
And yet they must
withstand them, ride them.
It's quiet, but
can you hear it?
[SHAKKY] Little by little,
the tides are changing.
And the world with them.
[NARRATOR] After being
ejected from Sabaody,
Monkey D. Luffy found himself
on a very unique journey.
[LUFFY screams]
Zoro! Nami!
I'm sorry!
Usopp, Sanji, Chopper!
Robin!
Franky, Brook!
Everybody!
Where did you go?
You guys can't be dead!
Damn it, there was
nothing I could do!
That stupid warlord
is gonna pay for this!
Ugh, I hate this!
It sucks!
How far am I
gonna fly, anyway?
[LUFFY panting]
Oh.
Hey, wait a second.
But someone might tell
you he can send you flying
for three days and nights
with those paw pads.
Can't say if it's true
or not, but that's the rumor.
[LUFFY] But that
could be good news.
Maybe everyone
didn't disappear,
they're just flying
around like me.
I hope that axe guy
was telling the truth.
Although three days of
this sure will be boring.
If I fall in the ocean,
that'll be the end of me.
[LUFFY's stomach growls]
I'm so hungry, too.
Screw this, I'm going to sleep.
Zoro... Nami...
Usopp... Sanji...
Chopper... Robin...
Franky... Brook...
All my friends.
[NARRATOR] On and on he soared,
through starry skies.
Then, at long last...
[LUFFY snoring]
[MONSTERS growling]
I'm alive.
[LUFFY]
Dunno what happened,
but I don't think my rubber
powers saved me this time.
Also, what's this bear
paw-looking thing
doing on the ground?
If everyone else had a landing
like this, they might be okay.
[BEAST growls]
[LUFFY]
Ah, well. Gotta get back.
Where am I?
And which way is the
Sabaody Archipelago from here?
Wait a sec!
I have my Vivre Card! Of course!
All right! Good thing
everyone got one, huh?
Ha! Let's go! Easy!
Follow the card!
We'll be back
together in no time.
That way!
[LUFFY yelling]
[panting]
Everyone start running
and look after yourselves!
We can't win this one!
We're too weak!
Get moving!
Just go! Get out of there!
We can figure out a plan
once we're safe! Run!
[LUFFY]
Why the hell am I so weak?
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
[LUFFY yells]
Ow!
Actually, that
didn't hurt that bad,
but that rock's
still in the way.
No doubt about it.
The card's pointing
in that direction.
Fine.
Giant...
Pistol!
Man, I can't do it.
I'm all out of power.
I need food!
Sanji! Ah, who am I kidding?
I know he's not here.
[branch snaps]
Thanks for all
the food, buddy.
That really brings me back.
Grandpa Garp used to throw
me in the jungle all the time
when I was a kid.
Actually, that kinda sucked.
This place is awfully
quiet for a jungle.
Feels lonely.
Hey, aren't these
Laughing Mushrooms?
Perfect! This is just
what I need right now!
[LUFFY laughing]
Yeah, now I'm having fun!
Even though I'm all alone!
Ooh, these look weird.
Let's try 'em!
Rrr, now I'm mad!
Laughing Mushrooms!
Hey, look,
there's more over here!
Crying mushrooms!
[MARGARET]
Hurry! I can see the smoke.
It's right over there!
[SWEETPEA] They've been
anchored offshore for a while.
You don't think they made
landfall in secret, do you?
If so, this could be
of great consequence!
[MARGARET] True, but that
scenario is highly unlikely.
We have heavy security
all over the island!
Even if they did find a way
to breach our iron defenses,
they would be foolish
to draw attention
to themselves with a campfire.
[APHELANDRA]
Then, who could it be?
[MARGARET] We'll just have
to find out for ourselves.
Let's split up into groups.
[SWEETPEA and APHELANDRA]
Got it!
[SWEETPEA]
What is that?
Margaret! Hurry!
You must see this!
[MARGARET]
Hm?
Look! Look!
Calm down. I'm right
here, Sweetpea.
What do you
make of it?
Huh?
Rather puzzling, isn't it?
Oh! This is terrible!
I think this is a human!
Is she from the village?
I don't know.
There're so many mushrooms
growing out of her body
I can't even tell.
Then the fire...
Do-- do you think it may have
actually been a call for help?
Ah-ha! Look here,
this must be why.
She ate these.
A Parasitic Mushroom.
When you eat one,
a whole sea of them pop
up all over your body.
We have to
do something!
Or these mushrooms
will sap away
all of her strength
and she'll die!
Then make haste.
Before all is lost!
Aphelandra!
Carry her to the
village, and quickly!
'Kay!
Stay strong,
small one.
We will find aid.
Let's hope.
[gong ringing]
[MARGARET]
We have an emergency!
[AMAZON PONYTAIL]
Hey!
Down in front! I can't see!
Goodness! Mushrooms!
What happened?
I haven't seen that girl in
the village before, have you?
No. Not me.
Hey, who is that?
With all those mushrooms,
It's hard to tell.
[AMAZON HAIRCLIPS]
Any idea where she came from?
[AMAZON MOHAWK]
Is she alive?
She ate a parasitic mushroom
and now they're growing
all over her body.
Belladonna? What do
think we should we do?
You can pull them off,
but we have to get them all.
Be thorough.
[BOTH]
They come off?
[MARGARET]
Oh, wow.
But some of the
bases are still stuck.
[BELLADONNA] Don't worry,
I'll take care of them later.
Just keep pulling.
[KIKYO]
She's so odd,
are you sure
that this was wise?
What could I do?
She was barely alive
when we found her.
I thought she might
be from the village!
Well, that should do it!
Good. Now, step back a bit.
[LUFFY yelping]
Hot, hot, hot!
I'm on fire!
Put me out!
Hold on, Belladonna!
What are you doing?
[BELLADONNA] This is the
only way to keep them
from growing back.
[MARGARET] Still, it
seems a bit excessive...
Ah! She passed out again!
[BELLADONNA]
Well, that's interesting,
it seems she was
covered in injuries.
Before she was
covered in mushrooms.
[MARGARET]
She was?
She must have gone through
quite the terrible battle.
We need to treat her wounds.
Do me a favor, Margaret.
Take her down to the river
and give her a good bath.
Uh, yes. Yes, of course.
[MARGARET]
Well, it appears that she's not
from the village
after all. How strange.
Yes. Huh? Hold on!
What is this?
Is something wrong?
We've been remiss in our
mushroom-picking duties!
There's one between her legs
that we failed to catch!
How careless of us!
Huh. You're right.
but this one seems different
than the others, doesn't it?
It has such a strange shape.
Wait. Look. It's another one!
Here, see? Right on the bottom.
It appears to be some
sort of sack mushroom!
Better pull it.
It won't come off, but why?
[AMAZON PURPLE HAIR]
Hey, what's going on?
What happened?
[AMAZON ROUNDEYES]
It's stretching.
[AMAZON TWINBUNS]
What is?
[AMAZON ROUNDEYES]
A mushroom!
[AMAZON PONYTAIL]
Let me see! That sounds funny!
That's enough.
Stop gawking, ladies.
They aren't putting
on a show for you!
Huh?
If we leave, so do you!
Hey, look. That isn't
normal, is it?
It's strange. She's
sort of rugged.
Not very well-endowed, either.
[SWEETPEA panting]
It's no use.
Come over here, Aphelandra,
you give it a try.
Me? Are you sure?
Mm-hmm!
Give it a yank!
It'll come right off!
Why don't we all pull
on it? That'll work!
No.
If the mushroom
refuses to come off...
...then we must burn
it as Belladonna did.
Until naught
but ashes remain.
[SWEETPEA]
Yes! A splendid idea!
Wouldn't you agree, Margaret?
[MARGARET]
Sure! Burn away!
[NYON] Nyo my! What's
this? Is something wrong?
[MARGARET]
Oh! Hello Granny Nyon!
There's a mushroom
growing on this girl
that won't come off
no matter how hard we try!
Do you think we should
all pull it together?
Or just burn it off?
Yo, goodness!
But who is she?
The mushroom's
a mystery, too.
Let's see...
Where could it be?
Oh nyo!
[AMAZON MOHAWK]
Whoa! Hey, Granny Nyon,
[AMAZON PONYTAIL]
You aren't ill, are you?
Nyo, everything is just fine.
Except that this person is a...
[NYON] This person
is a... a... is a man!
A man!
[ALL]
What?
I've never seen a man before.
Whatever shall I do?
[NARRATOR] Here lies the
maiden island of Amazon Lily,
inhabited by a tribe of female
warriors known as the Kuja.
Woe be to the man
who dreams of this land
and woe be to
the man who seeks it.
For if they shall ever
set foot upon its soil,
death surely awaits them.
[NARRATOR] Captured by
the women of Amazon Lily,
Luffy tries to escape in hopes
of reuniting with his friends.
However, the Snake Princess
is returning to the island.
If she learns a man has
been brought to the village,
both Luffy and the women
who rescued him
could pay the ultimate price.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece.
"Hurry Back to Your Friends!
The Maiden Island Adventure!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!