Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[ZORO] Thirty-Six
Caliber Phoenix!
He deflected Zoro's
attack with his bare hand!
I think I just figured
out what your ability is.
I possess the power
to deflect anything I wish.
You see, I ate the Paw Paw Fruit
and became a Paw-Palmed Human.
[FRANKY]
What the hell is he doing?
[NAMI]
Is that air?
It looks like a giant
bubble shaped like a paw.
[CHOPPER] And he keeps
making it smaller.
I think I know
what he's doing.
He's using his power to
deflect a giant air mass,
but he's compressing it
into a tiny ball.
The real attack will come
as soon as he releases all
of that compressed pressure.
That much air...
It'll send out a
massive shock wave.
Like an enormous bomb.
Did... I hear you right?
Like a bomb?
You mean he's gonna release
that and blow us all up?
This is bad.
I've thought it over
and I've made a decision.
I will spare your lives.
But on one condition.
In exchange for this
act of magnanimity,
you give me the head
of Straw Hat Luffy.
If I return with him,
that should be enough
to satisfy the government.
We won't betray
our own captain!
[KUMA]
Now, then.
Hand him over
before I change my mind.
[CREW]
Never!
This was your choice.
[LUFFY] "The Pain of
My Crewmates is My Pain!
Zoro's Desperate Fight!"
Now suffer the Ursa Shock.
[ZORO]
Lion's Song!
[ZORO] Of course.
I should've known.
So you're a cyborg
like Franky, huh?
Not quite. You're made of
something tougher than he is.
That steel bar.
He melted it.
[KUMA] A cyborg? I suppose
you could say that.
But my metal parts
are all I have in common
with your friend Franky.
[KUMA] I'm a creation
known as a Pacifista,
an in-development human-weapons
project of the World Government.
A Pacifista, huh?
[KUMA]
I was created
by the Government's
most renowned scientist,
Doctor Vegapunk.
One of the greatest geniuses
this world has ever known.
To put that
into perspective,
his discoveries
are so sophisticated
that it's believed
it will take the rest
of the world 500 years
to catch up to him.
Technology that advanced,
and you have Devil Fruit powers?
I'm starting to think you
have an advantage over me.
[ZORO]
Well, this is embarrassing.
My body's shutting down.
It won't listen to me anymore.
[ZORO] And the only
way you'll back down
is if we give you Luffy's head?
[ZORO coughs]
That is the only compromise
I'm willing to offer.
You want a head?
Then I'll give you a head.
However, I can't give
you my captain's.
You'll have to
take mine instead.
Please settle for that.
[ZORO] I may not
have the same bounty
on my head as
Luffy at the moment,
but I swear to you
that I'm destined
to become the greatest swordsman
the world has ever known.
Surely that must
be worth something.
[KUMA] You possess
that much ambition,
and yet you're
willing to give it all up
and exchange your life for his.
[ZORO]
The way things are lookin',
I don't see any other way
to save the rest of my crew.
What's the point
of having ambition
if I can't even save my captain?
Luffy is the man who'll
become King of the Pirates!
[SANJI] Real cute.
Stop trying to show me up.
[SANJI] Ya got the right idea,
but what about your dream?
Ya can't accomplish
anything if you're dead,
ya stubborn fool.
Don't tell me...
[SANJI]
Listen, ya giant oaf.
[ZORO]
Hey!
Don't bother with
moss head here.
If you're takin'
a head, take mine.
The government
might not consider me
a serious threat right now,
but you'll regret not
taking my head over his
once I start making trouble.
Now's your chance to
take on Black Leg Sanji.
[ZORO]
You jackass!
Go on and get it over with.
The only head
you're taking is mine.
Forget about these fools.
Kill me and get outta here.
[SANJI] I'm just as ready
to sacrifice myself as he is.
I've fed people my whole life,
and now I'll feed the worms.
[SANJI]
Hey. Do me a favor.
[SANJI] Tell everyone I'm
sorry I couldn't say goodbye.
[SANJI] I hate to
put you guys out,
but looks like you'll
have to find a new cook.
Mosshead, you son of a...
Now show me
you've got some honor.
You've made sure I can't
even touch Straw Hat.
Not unless I want
to shame myself.
Then you've got my respect.
[KUMA]
If that's what you want,
I give you my word.
I won't take Straw Hat's head.
[KUMA] But if you're
intent on taking his place,
you will experience
a living hell.
[KUMA] I've just repelled
all physical injury
from Straw Hat's body.
His exhaustion, his pain.
What rests before
you is the sum total
of anguish he endured during
his battle with Moria.
If you truly wish
to take his place,
then you must accept and
inflict his agony upon yourself.
[KUMA] As close to
death as you are already,
not only will it
undoubtedly kill you,
it will do so painfully.
Why don't you have a taste?
[KUMA]
Do you still want it?
[ZORO] Just let
me pick the location.
[KUMA] To inspire such
loyalty in his friends.
He couldn't be
anyone's son but yours,
could he, Dragon?
[RISKY BROTHER MASK]
Hey, is everyone still alive?
Are you guys okay?
He must've just
assumed we were all dead
after that explosion
and left the island,
which means that we won!
Stupid Paw-Man!
This hurts.
[LUFFY cheering]
[FRANKY] Oh, c'mon,
you've gotta be kidding.
How're you bouncing
around like that?
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
This is awesome!
My body feels as good as new!
I wonder why?
[USOPP]
Quit lying!
Calm down before
you hurt yourself!
[ROBIN] It's possible he
took so much damage
to the brain it
knocked him silly.
[FRANKY]
Let's hope not.
He was too damn
silly to begin with.
[LUFFY]
I feel great!
[CREW overlapping
concerned chatter]
No way that guy
just let us go.
Damn it, Zoro, what'd you do?
[SANJI]
That's him.
You really freaked me out there.
So what happened to the Warlord?
Where the hell'd all
this blood come from?
Hey! Are you still alive?
Where'd that paw guy go?
What in the hell happened here?
What happened here?
Nothing at all.
[CHOPPER] I've never seen Zoro
injured this badly before.
What could've happened?
[BROOK]
I saw what transpired.
[CHOPPER]
What?
[BROOK] Isn't it wonderful
to have comrades like him?
Hey, our dear friends,
I must fulfill the promise
I made to my own.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"The Promise from a Distant Day!
The Pirate Song
and a Small Whale."
I'm gonna be King of the
Pirates!