[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[NARRATOR B]
Last time on One Piece,
while trying to chase
down their lost comrades,
Luffy, Sanji, and Usopp
stumbled into the Lost Forest,
where they faced the
brutal priest Satori.
[SANJI groaning]
[USOPP groaning]
[LUFFY groaning]
[SATORI]
Aha! You're still alive!
I'm impressed!
And as a reward
for good behavior,
we going to finish
our little fun today
with a move I've received
several awards for. [laughs]
[NARRATOR B] Meanwhile,
the Sky Knight readies his mount
to save Chopper, who stands
guard at the Going Merry
and is next on the
sacrificial docket
of the devilish priest, Shura!
[CHOPPER groaning]
[gasps, yells]
And now...
...I offer your life to God!
[yells] No!
[CHOPPER groans]
Now die.
[SHURA growls]
--[GAN FALL yells]
--[SHURA grunts]
[GAN FALL]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's Gan Fall the Sky Knight!
You're nothing but a pathetic
shell of your former self.
And I'm through playing
games with a fool.
You showed up to this
fight a criminal,
which leaves me
only one option--
take you out.
[SHURA]
Ordeal of String!
[FUZA screeches]
[LUFFY]
"Profound Mystery!
Ordeal of String and
Ordeal of Love?!"
Ha, ha!
[laughing]
[SANJI grunts]
[LUFFY groaning]
[SATORI laughing]
[pants] What the--
[SATORI]
Introducing the Sphere Dragon!
[USOPP gasps]
It looks like all you did is
string a bunch of
surprise clouds together.
Is that the best you can do?
I have to say I'm disappointed.
[SATORI]
Oh, you won't be for long!
You see, my friend,
the dragon is loaded
with explosive surprises
and all kinds of
delightful shrapnel!
[gasps] But then that means--!
If you even touch the fire-bomb
sphere somewhere on it's body,
it'll be over for you
and your friends.
You'll be blown to bits
in the ensuing inferno!
Hope ya like fireworks!
Go, Sphere Dragon!
[gasps, screams]
Get ready for my
Gum-Gum Pistol! [yells]
No! Luffy! Wait!
[LUFFY gasps]
[SATORI laughing]
You idiot! That
freak just told us
if we touch that thing,
it'll explode!
Do you want to die
a fiery death?
--[LUFFY grunts]
--[USOPP gasps]
Well how are we gonna fight
it if we can't touch it?
[USOPP]
That's just it!
We can't fight this thing.
I think now's the
time to run. [yells]
[SATORI laughing]
[BOTH yelling]
[LUFFY]
So what do we do now?
[USOPP] I don't know!
You're the captain!
Okay, on "three," jump.
Three!
[LUFFY chuckles]
[USOPP sighs]
Oh, no! This is bad!
[LUFFY yells]
[SATORI]
Ha, ha, ha!
Well you are quite the little
survivors, aren't you?
[LUFFY, USOPP groan]
Okay, now you're just
toying with us!
Correct.
It wouldn't be as much fun
if you didn't experience
the full power of
the Sphere Dragon!
Shall we continue?
[AISA panting]
[AISA grunts]
[AISA grunting]
[AISA panting]
--[KAMAKIRI] Aisa!
--[AISA gasps, groans]
Where have you been, child?
Ah! Kamakiri!
The Upper Yard again, right?
And that's probably
Vearth in your bag.
[KAMAKIRI] Stay away
from that place, Aisa...
[KAMAKIRI]
...or you will die.
You can't tell me what to do!
You haven't even been
able to beat Eneru yet!
[KAMAKIRI grunts]
What a brat.
[BRAHAM]
An opportunity?
[WYPER]
That's right.
For some reason, Gan Fall
entered the Upper Yard,
which of course drew the
attention of the priests.
You see, that old bag of bones
thinks it's his responsibility
to protect the
people of Skypiea.
And that will only
make him weak.
[WYPER exhales]
We would be wise to strike
while our enemies are
occupied with each other!
The Great Warrior Kalgara said,
"Light the fire of Shandora."
Our people will do just that.
No one can deny us our destiny,
be it Gan Fall and or Eneru, and
now is the time to take action!
They have had the
audacity to reign as "God"
and that is unforgivable.
No matter how different from
one another they may seem,
I assure you they are the same.
And they must be eliminated!
[LAKI]
Wyper.
Huh?
It has been six years since
Eneru began his reign.
And for the first time
since he took power,
a rebel has appeared
on Angel Island.
A young woman, I hear.
Get to the point, Laki.
Because the Sky Knight rescued
the young rebel from judgment,
Eneru now has reason to
directly confront Gan Fall
in order to judge him.
A battle like this between the
former God and the current God
has never happened.
Strategically, this could be
most advantageous to us.
We must remember that Gan Fall
has never harmed any of us.
Not as the Sky Knight,
and not during his reign as God.
The fact that he never hurt
any of us doesn't change that
he ruled with absolute
authority as "God."
And although he is
our enemy's enemy,
that does not make him our ally.
If he and one of the priests
kill each other in battle,
that will serve our
purposes just fine.
Otherwise he is of no use to us.
If you have any doubts
at all about this fight,
stay out!
You'll just be in the way!
[AISA]
Hm?
--[BRAHAM] Aisa!
--[AISA gasps, groans]
Upper Yard? What Upper Yard?
I didn't go to Upper Yard,
I promise you I didn't!
You can't go into the tent yet.
Wyper, descendent of the
Great Warrior Kalgara,
is angry right now.
Careful.
Oh. He's scary when he gets mad.
[AISA]
Scarier than God.
[CONIS]
Help them? Us? How?
Conis. My dear child.
It's only right that
you and I should try
to create some way
for them to escape.
[BOTH grunting]
Wow, I can't believe
how fast they are.
Awesome.
[GAN FALL grunts]
I can see that diplomacy is
no longer an option for me.
[grunts] Diplomacy
is for the weak!
[grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[CHOPPER]
This battle is intense.
[GAN FALL yells]
[SHURA yells]
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[WOMAN A]
Heaven's judgment.
[MAN A] That young woman
did something foolish.
She brought this upon us.
She knows we're not
supposed to anger him!
[GAN FALL growls]
[SHURA grunts, yells]
[GAN FALL grunts, yells]
[FUZA squawks]
[groans]
[GAN FALL panting]
Please come back to us...
...God.
[GAN FALL pants, gasps]
[BOTH groan]
[gasps]
[BOTH groaning]
You're mine!
[FUZA screeches]
[SHURA laughs]
Is something wrong, Gan Fall?
Shura! What've you done?
[GAN FALL]
Why can't we move?
You old fool.
Time to die!
[GAN FALL gasps]
[gasps, screams]
[GAN FALL groans]
Mysterious... the strings are.
[gasps]
[SHURA] If you have the
audacity to enter Upper Yard,
you must answer to
the four priests.
You were foolish...
to think you could beat us.
[CHOPPER gasps]
He's falling! Oh, no!
[SHURA]
God Eneru is glorious,
perfect, and far
beyond your reach.
[GAN FALL] And our sacred land
will sing again someday.
Someday she must.
[CHOPPER]
Sky Knight! Sky Knight!
[CHOPPER screams]
[gasps]
[PIERRE screeches]
[CHOPPER]
I gotta save him.
I've just gotta save him!
He'll get eaten by skysharks
if I don't do something!
[FUZA squawks]
[SHURA]
Judgment has been made!
[CHOPPER] But how can I
save him? I can't swim!
And even if I could, the
skysharks would eat me, too!
[SHURA] He doesn't want us
to hurt any of his friends,
he's begging us to
not torch his ship,
and he says, of course,
that he doesn't want to die.
I'm at a loss here.
[groans] You're a greedy
little hairball, aren't you?
And you get under my skin.
Then...
...why don't you try
putting up a fight?!
Sky Knight...
[PIERRE squawking]
Pathetic Sky Knight.
You were God, now you're
nothing! Nothing!
Can't even defeat
a priest like me.
[CHOPPER screams]
I'll save you!
[PIERRE screeches]
[SHURA]
Ha! Ignorant little creature.
[FUZA squawks]
You're diving into
your own watery grave.
[CHOPPER groans]
[PIERRE squawking]
[SHURA] And now for the
Sky Knight's noble steed.
You no longer have a purpose.
Follow your master!
[PIERRE screeches]
[PIERRE groans]
[squawking]
[SHURA]
I do wish that I could be there
to watch the life drain
from your faces.
But alas, I have other
matters to attend to.
Ah.
I wonder if the three fugitives
have been captured yet.
Could a well really be
that interesting?
[ROBIN]
Yes. Don't you think it's odd
that a well would be
stuck under a tree?
The balance between civilization
and nature here is off.
Well, unless we find a way
to cross this cloud river,
we'll be stuck in this forest.
[ZORO] And we're still nowhere
near where we wanna be.
[ROBIN] It's like the
people who built this
didn't know the tree
would grow to be so large.
I've never seen
anything like it.
[ZORO]
Hey, Nami!
Can you see anything up there?
[NAMI]
The island where God lives...
Upper Yard.
[ZORO]
Nami! Say somethin', would ya?
What do you see?
Hey, can you hear me?
What do you think
she sees up there?
[NAMI gasps]
This island... can't be...
[SATORI laughing]
[SATORI]
There's no way you can win!
After all, I'm a priest,
and you all look so tired.
Why don't you just end
this now and die? [laughs]
My heart can't take
anymore of this.
Too many surprises.
Ow, it hurts.
You'll be out of
options quite soon.
It's sad really.
Your little boat has nearly
reached the forest's exit
and when that happens,
it's all over for you! [laughs]
You'll have nowhere to go
unless, of course,
you suddenly learn to fly!
[LUFFY panting]
[SATORI] You'll wander around in
this terribly unfamiliar forest
and die of exhaustion! [laughs]
[LUFFY]
That won't...
Hm?
...happen!
[SATORI]
Ha! Nice try!
My turn now!
[LUFFY gasps]
[SATORI]
Sphere Dragon attack!
You know you can't run forever.
And wherever you stop,
the fire-bomb ball will be
waiting to incinerate you!
[SATORI laughs]
[LUFFY panting]
[laughs]
[USOPP] Good, looks like
we can still make it.
I'll just leave things
here with you, Luffy!
[LUFFY yelling]
That tree... will not
give you any shelter.
[LUFFY]
It's like he's reading my mind!
Stay outta my head
and quit following me!
[LUFFY grunts]
[SATORI]
What are you doing?
[LUFFY grunts]
A wire! What the--?
Wait, this must be how
he controls the dragon!
I'll just...
No, stop!
...do this!
[gasps] You ruined
my Sphere Dragon,
you impudent little brat!
Now you die!
Get over here this
instance! [grunts]
[yelling]
[SATORI gasps]
Let go of the dragon, you fool!
[SATORI screaming]
[USOPP]
There it is!
Yeah, I was right!
I knew I could find the
way out of this place!
Of course! This makes
perfect sense.
Why didn't I think
of this sooner?
When we fell before, it was
from a very high altitude.
So it's only natural that the
exit be at the same height.
And now that I know
where the exit is,
the boat doesn't
really matter anymore.
All right.
That huge explosion
worries me. I'd better hurry.
Game time.
[USOPP]
Ow!
[SATORI panting]
That was close!
That maniac must've
had a death wish!
This isn't good. [pants]
I've got to intensify
my training.
I can't let a weakling like him
get the upperhand in a fight!
Not even for a second!
That might block me
from using my Mantra!
[LUFFY]
You're right!
[SATORI gasps]
That was close!
It's you! How are
you still alive?
--[LUFFY chuckles]
--[SATORI screams]
[SATORI]
Get off me!
You horrible little man!
I'll get you for this!
Let go of me right now!
[SANJI]
Do not let him go, Luffy.
You, too?
Hey, Sanji, where've you been?
I was out cold on
the forest floor!
Where else would I
have been, you idiot?!
But... that's beside the point.
[SANJI]
See, the point is
that you keep saying challenge
this and challenge that,
which normally
wouldn't interest me.
However, there are
two helpless ladies
waiting for me to
come to their rescue,
and I refuse to let them down.
So I'm proposing this.
And I think you'll like it.
Ordeal of love.
[SATORI]
This guy's an idiot, too!
Unhand me this instant,
you maggots!
[SATORI yelling]
It's just not fair!
You have no honor,
ganging up two against one!
[SANJI]
We have no honor?
You creeps kidnapped our friends
and tried to murder a
beautiful young angel.
And you accuse us of
not having any honor?
[SATORI whimpers]
I've been thinking.
It's pretty amazing that you
can predict our movements.
But what good is that...
...if you do can't anything
to avoid 'em, huh? [chuckles]
[SATORI screams]
[SATORI]
Stop! Stop, I said!
Are you listening?
How dare you disobey me!
I'm a priest in God's service!
Not being judged by me is a
first-degree crime in Skypiea!
Let me go!
Now listen here!
Attacking me means you declare
war on the Almighty God Eneru!
I got a question.
Do you ever cook?
Well, you don't have
to be a chef to know
which dish is best served cold.
[SATORI screams]
You know, this dish is
really quite simple.
Step one:
season the main course
with a smattering of defeat.
[SANJI grunts]
Then, you must brutally
and without hesitation
tenderize the meat.
[SATORI screams]
No! You can't do this!
No!
No! Please! No, don't hurt me!
[SATORI screams]
[SANJI]
Delicious!
[yelling]
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[LUFFY]
All in a day's work!
What's the next ordeal?
[SANJI]
After an ordeal of love
comes an ordeal
of romance! Ladies!
[NAMI]
C'mon, follow me!
We have to get to
the shore somehow!
[ZORO] Things are startin'
to look like trouble!
[WYPER]
Now is our chance!
Today we crush the priests
and take back Upper Yard!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Light the Fire of Shandora!
Wyper, the Warrior!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!