Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Alright, here I come!
Like an arrow
forged with lightning!
Lightning Bone Sword!
Gavotte Bond En Avant!
[BROOK] As they say,
mission accomplished.
[OARS]
Gum-Gum...
Oh, no! He's goin' after Brook!
[OARS]
...Battle Axe!
Skeleton!
Leave Robin alone!
Now Gum-Gum...
This looks bad.
Really bad.
[OARS]
...Gatling!
Sanji! Chopper!
[LUFFY]
"The Incredible Battle Starts!
Luffy vs. Luffy!"
Kushishishi! Kushishishi!
Kushishishi!
Let's see. Three left.
Now commence with the stomping
and finish them all off.
[USOPP]
Please no!
What now?
We've already thrown
everything we've got at him
and he's still standing!
There's gotta be something.
C'mon, think, you guys!
Hey, Usopp.
I'll make an opening for you.
Here goes nothing.
[USOPP] Wha... Wait,
make an opening for what?
Oh. I get it!
Well, it's worth
a shot, at least!
'Kay!
Hey! What's going on now? Usopp!
[OARS]
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
--[ZORO] What?
--[OARS] Now Gum-Gum...
One Hundred and Eight Caliber...
[OARS]
...Bell!
If one of those
hits me, I'm dead.
I can't keep this up.
Is Usopp ready yet?
You may be a giant,
but Usopp is about to show you
that real men come in all sizes!
Hey, pay attention.
[ZORO] If it was up to me,
I'd keep fighting you
'til I couldn't lift my swords,
but we're almost out of time.
What do you say
we end this right now?
[OARS]
Okay.
Kushishishi!
Oh, we'll end this.
But be honest, you don't
think you can actually win
after that beating
you took, do you?
[ZORO]
Uh-huh.
[MORIA] My! We've got a
real optimist here, don't we!
[ZORO] I'm pretty stubborn when
I set my sights on something.
Now let's see what you got.
Finish me if you can.
This moron's trying
to mess with your head, Oars.
Less talking, more pounding!
[OARS]
I know that already!
I'll beat him on my own, Master.
Just watch me!
[OARS]
Gum-Gum...
Zoro!
[ZORO]
One Gorilla,
Two Gorilla.
Three Sword Style.
...Pistol!
Two Gorilla...
...Slash!
I'll get you!
Crap!
My arm is stuck!
Damn it, argh!
[ZORO]
Three Sword Style.
Demonic Raven!
[NAMI]
Did... Did he stop him?
[ZORO]
Usopp! Now!
[OARS]
Right arm again?
That ain't gonna work!
I told you so!
That's enough of you!
[ZORO]
Where did he...?
Zoro!
There. That's another one down.
Hey, Oars!
Over here, stupid!
Got him.
The heck was that?
It felt like
something in my mouth.
You didn't!
You little bastard!
Hold on.
What just happened here?
I did it. I got him.
It's over, you guys!
Oars swallowed the salt!
[USOPP]
Yeah! Take that!
[USOPP cheering]
[NAMI] Wait. Why is
salt such a big deal?
Oh that's right,
you don't know, huh?
If you feed a zombie salt,
it kicks out their shadow!
Just watch! Oars is done for!
That's Luffy's shadow!
Oh yeah, you big dumb monster!
It's over! Good riddance!
You lose!
Kushishishi!
You thought you had me, huh?
[USOPP]
That was just Moria's shadow!
[MORIA]
Gimme a break.
You don't think
I know my own weakness?
Kushishishi!
It was so hard not to laugh!
Oh, but it was worth it!
I was guarding him with
my shadow the whole time,
watching you numbskulls stumble
all over yourselves for nothing!
Too bad! Kushishishi!
Kushishishi! Kushi!
I know how important
this salt is to you.
Take it back!
Usopp!
Kushishishi! Ahaha!
[NAMI]
You okay?
[USOPP coughing]
Oh no, the salt!
Brook risked
his life to get this!
No! No! This is all
we've got! We can't lose it!
Damn it!
How dare you
make a fool out of me!
I'll pick it up and try again no
matter how many times it takes!
[OARS]
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
Finish him!
No.
Usopp!
[NAMI]
Stop it! Please, that's enough!
You're killing him, you monster!
Stop! I said that's enough!
Kushishishi!
What's that now?
Don't want us
to stomp your friend?
Then we'll stomp you instead!
Kushishishi!
Crush them! Crush them all!
Stomp them 'til there's
nothing left to stomp!
And when you're done here,
crush the ones
we've already beaten!
They're still
breathing, you know!
You have a job to do!
I won't be happy
'til they're as flat
as a bunch of pancakes!
[LUFFY]
Hey, big guy.
Might wanna stop that.
What do you think
you're stomping, anyway?
You looking for these two?
'Cause you're not even close.
Huh? I...
We're still alive? Wow.
I dunno what's
going on, but thank you.
That was a close call back the--
What?
Who're you? Get lost!
[LUFFY]
You don't recognize me?
The name's Monkey D. Luffy.
L-Lu...
[USOPP AND NAMI]
Luffy?
[USOPP]
It can't be!
I mean, he's blue!
W-Well, I guess he
does look a bit like him.
C'mon blue guy, be honest.
Are you really Luffy?
Yeah, it's me. Stop asking.
[USOPP]
That's not very convincing.
But okay, what happened to you?
[MORIA]
I thought he was just rubber.
Does he have some sort
of transformation power
I didn't know about?
Unless maybe...
[LUFFY] So he already
took out the rest of the crew?
Uh, yeah. 'Fraid so.
He teamed up with Moria.
We hardly even stood a chance.
Is that right?
Then stand back.
[USOPP] Wait, you're
gonna fight him on your own?
He doesn't just have
your fighting ability.
He can stretch
like you now, too!
And I know you got big all of
a sudden, but he's way bigger!
I mean, you got a plan, right?
[OARS] Hey, what are
those guys talking about?
It doesn't matter.
Hurry. Crush them.
You got it.
Gum-Gum...
Here it comes! Ah!
...Rifle!
Huuuuuh?!
[LUFFY]
There's only one Luffy. It's me.
You got a problem with that?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 372A]
What is that?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 372B]
It's huge.
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 372C]
It's flying!
No way! It can't be!
That's Oars!
Awesome!
[USOPP] I mean,
that is Luffy, right?
We're sure about that?
I have no idea
what's going on here.
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372A]
He did it!
He really did it!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372B]
He put Oars in his place!
Now's our chance!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372C]
Let's find 'em!
Wait, who are those guys?
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372D]
I got nothing.
You see anyone?
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372E]
No, not over here.
Oh, hey!
Man. these guys
don't look so hot.
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372F]
I found another one!
Oh wow,
these wounds are really bad.
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372G]
They took a beating out there.
This guy's got
nothing left but bones!
[LOLA] It's too dangerous
to leave them here.
Hurry, get them someplace safe!
[USOPP]
Who are these people?
I can't tell what
they're doing down there.
You think they're zombies?
It looks like they're
taking the crew away!
We'd better go stop them, then.
Okay!
Now Gum-Gum Stamp!
Oh man.
This is getting way out of hand!
He's kicking Oars' ass!
That ain't right!
That just ain't right.
Pull it together out there!
Hey! Oars!
Hey, guys!
This is even
worse than we thought!
Master Moria's in Oars' stomach!
--What?
How?
How could the master of all the
zombies on Thriller Bark lose?
He has Oars at his command.
He's supposed to be
invincible, right?
This doesn't
make any damn sense!
Oars is a legend!
A demon!
And our master's one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
They should be able to stomp
every pirate in the world!
Just who the hell is this guy?
Yeah, I don't get it.
He's "Nightmare Luffy"?
So just to be clear,
you stole a hundred
shadows from the zombies,
then stuffed them
in Luffy's body,
and that's what
made him so big?
Yes, exactly right.
It gave him the
strength he needed.
To be honest, when
we saw him transform
we got pretty
freaked out ourselves.
Either way, that power
of his is only gonna last
another two or three minutes.
After that, all the shadows
will go flying out of his body
and he'll go back to normal.
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
I know we sprung this on him
without asking or anything,
but we just want
to be human again!
We just wanna see the sun
and leave this island,
no matter what it takes!
I know it's crazy,
but it's the only way!
The morning is
almost upon us now.
In the next few minutes,
the fate of every last victim
on the island will be decided.
Fight well, Nightmare Luffy.
We're all counting on you.
Huh?
He crushed the entire building!
Let's go before he
crushes us, too!
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
Yeah!
You really did it, Luffy!
Eat that, Oars!
Little punk!
I'll squish you flat!
Now Gum-Gum...
...Bullet!
Come on, pull it together,
Oars! You're pathetic!
Even if he's big and blue,
there's only one of him!
Damn it!
Where did he get all
that power from, anyway?
I'd better get out of here
before he comes after me.
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
All right, Gum-Gum...
[OARS]
...Axe!
Now Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 372D]
Master Moria!
[LOLA]
He's coming down! Be careful!
I guess we don't
need salt after all.
Wait a second. Where is Luffy?
The shadows.
They're all leaving.
Whoa, that looks bad.
Do you think he'll be okay?
Luffy!
Hey! You're alive, right?
Wait, we're not
dreaming, are we?
I never thought
I'd see this day.
It's true.
Straw Hat really is our savior!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE I] Oars
is down! The battle is over!
We're finally gonna
get our shadows back!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE J]
Thriller Bark has fallen!
[ZORO] Three-Sword Style,
Secret Technique:
Three Thousand Worlds!
[SANJI]
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
[ZORO] We're up
against your shadow!
[SANJI] Settle the
score yourself, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
You bet I will!
This ends now!
Third gear!
On the next One Piece:
"The End of the Battle is Nigh!
Pound in the Finishing Move!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!