Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the next
King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use
any means necessary
to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue.
The crew will cut a path
across the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] In an attempt
to rescue his brother Ace,
Luffy enlisted the aid
of the Pirate Empress,
Boa Hancock to sneak
onto a Navy Vessel
bound for Impel Down.
[GARP] I'm sure you heard about
what your brother's been up to.
Now, I don't expect us
to get along perfect,
but challenging the
World Government head-on
and wrecking up Enies Lobby
is over the line,
Oh, by the way.
I told the little punk
about his father.
[GARP] 'Course, the news
took him by surprise.
Can't blame the boy.
[ACE] "Our fathers?"
To hell with them.
And to hell with you if you ever
thought we could be Marines.
We've both got the
blood of criminals
flowing through our veins
and that was only gift those
bastards ever gave us.
I took the name
"Portgas" from my mother
because I owe her so much.
But I don't owe my
"father" a damned thing.
I don't even
remember the bastard.
Heh. He can keep his name.
[GARP] I know, I know, but
the man tried. He wanted to--
[ACE]
Enough, all right?
Listen to me.
Don't fight it.
Run wild with us.
Our flag will be yours.
[WHITEBEARD]
And I will call you my son.
[ACE]
Whitebeard is my only father.
Got it, old man?
Better for us to quit
while we're still ahead.
Buggy the Clown had a good run,
but I'm afraid his luck
as a pirate has run out.
[MOHJI]
No! I refuse to accept it!
He's a man among men.
The only way Captain Buggy can
go out is in a blaze of glory!
All right. Impel Down.
This is it.
[HANNYABAL] Welcome to
my prison, Impel Down.
Oops, jumped the gun there.
It's not, well,
exactly mine just yet.
I'm the Vice Warden Hannyabal--
well, for now at least.
A pleasure to meet you,
Vice Admiral.
Oh. And don't forget these.
[DOMINO] Keep in mind that
they're sea prism stone.
You call me a "visitor" here.
Not a prisoner.
Then you put me in those?
[NARRATOR]
Countdown to Ace's Execution.
33 Hours.
[LUFFY]
A Reunion in Hell?
The Man Who Ate
the Chop-Chop Fruit!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL buzzing]
You'd leave me powerless?
How cruel.
But necessary.
[SURVEILLANCE GUYS moaning]
[HANCOCK giggles]
Be gentle-- I'm delicate.
[DOMINO gasps]
[SURVEILLANCE GUY 422A gasps]
What happened?
[HANCOCK]
It's safe now, Luffy.
[LUFFY grunts]
Wow. That was close!
I was startin' to think
I'd just have to crawl
out from there like a cockroach
and hope for the best.
That power of yours really
is handy in a pinch, huh?
Even so. I'm afraid
that this is as far
as I'll be able
to accompany you.
They're quite insistent
on placing me
in those Sea Prism
Stone Handcuffs.
And once they take my cloak,
you'll have nowhere to hide.
I just wish...
I wish I could do more
to help you, but--
Aw, don't talk like that.
You got me in this
place, didn't you?
That's more than
I coulda done alone.
Even though there's
guards everywhere,
we made it all this
way no problem.
I can handle the rest.
[HANCOCK sighs]
Luffy...
Huh?
Breaking your brother out
will be challenging enough,
but if you get captured as well,
who knows what horrors
you might face.
One wrong step and you may never
see the light of day again.
I know you want to save Ace,
but this is dangerous.
Please, take care
of yourself, too.
[HANCOCK gasps]
I won't let you down,
you have my word.
Thanks for everything,
Hancock, you're the best.
I won't forget what you've done.
Not for the rest of my life!
[HANCOCK]
He just called me by my name.
My real, actual name.
For the first time!
[LUFFY] Cool! Whatever
works for you, Hammock!
Can I get seconds
over here, Hammock?
Hey, Hammock.
What're you doin'?
Hey, Hancock.
[HANCOCK giggling, sighing]
My life is finally complete.
I can die happy!
Hey. You can turn
that lady back now.
I should be fine up here.
Say it, Luffy.
Say my name again.
Uh, what?
[MOMONGA]
This is taking too long.
[HANNYABAL]
This situation is unprecedented,
she's probably just
being thorough.
Heh. A thorough body search.
[MOMONGA]
Hm?
[HANNYABAL gasps]
That's so naughty!
Get your mind out
of the gutter, damn it!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Beep! Beep!
[SURVEILLANCE GUY 422A]
Vice Warden Hannyabal!
We're not getting any visuals
from the surveilance snail
in the examination room.
Is something going on in
there we don't know about?
Huh?
[HANNYABAL] Domino.
Something wrong in there?
No answer, huh?
It's okay. I am the
Vice Warden, right?
Checking things out in there
is strictly business, you see.
Even if that business
happens to involve
two hot chicks
touching each other.
Ugh.
[HANNYABAL]
Huh?
[HANCOCK]
Hmph.
We have completed
the body search, sir.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Beep beep.
[SURVEILLANCE GUY 422A]
Scratch that last report.
Everything is fine here.
I hope I didn't cause
a problem, sir.
Did the exam take too long?
Huh? No. Everything's
fine on our end, too.
[HANCOCK] Hmph. I see that your
guests are treated as poorly
as your prisoners here.
Surely an empress
deserves better than this.
[HANNYABAL] It is a pity.
But in Impel Down,
we can't afford to make
exceptions to the rules.
[DOMINO] I wonder why I can't
shake this strange feeling.
[HANCOCK]
Lead the way.
[HANNYABAL] Ah, yes, if you'll
let me in front, please.
Or, just go that way.
Before we visit Ace,
we'll take this elevator
to what we call the
"Burning Heat Floor,"
where we'll stop by the
Warden Magellan's office.
Fair warning: As the name
implies, it's quite hot there.
[HANCOCK]
Luffy! Be bold, but be safe.
[whispering]
Bye Hancock-- Thank you.
[HANCOCK gasps]
Is something wrong?
[HANCOCK]
"Han... cock... I love you."
Oh! He really does love me!
[MOMONGA] Easy.
[HANNYABAL] Empress Hancock,
[HANNYABAL] what's wrong?
Do you need mouth-to-mouth?
[DOMINO]
Are you ill?
You were fine
just a moment ago--
What happened?
'Kay. Not sure where to
take things from here.
Hancock said Ace is
probably underwater.
Looks like that elevator
might head down a long way.
Oh yeah.
The Vivre Card
might come in handy.
Here we go.
[SEA KING 423A growls]
[GUARD 423A]
The Blugoris are returning.
[GUARD 423B] Looks like
they grabbed dinner, too.
Open the hatch.
[GUARD 423A]
Nice work.
[GUARD 423B] Get it to the
fridge and we'll be done.
[BLUGORI pants]
[HANCOCK grunts]
[MOMONGA]
Hm?
Hope you're feeling
better, Empress.
We should be passing through
level one any second now.
[PRISONER screams]
[PRISONERS screaming]
Lemme outta here, damn it!
[PRISONER 423B screams]
[MOMONGA]
It's even worse than I expected.
[DOMINO]
Surely you jest.
This floor hosts
relatively minor offenders
so these whippings are
mostly a formality.
Madness.
And yet, it's the truth.
Level one of Impel Down
is known as the
Crimson Floor, by the way.
[HANCOCK]
What's crimson about it?
[HANNYABAL]
That would be a secret!
Level 2 is the "Floor of
Wild Beasts from Hell."
Pretty straightforward.
As we move deeper underwater,
we reach Level 3,
The Starvation Floor.
Followed by Level 4,
the Burning Heat Floor,
which is our destination.
You can't tell from the surface,
but this structure is
actually quite expansive.
Since it takes a while for
this elevator to get to Level 4,
you'll have plenty
of time to indulge
in the cacophony of screams.
And is Fire Fist Ace on Level 4?
No and that isn't the
bottom floor, either--
we have a wide
selection of torturous...
[HANCOCK]
Luffy...
[LUFFY grunts]
Ace should be down
these stairs, somewhere.
[RANDOM PRISONER 423B]
No fair! You cheater!
We thought you
were just a clown--
you didn't tell us
you could do that!
[BUGGY]
Can it, would you?
The real clowns here
are you losers,
getting whipped like
dogs every damn day.
Of course I'm gonna break
out first chance I get!
[RANDOM PRISONER 423B] Are you
just gonna run out on us?
[BUGGY]
Huh?
That sounds like something
a friend would say
and you folks're
no friends of mine.
I'm a free eagle, chumps--
so deal with it!
If you don't like
being in there,
why don't you
slip out like me?
What's that? You can't?
Well, I guess you're just
going to have to die, huh?
[BUGGY cackles]
Kiss my ass, suckers! C'mon!
[PRISONER 423C]
You won't get away with this.
Buggy!
I'm getting away just fine!
[PRISONERS yelling]
[BUGGY panting]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL buzzing]
[BUGGY] A Surveillance
Transponder Snail?
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL buzzing]
[BUGGY gasps]
Hi fellas!
[SURVEILLANCE GUY]
We found him!
That's Buggy the Clown,
prisoner from Level 1,
community Cell number 4.
He's in the hallway in front
of solitary cell number 22.
[SURVEILLANCE GUY]
Grab him, quick!
Damn it. Stupid snail!
This is your fault!
[PRISONERS laughing]
[SURVEILLANCE GUY] Surveillance
Transponder Snail 71
has been shut off!
You blew it, Buggy old pal!
Don't come crying to us
when they're torturing
you to death!
Serves ya right, ya dummy!
Yeah! He'll wish he
was dead for sure!
[PRISONERS cackle]
[BLUGORIS panting]
[PRISONER 423H]
Here come the Blugoris!
[PRISONER 423I]
Happy hunting!
[PRISONER 423J]
Make him suffer!
[PRISONERS laughing]
[LUFFY panting] The Vivre Card
keeps leading me down,
but now what?
Guess I'm outta stairs.
[GUARD 423C] Alright men.
We're looking for prisoner 8200.
[GUARD 423D]
What, that stupid clown?
[GUARD 423E] No one knew
he had Devil Fruit powers.
You got the handcuffs?
[GUARD]
Yeah, we're good.
[GUARD 423C]
Let's move!
Split up and flank him!
[LUFFY]
Cool. I made it.
[GUARD 423C]
Hurry!
Wonder what's up?
[LUFFY grunts] So all of
these are prison cells?
[BUGGY screaming]
What's that?
Eh. I gotta get moving.
[BUGGY grunting]
Go away, you buncha jerks!
[BUGGY screams]
[BUGGY]
Have mercy on me!
[LUFFY]
This way?
[BUGGY panting]
[BLUGORI panting]
They're gone.
Heh? "Danger?"
It already has a skull!
Who's gonna press it?
[BUGGY gasps]
[LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY yelping]
Ah, jeez.
[LUFFY gasps]
[BUGGY yelping]
That was close.
[LUFFY]
Why did the traps go off?
[GUARD 423E] Hey, the traps
activated over there!
Surround the hallway!
Crap. The guards are coming.
[GUARD 423E]
Halt!
[LUFFY grunts]
Wuh-oh!
[GUARDS yelp]
Huh? They're gone.
Well, that was lucky.
[LUFFY grunts]
Huh? Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Huh?
Buddy, slow down, hold on a sec.
Kinda busy.
[PRISONER MOHAWK]
Yeah, that's what it looks like,
but how the heck did you
get outta your cell?
[PRISONER 423K]
Hey, what's going on?
I didn't "get out," I
"came in" from the outside.
Well, bye!
[PRISONER MOHAWK]
Hey, hold up!
There's no way that's the truth!
Yuh-huh. It's so true.
You don't look like a jailer.
So who are you and why
the hell're you here?
He's not behind bars
so maybe it's true!
You guys have some
really bad attitudes.
Wait a sec.
Any of you know where
I can find Ace?
Uh, Ace?
Wait, Ace? You mean, him?
The guy on death row?
That's the one. I came here
to bust him outta this place.
[PRISONER CHINSTRAP]
Yeah, good luck with that!
We don't get a lotta
info down here,
but I heard they
just brought him in.
If that's true and he is here,
then he's gotta be on Level 5.
No way you're
gettin' down there.
You're screwed pal.
That's the floor where
they hold all the prisoners
with a bounty of
100 million or more.
Level 5, huh?
Oh, by the way, pal.
While you're here, think you
could run to the jailer's room
and pick us up some keys?
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Yeah buddy, wouldn't
be no trouble, right?
[PRISONER MOHAWK]
This has gotta be destiny, man,
I mean what else would
bring us together like this?
It's like you were born
to set us free, right?
[BUGGY screams]
[LUFFY]
Huh? What're those things?
[PRISONER]
The Blugoris!
I don't like 'em.
Run! Hurry!
They're gonna kill you!
[BUGGY panting]
[BLUGORI grunting]
[LUFFY yelps]
[BUGGY screams]
Whoa! I take it
back, I like you!
Right side.
And left side!
Unite!
[BUGGY cackles]
How you like that, suckers?
You can cut me all you want,
I ate the Chop-Chop fruit!
[BUGGY yells]
Straw Hat?
What the hell
are you doing here?
Huh?
Oh. Buggy.
[BUGGY yells] Thanks for
reminding me why I hate you!
I see prison hasn't made
you any less annoying!
Speaking of, guess that
king of the pirate thing
ain't working out too well.
I came here on my own,
only dumb people like you
get caught and thrown in jail!
Say what?
You threw yourself in jail and
you're calling me the dumb one?
[BUGGY gasps]
You must've known I was here.
That's the real reason
you broke in, isn't it?
To save me.
[BUGGY]
Ew! I'm not into you, weirdo!
Just shut up and get
the hell out of my way!
I told Hancock I'd
take care of myself,
then you got all these stupid
axe monkeys chasin' after me!
[BUGGY] Oh. I see,
this is all about you, is it?
Stop touching me, you clown!
[BUGGY groans]
[LUFFY grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
[BLUGORI grunts]
[LUFFY, BUGGY muffled scream]
This was supposed
to be a cinch!
I called it "Buggy's
Peaceful Escape Plan."
Does this look peaceful to you?
Who cares?
[BUGGY screams]
[BLUGORIS grunting]
They're surrounding us. Damn it.
I hate this!
[LUFFY] Hey, shouldn't we
just beat those things up?
Easy for you to say--
you haven't been tortured!
Oh, how my delicate body
has suffered from the blows
of these monsters.
Why d'you think I'm running
away in the first place?
Yeah, but I wasn't
planning to lose.
Right. Clearly, you've
thought this out.
I'm on a mission here.
My cover's already been blown,
so I gotta get this
done in a hurry.
[BUGGY grunting] Y'know,
that's the number one reason
why I hate you and
that red head so much.
Both of you are
always so optimistic
in the worst way possible.
All right, fine, I'll go
along with your crazy plan.
It's not like I have a choice!
Time for my specialty.
[LUFFY grunts]
[BLUGORIS grunting]
Causing chaos!
Works for me!
[BUGGY grunts]
[LUFFY yells]
[BLUGORIS groan]
[BUGGY grunts]
[LUFFY grunts]
[NARRATOR] After forming
an unlikely alliance,
Luffy is able to race
through Impel Down,
thanks to the help of
Buggy's Chop-Chop powers.
However, when they make
their way to what is know as
The Crimson Hell,
they discover their descent
will not be as swift
as it first seemed.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Break Through the Crimson Hell!
Buggy's Chaos-Inducing Plan!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!