[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
♪Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
Huh? What the heck is that?
Hey! I see a flock
of birds starboard!
[SANJI]
Sounds like lunch to me.
You said it!
Gum‐Gum...
...Grab!
[SANJI]
Dial it down or we're gonna‐‐
No kinda fish I've ever seen.
It's no fish, it's a girl.
[screams]
[APIS]
He says it's a strong one.
A wind's coming.
[NAMI]
Here goes.
Ha! We got a good wind, huh?
We did it!
[ZORO] But it seems to me
we're not even moving.
You feel that?
[NAMI screams]
No! We're screwed!
We've entered the Calm Belt!
[USOPP]
The Clam Belt?
[LUFFY]
What's that?
[NAMI]
Calm Belt!
A part of the sea where
nothing moves a muscle!
[LUFFY]
So there's mussels and clams?!
[NAMI]
No!
What was that? An earthquake?
A good trick since we're at sea.
All of this chitchat isn't
going to get us outta here.
Fold the sails and
start paddling now!
We have to get back on course!
[SANJI]
You can count on me.
Don't panic.
And besides, this is a sailboat.
Why do we need to paddle?
[USOPP]
True.
And why would we go through
the trouble of doubling back
when the Marines
are waiting for us?
Look, there's no time to argue.
Just shut up and do as I say!
At least it's nice
and quiet here.
[NAMI]
Ugh!
Fine! If I need to explain
it to you, I will!
In our haste to escape
from the Marines,
we ended up going too far south
and now we're off course
and stuck out here.
[LUFFY] South? So we
entered the Grand Line?
[USOPP]
Woohoo!
If we were at the Grand Line,
you think I'd waste my
time explaining this?!
Now look!
The Grand Line is
sandwiched in the middle
between these two green areas
you see here, ya understand?
These areas, just
as they're labeled,
are what's called
the Calm Belts.
That's where we are!
Nobody knows why,
but inside the Calm Belt,
there's no wind and no current.
It's like a void where
everything's stagnate.
Given that sailboats move
by catching winds,
this is more than a dangerous
region, it can be fatal!
Get it?
[LUFFY] Nope, but it sounds
like we're in big trouble.
[NAMI] Good. You retained more
than I thought you would.
[SANJI] So this is what
that geezer meant
when he said it was dangerous.
[ZORO] Well that explains
why we haven't gotten
a single gust of wind.
[USOPP]
How're we gonna get outta this
if our ship can't move?
[LUFFY] Maybe the wind'll
start blowing again.
[NAMI] Wind never blows
in the Calm Belt!
And that's not all.
There's another good reason
that people call this
area dangerous.
It's infested with‐‐
[ALL yelp]
What was that?!
It's big!
Here they come!
Whoa!
[LUFFY]
Sea Monsters! They're gigantic!
The Calm Belt is also
home to the Sea Kings.
It's their main place
for breeding.
They're the biggest reason
people can't cross
the Calm Belt.
[LUFFY]
"Miraculous Creature!
Apis' Secret and the
Legendary Island!"
Any idea how we
get out of this?
Yes. Everybody,
don't move a muscle.
We don't wanna give
them any reason
to stick around or eat us.
Once they're gone,
we'll paddle back. Got it?
You call that a plan?!
[NAMI]
Shut up!
[USOPP]
Sorry.
A giant frog is attacking us!
[ALL screaming]
Hold on!
Your arm! It's stretching!
Luffy, did you get your ability
from eating a Devil Fruit?!
Yeah, that's right.
Hey!
Stretch your arm
downwards again!
[USOPP]
Luffy!
What are you doing?!
No idea guys.
Apis!
Watch out!
[APIS]
One... two...
What in the hell
did she just do?
Yanked a nose hair.
That didn't improve anything!
It sounds like it's gonna‐‐
[SANJI]
Brace yourselves!
I think this behemoth's
gonna sneeze!
No way! It's huge!
[LUFFY] Get ready!
We're goin' for a ride!
[ALL]
There's gotta be a better way!
Oh wow! It feels
like we're flying!
[USOPP] In case you haven't
noticed, we are flying!
[NAMI] Looks like we landed
back where we started.
[ZORO] Yeah, and no sign
of the Marines either.
[USOPP whimpers]
I thought I was a goner.
Quick thinking!
Thank you!
Okay! Set the sails!
[NAMI]
And our destination is?
[LUFFY]
Where else?!
Warship Island!
[USOPP]
I can't see a thing.
[LUFFY]
Well, we can see the fog.
[SANJI] Apis, are you certain
about the coordinates?
[APIS]
No.
[USOPP]
Heh. "No"? But you said‐‐
[NAMI] Relax. I'm sure we'll
come upon it any moment now.
You're so confident.
I sure wouldn't
side against you.
[APIS]
Look!
[LUFFY] Ooh! It's a sailboat!
It's gigantic!
Not so fast.
You say it's gigantic?
That doesn't begin
to describe it.
[LUFFY] Okay, fine.
It's super humongous.
[NAMI]
No! You're missing the point!
That's not a ship.
That's the island itself!
It was named because
it looks like a warship!
Yeah, I see it now!
[VILLAGER A]
That ship's flag!
They're pirates!
Pirates are coming!
We're being invaded by pirates!
Pirates?!
Stay inside!
I'm home! Hi, everyone!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
What are you doing?
Why are you with pirates?
[VILLAGER A] Why did you
bring them here, Apis?
Hey, you, I have a question.
Yeah? What do you want?
Do you know of any good
barbecue restaurants here?
[VILLAGERS]
Huh?
What kind of a question
is that, pirate?
Relax! They're not bad pirates.
They're nice and helpful!
I didn't think there
was such a thing
as a nice and helpful pirate.
[APIS]
Yep!
How is it you ended up
with these people?
The last time we saw you, you
were taken away by the Marines.
That's right.
But I escaped from the Marines.
and then... I was
stranded in the ocean,
but they rescued me
just in time.
[LUFFY]
Yep.
[VILLAGER A] Apis, why
were you taken from us
in the first place?
[VILLAGER B] Yeah, the reason
the Marines came after you
is a mystery!
[VILLAGER C] It isn't safe
for you to stay here.
Those Marines are
still lurking around.
Where should I go?
[VILLAGER C] We really would
like to help, but...
Wait a minute! These strangers
are pirates, right?
Ehh... So what do I do?
Listen, we aren't
out to get you.
[BOKUDEN]
Apis.
[ALL gasp]
Come to my house, child.
[APIS]
Huh?
[NAMI] Who's that?
Don't know.
Grandpa Bokuden!
[BOKUDEN chuckles]
I'm glad you're safe, precious.
Thank you for saving
my granddaughter's life.
I'm in your debt.
I know.
In honor of Apis' safe return,
I'll throw a celebration
for you and your crew.
What's on the menu?
Maybe barbecue?
Sorry, I'm afraid not, Luffy.
But Grandpa Bokuden's pork buns
are the best in
the whole island!
All right! Let's eat!
Sure, I could eat.
[gasps]
[MARINE A]
There she is!
Eric!
I've been here all along, Sir.
[NELSON] I was under the
impression that the girl
got lost in the Calm Belt,
never to return alive.
That's right. She is no more.
No, she's‐‐
[NELSON]
She's back on Warship Island!
Go capture her!
And don't fail me!
You can be sure she won't
slip through our grasp again.
[BOKUDEN]
There we go.
Almost ready.
Just a little bit longer now.
Can't wait!
Smells good!
Finally, real food.
Old man, how much longer
do we have to wait?
[BOKUDEN]
Hm?
Oh, well, if I had to guess, I'd
say no more than 4 or 5 hours.
[LUFFY, USOPP]
What?!
[LUFFY groans]
I'm so hungry.
[NAMI] Bokuden, why are
the Marines after Apis?
What could they
possibly be after?
Apis, do you know why?
[APIS]
No, sir!
[NAMI] That's not
what you said earlier.
You knew but refused to tell.
[APIS]
Oh, that? I lied.
[USOPP]
Huh?
Well... then I don't know...
[USOPP]
You're kidding me!
I'm sorry,
but there's really nothing
significant about this island.
Nothing, I reckon,
except for an old legend.
A legend?
[BOKUDEN] Some say the
people of this island
are descendants of
those from Lost Island,
which sank into the sea
thousands of years ago.
It was also home to
the Millennial Dragons.
The bones of these dragons
are called Dragonite.
Or the Elixir of Immortality.
But it doesn't make sense
that the Marines would invade
your home over a legend.
And why steal the girl?
[USOPP]
I agree.
They'd have to have a
better reason than that.
[NAMI] It certainly sounds
desperate to me.
We're overlooking something.
Maybe the legend holds a clue.
Well then, we should
start at the beginning...
Here we go again...
Kill me now.
[BOKUDEN] ...his heir,
Poke‐Portes, had three children.
The eldest was Boke‐Hontas.
The second son was
Boke‐Bon‐Boko,
and the third was Boke‐Boke‐Pon.
One day, the king said
to his three children,
"Listen to me and obey.
Go find the tree
that grows stars,
which is said to be
in dragon's valley."
So Boke‐Hontas, Boke‐Bon‐Boko,
and Boke‐Boke‐Pon journeyed...
Thank goodness
I got outta there.
Once Grandpa starts that story,
he goes on forever.
[BOKUDEN]
Now, the 317th ruler,
King Ingri‐Mongri the 3rd's son,
Ingri‐Grimori, was quite...
[NAMI] I thought this was a
legend, not a history lesson.
[USOPP]
Who knows...
[snoring]
[BOKUDEN] He was responsible for
implementing major reforms...
[snoring]
Ohh... I'm starving.
I think it'll be a while
before we eat again.
[USOPP] Those pork buns smell
delicious. I want them now!
Pork buns, wh‐‐?
[BOKUDEN] ...65 offspring,
most of them boys...
Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Restroom...
Hold on, Grandpa Ryu.
Oh no!
He's coming here! What do I do?!
Please go! Don't make me!
Oh, yeah... Yummy.
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[LUFFY snoring]
[APIS]
No way!
Hold on. I didn't
even hit him yet.
Pork... bun...
[BOKUDEN] And the 1,111‐‐ No,
the 1,121 king, was Hoke‐Hontas.
He ruled during the most savage,
bloody period in our history...
Hey. Where are you
sneaking off to?
It's okay. Luffy's been
gone a long time.
I'm gonna go check
on him. Be right back.
Uh! No fair.
Nami's simply gorgeous,
even when she's sneaking around!
[NAMI] Ugh. Give it a
rest already, grandpa!
[LUFFY snoring]
[NAMI]
Luffy!
[screams]
[NAMI]
Every bit of food is gone!
So delicious!
What is everyone else gonna eat
now that you've
inhaled everything?!
What? I didn't eat them.
Right.
[NAMI]
This is odd.
There's a trail.
[LUFFY]
Hm... A dead end?
It makes no sense...
[NAMI] Why are you sticking
your head in the bush?
[LUFFY]
Hey, look.
[NAMI]
Looks like the trail picks up
on the other side of this cliff.
Luffy!
Gotcha! Gum‐Gum!
Suspension Bridge.
Grandpa Ryu!
[NAMI] We're on the other
side of the mountain.
[LUFFY]
How far are they gonna go?
Uh! A cave!
[APIS]
Yes, everything turned out fine.
This funny group of pirates
saved me and brought me home.
No, they're not scary at all.
They were very good to me.
I knew you'd be hungry,
so I brought you some of
Grandpa Bokuden's pork buns.
Here you go.
Whoa! Slow down!
You're gonna make yourself sick!
Sorry. I still don't know.
I'm searching as hard as I can,
but I haven't found a clue.
I'll sort this all out.
I promise.
Listen. That's Apis, and
she's talking to someone.
Hey! Apis! Where'd you
put all the pork buns?
Luffy, you're an idiot!
Stay back! Don't come near!
[gasps]
Luffy, what the hell
are you gawking at?
[screams]
[LUFFY] Amazing! I can't
believe this! I‐It's amazing!
Hey, Luffy!
You do exist. I knew it.
That's awesome!
Get off of him! Leave him alone!
[NAMI]
Is this possible?
I thought dragons
were just legends.
But here's one right
before my eyes!
Incredible! Where in the
world did you come from?!
[LUFFY]
Sure, I think I understand.
You wanna go home. Is that it?
[APIS]
Okay.
Luffy, Grandpa Ryu says
it's fine with him
if you wanna be his friend.
He says he can tell
you're a good person.
[chuckles]
Hey, I've been able to
read Grandpa Ryu's mind,
but how did you do it?
I just did.
[APIS]
But how?
I dunno. It just happened.
How'd you know?
[APIS]
I, um...
Oh...
Could it be... a Devil Fruit?
It's okay. Really, there's
no need to be shy about it.
[APIS]
Mh‐hm.
Yeah, I ate one once.
It was called the Whisper
Whisper Fruit or something.
Since then, I've been able to
read the mind of any animal.
So that was it.
How you knew that gust
of wind was coming.
[APIS]
Mh‐hm.
The seabirds were kind
enough to tell me about it.
It was thanks to the
Whisper Whisper Fruit
that I met Grandpa Ryu as well.
Who's there?
[APIS] I remember the first
time I heard his voice.
It was so sad.
I'll help you! Just hold on!
It was you who
called me, wasn't it?
[APIS] When I found him,
he was helpless.
He'd used up the
last of his energy
searching for his friends.
He got separated from
them while flying home
to the Dragons' Nest
on Lost Island.
Wait a minute.
I thought Lost Island sank
into the sea a long time ago.
Lost Island will surface
again eventually.
Grandpa Ryu is absolutely
certain about that.
Grandpa believes the island
will reappear any day now.
But while he's pretty sure
about the "when,"
it's the "where" that's
causing the problem.
He doesn't remember
where it used to be.
It's not his fault.
Grandpa's just gotten old
and lost the energy to fly.
But his spirit's
as strong as ever.
He keeps telling me he wants
to go back to Lost Island
more than anything.
If only I could figure out
a way to find it.
I've searched through old
records, studied ancient maps.
The legend itself doesn't
hold any clues.
So when the Marines stopped by,
I took a chance and
asked for their help.
That was a big mistake.
The only thing they
were interested in
was finding Dragonite.
[NAMI] As in the source
for immortality?
So that's why they
kidnapped you?
To help them find Dragonite?
[APIS]
Yes.
They wanted me to tell
them everything I knew,
but I wouldn't.
Then they became obsessed
when they noticed the pendant
I'd made with a claw
Grandpa Ryu gave me.
[NAMI] Then you escaped
during that storm.
This is all too dangerous.
[APIS]
I know.
That's why I've kept this
a secret from the others,
even Grandpa Bokuden.
I don't wanna cause any
more trouble for them.
But I have to make sure Grandpa
Ryu gets back to his home,
no matter what it takes.
It's the only way to save him.
He says that he'll
get his energy back
once he returns to
the Dragons' Nest.
I'll find a way
to get him there,
no matter if it takes
me a lifetime!
I know how painful
it feels to be far
from home and
everything you love.
Right! If he wants to
go home, then I'll take him!
Huh?
Luffy! Wake up!
You can't take him home!
Lost Island sank into
the sea, remember?!
Look at him. This is a
legendary Millennial Dragon!
He really exists, which
means Lost Island does too!
Luffy, the island sank!
I know! And now
we're gonna find it!
Underwater. No map. It's insane.
I'm in!
All right!
You'll really take him?!
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
Ah, thank you!
[LUFFY] But first
things first, let's eat.
Luffy, wait!
There's one more thing
I forgot to tell you.
Grandpa Ryu is kinda senile.
[ERIC]
That brat was wearing a pendant
that prominently featured
a Millennial Dragon's claw.
Therefore, it stands to reason
she knows all about its
sanctuary, the Lost Island.
That means she must hold
the secret of the Dragonite.
I'll have her soon enough.
♪All that's in my
heart confuses me,
I cannot understand,
As I face what I must do,
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand.
I'll set sail alone,
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near,
As I drift away,
I pray you watch me
as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise,
I began to wonder,
What could be the reason,
It's so hot inside.
No answer has come,
But I can't get away
from what's true,
It's because of you...
Show me how to
catch those feelings,
Get 'em to come back to me,
I'll do what I must,
Because they're
everything I wanna be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back
from yesterday,
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we
can make the way.♪
[SANJI] Take the Millennial
Dragon back to his home?
Why'd you make that promise
without asking us first?
[LUFFY] You know you
wanna find Lost Island!
[ZORO] The Marines are
right on our tail!
[NAMI]
We need to all pull together!
[SANJI] Never fear, Nami!
I'm at your side!
Wow! I'm really looking forward
to this new adventure!
[LUFFY, ZORO, USOPP]
Are you stupid?
[SANJI]
Yes, I'm in love!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Eric Attacks! Great Escape
From Warship Island!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!