[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue.
The crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy has broken
out of Impel Down,
the world's greatest prison,
and is currently headed
to Navy Headquarters
to rescue his brother Ace.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, after being scattered
across the globe,
the rest of the Straw Hats
are locked in the midst
of their own adventures.
[LUFFY]
"The Friends' Whereabouts!
The Chick of Giant Bird
and a Pink Showdown!"
[LUFFY] I get ya.
So it's gonna be even harder
to break into Navy HQ
than Impel Down.
[JIMBEI] They're anticipating
Whitebeard's assault
at any moment, so they're
prepared for all-out war.
And there's no doubt that
they've manned the place
with the most formidable
and infamous figures known
to the world today.
None of us here want
to get ourselves caught
up in a full-blown war,
but I'm afraid that might
be inevitable now.
[NARRATOR]
A short time before any of this,
positioned deep
in the Grand Line,
we find Peachy Island, home
of the Kamabakka Kingdom.
[SANJI panting]
[SANJI] Dammit. I run and I
run, but they never give up!
[ELIZABETH] What's wrong,
pumpkin? Aren't you one of us?
[QUEENS]
Wait!
[ELIZABETH]
[SANJI]
Crap! Quit chasing me!
[QUEENS laugh]
[SANJI]
What?!
[SANJI] This is messed up!
They're freakin' strong as hell!
They may be wearing dresses,
but there's nothin' sissy
about these punks!
Oh, Nami and Robin!
How I long to see your
beauty once more!
[CAROLINE]
Is that so?
There have been some
candy boys in the past
who have had trouble accepting
themselves after washing ashore
on the banks of our
paradise. No matter.
We simply need to extend
an elegant helpin' hand
to the lost soul. I suppose
I should ask if he's strong.
He won't win any
bodybuilding contests,
but his kicks aren't
a total mess.
[CAROLINE] Well, it's been
ages since we've done so,
but I think the traditional
method of the Kamabakka Kingdom
would be best employed
here. [laughs]
[SANJI] Don't you have anything
better to do? Go away!
Quit chasing me! Why won't
you leave me alone?
[QUEENS]
You'll see!
[SANJI]
Like hell, I will!
[SANJI panting]
[SANJI pants]
Where am I?
I wasn't even looking.
Am I safe in here?
What the hell is wrong
with you psychos?!
[laughs]
[SANJI screams]
[groaning] Ow.
[CAROLINE]
I've been waitin' for you.
[SANJI]
Uh...
Hey, hold on. Who is
this bastard?
You do not disrespect
her like that.
Her name is Lady Caroline.
[SANJI]
You the queen here or something?
Me? The queen? Oh, please!
[QUEENS laugh]
[CAROLINE] To be exact, I'm
the queen substitute! Caroline!
[QUEENS]
Oh!
Caroline!
[SANJI]
Uh. You're just a stand-in?
Kamabakka Kingdom is
ruled by one alone,
the legendary Queen Ivankov!
It'd be presumptuous
to call myself queen
just because she's away.
I couldn't give two turds if
you're the actual queen or not.
You've clearly got their ear, so
get it straight! I'm done here!
This is hell! Now get
me off of this rock!
[laughs] Very well. I hear you.
Huh?
[CAROLINE] However. If you're
so desperate to leave, first
you must fight the strongest
of our kingdom and win.
Deal?
You're damn right it's a deal!
Anything to escape
this nightmare!
[QUEENS]
Ooh....
[ELIZABETH chuckles]
Okay!
Let's get you changed
into one of our
traditional Kamabakka combat
outfits before the match.
What? A costume? Seriously?
[QUEENS laughing]
[SANJI]
Your "combat outfit," huh?
And I fell for it, too!
[ALL]
Aw, you look cute!
Shut up! I do not!
I've had just about as much
as I can take of this crap.
Just fight me. I'll finish
you off with a single blow.
Once I do, I can forget all
about this idiotic island.
[ALL]
Ah! Gorgeous!
Really? You're the
strongest one on the island?
[CAROLINE] Well, how
do you think I became
the substitute queen
of Kamabakka Kingdom?
My prowess in the
Kamabakka style!
I am the New Kama Kenpo
Grandmaster... substitute.
Would you stop doing that?!
Come on. Let's just
get this over with!
[CAROLINE]
Gladly! I'll show you my moves!
Yeah, I don't plan on givin'
you the chance to get that far.
I hate to burst your bubble, but
you're goin' down with one kick!
And Concassé!
Now let the dust settle.
Wha...? Where is he?!
[CAROLINE]
Right behind you, candy boy!
[SANJI groaning]
Oh!
[SANJI grunts]
Fine!
[SANJI] What the hell? Why
can't I land a single attack?
And his eyes. Why does
he keep looking down?
And what's up with these
weird ducking moves?
Ah... aw, don't tell me
he's looking at...
[CAROLINE]
Oh! Nice up-skirt, honey!
[SANJI]
Ah! Hey, don't look, you perv!
[SANJI panting] Not that
I care! I mean, I'm a dude!
Why would I be embarrassed if
you see my stupid underwear?
'Cause I'm not!
Sounds like your maiden-like
modesty is comin' out!
[SANJI] That's the stupidest
crap I've ever heard!
You're not getting
under my skin!
What the hell do I care
if you see my underwear!
[CAROLINE]
Are you sure about that?
You're certainly not
kicking quite as high.
Seems like proof that you
really are embarrassed. See?
Hey, don't measure
my deadly kicks!
I'm only trying to show you that
you have doubt in your heart.
Shut up! You don't know
what you're talking about!
Oh, don't I?
Whoa, n-n-n-n-no, stop that!
As I thought. You're
wearin' your masculinity
as a shield, hiding
your true feelings.
[SANJI]
What?
[CAROLINE] There's no greater
freedom than being yourself.
[CAROLINE] So? Are you
done with your kicking?
I take it that you're inviting
me to attack you now?
New Kama Kenpo Technique!
Awakening Inner Maiden!
[SANJI]
Uh!
Why? It's just stupid underwear!
Right? So why am I paralyzed
with embarrassment?
[SANJI]
Whoa! Stop!
[SANJI] What? Did I really
just scream like a girl?
What's happening?
Why do I... Why do
I feel this way?
I'm so confused right now.
Am I...?
I am.
I feel like I'm losing
myself. I'm letting go.
And I'm... becoming
somebody else!
[SANJI] "Dear Nami and
Robin. How are you?
I hope this finds you well.
I do so look forward to seeing
the two of you again.
I'm certain when
that time comes,
we'll be better friends
than ever before!"
[NARRATOR] Deep in the South
Blue lies Birdie Kingdom,
where a race of giant
birds reign supreme.
[sighs] Oh, man, I really
want off this stinking island.
This place is
seriously the worst.
[CHOPPER] Birds treating
me like I'm their toy.
And humans constantly trying
to eat me in a hot pot.
[CHOPPER] If that's not
bad enough, and it really is,
the birds and the humans won't
stop fighting each other.
There's gotta be
a way out of here.
[chirps]
Calm down. I gathered
up a nice dinner for you.
[BIRDIE chirps]
[CHOPPER]
How are your legs feeling today?
Did they get any
better overnight?
Here, let me take a look.
Quit movin' around, now.
[CHOPPER]
Hey. They're all healed up!
All right. Better eat these
to get your strength back.
[BIRDIE chirps]
You're sure lucky I was
around. Just imagine.
What if I'd been out searching
for herbs or something?
[CHOPPER] This should fix
an upset stomach right up.
[CHOPPER gasps] Ah! What in
the heck was that noise?
Are the humans after me again?
Please! Please don't let them
throw me in a hot pot!
They're gonna eat me!
That's a big cheeper. [gasps]
[CHOPPER] I guess she must've
fallen out of the nest.
[BIRDIE cries]
[CHOPPER] She's way too young
to communicate with me,
although I can tell she's
hurt. That much is obvious.
[gasps] Wow,
that's really bad.
Not that I'm all that surprised,
just look how far she fell.
Hey, try not to move!
C'mon, stop, you're only
gonna make it worse!
Hey! Calm down
and do what I say!
Trust me, I'm a doctor!
[BIRDIE coos]
[BIRDIE chirps]
[CHOPPER]
Ah, jeez, you sure do eat a lot.
You're gonna wear me out
if I have to keep collecting
this fruit for you all day!
But she needs all
the food she can get
so she can grow up strong
and be able to fly someday.
And then she can return
to the nest. Oh, yeah!
You gotta do me a favor
when you learn to fly.
You can get me off
this crazy island
and take me to the
Sabaody Archipelago!
Luffy! Here I come!
[laughs] Awesome, huh?
I mean, it's almost
like I planned it
when I helped you out!
You gotta promise me, okay?
And don't forget about it!
[chirps]
[CHOPPER laughs]
Hey! Knock it off!
That tickles, you
little monster! Stop!
[laughs, groans]
Oh, c'mon! You, too?
Do I really look that much
like a damn bird toy?
[sighs] So warm.
It's great to see
you guys again.
Not that I actually missed
your ugly jerk faces.
[CHOPPER] Uh. Hang on.
I wonder where she went?
Oh well. Her legs are
all healed up by now.
She must've gone
out for a walk.
Whoa, what?!
[CHOPPER] This is really bad.
I better find her fast.
Judging by these prints,
she can't be far.
[TRIBESMAN A]
I starving, you guys.
[SHANBA]
We know.
We all starving, tha why we
try to find escaped raccoon,
you dummy, why you
think we here?
That was reindeer,
you the dummy!
--Shut up.
--Who cares what is?
We going to catch and
make some hot pot!
[TRIBESMAN A]
Now you talking!
[SHANBA]
Me salivating!
Oh, no. Not good.
Not good at all!
[CHOPPER groaning]
[gasps]
[chirps]
[CHOPPER] Hey, I found you!
I'm so glad you're okay!
[TRIBESMAN A]
I don't think it here, guys.
[CHOPPER gasps]
Shhh!
So we check out another
part of jungle, right?
Yeah, you right.
Good, they didn't see us.
So, you went wandering
and got lost, huh?
--[BIRDIE chirps]
--[CHOPPER laughs]
I guess it's safe to
say you're better now,
but you gotta be quiet, okay?
Those guys'll find us if
we make too much noise.
[chirps]
--[chirps]
--Uh! No! Shut up!
[TRIBESMEN]
Huh?!
[CHOPPER]
Aw, dammit!
Right there! I see reindeer!
I see bird, too!
[panting]
[TRIBESMAN A] Double hot
pot for dinner tonight!
Chicken hot pot and
reindeer hot pot!
You're kidding me!
They've got us cornered!
--Uh...
--[chirps]
Nowhere left to go.
[TRIBESMAN B]
Give up, dinner.
--[CHOPPER whimpers]
--[BIRDIE chirps]
[BIRDS squawk]
[ALL gasp]
Big birds comin' to
save the cheeper!
We shoo them away!
Awesome! Are you guys
really coming to help us?
[CHOPPER] Your baby got
hurt but don't worry,
I've been takin' care
of her for you,
but you don't need to thank me
or anything, you big bastard.
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[CHOPPER groans]
[CHOPPER] I totally knew you
were gonna do that!
[CHOPPER]
Guard Point!
[TRIBESMEN scream]
And they're right back
to fighting again.
Of course.
[gasps]
I guess she must be the mother.
Take care! And don't
forget the promise you made!
As soon as you get big
enough and know how to fly,
you gotta take me
to see my friends
at the Sabaody Archipelago!
[chirps]
I'm counting on you!
[BIRDIE chirps]
Uh! But, how long
is that gonna take?
How long am I stuck here for?!
[CHOPPER gasps]
[screams]
[CHOPPER] I'm officially sick
to death of this stupid place!
What is wrong with the humans
and the birds on this island?!
Can't they just
try to get along?!
Luffy! Everybody!
Please get me out of here!
[NARRATOR] Robin is captured in
a place known as Tequila Wolf.
A young girl named Soran,
whom she befriended,
seeks to help her, but
she can't do it alone.
Meanwhile, Usopp trains to
become a hero of the forest
but his appetite is proving
to be a distraction.
[LUFFY]
On the next, One Piece.
"The Friends' Whereabouts!
Revolutionaries and the
Gorging Forest's Trap!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!