[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[ENERU] And now the five
of you will continue on
in the final stage of the game.
What are you willing
to do for that power?
Are you willing
to kill each other?
[ALL]
You're the only one dying today!
[laughing]
[ENERU]
Insolent fools!
[LUFFY]
"Showdown in the Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!"
[CHILDREN laughing]
[CHILD B]
Here!
Hey!
[CHILD A] I think this house
belongs to that pretty lady.
The one who plays her harp
on the beach all the time.
Yeah. You're right.
This is her house. For sure.
Her name's Conis,
and she lives here with
her dad, Pagaya.
They both seem like
really nice people.
They even invited me over
to have lunch one time.
I heard that girl and her
dad are really bad people.
Stay away or you'll
get in trouble.
[CHILD C]
My mom told me that, too.
She said that they were
helping the Blue Sea People.
[gasps] That can't be.
I swear! It's true!
They're trouble!
My father said he'd ground me if
he caught me anywhere near them!
Your father said that... I see.
Oh. I'm sorry, I just
remembered your father is...
Heh... My daddy's
a member of the Enforcers,
and he's out on patrol.
My mom says he'll be
coming home soon.
And I can't hardly wait, 'cause
I've never even seen his face.
Oh, man.
I think it is so
awesome your dad is
one of the Divine Warriors.
Yeah, it is pretty cool.
[CHILD A]
Yeah it is.
And I'm sure your dad will come
to home to see you real soon.
[CHILD B]
Yeah.
[horn blares]
[MAN A] Skypiea will be dropped
back into the Blue Sea world.
This nation will
no longer exist!
[CONIS] I can't let
his death be in vain.
I must tell the others.
I have to warn them,
no matter what it takes.
[laughing]
[ENERU]
You dare to threaten me?
Listen to yourselves!
[laughing]
[whimpering]
Whoa. This guy's dangerous!
[ENERU laughing]
I must admit,
I'm quite impressed.
But you have no idea
what you're up against.
Even the four of you together
don't stand a chance against me.
You cannot comprehend...
...the extent of my powers
and what I'm truly capable of.
[laughing] Look at you.
An elderly buffoon
wanting peace.
A warrior who single mindedly
seeks his homeland.
And thieves from the Blue Sea
who are only concerned
with treasures.
All of you, for one reason
or another, seek to save
this wretched place
called Skypiea.
But you cannot, because this
nation is fundamentally flawed.
[GAN FALL growls]
[GAN FALL]
I refuse to stand here
and listen to such nonsense.
Now tell me where
the Divine Warriors are!
And what exactly is
your goal here today?
Why, an ascension.
My old friend.
What do you mean?
[ENERU]
I mean, when I ascend
I will return to
my rightful place.
[GAN FALL]
What's that?
Are you saying that you're
leaving Skypiea?
[ENERU]
That's right.
I will soon leave this
dreadful wasteland.
On the island where I grew up
there were legends of a place
regarded as God's Home.
As God's home?
People call this place
Endless Vearth.
And there... the ground
extends as far
as the eye can see
in all directions.
It's my dream to find
this place. This paradise!
Endless Vearth.
A home fit for a God!
My time spent here battling
over the inconsequential
lands of the Upper Yard
has been nothing
but a petty triviality.
[ENERU]
Listen to me.
I tell you this place that you
cherish is an abomination.
Consider this...
[ENERU] It was born in the sky,
though it's not a cloud.
It lives in the sky,
though it's not a bird.
[ENERU] This nation
which exists in the sky
is an utterly unnatural one.
When we die we all return
to the Earth, to the soil,
but here... there is none.
What exactly are you getting at?
[ENERU] You really shouldn't be
surprised by my intentions.
As God, I'm bound to adhere to
the divine province on nature.
That's why...
this unnatural nation...
...will be ripped apart
and pulled from the sky!
[gasping]
[gasps]
[growls]
[GAN FALL] You're planning on
wiping out Skypiea completely?
[ENERU]
It's only natural.
[GAN FALL]
Don't be so conceited.
The term "God" is just
a title used to refer
to the leader of this nation!
True. But that will soon change.
[GAN FALL] A true God does
not live amongst the humans
like you do and treat
them as his playthings!
[ENERU]
Former God...
Gan Fall. [laughs]
You're worried about the
Divine Warriors, are you not?
[ENERU] Six years ago, your
Divine Warriors lost a battle
against my forces and I took
650 of your subordinates
under my charge.
They served me well,
until this morning
when I could find no
more use for them.
I told you, did I not?
The six of us here now
are the only ones left alive
in this forsaken place.
Such a shame.
[GAN FALL]
You... monster...
[ENERU] It's not that I
wanted to harm them.
But when I told them my goal,
they dared to challenge me.
[laughing] And they paid the
price for that insubordination.
[laughing]
They were good men, and they all
had families on Angel Island.
[ENERU]
Yes, I'm aware.
I supposed I'll have to bury
their families beside them.
[GAN FALL]
You are...
...the devil!
[GAN FALL yelling]
[ENERU]
Five million...
Ten million...
Twenty million...
[GAN FALL]
We were...
We were consumed by bloodlust.
The Shandorian Warriors.
They only attacked
God's Island, Upper Yard,
because they wanted to regain
the homeland of their ancestors,
which we took.
[squawks]
[PRIEST A] My Lord, you're
not thinking about that again,
are you? Look around.
Look at the peaceful existence
of the citizens of Skypiea.
It wouldn't be this way had
our ancestors not taken control
of the Upper Yard 400 years ago.
And it is our duty
to carry on this battle to
ensure the peaceful nature
of this nation.
We've tried to
negotiate with them.
But if they cannot abide
by these negotiations,
they do not deserve
your compassion.
[GAN FALL]
Four hundred years.
I think that it's time for this
endless strife and bloodshed
to come to an end.
I only wish that we could
all live in harmony.
And put these needless
battles behind us.
[PRIEST B]
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
[PIERRE whimpers]
[PRIEST A] Is it another attack
by the Shandorians?
[PRIEST B]
It's not them.
[PRIEST A]
What do you mean?
It's a man who calls
himself God Eneru.
What? God Eneru?
[PRIEST A]
Who does he think he is,
presenting himself as
a god before Gan Fall?
[PRIESTS gasp]
[PRIESTS scream]
[gasps]
[GAN FALL]
This can't be...
[ENERU]
Divine Warriors, huh?
They were nowhere near as
formidable as I expected.
Tch. And who are you?
[ENERU]
I guess at the very least
you could say they were
loyal followers.
Eneru...
So you're God, huh?
Well, not anymore.
[GAN FALL]
How dare you!
[squawking]
[OHM]
Eneru.
What should we do
with this old man?
He's pathetic. He's useless.
Can we kill him?
[ENERU]
Just throw him into the sea.
I doubt he can even be
used for manual labor.
[ENERU laughs]
This shrine on the other hand
could be quite useful to us.
But what we really need are the
services of the Divine Warriors.
They could be put to work in
bringing about my ultimate goal.
They will never
help you in your cause.
Silence. You're no longer
in charge, old man.
[GAN FALL screams]
[ENERU laughing]
[ENERU]
Twenty million volts.
[screams]
Vari...
[NAMI]
No, get away from him!
[WYPER gasping]
[ENERU]
God does exist in this world.
[GAN FALL]
How mortifying.
And that God is me.
It's the devil fruit.
It's the Rumble Rumble Fruit.
If I'm not mistaken,
this particular fruit
is said to have the
power of invincibility.
[ROBIN]
The power of lightning!
But... lightning.
There's no way!
A human has no
chance against that!
[ENERU]
It is time.
All that I have foreseen
will finally come to be.
The four of you should
feel honored
to have survived this long.
[laughing]
Now... Come along,
you will join me
as I gain passage
to my dream world...
...to the Endless Vearth!
Come with me!
Come and fulfill your destinies.
Why would we?
[ENERU] There I will build an
indisputable Nation of God!
Where only the chosen ones
are permitted to live.
A utopia of boundless
and eternal power.
What is he saying?
[ENERU] I will not let those
who are unworthy,
like those incompetent
subordinates of mine,
sully the stature of
this new nation.
Only those who pass
my judgment may bask
in the glory of my company.
[ROBIN]
But...
And, what will you
do if we refuse?
No. Robin.
[ENERU]
Refuse?
But why? Why refuse to join me?
If you stay here you'll
fall into a bottomless pit
along with the rest of
this unnatural nation.
I have no doubt you could
destroy the entirety
of the Upper Yard
in one fell swoop.
But if you decide to
destroy all this,
then won't you also be
destroying something
that you cherish?
Do you mean the Golden Bell?
[ROBIN]
Yes, that's right.
What's the Golden Bell?
[WYPER growls]
[ROBIN]
The Golden Bell.
[ENERU laughs]
Oh, don't worry. No need.
I've already made arrangements.
Based on what I know about
your travels across Skypiea,
I believe I know where
the bell is located.
[ROBIN gasps]
[ENERU] That's right.
I know what you're thinking.
And it won't be long
before I have the bell.
You seem surprised.
Did you really think
that you, a mere human,
could ever get the better of me?
How foolish of you.
[NAMI]
Robin!
There's nothing I hate
more in this world
than a cold, calculating woman.
[ROBIN gasping]
[ROBIN screams]
[ENERU]
Hmph.
No...
[WYPER growls]
[grunts]
[ZORO]
How dare you!
Heh.
I do as I please.
[ZORO growls]
You've got skills.
And you are completely
out of your mind.
[ZORO grunts]
[WYPER]
Burn Bazooka!
[ENERU chuckles]
Kari!
[WYPER grunts]
[ZORO grunting]
Uh. No way!
How did he manage to neutralize
the bazooka's blast?
[ENERU] Hmph. You still
don't get it, do you?
Your energy doesn't
even register to me.
I'm more powerful than you
could ever comprehend.
The thunderclap reverberated.
And that only happens
when the air expands
at the speed of sound.
That's really powerful.
That amount of power is greater
than anything we can handle.
It's true...
He really is made of lightning.
[ENERU]
The time is near.
Prepare yourselves.
Soon those who
remain will set off
for the Endless Vearth together.
Do you even understand what
a rare privilege this is?
And why do you assume
we'll come willingly?
[ENERU]
Hm?
[ZORO growling]
[ZORO] I don't give a damn about
your so called "dream world"!
Zoro!
Stay away from him!
He's too powerful!
You need a lesson.
Soon your body will know
the power of God.
[ZORO growling]
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO]
Uh...!
[ENERU]
I possess a tremendous power
that you puny humans can
never hope to overcome.
Can you feel it now?
The despair?
If one loses all hope
it is an experience
not unlike losing one's life.
[ENERU laughing]
[ZORO screams]
[NAMI]
Zoro!
[ENERU] People fear death
above all things.
[ENERU] That's why people
prostrate themselves
before an insurmountable
power and beg for mercy.
It is simply the natural
order of things.
Beings are meant to bow
before that which they fear.
It's a shame.
You are bound by your instincts.
[ZORO] Can't believe how
incredibly strong he is.
Hm?
[NAMI gasps]
What do you think
you're trying to do?
[panting]
And now... time to die.
[WYPER] Are you familiar with
the Sea Prism Stone, Eneru?
[ZORO]
Sea Prism Stone?
That's a stone that can
counteract Devil Fruit powers.
[ENERU] Well then, do your
worst, Shandorian.
Sea Prism Stone.
It's said to harness the power
of the entire ocean
into a single blast.
It's the sea condensed
into solid form.
If anything can overcome
the power of the Devil Fruit,
it's the Stone.
[WYPER]
Die!
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
You're aware of the
consequences, are you not?
Your body will pay a
heavy price, as well.
Why sacrifice yourself for a
homeland you will never regain?
If I must... I'll die. Glady...
If it means I can
take you with me!
[gasps]
[ENERU]
Don't do it.
Reject!
Hey, did you guys hear that?
[NAMI]
No way...
He really did it.
[panting]
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[ENERU]
It's not that people fear God.
God is fear itself.
And when you look upon me in
fear, you look on me as a God.
I will put an end to this nation
in the sky with my mighty power!
[LUFFY] What? I don't have a
clue what you're babbling about.
On the next One Piece!
"Ambition Toward the Endless
Vearth. The Ark Maxim!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!