[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man...
As long as there are people who
seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY]
"An Ancient Island!
The Shadow Hiding
In Little Garden!"
Aw, no snow. Too bad.
Snow, in this climate?
Sure, why not?
Already happened once.
You just missed it
cause you were asleep.
Hey! What about you?
Do you think it's gonna snow?
I wouldn't rule anything out.
But the sea you were
in the first time
it snowed was special.
The seven magnetic fields that
emit from Reverse Mountain
tend to make things
particularly chaotic.
[VIVI] But that doesn't mean
you should relax your guard
while sailing these waters.
The odds of it being as wild as
your first journey may be small.
Still, these waters
aren't normal
and are certain to hold
surprises of their own.
Remember: Never
underestimate this sea.
[SANJI]
Hey, guys!
Anyone care to sample
my special drink?
[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY]
Woo‐hoo!
[VIVI gasps]
[LUFFY] Hey, you guys want to
get out the fishing gear?
[ZORO]
Fishing! Hell yeah. I'm in!
[USOPP]
Sounds good to me!
I'll even make you one of
my custom fishing rods!
You'll love it!
[SANJI]
No, no! It goes like this.
[KAROO squawks]
[USOPP, LUFFY gasp]
[SANJI] Wow, somebody's
sure thirsty. Have another.
[LUFFY]
Ha, ha! Wow!
[LUFFY laughs]
[USOPP]
Oh, yeah! Look at him go!
[LUFFY] The sounds he makes
when he slurps are hilarious!
[USOPP]
Yeah, give him another one.
They're acting like idiots!
[NAMI]
Maybe this will help.
[VIVI]
Uh?
Just relax.
These boys may go through
their goofy phases,
but when things get rough,
they get to work.
Trust me. I should know.
Sorry. I don't know
what's wrong with me.
I'm getting worked
up over nothing.
This ship will put you at ease.
You'll cheer up in no time!
[USOPP]
Attaboy!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY, SANJI, ZORO laugh]
[NAMI laughs]
Yeah. They're... funny.
Hey look, it's a dolphin!
Pirate's best friend!
Whoa! Beautiful!
[STRAW HATS]
It's huge!
[LUFFY laughs]
Let's go!
[KAROO squawks]
[ZORO]
Move it!
[USOPP]
Okay!
[SANJI]
Going!
[SANJI grunting]
[USOPP]
Got it!
Take that side!
[SANJI]
Gotcha!
She was right!
Okay, hurry! Let's move!
Get ready.
It's gonna be a big one!
Nami! Which direction now?
[NAMI]
Gimme a second. I'll check.
Port side... full!
[STRAW HATS]
Turning full!
[LUFFY laughs]
There's no mistake.
Cactus Island and this one here
are definitely pulling
against each other.
Our next stop!
[LUFFY laughs]
[USOPP laughs]
[LUFFY] This is it! Our second
island in the Grand Line!
[MISS GOLDEN WEEK]
Mr. 3.
[MR. 3]
Yes, my dear. Hold on.
Ahh.
There's nothing quite like
the rich aroma of Earl Grey.
I'm bored.
[MR. 3] On the one hand,
you say you're bored.
On the other, you don't
like working. Correct?
[MISS GOLDEN WEEK]
Mm‐hmm.
[MR. 3] Then why don't you
cease your complaining
and revel in the enjoyment
of this rare slice
of freedom circumstances have
generously afforded you?
How grand to be able
to take a long vacation.
A privilege few officers
ever get to indulge.
One more thing...
I would appreciate your mindful
and immediate discretion
in not calling me by
my code name in public.
Otherwise, people will discover
that I am indeed Mr. 3.
Sure.
Mm...
Incidentally, I couldn't
help noticing
you've been perusing
that piece of paper
over the last several days.
Why does it grab you so?
It's an order from Boss.
[MR. 3] Why didn't you
tell me sooner?!
It says Mr. 5 has
been taken down.
If someone had to
be terminated,
I wish it would've been
someone useless like Mr. 2.
So it would benefit you.
With a fat promotion.
It's not that, necessarily.
Rather, the downfall of Mr. 5
is hardly exciting news at all.
The man excelled at nothing
but his own idiocy,
clinging to his Devil Fruit
Power like a drowning rat.
You are correct that a modicum
of my indifference stems from
the fact that 5's misfortune
brings me no gain.
All we may learn is
power means nothing if
not properly harnessed.
[MR. 3] Superior
criminals are those
who execute their crimes
using superior intellect.
Nevertheless, whoever beat Mr.
5 should be made an example of,
if for no other reason than
to preserve the reputation
of terror our organization has
painstakingly cultivated,
and indeed for criminality
as a whole.
I can see why they call
this place Little Garden!
I can't.
What's "little" about it?!
Yeah, this island looks
pretty harsh if you ask me.
Why the cute name?
[USOPP] Y‐Y‐Yeah, it looks
like a jungle out there!
Maybe we'd be better
off skipping this one.
We have to be careful.
I can't help but remember the
warning Miss All Sunday gave us.
But your luck gets even worse,
because of the direction your
log pose is indicating.
You see...
...the name of the next
island is Little Garden.
We won't even need
to lift a finger.
You'll all be dead long
before you reach Alabasta.
So what, we might be attacked
by giant monsters?!
[LUFFY]
Heh! Who knows?
[USOPP] Listen, I'm sure we can
make it to the next island
without going ashore
on this one!
The only way to reset
the log is to go ashore.
Not to mention we're
in dire need
of re‐stocking our food supply.
We didn't get so much as a sack
of flour in the last town.
Guys! There's our ticket in.
[NAMI]
Huh?
[LUFFY] Think they'll have a
barbecue restaurant here?
[SANJI] We didn't travel
all this way for barbecue!
[LUFFY] I thought the point
of this visit was to get food?
[SANJI] Food as in supplies
we're going to cook later!
Jeez, what're you thinking?
[NAMI]
I don't know.
Usopp might be right
about this one.
Just take a look at the
gargantuan plant life here.
I've never seen anything
like it, not even in books.
[BIRD screeches]
[NAMI, USOPP scream]
You're so adorable!
Thank you!
That's not funny!
I was talking to Nami!
What was that screeching?!
[SANJI chuckles]
It's all right, love.
It's only a bird.
Perfectly harmless.
Just like this jungle.
Nothin' to worry about.
[NAMI, USOPP scream]
[SANJI]
Uh... What's wrong?
[SANJI] What the hell's the
matter with you, ya damn bird?!
Ooh. It's big. Could be tasty.
[rumbling]
Hear that?! Is that
the kinda noise
you expect to hear
in a normal jungle?!
That sounded like
a volcano erupting!
We're all going to die!
A tiger?!
It's gigantic!
Uh!
[roars]
What?! Luffy, what
just happened?!
I know normal!
This is definitely not it!
Someone explain to me
how a mammoth tiger
can just keel over
covered in blood!
Log‐Pose and food be damned!
We're not stepping foot on
that island and that's final!
We can still reset the
readings on the ship.
We'll just sit tight until then.
When that's done, we'll
leave and never look back!
[USOPP]
Great!
Yeah. Great. We'll
all just stay here!
[LUFFY laughs]
Sanji, go make lunch!
You want lunch?
[LUFFY]
Yep, and one more thing!
Make it a great big
"pirate lunch"‐‐
with lots of meat
and no veggies!
I'm going to need
some more energy!
Uh! Energy for what?!
What are you doing?!
You're not leaving here!
You know! Heh, heh!
Fun stuff! Do ya
wanna come along?
[NAMI growls]
[NAMI]
It's useless. I can't stop him.
He's too enthusiastic.
[USOPP]
Is he crazy?!
Somewhere out there is
a monster big enough
to grind a tiger into paste!
Sanji! I'm starving!
Right. Be patient.
I'll have it to you
as soon as I can.
[LUFFY laughs]
Say, Luffy!
Would it be all right if
I come along with you?
[USOPP yelps]
Sure! Sounds great!
[NAMI]
No! Vivi, you can't be serious!
Yeah. I'd rather not sit here
with nothing to do but
worry about my troubles.
This will keep me busy
until the log's reset.
Out of the question! Seriously!
It's way too dangerous
for you out there!
I'll be fine. Besides,
I'll have Karoo with me.
[squawks]
Hey something's wrong.
Karoo doesn't look too good.
He might be in shock.
Vivi, if you go exploring,
you'll need to eat.
I'll pack you a lunch.
Thanks.
While you're at it, could you
fix something for Karoo?
Of course! You just
leave it to me!
Now you're all set
and ready to go!
Two pirate lunches
for Luffy and Vivi,
and a special drink for Karoo!
Heh! Thanks.
[VIVI]
Well. See you guys later!
Don't worry!
Everything will be fine!
Vivi. What a girl.
She's so brave.
And just what would
you expect from someone
who could infiltrate
the enemy's ranks.
[ZORO sighs] I'm bored.
I'm gonna take a walk.
Take a walk?!
Uh! Hey! Zoro! Wait up!
[ZORO]
Hm?
You know we're kinda
short on food, right?
If you find any animals that
appear edible, bring'em back.
Okay, that's easy.
I could see why you'd want
to send me, cause I can
bring back somethin' you
couldn't catch yourself.
[SANJI] What the hell
does that mean?!
[ZORO growls]
[SANJI] I won't let that
remark go unchallenged!
You're saying you can capture
bigger game than I can?
Like my hunting skills
are inferior?!
Yeah, that's right.
Challenge accepted.
Okay! Winner brings back
the most pounds of meat.
Whaddaya mean pounds,
'cause I'll bring back tons?!
[SANJI] Why don't you let your
hunting do your talking for you.
[ZORO]
Heh. Good luck, cook!
I will never understand it.
Why do those two jerks have
to be so competitive?
Don't cry. If it makes
you feel better,
I'm just as stumped by
their behavior as you.
[animals chattering]
[USOPP, NAMI gasp]
We're sitting ducks.
Don't you think I
already know that?!
[USOPP, NAMI exhale]
Why didn't I think
of that before?!
Uh?! Where are you going?!
[USOPP]
Nami, what's wrong?!
[NAMI] Mm. That's not it...
Mm... Not this one either.
‐‐Nope.
‐‐[USOPP grunting]
Nami! Whoa! Hey!
What the heck are you
looking for anyway?! Huh?!
[NAMI]
Quiet!
I remember reading
about it in a book.
[USOPP]
Uh. Reading about what?
[NAMI]
Little Garden.
[LUFFY chuckles]
[VIVI]
Hey, what's the matter?
Over here! Check it out!
It's a shellfish that
looks like a squid.
[LUFFY]
Shell squidfish! Heh, heh!
How strange.
It sort of resembles
an ammonoid.
Cool, huh?
[KAROO squawks]
I've got a feeling someone's
been following me for a while.
Nah, couldn't be.
[T‐REX roars]
[SANJI grunts]
Can't you see I'm busy?!
[T‐REX roars]
[SANJI]
Collier Coup!
[ZORO] Hm... I don't know
what you're supposed to be,
but I'm guessing you're edible.
[NAMI]
Let me see... which one was it?
Maybe...
Oh, I think I read it recently,
but I don't remember.
The title's on the
tip of my tongue.
Hm...
[LUFFY]
Huh. That's weird.
What's a Sea King doing on land?
A dinosaur!
Awesome!
[VIVI gasping]
No way! This is unreal!
[LUFFY]
Uh, huh?
Somehow this island
has been frozen in time.
Stuck in the age
of the dinosaurs!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[VIVI] Travel in the
Grand Line is so difficult,
so no species ever migrated
between the islands
and their unique ecosystems
were preserved!
Some of these islands
have developed
extremely sophisticated
cultures,
both biological
and sociological.
While others remain in a sort
of evolutionary stagnation,
with little to no progression
for several thousands
or tens of thousands,
or, in this case, it seems,
even millions of years.
I can only assume that
it's the random climates
within the Grand Line
that make this possible.
I mean... What other
explanation is there?
We're standing on the island
that pre‐dates mankind.
[LUFFY laughs]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Dinosaur!
Are you insane?!
Usopp! Usopp?!
[USOPP]
Huh? Nami. What now?
So did you find your book yet?
Uh‐huh.
[T‐REX roars]
You're a rude son of a bitch!
[SANJI growls]
We both use Three Sword Style.
[ZORO yells]
[NAMI]
This is bad.
This... island.
What. What's wrong Nami?!
[NAMI whimpers]
[USOPP whimpers]
[SANJI]
Strange.
Why do I get the sense
that Nami needs me.
[NAMI gasping]
[LOUIS ARNOTE]
To those who reside here,
and call this island home,
it must seem as if they've
stumbled upon their
very own private garden.
Thus, I have aptly
named this wondrous,
terrifying place. Little Garden.
Louis Arnote, Explorer.
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I wrote you a
love song to let you
Know that I wanna be with
you 'til the end of time
Even when the sparkle fades
The doubts in vade our
once so trusting minds
Promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies
We built a castle of sand
And now we're watching
it wash away,
It doesn't have to end
We'll start again,
this time 'round,
we'll build a stronger love
Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I just wanna hold you
and not let go
You know that I'll be with
you 'til the end of time
Oh, you've got me heart and soul♪
[NAMI, USOPP scream]
A giant!
[USOPP]
Pretend we're dead.
[NAMI]
Doesn't that only work on bears?
[LUFFY]
Woo‐hoo! It's huge!
Say, are you human?
[ZORO]
With a big catch like this...
[SANJI]
In this hunting match...
[ZORO, SANJI]
...I'm the winner!
[LUFFY] Hey, old guy,
where're you going?
[NAMI, USOPP]
Duel?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Huge Duel! The Giants
Dorry And Broggy."
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!