[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
Raigo.
Angel Island's gone.
How could you?
The City of Gold...
You know for a fact
it exists, right?
I just...
I need let Old Timer and
the others down below know
that the City of Gold
is actually up in the sky!
If I ring the bell,
they should hear it.
Otherwise, Old Timer
will keep searching
the ocean floor forever!
I can't let Eneru take it.
So I'm not stopping
until I hear the sounds
of the Golden Bell.
[LUFFY] "Knock Over Giant Jack!
Last Hope for Escape!"
[AMAZON] Even Heaven's
Gate was blown away
in the twinkling of an eye.
Angel Island.
It's completely destroyed.
But what are we supposed to do?
And where do we go?
To Cloud End, and then
down to the Blue Sea
like Captain McKinley said!
It's our only choice.
Hold on.
There are still a lot of people
in the White-White Sea
who haven't been evacuated yet!
[ISLANDER B] The Milky Roads
leading there've been destroyed!
They're gone!
I don't know how we can
bring those ships down
without them!
[ISLANDER C] So you're saying we
just leave those people to die?
[ISLANDERS yelling]
We're all doomed.
[AMAZON sighs]
The White-White Sea is lost.
Skypiea... it's fading away.
So this is it.
Splendid!
At last!
The grand belfry
that was once the pride
of the legendary
city of Shandora!
Now it's mine!
A prize befitting a god
of my power and glory!
The fabled bell, the one
that heralded the start
of this land's
400-year old conflict.
How pathetic.
To think they carried on
their pointless little battle
for centuries...
...only to see
everything be destroyed.
[LUFFY grunts]
[NAMI] Luffy, you can't
catch up with him!
[LUFFY gasps]
[NAMI] Eneru's ark hasn't
moved from that spot.
That can only mean one thing.
[NAMI]
Luffy.
Eneru's been up
there for a while.
He must have taken
the golden bell by now.
[NAMI] No matter hard
you stretch your arms,
there's no way you
can reach up there.
[LUFFY] If he took it,
I'm gonna take it back!
Gimme the waver!
[engine running]
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY grunts]
[NAMI] He's too far from
the top of the beanstalk.
What can we do?
How can we get to him?
[LUFFY yelling]
[NAMI]
There must be a way!
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI]
The others!
[ENERU]
Every inhabitant of Skypiea
will suffer my terrible wrath!
All will perish, including the
voices directly beneath you.
[LUFFY grunts]
[NAMI]
That's right!
Everyone's still down there!
But how do we let them
know we need help?
[LUFFY yells]
Watch out!
Something's falling
towards us again!
--[ZORO] Wait, it's...
--[USOPP] Take cover!
[AISA]
A leaf?
[USOPP]
Huh?
[AISA]
Hey, look!
There's something written on it.
[gasps]
It's a message!
From Nami and Luffy!
[USOPP]
Huh?
What's it say?
"Cut down this beanstalk
and make sure it falls
towards the west."
[USOPP]
What?!
But... What'll happen
if we do that?
Hey, Knight?
Which way's west?
Well...
You mean we're
really gonna do it?
I mean... Which way's west?
[GAN FALL] There, in the
direction of the cloud
where Eneru's ark
is currently moored.
[ISLANDERS gasp]
[ENERU] I've accomplished all
of my objectives but one.
So now...
It's time I destroyed
this pathetic land
and the Cumuloregalis
Clouds it rests on,
and set off for
the Endless Vearth.
[laughing]
I'm actually gonna miss toying
with the Skypieans' lives!
[USOPP whimpers]
Eneru!
Damn him.
Do you see that?
This one's even bigger!
Maybe we should get out of here
wh-while there's still
some place to get!
[ENERU laughing]
Say goodbye, Skypiea!
It's even bigger
than his last one!
That bastard!
Now that he's got his grubby
hands on the golden bell,
he has no more use for Skypiea!
That creep's pretty
easy to figure out!
Well, don't just
stand there, Luffy!
We can't let him
get away with this!
Wait, "we"?
But weren't you gonna escape?
Yeah, well...
I can't leave now
with what's at stake.
Besides, you want to
ring that golden bell, right?
I've gotta!
For Old Timer!
But... with your arm,
you can't drive the waver.
If I left you here,
you'd keep trying to jump up,
so leave the driving to me
and I'll get you up there.
Listen.
You've got to promise
that you'll get us
out of this mess
in one piece, okay?
Yeah. You got it!
And thanks!
[NAMI] We've only got one
chance to get this thing right!
I just hope they got my
message and understand
what we're attempting to do.
Let me get this straight!
They're gonna jump to the ark
from the falling beanstalk?
[ZORO]
You got any better ideas?
Well that's crazy.
They can't be serious.
Fine, then I'll leave it
to you to climb up there
and stop Luffy.
He won't listen!
Look, I don't care
how crazy it sounds!
We have no choice!
We've gotta let him do this!
[WYPER, AISA grunt]
[USOPP]
Wh-What the--?
[ROBIN]
Long nose!
[USOPP]
I got 'em!
[yelps]
If we stay here, we're just
gonna get pushed down
to the ruins below! Run!
Get away from the beanstalk!
I'll take care of it!
All I need to do is cut the vine
down towards that ship, right?
But--!
[ZORO] That maniac is about
to wipe this land away,
and there are only two
people who can reach him
before he sets that thing off!
Zoro, wait!
Nami! Luffy!
Ya better get ready!
You fools from the
Blue Sea just don't know
when to give up, do you?
It's far too late
to change things now.
The minute you entered
the survival game,
your fates were cast in stone.
Anything you do is futile.
O-Okay, he's gonna be just fine.
Zoro buddy, you're the
only one who can do this!
It's up to you!
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO]
Eneru, I am so sick of you!
[ZORO yells]
All right! He did it!
[USOPP]
Zoro!
Insolent little worm.
He did it!
He did it and got zapped.
But he did it!
[ROBIN]
Oh, no. The vine!
The vine's not falling!
But he cut it!
What is that thing made out of?
It looks like a plant,
but it's solid as a rock!
[WYPER]
Pathetic!
This is what you outsiders
get for butting in!
[AISA]
Wyper, what are you doing?
[WYPER]
Quiet!
We Shandorians are the
descendents of Kalgara,
not that kid in the straw hat!
If anyone is to ring that bell,
it should rightfully be us!
Don't listen to him, Robin!
He's too banged-up to stop us!
Besides, Nami and Luffy
are counting on us!
Our only priority right now
is knocking that thing down!
Speaking of which,
Zoro's already cut through
half of the stem!
It probably shouldn't take
much to cut through
the rest of it!
My awesome Dance of
the Exploding Stars
should do the trick!
After just one little hit,
even a gentle breeze
will knock that thing over!
Once again, it's up to me!
The last line of defense
in our merry band!
Robin, leave all the
dangerous stuff to me!
You tend to our fallen comrades!
[ROBIN] They look like
an oak leaf mochi cake.
[USOPP]
Forward!
[laughing]
[ROBIN]
Hmm?
About that bell...
Four hundred years ago,
an explorer from my world
said he stumbled
upon a city of gold.
People laughed at him
and called him a liar.
But he has a descendent today
who still believes the stories,
and has spent years
searching the Blue Sea
for any evidence
of this City of Gold.
If that golden bell can be rung,
everyone will know the
City of Gold is in the sky
and not a myth.
That's the reason
Luffy's up there.
Now do you understand?
[USOPP]
Exploding Star!
[ROBIN]
Noble, isn't it?
Trying to vindicate
a man he never met?
He's had chances to escape.
But he's stuck around
to see this thing through.
That guy's nuts!
[USOPP]
Rolling Exploding Star!
Usopp Rubber Band of Doom!
Regular Exploding Star!
[explosions]
[WYPER]
What--
What is the name of this
explorer's descendent?
[ROBIN]
Montblanc Cricket. Why?
The name of his
ancestor who came here.
Please tell me.
Was it Noland?
How--?
Wyper?
[grunts]
What's going on?
Why are you crying?
[WYPER]
Is this a sign from you?
Or a miracle?
What is it,
Great Warrior Kalgara?
[KALGARA]
Come, Nola!
We'll ring the bell again
today so the sound
reaches the ends of the earth!
Let's send the sound
you love to say hello
to our friend Noland!
[YOUNG SNAKE hissing]
[YOUNG SNAKE whines]
[SNAKE growls]
[USOPP grunts]
What the--?
What just did that?
Guess it doesn't matter,
'cause it couldn't even budge
that beanstalk!
Maybe one of my triple
explosions will do the trick.
--[WYPER] Move.
--[USOPP] Hey!
[WYPER]
Kalgara.
The descendent of your best
friend from the Blue Sea.
He's waiting for it.
The ringing of your golden bell!
[sniffling]
It's time we
rewarded his patience!
[WYPER]
Reject!
What the heck was that?!
Wyper!
[ROBIN gasps]
[GAN FALL]
That fool. A reject dial.
[WYPER]
Now fall, Giant Jack! Fall!
[GROUP gasps]
[USOPP]
Guys! We've got to run away!
[engine revving]
This is it! Get on, Luffy!
Gun it! Go!
I should mention,
I've never revved this waver's
jet dial up to
maximum power before.
I was a little scared
to see how fast it would go.
I guess we're gonna find out
now if it'll be too strong
for me to control, huh?
Go for it, Nami!
[NAMI]
Okay!
[NAMI yelps]
[NAMI]
Hang on, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
I am!
[ISLANDERS chattering]
[ISLANDER D]
It's falling!
[ISLANDER E]
He's right!
[ISLANDER F]
What's going on up there?
Well, Nami, Luffy.
Good luck!
We're counting on you!
If we let this place
be destroyed,
we'll never get to ring
that bell, and Cricket
will never hear it!
He helped us,
so we gotta help him!
Ring that bell and ring it loud!
Jump to Eneru's ship
and stop that guy!
Do it!
Everything's up to you
guys now, you got it?
Do it!
[ENERU]
My, my.
Now why can't you wait
for the completion of Raigo
like the rest of the insects?
Their impatience
will be their undoing.
Very well, then.
[NAMI yells]
Something's coming!
[LUFFY]
Don't slow down!
I'll take care of
whatever it is!
[NAMI yells]
That shot was pathetic!
[ENERU laughs]
That you should even
try to reach me now
is insolent far beyond
the point of stupidity!
Now pay for your folly!
Mamaragan!
That creep!
He's trying to destroy
the base of the beanstalk!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY]
Do something, Nami!
[NAMI]
Like what?
We're going too fast
and we're too high up!
If this thing loses
its foundation,
it'll crash before
we get to the top!
We won't reach Eneru,
and we'll fall to our deaths!
Upper Yard's being pummeled!
This is the end!
Luffy! Nami!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY growls]
[ENERU laughs]
Lightning may not harm you,
but your abilities
are absolutely useless
if you can't reach Maxim!
Now fall and face destruction
with the rest of Skypiea!
Say goodbye, boy!
[ENERU laughing]
[laughing continues]
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice
While you wander far from home,
gazing up at the sky
You are just like the moon
You never change as
you climb into the night
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear,
fading so suddenly...
Stay as you are,
don't lose your way
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams,
through endless nights
they come to you
Again and again, until you
see them shining through!
You may not return,
I hope that you'll learn
to put your past behind,
and just keep moving on
[NAMI]
Listen, Luffy!
Make sure you end it this time!
[ENERU]
Disappear with this land!
[laughs]
[WYPER] No matter how
much of it you destroy,
this land will not be beaten!
[LUFFY]
What kind of god are you?
I'm gonna ring that
bell no matter what!
[GAN FALL] Let me hear the
singing voice of the island.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Miracle on Skypiea!
The Love Song
Heard in the Clouds!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!