[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!
[LUFFY]
Hey, look! We're out!
[LT COMMANDER] All ships are
to pursue them immediately!
Eric just
reappeared as well.
We'll have to wait for him to
reboard before we go after them.
[USOPP]
Woohoo! Eat our sails!
[NAMI] But once we stop
at Warship Island,
they're going to catch up.
Guys, what're we gonna do then?
Do we even have a plan?
We'll be okay!
Oh, yeah?! How?!
All we have to do is
find the Dragons' Nest,
and then Grandpa Ryu will
get better and help us out!
I hate to be the
bearer of bad news.
[laughing]
The small fries have leapt
forth! Good! Now is the time!
All ships, take up positions
to the left and right!
Crane Wing Formation!
What do we do?!
They have us blocked off!
We jump onto those ships,
fight off the Marines,
and cut those links!
It's our only choice!
Huh. Actually,
it's not a bad idea.
[LUFFY]
All right! Let's go!
[laughs]
Bring it on!
[LUFFY]
"Luffy, Completely Surrounded!
Commodore Nelson's
Secret Strategy!"
[NELSON laughing]
[NELSON] Marvelous! A truly
beautiful sight to behold!
[NELSON laughing]
Hear me! Continue the attacks!
We will not relent
for an instant.
[MARINE C]
Yes, sir!
But be careful.
I don't want so much as
a scratch on that raft.
Right! Understood.
[chuckles]
For years, the Millennial
Dragon eluded me.
Now the beast is finally
within my grasp!
What this victory really
means is the Dragonite,
the Elixir of Immortality,
is now as good as mine!
[laughing]
[MARINE B]
Sir!
The Commodore's flagship
says his plan has succeeded
and that the attack on
the enemy is still ongoing!
[LT COMMANDER] Apparently,
this mission is over.
Our job is complete.
[ERIC] If Nelson gets his fat
hands on them now,
he'll ruin everything.
I won't allow it!
[ERIC]
Hold on, Lieutenant Commander!
What do you want now?
I need you to provide
me a rowboat.
In addition, I'll require three
of your crew to man it.
[LT COMMANDER] A rowboat?!
And why would you need that?!
Because a mast would
just be in the way.
You can't row into
the battle zone!
[ERIC] You're not here to
tell me what I can't do.
Now do as I say.
[USOPP]
Apis!
It's dangerous out here!
Now go back inside!
But I can't leave Grandpa
Ryu all by himself!
Hold on! Come back here!
Have you lost your mind?!
You'll kill yourself! Apis!
[APIS]
Grandpa Ryu.
Hang in there just
a little bit longer.
I'm gonna get you
to the Dragons' Nest.
I promise you that.
Man, she's brave!
Look at her!
She loves that dragon.
All right, you can
count on me, Apis.
I'll help you break
through the front lines
and reach the
Dragons' Nest, okay?
[USOPP screams]
[USOPP]
They got us!
They circled around and
attacked from behind!
Sanji! We've been hit! Sanji!
We're doomed! It's over!
[SANJI] Pipe down, will ya?
We haven't been hit.
[USOPP]
Seriously?
[SANJI]
Yeah.
[USOPP]
I'm saved!
Who was the one going around
saying we'd been hit anyway?
That was you.
[LUFFY]
Yeah, that's it! Go!
[laughing]
Hey! Cannonball coming this way!
I can't do any more from here!
You do something about it!
[LUFFY]
No problem! I'm on it!
And Gum‐Gum...
...Balloon!
Oh, wow!
No way!
Those impudent bastards!
How dare they defile
one of my warships!
What are you doing?!
Strike them down with
the Super Giant Cannon!
Sir!
[NELSON] There will be
no leniency! No mercy!
No escape for you
wretched heathens!
[MARINE H] Prepare to fire
the Super Giant Cannon!
[alarm blaring]
[MARINE E] The enemy vessel
has been trapped dead ahead!
Ready to fire!
We're in trouble!
One hit from that
monstrous cannon
and our ship will be
blown to shreds!
[LUFFY]
We'll be fine!
I'll just bounce it back.
[NAMI growls]
We need a permanent solution!
I'll turn the ship around!
You guys work the rear sail!
Go!
[LUFFY, ZORO]
Right!
You like shooting cannons?!
All right, you buncha Marine
thugs, I got a shot for ya!
[LUFFY]
Okay, here we go!
Eat this!
Fire!
[MARINE E]
Yes, sir!
[NELSON coughs]
What the hell just happened?
An enemy cannonball
slammed directly
into our main cannon, Sir!
You morons!
Don't just stand there!
Lift me up!
[MARINES]
Yes, sir!
[USOPP] How'd that medicine
go down, fellas?!
That's what happens
when you get served
a heaping helping
of Usopp Payback!
[SANJI] Big talk for
someone who got lucky.
[ZORO]
You're full of it.
[USOPP]
That was pure skill, guys!
Wow. Direct hit!
You're amazing, Usopp!
Uh. Yeah!
It'll be fine.
Don't worry, okay?
All you have to do is
keep protecting Apis.
We'll do the rest.
Hey, who are you talking to?
Grandpa Ryu.
Eh?
Now's our best chance!
If we act quickly, we can cut
through their barricade
and clear a path outta here!
That's a great idea.
Luffy?
Leave it to me!
Gum‐Gum...
...Bridge!
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
Hang in there Grandpa Ryu!
Here goes!
[yelps]
Hey, nice catch.
Damn you!
Report. What is the
status of the enemy?
[MARINE C]
Sir!
The enemy has
breached our defenses.
Three of the pirates
have been able to board
ship one on the portside.
What?! That's unacceptable!
Chains of steel, huh?
[LUFFY]
Can ya cut 'em?
[ZORO] There isn't
anything I can't cut.
[LUFFY]
Great! Get to it!
This is overkill.
I'll take the right side,
and you take the left.
Whatever.
I'll leave these guys to you.
[LUFFY, SANJI]
Thanks!
No one gets by the fighting
Marines of the Nelson Fleet!
You're dead, pirates!
[MARINES yell]
[USOPP]
Yeah! That's it! Way to go!
Show those pirate‐hating bullies
who really owns the sea!!
Beat 'em! Sink 'em!
Slice 'em into chum!
[growling]
Those vermin think
they can break through
my magnificent chain?!
You'll capture them
at all costs!
Or I swear I'll maroon every
last Marine in this fleet!
[MARINES yelling]
Now Gum‐Gum Gatling!
[laughing]
Here they come!
Now Gum‐Gum...
...Pinball!
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY chuckles]
They're so amazing.
I had no idea.
There's only one chain left!
Let's get moving!
Huh? You got it, Nami!
Don't stand there, you
imbeciles! Somebody stop them!
[screams]
[chuckles]
[NELSON]
Oh, Eric!
Excellent work!
Now the Millennial Dragon
is mine for the taking!
What was that?
I know you!
You're that sicko guy!
It's not "Sicko."
It's "Sickle," you brat!
Enough! You've lost! Now hand
over the Millennial Dragon!
Stay back! You can't have him!
You'll never get Grandpa Ryu!
Give him to me right now!
No!
Keep in mind I have the ability
to slice you into ribbons
at any given moment.
Stop right there!
Lay one fingernail on that kid
and I'll make you
beg for death!
[USOPP]
Yeah!
A‐And then you'll have to deal
with me, ya creepy sicko!
[chuckles]
More empty threats.
Fair warning, little pirates.
My wind slash missed
you on purpose.
[gasps]
A demonstration.
The next one will cost you.
Force me, and I'll blow
your ship apart.
[LUFFY]
What's wrong?
It's him.
Huh. So what's he doing?
[ERIC]
Tie their raft...
[ZORO] Looks like he's
stealing the dragon
and taking Apis hostage.
[LUFFY]
Oh no he's not!
Stop!
If you try to fight him,
he might kill Apis and the
others with his wind slash move.
All right. No punching.
I'll kick him.
Will you listen to me?!
[ERIC] I'll be taking the
Millennial Dragon now!
Nothing personal!
[USOPP] Oh, it's personal!
Give Apis back!
Excellent work, Eric!
Now bring the beast here.
[ERIC] I'm sorry, Nelson,
but this prize isn't for you.
[NELSON]
Huh?! What did you say?!
[ERIC] The only reason I obeyed
your ludicrous demands
was to use your fleet's ability
to gather information.
[NELSON]
Excuse me?!
[ERIC] Don't pretend
you're any different.
You tried to use me
with just as much vigor.
[NELSON] I spent a great sum
of money for your services!
[ERIC] I've worked off
that chump change
you threw me by now.
So I'm done taking orders from
you, you blubbering sea lion.
Sea lion?! Blubbering?!
I have big plans
for the Dragonite
this beast will provide.
I'm going to make myself
exquisitely perfect!
[growls]
[NELSON]
You'll pay for this betrayal!
I want this backstabber dead!
Shoot him. Kill him!
It's starting all over again!
[ERIC]
If you want to survive,
I suggest you start rowing
with greater enthusiasm!
[MARINES sream]
[APIS]
Stop...
Please stop harassing
Grandpa Ryu!
He hasn't done anything to you!
Do you hear me?! All he wants
is to be left alone in peace!
Oh, quit your whining.
I have to take Grandpa Ryu
back to the Dragons'
Nest or he'll die!
Just let us go!
Ah! What's the
matter with you?!
Let me go! Let me go!
You are now my hostage.
End of discussion.
And while we're on the subject,
the Millennial Dragon
belongs to me.
[APIS] Grandpa Ryu
doesn't belong to you
and he never will!
He deserves to be free!
That's all I can
stand from you.
If another word escapes your
lips, I'll tear you apart!
[ERIC screams]
Enough of this!
Damn kid. Serves her right.
[MARINES screaming]
What are you morons
running from?!
Hey! Hey! Hm?
[screaming]
[APIS laughing]
[APIS] Are you hungry, Grandpa?!
Try some of this. It's yummy!
You need to get
your strength back!
Don't worry, I'm not leaving
your side until you get better.
You're gorgeous!
The flowers really bring out
the color in your eyes!
[roars]
[MARINES yelling]
I can't take the noise!
Oh no! Make it stop!
Yeah, so Grandpa Ryu is loud.
[gasps]
Grandpa! You stood up!
That's great!
[APIS laughing]
[APIS]
You're back!
[APIS laughing]
Huh? What?
Really?!
Oh, boy!
You don't suppose he's...?
That's it! Fly Grandpa Ryu!
You can do it!
[APIS] You did it, Grandpa!
You're flying!
[APIS laughing]
Unacceptable!
If I can't possess the
Millennial Dragon...
...then no one will!
Kill it! Shoot it down from
the sky immediately!
All I need is the Dragonite!
[APIS screams]
[APIS]
No, stop!
Fly away, Grandpa! Go high!
Find someplace where the
cannons can't reach you!
Shoot it down quickly!
Now! Kill it now!
Leave him alone!
Now's your chance
to escape! Hurry!
[NELSON]
What are you waiting for?!
Blow it away! Fire all cannons!
[MARINE C]
Yes, sir!
I have to get the Dragonite.
[screaming]
[APIS]
Grandpa, wait!
You're going the wrong way!
[screams]
Idiots! It's coming this way!
Someone save me! Shoot it down!
[roars]
I see its fangs!
What are you waiting for?!!
[yells]
Ryu!
Hang in there, I'll help you.
Hey, what are you
trying to get at?
Don't you talk about dying!
[LUFFY] Believe me, I know
where you're comin' from.
I won't let anything happen
to Apis, I promise.
And I'll make sure you get
back to the Dragons' Nest.
Now promise me
you'll stay alive.
Grandpa!
♪All that's in my
heart confuses me,
I cannot understand,
As I face what I must do,
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand.
I'll set sail alone,
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near,
As I drift away,
I pray you watch me
as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise,
I began to wonder,
What could be the reason,
It's so hot inside.
No answer has come,
But I can't get away
from what's true,
It's because of you...
Show me how to
catch those feelings,
Get 'em to come back to me,
I'll do what I must,
Because they're
everything I wanna be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back
from yesterday,
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we
can make the way.♪
[LUFFY]
Hang in there, Grandpa Ryu!
If you wanna make it
to Lost Island,
you're gonna have to stay alive!
[USOPP]
Damn those Marine jerks!
[SANJI]
This isn't good.
I mean come on,
Luffy can't even swim.
[NAMI] Hold on a minute!
What's going on?!
The whole sea is shaking!
What in the world's happening?!
[USOPP]
Whoa! What's that ahead?!
It's coming this way!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Through the Sky They Soar!
The 1000 Year Legend
Lives Again!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!