[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] The Navy triumphed
in the War of the Best
and Luffy, unable to save his
brother Ace, fell into despair.
But this is a story from ten
years ago, in the East Blue.
What the hell did you do?
[ACE groans]
Ace! No!
Don't do it!
[gunshot]
[LUFFY]
"Where Can Freedom Be Found?
A Sad Departure of a Boy!"
[gasps]
[BLUEJAM grunts]
Dadan!
Don't you dare hurt my boys!
[ACE gasps]
I'm not afraid to kill you!
[BLUEJAM grunts]
[ACE grunts]
[DADAN panting]
Thanks, but what are
you guys doing here?
We aren't too late, are we?
Yikes, you got roughed
up pretty bad, Luffy.
You okay?
I'll make it.
And what about Sabo?
I don't see him.
He's safe in High Town.
He isn't with us anymore.
[ACE growls]
Easy, now.
[BLUEJAM]
I know you.
You're that bandit
gorilla from Mount Corvo.
Bandit, yes, gorilla, no.
But that's not the point here.
The point is, like it or not,
these kids are my
responsibility.
[BLUEJAM grunts]
Even if I've felt like
killing the brats myself,
that doesn't mean you get to.
Now, I'll say it again,
nobody hurts my boys.
So, I'll let you walk away,
but if you don't, I guarantee
you're gonna be sorry.
[BANDITS grumbling]
[BLUEJAM grunts]
I got nothin' to lose.
All right, then. Let's dance.
[DADAN]
Now! Everybody run!
[BANDITS]
Roger, Boss!
[DADAN, BANDITS panting]
Hurry up! What're you doin'?
Ace, we gotta get going!
[ACE grunts]
What's the matter?
[ACE]
I'm staying.
[BLUEJAM]
Huh?
I won't run!
[DADAN gasps]
You've got nothing to gain
here, you little idiot!
Look, this place is on fire!
Also, Bluejam is
a hardened criminal!
A little kid like you shouldn't
be fighting him to the death!
--I-I gotta help Ace!
--Luffy, cut it out!
Dammit! Stop!
[BANDITS gasp]
Take Luffy and get your
butts back to the hideout.
What about you?
I'll take care of Ace,
no matter how many
asses I gotta kick!
[BANDITS]
You're so cool.
Now, go!
[BANDITS]
Yes, ma'am!
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[BANDIT B]
Come home safe, Boss!
We'll be waiting for you!
[BLUEJAM]
Look at that, how brave.
But at the end of the day,
you're just a woman and
a child against a pirate.
Do you like those odds?
Only two kinds of people
survive in battle:
the strong and the cowardly.
Bravery doesn't enter
the picture, I'm afraid.
Oh, is that so?
[BLUEJAM]
Hmm. Have it your way.
Take this!
[DADAN yells]
[MAN A]
We're all dead!
Look around you!
There's no way out now!
Everything was fine! How
could this happen so quickly?
[MAN I]
I'm burning! I'm burning!
[MAN J]
You and everyone else!
[MAN C yells]
Just let me die already.
[MAN E gasps]
[MEN groaning]
[MAN F]
What the heck was that?
Hey! It made a path
through the fire!
[MAN K] Whoa, did somebody
do that on purpose?
[MAN L] Who cares! Now we
can get out of this hellhole!
[MAN H]
Hey! Look you guys!
There's a ship here! It's
waiting down by the shore!
[MAN M] I dunno who
and I don't know how,
but I think they're here
to save us! Let's go!
[ALL shouting]
[MAN N] Hurry, before
the fire comes back!
I've seen nobles do
some dreadful things,
but this takes the cake.
Absolutely reprehensible!
Anyhoo, this locale is
rather out of the way.
How did you hear the news?
Were you keeping
an eye on this country?
Or perhaps, is there something
here of interest to you?
What's happening here
will happen in the rest
of the world soon enough.
Human beings can't
be thrown away.
A world that allows
that must change.
No matter how long it takes,
I will stomp out this
misery and injustice.
I can't stay here, 'cause if
I do, then I'll never be free!
The children born
in this country
must have a future that
they can believe in.
[ALL gasping]
If it's freedom you want,
so long as you have the
will to fight for it,
you are welcome
aboard this ship!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL cheering]
[SABO'S MOM]
Did they find Sabo yet?
[SABO'S DAD] I called
in the military for help.
They'll find him soon enough.
All we can do now is wait.
[SABO'S MOM] I see. He does
like to give us a hard time.
That he does.
[NOBLE BB] Are you sure
that wall will protect us?
Seems like the fire could
spread here any second.
It won't last long.
Surely, they'll let us into
High Town till it passes.
Not a chance.
[NOBLE O gasps]
[NOBLE A]
Those gates are so tight,
even a flea can't get through.
[BANDITS crying]
Let me go!
Come back, Boss!
[BANDIT C, BANDIT D]
Ace, too!
No! You can't die!
[NARRATOR] No matter
how their friends cried,
Ace and Dadan did not
emerge from the flames
consuming Gray Terminal.
[grunting]
[panting]
[MAGRA]
Easy, kiddo.
You're still hurt,
what're you doin'?
[LUFFY] What do ya think?
I'm looking for Ace and Dadan!
[MAGRA sighs]
That's not gonna work!
[LUFFY]
Ow!
[MAGRA]
See? Told you!
You'll just make things worse!
[LUFFY grunts]
I'm worried, too, but for right
now, we just have to wait.
The military is down
in Gray Terminal.
Word is, they were sent
in to clean up everything
after the fire died down.
And by "clean up," I mean
"take care of any
remaining evidence."
I'm sure that extends to
killing off the survivors, too.
You'd be no exception.
But, Ace!
I can't just leave
him out there!
And we have to let Sabo
know that we didn't die!
[crying]
[NOBLE SOLDIER A laughs]
Hell of a view, don't you think?
[NOBLE SOLDIER B] Hell of
a mess we have to clean up!
Nothin' to laugh about,
that's for sure!
[NOBLE SOLDIER C]
Huh. Orders say to shoot
any survivors we find on sight.
[NOBLE SOLDIER D]
Yeah? What survivors?
[NOBLE SOLDIER C]
It's weird, though.
I've hardly seen any corpses.
[NOBLE SOLDIER D]
That fire was pretty intense.
Probably burned up
their bones, too.
I was up all night, scared that
fire would get over the wall.
Shoulda known they wouldn't
burn decent people like us.
I heard Bluejam's ship
wasn't quite so lucky.
[NOBLE B]
Good!
Let's hope the bastard
was on it when it burned.
[SABO groans]
It's morning!
[groans]
[groaning]
[panting]
[DOG panting]
[NOBLE N] Why, good morning!
What a beautiful day!
Yes. I dare say it's even
more lovely than yesterday.
[grunts]
Damn it, they're
all over the place.
[gasps]
[NOBLE SOLDIER E]
It's been a long night.
What d'you say you give up
the hide and seek and go home?
[slap]
[SABO groans]
Can't you see it will
always end this way, Sabo?
The police and military
have photos of you.
Try all you want.
There's no escape!
You'll never get out of High
Town, let alone this house,
unless I expressly permit it.
[SABO grunts]
I need you on guard duty.
Now, I'll look into
getting you new uniforms.
[NOBLE GUARDS gasp]
I'm sorry sir, but
we have other duties.
I'm a nobleman. That means
I get what I want.
Don't worry, I'll have
a word with your superiors.
[NOBLE GUARDS]
Yes, sir.
Listen, Sabo.
It's not too late for you.
From now on,
you'll lock yourself
in your room and learn
to be a proper noble.
[SABO]
No!
I don't want to be cruel,
but I am certainly capable of it
and anything else I so desire.
You could disappear,
just like your friends.
[gasps]
[SABO'S DAD]
Are we clear?
I think so.
[SABO]
Ace. Luffy.
[SABO'S DAD] If Stelly can
study hard, then so can you.
Everything will work out fine.
[SABO grunts]
And then your parents,
who worked so hard to build
a proper future for you,
can finally be happy.
Won't that be nice?
[SABO'S DAD] I'm sure it'll
be nice for you as well.
Just give it some time.
[STELLY]
Papa!
[SABO'S DAD, STELLY laughing]
[STELLY]
If you're sad, I can help!
[STELLY giggles]
[SABO'S DAD chuckles]
Dependable as always, Stelly!
We've got that big ceremony
coming up, you know.
Let's buy you some new clothes.
[STELLY]
Heh.
[SABO'S DAD]
You'll look so handsome
for the Celestial Dragon!
[SABO]
There's nothing I can do.
I'm helpless.
[SABO'S MOM] All right, that
should do it for today's lesson.
[gasps]
Study hard and I'll check
your homework tomorrow.
Have a pleasant afternoon!
[SABO]
Don't worry, guys. I'm fine.
And you're tough,
so I know you're okay, too.
There's no way you
died in that fire.
[SABO] I just wish
I could see you, even once.
[SABO]
But if people follow me,
they'll find out
you're still alive
and you'll be in danger again.
[SABO]
It looks nice from the outside,
but this house is a birdcage.
I'm gonna lose my mind
if I have to stay in this
stuffy, stuck-up place.
[birds chirping]
[SABO]
I thought I found freedom,
but it seems to
keep slipping away.
Hey, your shift is over.
Oh, yeah? I lost track of time.
That's because
you were sleeping.
No kidding.
By the way, how are
things going in town?
The big ceremony
is tomorrow, isn't it?
[NOBLE GUARD A]
Yeah, and it's wild out there.
Everyone's worked up.
[NOBLE GUARD B]
Well, that sucks for me.
A once in a lifetime chance
and I'm stuck in here.
They have me working all day,
while they go to the ceremony.
Nobody else is gonna
be in the house,
so I gotta watch the kid
to make sure he doesn't bail.
[sighs] A World Noble...
I've never seen one.
I wouldn't say it's
all bad, buddy.
I mean, just think,
the harbor will be a mess.
The whole town's gonna be there.
That's a lot of people
to keep track of
and you only have this one.
That's easy peasy.
If that's how you feel,
why don't we trade places?
[NOBLE GUARD A laughs]
Yeah, you wish.
[SABO'S DAD]
All right! We're off.
Take good care of Sabo.
We won't be back until late.
[NOBLE GUARD B]
Yes, sir. As you wish.
[NOBLE GUARD B yawns]
[CROWD chattering]
[meows]
[NARRATOR]
After much anticipation,
the day of the
World Noble's visit
to the Goa Kingdom
arrives at last.
A lavish ceremony is prepared
to greet his ship as
it enters the harbor.
[CROWD chattering]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click!
[SOLDIER A] Hello, this is
Team A on the coast.
[SUPERIOR A] The Celestial
Dragon's ship is pulling in
as we speak. It should arrive at
your location in a few minutes.
Understood, sir.
Everything looks good.
We'll keep an eye out for
anything strange, though.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
[CROWD laughing, chattering]
[NOBLE E gasps]
Hey, wait!
Is that... a ship leaving port?
[CROWD gasps]
A what?
A fishing boat?
Hey! Come back!
You're blocking their path!
Why, it's just a child!
A little boy is
steering that boat.
Then, h-he's a noble?
But surely all the families
are here watching!
It can't be.
[SABO'S MOM gasps]
No, it can't!
Sabo. He's still at home.
I gave the guard strict orders.
[gasps]
Nice weather today!
It's just perfect
for setting sail!
Crap! That's mine!
It was stolen!
I have nothing to
do with this mess!
His flag! He's got
a jolly roger on it!
Is he trying to be
a pirate or something?
Does it matter? The kid's
flag isn't the issue here!
[NOBLE L] He's heading
straight for the ship.
The Celestial Dragon
isn't gonna like this.
[SUPERIOR A]
Either you lose that boat,
or you lose your job,
do you hear me? Fix it, now!
Uh, yes, sir!
Hey!
Get back here, kid!
Are you nuts?!
I'm not afraid of anything
as long as I'm free.
I just have to be
far away from here.
I have to follow my own dream.
Nobody's gonna change me.
Huh? Holy crap, Sabo,
what do ya think
you're doin' out there?
[NOBLE SOLDIER F] Give them
a warm welcome, everyone!
[gasps] Wow, that's
one big ship!
It could run right
over me, easy.
Let's avoid that, shall we?
[gasps] He's moving.
That almost got pretty ugly.
[CROWD cheering]
[JALMACK]
What is this display?
Are the commoners
attempting to welcome us?
Yes, sir.
[JALMACK]
Hm?
[NOBLE AA]
This is a first for me!
The Celestial Dragons hardly
ever make visits like this!
[NOBLE CC]
I hope nobody mucks this up!
We didn't burn all
those people for nothing!
[JALMACK] By the way, what is
that wretched little thing?
[SUBORDINATE A] Hm. It seems
to be a fishing boat, sir.
That's so cool.
I hope I'm the captain of
a big ship like that someday.
It's time to learn your place!
[yells]
[CROWD gasping]
Insolent fool!
What's going on?
He just opened fire!
[NOBLE O screams]
[NARRATOR] Ace and Dadan
return to their hideout safely
after their battle with Bluejam.
However, the mountain bandits
scarely have time to celebrate
before the news of Sabo's
tragedy reaches their ears.
Luffy despairs
and Ace vows revenge,
but a letter from Sabo
changes their perspective.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Take Good Care of Him!
A Letter From the Brother!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!