[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest the of his crew,
Luffy has arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
He breaks into the plaza and
eventually makes his
way to the scaffold!
There, with some unexpected
help from an old enemy,
Luffy finally frees Ace!
Then, the brothers
begin their escape
as Whitebeard gives
his sons a final order!
[WHITEBEARD]
Make no mistake.
I'm a relic of a bygone era.
Long have I sailed, but no ship
can carry me into the new age.
Let's finally
put an end to this!
[LUFFY] "The Power That Can
Burn Even Fire!
Akainu's Ruthless Pursuit!"
[MARINES screaming]
[MARINE AA]
Marineford's falling apart!
[MARINE BB]
Somebody stop Whitebeard!
Damn! At this rate, he's gonna
bring down the whole island!
[PIRATES]
Pops!
[HARUTA]
We came here as a family.
We should leave as one, too!
[PIRATES]
Yeah, Pops! Come with us!
You mean to disobey
your captain's order?
I told you fools to get away!
[PIRATES]
Pops, no!
All right! This might
be our only chance!
Hit Whitebeard with
all you've got!
[WHITEBEARD growls]
[MARINES yelling]
I won't do it!
Hey! Come on, we're better
off doing what Pops says!
Are you crazy?
Pops is our father!
I won't leave him here to die!
[PIRATE C, PIRATE AA]
Yeah, let go!
[PIRATE D]
Don't be stupid!
Do you think any of us
want to leave Pops behind?
[PIRATE E, PIRATE F]
Move!
[FOSSA] Bickering about
your own petty feelings
at a time like this.
That's the kind of stuff
Pops wouldn't stand for!
Can't you see that he's
trying to do what's best for us?
[PIRATES gasp]
[crying]
[PIRATES]
Sorry!
[PIRATE BB]
Everyone, get back on the ships!
Hey, Ace!
[PIRATE CC]
Come on! Hurry it up!
We're about to take off!
[PIRATES yelling]
Commander Marco,
let's head back!
[MARCO]
Pops...
[laughing]
You completely
ruined the Navy's plan!
Die!
Don't kill me! I just
want to leave this disaster!
You don't have to do this!
Sheath your sword!
[MARINE D grunts]
[MARINES]
Huh? What the...?
[MR.3 laughs] My exquisite
wax shell is impenetrable!
You will need more than a cheap
blade to pierce this carapace!
Damn it! More
Devil Fruit powers!
Figures.
No wonder he was able to protect
Fire Fist Ace on the scaffold.
He even blocked Fleet
Admiral Sengoku's attack!
Oh, uh, well, I wouldn't
say I'm that powerful.
My skillset is better
suited for the arts.
[yelps]
[MR.3]
Thank you for your time! Adieu!
[WHITEBEARD grunting]
Whitebeard... Unreal!
He oughta be dead.
What's it gonna take
to put this guy away?
[SENGOKU]
He no longer has to worry
about saving Fire Fist Ace.
Admiral, sir?
[SENGOKU]
So long as his men can escape,
he'll sink Marineford
and all of us with it.
He's prepared to die.
I've no doubt.
[GARP grunts]
Vice Admiral Garp! You okay?
[GARP] Whitebeard
thinks our era is over?
Yeah, the old man
is probably right.
[MAN AA] We still don't know
what happened to Whitebeard!
[MAN BB]
What about his allies?
Did he really
sell them out or what?
[MAN BB] This blackout's
getting ridiculous!
[WOMAN AA]
How long will we have to wait?
[MAN A] Ugh! If that stupid
clown didn't block our view
with that fat head of his,
then maybe we'd have a clue
what was actually going on!
[PRISONER I]
Is that who I think it is?
Can it really be
the renowned pirate,
Captain Buggy?
[BUGGY]
Huh?
I'm sorry did
someone say my name?
Weird. So, was he trying
to tell us something?
Perfect. How am I supposed to
write a story on the battle now?
What's wrong with their snails?
We don't got all day!
Really?
That piece of crap is
still hiding in its shell?
Come on! Get back
out here, Mr. Snail!
We still need your help!
Captain Buggy's ready
to defeat Whitebeard!
[snorts]
[BUGGY] Don't they
realize what they're saying?
Yeah, Whitebeard's wounded,
but he's tearing down buildings!
Just look at the bastard!
Why'd I have to go
and say I'd beat him?
These morons believe
anything you tell 'em!
It's their fault for feeding
my ego! I can't help it!
[PRISONER AA]
Lure it out!
We gotta showcase
Captain Buggy's awesomeness
for the entire world to see!
Bring it over here!
I'll just smash the shell open!
[PRISONER BB] Yeah!
One strong pound oughta do it!
[PRISONER CC] No, stick
your hand in there and yank!
[PRISONER DD]
Let's soak it in salt water!
Snails love that, right?
[PRISONER EE]
Good idea!
[PRISONER FF]
Let's do it!
[BUGGY] Quit messing with
the poor thing, you fools!
[PRISONERS]
Huh?
Just think about it.
It's not like he wants to be
here slaving away for the Navy,
getting stuck in their battles
and beaten up by guys like us.
He's just trying to do
his job in difficult times.
Filming a war like this
has gotta be traumatic.
So, relax and cut
him some slack!
No! How will you
broadcast your plan?
The "Captain Buggy Beats
Whitebeard Senseless
as the Entire World
is Watching Live" plan!
Yeah! Isn't that
what you wanted?
To stick it to
the Navy and Whitebeard
to prove that you're
the King of the Pirates?
I'm disappointed!
Seriously, Boss!
[BUGGY] Good grief! Sure,
they're loyal, and stupid,
but they're also a bunch
of hard-ass prisoners
who were locked
up in Impel Down!
I better not piss
them off too much!
[PRISONERS gasping]
[BUGGY]
Huh?
The Transponder Snail
came out on his own!
Wha...? Is he...
Is he crying?
[PRISONER C]
It's a miracle!
He must've been touched by
Captain Buggy's kind words!
[BOTH gasping]
Captain Buggy's compassion
isn't lost on even
the simplest of creatures!
He's truly amazing!
[PRISONERS gasp]
[PRISONERS]
We're flattered to be serving
such an inspiring leader.
Captain Buggy was meant
to conquer this world!
[BUGGY]
No, stupid escargot!
Why couldn't he just
stay in his shell?
Are you trying to get
Whitebeard to kill me?
Thanks, snail!
[PRISONER C]
Okay, let's try again!
[PRISONER GG]
Start by making a declaration
to conquer the world!
Whenever you're ready!
All right, you got this!
[PRISONER II]
Cue smoke! Lights are ready!
Start rolling, you guys!
[BUGGY]
Well, crap! No backing out now.
Here goes nothin', I guess!
Right! Come on! We're
starting the broadcast!
And make sure you capture the
moment that I kill Whitebeard,
'cause that's
totally gonna happen!
[PRISONERS]
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
[CROWD gasps]
Hey, look!
It's back!
[MAN CC]
But what's going on?
I-I can't make out anything
through that smoke!
So, did the Navy beat the
pirates, Whitebeard, and Ace?
[BUGGY]
Uh, um, uhh...
[PRISONER C] Transponder Snail,
go down a little!
[CROWD gasps]
Why hello, everybody!
Time for Captain Buggy!
[MAN A, MAN E yelp]
[CROWD]
This guy again?!
[PIRATE DD]
Get to the sea now!
Hurry up and on the ships,
we gotta make it back to
the New World, and fast!
[MARINE CC]
Don't let them get away!
Kill as many pirates as you can!
I'm the only pirate you
should be worrying about!
[PIRATE EE]
Commander Jozu!
[PIRATE FF]
He's in pretty bad shape,
but I think he can make it.
First we gotta get him outta
here to safety! Everyone, lift!
[PIRATES gasp]
Hey, Blenheim! Get over
here on the double!
[BLENHEIM grunts]
[IVANKOV grunts]
Hurry, Straw Boy!
It's time to make an
exit, on the double!
[LUFFY] Ace, let's go!
The old guy made up his mind.
I know. This is it.
[MARINES yelling]
[ACE growls]
Back off, you bastards!
[MARINES yell]
[WHITEBEARD panting]
[ACE panting]
[panting]
[WHITEBEARD] The time for
words has passed my son...
[ACE panting]
[WHITEBEARD]
...but tell me one last thing.
[ACE panting]
[WHITEBEARD]
Are you happy to have
this old fool as your father?
[ACE gasping]
[WHITEBEARD chuckles]
Ya got some fight left?
Look, I'm not gonna
kill you today. All right?
Don't fight it,
you're too valuable to
die in a place like this.
Run wild with us and
our flag will be yours.
And I will call you my son.
[ACE crying]
Of course, Dad!
[inaudible]
Hey, what happened?
[MAN DD]
The scaffold was destroyed!
[WOMAN BB]
They're in the plaza!
Was Fire Fist Ace executed?
Please say somethin'!
Shift the camera to Whitebeard!
I'm Captain Buggy, a legend!
[grunts]
[PRISONER JJ] Tell us,
Captain Buggy the Clown,
is it true you're going
to beat your fellow legend,
Captain Whitebeard?
And will you loudly
proclaim your stake as one of
the Four Emperors by carrying
the severed head of your victim?
I'm Captain Buggy, a legend!
[PRISONER JJ]
Hey, say something else!
[gasps]
[PRISONER JJ] They got that part
already! Change it up a little!
[MAN EE]
Enough with Buggy!
Show us what's
happening at Marineford!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
[MAN FF] Come on,
who cares about this weirdo?
Get him outta the way!
[BUGGY] Okay, use that
filter! Nice! Very flashy!
[MAN GG]
What's he doing now?
[CROWD shouting]
Keep it up! We're almost there!
[PIRATE L yells]
[JIMBEI]
Ace! Luffy! Stay in front!
[LUFFY, ACE]
Huh?
They're specifically
targeting you two!
We cannot let the
old man waste his life.
He will not fall in vain!
[JIMBEI]
Farewell.
We've stolen a Navy ship!
Hop aboard!
[PIRATES shouting]
[ACE, LUFFY, JIMBEI panting]
[AKAINU] Do they really think
they stand a chance of escaping?
How naive.
Admiral Sakazuki!
[AKAINU]
Move aside. I'll handle this.
[PIRATES groaning]
[grunts]
[panting]
Never mind that.
Just don't stop running
until you reach the ship!
[AKAINU] As soon as they rescued
Fire Fist Ace, they fled!
What a cowardly crew!
Just like their
washed-up captain!
[PIRATES]
What?
He's just trying to get
you riled up, don't listen!
Keep it moving. Don't fall
into his trap, you hear me?
Yeah, that old man, huh?
Some captain he is.
It's not your fault...
That's just Whitebeard.
A washed-up failure!
[ACE gasps]
[ACE growls]
Ace!
[panting]
A failure?
Huh?
Take it back or else.
Ace! No! Don't!
Just keep moving!
He can say whatever
he wants, let's go!
No one gets away
with mocking Pops!
Stop!
Take it back?
It's not an insult,
it's the truth.
Let me tell you a story.
Your father conquered
the Grand Line,
something no other pirate
has ever accomplished.
After that, he opened the
door to the Great Pirate Era
by sacrificing his own life.
I hate to say it,
being a Navy admiral,
but he was King of the Pirates!
No question.
Keeping all that in mind,
Whitebeard has failed.
His lack of ambition meant
he'd never be king of anything
but you simple-minded cronies.
Once he brainwashed enough of
you into doing his dirty work,
he got lazy.
Every now and then,
you'll find someone
who paints him as a peacekeeper.
"Start trouble here and
Whitebeard will come runnin',"
they say.
Heh. Empty boasts to keep
idiots like you fearful.
You call him hero, when he's
nothing but a coward.
When Gold Roger was around,
Whitebeard always
had second billing.
Yet even after Roger's death,
he couldn't become King.
So there it is, the tale of
your father's whipping boy:
The Great Failure Whitebeard!
Soon enough, he'll be dead,
and no one will remember him.
[AKAINU] I can't help but
feel sorry for the man,
and all you punks call
him your "Pops."
Did you make this
fake family to humor him
or are you just as deluded?
Shut it.
[AKAINU]
He sailed the seas for years,
couldn't amount to anything,
amassed an army of losers,
and in the end was even stabbed
by one of his own "sons"
who put more stock in
my word than his own.
And still, he'll die
to protect that man.
Have you ever heard
of a more pathetic life?
That's enough!
Leave him! Run!
[PIRATES]
Ace!
You're wrong.
There's nothing fake
about the family he gave us.
But I wouldn't expect
a heartless bastard
like you to appreciate that.
Like I said,
he convinced you punks
you meant something
to the world!
But your kind doesn't
deserve a home,
you deserve the gallows.
Can it!
You know it's true!
You'll all die as failures,
and Whitebeard's nothing
but a lonely old fool!
Whitebeard is the greatest
pirate who ever lived,
you hear me?!
You don't know anything
about the man who saved my life!
[PIRATES]
Get away from him, Ace!
This is his era!
Don't you forget it!
[ACE yelling]
[yelling]
Your "Pops" will end up
the same as you, boy--
dead, and by my hand!
[ACE yelling]
How? Did he burn him?
Thanks to your Logia-Type fruit,
you're not used to being hurt.
It's made you too cocky.
You may be made of fire,
but my magma burns
even hotter than that!
Just like Whitebeard,
second rate till the bitter end.
Ace!
[LUFFY gasps]
[JIMBEI]
Luffy, stay out of harm's way!
You're in no
condition to battle!
[panting]
Ace's Vivre Card!
[LUFFY gasps]
[AKAINU] Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
and Dragon, the revolutionary...
To think that the two of
you were adopted brothers
all these years.
What a victory it'd be
to end both bloodlines.
Everyone else can escape.
The two of you are the
only targets I'm after!
Say goodbye.
[gasps]
[ACE]
Wait!
Luffy!
[gasps]
[LOLA]
This is definitely a Vivre Card,
but there's something
I neglected to tell you before.
The life force of the owner
is also reflected on the paper.
Does this belong
to someone close to you?
[LUFFY]
Yeah! It's my big brother's.
Now, you hang on
to that, always.
That scrap of paper's going
to reunite us some day.
[coughs]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] Ace protects his
brother from Akainu,
but suffers a mortal
blow in the process.
Jimbei and the Whitebeard
Pirates rush to his aid,
but soon realize
he is far beyond help.
As Ace takes his final breaths,
he gives a heartfelt
message to his comrades.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Looking for the Answer!
Fire Fist Ace Dies
on the Battlefield!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!