[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[CHIMNEY] Hey, pirate people!
--[GONBE] Meow!
--[KIWI and MOZU] Straw Hat!
[ALL panting]
[LUFFY] You need something?
Franky wants to
talk to you guys.
He's got something
big to show you!
It's been a long night,
but they finished
his ship of dreams!
And boy is it super cool!
Meow!
Huh? You mean it's done already?
That was really fast!
[MOZU] Of course!
That's what happens
when the best shipwrights
in the world
work around the clock!
[KIWI] You better believe it!
What're we
waiting for? Let's go!
Yeah!
[ZAMBAI] Straw Hat!
We've got bad news!
[KIWI] Oh, hey, you guys!
[MOZU] What's going on?
They look upset.
[KIWI] I wonder what's wrong.
[panting]
To be honest, we just found
out about this ourselves.
Have you seen
the wanted posters?
Wanted posters?
[ZAMBAI] You've got a huge
bounty on your head, Straw Hat!
They're gonna
hunt you down for sure!
Actually,
you've all got bounties.
The whole crew is wanted!
Took long enough! How much?
Not me, too!
I'm wanted?!
No point in talking, just look.
[ZAMBAI] Wanted posters
for all seven of you.
[ZAMBAI] Straw Hat Luffy with a
bounty of 300 million Berries.
[laughs]
All right! It went up!
[ZAMBAI] Pirate Hunter
Zoro with a bounty of
120 million Berries.
[chuckles]
[ZAMBAI] Cat Burglar Nami with
a bounty of 16 million Berries.
No!
[ZAMBAI] Cotton-Candy
Loving Chopper. Pet.
With a bounty of 50 Berries.
Ah--fifty?
[ZAMBAI] Demon Child Robin with
a bounty of 80 million Berries.
Who is that?
[ZAMBAI] Black Leg Sanji.
Attempt to take a photo failed.
Bounty: 77 million Berries.
[sighs]
Hey look,
Sniper King has one, too!
Only fifty?
Well I know this is probably
big news for you and all,
and I'm sure there's
a lot of pirate stuff
you want to talk about,
but uh, hold on a sec okay?
I came here 'cause I gotta
favor to ask of you guys.
Take a look at this.
It's Franky!
[ZAMBAI] Cyborg Franky, with a
bounty of 44 million Berries.
This is awful, Big Bro's wanted
by the World Government!
What're we gonna do now?
Yeah, that's the question.
I was so happy when I found out
we didn't have bounties.
But then this had to happen!
Everyone in the whole
city knows about our bro.
He can't stay
in Water 7 anymore!
And if he gets arrested again,
I don't think we'll have
the power to save him
like we did last time!
[ZAMBAI] But I'm sure he's
worried about us, too.
Knowing him, he probably
wouldn't leave the island
no matter how much
we begged him.
That's why we came to you.
We have no other choice!
We're begging
you here, Straw Hat.
Even if he tries to fight,
you gotta take our
bro out to sea with you!
Come on!
His parents were pirates--
It's in his blood!
Please, Straw Hat!
All we want is
what's best for our bro!
[FRANKY FAMILY]
Please, you gotta help him!
Come on, you guys
don't have to beg.
I already decided I was gonna
make him my shipwright.
[FRANKY FAMILY gasps]
[ZAMBAI] You mean it?
And the rest of you
are okay with that, too?
[SANJI] My face.
Ugh. I don't care anymore.
Uh...
Of course.
Well, there you have it.
Ah! Thank you.
Now that they've agreed,
it's time to move!
C'mon! You know
what we gotta do!
[FRANKY FAMILY] Yeah!
[cheering]
But wait, where are you going?
Yeah, Scrap Island
is that way, remember?
[ZAMBAI] I can't tell you.
I'm sorry, but we've got
some dirty business to do.
You're better off not knowing.
Mozu. Kiwi.
Thank you for all you've done.
[LUFFY] The King of Animals
that Overlooks the Sea!
The Dream Ship
Magnificently Completed!
All right, then.
Just to make sure, are we all
on the same page about Usopp?
[NAMI] Ah...
Heh. Yeah.
This is about
doing what's right.
I know. Let's move!
You've been depressed
for long enough.
Shut up! Why's mine the
only one with a drawing?
Who cares about the picture?
You've got a bounty!
Who is this, huh?
'Cause it's not me!
I thought it was a photo
'til you said something.
[blubbering]
[ZORO] Who has a
handsome face, again?
[SANJI blubbering]
All the women in the
world are gonna laugh at me.
Uh! That guy lied to me.
He said he was a reporter
for the local paper.
[NAMI] Having a bounty
kind of stinks,
but on the upside, the picture
turned out pretty cute.
I fought like a
true man back there!
I'm a pirate just like
all the rest of you!
And what do they mean by pet?
I'm a doctor, darn it!
Am I really only
worth 50 Berries?
Well, try harder then!
[MOZU] Hurry up, Straw Hat!
What're you doing in there?
[LUFFY] Huh?
Don't you wanna
see your ship?
Can't keep our big bro waiting!
I know, I know!
Well, hope we're not
forgetting anything!
Once we get Franky and
our new ship, we're outta here!
Hey. Sanji's not
moving anymore.
Guess we'll just
have to find a new cook.
[SANJI] What? Just gimme
a minute, damn it!
Please, Pirate Lady!
Can't you stay a little longer?
Chimney. I'm sorry.
Thank you guys for everything.
Mmm.
[CAPTAIN 321A] This is
certainly an unusual case.
There may not be many of them,
but every member of their crew
has a bounty on their head.
[CAPTAIN 321A] They're worth
over 600 million total.
Impressive.
But I was wondering...
What about this
"Black Leg" character?
Why is there no photo of him?
[ATTACH] I--well--
I assure you, sir,
I did take one,
but look at what happened
when I developed the film!
It's quite unsettling.
The photo is completely black!
[CAPTAIN 321A] Did you
by any chance forget...
to take off the lens cap?
[ATTACH] Hm?
[MOZU] Big Bro!
[KIWI]
We brought the Straw Hats!
[snoring]
[KIWI and MOZU]
Big Bro, where are you?
They're here.
Oh. I see something big!
[CHOPPER] You think that's it?
Hey Franky!
We're ready for our ship now!
Oh, hey Ice Pops, what's up?
[ICEBERG] Good to see you.
Yeah you, too,
but where's Franky?
Unfortunately, Franky
can't be here at the moment.
[ICEBERG] But the ship
is indeed complete.
Shall we take a look?
Uh-huh!
I think you're
going to be impressed.
I was floored simply
looking at the blueprints.
This ship can sail any sea.
[ICEBERG] It may take you to the
end of the Grand Line after all.
Just let me see it already!
Hurry!
[ICEBERG] There's a message
that Franky asked me
to pass on to you, Straw Hat.
He said that
if you're going to be
the King of Pirates someday...
[ICEBERG] ...then your ship
should be the King of Beasts!
It's amazing!
--You can say that again.
--Uh huh!
--Oh wow!
--How lovely.
Oh yeah.
[LUFFY] It's super big
and super cool!
It looks ready to break stuff!
Aah! And it's really free?
Huh.
It's gotta be
twice as big as Merry.
Wait, is the sail
a sloop? It's huge!
Show me the kitchen, hurry!
I wanna see!
I love the figurehead!
[ROBIN] What kind of flower
is it supposed to be?
[ICEBERG] Mwell, I think
he intended it to be a lion.
[LUFFY] The inside
is awesome, too!
And the deck has
a lawn! It's so soft!
[CHOPPER] There's a slide!
It might be nice to do
some gardening up here.
Good for a nap, too.
[SANJI] Quick!
Where's the kitchen?
[NAMI] It must have
great mobility
with a gaff sail of that size!
Yes, they call this kind
of ship a brigantine.
Brigantine ships are
square-rigged in the front
and have a gaff sail
in the back, like a sloop.
They're quite versatile if the
navigator is up to the task.
Hm. Sounds like
a challenge! I love it!
[NAMI] Time to
check out the interior.
[SANJI] Ooh! It's got
a fridge with a lock,
just like I always wanted!
And look at
this oven! It's huge!
Oh, you're the best, Franky!
You made all my
dreams come true!
Hey, Ice Pops.
This is cool and all,
but where did Franky go?
We gotta thank him for this!
I'm sorry,
but it would appear that
he doesn't want to see you.
Huh?
Straw Hat. You were going
to invite Franky
to be your shipwright,
weren't you?
Yep. Wouldn't have it
any other way.
Besides, this is
his ship after all--
he has to come.
Then that might be your problem.
[LUFFY] Y'mean he
doesn't wanna join?
[ICEBERG] Just the opposite.
Rather, if you invited him
he wouldn't be able to refuse.
That's why he's
hiding right now.
Mwell, what I'm saying...
is that he wants to
join you in his heart.
[ICEBERG] Of course, you can
probably see that for yourself,
looking at all the love and care
he put into building this ship.
[CHOPPER] Whoa! Check it out!
There's an aquarium
in here, too!
[NAMI]
Oh, wow! It's beautiful!
And he's quite
fond of your crew,
so please don't blame
yourself for this.
[ICEBERG] But he
believes it's his duty
to stay on this island.
His bond has become
the chain that binds him.
Yeah?
Yes. Though if you ask me,
I think he's being
needlessly
stubborn over nothing.
Still, that's how he feels.
[ICEBERG]
So trying to reason with him
would be a waste of time.
If you really
want him to go with you,
then your only choice
is to use force.
Since he's not willing
to break that chain,
[ICEBERG] you'll have to
do it for him!
Use force?
And after he was so nice to us.
[LUFFY] Well, I guess
I can give it a shot.
C'mon, we gotta see
Big Bro off with
smiles on our faces! No crying!
I keep telling
the tears to stop man,
but I--I don't think
I can do it, no matter--hey!
[FRANKY FAMILY] Huh?
[FRANKY FAMILY gasps]
Bro, what the heck
are you doing here?
[FRANKY] Huh?
Why wouldn't I
be here, dumbass?
This is the Franky House,
right? I live here.
Yeah, but--
Are you sure about
what you're doing, Big Bro?
I mean you--you wanna
sail with the Straw Hats
on that ship
you built, don'tcha?
[FRANKY] Huh? What kinda
stupid question is that?
Of course not.
[FRANKY] Heh. Besides,
look at this mess.
What would you do without
me when you lug-heads
can't even build a house right?
Don't say that!
We just got back from
begging the Straw Hats
to take you with them!
Even if it'll be tough
without you, you gotta go!
[grunts]
You damn fools!
Mind your own business!
But! They want you to go, too!
The Straw Hat Crew
needs a shipwright!
You can't just turn them down!
Gimme one reason why
I should become a pirate
after all we've been through!
I can tell just by
looking at'chya.
[ZAMBAI] I mean,
you shoulda seen yourself
building that ship, bro.
In all the time
we've been together,
I've never seen you
smile like that even once.
You were like a new man.
You were doing what
you were meant to do.
Big Bro.
You knew the Straw Hats
were gonna ask you
to be their shipwright
before they left, didn't you?
That's why you
ran away, isn't it?
But thanks to this,
it doesn't matter anyway!
Shoulda known.
Guess it was only
a matter of time.
Even if you wanted, you
couldn't stay with us anymore!
And even if you don't think
we can make it without you,
we don't wanna drag you down!
But thanks to this,
it doesn't matter anyway!
Shoulda known.
Guess it was only
a matter of time.
Even if you wanted, you
couldn't stay with us anymore!
And even if you don't think
we can make it without you,
we don't wanna drag you down!
You cowards are just
scared of the Navy, aren't you?
I bet you're trying to
get rid of me, huh?
[FRANKY FAMILY sighs]
Maybe you forgot already,
but you people were
dying in a ditch
before I picked you up
and made you what you are today!
[ZAMBAI] Come on,
bro, don't be cruel.
Of course we
know that. But still!
If I'm not here,
you guys'll probably
starve to death in a week!
[yells]
I got his undies!
Whoa! He took his swim briefs!
Yes! Brilliant!
Don't lose 'em!
Pass 'em here!
Take the undies and run!
Gimme back my briefs!
[FRANKY FAMILY gasps]
[yells]
That's the only
pair of those I got!
[FRANKY FAMILY SILVERHAIR]
Everyone scatter! Let's go!
Have it your way! [grunts]
[FRANKY 321A]
He's coming after us!
You bastards think
I need undies to beat you?
I can take you down
stark naked if I have ta!
Only one of us
needs to survive!
We gotta make it to
Scrap Island no matter what!
[ZAMBAI] Get those
undies to Straw Hat!
[grunts]
[distant scream]
[FRANKY] Strong Right!
[FRANKY] Gimme back my briefs!
Too bad, bro.
They're long gone now.
Damn it, I saw 'em!
Don't you dare
play dumb with me!
[FRANKY 321B] Over here!
Hurry! Pass 'em!
Crap! A fakeout!
[FRANKY grunting]
Keep heading south and
don't look back! We got this!
Huh? What's with
all the ruckus?
[GENTLEMAN 321A panting]
There--there's a pervert!
Franky's running wild
and pantsless!
Again?
No! He'll destroy the city!
[commotion]
That's disgusting!
[screams]
I'll kick your ass
naked if I have ta!
He's even more
indecent than usual!
[screams]
Whoa! Check out the--
Hurry, get the children inside!
Don't let them see the pervert!
[FRANKY] Strong Right!
[FRANKY FAMILY groans]
[FRANKY grunts]
You're under arrest
for public indecency!
Surrender immediately!
[FRANKY] Huh?
[yelps]
You... can't give up...
the undies!
[grunts]
[distant yell]
[FRANKY FAMILY SPLITHEAD]
The Yagara's ready to go!
Good! Move it!
[YAGARA] Eee!
[FRANKY FAMILY BALDY yells]
[FRANKY 321J] The backstreets
have turned into a battlefield!
[FRANKY FAMILY
SILVERHAIR groans]
My legs. So tired.
I'm done for!
[LUFFY]
Hey! Pass 'em to me! Hurry!
[gasps]
Up here!
It's Straw Hat!
Don't you dare!
[yells]
[LUFFY] Let's see
where they go next!
[FRANKY] Little turd!
Come back here!
[CITIZENS groaning]
So, how'd you like the ship?
It's awesome! [chuckles]
In fact, I think it's the
coolest ship I've ever seen!
Thanks a lot!
Aah! My innocent eyes
have been tainted!
Stop him!
Throw that freak in jail!
Damn straight it's awesome!
It was made from my
super blueprints after all!
I included all of your requests,
and hooked it up
with my one-of-a-kind
Soldier Dock System.
Have you had
the chance to try it?
Sorry, but not yet!
[FRANKY] Well just you wait,
'cause it's gonna blow you away!
[FRANKY]
What about the fish tank?
[LUFFY] Love it!
If you catch fish and
dump 'em in the tank up top,
you'll be able to
see them swim around
in the room below.
It's an aquarium
and a dining room all in one!
The whole crew can meet
down there for a fancy dinner
and you know you'll always
have fresh fish to pick from!
Looking forward to it!
Just like I promised,
it's the best damn ship
that a man can build!
[FRANKY] A ship of dreams,
for both of us!
Now give me back my briefs...
or I'll blow you to smithereens!
[yells]
[LUFFY] Chopper!
[CHOPPER] Got it!
Look, here he comes!
We're counting on
you two for this one!
[ZORO] No problem!
Huh?
[ZORO, SANJI] Get in!
[FRANKY yells]
Ready? Aim for
Scrap Island!
What the hell
are you trying to do?!
The Franky Family's
Secret Weapon!
Fire! Shoot Anything Cannon!
Hey! Cut it out!
This has gone on long enough!
[FRANKY screams]
Hey! Aren't we supposed to
send his undies there first?
[LUFFY] Grab on, Chopper!
Huh?
Now, Gum-Gum... Rocket!
[CHOPPER screams]
[distant murmurs]
Franky was flying!
Heaven is punishing us!
Careful! He could
get up and go wild!
Ooh!
[CHIMNEY] Franky's naked!
--[KIWI and MOZU] Big Bro...
--[CHIMNEY] Franky's naked!
--[GONBE] Meow! Meow!
[laughs]
Mwell... This certainly
took an interesting turn.
[FRANKY] Aah...
[LUFFY] Franky!
Huh?
Thanks, the ship is great!
Just like you said,
it's the best!
We'll take good care of it!
Heh. Yeah!
I had fun with you guys!
Have a safe trip!
[LUFFY] Oh, I hate to
break it to you,
but if you want
your undies back,
then you're gonna
have to join our crew!
[growls]
[FRANKY] I was sure you guys
were useless without me,
but you really pulled
one over on me this time.
What am I supposed to do now?
No matter what you say,
this town is
still special to me,
and you guys are, too! I--
[FRANKY sobbing]
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Goodbye My Dear Underlings!
Franky Departs!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!