Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy was sent flying
from the Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma.
After soaring through
the sky for hours,
he found himself in a kingdom
inhabited entirely by women,
Amazon Lily.
[NARRATOR] After a
scuffle with the Kuja tribe,
Luffy escaped, only to
return in search of a boat.
[gong ringing]
[ENISHIDA]
Your attention please!
The Snake Princess
will now bathe!
[LUFFY] This is... a huge bath!
A man?
Hey...
That thing on your back.
It looks...
...kinda familiar.
You saw it?
[LUFFY]
Heartless Judgment!
Margaret is Turned to Stone!
What's the matter?
I heard a loud crash!
Are you okay? What happened?
Am I seeing things, or...
...is that a man?
What is a man
doing on our island?
Shroud yourself
from his leering gaze.
Huh? No!
My secret is out.
He saw my back.
Then we mustn't let him
leave the castle alive.
Why not?
What's the big deal?
I just saw her back.
But y'know, it's kinda weird.
I coulda sworn I've
seen that somewhere before.
What you saw is a secret
we would die to protect.
Or rather, one that
we would kill to protect,
in this particular instance.
Secret? That thing?
Why's it a secret?
Who are you?
[HANCOCK] Take those questions
to the grave with you.
Love-Love Beam!
Hold on. What?
It's a Slow-Slow Beam!
No! It's making...
...me slow!
Love-Love Beam!
[LUFFY yelling]
Why won't he
transform into stone?
Don't tell me he doesn't
feel any excitement
after seeing me in the bath!
I am without flaw!
But that's simply beyond
the realm of possibility!
The sublime grandeur
of your nude form
can irreparably
beguile any creature!
His fear of death
must be overwhelming
the impure urges within him.
He's a pitiful coward,
but he's a lucky one!
[LUFFY] You keep
talkin' 'bout dying, so bye!
I was just looking for
someone important to talk to!
From this high up?
He's out of his mind!
I've got him.
Now Pistol Kiss!
What the...
They didn't bounce off me.
What kind of bullets were those?
That man is a
dangerous intruder!
Kuja Pirates!
Go forth and capture him!
Uh... Yes, ma'am!
A man?
How did a man even get here?
Who cares? Let's just
go and catch the bastard!
Right.
[coughing]
That hurt!
[RAN] If you want to live,
you'll do as we say.
[DAISY] Of course he will, Ran.
No man alive is stupid enough
to defy the Kuja Warriors.
He's pretty scrawny, anyway.
[giggling]
It is a man.
A real live man in our village?
I've got a hunch you guys
are the all-woman
pirate group I've heard about.
I'm lookin' for your boss.
Where is she?
Why do you want to know that
and why should I tell you?
Well, your boss has
got her own ship, right?
If I find her,
I was hoping she
might be nice enough
to give me a ride
to go see all my friends.
That's just ridiculous.
All men are forbidden
in Amazon Lily,
which makes you a trespasser.
Clearly, she won't
let you leave here alive!
Men sure are dumb.
[giggling]
I can't let myself go
and get caught again!
Now Gum-Gum...
[RAN] Seize him!
...Rocket!
[AMAZON 412A]
What the...
After him, quickly!
You heard the
Snake Princess' orders!
He can't escape, no matter what!
[AMAZON 412C] There's a mannnn!
[AMAZON 412C]
There's a man on the island!
[AMAZON 412D] A man?
The Kuja Pirates are trying
to capture him right now.
We should pitch in
and help them out, too!
[AMAZON 412E]
You're right! Let's go!
She's already put
our land in peril.
But to allow a man onto
the island at a time like this
smacks of insolence.
I've tried to hold my tongue,
but frankly, I'm starting
to worry about our future
with her in charge.
[RAN] Don't let him get away!
[MARGARET]
The Kuja Pirates are back!
And from the look of things,
the man has returned
to the village as well.
[APHELANDRA]
There he is! Up there!
[LUFFY] Darn.
I really thought she'd be
in the tallest building here.
Let's see, if I was
important, where would I go?
How did they find me so fast?
I jumped the whole village!
We'd better
hurry up and kill him
before the Snake Princess
can interrogate him.
Those girls
really wanna shoot me.
[MARGARET] He fell!
There he is! Behind us!
[LUFFY] Aw, crap!
[RAN] Halt!
[chuckling]
[NYON] Nyot so fast!
[NYON] A pirate worth
300 million Berries.
But what is he doing
in Amazon Lily?
[RAN] I found him!
Sorry, I gotta run!
Thanks for the grub, though!
Hold on!
Let me have one
last look at your face!
[NYON] I said hold on!
This place is freaking nuts.
Even the old ladies are strong.
[RAN]
Ha! We've got you cornered.
We're too late.
The Kuja Pirates captured him.
There's nothing we can do.
I fear we must prepare
for the worst, my sisters.
[NYON]
There's nyo doubt about it.
It really is him.
[AMAZONS praising]
[LUFFY] Get offa me,
you stupid snakes!
What kind of snakes are these?
They feel like
they're made of iron!
It seems luck is against us.
Let's just hope they
skip the interrogation
and kill him right away.
But they'll kill him
no matter what.
Won't they?
What's with this country?
They weren't joking
when they said
there aren't
any men around here.
[AMAZONS praising]
I'm ready for
my explanation now.
Specifically,
I would like to know
how you got onto this island
and what you want here.
I don't know!
I'm just as confused as you!
I got sent
flying through the sky,
and the next thing
I knew, I landed here!
An unlikely story.
Lying to me
will only guarantee you
an excruciatingly painful death.
You're here
because you want something.
Well, yeah,
I could really use a ship.
Actually, it'd be
better if you guys
could just give
me a lift, though.
Either way,
I'm in a pretty big hurry
and I need to
get going right away.
You are the boss
around here, right, lady?
So help me out!
Who does this
disrespectful punk think he is?
The Snake Princess is right!
That story is clearly
an implausible fabrication!
Don't listen to him,
he's plotting something!
You can't deceive us!
Anyway, guess I should pay
you back for all your help.
If there's anything
I can do for you, just ask.
I can't rest 'til I know
my friends survived like I did.
That's all that matters.
'Cause as long as they're alive,
we can get back up
and keep fighting!
[AMAZONS chattering angrily]
The only way that you will
leave this island is by dying.
And your departure is imminent.
Please, Snake Princess,
he's not lying!
[AMAZONS gasp]
I know how this must sound,
but I don't believe this man
is the kind of person
who can tell a lie!
--What is she doing?
Please, Snake Princess.
I believe he's
telling the truth.
This man is
incapable of anything
but a childlike sincerity.
I honestly don't
think he would ever
try to inflict
any harm upon our land.
Hey, thanks, buddy!
I knew you didn't
really wanna kill me!
You're one of our
warriors, aren't you?
[MARGARET]
Yes, my name is Margaret.
Given that men
are forbidden here
under penalty of death,
he sealed his fate the
moment he arrived in our land.
Why defend him?
Because I share
the burden of guilt.
The person who brought him here
and who allowed him
into the city...
It was me!
[AMAZONS gasp]
Margaret, no! You can't!
Snake Princess!
Please still your fury.
It was not her fault!
It's true!
We found him
knocked out in the forest
totally covered in mushrooms!
We thought he was one of us
so we brought him back here!
[MARGARET]
Sweetpea! Aphelandra!
We're just as
guilty as Margaret,
but under all those mushrooms,
we just couldn't tell!
It was an
honest mistake, Empress!
Stop it!
I won't let you do this!
I'm the one who
said we should bring him
back to the village, not you!
Does she realize
what she's doing?
She's trying to be honest,
but she's
just being stupid.
[laughing]
You guys are all right!
You were trying
to kill me back there,
but now I see you're
actually pretty nice!
I bear the sole responsibility
for bringing
the man here, Empress!
--Please, Margaret!
[HANCOCK] It's all right.
[HANCOCK] Now lift your head,
honest little Margaret.
I have a soft spot for
hopelessly sincere people.
Now tell me, Margaret.
Do you wish for my forgiveness?
I... I do.
You may rise to your feet.
Well, that's the
Snake Princess for you.
Not only is she beautiful,
she's also
filled with compassion.
We love you, Snake Princess!
Love-Love Beam!
Huh? What the...
Why didn't you keep quiet?
Hold on! What happened?
What's wrong with you guys?
[LUFFY]
They turned to stone! Why?
[LUFFY] Hey...
[LUFFY] Hey!
[LUFFY] Hey, you!
What the hell did you do?
These three
saved my life, you know!
[HANCOCK] Precisely.
And now they have
been justly punished
for their transgression.
Then it's my fault.
[LUFFY] Wait!
Turn them back to normal now!
[HANCOCK] How amusing!
You think you can
give me orders, do you?
Turn them back, dammit!
I believe it's
time to release Bakula.
Bakula?
The man's already dead
and he doesn't even know it!
I told you to turn them back!
This is the female
warrior nation of Amazon Lily.
Here, strength is
regarded as true beauty.
Show us what little
strength you may possess,
and be grateful that I've
given you death in battle.
[HANCOCK] Behind you stands
the panther known as Bakula.
The beast has served
as the official executioner
of Amazon Lily
for generations now.
[HANCOCK] When it's done,
there won't be a single
bone left to remember you by.
Oh, my,
our furry friend seems
to be rather famished today.
Indeed, we're in luck.
It so happens that Bakula
hasn't been fed in several days.
You should be happy, man.
Bakula normally tortures
and toys with its prey first.
But he'll eat you
in a single bite today.
I don't care about your cat.
All I care about is them!
Turn them back, now!
Do you hear how that savage
is speaking to
the Snake Princess?
Tear him limb
from limb, Bakula!
Now, Bakula!
[AMAZONS] Eat him!
He's strong.
He just knocked Bakula out
with a single blow!
And he didn't
even use any Haki.
Then... that was
just brute strength?
What the hell
is wrong with all of you?!
That woman up there.
She turned three of
your own people into stone!
How can you just sit up
there and laugh like that?
[AMAZON]
I never!
That little savage has
the gall to shout at us!
Don't listen to him!
He's just an animal!
Sure, I feel
sorry for those three.
But the Snake Princess had
every right to do what she did!
[AMAZON 412C] Of course!
It was justice!
They violated
the law of our land!
What you don't understand...
...is that I'll be
forgiven for anything I do.
Absolutely anything.
And the reason why...
...is because I'm beautiful.
[screaming]
Just look at me.
I'm sure you must agree.
Actually, you make me sick.
[MARIGOLD] Stay strong, sister!
This simply cannot be happening.
There's no man alive
that can resist my allure!
It's just not possible!
So long as that man
exists in this world,
I shall never know peace again!
How dare you hurt
the Snake Princess like that!
Make the man
suffer for his crimes!
Execute him!
[AMAZONS] Execute! Execute!
[HANCOCK]
Marigold! Sandersonia!
Defend my honor
and take his head!
[AMAZONS] Execute! Execute!
You got it. We'll get
the job done, big sis.
So these girls
have powers, too.
[AMAZONS] Execute! Execute!
Execute! Execute!
[chanting continues]
[NARRATOR] When Empress
Hancock orders her sisters
to execute Luffy,
they transform
into fearsome serpents
and begin a deadly assault.
Luffy fights for his life,
but soon discovers
that the two women
have a mysterious ability
that allows them to slither
through all of his attacks
unharmed.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
A Difficult Fight for Luffy!
The Snake Sisters' Haki Power!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!