[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[USOPP]
Sound the alarm!
They're here!
They're here and they're
gonna kill us all!
Oh, no!
Pirates! Pirates!
Pirates are attacking!
Run!
Everybody run for your lives!
Pirates! Pirates!
Everybody run!
Pirates are coming!
[LUFFY]
"The Honorable Liar?
Captain Usopp!"
There's absolutely
no way we'll make it
to the Grand Line
in this condition.
[LUFFY,ZORO]
Huh?
You're right, we're gonna
need a whole lot more meat.
[LUFFY] Eating fruit
everyday is for the birds.
We'll also need
some booze. [grunts]
[NAMI]
Shut up, you boneheads! Ugh!
That's not what I mean.
The Grand Line's
a dangerous place
we'll need more than beer
and meat to survive there.
Not to mention the place
is crawling with pirates
who are also in search
of the One Piece,
and they all have ships that
are way better than this.
And we don't have a crew.
[NAMI] We don't have a crew,
we don't have any equipment,
or even a real ship
for that matter!
There is now way we'll
ever make it like this.
Yep, we'll need a cook
and maybe a musician
to keep us entertained.
A musician? [laughs]
[NAMI]
So... stupid.
A little to the south of here
is an island with some
settlements on it.
And it looks like
we might be able to get our ship
and some of the supplies
we need there.
Fresh meat at last!
And lot's of booze, as well!
[NAMI]
Is that all you think about?!
Ugh! What am I gonna
do with you two?!
[USOPP]
The pirates are coming!
Run if you want to live!
They'll be here any minute now!
Run! [panting]
The killers are on the shore!
Their bloodlust is unquenchable!
[USOPP panting]
Uh...we're doomed!
[USOPP]
The pirates...
are a...
Lie!
[laughing]
[USOPP grunts]
[USOPP]
That hurt!
You little liar! You're not
gonna get away this time!
We've had enough!
This little game is over!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
Wait, wait, wait!
Now, run!
[yelling continues]
[USOPP laughing]
[USOPP]
Just try and catch me!
‐‐C'mon slow pokes! [laughs]
‐‐[VILLAGERS yelling]
Aw, man! Looks like
he got away again!
That kid's a no
good troublemaker!
He'd better hope I
never get a hold of him!
Looks like nobody's getting
a hold of him today. Hmph.
[USOPP giggles]
Ah! Yet another job well done!
It is my solemn duty to send
the wind of excitement through
this boring, old village.
[PEPPER]
There he is!
[USOPP]
Hm?
Hey you guys! What's going on?!
[PEPPER] I bid you good
morning, Captain Usopp!
Fear not! Your loyal crew,
the Usopp Pirates, have arrived!
[USOPP grunts]
Pepper, Carrot. It's just
you two? Where's Onion?
Have you seen him around today?
[ONION screaming]
[ALL]
Hm?
[ONION]
Sound the alarm!
They're here! They're here!
They're here and they're
gonna kill us all! Oh, no!
Hey, it's Onion.
I wonder what he's
freaking out about.
Pirates! Pirates are here!
Run for your lives! Pirates!
We don't stand a chance!
Bloodthirsty murderers have
landed! Run everybody, run!
[USOPP]
Huh?
Stop playing.
[ONION panting]
I'm not playing!
[USOPP]
Eh...It's for real?
Yes, it's for real!
Pirates are here!
Gah! Gotta go!
Um... time for me
to have my snack!
[KIDS]
You chicken!
[USOPP]
Actually, I'm sick! Yeah!
I have, "I'll‐die‐if‐I‐
don't‐eat‐my‐snackiosis".
[PEPPER, ONION]
You liar!
You always told us that you
wanted to become real pirate
someday, and now's our chance!
[PEPPER]
Yeah! What's with you?
What kind of a pirate is
afraid of other pirates?!
If I recall correctly,
it was Buggy the Clown's mark.
[USOPP]
B‐Buggy the Clown?
Uh...I think I'll just...
But I only saw two tiny boats!
And there were
just three people.
It's go time, Brave
Usopp Pirates!
We do have a village to protect!
[KIDS]
Uh...
Let's go, men! Move out!
[KIDS]
Uh...Sir!
[LUFFY]
Ahh!
[ZORO grunts]
Feels good to be
on dry land again!
[LUFFY] There's a village
somewhere around here, right?
[NAMI] Yeah... It looks
like small one, though.
[LUFFY]
Ooh! Ooh! Then, there's meat!
There's meat!
There has to be a place to
eat meat in this village!
Just forget about meat
for a minute, would ya?
[rustling]
[ZORO yawns]
[ZORO]
Huh?
Careful...
...we're being watched.
Huh? By who? Where are
they? They got meat?
Look out!
[LUFFY yelping]
‐‐[NAMI screaming]
‐‐[LUFFY yelping]
[LUFFY]
Ohh! That's so cool!
Is this supposed to be
when we're impressed?
[USOPP laughing]
I am Usopp!
Leader of the invincible
nation of pirates
who reign over this island!
You stand before
a living legend,
the most revered
pirate who ever lived!
I am the Great Captain Usopp!
[LUFFY]
Ahh!
Hm?
Surely you know that plotting
an attack on this island
would mean certain death!
My army of 80 million super‐mean
pirate soldiers would
squash you like bugs!
Awesome!
[NAMI sighs]
[NAMI]
You expect us to believe that?
Ah! She knows!
Yep! Well, now I know.
How could I have
been so dumb?!
I practically told
her I was lying!
I am such an idiot!
So stupid!
[NAMI]
Uhh...
What?! He was lying?!
[USOPP]
Curse you, you crafty tactician!
80 million may have
been an exaggeration,
but I have a great many
men under my control!
[KIDS whimper]
My guess is three.
[KIDS screaming]
She does know!
[screaming continues]
Hey! Where're you
guys going? Come back!
[NAMI] A pirate using
a slingshot, huh?
Well, now I've seen it all.
[laughing] That's pretty cool!
Shut your mouth or
I'll shut it for you!
I'm a proud man and
I won't stand for it!
This is your
last warning,
or you'll get to see
why they call me...
"Proud Usopp", and not
"Pushover Usopp".
Is that clear?
You've already seen for yourself
just how good I am
with this thing, so,
you know I could rival
anyone carrying a pistol!
Now that you've drawn your
pistol, are you willing...
...to use it?
[USOPP gasps]
[LUFFY] Guns aren't for
threats, they're for actions.
Are you willing
to risk your life?
[ZORO chuckles]
[ZORO] I can assure you,
we're real pirates.
Consider your next
move very carefully.
[USOPP grunts]
[grunting continues]
[USOPP grunting]
Now that you've drawn your
pistol, are you willing...
...to use it?
[USOPP gasps]
Guns aren't for threats,
they're for actions.
Are you willing
to risk your life?
[USOPP grunting]
[grunting continues]
[USOPP grunting, gasps]
[USOPP sighs]
[USOPP whimpers]
Gah. Real pirates definitely
have a lot more punch
behind their words, 'cause
they can actually back 'em up!
That's so cool....
[LUFFY]
Hm!
[LUFFY, ZORO laugh]
I stole that!
[USOPP]
Huh?
[LUFFY] I stole those words
from Red Haired Shanks,
a pirate I know.
What?
You know Red Haired Shanks?
You really are a real pirate!
Wait, you gotta be lying,
do you really know him?
Yep! I know your dad too.
His name's Yasopp right?
[USOPP]
Huh?
[USOPP laughs, yelps]
[LUFFY chuckles]
[USOPP]
Uh... You're right.
My old man's name is Yasopp.
But, how?
How in the world
do you know him?
[USOPP]
This is good, huh?
So, I met your dad when
I was just a little kid.
Hold on, does my old
man really know Shanks?
Know him?! When I met your dad
he was a part of Shanks's crew,
so they were probably
pretty good friends.
I can't believe it!
My old man, sailing the high
seas with famous pirates.
[LUFFY] I haven't heard
from him in a while,
but I'll bet he's
still with them.
He was a heck of
a sharpshooter!
I'd keep him on my crew!
Whoa! Good shot!
Eh, That's nothing,
I could shoot an ant between
the eyes from across town!
[PIRATES chattering]
[YASOPP]
Ah! You know something, Luffy?
I got a kid named Usopp,
and he's just about your age!
You told me about him already.
A hundred times.
A hundred?
[LUFFY grunts]
Well, too bad!
I'm tellin' ya again!
It broke my heart to leave.
But I had to go.
You see, Luffy?
When the pirate flag beckons,
you must heed it's call!
[PIRATES CHEER]
[LUFFY grunting]
He used to go on and on
and on about his son.
I think I heard enough about
you to make my ears bleed!
And lemme tell you,
he was a great pirate!
Yeah? Really?
I sure am proud
of my old man.
He leapt into a pirate's
life on the endless sea.
And chose a life
of real adventure!
Maybe you can help us!
Do you know someone who could
provide us with a decent ship;
or even anyone who knows
how to sail for that matter?
[USOPP sighs] Well, It's a
pretty small village...
Sorry, but I just don't think
we'll be able to help you.
[ZORO]
What about that huge mansion?
[USOPP]
Ee!
The one on top of
that hill over there.
Hey! Do you know them, Usopp?
With all that money, surely they
could help us get our boat.
You stay away from there!
[NAMI, LUFFY, ZORO]
Huh?
Gah! Uh...
I just remembered something
that I really gotta do!
Everybody knows
me at this place,
So, uh, stay and eat
as much as you want!
Well, uh, gotta go!
Why was he in such a
hurry to get outta here?
[KLAHADORE]
You wish to see Usopp...
Don't start this, again.
May I see him?
I like talking to him.
[sighs] No, ma'am.
That man is, without a
doubt, a chronic liar.
For someone in your
weakened state,
Usopp's outlandish stories
might be too much to handle.
But I...
Your late parents instructed
me to protect you to the fullest
of my abilities. It would
be against their wishes
for you to see him, Miss Kaya.
Now then, I'll leave
your medicine right here.
Please be sure to take it.
Killjoy...
[KLAHADORE]
"Killjoy" will do.
A name I'll bear,
if you are kept safe.
‐‐[KAYA whimpers]
‐‐[doors clatter]
[USOPP]
Pardon the intrusion... Ow!
[KAYA gasps]
Usopp! You came!
Of course! How are you?
You seem a little down.
[KAYA]
I guess I am.
I'm tired of talking like this,
I'd like to invite inside
like a proper guest,
but there's just no way
Klahadore would ever allow that.
He's not a bad person, though.
Don't sweat it!
Remember, I'm a brave
warrior of the sea,
who likes endless
oceans and the open sky!
Houses weren't made
for rogues like me.
I'd probably just feel
cramped in there. [laughs]
So, what adventure are you
going to tell me about today?
[USOPP]
Hmm. Well let's see...
Oh, I know!
What about the story of me
fighting a giant goldfish
at the south pole, when
I was only five years old!
[KAYA]
A goldfish?
[USOPP]
A giant goldfish!
What first astounded me was
the immense size of it's poop!
It was so big that
when I landed on it,
I thought it was solid ground.
It looked like an island!
[USOPP, KAYA laughing]
[KIDS]
Hm?
Are you sure this
is the place they took him?
Yeah, those terrible
pirates dragged him inside
and now it's up to us
to save our captain!
But, guys, those're
real pirates!
What if they've grilled
and eaten him already?
You idiot!
It's grisly old witch hags who
eat their victims, not pirates!
OK you guys, this
time it's for real.
[KIDS gulp]
This is gonna be the most brutal
and epic battle of our lives,
we must show no mercy because
they will never show it to us!
[KIDS]
Hm!
[KIDS] The Usopp
pirates, have arrived!
‐‐[LUFFY] Huh?
‐‐Who're these kids?
Captain Usopp is gone!
Did they...
Fess up, you filthy pirates!
What have you done with
our beloved Captain?!
Tell us now!
[ONION, CARROT]
Yeah! Tell us now!
[LUFFY sighs]
That meat sure was good!
‐‐[KIDS gasp]
‐‐What meat?
These pirates are cannibals!
[giggles]
What have you done, you savages?
[ZORO] If you're looking
for your captain...
...we ate him.
[KIDS]
Wah! Cannibals!
What are you punks
looking at me for?!
[LUFFY, ZORO laughing]
[NAMI] You just had to say
something stupid, didn't you?!
[PEPPER laughs]
You really had us going there.
[LUFFY]
Whoa! This place is huge!
And If our captain
ran off at this hour,
then this is the
place he's gonna be.
Oh... What in the world
does Usopp come here for?
He comes to lie.
To lie? That's terrible!
[PEPPER]
He's not a bad guy!
He's great! Isn't he?
Yeah! He's awesome!
How is a liar awesome?
[PEPPER] Well, Kaya,
the girl who lives there,
has been in a terrible
depression that's kept
her weak and in bed since
her parents got sick
and died a year ago.
She's very rich,
but all that money
couldn't help her
recover from her sadness.
[ONION] So our captain tells
his special made‐up stories
to make her laugh
and cheer her up!
[CARROT] Captain Usopp is
the best at telling lies!
Wow, that really is
pretty nice of him.
[KIDS]
Yeah!
The best thing about
him is his mischievous side,
he's always up to something!
I like him 'cause he's
not afraid to be silly!
And I like the
Captain's crazy lies!
So when he tells
her those stories,
he makes her feel better?
[CARROT]
Yep! Lot's better!
[LUFFY] Great! I think we should
ask her for a ship after all!
We're not the ones who make
her feel better, Usopp is.
[ONION]
Getting in is impossible!
Those guards at the gate
don't let anyone through!
‐‐[ALL] Uhh...
‐‐[CARROT] Where's Luffy?
‐‐I'll go ask her!
‐‐[ALL gasp]
[ZORO]
No! You're not gonna‐‐
[LUFFY]
Gum‐gum!
[KIDS yell]
His arms are all stretchy!
He's some kind of monster!
Pardon the intrusion...
[ZORRO]
N‐No, no, no, no!
‐‐LUFFY] Rocket!
‐‐[ALL yelling]
[USOPP] So after that terrifying
and traumatic little incident,
we escaped into the sky riding
on a giant slingshot ball!
What's that?
[USOPP]
Hm? Uh...
Yahoo!
[Yelling]
[LUFFY]
That worked well...
Yeah, real well!
My goodness, are you okay?
Uh... Don't mind them Kaya,
this happens to me all the time.
That's just the price of
being a famous adventurer!
They're just new recruits
who heard about me
and came to join
the Usopp pirates!
Nope, not me. I came
here to see you.
I wanted to ask you a favor.
A favor? From me?
[LUFFY]
Uh‐huh.
I was wondering if
there was any way
‐‐you could help us geta boat.
‐‐[KLAHADORE] You there!
What do you think you're doing?
Klahadore...
Get out!
I'll have you know that this
is criminal trespassing.
[USOPP gasps]
Hey guys, who's he?
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[NAMI] Who does that
butler think he is,
treating us like
bunch of thieves?!
[LUFFY] Yeah! We only
snuck in to get a ship!
[ZORO] Hate to break it to
you Nami, but we are thieves!
[NAMI] Well, that weird guy
is way more suspicious than us!
[ZORO]
Hm? What's with that ring?
[NAMI]
Hey, look! The butlers with him!
What's going on?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"The Weirdest Guy Ever!
Jango the Hypnotist!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!