Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless
array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary
treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use
any means necessary
to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy was sent flying
from the Sabaody Archipelago
by the Warlord of the Sea
known as Bartholomew Kuma.
I have my Vivre Card! Of course!
All right! Good thing
everyone got one, huh?
We'll be back
together in no time.
[NARRATOR] Alone and lost
on a strange island,
Luffy intended to use
his Vivre Card to
reunite with his crew
until curiosity got
the better of him.
[LUFFY] Hey, aren't
these Laughing Mushrooms?
[MARGARET]
Hurry! I can see the smoke.
It's right over there!
Rather puzzling, isn't it?
[NARRATOR] After eating
a parasitic mushroom,
Luffy passed out and was
carried to a nearby village
by a group of
mysterious women.
Hold on! What is this?
Is something wrong?
[SWEETPEA]
There's one between her legs
that we failed to catch.
How careless of us.
Huh. You're right,
but this one seems different
than the others, doesn't it?
It has such a strange shape.
It appears to be some
sort of sack mushroom!
[NYON]
Nyo my! What is this?
Is something wrong?
[MARGARET]
Oh, hello Granny Nyon!
There's a mushroom
growing on this girl
that won't come off,
no matter how hard we try!
Oh nyo!
[AMAZONS]
Huh?!
[NYON] This person
is a-- It's a man!
A man!
I've never seen a man before.
Whatever shall I do?
[LUFFY]
"Hurry Back to your friends!"
"The Maiden Island Adventure!"
[NARRATOR] This is the
all-female land of Amazon Lily
where men dare not tread.
On occasion, the
women who live here
will leave the island
and return with child,
but oddly enough, they only
seem to give birth to girls.
Here, a thick jungle
surrounds a mountain
that stretches
towards the sky.
Nestled inside
its rocky exterior
is a fortress-like village
that houses the entire nation.
[AMAZON]
Come on in, ladies!
Oh, wow. Cute ribbon!
I couldn't resist.
I bought a matching pair!
That was a real disaster.
[AMAZONS laughing]
Step right up!
We've got Sea King so
get it while it's fresh!
Now, that looks yummy!
And it'll make your
skin nice and soft, too!
Fresh picked fruit! From the
jungle, straight to you!
[NARRATOR]
Fun-loving and hard-working,
no job is too challenging
for these women.
Hey, lookie what I got!
That'll be perfect!
Just set it down right there!
[AMAZON 409J]
Sure thing!
[NARRATOR]
Raised from birth as warriors,
they are as brave and
adventurous as any man,
but have an undeniable
grace about them.
Their seclusion has also
given them an air of innocence.
Here in this paradise,
there is no need for men at all.
Because these women,
above all else, are strong.
[AMAZON ANNOUNCER]
Here are today's odds!
[AMAZON 409L]
A thousand Gol on Poppy!
[AMAZON 409M]
1,500 on Pansy!
[POPPY yells]
[ BOTH grunting]
[CROWD gasps]
[POPPY cackles]
[PANSY gasps]
[POPPY yells]
[PANSY groans]
[NARRATOR] In this land,
strength is beauty.
And tempting though
its lovely sights may be,
any man foolish enough
to gaze upon these warriors
will not live to tell the tale.
[SWEETPEA]
The man is awake!
[AMAZON PURPLE HAIR]
Let me see! Let me see!
[AMAZON MOHAWK]
Okay, we'll take turns!
[LUFFY yawns]
He's moving around!
Look at his chest!
It's so flat!
Awfully chiseled-looking,
isn't he?
Rather underwhelming, I'd say.
And his hair's so shaggy.
[AMAZON FLUFFY] It seems
like he was sleeping forever!
[AMAZON AUBURN HAIR]
But I heard he was eating
while he was asleep.
Is that a man thing?
[AMAZON GLASSES]
What is it that men eat, anyway?
Just raw meat?
[MARGARET] I get the feeling
this one will eat anything.
[LUFFY] What's goin' on?
It sure is noisy.
[AMAZON SHORTY]
Oh! He can talk!
Hey.
Hold on, where am I?
What the heck was I doing
before I passed out?
Oh, that's right.
We got split up and I
landed someplace weird.
[SWEETPEA]
What's that?
[AMAZON TWINTAILS] Whoa,
is he speaking our language?
Everyone! He's saying something!
[LUFFY] I remember
eating some mushrooms,
but after that-- Ah!
My hat's missing!
Hey! There it is!
Give it back, you jerk!
[AMAZONS scream]
[AMAZON HAIRCLIPS]
Weird! Our bodies can't do that!
Yeah. That's better!
Oh, wow!
That means men can
stretch their arms!
Interesting!
Very good. Most
intriguing, indeed!
Man, would you tell
us your name, please?
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Oh, I'm Luffy.
Whoa! That's weird! I'm naked!
[AMAZONS]
We know!
[LUFFY]
It's kind of breezy in here.
Anybody know
where my stuff went?
[AMAZON]
Men are slow-witted.
And they cover
their heads first,
even if their
bodies are exposed.
[MARGARET] Uhm, pardon me
for asking, but, uh...
Before you get dressed,
could you please tell us
what's in that little bag that's
in between your legs there?
[LUFFY]
Bag?
Come on, you don't
know what those are?
[LUFFY]
What a weirdo!
These are my family jewels.
[AMAZON]
They're jewels?
Jewels, huh?
Family jewels.
How fascinating!
[SWEETPEA]
Bizarre.
Interesting.
A bag of jewels!
[AMAZON 409N] I can't see
them! Scoot over, Margaret!
[MARGARET]
Oh, sorry!
[AMAZON 409O]
Your notebook's in the way!
[NERINE]
Oops.
So, what are these jewels?
It's my treasure!
That's why I always
gotta keep 'em safe!
[AMAZONS gasp and yell]
Treasure?
To think that men have
such an incredible secret.
[AMAZONS]
Family jewels!
I wish I had some too!
Then could you please
take them out?
We'd just like
to hold them for a second.
Are you nuts? You'll kill me!
Not a chance!
Might as well
get dressed, then!
Your clothes were all
torn when we found you,
so I made some new ones
that are just like them.
Wow. Hey, thanks a lot!
That was real nice.
And we don't even
know each other!
I made a few
improvements as well.
[LUFFY whimpering]
So flowery.
The vest says "I'm serious"
but the frills say "I'm cute!"
His enemies will shake
with fear and jealousy alike!
You're a genius, Margaret!
Aw, look, he's so
happy, he's shaking!
He's thanking you
on his hands and knees!
[LUFFY yelling]
What the hell is
wrong with you?
Are you trying to
make fun of me? Huh?
[KIKYO]
Prepare to attack!
[LUFFY]
Whoa, what?
[AMAZON STOCKY]
What a vicious temper!
He shows his true nature!
[AMAZON TALL]
You see, my sisters?
Even after we save
his life, he turns on us.
Growling and snapping
like the beast he is!
His temperament
is indeed savage!
His words and actions lack
any elegance whatsoever!
We are incompatible.
With him and every man!
Even so, Kikyo, his offense
towards us is truly minor.
We need not kill him!
Hey, before you
guys shoot me,
just a second ago you
said you saved my life.
[LUFFY]
What happened?
I don't even know!
You ate a bunch of
parasitic mushrooms
and collapsed, then
you were found
and brought here
by these ladies.
Okay. That's what happened.
In that case, thanks a lot.
Sorry for flipping out and
complaining about the clothes!
Just don't shoot me!
Your apologies are meaningless!
This is Amazon Lily,
female empire!
All men are forbidden!
And for centuries now, we have
upheld this absolute rule!
You shall die like every man
on this island before you.
All women, whoa.
No guys, huh?
[KIKYO] Now that we
know your true nature,
we have no sympathy for you!
Wow, you're right.
Now that I look,
you are all girls.
Man, what a crazy country.
And still you prattle on,
you ignorant worm.
Hey.
He's not so bad,
do we gotta kill him?
Aphelandra!
[KIKYO] The Snake Princess
will soon return.
How do you think she will feel?
She would never
approve of this situation!
You will also be
charged with the crime
of bringing a man
into the village!
[KIKYO]
Margaret.
Sweetpea.
Aphelandra.
I'm doing this
for your sake!
This incident must
be kept secret.
[LUFFY] Hold on a sec.
Can't you just let me go?
My friends, they're
waiting for me on Sabaody.
And I promised
I would meet them there!
Shoot him!
[AMAZONS yell]
[LUFFY yells]
Look up there! He broke
through the roof!
[KIKYO]
Don't let him escape!
[AMAZONS yelling]
Those girls are super
good at shooting arrows!
I gotta get away
from here, fast!
[LUFFY screaming]
My, my... he's a rather
nimble one, isn't he?
Aphelandra!
[APHELANDRA]
Got it!
Oh well, I tried
to save you.
[LUFFY yells]
[PORTLY AMAZON 409A]
He fell!
[PORTLY AMAZON 409B]
Now he's bouncing!
Huh-- so what
should I do now?
[KIKYO]
Damn it! After him!
Do not let him get away!
[PORTLY AMAZON 409A]
Over there!
[AMAZON 409G]
Only one cut of meat left
'til we're all sold out!
If you want it,
you better hurry up!
[AMAZON 409G] That doesn't
mean you get it for free!
[LUFFY]
I'll pay you later!
[KIKYO]
Enemy on the loose!
[AMAZONS gasp]
[KIKYO]
The man has escaped!
[AMAZON 409P]
My food disappeared!
[AMAZON 409Q]
What is that?
[AMAZON 409R]
He's over there!
[AMAZON 409S]
Hey, my food's gone, too!
[AMAZONS panting]
[AMAZON 409U]
Strike him down!
[AMAZON 409V]
You can't run forever!
There weren't this
many a second ago!
[AMAZONS]
Get back here!
I shall apprehend him!
Toss me!
Okay!
Halt, you villain!
My... he's so limber!
I'm unable to stop!
Sweetpea, no!
[KIKYO]
That's far enough!
There's nowhere to run.
[LUFFY] You guys really
wanna kill me, huh?
Oh, I almost forgot!
Where's my Vivre Card?
[grunting]
I had it in the pocket of
my pants before I lost them.
So, let's see.
There she is! Perfect!
[yells]
We can't talk in this crowd.
I'm sorry, but there's
something I gotta ask you!
[MARGARET]
Let me go! Help!
[KIKYO] That fiend! What does
he want with Margaret?
[MARGARET screaming]
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Balloon!
[LUFFY] Hey. Are you
all right over there?
[MARGARET]
Stay away from me!
How, how did you turn fat?
[MARGARET]
Are you out of your mind?
Jumping from all
the way up there...
You men are monsters!
I don't know what you did
or what you were thinking,
but it's a miracle
that we're still alive!
Oh yeah?
[MARGARET]
Stay back!
I'm not gonna do anything.
[MARGARET]
I've heard it said that all men
have some sort of
dangerous cootie virus!
Is that what caused you to
grow so fat all of a sudden?
[LUFFY]
I hate to break it to you,
but I don't think
cooties are real
and the fat thing
is kind of hard to explain,
so let's just say that
yeah, all guys turn fat.
Anyway, there was
something I left
in the pocket of
my old pair of pants.
Do you still have it?
'Cuz it's super
important to me.
Uh. Let me see.
Is this what you mean?
[LUFFY]
Yes! Yes! Man, I was so worried!
I dunno what I would've
done if I'd lost it!
Thank you! You're
a real lifesaver!
Get your hands off me!
Stay put! You're mine!
Something was written on it,
so I kept it just in case.
So, what is it for?
[LUFFY]
Here, look!
How unusual! It looks
like it's moving!
A bunch of stuff happened,
and then all my
friends went flying
through the air
in different directions.
But now, with this
piece of paper,
I can find my way back
to them, wherever they go.
Heh, they're strong,
so I'm not worried.
Anyway, guess I should pay
you back for all your help.
If there's anything
I can do for you, just ask.
Oh, there is!
Could you take out your family
jewels so I can see them?
That's not even funny!
You're gonna kill me!
[MARGARET] Hmph. Men are
savages and cheapskates!
[LUFFY]
Just put the sword down
and leave my jewels
alone, please!
These friends of yours,
who are they exactly?
Oh.
Well, we're all
a pirate crew.
Do you know what
pirates are here?
Yes, of course I know.
In fact, the empress of this
country is a pirate as well.
Whoa, really?
So, you guys have like
an all-girl pirate crew?
Are they strong?
[MARGARET]
What a foolish question!
Only the most elite
warriors are allowed
to ride aboard the pirate
ship of our empress!
So yes, of course
they're strong!
In this proud nation,
all of the women look up
to the Snake Princess!
Her beauty is unparalleled.
She's strong and noble.
She's called the
"Pirate Empress."
Boa Hancock!
She and her sisters are the
protectors of this island.
And, well, truth be told,
they're our heroes.
[AMAZON whimpers]
[AMAZON 409BB] Oh no!
The ship of the Snake Princess
is nearly here!
[AMAZON 409CC]
Huh?
[bell ringing]
Curses. This isn't good!
We must deal
with the man quickly!
[panting]
Kikyo, he jumped over
the wall and disappeared.
What should we do now?
[KIKYO]
Warriors! To the jungle!
We will rescue Margaret.
Then put the man to death!
The Snake Princess
has returned!
[NARRATOR]
Navy Vice-Admiral Momonga
contacts the Kuja Pirates
with an official
summons for Boa Hancock.
However, despite being one
of the Warlords of the Sea,
Hancock refuses the Navy's
request and unleashes
her Devil Fruit power on
the unsuspecting marines!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Everyone Falls in Love!
Pirate Empress Hancock!."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!