Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Hey, look down there!
Someone else came
out of the building
and it looks like
Chef Curly Brows!
Damn it!
I failed her.
[LUFFY]
Moria!
Get back here!
Are you running from
your shadow or chasing me?
Giant monster me
is gonna be a problem,
but if I wanna get
everyone's shadows back,
then I guess I'm gonna have
to beat you anyway, aren't I?
So get back here!
Too bad!
But it looks like the
last laugh belongs to me!
She's still out cold.
I'll take her someplace safe.
Don't you worry!
It may be in private,
but we'll have our wedding yet.
My sleeping beauty.
That is not good!
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
Hey, Robin! Chopper!
We're in trouble here!
Big trouble!
The... the Luffy Zombie
has our faces.
No wait, I mean, on his arm!
He has our wanted posters!
What do we do now?
Aw man. This is no joke!
He's gonna hunt us down!
Show yourselves!
Come out, Straw Hats,
you can't hide from me!
C'mon Captain,
you're not gonna tear apart
your own crew, are you?
It seems he's
been given the order.
I just hope the
real Luffy is all right.
Don't eat me, I'm all bones!
Are we supposed
to fight that damn thing?
No way.
[LUFFY]
"Luffy is the Enemy!
The Ultimate Zombie
Vs. the Straw Hat Crew!"
Wh-Wh-what is that
thing? It's terrifying.
Of course it is.
It's a monster, after all.
Wait, is that...
[ZORO]
Hey! Usopp!
Is that you down there?
You hear that? What the--
Someone just yelled my name.
[USOPP]
Zoro!
What're you doing up there?
There's Franky, too!
And look, Brook is
with them, they're all safe!
[ROBIN]
For now.
It looks like they managed to
save the skeleton
in time, at least.
Nami, on the other hand,
I'm still pretty worried about.
Hey. You're standing
in my damn way.
And what're you
doing interfering?
What's gotten into you, Luffy?
[OARS]
Luffy?
I think I'm supposed
to crush that guy.
He's my enemy.
My name's Oars.
Hello there.
Really?
What's with the introductions?
Idiot.
He just says
whatever he wants, huh?
He definitely takes after Luffy.
Look at this.
That moron's picking
a fight with the monster.
That damn stupid cook.
Has he even rescued Nami yet?
Probably not.
I think he's in worse
trouble than she is now.
[CHOPPER]
This is bad. This is really bad!
Sanji's in trouble!
This is unexpected.
I was under the impression
that all they wanted from us
were our shadows.
But he looks more
primed for violence.
I guess they
decided they already got
the cream of the crop
with Luffy's shadow.
Scary. It's scary!
No way we can fight that thing!
Well I can't just stand back
and watch Sanji get slaughtered.
[USOPP]
Whoa, hold it!
Listen, we're just
gonna get ourselves killed
if we all try to get involved.
Sanji can handle
this guy on his own.
And don't worry.
He's got a better
chance than any of us
at getting out of this alive.
How? His face is on a
wanted poster too, right?
I don't see how his
situation is any better
than the one we're in here.
And that's exactly
where you're wrong!
You're not
thinking clearly, Robin.
You've seen his
wanted poster, haven't you?
There's no way he'll
realize that's Sanji.
[CHOPPER]
That's true!
Sanji's wanted poster
doesn't look anything like him!
[ROBIN]
You've got a point.
I'd forgotten about that.
You look justa same
as your wanted poster.
--What?
That drawing
looks nothing like me!
What do you mean? It's so good.
Are your eyes rotting? Idiot!
But you admit you're
part of the pirate crew, huh?
[SANJI]
Yeah, what of it?
Then you're dead.
Oh, crap! Oh, crap!
Oh no! Sanji!
Wanna try me? Then bring it on.
Wait!
Moria!
Kushishishi!
Quit laughing!
Dammit! Stupid shadow guy!
Come and get me, Straw Hat. Huh?
Well, I'll be.
Who put this dead end here?
I finally caught up with you.
Prepare yourself
for an ass kicking.
I think you're the one
who needs to prepare himself.
Did it occur to you
that I'm keeping you busy
chasing after me?
All while your
entire crew gets slaughtered
by your own shadow?
Jackass!
Kushishishi!
[LUFFY]
Shut up!
My crew doesn't need me to
fight their fights for them.
Ya think so?
Then we might as
well keep this little
cat and mouse charade of ours
going a while longer.
Brick Bat attack!
[LUFFY]
Dammit!
[MORIA]
Come find me when you're done.
[LUFFY]
Gum Gum Gatling!
Get back here, you fat onion!
Master Moria! Where are you?
Everything's destroyed!
[HILDON]
Master Moria! It's really bad!
What are those guys doing?
How dare you!
You fugly faced penguin!
You're the one with
the fugly face, old man!
Cut it out, you guys!
This is not the time for you
two to be fighting each other!
And how are you even fighting,
did someone command you to?
It was an order
from Hogback himself!
Yeah, now beat it,
ya crappy bat!
Really?
I'm having trouble believing
he would give you an order
to fight each other.
What exactly did he say
when he told you to do this?
--He said kill the others!
[JIGORO]
Now you're gonna die!
[DOGGUIN] Stop getting
in the way of my orders,
you wrinkled old husk!
--Oh, fine, whatever.
[JIGORO]
Stop not dying!
Crap.
He really did a number on me.
Well too bad, you bastard.
You were tough.
But you still
couldn't put me down.
I've been waiting so long
for this blessed ritual
to bind our souls.
Well then.
Let's continue
with the ceremony.
You may kiss the bride.
[ABSALOM thinking]
Finally! It's happening!
Perfect, I found Absalom!
Thank goodness!
If anyone can tell me where to
find Master Moria, it's Absalom!
[ABSALOM]
Here I come, my love!
Absalom!
What the hell is wrong with you?
You perverted degenerate!
He said it!
He said it right to his face!
Oh, no! He's gonna kill us all!
[ABSALOM] Hildon!
Are you blind, you idiot?
What's so damn
important, anyway?
Huh?
He's gonna let that slide?
Uh...
I'm trying to find Moria and
thought he might be with you.
Is something
wrong with your eyes?
You see any fatties in here?
[HILDON]
No, no, I guess not.
[ABSALOM] Well if that's all
you need, can you get a move on?
In case you didn't notice,
I'm sort of busy right now.
[HILDON]
Right. Sorry. I'm off!
One more thing. Hildon.
Sure, what is it?
How dare you call me
a perverted degenerate!
That was a jerk move.
--Now he gets pissed off?
[MORIA]
Kushishishi!
Quit running!
Fight me, you coward!
Kushishishi!
Who was that?
You! Stupid shadow guy!
Stop running! Moria!
My body was not
built for this much flying.
It's him!
I finally found him!
Master Moria!
I've been frantically looking
for you all over Thriller Bark!
What d'ya want,
Hildon? What's up?
It's awful!
That giant zombie's
out of control
and destroying
everything in his path!
He'll sink the island
if he's not stopped!
Ya don't say.
I guess you better hop to
and do something about it.
Don't worry, I'm sure
you can handle it. Later!
Master! Hold on!
Get outta the way!
Move it, move it!
Stay still, let me squash you!
Sanji, no!
[BROOK]
Is he an idiot?
Sanji!
[SANJI]
You punk.
Ya almost broke
my damn cigarette.
Alright, ya got your shot in.
Now it's my turn.
Sanji's okay!
I thought he was done for!
I'm not finished yet,
ya twerp.
[OARS]
Gum-Gum...
It's Luffy's move!
Oh, crap! Can he stretch?
Did he get Luffy's
rubber powers with his shadow?
...Sickle!
Okay, he didn't stretch,
but does it really matter?
With that strength and
with as long as his reach is,
it's basically the same thing!
He may look like a brute,
but he's got the
speed to back it up.
We better stay out of his way.
It's lights out if he hits us.
[BROOK]
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oars.
I knew I recognized that name.
It's him.
The demon from the legends, once
known as the "Continent Puller."
Alright.
I've gotta admit Luffy's zombie
is kind of a bad ass.
Collier Frit!
Sanji!
How can something
that big move that fast?
No more fancy footwork
for you, ya pipsqueak.
Oh, crap! He's got him now!
Sanji!
[FRANKY] What the hell's
he gonna do to him?
No! Stop it!
Sanji, look out!
Alright, pirate! Squishin' time!
[USOPP]
Fire Bird Star!
[OARS]
Hot.
Ah, I'm... I'm sorry!
Sanji, no!
[OARS]
Tall woman with black hair.
And that's the
little fuzzy thing.
--No, he's coming!
[ZORO]
This is bad!
Franky, we gotta do somethin',
draw him this way!
I'm on it!
I think this'll
get his attention!
[FRANKY]
Hang on! I got ya!
You guys get down
to the lower roof, fast!
One Gorilla!
Two Gorilla!
Three Sword Style!
Double Gorilla Split!
Now Gum-Gum...
...Volcano!
Zoro! Holy crap!
What do we do?
Even if that
punch didn't kill him,
there's no way he can survive
falling from that height!
C'mon, c'mon.
[FRANKY]
Take this, you monster!
Weapons Left!
He dodged it again!
How can he be that agile?
What's he doing now?
Franky, no! Skeleton guy!
Zoro's falling towards us!
Oh, crap!
He'll die if he hits the ground!
Cien Fleurs! And Spider Net!
I owe ya one, Robin.
Dammit.
[USOPP]
You might be huge,
but you're still a zombie!
Special Attack: Salt Star!
Taste good?
It wasn't...
It wasn't enough!
He's too big!
Now Heavy Gong!
Luffy.
You jerk.
[OARS] I don't know you.
My name's not Luffy.
'Member? Moria's servant.
Name's Oars.
[LOLA] Absalover? Forget
about that woman and kiss me!
[ABSALOM]
I'll never kiss you!
[LOLA]
Then marry me!!
[ABSALOM]
Not happening!!
[LOLA]
Then kiss me!!
[ABSALOM]
Are you even listening to me?
[LOLA]
You just don't get it, do you?
[ABSALOM]
You're the one who doesn't...
Aw, crap! You woke her up!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"You're Going Down, Absalom!!
Nami's Lightning
Attack of Friendship!!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!