[NARRATOR] Spring has finally
arrived in Grand Jipang.
It's said that in spring,
one can sleep
right through sunrise.
If that was so, you'd
think the townspeople
must be taking it easy, but
that's not really the case.
Tomorrow's the big day!
And this is just the
perfect weather for it!
Yeah.
This is gonna be great!
[TOWNSWOMAN A]
On my way here,
I stopped by
Pinwheel and put in
my family's order
for bento lunches!
Sounds like it'll
be a nice afternoon!
[NARRATOR] And this is
what the townspeople
are so excited about.
Each year, a festival is
held under the branches
of this gigantic
millennium sakura tree.
Its gorgeous blossoms are
the pride of Grand Jipang,
and everyone in town
comes to see them.
I'm sure they'll be happy
to share some food with me.
[NARRATOR] With a
celebration like that,
even a hungry monk
finds it hard to stay away.
[ZORO]
Shut your mouth.
[NARRATOR]
Anyway,
even during the festival,
there are those who have more
pressing matters to tend to.
[LUFFY] "Influenza"?
What the heck is that?
More commonly
known as "the flu",
tt's a type of
infectious disease.
[CHOPPER]
It's contagious,
so he shouldn't leave the house.
And he needs lots of rest.
--What?
But he can't!
We're all supposed to go to
the sakura festival tomorrow!
That's impossible!
If he does that,
his condition will worsen.
There's a chance
he could even die!
How awful.
Carrot was really looking
forward to it this year, too.
Sensei, can't you
do anything for him?
You're a doctor!
Be that as it may,
even a doctor has
things they can do
and things they can't.
[CARROT]
I'm sorry, guys.
[coughing]
It's my fault that
I got sick, okay?
No reason to blame
Blue Nose sensei.
Look, don't worry about me.
There's always next year, right?
Just go to the
festival without me.
[USOPP] Everybody
keeps going on and on
about the sakura festival.
It's so annoying!
Come on!
Don't talk like that!
Thanks to that festival,
we have a ton of bento
lunch orders coming in.
That sakura tree is
a blessing for us!
She's right, you know.
Speak for yourself--
it's a curse for me!
While everyone else
is out having fun,
I'm stuck patrolling the city!
It's nothing but a
nuisance, I tell you!
That's ridiculous!
The whole town will be empty.
What on earth are
you patrolling for?
You should just take it easy!
Isn't that right?
[LUFFY] This sucks!
Isn't there something we can do?
[CHOPPER]
Not really.
I wish there was
some way I could show him
the millennium
sakura tree blooming.
And I wish
there was some way
I could heal him
so he could just go.
Hey! What's up
with those two?
[USOPP] Beats me, but
they've been like this all day.
No matter
how I look at it,
I can't think of one
single thing I can do.
[CHOPPER]
Me neither.
Hey, wait a minute!
Where are you going?
[LUFFY] See ya later,
Blue Nose sensei.
[CHOPPER]
Yeah. See ya.
What's the deal?
It's not like them at all to
act like that at festival time.
Boss didn't even
finish his food!
[NARRATOR]
And, after a restful evening,
the day of the sakura blossom
blooming festival
finally arrived!
I made you medicine, Carrot.
[USOPP]
What the hell is this?
The sakura tree!
It vanished without a trace!
It's a mystery, I tell you.
How and why would anyone
steal something that massive?
Good point!
Pulling off a stunt like
this is less about money
and more about power.
Knowing that, my detective
skills are telling me...
...the culprit
must be our lord!
Not Cobra-sama!
Yeah.
He wanted that
tree all for himself,
so he and some of
his men came down here
in the middle of the night,
carefully dug it up, and--
Idiot! Why the hell would our
lord do something like that?
Serves me right.
Don't know why I asked
you in the first place.
Where's Straw Hat?
We've got an emergency here!
Well, I went looking for him,
but couldn't find him anywhere!
But I'm sure he'll
be here real soon.
[LUFFY] I wish
there was some way
I could show him the millennium
sakura tree blooming.
[USOPP]
The millennium sakura tree.
No, he couldn't have!
Hey! Have you guys
seen the Boss around?
Whoa. What the--?
What's going on here?
[SANJI] Well, since the
sakura tree's gone missing,
everybody cancelled
their bento lunch order.
[NAMI] Thanks to
that no-good tree thief,
we're going to take
a huge loss on this!
Pinwheel is done for!
Whoa. Sorry to hear that.
Hey! Hey! Come here!
What is it?
Well, see...
[whispering]
So Boss is the
sakura tree thief?
Shh!
I don't have any proof--
it's just a hunch.
Do you remember what
he said yesterday?
Yeah, it was
something about wanting
to show the sakura
tree to someone.
Right! Exactly!
And I haven't seen
him all morning.
When you put everything
together, it all adds up.
[NAMI] Who did you say
the tree thief was?
That little Straw Hat bastard!
Wait! Like I was saying,
it's just a hunch, so--
[NAMI] Enough! It doesn't
matter who did it!
Just find them and
arrest them already!
This criminal must
be brought to justice
so we can resume the festival
and sell off every last
bento lunch in Pinwheel!
Now get going!
[USOPP and SANJI]
Yes ma'am!
[USOPP]
So, you find him?
[SANJI]
Nope. No luck.
[USOPP] Did you check
Blue Nose sensei's place?
[SANJI]
Not yet.
But somebody told me
they saw the good doctor
headed over to
Carrot's house earlier,
so I'm on my way there
now to check it out.
At Carrot's house, huh?
[SANJI] Yeah.
Not only that, they
said he was muttering
about the sakura
blossoms as he walked by.
I don't like it.
♪ [LUFFY (SINGING)]
Sakura! Dun-dun-dun! ♪
♪ Sakura! Dun-dun-dun! ♪
♪ Blossoms drifting
in the spring sky! ♪
♪ Dun-dun-dun!
As far as the eye can see! ♪
♪ Dun-dun-dun! Hazy like a-- ♪
[LUFFY]
Hey! What's up?
What are you two doing here?
Don't "what are you
two doing here" me!
Explain yourself!
Where did you get that
sakura branch, Boss?
This?
Enough already!
What did you do with the
millennium sakura tree?
What do you mean
"what did I do with it"?
You just don't know
when to quit, do you?
Are you trying to say that
despite having that branch,
you don't know anything
about the missing sakura tree?
Hold on a sec!
Did you say the tree's missing?
[USOPP] Oh, come on!
Fess up, will you?
We can still try to
sort this out. Trust me!
[LUFFY] I don't know
what you're talking about.
I found this on the ground
and thought it'd be nice
to show it to Carrot!
I'm sick and tired of your lies!
Now tell me what
you did with it!
[RIKA] It was me!
I put it by the door
where he could find it!
Ha, I knew it!
You found it on the ground
by the door where--Orika?
I'm so sorry!
[RIKA] After hearing
what Blue Nose sensei said,
we really wanted
to find some way
to show Carrot
the sakura blooms.
So Pepper, Onion,
and I went to the tree
in the middle of the night
to see what we
could come up with.
[RIKA]
Are you guys okay?
[PEPPER] We're fine!
Really! No need to worry!
[PEPPER] Look!
That one's perfect!
I'm sorry.
Please allow us this one
branch to show our friend.
Somebody's coming!
Come on, you guys!
We gotta get out of here!
We can't!
There's no time!
Take that branch
and go on without us!
I won't leave without you!
We'll be fine!
As soon as they're gone,
we'll climb down and come home.
Just leave the branch
in front of Carrot's doorway.
Don't let anyone see you!
Uh, okay.
[PEPPER]
Hurry!
[SANJI]
I see.
So after that, you
brought the branch here
and left it where
Carrot could find it?
Yeah. Sorry.
[USOPP]
Hold on. Wait a sec.
Does that mean that the culprits
that stole the sakura tree are--
No way it was
Pepper and Onion,
and it wasn't me, either.
So the true
thieves are the ones
that arrived after
Orika ran away.
Oh, no! This is terrible, Boss!
--[LUFFY] Hm?
--[SANJI] Before we came here,
I stopped by to check in
on Pepper and Onion,
and neither of them were home!
There's only one
place they could be.
Wait! Are you saying--
[CARROT]
Boss!
[USOPP]
Don't worry!
We'll take it from here!
Orika, keep an eye
on Carrot, okay?
[RIKA]
Right!
[LUFFY]
Oh! Blue Nose sensei!
Take good care of Carrot!
What's going on?
[USOPP]
Thank goodness!
He's still sick, so check
in on him, please! See ya!
Sure! Bye!
Hey, Boss!
Couldn't all the information
in that letter that was
on the arrow be fake?
No way! It's the truth,
I just know it!
Hurry! We gotta
get to the harbor!
What's gonna happen to us now?
I don't know!
[BUGGY] So. What do you
think, my foreign brother?
I bet you've never seen such
an amazing sakura
tree in all your life!
A world traveler and
gatherer of rare items
such as yourself should be eager
to add it to his collection.
Wouldn't you agree,
Silver Fox Foxy?
[FOXY laughs]
[FOXY]
Indeed, brother Buggy.
This beautiful specimen
will be a magnificent addition.
I'm sure my dear Porche will
be ever so pleased with it,
as well.
Then I suppose we should
finalize this transaction.
[laughing maniacally]
With the money from this,
all of my magnificent plans
will finally be able
to come to fruition!
Now. How about you give me
the 10 million Ryo-Berries
you promised me.
[FOXY]
Oh, I don't have any money.
You what?!
D-d-d-don't h-h-have
a-a-a-any m-m-money?!
What the hell are
you trying to pull?
Do you have the
slightest idea how much
of a pain in the ass it
was to get this thing here?
You were lying to me from
the beginning, weren't you?
I bet you're flat broke,
you bastard!
[FOXY] No, no.
I've got plenty of money.
I'm what you
would call "loaded".
And if I sell this tree
to another country,
I'll be even more so.
See how that works?
What I meant to say
is I don't have
any money for an
overdressed clown like you.
[BUGGY] How dare you
mock me so flashily!
This was a lot of
trouble, damn it!
Prepare a Buggy Ball, men!
We're gonna blow him away!
[BUGGY PIRATES]
We're way ahead of you, Boss!
You're gonna regret that.
[laughing]
Hey! That's--
You're the one
that sent this, right?
Thanks a lot!
Where's the sakura tree?
[ROBIN] It's on the far side
of that island over there.
It appears to be onboard a ship.
It's such a
beautiful specimen.
They're probably
planning to sell it
to some other country,
far away from here.
[ROBIN] Fortunately,
there's a ferry available.
You should hurry
before it's too late.
That island's being developed
by the government
so people can live on it,
but it's still
deserted right now.
It'd be a pretty
inconspicuous place to do
some dirty business without
being seen by anyone.
We should get over
there and check it out.
Thanks again for the--
Where'd she go?
[USOPP]
Whoa! She's gone!
At least she helped us out
before she disappeared.
Whatever. Let's get going!
Hey! Wait up, Boss!
She's so beautiful.
You bastard!
[FOXY laughing]
[FOXY] Behold the
magnificent power
of the Slow-Slow fruit!
I bet you fools never
thought you'd meet
your demise in such a
fabulous way, did you?
But you won't die yet.
The effects'll last
another thirty seconds.
Still, no sense in wasting
that cannonball of
yours, now, is there?
Why don't we find you a
better seat for the show?
Yeah. Right over here.
[BUGGY]
How dare y--
[distant crash]
Whoa! What's that?
Looks like something blew up!
I sure hope Onion and
Pepper are okay over there.
[LUFFY] Thanks, Pops!
I think we can go the
rest of the way on our own!
[PAGAYA]
Oh? All right, then.
I'm sorry for not taking
you all the way across.
Very sorry, indeed.
[FOXY laughing]
So tell me.
How does it feel to get blown up
by your own men's attack, eh?
[BUGGY]
It hurts like hell!
I'm not gonna let you
get away with this!
Get him, boys!
Fools! Slow-Slow Beam!
No! Boss Buggy!
[ALL screaming]
Whew!
Wasn't expecting that!
[SANJI]
Hey, Usopp, you okay?
It's Boss!
What the hell? Hey!
What's your problem, damn it?
[LUFFY]
The sakura tree!
That must make
you the tree thief!
How dare you!
You come in from out of
nowhere, destroy my ship,
and then have the nerve
to throw around
accusations like that?
Who are you?
I'm Straw Hat Luffy,
a policeman.
And I'm tired of your
sakura-stealing mouth!
You're under arrest, split-head!
[FOXY]
Split-head?
[SANJI]
Wow, he's really depressed.
This guy's got issues.
More importantly, Boss,
I see a familiar face
up there on deck.
[LUFFY] Buggy!
You just never learn!
[LUFFY] Gimme back
that sakura tree!
[LUFFY]
What the heck?
Whoa, that's weird.
What's he doing?
Not much of anything!
He's been slowed down by the
power of my Slow-Slow Beam!
You need to be careful, Boss!
This guy's got
some strange powers!
Pepper! Onion!
What's with him?
He just now felt that punch?
[FOXY] You're about
to suffer the same fate!
[FOXY] They call me
Silver Fox Foxy.
I'm a man who obtains
everything he desires.
And no lowly, nosy, policeman
is going to stand in my way!
Slow-Slow Beam!
--Boss, no!
[laughing]
Listen kiddo, I don't care
if you're the law around here
or not!
You're about a
thousand years too early
to go up against
the likes of me!
[FOXY] And it seems
like you've brought
some annoying little
friends with you, too.
Oh well, nothing I can't
fix with a few cannonballs.
Not if I can help it!
Poor Boss!
[ZORO] Hey!
Keep it down, will ya?
What a pain. I'm trying
to get some sleep here!
[ONION and PEPPER]
It's the monk!
[ZORO]
Is it morning already?
Wait! Oh, yeah! Today's
the big sakura festival!
Hey! Where the hell am I?
What's going on?
Why're you up there, anyway?
Someone stole the
sakura tree last night
and us along with it!
There's not gonna
be a festival now!
Oh yeah?
Who did that? Tell me!
Give back the tree, you bastard!
[FOXY]
No way!
He stopped him in mid-air?
[USOPP]
Dammit!
Special Attack...
Exploding Star!
Nope!
What is this?
[ZORO]
So it was you.
How am I supposed
to get my free food
if there's no festival?
One fool after another!
Well, I've had enough!
Funny, I was about
to tell you the same thing!
Now Gum-Gum--
Huh? 30 seconds already?
Now you're gonna pay.
You're dead!
[FOXY]
Double Slow-Slow Beam!
Chop-Chop Festival! Haha!
[FOXY] He deflected
it with his sword?
[LUFFY] You tried to
steal away everyone's fun!
I'm never gonna
forgive you for this!
I'm the one who's
never gonna forgive you!
Don't think this is over!
You're right. It's not.
It'll be back in just a second.
Oh? What will?
[LUFFY]
My right hand.
Billy Club!
[FOXY screaming]
You really sent
him flying, huh?
By the way.
What should we do about him?
[LUFFY] You've gotta be the
dumbest guy in the world.
Just give the crazy
plans a rest already.
Looks like you'll be
missing the festival this year.
Gum-Gum--
Billy Club Bodhisattva!
There.
Let's head back to town.
[SANJI]
Sounds good.
[LUFFY]
You coming, too, Monk?
[ZORO]
Sure.
[BUGGY] Thank you
for all your hard work!
[CHOPPER]
I don't understand.
Theoretically, that
should have healed him.
[LUFFY]
Carrot! Carrot!
Hey, Carrot! Hey!
Look!
We found the
millennium sakura tree!
Hey, Carrot!
Hope this'll make
you feel better!
Get well soon
so we can go play!
You dummies.
Worrying about me like that.
[RIKA laughing]
Thanks so much!
[USOPP] Come on!
Over here! A little closer!
Thank you, guys!
I'm feeling better already!
[CHOPPER] Whoa.
He is feeling better!
Did my medicine
finally start working?
[laughing]
[CHOPPER]
No.
I think it was a different
kind of medicine.
[LUCCI]
After all that talk,
I was expecting an opponent
with a little more backbone.
How disappointing.
Did you run out of strength
after that last attack?
[LUFFY] If it's
backbone you want,
wait'll you get a
load of my next move!
It's time to end this!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"I Can't Protect
Anyone Unless I Win!
Third Gear Activated!"