Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] With a mighty "C"
emblazoned on his cape.
Who is this tiny hero
who protects the
peace of this world?
Why, Chopperman, of course!
[CHOPPER]
Chopperman to the Rescue!
Protect the TV Station
by the Shore!
[USOPP] What's so great
about that pipsqueak, anyway?
If he was a real hero,
he would see how brilliant I am
and let me take over
the World Government!
[NARRATOR]
Evil Incarnate, Dr. Usodaba.
This mad scientist
is always plotting
to rule the world
with an iron fist,
a wicked mustache
and the power of his
underground organization.
Though if my minions
would do their jobs properly,
maybe this wouldn't
be a problem!
Yes, I'm talking about you,
you freeloaders!
Huh?
[NARRATOR]
The naughty monster, Sanjiropus!
He insists that
he isn't naughty,
but is always thinking
about naughty stuff!
I'm always
a perfect gentleman.
[ZORO] Yeah, right.
[NARRATOR] Mysterious
Rice Ball Monster, Zorokiller.
[NARRATOR] He loves rice balls!
If you don't have rice balls for
him, he'll never forgive you!
That's right, I won't!
Would you good-for-nothings
stop sitting there
and start taking over
the world for me?
More tea.
Sure! Right away!
Hey, you can't boss your
boss around like that!
Now pour me a cup.
[USOPP] I may be evil, but I
need love just like anyone else.
How can I find minions
that are evil in a good way
instead of evil in a mean way?
[SHOUPAN] Be a star in
our new singing competition!
Show the whole world
your hidden talent on live TV
to win fame and fortune!
[USOPP] That's it!
Soon the whole
world will love me!
[laughing evilly]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
at Chopperman's secret base,
somewhere secret
that we can't tell you...
You wanna do this
the hard way?
Huh? Spit it out already!
[NARRATOR] Chopperman's
lovely assistant, Namifia.
She's in charge of
assigning missions to our hero
to make sure that he
doesn't watch TV all day.
If you don't ring,
I'll wring your neck!
I mean, please,
Mr. Transponder Snail!
I'm begging you!
We won't be able to
pay bills this month!
Who am I kidding?
I guess our only option is
to cut the snack allowance.
[CHOPPER laughing]
A polar bear, huh?
Panda.
[CHOPPER laughing]
Hey, Namifia.
I'm out of potato chips.
Would you mind getting
another bag for me, please?
[NARRATOR]
Champion of Justice, Chopperman.
He's a hero that protects
the peace of the world.
What did you expect?
That really hurt!
Why are you so mean to me?
This is no time to sit idly by,
watching TV and
eating potato chips!
It's a tragedy!
The world is at peace
and all the bad guys
are taking a day off!
Yeah, but isn't
that a good thing?
Not for us, it isn't!
If people don't call in
asking us for help,
then how in the heck are we
supposed to make any money?
Who cares how much cash
we have in the bank?
You can't put a price tag
on world peace!
But you can put a
price on potato chips,
which we can no longer afford.
No, I'm sorry!
Hm?
Next, we'll cover
local news stories.
Maybe we'll be lucky
and something really terrible
is going on right now.
Like a giant robot
going on a rampage,
or an army of space lizards
kidnapping the mayor.
[CHOPPER]
Hey! Gimme back the remote!
Not a chance.
[CHOPPER] But I wanna
watch my comedy shows!
--Pretty pretty please?
--No way.
[SHOUPAN] Yeek!
[USOPP laughing evilly]
Good evening ladies and gents!
There has been a
small change of program.
--It's Usodaba!
In case you haven't noticed,
my Evil Organization has taken
over your beloved TV station!
Sweet! Just what we needed!
[CHOPPER]
Did he get his own TV show?
As you might suspect,
this is part of one
of my genius schemes
to take over
the World Government!
Don't change the channel,
because I'm going to
give you every gory detail!
In order for the Usodaba
Gang to tighten its iron grip,
we are now taking
applications for new employees,
open to everyone free of charge,
for a limited time!
--Huh?
[USOPP] No pesky job interview!
No background check, either!
As an added bonus,
our first applicant will receive
a very special,
one of kind treasure
from my own personal collection!
[USOPP] It's fast! It's strong!
But it's still just a model,
so no, you can't ride it.
It's the awesome, super-rare,
Air Force C-Max Limited Edition
Pre-Painted Red Color Version!
I do hate to see it go,
seeing as I had to wait in line
a week in the freezing cold,
sleeping on the street
and peeing in a bucket,
but for my minions,
no cost is too great!
The Air Force
C-Max Limited Edition?
No way!
The phone lines
will be opening shortly,
so I look forward to seeing
you all in the Usodaba Gang!
This looks like serious trouble!
Chopperman, are you ready to go?
Yeah!
[NAMI]
You know what your mission is?
Of course I do!
I have to hurry so I can
get the Air Force C-Max!
You've gotta be kidding me!
[CHOPPER] Sorry, can't hear you!
Joining the bad guys!
I think I need to
find a new line of work.
Wait a sec!
The Giant Luffy Bomber!
All I have to do is use that!
It's gone!
Oh, I forgot.
I sold it to get
all these fabulous rings.
[USOPP laughing evilly]
[USOPP]
What do you think, Robiflowern?
I bet I made all the
ladies weak in the knees
in my first big TV appearance.
I wouldn't know.
I wasn't paying attention.
[NARRATOR]
Flower Monster, Robiflowern.
[NARRATOR] An evil
creature whose wickedness
can only be stopped by
Chopperman's Secret Technique.
The Cute Spark!
So what do you think, guys?
Is your boss
pretty awesome or what?
[SANJI] Huh?
When I get new minions,
you guys are totally fired!
More tea.
Sure! Right away!
Hey, you can't boss
your boss around like that!
Now pour me a cup.
[USOPP] Fine. Be jerks.
Soon enough I'll have
a whole army of admirers.
[MINIONS] We love you, Usodaba!
You're a genius, Usodaba!
Here's your tea, Usodaba!
[ROBIN] I admit, taking over
a TV station was a good idea,
even if you came up with it.
Could you tone down
the contempt a little bit?
Everyone and their dog knows
my plans are always perfect!
Soon, all the
people tuning in at home
will see how awesome and
powerful the Usodaba Gang is!
Then a whole sea
of new applicants
will come clamoring
over each other
for a chance to kiss my feet.
With my army of adoring fans,
taking over the World
Government will be easy!
And I can finally show
those ingrates the door.
Now that you have the station,
what kind of show
are you going to make?
I'm glad you asked, my dear.
[USOPP] I'll steal their hearts
with the sound
of my sweet singing voice!
[SANJI] Not so fast!
Better leave this to me!
I have the face for TV,
and I'm sure all the lovely
ladies sitting at home watching
would agree with me.
Don't you think so,
too, Robiflowern?
[ROBIN] Sure.
I just hope you
won't mind sharing me
with my inevitable
legion of fangirls.
[ROBIN] I don't know about him.
[USOPP] Let him do
what he wants, Robiflowern.
Arguing with him
is a waste of time.
I need you on the phones,
'cause when those calls
start pouring in,
you're going to need all six
of those arms to answer them!
[ROBIN] Understood.
[chuckling]
[USOPP] The call center
will be plunged into chaos!
No amount of annoying
hold music or busy signals
will deter the masses
from worshipping me!
[laughing maniacally]
[SANJI]
Sanjiropus' 30 Hour Cooking!
[laughing maniacally]
Hello!
I'm the charming kitchen
creature of your dreams,
Sanjiropus!
[SANJI] Today,
I'll show you a simple recipe
that transforms leftovers
from disgusting to delectable!
No matter what kind of
crap you have in your fridge,
I can turn it
into a masterpiece!
All it takes
is three quick seconds.
And voila!
Can we get that
in slo-mo, please?
All right,
that should do it for today!
For the next
29 hours and 59 minutes,
I'll be staring at you ladies
lovingly from inside the TV.
Are you stupid?
The food's gonna get cold
if you leave it out like that!
That's your complaint?
[USOPP] You leave me no choice.
I'll have to serenade
my adoring public--
[ZORO]
Not a chance!
Get outta here.
I'll put on a show the
audience won't soon forget!
You just sit there and watch.
[sobbing]
[PORCHE] Oh no!
Let's have some fun, missy!
Someone help me!
There's no use crying now!
[ZORO] Don't move!
And who the heck are you?
What does it matter?
Just cut him to shreds!
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY] He's a lot
stronger than he looks!
Ow...
Spare me, it isn't my fault!
I wasn't raised right!
Hey, pal.
You don't happen to have
any rice balls, do you?
What?
Make sure you
have some from now on.
Um, thank you?
That didn't make
a lick of sense!
If they keep crapping up
the airways with this trash,
my plan is going to backfire!
[CHOPPER] 'Scuse me!
I'm here to join
the evil empire!
Finally, someone showed up!
Hey, boss!
Are you mocking me?
No, I really
wanna join your gang!
Or I really want
the toy, at least.
You still have the Air Force
C Max Limited Edition, right?
What do you take me for?
If you think I'm going to
give my most prized possession
to my worst enemy,
you're out of your mind!
Wait a moment.
But I really really want it!
Would you like me
to escort him out?
No. Not yet.
Hey, runt.
You said you wanted this?
Yeah, a whole bunch!
Then here, I'll give it to you.
You mean it?
--Oh, yay!
--But in exchange,
you have to lose to me in a
televised pro wrestling match
in front of a
live studio audience!
It's that, or no deal!
I have to lose?
But the hero never loses.
You just have to
pretend that I beat you.
A small price to pay for the
Air Force C Max
Limited Edition, I think.
I'm good at pretending!
I'll do it!
Get him ready for the show!
He's going to be a star!
[UNDERLING 51] Right!
I'm gonna be on TV! Hooray!
Are you sure about this, sir?
[chuckling]
What better way to
show the world how awesome I am
than to beat Chopperman
in a wrestling match!
Pro wrestling is known
for its integrity and realism,
so there's no way
that anyone would suspect
that we were faking it!
Right, of course.
Just watch, the main event
is finally about to start!
[SHOUPAN] Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the
match of the millennium!
Tonight's main event
is Usodaba vs Chopperman!
We're broadcasting live from
atop this fantastic globe arena
where the audience
is wild with anticipation!
I'm Shoupan, your
ringside announcer for tonight.
And sitting next to me
providing commentary
is the impressive
Minoru "The Wind"!
Good to be here.
[SHOUPAN] It seems
our wrestling mad scientist
is putting on a show
before the fight.
Ladies and gentlemen,
before I smash
Chopperman's face in,
let me serenade you with
a song I wrote just for tonight!
Cue the music!
[SHOUPAN] Well, never mind that,
because here comes Chopperman!
Yay! Are you watching, Namifia?
[cheering]
All this cheering
doesn't make me happy,
you big buncha jerks!
The crowd has spoken,
cuteness beats evil any day!
[USOPP] This is the last time
you ever make a fool of me!
You'll be sorry when
I'm popular, just you wait!
[bell rings]
Usodaba Neck Breaker!
Ow, that hurts!
Hey, I thought this
was just for pretend!
You better hold up
your end of the deal!
You still want your
little prize, don't you?
My prize?
The Air Force C Max
Limited Edition!
Wow, Usodaba sure has spirit,
but Chopperman not so much.
Is something wrong?
Maybe Chopperman got a
bad grade on a math quiz
and he's feeling down.
I know that always
used to bum me out.
Well, whatever the cause,
it's a one-sided match.
Yahh!
Owowowowow!
I never knew
Usodaba had it in him!
He looks flabby, but he sure
does have some enthusiasm!
He's not bad.
I never knew Chopperman
was such a little weenie.
He is pretty lame.
I thought Usodaba
was a scientist,
but he's got some
pretty smooth moves!
Go Usodaba! Go Usodaba!
--Go Usodaba!
[CROWD]
Go Usodaba! Go Usodaba!
And it seems the crowd
is turning around fast!
Even cuteness can only carry
you so far if you're weak!
[SANJI] Hello,
is this the wrestling arena?
Yes, Sanjiropus,
do you have any
news for our viewers?
Over here at the call center,
the phones are
ringing off the hook
with people just dying
to join the Usodaba Gang.
[USOPP] Finally!
Finally they see my greatness!
Haven't we done
this long enough?
I wanna get my
toy plane and go home!
[USOPP] Don't be a baby,
we're almost done!
I'll do my finishing move now!
[USOPP] I'm gonna
finish you for real, though!
[SHOUPAN] Uh-oh! Usodaba
has climbed to the top rope!
Chopperman's in
big trouble this time!
Could this be the birth
of a new dark hero?
[ROBIN] Farewell, Chopperman.
But before that,
how about a little song?
Gah! My precious Air Force
C Max Limited Edition!
Don't die on me!
Whew! It looks like
I can still fix it.
Thank goodness!
[CHOPPER] Thank goodness!
Gimme!
Yeah, right.
But you promised!
Oh, did I?
Well, that's too bad,
because I had no intention
of giving it to you.
I lied.
Bu--But that's so mean!
[laughing evilly]
I never wanted you
as a part of my evil empire
in the first place!
I just wanted to be
more popular than you!
But I tried so hard!
Forget the song!
Let's get that Usodaba
cheer going again!
[CHOPPER] Not so fast!
This fight isn't over yet!
Scoff! Don't make me laugh!
[CHOPPER] Special Attack...
...Try my Cute Spark!
Aww! How cute!
They don't call it
"Cute Spark" for nothing!
[CHOPPER]
Cute cute cute!
[NARRATOR] Let me explain.
Chopperman's "Cute Spark"
renders any enemy helpless
by melting their hearts.
Who can say no to those eyes?
Aww!
Vroom vroom! Vroom vroom!
What the whaaa?
How can anything
be that adorable?
It's just stupid!
Fight it, Usodaba, you're
walking right into his trap!
[CROWD] Chopperman!
Chopperman! Chopperman!
[USOPP] Stop it!
Aw, Chopperman is so adorable!
Suck on a lemon, Usodaba!
Chopperman's cuteness
has stolen their hearts
and Usodaba is old news!
Let's check in with
Sanjiropus at the call center
and see how things
are doing there.
Well, one fan wrote in,
"I hope Uso-dookie-da
has a heart attack".
That's not my name!
Hey, Long-Nose. Go get a job.
What is that supposed to mean?
This wrestling match
is finally starting
to get interesting!
Whose side are you on, anyway?
Curses.
[MINORU] Chopperman, tag me in!
Be like the wind!
[USOPP] Hey!
Who said this was a tag match?
How dare you hurt
Chopperman's feelings,
you heartless monster!
[SHOUPAN] Minoru rushes in like
the wind and blows Usodaba away!
[cheering]
It's time for
my secret weapon.
[distant rumbling]
Wha--What's that?
Hey! Look outside!
Cyber!
[NARRATOR]
The Giant Robot Frangasharn!
Dr. Usodaba's latest creation!
He's so new, I can't even
tell you anything about him!
Go forth, Frangasharn!
Destroy whatever you like!
I'm not picky!
Yeah!
[screaming]
[CHOPPER] Leave it to me!
Why fight for myself
when I have giant
robots to fight for me?
[CHOPPER yelling]
[LUFFY] Careful.
No, it can't be!
[NARRATOR]
The giant robot, Luffybomber!
It's big! It talks!
And for better or worse,
it always does what it wants!
Sorry I'm late!
You better be grateful for this.
I had to sell
all of my rings back.
But as soon as this is over,
I'm buying them back!
Thanks, Namifia!
They're stealing
my spotlight, Frangasharn!
Go shut them up!
[FRANKY]
Don't gotta ask me twice!
Banzai!
'Kay. Are you ready?
Yeah!
Crush those morons, Frangasharn!
No, stop it!
That's cheating!
What are you trying to do?
--He picked up the globe!
[USOPP] Are you crazy?
There's a ton of
innocent bystanders in here!
Oh. Wow, they
really got away fast!
[LUFFY] All right, here we go!
[FRANKY] Not bad.
[USOPP] I'm going to die!
[USOPP] Huh? Gahh!
Don't touch me! Let me go!
I mean don't let me go--
I mean...
[CHOPPER] You big meanie!
How dare you lie to me!
I'm gonna bust your face
with some Chopper Violence!
[USOPP screaming]
--All in a day's work!
[CROWD cheering]
Any words for your fans?
This cheering doesn't
make me happy at all,
you big buncha jerks!
[USOPP] This stinks.
All that work and now he's
more popular than before.
I'll get you next time!
This is a heavy price to pay,
even for peace, but anyway.
The public really does
seem to love him, huh?
I have an idea!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
Yes, this is the
Chopperman Fan Club.
How can I help you?
[NAMI] Yes, we accept cash,
check, or fine jewelry
for the membership fee.
My gosh,
I'm such a genius!
How many of these
do I have to do?
My arm is tired!
Just that pile and
3 more in the closet.
If you finish
by the end of today,
I'll get you that
model plane you wanted.
Only a few thousand more to go!
Oh boy! I'll give it my best!
[NARRATOR]
So it's a happy ending at last.
For Namifia, at least.
[NAMI]
Hello, Chopperman Fan club.
[NARRATOR]
Keep fighting, Chopperman!
Never give up!
[CHOPPER]
Okay!
[LUFFY] Ooh!
It's the haunted sea
Granny Kokoro warned us about!
Bring on the ghosts!
I wanna see if they're as
scary looking as everyone says!
[MALE VOICE]
I bet they're incredibly scary!
[LUFFY] Awesome!
I can't wait!
Wait--Who are you?
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
The Mysterious Skeleton
Floating Through the Fog!
Venture into the Devil's Sea!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!