[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[CHOPPER screams]
I would have been better off
eaten alive at the altar!
You have some business with me?
[DIVINE D]
Yes, simple business actually.
[ROBIN]
Seis Fleurs!
And with a twist.
Such a lack of respect.
[WYPER growls]
Have you ever seen a
Flying Blade Attack?
[ZORO]
Thirty-Six Caliber Phoenix!
[NAMI]
It can't be!
[ENERU laughs]
[LUFFY]
"The Roaring Burn Bazooka!
Luffy vs. War Demon Wyper!"
[USOPP cries]
What have you done?
You... You killed our Sanji!
[USOPP]
It's useless.
No pulse.
I wish Chopper were here.
He'd know what to do.
Hey! Sanji, Sanji. Sanji!
It wasn't supposed
to be this way!
Hold on, Usopp!
Your checking his
right side for a heartbeat.
The left side is
where his heart is!
[beating heart]
[shrieks]
He's alive!
Back from the dead.
I can't believe it.
But he's still not well,
just look at him.
No!
You can't die again!
I need you here!
Eneru!
There's no reason
for you to be so resentful.
It's spoiling our beautiful
reunion, don't you think?
It would serve us both
well if you cheered up.
Just a little, eh, Gan Fall?
[ENERU laughs]
Hey! You!
I don't know
what you did to him,
but you better not try
any more monkey business!
Or my 8,000 followers
will rip you to shreds!
I'll tell you what.
I'll forgive you and call off
my hordes of angry followers
if you just leave, right now!
How's that?
'S that sound good?
This is your final warning.
[USOPP]
Huh? It worked.
He left.
[USOPP squeaks]
Damn you!
You will stay quiet.
Or join your friends.
[ENERU]
Am I being clear?
Very good.
[NAMI]
Who is this guy?
And how did he do that?
What do you want, Eneru?
What wicked reason could you
possibly have for coming aboard?
[ENERU] During the six years
I've been on this island,
I've kept your former
subordinates very busy.
They've been slaving away
for me all these long years,
and they've hardly
had a moment to rest.
My Divine Warriors
have been reduced to slaves.
They are most extraordinary.
Truly they are of great talent.
But it appears that their
years of hard labor are over.
You see, this island
is no longer useful to me.
Consequently, I no longer
require the services
of your former Divine Warriors.
Perhaps you suspect that I have
sinister motives in coming here,
but I have simply come
to bid you farewell.
That is all.
[ENERU] I will say this,
sometimes I envy
the blissfull, innocent
stupidity of Skypiea's people.
The fools here can only see
this island as nothing more
than a clump of
vearth in the sky.
[GAN FALL]
What are you talking about?
Stupid old man.
All these years you never
guessed the true reason
we seized this island?
The reason that the Blue Sea
flies are here meddling
in the islands affairs.
And the reason the Shandorians
fight so bravely to return
to their sacred homeland?
You see, all this is happening
for one purpose and one alone.
There is something here
that they all seek.
[ENERU]
The great treasures of Shandora,
the legendary city of gold
that prospered on the
Blue Sea so long ago!
Gold is what brings us all here!
What is gold?
And why is it
so important to you?
[laughs]
Your ignorance never
ceases to amaze!
The only people in the world
who know nothing of gold
or it's value live in the
midst of an untold fortune!
You didn't even know
what the goal was,
so how could you
have won this game?
Interstingly enough, our game of
survival is in it's final play.
Whoever wins, gets the gold!
[laughs]
Can you hear it now?
The sounds of our
lively little competition?
[ENERU] As a matter of fact,
I'm a contestant myself,
so I must be off.
Wait, Eneru.
The Divine Warriors.
Are you going to set them free?
[ENERU]
God only knows.
And he's not telling.
[GAN FALL]
Eneru, wait!
He disappeared.
[USOPP coughs]
[NAMI]
Usopp! You're still alive!
Huh?
Ha-ha!
Gum-gum Ba.... lloon!
[LUFFY] I can do this
all day if you want,
but you can't win.
Rifles and cannons won't
leave a scratch on me.
Rubber body and all.
[WYPER]
So it would seem.
Time for a change of tactics.
[LUFFY]
Hmm?
Uh... Hmm?
Uh...
[coughs]
Gross! What is that smell?
[WYPER] This weapon
is called the burn bazooka.
By igniting the gas released
from the breath dial,
a deadly blue flame is created.
Which will incinerate anything
in it's path instantly.
Let's see if you can
bounce this back at me.
[screams]
[LUFFY]
What the heck is that thing?
It burned right
through that giant tree.
[LUFFY]
Where'd he go?
He disappeared!
[LUFFY]
Gum-gum...
...Pistol!
...Stamp!
That was close.
[LUFFY]
Gum-gum...
...Spear!
[LUFFY]
So you like bazookas, huh?
Get a load of this!
Now, you die!
[LUFFY]
Gum-gum...
[WYPER]
Burn...
[LUFFY, WYPER]
...Bazooka!
[LUFFY screams]
[screams]
[WYPER]
Straw Hat!
[LUFFY]
That bastard's dead.
[WYPER]
Where are you, Straw Hat?
I'll find you!
I know you're still alive!
Yeah!
And I plan on stayin' that way!
[screams]
What the heck is goin' on here?
[WYPER]
What is that?
[WYPER] Where could
that kid have run off to?
[rumbling]
[WYPER]
Strange.
No matter.
I shouldn't be wasting
my energy on him anyhow.
I have a more important battle.
All of my strength
needs to be saved
if I'm going to win
my fight with Eneru.
And I'm certain,
if I use the
reject one more time,
my body will be reduced
to a pile of ashes.
It's the end of the line, Eneru!
So, have you had enough yet?
Don't give up now.
We must not let him
get any further!
Shut up!
I'm after Eneru's head!
Make way!
Another one?
[GENBOU] Hmph. These
weaklings aren't worth my time!
[YAMA] What exquisite
ammunition you have there.
Matter that dense does not
naturally exist here in the sky.
[YAMA] The vearth mineral
called iron, isn't it?
[YAMA] You have managed to
make quick work of my men,
which is a difficult task
to say the least.
My guess...
...is that you are the great
Shandorian warrior, Genbou.
Commander Yama, good guess!
Now get out of my way!
[GENBOU]
Hmm?
[groans]
[GENBOU]
No!
I refuse to die!
Not like this. Not here.
[YAMA]
Ah! Still alive I see!
You are tough!
Very well, as a gesture of
respect for your warrior spirit.
I will end your suffering
with my secret technique.
[GENBOU]
Ten Axe Attack!
Damn you, Yama!
[YAMA]
Axe Mountain!
So very close, yet,
so very far away.
[laughs]
[HOTORI]
Ha-haaa!
[KOTORI]
Haa-ha!
[NAMI]
Who are you guys?
[HOTORI]
That's a stupid question!
[HOTORI, KOTORI]
We're Deputy Divine Comanders!
[KOTORI]
You killed our brother Satori!
[HOTORI]
Now you're gonna pay!
Brother?
What do you mean?
I haven't killed anybody.
[HOTORI, KOTORI]
Ha-haha. Ha-ha!
Ha! You can call me Hotori!
Ha! And you can call me Kotori!
And you guys killed our
beloved big brother, Satori.
Ha-ha!
Sorry to bust your bubble,
but I don't know your bother.
I believe that Satori was one of
the four Priests that
served under Eneru.
The Lost Forest, was once
their dead brothers domain.
Then, that
must be the Priest
that Luffy and
the guys took out.
Yes.
Seems they want revenge.
Ha! See!
You liars knew who
he was this whole time!
Now, you're all gonna pay!
Pierre!
We must deal
with these two quickly
and return to
the business at hand.
We need to find Eneru
and rescue my Divine Warriors
before the unthinkable happens.
Now, stand back, young lady!
I may be injured, but I'd never
lose to the likes of those two!
No. I won't stand
back this time.
'Cause sometimes I'm the one...
...who has to
protect my friends!
Very well then.
First we need to determine
which dials they possess.
All right!
Time to avenge our brother!
Ha-ha!
Hey, everything stopped.
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Where am I?
[CHOPPER]
Hello!
C'mon guys!
It's me!
Are you there?
Just answer me, please!
I wonder how long it's
gonna take the rest of them.
This is boring.
Where is it?
Where did it go?!
Uh, Gedatsu, your eyes
are rolled all the way
into the back of your head.
Honestly, how could you expect
to see anything like that?
So careless!
Now, how's your vision?
Can you see this?
Here it is, that puny creature.
He's one of those
Blue Sea dwellers.
Is that right?
I just thought
it was a raccoon dog.
[DIVINE E]
Racoon dog?
No. He's nothing like
a wild animal.
He walks upright.
That is unquestionably
a creature
that comes from the Blue Sea.
Luffy!
Where are you hiding?
Come on!
Wake up already, Zoro!
Robin!
Hurry up, this is getting lame!
Awww. Where is everybody?
This is where
we're supposed to meet!
Guys!
C'mon, I'm lonely,
and I'm getting a
little freaked out here!
[GEDATSU]
Where'd you go?
Come out right now!
[CHOPPER shrieks]
Scary creepy no eyes man!
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[CHOPPER]
Are you a Priest?
[GEDATSU]
You're on my territory!
There are Swamp Clouds
all around us!
There is no escape!
[CHOPPER] Everyone
always has to protect me
'cause I'm such a coward.
That's why
they can't rely on me.
That changes now!
I'm gonna raise a pirate flag
right here and beat this guy!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Ordeal of the Swamp!
Chopper vs. Sky Punk Gedatsu!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!