It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
After being left behind
at the front gate,
Sniper King heard
a shocking story
from one of the
giant gatekeepers.
But everything changed when
we visited a certain island.
They weren't
captured 50 years ago.
That's nothing
but a big fat lie!
On the other side of
the gate, the Straw Hats
were catching up to Luffy
thanks to Sodom and Gomorrah.
But just before they reached
the courthouse, tragedy struck.
We've been hit! No!
Sodom!
Grit those teeth
and hold on, Sodom!
You can't fall yet!
Guys, you're gonna have to jump!
Get off him, quick!
He's coming down!
Meanwhile, on top
of the courthouse,
Luffy and Blueno
were facing off.
So Robin is in that
building behind you, huh?
Outta my way, bull guy!
Listen boy.
Perhaps you
haven't realized this
but what you are doing right now
is nothing short of
a world-class crime.
Hm?
You will not only face
a merciless death,
but serve as an
example to the entire world.
Here we go!
Iron Body.
Gum-Gum Rifle!
This doesn't make any sense!
He wasn't like this at all
when I fought him before!
How is it that he's
so much stronger now?
Gatling!
Shave!
All that matters is
getting Robin outta here!
All the forces are gathering
at the courthouse.
At long last, the battle
with CP9 has begun!
I see!
Meow!
My goodness, those pirates
sure are reckless, aren't they?
Hey Granny!
Meow! Meow!
Oh boy, now what?
Come see! Come see!
Meow!
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
It's coming.
Wait, aim carefully!
Get it in your sights, men!
It's a trench mortar.
Gomorrah! Dodge!
Damn bastards had an
ambush waiting for us.
Taking the main road
sure was a bad idea!
Turn around, quick!
Not so fast!
Sorry, Sodom.
Stop right there!
Chopper.
Puru-puru. Puru-puru.
Hm? Who could be calling?
Yes? Hello?
Howdy howdy!
Granny Kokoro!
What's going on?
All right, sounds
like you're still alive.
So, where are you?
We're almost at the courthouse,
but we're under attack.
Why do you ask?
Oh, perfect timing.
There's a little something
I forgot to tell you.
That doesn't sound reassuring.
Well, I'm sure you're busy,
so I'll make it quick.
Listen carefully.
If you remember
that map Paulie drew,
you might notice there's no path
from the courthouse to
the Gates of Justice.
That's been bothering me but
I was afraid to ask about it.
Look at the courthouse.
You see those
towers on either side?
Yeah, I see them.
All right, now there's
a lever on the top floor
of each of those towers.
If you folks can get in
there and pull both of 'em,
a drawbridge'll come
down from the courthouse
to the Gates of Justice.
Whoa!
But how do you know
about all that stuff, Granny?
I came here with Tom
ages ago to fix that bridge.
Damn stupid
ungrateful Government!
Don't take it out on me!
Chimney wants to talk, too.
Pirate lady.
Hey, can you hear me? Hello?
Yeah, I've got
you loud and clear!
Guess what?
I just saw your
rubber pirate buddy!
He was over on the rooftop
of the courthouse just now!
Meow! Meow!
So that's where he is!
There was a bunch of smoke
and broken stuff up there too,
so it looks like
he's wrecking the place!
Thanks!
Hopefully we'll get there soon.
And by the way, don't
hang up the transponder snail.
I'd like to keep track of
what's goin' on with you folks.
No problem. See ya!
Can't keep the captain
waiting. Right, men?
Gero! Gero!
Good.
You head straight
for the courthouse.
The sooner that your crew can
get back together, the better.
That's what I say.
Sounds good.
Meanwhile, we'll
split in two groups
and bring down the drawbridge.
You hear that, Gomorrah?
To the courthouse!
Gomorrah!
Damn. Who the hell is that?
Don't get too cocky, scumbags.
All right! The second
one's down, too!
How's that, huh?
Not so fast now, are ya?
Everybody, move in!
Attention, all Marine guards.
Here at Block D in
the southeast quadrant,
the pirate's King Bull
has been eliminated!
All units should
move in immediately.
Form a blockade
around the entire area.
I repeat!
All military personnel
surround Block D now!
Seems that the jurymen have
delivered the verdict for us.
And it's guilty as usual, huh?
Say something, man!
Yes sir.
On our way!
The marines we trampled over
are catching up to us again.
Not good.
And it's not just them.
We're surrounded here!
We've got trench
mortars aimed at us, too.
There's gotta be
like a million bajillion
of those guys out there!
We can't even run away anymore!
What're we gonna do?
What is this?
An earthquake?
Where did they come from?
Neato!
Hey.
Look!
All right.
Oimo and Kashii are
back on their feet!
We're screwed.
I don't have the strength to
fight these guys a second time.
We were so close!
Crush those criminals
into the ground!
Grind their little bones
between your toes, giants!
Pound 'em, Kashii!
Pulverize 'em, Oimo!
C'mon.
What're you big
lugs waiting for?
Make them pay!
You bastards.
How dare you?
Lie to us!
What the hell?
Don't tell me they betrayed us!
And now, with our bosses safe,
before we mourn all
those years we wasted--
We're going let out every
last ounce of our anger on you!
Are you ready,
King of the snipers?
Let us not waste words.
Hoist the signal for
the counterattack!
Soon we shall be
reunited with our comrades!
Damn, you got it good.
Not everyone gets
their own rescue squad.
Hey, keep it down!
Sorry!
Hmph.
Well, just sayin'.
It's not like I'm bitter 'cause
my men aren't coming to save me.
They got better
stuff to do, I'm sure.
Ah, that's right.
I almost forgot.
Before you leave, you
should take these with you.
Wait a sec!
Those are Devil
Fruits, aren't they?
Yoyoi.
My!
What a surprise!
Chapapa.
I've never seen
one in person before!
It's my first time as well!
Stay away!
Don't let those things near me!
You ate one, too.
What's your problem?
Why the fuss?
What?
Haven't you heard?
The reason they're called
"Devil Fruits" is because
the people who eat them
have a little devil living
inside their bodies!
Just think.
If I get too close
to one of those things,
the devil inside
me might pop out
and start fighting with
the devil inside the fruit.
If something like that happens,
my whole body'll
be blown to bits!
You're kidding me.
That's nonsense.
You're a member of an
intelligence agency
and you believe that?
What a shame.
The condition for the
transfer of devil fruit powers
has been confirmed by
scientists on the Grand Line
for quite some time.
The condition you're
talking about only happens
when someone
eats two Devil Fruits.
I don't know if
devils are involved,
but their bodies do burst apart.
The price for greed.
What fools.
If you think about the risk that
comes with eating one fruit,
you can only imagine
what kind of disaster
you might bring upon
yourself by eating two of them.
Huh.
So that's how it works. Still.
I'm surprised.
I can't believe
you got two of these.
Pretty impressive, Chief.
How'd you pull that one?
Let's just say
I have connections.
How's that?
At any rate, best of luck.
That's right, CP9!
Grow stronger and stronger!
As always, there is
a certain risk involved.
We don't know what kind of
devils reside in those fruits.
I've never seen a fruit like
this in any reference book.
You can feel a strange
power coming from them,
a heaviness in the air.
It's like they're
from a different world.
That's what everyone says.
I've been told that
you only learn the name
of the fruit once
you absorb its powers
but there's no guessing what
kind of ability you'll gain.
Well, there's no denying
that there's a risk involved.
The wrong power
could ruin your life.
And either way, you'll
no longer be able to swim.
It's not an issue of what power
you get, but how you use it.
No matter what,
you won't get weaker.
And as for being unable to
swim, it's hardly a problem.
It's a rare treasure.
Of the thousands
who search for them,
I'm sure most end up
empty-handed
or dead by the
end of their journey.
Just try it already.
It'll be interesting.
Don't do it. Are you crazy?
That thing's evil!
Also, they taste
like crap, I tell you.
Crap!
Yeah right. He's jealous.
He doesn't want them
getting stronger! Chapapa.
Shame.
You should know,
Jabra, that envy
and resentment
are a man's downfall!
Yoyoi!
Hey! Shut up!
C'mon. Just stop.
Think about this!
If you sell these things,
you could make millions.
But one bite
and you'll be cursed
for the rest of your life!
Chapapa.
Yep.
Interesting all right.
Here goes.
Hope it's good.
They ate them!
No!
Coo coo!
Coo cooloo coo!
Chapapa.
What's wrong?
Yoyoi.
Is your body besieged with
a strange metamorphosis?
Chapapa!
Gross.
Say so sooner!
It's really gross.
Yeah, we got that!
Chapapa!
And yet, you ate the
whole thing without a word!
Well? C'mon!
Try doing something already.
I wanna see what kind
of powers you got!
I don't feel as if
anything is different.
Soon you'll understand
the extent of your changes.
The birth of new Devil Fruit
users is always exciting.
Enjoy yourselves, but I'd try to
get those powers under control,
while you still can.
Depending on our orders,
you might have to use
them in real combat soon.
It seems Blueno couldn't wait.
We'll have to see if
he saves any fun for us.
You're not bad.
Not bad?
I never thought he'd be able to
keep up with the speed of Shave.
I'll have to watch that.
And since he's made of rubber,
direct attacks won't work.
Moon Walk!
Now, Gum-Gum--
Tempest Kick!
Iron Body!
Wheel!
Door-Door!
Was that a door on the ground?
Door-Door.
Whoa, wait a sec!
Now there's a bunch of little
ones all over the place, too!
Damn it, I can't move!
This sucks. It's a stupid trap!
You're the one doing this?
But how? A Devil Fruit?
The Door-Door Fruit, naturally.
A Door Man?
I turn all that
I touch into doors.
Revolving Door.
Whoa, what?
I'm not moving anywhere
but I'm spinning!
I dunno which way is the front!
Make it stop!
Tempest Kick!
Cook. See that?
Yeah. I saw.
You know what that means.
Luffy's already fighting CP9.
What?
Huh?
Seriously?
Damn it.
We're too late!
But there's nothing we can do!
We're totally surrounded.
And after taking
that last big hit,
I don't think Gomorrah's
going anywhere!
Everyone open fire and
shoot those pirates down
from the monster
before it gets back up!
Look. We gotta run.
We can't wait here any longer.
Yeah.
Let's cut through
to the courthouse.
It's our only option.
Right! Let's go!
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Wait. Nobody get off!
What? Why?
Everyone, hold on tight!
That...
That's what Gomorrah says!
It's still alive!
The monster's getting back up!
Fire!
Stop it with the trench mortars!
Take that thing down!
Return fire! C'mon. Hurry!
Go, Gomorrah! Charge!
After hearing all
the field reports,
our guard casualties total
must be over 2,000 men!
Wait, not five?
In the history of this island,
this is, without a doubt,
the absolute worst thing
that has ever happened
at Enies Lobby!
What the hell's going on?
On the next One Piece:
"Almost to Luffy! Gather
at the Courthouse Plaza!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!