It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
Riding on Rocketman,
the Straw Hat pirates
have infiltrated
Enies Lobby's Main Island.
So anyway, what
about our Captain?
Any guesses on where he went?
Who knows.
The island's pretty big.
Where should we start?
Huh?
That's got to be where he's at.
Luffy, who ran
ahead of the others,
is desperately trying to make
his way to the courthouse.
Spear!
He jumped onto the tree!
I'm not getting anywhere.
Don't those dumb jerks
have anything better to do?
What's up?
You take the reins.
Here.
Wait.
What's going on here?
When you see 'em, I want you
to pass on a message for me.
"You're all fired."
You got it.
All right, jump!
Not so fast!
Half Knot Air Drive!
Whoa!
He took out those
Watchdogs out in one hit!
You ready for round two?
Meanwhile, Robin
and Franky were caught
in the middle of a desperate
situation of their own.
Both the triggers needed
to revive the Ancient Weapon
are right here, at my mercy!
You get it, now?
When I say the winds of this
world are blowing in my favor,
I most assuredly mean it!
Every man and every nation in
the world must answer to me!
All that power at
the tip of my fingers!
I don't understand.
Why would Aokiji allow you
to invoke the Buster Call?
What gives you the
right to question me?
You shut your mouth!
You get to play a part in
the rebirth of this world!
Isn't that enough for you,
you insolent witch?
I believe you should
even be thanking me!
I'll cleanse this world
of Ohara's legacy
by bleeding you dry.
Understand, Nico Robin?
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
Now listen, and listen well.
From this moment on,
I'm going to make you suffer
pain so excruciatingly agonizing
that you'll wake up every
morning wishing you were dead.
So prepare yourself.
I'm going to hurt you
and use you then
throw you out into the sea!
A life as sinful as
yours deserves nothing less!
Oh, and by the way,
I just received some
interesting news.
Apparently, a moronic
group of riff-raff has decided
to infiltrate our island in a
hapless attempt to rescue you.
You don't mean--?
Yes.
But, don't you worry.
I'm sure they've been
apprehended by now.
Straw Hat Luffy and his
crew will trouble us no more.
They're so stubborn.
They're little more
than insects compared
to the might of the ten thousand
soldiers of Enies Lobby.
Conveniently, we were
already preparing
a prison transport ship.
What perfect timing they have!
Along with Cutty Flam, they'll
make a wonderful addition
as the latest inmates
of Impel Down.
Hold on!
That wasn't part
of our agreement!
In exchange for my
cooperation and surrender,
you promised that you'd let
the Straw Hats escape safely!
Come now!
What are you getting
so worked up about?
Lucci!
Remind her of the exact
conditions that were offered!
The terms of the
arrangement were,
that excluding Nico Robin,
the Straw Hat Pirates
would be allowed to
leave Water 7 safely.
Correct.
There you have it.
Fairly straightforward, I'd say.
After allowing them
to leave Water 7 safely,
as promised, the Straw Hats
decided to come here.
Is this some kind of joke?
You're going to break
the heart of our agreement
over a ridiculous technicality?
These dirtbags are
the lowest of the low.
Not a shred of decency
in any one of 'em!
Huh?
What did you say?
Shut up, you
filthy piece of trash!
We're not under any obligation
to keep our promises
to a bunch of criminals!
You hear me?
Take that, and that, and that!
You, too!
Don't get cocky
with me, understand?
Deceiving and capturing pirates
is what the Navy does,
you insolent wench!
You're just the
idiot who fell for it!
You coward.
Still running that
mouth of yours, I see.
Rest assured.
I'll choose a
fitting death for one
who's spent her life lying,
deceiving, and betraying others.
Before the supreme power of
justice, resistance is futile.
But look on the bright side,
at least your friends will
suffer and die with you!
Hurry!
Don't let him escape!
He's alone!
Surround him!
Get him!
Move!!
Get outta my way!
Stupid bastards!
Commander!
This guy's really scary!
Don't falter, men!
Bring him down!
Attack!
Commander!
There! Yep!
That dead end's
gotta be the place!
They better not
have taken you away yet!
Robin!
I suppose that's enough for now.
You two!
Get them out of here.
Yes, sir!
There's a Sea Prism Stone
lock on her restraints.
Make sure it's secure.
Cutty Flam goes to Impel Down
and Nico Robin to
Navy Headquarters.
As soon as the ship's ready,
we'll set sail through
the Gates of Justice.
Right!
It shall be done, sir!
Also, take extra
precautions with Cutty Flam.
He can be extremely violen--
Has Straw Hat been sighted?
Yeah.
We got a report about it a
little while back, chapapa.
When he heard the news,
Chief got so worked up.
It was embarrassing.
They said there were
only five casualties,
but that can't be right.
The receiver is off the hook.
Don't give us any
trouble, tough guy.
Let's get going.
You can return to
your quarters for now.
Thanks to this catch,
CP9 will be the toast
of Navy Headquarters.
Our status will rise
to incredible heights,
in a covert way, of course.
And for that,
I'd like to propose a
little toast of our own!
I'm not in the mood
for some ridiculous toast.
Nor am I interested in our
status or political influence.
Our brand of justice
is to assassinate
in the name of the
World Government.
As long as they continue
to recognize you as
the commander of CP9,
we will fulfill our
duty to the letter.
But we're under no obligation
to support your
personal ideologies.
That's--
That's a sound argument.
But then, what is
it you want exactly?
Perhaps all that
we seek is blood.
And with CP9, we have
the privilege to kill.
These guys give me the creeps.
Like he said, they assassinate
legally in the name of justice.
And they're very
good at what they do.
Quite dependable.
As long as I have
them working for me,
there's nothing
I can't accomplish!
I'm invincible!
Hey!
What's all that commotion about?
Something's coming!
Way to go, Sodom and Gomorrah!
Keep charging forward!
Oh, no!
It's them!
Those pirates that broke
through the Main Island's Gate!
Fire!
Don't let up!
Gero, Gero!
Unless you wanna die,
get outta the way!
Take that!
And that!
Fall back and then
restore formation!
Damn!
Stupid pirates!
You shouldn't be so cocky!
Now I've got you, pirate lady!
Get outta here!
Beat it!
Smooth sailing.
These two make it easy.
Keep going until we reach
our Captain, King Bulls!
Damn!
There's so many of them!
There's no end to
these stupid Marines!
They boxed me in!
He's headed your way!
There he is!
Capture him!
Don't let him go any further!
I need to find out where
they're holding Robin and fast!
But I can't keep looking
with these guys in the way.
Attack him from both sides!
He went down that alleyway!
After him!
He's fleeing to the rooftop!
Halt!
Whoa!
What the heck?
These guys are really stubborn.
You won't escape this time!
End of the road!
Fine.
I'll get there in one shot!
Now Gum Gum.
Surrender, Straw Hat!
Stop him!
Rocket!
See ya!
Damn!
I hate that guy!
Don't let those
pirates go any further!
Stop them!
Bring down every
last one of them!
Keep firing!
Send those marines packing!
Whoa, really?
Stupid bastards!
Oh.
Oh, I see.
Understood!
So then, when Sodom
and his brother Gomorrah
were about to die in
the belly of a Sea King,
the Franky Family showed up!
They were rescued
and told these fateful words
that he still remembers:
"Look, we're already full
so we're not gonna eat you!"
And from that day forward,
the two brothers swore
their undying loyalty
to their savior, Franky.
So let me get this straight.
The Franky Family brought
down a Sea King, ate it,
and they just
happened to be saved
because Franky
was already full?
Pretty much.
Fine.
Whatever.
You mind watching
where you're going?
You're making me nervous.
"I will follow Big Bro Franky
until the day I die!" he says.
I bet he's really happy
that one of us can
understand what he's saying.
He said "By the way,
the masked guy
that was with you never
made it on board my back.
Is that okay?"
He's talking about Sniper King!
Where is he?
Why now? Why now?
Idiot.
Did he fall off?
Didn't you hear?
He hasn't been
here from the start!
Don't tell me.
Did he run away again?
Move it!
Get out of the way!
Arrogant pirates!
You can't keep this
foolishness up forever!
Stand aside and let us pass!
If you wanna pass, you'll have
to go through me to do it!
Fine then!
Attack!
Is that really the
best you've got?
Battleship Cannon!
Come on!
There's only three of them!
Do something!
So, you're good at
fighting, aren't you?
Then you can beat
those guys, huh?
You bet.
We'll get her back.
We just needed motivation.
Now that we know
Robin needs saving,
there's no limit to what Luffy
and the rest of our
crew can accomplish!
I'm gonna beat up
every last one of them!
There's a new move I wanna try!
I believe in him.
He can do it.
Go!
Get that rope guy!
Not gonna happen!
Shrouds and Ratline Knot!
We're done for!
Consider this a dead end.
Give up and go.
Lieutenant Commander!
Terrible news!
What is it?
It's Straw Hat Luffy, sir!
We can't find him anywhere!
He gave us the slip!
That's impossible!
We've got thousands of
Marines here looking for him!
Even so, no one can find him!
Don't tell me.
Is he somehow already
inside the courthouse?
No!
Not even an insect could've
gotten past our defenses, sir!
Go!
We must find Straw Hat
at any cost, men!
This is the last building.
She's gotta be here.
Right.
But there isn't a bridge.
Looks kinda far, too.
Oh well.
Guess I'll try jumping over.
What the heck?
Air Door.
Hey!
You're the bull who's working
with that stupid pigeon guy!
There seem to be
some discrepancies
between the report
and the actual situation.
Whoa!
How'd you just appear like that?
Awesome!
Magic?
To be honest, it did
seem a little suspicious.
No way you only
took out 5 marines.
Man, you really surprised me!
An invasion like
this is unprecedented.
This is the furthest
anyone has ever infiltrated
into the mouth of
the World Government.
But that ends here.
Outta my way, bull.
Tell me.
How long do you plan
to keep fighting?
Until I die.
Get outta my way.
Listen, boy, do you have
any idea what it means
to challenge the power
of the World Government?
Blah blah blah.
Whatever!
I'll deal with that stuff later.
Fool.
You still believe
you'll have a future?
All I care about is
getting Robin back now!
On the next One Piece:
"Give Robin Back!
Luffy vs. Blueno!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!