[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at a brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other instead.
Anxious to prevent
the coming battle
between the rebel
and royal armies,
Princess Vivi rushes
through the desert
in search of the rebels.
However...
Right now all I wanna do
is kick Crocodile's ass,
you understand?
Maybe we can keep the people
from starting a rebellion,
but that won't stop Crocodile.
Well, you can at least
try putting all of our lives
on the line together!
Aren't we friends, huh?
[LUFFY]
So now tell me.
Where can I find Crocodile?
[NARRATOR] And it was
at this moment that Vivi
made up her mind.
[LUFFY]
"The Battlefront of Alabasta!
Rainbase, the City of Dreams!"
[VIVI crying]
You all.
[VIVI]
Luffy. Luffy was right.
I've made up my mind now.
Change of plans. We're going
to go find Crocodile.
Yeah!
That does seem like
the quickest way
of stopping the fighting
from happening.
And we can quit wandering
around the desert, too.
That was beginning to get old.
So. Where is he, anyway?
This damn Crocodile guy.
[VIVI]
Let's see.
This is the capital city,
Alubarna, where my father rules.
And the rebel army
is camped here,
getting ready to
invade Alubarna.
So we just need to get to
Crocodile before the rebels
can get to Alubarna.
[VIVI]
This is where Crocodile is.
Over here. Rainbase.
Rainbase.
It's a city a bit
to the north of us,
about a day's journey from here.
[LUFFY groaning]
[USOPP groaning]
Okay. Did I or did I
not tell the two of you
to quit with the
pathetic moaning all the time?
[USOPP, LUFFY arguing]
You could at least
let us ride Eyelash
for a little bit.
‐‐You're a big, fat camel hog!
‐‐Get off your high horse!
Hey, Chopper.
You've managed to make
it all day without collapsing.
Yeah, I'm trying hard not to.
Vivi. Does this Rainbase
city have a water supply?
Oh, yeah.
No shortage there.
It's a gambling town,
almost completely
isolated from all the fighting.
Wah! Gambling?
No way, Nami!
We're not going there to gamble.
I guess people need
some places to relax,
even here in Alabasta.
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum... No way!
No, no, no, no, no!
[USOPP]
Come on! Gimme some!
Gum‐Gum... Leave me alone!
[USOPP]
Come on, Luffy!
Just give me one
sip of it, please!
Isn't that why he gave it to us?
The old guy from the
sandstorm place gave it to me!
He had to dig all night just
to get this much of it.
We can't just go drinking
it like it's regular water
or something. So no way!
Wow! You can restrain
yourself sometimes.
Well, yeah.
Of course I can, Nami!
That was a rude thing
to say, you know!
[USOPP]
Can't take another step.
Need water.
So, how long
till Rainbase, Vivi?
Hey, Luffy.
Thanks a lot. I never would
have been able to make
this decision on my own.
[LUFFY]
Okay, then give me food.
[VIVI]
Huh?
[LUFFY] After I beat up
Crocodile, give me food.
I'll eat till I explode!
I promise I will.
Please, Koza!
Just let me join
you and the rebels!
I will not.
And why not?
Don't I have every right to
be part of the rebellion, too?
I hate the king
and the royal army!
Just let me fight with you
so I can prove it!
Faracla, show the kid.
He got that wound
trying to protect me
in the middle of a battle.
Would you like to
see the medical tents
and the gravesites, too?
It isn't pretty.
I'm not scared.
You can't scare me!
The cities have dried up
and a lotta people
have died 'cause the
king stole all the rain
from everyone!
My friends got sick 'cause
there wasn't enough water!
It's all the king's fault!
I only want the chance.
Just let me fight!
I'm not scared of getting
injured, or even dying!
That's where you're different
from us and why I can't let
you join our ranks.
We're all afraid,
and none of us wanna fight.
Well, why do you
fight then, Koza?
We don't do it
because we want to.
We do it because we have to.
Because that's what our
country needs us to do.
Whether you understand
that or not
makes little difference.
So just leave.
Damn it,
I told you to leave now.
Battle is no place for
a child, do you hear me?
What's wrong, huh?
It's not like you to
rant and rave like that.
Especially at a kid.
It was like looking at
myself when I was his age.
It made me angry.
And the worst part is I haven't
changed a bit since then.
Have we gathered all
the weapons we require?
[SUBORDINATE B] No, it's
proving quite difficult.
[KOZA] We need to begin
contacting all the other towns.
As soon as we have
all the weapons,
we will begin our final,
all‐out attack on Alubarna.
[CHAKA]
Sire!
It's only a matter of time now
before the rebel army
attacks Alubarna.
We must take action against
the rebels quickly,
before it's too late!
I said no!
We'll not attack them.
This is not some little quarrel.
If we strike first,
they will strike back.
Sire.
We are barely clinging
to power right now as it is.
That does not matter.
I don't care about
my rule at the moment.
Ever since the
Dance Powder incident,
it's been clear that
someone's trying
to tear apart our country.
Are you suggesting that
we attack our citizens
before we determine
who's behind all this?
Because that would be
the true destruction
of our kingdom.
Don't you know?
A country is its people.
But sir, whoever is behind this
hasn't shown himself so far.
We can't sit back and wait
for this unknown force
to divide us; we must act!
Can't you see?
Please understand. I can't.
[CHAKA] The king will not allow
us to take the offensive now.
[PELL] We can barely even
keep our own soldiers
happy at this point.
I would feel much better
if we had Igaram
with us at a time like this.
[COBRA] Igaram has left
a note saying that
he's leaving the
island for awhile.
[PELL] Even as we speak
he and Princess Vivi
are still out there somewhere,
trying hard to figure
out who's behind this.
I hope they can.
[SUBORDINATE]
Chaka, Pell, come quickly!
What is it?
It's Karoo.
He's returned to the palace.
Karoo's back?
We heard, your Majesty!
Who sent that letter?
[COBRA]
There's no mistaking it.
It's my Vivi's handwriting.
So your Majesty, it means‐‐
Karoo brought news from Vivi.
What does it say?
[VIVI]
Father.
Everything I have written
here is true beyond a doubt.
Please read this
letter carefully.
[CROCODILE laughing]
[VIVI] I've discovered the
identity of the person
who's trying to destroy
Alabasta Kingdom.
It is a Warlord of the Sea,
Crocodile!
[VIVI] Because of Crocodile,
Igaram is dead.
He died as he lived.
A hero to his country.
It's Crocodile!
I stupidly thought he was loyal
to the World Government.
I never even wondered
if he was the one
behind all of this.
How can he be dead?
He died as he would have wanted,
protecting Princess
Vivi and Alabasta.
[VIVI]
But now, Father.
I have joined forces with
an amazing group of people.
They have given me great
confidence and power.
If I continue to
work beside them,
I believe we will be able
to make a difference
in this country.
We have reason to hope now.
Alabasta can and will be saved!
Please have faith, Father.
We can do this. Vivi.
Vivi's letter mentions
that you fought
very valiantly as well, Karoo.
You served her well.
Oh, it looks like
you've been hurt.
Let me see.
[KAROO squawks]
Okay.
No matter what happens
on that island, remember.
This thing on all our arms
is a sign of our friendship.
[KAROO squawks]
[COBRA]
Chaka.
We know the enemy's identity!
Prepare the soldiers
to move out!
Vivi's courage and Igaram's
death won't be in vain.
We're going to take action now.
We'll head for Rainbase,
and Crocodile.
Please do not be so hasty,
Your Majesty.
Rainbase is far away
and there are many
preparations to be made.
What's more, Crocodile has many
of the citizens
firmly on his side.
Even more of them
than you do, Sire,
with all due respect.
If we send forces to
Rainbase now, your Majesty,
the rebels will use
our absence to attack.
And they will take
the palace easily,
in which case‐‐
It doesn't matter if
the rebel army destroys
this palace completely.
It is only a building.
I've told you before,
a country is its people.
Even if our royal army
does fall in the end,
if we can just defeat Crocodile,
this country can still
be reborn as long as
its people are safe and whole.
If we battle the
rebel army instead,
then that will all change.
In that situation,
Crocodile's the victor.
Understand?
Majesty.
Yes, I see.
For right now, we do not
need to be focusing
on the rebel army.
We just need to
take out Crocodile.
This is one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea
that we're fighting.
He is strong and cunning.
There will be many casualties.
But we must accept that
and battle onward.
Chaka! We need
to hold a war counsel.
Assemble the officers!
Pell, scout ahead
and conduct reconnaissance.
Right.
[CHAKA] Forgive me for
having underestimated you,
Your Majesty.
You are a true man
of your country.
[COBRA] We head for battle
tomorrow morning!
[CHAKA, PELL]
Sir!
All soldiers are
to head for Rainbase.
There.
So is that the city?
[LUFFY, USOPP groaning]
That's it?
[LUFFY]
Oh? Are we here?
[VIVI]
Crocodile!
Yeah!
Time to kick Crocodile's ass!
[LUFFY]
That's Rainbase, huh?
So after all that's happened,
are we operating
under the assumption
that Baroque Works
knows that we're here
on the island with them?
It seems likely.
We did run into Mr. 2,
so I think it's safe to assume
that they have
at least some idea
that we were headed to Alabasta.
Who cares about that?
They know exactly
what we look like,
so we won't be able
to do much of anything
while we're in Rainbase‐‐
just lay low.
And why is that?
Because, if we get spotted
before we can find Crocodile,
I'm sure he can
probably come up with
all sorts of nasty ways
of taking care of us.
Assassination is kinda
their area of expertise.
Laying low!
But we're coming, Crocodile!
You weren't even
listening, were you?
Well, no matter what happens,
I will take it upon
myself to protect
Nami and Vivi from any harm.
I'm always happy to
play prince charming‐‐
for a lady.
Smooth one.
Smoother than you are, Zoro!
I need water!
There is none, let it go.
[LUFFY]
I'm going!
[USOPP]
Wait for me, Luffy!
Hey! You might wanna
take some money along!
[TASHIGI]
Captain Smoker.
Why do you think
that they'll be here?
What reason would
the Straw Hats have
for coming to Rainbase?
[SMOKER]
Let's just call it a hunch.
Yeah! Finally, we can get water!
I can't put my finger on it,
but something stinks.
I just feel like
there's something big
lurking in the shadows.
Hey, old lady,
give us some water, 'kay?
Yeah, yeah, a whole barrel!
No, we want more than that!
Five barrels, yeah!
So then, you really
do believe that there is
some sort of a connection
between the Baroque Works
crime organization and
the Straw Hat's crew?
[USOPP, LUFFY]
Water, haha!
Here.
[SMOKER] The only thing I know
for sure is that Straw Hat
is out to get Crocodile,
one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea.
[USOPP]
This is the best water ever!
We need to hurry up and get
some back out to the others!
[CHOPPER] I'm gonna go use
the little boys' room.
Do you really think
we can count on them
to stay out of trouble?
Even they can handle
little errands okay, right?
I dunno.
I'll bet they'll manage
to screw something up.
It is Usopp and Luffy.
I'd start getting ready
to run if I were you.
‐‐[LUFFY] Run away!
‐‐[USOPP] Yeah!
‐‐[LUFFY] Protect the water!
‐‐[USOPP] Right!
Damn it! We're going after them!
Get the Marines, Tashigi!
Sir!
Oh, right.
How much do I owe you?
If you know those brats,
you'd better add all the water
they took to your tab.
Of course. I'm so sorry.
[LUFFY] What are the damn
Marines doing here?
[MARINES yelling]
[USOPP]
How should I know that?
Let's just keep running for now!
You win.
It looks like the Marines
are chasing them.
No way!
So why are those
idiots running this way?
Hey. Tony hasn't made
his way back here yet!
He'll be fine.
Chopper can manage on his own.
[LUFFY] Hey, you guys,
I think the Marines are here!
Hey, thank you!
We hadn't noticed that, Luffy!
Hurry it up! We can't
lose them this time, men!
[USOPP yelling]
[SMOKER]
Those idiots sure can run.
I'll give 'em that, anyway.
[USOPP] This is bad!
Baroque Works will see us...
...if we run through the city!
I think it's a little
too late for that, Usopp.
[LUFFY]
Then it's decided. Let's go!
[VIVI]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
To wherever Crocodile is.
How about it. Ready?
[VIVI] Do you see that
building up ahead
with the alligator on its roof?
That's the casino
that Crocodile runs.
It's called Raindinners.
I see it.
So that's where Crocodile is.
It'll be better if
we all split up now.
Yeah, it's looking that way.
Right! See ya later.
[GROUP]
Right!
‐‐[LUFFY] Don't die!
‐‐[MARINE B] They split up!
[MARINE C]
Don't lose 'em!
Smokey! Hey!
You've got some real
nerve there, Straw Hat.
But don't think
you can run forever!
[SMOKER]
White Vine!
Gum‐Gum Balloon!
Too close!
Damn.
Ahh! I really do
feel a lot better now.
Where are they?
Luffy's smell's that way.
And that's Zoro's smell!
Sanji's goes this way.
What's going on?
[MARINES yelling]
[ZORO]
Dammit.
Oh, no, look over there.
[MILLIONS A]
It's them, all right.
No doubt. Kill 'em!
It looks like it's the
Baroque Works Millions.
Well, then I guess
we're stuck between
a rock and a hard place, huh.
Go on without me.
Hurry!
Okay.
[SANJI]
Hey, Usopp!
You look after Nami.
[USOPP]
Why?
Just do it. I'll take
care of the Marines.
[MARINES yelling]
Okay, I'm on it.
‐‐But, Sanji...
‐‐[SANJI] Just go!
[SANJI]
Without that smoke freak around,
they should be easy to handle.
Terribly sorry.
[SANJI yells]
[VIVI] I hope Mr. Bushido
will be all right.
Is that all, really? Pathetic.
Roronoa Zoro.
I knew we'd meet again.
[ZORO]
That voice...
I've been looking for you.
What do you think you're doing
carelessly cutting
down civilians like that?
That's low even for you!
Look, I have my own reasons
for doing it, all right?
Besides, I have
absolutely no desire
whatsoever to fight you again.
We settled our dispute
fine in Loguetown.
[TASHIGI]
We did not.
I'm not through. I haven't
even dealt you a single blow.
[ZORO]
She looks way too much like her.
And put that damn face
of yours away, will you?
[TASHIGI]
What did you say?
You're insulting me?
That's a really pathetic tactic.
I'll make you pay!
Uh‐uh. She's the one
person I can't handle.
Hold it!
[MILLIONS B]
Get back here, you rats!
[NAMI, USOPP yelling]
[MILLIONS B]
It's two of them, all right.
We're... we're okay!
Way to go, Usopp!
Look! Up ahead!
It's the entrance
to Raindinners!
And it looks like it's
in the middle of a lake.
[USOPP]
What? No one's here yet?
[MILLIONS C]
All right! Let's get 'em!
[MILLIONS D]
Like fish in a barrel.
Ah. We're screwed!
It's Zoro!
Hold on! I thought Vivi was
supposed to be with you!
She was!
Are you saying she's not here?
Not yet, but maybe she
just went inside already.
Yeah, let's go in, too.
‐‐[LUFFY yelling]
‐‐[USOPP] Luffy?
[SMOKER]
Get back here!
[ZORO]
It's that smoker guy!
Hey, you guys, let's go!
We have to run inside now!
[USOPP]
Right behind you!
[LUFFY]
So he's in there.
Then I guess that's
where I'm going!
[CROCODILE]
Oh?
Vivi and the pirates are
in town paying us a visit?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Yes.
We just received word
from the Millions
that they've arrived.
[CROCODILE chuckles]
Let's be sure to welcome them.
Very warmly.
Yes.
Listen up, Crocodile!
I'm coming for you!
And I'm about to kick
your sandy ass!
Get ready!
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[LUFFY]
Come out here, Crocodile.
I came to Alabasta
to kick your ass!
[NAMI]
Don't be an idiot!
That's not gonna
make him come out!
[USOPP] We're already fighting
someone the people love.
Do you wanna make these
customers our enemies too?
[NAMI] Without Vivi,
we don't have any idea
who Crocodile is.
Wait. Come to think of it,
where is Vivi?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Trap of Certain Defeat!
Storming Raindinners."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!