Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy left
the female-only nation
of Amazon Lily to
rescue his brother Ace
from execution by
the World Government.
With the help of
the Snake Princess, Hancock,
Luffy stowed away
on board a Navy ship
headed to the colossal prison
known as Impel Down.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the other Straw Hats,
scattered around the globe
by Bartholomew Kuma,
face struggles of their own.
[LUFFY]
The Friends' Whereabouts!
Bridging the Islands
and Vicious Vegetation!
[HANCOCK] Love-Love Beam!
I'm starting to worry that we
might not survive this trip.
You'd think they'd learn by now.
Luffy. The food
has arrived. Luffy?
Hey. Seems like we should've
reached Ace by now, huh?
[HANCOCK] No. I'm afraid
we still have a while to go.
Okay...
[gasps] Awesome! I'm starving!
[HANCOCK] Luffy.
Hm?
Would you care
for a cup of tea?
Sure, that sounds good.
Thank you. Darling.
[HANCOCK] My pleasure!
Oh. I'll just
brew some up then.
So, Luffy. Why don't
you tell me a little
about your friends--
I don't know a thing.
[HANCOCK] Of course, you don't
have to if you don't want to.
I'm just making conversation--
it's not like I'm trying
to dig into your personal life
and find out every
little thing about you.
Okay. Which one
should I start with?
Zoro. Sanji. Usopp.
There's Brook.
Franky. Nami or Robin.
[HANCOCK] Nami? Robin?
Those sound like girl's names!
[LUFFY] They are. You're
watering the table, y'know.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
you and I can't be together.
But why? Tell me why, Luffy!
Because I'm already
with Nami and Robin.
[NAMI and ROBIN giggle]
I don't care!
I won't give up that easily!
You really suck at making tea.
[gasps]
A woman?
[GIRL]
Her clothes are so strange.
She can't be from here.
[ROBIN coughs]
She's alive.
Are you okay, miss?
Well, I'm not really sure.
Where am I? It's cold.
[GIRL] You're in Tequila Wolf.
It's a country in the East Blue.
[shivers]
You're shivering. Do you
want to come back to my house?
Well, if it doesn't put
you out--yes, I would love to.
[SLAVER 420A] Keep movin'!
Pick up the pace!
[chuckles]
[ALL] Hm?
Soran! Did you go out again
without asking us?
[SLAVE WOMAN A]
Don't risk it, child!
The officers
didn't see you, right?
[SORAN] Mm.
Who's that you've
brought with ya?
[SLAVE WOMAN EYELASHES]
I don't know her.
Doesn't look like
she's from here.
I found her in the snow.
She was freezing.
She's a drifter?
It's more likely
she's a fugitive.
Well, at least
we know she's crazy.
No sane person
would wanna come here.
I can tell when I'm
not welcome someplace.
It's fine, I'll leave.
I'll take responsibility
for her, okay?
You're not the only one
who lives here, child.
What do you think
will happen if the officers
find out we're giving
shelter to a stranger?
[SORAN] I'll take the blame!
[grunts] You can't
reason with that girl.
And where do you
plan on hiding her?
She'll stay in my room.
The loft upstairs?
Ah, she'd be okay up there
for a day or two, I suppose.
Don't tell me you're serious.
We should turn her in before
it's too late and we get caught.
It's already too late--
we've let her into our house.
Might as well show her
some courtesy at this point.
Uh! You do what you want,
but keep me out of it.
[SORAN] Thank you.
Don't go thinkin'
this is for good.
She's leaving once
her wounds are healed.
You know she's better off
getting out of this country
as quick as she can.
[ROBIN]
They seem like kind people.
Yeah.
[ROBIN] Thanks.
Something about you
smells so nice.
[ROBIN] I'm not wearing
any kind of perfume.
Maybe it's the scent
of the outside world.
What do you mean by that?
Well, you see, I haven't
left here since I was born.
Are you some kind of traveler?
Did you come here
from a warm climate?
[ROBIN] Yes. I've been
traveling the world on a ship.
Is it a big ship?
What's the island
you came from like?
And were there any beautiful
birds or flowers there?
And was there--
[ringing]
Soran! Time to work,
break's over!
Hurry up and get ready!
I have to go work now.
You work this late at night?
[SORAN] We work all day every
day and all night every night.
You should get some rest now.
But I'd love to hear about
your travels when I get back.
Sure. I'll be
right here... Soran.
Bye.
[ROBIN] I don't think I can
make it in time to help them.
[distant clanging]
[door opens]
[gasps]
[SORAN]
I'm sorry, did I wake you?
[ROBIN]
Soran, you're covered in dirt.
It's okay.
Just what kind of work
do they make you do here?
We're trying
to build a bridge.
[ROBIN] What?
This country is nothing
but one giant bridge.
[distant clanging]
[SORAN] It's eventually
supposed to connect
a bunch of islands together.
The construction has been
going on for centuries now.
At least that's
what the officers say.
For whole centuries?
If you don't mind,
do you think you can tell me
about where you're from?
[ROBIN] You mean my home?
The island I'm from is now gone.
But my true home is on the sea
and I've traveled
to countless islands.
[gasps]
[ROBIN] Soran?
Mm!
[ROBIN] What're these?
They're islands
from around the world.
I drew them all
from my imagination
since I've never been
outside Tequila Wolf.
[SORAN] But whenever
I'm drawing one,
it makes me feel like I'm there,
like I'm actually
visiting that island.
And I forget all about
being stuck here!
Wow. These are great!
[gasps] Sky Island!
Wait, you know it?
So you mean it's real?
[ROBIN] Yes.
[SORAN] And you went there?
Will you tell me all about it?
Of course. Now let's see...
I guess I should start
at the beginning of our trip.
Wow! Amazing!
I knew the outside world
was incredible,
but I'd never
met anyone who'd seen it!
In this place,
they push us around every day
and they work us
until we're so exhausted
that we just collapse.
But now that I think about it,
maybe it's not so bad--
I mean, at least
we're building something
that will help
to connect the world.
And once the big bridge
is finally complete,
everybody everywhere
will get to see
so many beautiful islands
whenever they want!
There's nothing I'd like more!
I'll travel all over the world!
[SORAN] And I'll draw pictures
of the real islands I visit!
[gasps]
That's a lovely thought.
Will you tell me about
the other places you've been?
Sure, of course.
[SLAVE WOMAN EYELASHES]
Do you mind if we listen, too?
[ROBIN] Not at all.
The woman's up in the loft.
Good job. Let's head in, men!
Hey, wait!
Don't forget we made a deal
and I held up my end
so you have to get me
out of this country!
Nobody move!
[SLAVE WOMAN 420A]
What's going on here?
[SLAVER 420A] Move it!
We've come for the stranger.
Get in our way and you will die.
What's all the noise?
Somebody ratted us out
to the officers.
They're looking for her.
What do we do?
[SLAVER 420A grunts]
You guys need somethin'?
We've got it on
good authority that you lot
are harboring a suspicious
woman in this house.
You know we can't take
any chances these days.
There are too many people
out there opposed to
the construction of the bridge.
Now turn her over!
We don't know
what you're talking about!
[SLAVE WOMAN EYELASHES] Look,
you're just wasting your time.
There's no one here,
now leave us alone!
We're exhausted.
--[SLAVER 420A] Shut up!
--[SLAVE WOMAN EYELASHES] Uh!
Are you okay?
If you refuse
to cooperate with us,
we'll have no choice
but to arrest you
and question you individually.
[whimpers]
[CAPTAIN] I take it
you're familiar with our
interrogation tactics.
Is that what you want?
[SLAVER 420B grunts]
[SLAVER 420A]
Captain, I found these.
[gasps]
[CAPTAIN] All right.
And what is this crap?
[SLAVER 420A] Islands?
Those are my drawings!
Now give them back!
[CAPTAIN] Hm. Islands, huh?
[laughs]
That is some sick sense
of irony you've got there, kid.
Give them back!
[CAPTAIN] Hm.
[CAPTAIN]
You want your drawings back?
Then you better tell us
where the woman's hiding.
What woman?
[gasps]
[CAPTAIN]
Now let's try that again.
Where is the woman hiding?
I don't know.
Do you want off Tequila Wolf?
Cooperate and
I'll get you out of here.
[CAPTAIN] Then you can see
the outside world in person.
I don't know!
I'm giving you one last
chance to fess up!
[CAPTAIN]
Tell me where she is!
[gasps]
Look! I don't know!
[CAPTAIN grunting]
[SORAN whimpers]
[CAPTAIN yells]
All you're doing is digging
an even deeper hole
for yourselves.
I'll make sure you all
rot on this bridge
for the rest of your lives!
Now take them all in
for questioning!
[CAPTAIN]
Torture them until they tell us
what we want to hear!
And I want the kid
to get the worst of it.
[SLAVER 420A] C'mon! Move!
[SORAN] Where is she?
[whistle blows]
[distant gunfire]
[BOTH] Aah!
Now Clutch.
[groans]
Ahhh!
Aah! Uh... Huh?
Uh, what's going on?
Hey, you guys?
[SLAVER 420F]
Aah! Stay back, I'll shoot!
Put your hands up!
[SLAVER 420F yells]
[whimpers]
[yells]
Please don't hurt me!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
[SLAVER 420F] Huh?
[grunts]
I got you now! She's down here!
[SLAVER 420F]
I have her in my sights! Hurry!
I need backup!
She's dangerous!
[gasps]
Why are you still here?
Didn't you hear him?
Yeah, the guy just said
he's got the woman
you've been looking for!
Why don't you quit
harassing us and go get her!
I think you've worn out
your welcome here.
[growls]
Uh, Captain?
Would you quit
standing around
and get down there
and cover him!
Yes sir!
I'm letting you
off the hook for now.
But you are sorely
mistaken if you think
I'm going to forget about this!
[SLAVE WOMAN PARTED HAIR]
Have fun with that!
[CAPTAIN yells]
[CAPTAIN groans]
[SLAVER 420B]
Sir? Are you all right?
Raaahhh!
[ALL exhale deeply]
I hope she's okay.
[SLAVER CAPTAIN] Tequila Wolf
is a nation of laborers.
[SLAVER 420G] Pull! Pull!
[SLAVES grunting]
[SLAVER CAPTAIN] The people we
have constantly toiling away
to build this bridge
are criminals
from all over the world.
Either that or they're
citizens of countries
that refused to ally
with the World Government.
[wheezes]
[SLAVES grunting]
[SLAVER 420H]
Get up! On your feet!
[SLAVER CAPTAIN]
In short, they're slaves.
How much longer
until the bridge is complete?
[SLAVER CAPTAIN]
I have no idea.
But it's been under constant
construction for 700 years now.
700? But for what purpose?
[SLAVER CAPTAIN] You don't need
to concern yourself with that.
Now that you're here
we're putting you to work
so the only thing
you need to worry about
is making the bridge. Got it?
[NARRATOR]
Like a flower blossoming
in the middle of the ocean,
we now arrive
at the Bowin Islands.
[USOPP] Let's get this
exploration party going!
I will of course be
the leader of the group.
The fearless Sniper King, Usopp!
And here's my loyal
and trusty crew!
Enh! Enhhh!
Who sadly
couldn't be here today.
[USOPP] I give up!
Where the hell am I?
Ugh! I don't even know
if my friends are alive.
Without me, it's doubtful
they will be for long.
In fact, I bet they're crying
my name right this instant.
Mhm! They're lost without me!
I better hurry up
so I can go save them!
[rustling]
[screams]
Just the wind.
[clears throat]
The one-man crew of
the Usopp exploration party
must remain ever
vigilant and watchful. Indeed.
Let's go, Usopp. Let's go!
Mmmm....
[panting]
Uh, I can't take this.
I'm lonely.
Hey! Is anyone out there?
out there... out there...
Oh please, don't let this
be a deserted island!
Oooh! Oh, no, it's the
My-Heart-Will-Stop-Beating-
if-I'm-Left-Alone-Syndrome!
Collapse.
[birds chirping]
[whimpers]
[USOPP] Hey! There's
gotta be someone out there!
Don't be shy,
come out and say hello!
Ah! I knew it!
How are ya?
[growls]
[screams]
You're rather energetic today!
[shouting, yelps]
[yells]
[USOPP] Eeeh!
[USOPP yells]
[BUG groans]
[MAN] Aaa--ooh, oooh!
[birds chirping]
[USOPP gasps]
Huh?
[USOPP] Hm?
[MAN] Gonna eat that?
Are you kidding?
But you saved my life so
you can eat whatever you want!
Thank you, whoever you are!
[MAN] My name is Heracles'n.
[USOPP] Wow. That's a
pretty cool name ya got there.
[HERACLES] Really? Think so?
[USOPP chuckles]
I'm Usopp! Nice to meet ya.
[USOPP]
Ooh! Is this thing edible?
I've never seen
this kind of fruit before.
[HERACLES]
Sure, Usopp'n. It's fine.
By the way, you can call me...
Heracles'n!
Yeah, okay.
Heard ya the first time.
Well it definitely
smells delicious, at least.
Hmmm. Maybe I'll just
give it a little lick.
[USOPP hollers]
[USOPP shrieks]
[PLANT roars]
[HERACLES] Usopp'n!
What the--?
Was that thing a plant?
And did it really
just try to eat me?
[HERACLES] Sure.
They are man-eating plants'n.
Man-eating?!
[USOPP yells]
Whoa!
[sighs]
[PLANT growls]
[USOPP yelling]
What the hell is this place?
[HERACLES] This is the
Swindling Forest, Glinston!
[USOPP] Help. Help! Help!
[HERACLES] By the way,
you can call me... Hera--
[NARRATOR]
Zoro arrives at an old castle
inhabited by Perona.
Although he is eager
to return to his crew,
Perona seems strangely intent
on keeping him there.
Meanwhile, Brook is
mistaken for Satan
when a group of cultists
believe they've
summoned the dark lord.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece,
The Friends' Whereabouts!
A Negative Princess
and the King of Demons!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!