[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!♪
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
its people have
taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other.
Crocodile's plan was
finally being carried out.
Bon Clay transformed
into a false King Cobra
and attacked Nanohana.
[NARRATOR]
In response,
Koza spurred the rebel
army into action.
Meanwhile, Vivi escaped
the perilous trap
that Luffy and the others had
fallen into at Raindinners.
Her only hope for saving her
friends was to find Sanji.
Will Alabasta fall?
Or will it find true peace?
Moment by moment, the sands
of the hourglass of fate
run down toward the final hour.
[CHOPPER]
That's right! Keep chasing me!
I'm Mr. Prince!
[LUFFY] "The Key to a Great
Comeback Escape!
The Wax‐Wax Ball!"
[PEOPLE chattering]
[VIVI]
Tony's acting as a decoy?
[SANJI]
Don't worry. He'll be fine.
He's buyin' us some time.
But we've gotta hurry.
Take me to Luffy and the others.
[VIVI] Sure, but, Sanji,
I thought you got shot earlier.
[SANJI]
Hm?
[MILLIONS A groans]
Uh, hello?
We've got him, sir.
And don't worry.
He won't be going anywhere.
[CROCODILE]
So, where are you? Speak up!
I'm at the front
of the big casino
with the alligator
on top in Rainbase.
Raindinners.
[SANJI]
Nice job.
That was such a
convincing performance
that your boss is on the way.
You should really consider
a career in acting.
[MILLIONS A chuckles]
[MILLIONS A]
Really? Gee, thanks!
Hey, um, you're gonna
let me go now, right?
No, sir.
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[MILLIONS A groans]
[MILLIONS A]
Yeah, I didn't think so!
[SANJI]
More of those Millions creeps
are checking out our handiwork.
Better get going.
You know what to do, Chopper?
[CHOPPER]
Mmm‐Hmm.
I'm gonna do whatever
I can manage.
[SANJI]
Right.
I'm counting on you.
[crunch]
[MILLIONS B]
Huh?
Who are you supposed to be?
[CHOPPER]
My name is Mr. Prince.
[MILLIONS B] Did you see who
did this to our friends?
Hey, wait a minute!
Was it you? Did you
take them down?
[CHOPPER]
Whatever I can manage.
[CHOPPER] Yes, I did it!
It was me! Mr. Prince!
[MILLIONS yelling]
[CHOPPER]
My name's Mr. Prince! Ya hear?
Mr. Prince!
What the hell?
A‐A guy.
He was called Mr. Prince.
I see.
[PEOPLE screaming]
The bridge collapsed.
[MAN A] The bridge to the
casino just collapsed!
[SANJI] That's how Chopper
and I did it, more or less.
But is Tony going
to be all right?
[SANJI]
Yeah.
[SANJI] That little furball's
got a few tricks up his sleeve.
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[TOWNSFOLK A] I heard something
happened at Raindinners.
[TOWNSFOLK B]
They say the bridge collapsed.
[CROCODILE]
You bastard.
I know you're here
somewhere, Mr. Prince.
[CROCODILE]
When I find you,
I'm going to introduce
you to my hook.
[CHOPPER]
Please don't notice me,
please don't notice me,
please don't notice me.
‐‐[USOPP screaming]
‐‐All of us are gonna die!
That water's gonna be up to
our necks any minute now!
[NAMI]
Hey! Hey!
Hey, you stupid gator!
If you're hungry,
come and get me!
[USOPP] Are you nuts, Nami?!
What are you doing?!
[wheezes]
I'm trying to lure that
gator in close enough
so he'll bite this cage apart!
[USOPP]
Hey, that's not a bad idea!
Yeah, come and get us,
ya stupid banana!
Ya rotten banana!
Look! I told ya, that
thing's not a banana.
It's an alligator with a banana
growing out of its head.
But it's called a bananagator.
Let me explain it to you.
You've heard of the
monkey dance, right?
Ya dumb banana!
Shut up and listen for a second!
Okay, look, there's a dance
called the monkey
dance, you follow?
Even though it's got
the word "monkey" in it,
it isn't an actual monkey.
Gah! Don't touch those bars!
How do you know
they're not bananas
if you haven't eaten one?
Watch out!
[roars]
[LUFFY, USOPP, NAMI screaming]
[USOPP]
The cage is too tough!
[LUFFY]
The banana didn't even dent it!
[USOPP]
Vivi! Please hurry!
[SMOKER]
Hey, Straw Hats.
We're all about to die! How can
you just sit there like that?!
You should be trying to
get us outta here, too!
[SMOKER] Tell me something.
How much do you guys know?
What exactly is Crocodile after?
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Huh?
[SMOKER]
The woman at Crocodile's side,
did you know the
World Government's
had a sizeable price on
her head for 20 years?
As I recall, over
70 million Berries.
[USOPP]
Seventy million? Holy moly!
But why is it so much?!
That's almost as much
as Crocodile had!
[SMOKER] The moment
those two joined forces,
this insurrection became more
than just a simple coup.
If they're not stopped
here and now,
this could very well
turn into something
the whole world will
get dragged into.
[NAMI]
The whole world?
Wait, what do you mean?
This is starting to sound
a little far‐fetched.
I don't care if
all that is true.
[NAMI, USOPP]
Huh?
I don't need any other excuses!
I'm still gonna kick
that guy's ass!
[SMOKER]
I see.
So, how do you intend
to get outta here?
[LUFFY screams]
It's all the way up my legs now!
[USOPP]
Help! Help! I'm drowning!
Ugh... All of a sudden,
I feel a little...
No! Hey! Wait!
Just tough it out! Vivi said
she'd bring some help back!
[NAMI] Vivi, I know you're
doing all you can,
but please hurry back!
[ZORO]
Dammit!
If only my
swordsmanship were better,
I could cut through
this stupid cage.
We'd be free!
[SANJI] It's really impolite to
make a lot of noise at mealtime
like you were doin'.
[ZORO]
Huh?
[SANJI]
I'll teach you how to behave!
Bad Manner Kick Course!
[SANJI]
Hey, guys. Been waiting long?
[BOTH]
Yay! It's Mr. Prince!
We're finally gonna
get outta here now!
Thank you.
Well, don't just stand there!
Find the key and
get us outta here!
[SANJI]
Nami, my dear!
Do you love me now? Huh?
Well? Nami, my sweet...
[NAMI]
Um, sure!
And I'll love you even more
if you hurry up
and open this cage!
[ZORO]
He is one lovesick idiot.
Vivi! All right! Way to go!
[SANJI] More diners
with bad manners, huh?
[LUFFY]
Get 'em, Sanji!
Smash those weird
bananas into pudding!
Don't worry, I'm gonna
teach these bananas
some proper table
manners all right.
Since theirs are so bad
they attacked a lady,
I'll do it the hard way.
I'll take my sweet
time doing it, too,
'cause nobody does that to Nami.
[USOPP] We don't have
any time for chivalry!
One second strikes!
No, make that one
instant strikes!
[SMOKER] The third one who
just came in has the key.
[LUFFY] Hey, how do you
know that, Smokey?
[SMOKER] Guess your ears
aren't as big as your mouth.
Isn't that one's growl
the same as the one
who swallowed the key?
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[LUFFY chuckles]
Uhh, I can't really tell.
[CROCODILE] Smart thinking,
collapsing the bridge
to buy time like that.
There're obviously more Straw
Hats here than we'd thought.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY] So that was
all done to lure us away
so they could
rescue their friends?
[CROCODILE]
Of course it was.
[BOTH]
Key!
[LUFFY]
There it is! Get it!
[ZORO]
Huh?
[USOPP]
Hey, wait a minute!
[LUFFY]
That doesn't look like the key!
[MR. 3]
Wax‐Wax Ball...
...Release!
[gasps]
[NAMI, LUFFY, USOPP]
What the‐‐?
Yes! Water! At last!
It's a miracle!
Hey! It's him!
Mr. 3!
Mr. 3?
What was he doing in the
belly of a bananagator?
Woo‐hoo!
I'm alive again!
I thought I was a goner.
Stupid Crocodile!
So you thought you
could get rid of me,
but you didn't try hard enough!
The moment I was swallowed,
I used the last of my power
to create that Wax‐Wax Ball!
That was how I survived!
Huh?
A key?
[LUFFY, USOPP, NAMI shouting]
[MR. 3]
Hm?
[MR. 3 screams]
[MR. 3]
Not you guys again!
[MR. 3] Wait. Why do
they want this key so bad?
Hold on.
A room that's surrounded by
and flooding with water.
A cage full of Straw Hats.
And they're screaming
like mad for this key.
Now I see what's happening here.
Mr. 3, I presume?
[MR. 3 screams]
[MR. 3 pants]
How'd you know who I was?
Well, your hairstyle
gave it away.
I'll take the key. Toss it here.
[MR. 3]
Hm?
[chuckling]
Sure thing! Here goes!
[SANJI]
Hey.
[ALL scream]
[MR. 3 laughing]
[MR. 3]
I don't know who you are,
but if you want
the Straw Hats out,
you're no friend of mine!
You want the key, go find it!
Good luck!
You'll need it with all
those alligators around!
Trust me, I know!
Jerk.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
So what happens if their rescuer
is able to ascertain which
bananagator swallowed the key?
[CROCODILE]
Hmph. Well...
Even if they were
able to get the key,
it wouldn't make any difference.
I've had the real one with me.
The key in the gator's
belly's a fraud,
but that's for me to know
and them to find out.
You're bad.
[MR. 3] Better find it soon;
that water's rising.
That bastard.
That was a dirty move,
even for that creep!
We're running
outta time! Hurry!
Lousy, good‐for‐nothing wax guy.
[USOPP]
Huh?
Wait a minute, Sanji!
He might be good
for something,
like using those wax
powers to make a key!
You're right.
[MR. 3]
Huh?
[MR. 3 groans]
[SANJI]
Nice work, Candle Man.
Now there are just two
more things to do.
[chuckles]
[MR. 3]
Uh?
[screams]
Let's go. We have to hurry.
Right, we've gotta
stop the rebels
before they attack Alubarna.
We should be able to get
out through that hallway.
There's a problem with that!
Namely, dozens of bananagators!
[LUFFY growls]
[LUFFY]
That's it?
I can take on hundreds of
those weird bananas!
Um, that problem's solved.
[VIVI] And I had so much
trouble with just one of them.
No, don't be so
hard on yourself.
Those two just have crazy,
abnormal strength!
Yeah?
I'd be even stronger if
I wasn't soaked right now!
Ah! This place is falling apart!
[SANJI]
Yeah, we can see that!
[USOPP] Oh, no! The
passageway's crumbling, too!
[SANJI] We've gotta get
out of here! Right now!
[LUFFY screaming]
All right, Straw Hats!
Time to pay!
If the bananagators haven't
finished you off yet,
you'll wish they had by
the time I'm done with you!
Huh?
[CROCODILE]
This can't be.
[growling]
Hey, you alive there? Luffy?
Usopp! Please! Wake up!
Come on! Just kick your
legs or something!
Hey, help us pull
you outta here!
Jeez, why would a pirate
want Devil Fruit powers
if it means he can't swim?
[SANJI]
What? Smoker?
Hey, Zoro, what are you doing?
In case you forgot,
that guy's our enemy!
[ZORO]
Back off!
I didn't wanna do it, but he
was about to die, that's all!
[SANJI]
Whatever.
We gotta get moving, guys.
We've lost too
much time already.
Vivi, can we still make it?
I don't know.
[SANJI]
Hey, Nami?
You still have that
perfume I bought you?
Huh? Yeah. But why?
Put some of it on, please.
'Kay.
[SANJI]
Aww, just one whiff of it
makes me swoon like
a schoolboy in love!
[ZORO] Not to mention make
you act like an idiot.
[SMOKER]
Roronoa!
Why did you save my life?
[LUFFY] Zoro! Quick!
You gotta save Smokey!
[ZORO]
What? He's our enemy!
He can take care of himself!
[LUFFY]
No, he can't!
He's got Devil Fruit powers
so he can't swim!
He'll drown if you
don't help him!
[ZORO]
For cryin' out loud, Luffy,
do I really have to do this?
Ah, jeez!
All I did was follow my
captain's orders. That's it.
So, wouldn't read too much
into it if I were you.
It was one of his crazy
whims. Pay it no mind.
[SMOKER] Then you wouldn't
have any gripes with me
carrying out my duties
and arresting you, right?
See? I knew this was a bad idea.
This is what you get
for saving a Marine.
[MARINE A] They're here?
The Straw Hat Pirates?
[MARINE B]
Yessir, and it looks like
they have Captain
Smoker surrounded!
[MARINE A]
Not for long they won't!
[MARINES]
Yeah!
Yeah! All right!
Full speed ahead to Alubarna!
Where's Crocodile?
Let me at 'em!
[NAMI]
Finally awake, huh?
[LUFFY growls]
[LUFFY gasps]
You want some of this?
Bring it on!
Agh! It's Smoker!
Luffy, forget it! Let's just
get outta here! Come on!
I should. But you
just saved my life.
[MARINE A]
This way! Hurry!
Go.
[SMOKER]
This is the only time
I'm letting you Straw
Hats off, got it?
When we next meet,
it's gonna be as enemies.
[MARINE B]
There they are!
[MARINES yelling]
[MARINE B]
Get 'em!
[laughs]
[MARINE A] Reinforcements have
arrived, Captain Smoker.
Hold on!
Don't let them escape!
[MARINE B]
Cut 'em off!
Well, that's our cue. So, Vivi,
which way to Alubarna?
That way! Due east
across the desert!
[MARINE A]
They're running! After them!
Luffy, c'mon! What are you
doing? Aren't you coming?
Yeah.
[MARINE A]
They won't escape us, men!
[MARINES]
Yeah!
[chuckles]
Hey. You're not such
a bad guy, Smokey!
[SMOKER]
Huh?
[chuckling]
[growls]
[SMOKER] Would you get the
hell outta here, Straw Hat?
[LUFFY laughing]
[ZORO]
Heh.
[MARINE A]
Don't worry, Captain Smoker!
We won't let those
pirates get away!
[USOPP] Hurry! Those Marines
are hot on our heels!
[LUFFY]
All right, guys!
We got lots to do so
we're not gonna stop
till we get to Alubarna!
Are you with me?
[SANJI, USOPP, ZORO, NAMI, VIVI]
Yeah!
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[NAMI]
It's Crocodile!
[CHOPPER]
Ah! He's come after us!
[LUFFY]
I can handle him alone!
You guys go on ahead!
[SANJI]
That idiot!
[ZORO] Keep moving!
We've gotta get to Alubarna!
[USOPP]
We're leaving him behind?
[VIVI]
Luffy! Be careful!
We'll be waiting for
you in Alubarna!
[LUFFY]
Right!
On the next One Piece!
"Merciless Mortal Combat!
Luffy vs. Crocodile!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!