[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
This isn't the exit.
It's the entrance!
[laughing]
[LUFFY]
Sky island!
Heso.
[PAGAYA]
Gang way!
Stopping this thing
is a bit of a trick!
[yelping]
[groaning]
[PAGAYA] My goodness.
I-Is everyone all right?
You're the one who crashed!
[NAMI] Riding a waver
requires finesse, Luffy!
[laughs]
Oh, Nami, you're a
vision riding that waver!
That's incredible!
I can't believe it!
This is her first time?
Yeah! How come she can
do it and I can't?
Hey, guys. Any of you
know where Nami is?
I'm worried. Do you
think she's okay?
I have my concerns, but I can't
say one way or the other.
Uh, what're you talkin' about?
In the clouds, there's a
place called the Upper Yard
that no one is ever
allowed to step foot on.
It's not too far away.
[USOPP] What's so bad
that no one can ever
go over to this island?
Is it full of monsters?
It's sacred ground.
Sacred ground?
But it's so much
more than just that.
It's the island...
where God lives.
[LUFFY]
"The Forbidden Sacred Ground!
The Island Where God Lives
and Heaven's Judgement!"
There's actually a God?!
And he lives on an
island up here
that no one's
allowed to walk on?
[CONIS]
Right.
You mean the God? The same one
from all the old stories?
And he actually lives on the
island next door to you?
He does.
I'm sure that everyone
noticed the big sign
that said "Godland Skypiea."
That means this land is ruled
by the almighty God Eneru.
God's name is Eneru?
He knows and sees everything.
He's truly omniscient.
[USOPP]
Everything?
He keeps his all-seeing eyes
focused on everyone. Always.
For real?
Like right now?
[CONIS]
Oh, yes.
[screams]
I hate it when people stare
at me and I can't see them!
"God," huh...
Wait, you mean, you don't
believe in God? But why not?
Well, for me, it's not
a matter of belief.
I don't see proof of it
one way or another.
And to be honest,
I don't really care to.
But if you want to, go ahead.
It's not up to me to deny
anyone their little beliefs.
So, Conis, if this guy Eneru
lives in the Upper Yard,
and it's so close, then you must
have set eyes on him before.
Absolutely not. It's
forbidden to go there.
The Upper Yard is sacred ground
and a place only for
our God to rest.
I'm sorry.
[NAMI] I can't get over
the size of those trees.
Wait a minute.
So they do have earthen
ground up here.
I see.
A place we're not allowed to
go to no matter what, huh?
Ah!
I've seen that look in
your eyes before, Luffy,
and it always gets
us into trouble!
When the lady says
we can't go there
because it's sacred or whatever,
that's exactly what she means!
We cannot go there!
I am not letting you drag me
down with you this time!
No. Hey. Heh.
I understand we're not
supposed to go there.
[chuckles]
Come on!
You really think I'm the kinda
guy who would do that? Heh.
[STRAW HATS]
Yes. Absolutely.
[LUFFY]
Hey, wait.
If this guy is God, then
shouldn't he forgive you
no matter what you do?
Walking around on some
forbidden island
doesn't seem like
a big deal to me.
No.
Breaking any law set
forth by our almighty
is nothing less than sacrilege.
[LUFFY] So I guess it
doesn't matter either way.
[CHOPPER] He'd go even if it
meant he'd die in the process.
Tell me, I assume there
are some dramatic
and vicious consequences
of entering the Upper Yard,
do you know what they are?
Yeah. I do.
What are they?
[PAGAYA] It is our belief
that if you go there,
you will not return alive.
Everyone who goes there dies?
I must admit, I am just
as worried about Nami
as all of you are.
I hope she hasn't sailed
too close to the Upper Yard.
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI]
Nami! Nami...
All right. Let's go
and find her!
We're wasting time!
[USOPP] You don't care
about saving Nami!
You just wanna satisfy
your twisted urge
to do the exact opposite
of what you've been told!
[SANJI]
Nami!
[NAMI] Those are the biggest
trees I've ever seen in my life.
They've gotta be
hundreds of years old.
That, or things grow bigger
a few miles up in the sky.
And they're so tall.
I can't even see
where they top out.
[MAN A]
I'm positive.
The treasure has got to be here.
[MAN B]
But I don't see anything.
[MAN A]
Look harder.
We didn't come here for nothing.
[MAN A]
It's close! It has to be!
[MAN B]
But where?
[NAMI]
There are people up there.
[MAN A] We're getting warmer.
Pick up the pace!
[NAMI]
The voices came from over here.
Luffy, we gotta get going.
[LUFFY] Yeah, I know.
Just gimme a second.
Fine. Don't listen to me.
But you're gonna feel awful
if something bad happens to Nami
while you're busy
stuffing your face.
The food'll be here
when we get back!
[LUFFY]
Mh-hm. I'm right behind you.
Conis, I know this guy,
and I could be here
all day waiting on him.
Could you tell me how to
get to the Upper Yard?
I gotta go help Nami.
But you don't know for sure.
[SANJI]
Hm?
About Nami.
She might just be
out on the clouds
and nowhere near the Upper Yard.
I mean...
[CONIS] I can't explain how
devastating it could be to us
to incur the wrath
of our God Eneru.
This Eneru doesn't sound like
the nicest God you
could've found.
He doesn't have to be. He's God.
[NAMI]
Huh?
What a wreck. Looks like
there's no one on board.
[NAMI]
Hmm...
Claw marks. And something
big by the looks of them.
[MAN A]
I'm positive.
The treasure has
got to be here.
[MAN B]
But I don't see anything.
[MAN A]
Look harder.
We didn't come here for nothing.
It's close! It has to be!
Wait, those voices are
coming from that shell.
[MAN A]
We're getting warmer.
Pick up the pace!
Crazy. It sounds like there's
a person trapped inside.
[MAN A] We have to keep a record
of everything we find and do.
Who knows how valuable
the information could be?
I see. So this shell
can record voices.
[MAN B]
Forget this. I'm outta here.
I can't stop shaking.
I'm so scared.
Can you feel that?
That's God's anger.
[MAN A] Wait, I hear
something. What is it?
[MAN B]
It's... It's God!
[MAN B, MAN A screaming]
[NAMI]
Were they killed...
...by God?
This place, it's so creepy.
That's it. I think it's
time to get outta here.
[gasps]
[ZABO]
Help!
Somebody help me!
[LUFFY] Time to set sail
for the place of no return
that we're not supposed
to go to anyway!
[PAGAYA]
Hmm...
Ah, I'm so very sorry.
There's no headwind blowing.
If you were to set
sail at this moment,
you'd spend an extraordinary
amount of time
getting to the Upper Yard.
[LUFFY]
What?
[USOPP] So, what's an
extraordinary amount?
It's exponentially longer
than it would take
if your ship was powered
using our dial energies.
But it's not.
That's real nice,
but we need a number.
Sorry. Only the wind
knows your answer.
Oh, of course! The wind!
The cloud...
Old man, you gotta know a
faster way to get us there
other than just sitting
here and waiting
for the wind to pick up.
[USOPP] See, Luffy!
It doesn't matter what we do!
You're always gonna find
a way to put me in danger!
I can't live like this!
[LUFFY]
What's your problem?
[USOPP]
I'm nervous.
[whistling]
Oh, no!
[HOLY THE DOG roars]
[HOLY THE DOG whines]
[gasps]
Bastard. He took my prey.
[NAMI]
Those voices. Those sounds.
What were they?
[laughing]
[SHURA]
Just give up!
[SATORI]
You should do the same.
This boy is mine! Ha-ha!
Not if I can help it!
[SATORI] Oh, but it doesn't
look like you can!
[SATORI laughs]
Wait. What the--?
Who are they?
Something tells me
I don't wanna find out.
What's going on?
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
Finally, we have someplace
dangerous to go!
I can't sit around on this beach
and wait for the wind
to pick up any longer!
Hey, Luffy! What's that
thing you're carrying?
[yelling]
Oh, no! That's not that
old broken waver, is it?
You'll kill yourself!
[LUFFY]
Here I come!
[BOTH scream]
[ZORO]
What an idiot.
[USOPP]
How could he possibly not know
that was going to happen?
[LUFFY]
Help me!
So, uh, does anyone
wanna save him?
[ZORO, USOPP, SANJI]
Let him drown!
Man, you are such a
pain, you know that?
[PAGAYA] Hmm. So this is
your old waver, huh?
You should take
better care of it.
It's not ours. We found
it like that that.
[PAGAYA] Would you like me
to take a look at it?
Assuming it's fixable, I should
be able to do that for you.
How would you know
how to fix it?
I'm an engineer that
specializes in dial ships,
so I should know.
Yeah? Really? Then what
are you waitin' for?
Uh.
Get to work, old man!
[WYPER]
Eneru.
Leave this one to me.
He's my prey.
Oh. So you have the itch
to compete, do you?
Well, you'll be happy to know
that I would enjoy fighting you.
To kill my boredom!
[PURPLE VULTURE caws]
Heh. Very funny Shura.
We'll see how confident you are
after I feed you and your
ugly friend to my pet dog!
[SATORI]
Oh-ho! I sense a confrontation!
Too bad it's between
a couple of weaklings.
[laughs]
[GEDATZ]
Speak for yourself.
[gasps]
What the--?
You, down there, help!
Please, give me a ride! Please!
You want a ride? But this
is a one person boat.
Please help me!
I came here from
another sky island
in search of some
missing treasure!
But I don't care
about that anymore!
I just wanna get
out of here! Please!
Oh, I can't. There's no room.
Either give me the boat
or I'll slice you up!
[screams]
[ZABO]
Guerilla!
No.
[gasps]
[WYPER]
Is this Eneru's doing?
How dare you harm Vearth!
[WYPER yells]
[NAMI screaming]
[OHM] Get some water
dials down here now!
The fire's spreading!
[MCKINLEY]
Form up. Salute!
[WHITE BERETS]
Heso!
Good day. Heso!
What are the White
Berets doing here?
Oh, no, something
must've happened.
You are all warned to
use extreme caution!
I've received word
that illegal entrants
have infiltrated Skypiea
through Angel Beach today.
There are reportedly
seven suspects!
But do not worry!
You can help with our
search and investigation
by reporting all
suspicious activity!
Leave it to the White Berets!
[WHITE BERETS]
White Berets!
[GEDATZ]
Did you see that?
It appeared as if he was talking
to someone in the water.
[SATORI]
He was probably delusional.
[SHURA] Would someone
please shut that dog up?
[SATORI] He was most likely
begging for his life.
[SATORI laughs]
[OHM] Why did Eneru take
care of that guy himself?
Isn't that why he sent us
here in the first place?
[GEDATZ]
We probably ran out of time.
[SATORI]
Ran out of time?
[GEDATZ] Yet another
group of illegal entrants
have already
infiltrated Skypiea.
[SHURA]
Again?
[GEDATZ] Old lady Amazon
informed us that it's a ship
with seven Blue Sea
dwellers on board.
[NAMI]
Seven Blue Sea dwellers?
That's probably us!
We're here illeagally?
But if you wish to proceed,
you must first pay
the entrance fee
of one billion
extols per person.
That is the law.
[NAMI] Because we didn't pay
the entrance fee? No way!
The people who were on
that abandoned boat...
And that guy I just saw.
Did he enter illegally, too?
Because if that's true,
I don't want that bright
flash of light coming for me
and frying me to death.
[SHURA] Seven Blue Sea dwellers
should be a cake walk for us.
[OHM]
Seven heads.
Looks like one of us is
gonna have to share.
[NAMI] What the heck is
happening on this island?
And who are those people?
[NAMI]
This is crazy!
I need to get back to
the others to warn them.
I just hope I get to them
before it's too late.
[CHOPPER chuckling]
Beat this one, Usopp! Look!
[chuckles]
I don't think that'll
be a problem!
See? My cloud sculpture's so
good it should be in a museum!
[USOPP laughs]
[CHOPPER]
That's amazing!
That's the worst looking
art I've ever seen!
This is what I think of
your uninspired work!
Nami could be in
danger right now
and you're playing around
in the clouds like a child!
How dare you!
I hope your favorite
sculpting hand rots off!
[LUFFY]
So can you fix it?
[PAGAYA] I've never seen
parts like these before.
Come on, just fix it already!
[PAGAYA] I'm sorry,
but until I have a chance
to look at this closer,
I don't know if I can fix it.
Will you at least try?
[PAGAYA]
Yes, of course.
Huh?
Looks like we have company.
[MCKINLEY]
You there! On the beach!
Don't move!
Does he mean us?
[SANJI] Hey, uh...
why are they crawling?
[USOPP]
Who knows?
I mean, they've
obviously got issues.
[CHOPPER] Because they're
crawling around like crabs?
[MCKINLEY]
White berets, halt!
[WHITE BERETS]
Heso!
[CONIS]
Heso.
[PAGAYA]
Heso, gentlemen.
[SUU]
Suu-suu.
Speak our language!
We can't understand you.
What are they? Soldiers?
Usopp said they have issues.
Well, look what we have here.
You must be the
Blue Sea dwellers
who have illegally entered the
sovereign land of Skypiea!
[ALL]
Huh?
Prepare to have the weight
of Heaven's Judgment
brought down upon you!
Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear-blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...
[ZORO] How may different degrees
of crimes are we guilty of?
[CONIS] The ones that
should concern you
are fifth degree crimes,
because that's when
you'll be banished to the
land of the drifting clouds.
[USOPP]
So what? Big deal.
[LUFFY] Sounds fun. I'll take
a free vacation any day.
[CONIS] But you'll die!
It's a death sentence!
[NAMI, CHOPPER, USOPP]
Death sentence?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Already Criminals?!
Skypiea's Upholder of the Law!"
I'm gonna be the
King of the Pirates!