Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Our reinforcements
pulled it together after all.
And just in time, too.
Dying alone isn't
the answer, Robin.
No one should have to face that.
You don't have to
sacrifice yourself.
You don't have to suffer.
It doesn't make sense to
sacrifice so much for me!
So why? Tell me!
"Parting Builds a
Man's Character!
Sanji and Chopper."
What happened to your leg?
You had to have known that
without that leg you'd
never be a pirate again.
That's right.
You old fool. Why'd you help me?
It doesn't make sense to
sacrifice so much for me!
So why? Tell me!
Because.
For my entire life I've
had the same dream as you.
The All Blue.
But your men said
that it doesn't exist.
Of course it does!
Never mind them.
When the time comes,
head to the Grand Line.
That's where the
All Blue is sure to be.
My days as a pirate are done.
But you have your
whole life to find it.
Don't die now!
Get up! C'mon old man!
Don't you dare give up!
That old coot!
He gave up his leg,
so that I could live!
There's no way to
repay the old geezer
for his kindness unless
I risk my life for him!
That's how you wanna
repay your debt?
The old man didn't save you
so that you could kill yourself!
He did it so you could do
something with your life.
Not to die like a fool!
And so your big idea is
to help them attack us?
Chore Boy!
That's rough.
You alright, Chore Boy?
I'm not finished with you.
If you hadn't made me so angry,
I would have killed
you more quickly.
Dammit!
There's no way that Chore Boy
can take much more of this.
That spear is way too powerful.
No, you're wrong.
Even with a hundred
thousand more weapons,
our Chore Boy can still
bring him to his knees,
because he does not know fear.
Stand or fall. Life or death.
In a struggle for
your very existence,
you cannot have
even the slightest bit
of fear or you will be lost.
What are you talking about?
When he's fighting.
He's not afraid of anything!
Not even death!
Is it just instinct
or all a plan?
We'll know soon. If he lives.
What plan? Killing himself?
There is no doubt that Krieg
and his pirates are strong.
But Chore Boy has something
they'll never have.
Krieg may have more pirates
at his command than
anyone else before him.
He may have terrible weapons
that cause mass destruction
to everything in his path.
But he will never
have that kid's heart.
Time for me to end this.
Right now!
Now Gum-Gum!
Giant Hammer!
Wait.
Your dream is foolish.
Then again, so's mine.
Now is as good a time as any.
Why not start
my quest right now?
Sanji.
I'll be joining your
little crew on your journey
to be King of the Pirates.
You hear me?
I want to be the
cook on your ship.
All right? What do you say?
Yeah!
Of course!
This is great, Big Bro Luffy!
Woo-hoo!
We got a cook!
Now we'll get the
tasty food! We got a cook!
Super tasty awesome time!
Are you guys happy now or what?
Sorry.
Really. I'll leave now.
Ha! I don't like it!
To tell you the
truth I was hoping
to give you the boot from
this restaurant personally.
But it seems that you
don't have a problem
with straight up abandoning us.
I'm especially sorry
for making the lot of
you resort to bad acting.
Hey, wait! How'd you know?
I heard everything!
You bunch of jerks!
What?
Was stomping on
my pride the best plan
that you could come
up with? Was it?
You damn geezer!
Every little thing has
to be a fight with you.
Well I'm sick and
tired of it! Bring it on!
I have never liked children.
As a matter of fact
I hate children.
There wasn't a day passed
when I didn't regret
letting a useless little
brat like you live, Sanji.
Ha! Fine by me
you rotten old man.
Enjoy the rest of
your miserable life.
Whoa! This is a nice ship!
You sure it's okay to use her?
Of course! It's Sanji's ship!
Let's get going.
You don't need to say goodbye?
No, it's fine.
Sanji!
Take care of yourself, okay?
Chef Zeff!
Thanks, you geezer!
I'll never forget your kindness!
I owe my life to you,
old man! So thank you!
You asshole!
I'm gonna miss you so much!
I'll miss you, too!
You damn wusses!
Real men should part without
a word, let alone tears!
Let's go! Set sail!
I will see you again!
I'll come back someday!
As long as you sail with
enough faith in yourself
that you have no fear,
not even of death.
You will find the All Blue.
I'm sure of it.
All right, men!
Customers will be here soon!
Get to work already!
I know how it feels
to be alone, Robin.
I used to be the same way.
Looks like you've been shot.
We need to stop the bleeding
right away or you're dead!
Of course! Yes! Yes!
You'll be a wonderful doctor!
Doctor. I can't breathe.
I know you'll be
a wonderful doctor!
I wonder if she ever had anyone.
Someone who meant as much to
her as the Doctor did to me.
Wow, there really are some
strange creatures in this world.
I bet you've spent your
whole life all
alone with no friends.
You're a monster.
Nobody likes you,
people want to kill you,
but here you are trying
to save this country.
That's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard!
Shut up!
Even if I don't have friends,
I can still fight for
something I believe in!
And as long as the
flag flies. I will!
Hey, that's not true!
Huh?
You do have friends!
I'm your friend, reindeer! Me!
Hey, you're going
to come on our ship
and be a pirate with us! Kay?
I can't.
Sure you can, reindeer!
It's a whole lot of fun!
That's not a great argument!
I can't.
I'm not a human. I'm a reindeer!
I have antlers and
hooves, don't you see?
I even have a blue nose!
Okay. Maybe I do
want to be a pirate.
But I can't ever be one of you.
I'm not human! I'm a monster!
I can't be your friend,
and I can't become
a pirate on your ship!
You see? I'm just here
to say thank you.
I really do appreciate you
asking me to join your ship.
That was really nice,
so thank you.
I am going to stay here for now.
But if you wanted to,
you could stop by here again.
Shut up! Let's go!
Most people don't make friends
by telling someone to shut up.
That was fun!
Hey, reindeer,
can we do that again?
You idiot! We don't
have time for that!
Whew! I thought that
I was going to die.
Hey, where am I?
What's going on?
Oh, Sanji!
You're awake! You okay?
Doctor! It wasn't a fantasy
like she said, right?
You finished your work.
You accomplished your dream!
Or was that all a lie, too?
I've done it, Chopper!
My research is a success!
Did you lie because
you knew how sad
I'd be if you died
without completing it?
"Nothing is impossible for a
man who raises a pirate flag!"
Please, say it again, doctor!
All right now, young men!
Are you ready?
Yes!
Then fire!
Listen to me, Kureha.
This dust is special.
Dr. Kureha! What are you doing?
Just shut up and watch.
Doctor Kureha, all the
cannons have been fired.
Then light them up!
Look!
Ah cool!
Yeah.
Wow!
I will make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
Once my invention is perfected,
this country is
as good as saved!
This is no ordinary
red dust, Kureha.
This dust is designed
to attach itself
to the white snowflakes as
they come down from the sky.
The white snow will then
become a beautiful shade of
pink for everyone to see.
Doctor! Doctorine!
I promise you I'm not
going to shoot you, see?
My name is Hiriluk.
Doctor Hiriluk!
Tony Tony Chopper.
Cool name, huh?
Anyway, that's what
I'm gonna call you.
You're going to
become a great doctor.
I'll make sure of it!
Even if I should disappear right
now, my dream will come true.
I've had a marvelous life!
Thank you so much, Chopper.
Now.
Have a safe trip, my stupid son.
Robin. You're not
alone anymore, okay?
No matter what it takes.
We are going to save you!
Look, it's the sea train!
Let's go!
Bored.
Yeah.
If yous guys don't
bring me some meat,
I'm gonna frickin' kill ya!
"And why do you smoke
cigars", you ask me?
'Cause the air in this frickin'
world stinks, that's why!
I called yous guys here
today for one reason only.
I think it's time we made clear
who's the boss of this
town once and for all!
It's me, dumbass!
No way! Any idiot
can see it's me!
Sanjino.
A bonehead like you who
doesn't slick his hair back
isn't even qualified
to run this town.
I've got my reasons, okay?
It's slicked back
on one side, isn't it?
One side? Don't make me laugh!
That's like saying you've
only got half a pair of balls!
What?
That's the last straw!
This means war!
Why the hell are
you starting a war?
Fine then. War it is.
Make him eat lead, Usotooya.
I'm-ah gonna
take-ah out-ah Zorocia.
Usotooya failed! He's been shot!
Take out Luffione while
his men are distracted!
I'm-ah gonna
take-ah out-ah Luffione.
Chopalini failed!
He's been shot!
Know your enemy well, Namimore.
I'm-ah gonna
take-ah out-ah Sanjino!
Mamma Mia.
The Sanjino Family
has been taken out!
Where's his safe?
He sure was loaded!
Namimore failed! She's down!
Oh well, at least
broad took out Sanjino.
Robito! You're up!
Go take out Luffione.
Not interested.
What?
Zorocia has been betrayed!
He's been shot!
Whoa! They actually
shot each other!
Robita failed, too! She's down!
Hell, yeah! I'm the boss!
Now I can completely
stuff myself
with as much meat as
I want in this town!
What the hell?
Who-dah thought
meat would taste so bad
when you eat it all alone?
I'm finally realizing what
the most important
things in life is all about.
Ya know? I feel so lonely.
If this is a dream,
then I wanna wake up.
What a dream!
Who're you?
And that was a dream?