Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece.
The legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum
Fruit, sets sail to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer
numerous obstacles, they capture
the unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use
any means necessary
to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] In search of a
coating mechanic to help them
reach Fish-Man Island,
the Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago.
Before long, their mermaid
friend, Camie, was kidnapped
to be sold into slavery.
After locating her at an
auction house, Nami attempted
to avoid confrontation
by bidding on her.
[CROWD shouting, cheering]
[DISCO] All the way from Fishman
Island, the mermaid, Camie!
Camie!
They're selling her!
Do something!
I'm on it. We'll get
her back no problem.
200 million is gonna
be more than enough.
[NARRATOR] However, an
unexpected appearance
thwarted Nami's plan.
I bid 500 million!
How could this happen?
We don't have that much!
There isn't any time left!
If we don't do something now,
they'll take her away and
we'll never get her back!
[NARRATOR]
When all of a sudden...
Luffy!
Luffy, save me!
[LUFFY panting]
Camie!
I've been looking
for you everywhere!
[HACHI] Hold on, Straw Hat!
What do you think you're doing?
[NARRATOR]
Trying to hold Luffy back,
Hachi neglected to
keep up his disguise.
[RICH FEMALE PATRON 396A]
His arms! He's a fishman!
[NARRATOR]
And the Octopus Fishman was shot
by a Celestial Dragon.
[LUFFY grunts]
[inaudible]
[HACHI]
It's my fault.
I screwed up, okay?
Please don't forget your
promise. Like I said, you can't
defy the Celestial Dragons,
even if they kill someone!
[LUFFY grunts]
That's enough! Stop all that
annoying babbling, fish!
Before I shut you up for good!
How dare you. Don't
look at me like that.
You're gonna get in
really big trouble!
Straw Hat Luffy.
He's serious.
Now you're annoying me, too!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY]
Major Panic!
Desperate Struggle
at the Auction House
[LUFFY panting]
[CHARLOSS groaning]
[KNIGHT 397A]
He hit Saint Charloss.
[HACHI groaning]
[PAPPAGU whimpering]
[CAMIE gasping]
[DISCO gasps]
Cha-Charloss...
Hmph.
[KID chuckles]
[LUFFY] Sorry, everybody.
Now that I've punched this guy,
there's gonna be a navy admiral
comin' here with a warship.
I'm just pissed I didn't
get to cut him down.
You beat me to it.
[NAMI]
Hachi! Hang in there!
[HACHI] Do you know how much
trouble you guys are in now?
Eh. That's just Luffy.
What can ya do?
Nothin'.
Well. That's that.
I guess we're fightin'.
First off, we gotta get
the key to Camie's collar.
It's probably backstage.
[CHOPPER]
In the meantime.
I'll tend to Hachi's wound.
[PAPPAGU, HACHI groaning]]
[ROSWALD]
Charloss...
[SHALRIA] Dear brother!
What have they done to you?
No one has ever laid a hand
on him, not even you, Father.
[ROSWALD]
You scum!
How dare you raise
a hand to my son!
[CROWD gasping, screaming]
They angered the Dragons.
Are they crazy?
[PATRON 397A]
Run for your lives!
[PATRON 397B]
Hurry! Keep Moving!
[PATRON 397C]
Quit pushing!
[ROSWALD] Our righteous
bloodline is directly descended
from the Creators of this world!
You'll suffer for
your dissidence!
[SANJI] No one gives a damn
who you're related to!
[BLACK KNIGHT 397A] That bastard
kicked Saint Roswald!
[SANJI]
Joue! Concasse!
Hey! Get a move on, Franky!
Free Camie!
I'm on it! You just
leave it to me!
[PATRON 397C] Seize them,
guards! Capture those pirates!
[CHOPPER whimpers]
There are tons of 'em!
[MAN 394B]
Are you serious?
[GIANT 394A]
Quite the ruckus.
Sounds like somethin's
goin' down.
[RAYLEIGH]
All out. Well, that settles it.
Settles what?
[BLACK KNIGHT 397B] What kind
of fool risks their lives
to protect a lousy fish?
Gum-Gum! Whip!
[KNIGHTS groan]
[ZORO grunts]
[KNIGHTS yelp]
[BLACK KNIGHT 397B]
Gotcha now!
[ZORO]
Tatsu...
Maki!
[KNIGHTS screaming]
[FRANKY grunting]
Strong Right!
[KNIGHT groan]
Fresh fire!
[KNIGHTS screaming]
[FRANKY]
Move it, tin heads!
[SHALRIA]
Such senseless violence!
Brutal scum.
[NAMI screams]
[BLACK KNIGHT 397H]
Get back here!
No! Leave me alone!
[NAMI grunting]
[NAMI groans]
[KNIGHTS grunt]
Armor in a storm? Not so smart.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Thunder bolt tempo!
Sorry.
[ROSWALD growling]
[KNIGHTS groaning]
[FRANKY]
Heh! Yeah!
[ROSWALD growls]
[ZORO grunting]
[KNIGHTS groaning]
[ZORO growls]
[ROSWALD growls]
[groaning]
[ROSWALD] You insist on
defying us to the very end!
Why can't you just
accept your fate?
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
Battle-Axe!
Back down! Our friend
isn't for sale!
[ROSWALD] Summon the navy
admiral and the warships!
[ATTENDANT 393A gasps]
We'll make those pirates suffer!
[USOPP] Shouldn't we
be there by now?
[FISH RIDER 387A]
We're on Grove 1 now. Hold on.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Cah-lick.
[FISH RIDER 386A] Straw Hat, the
cute redhead, the young master,
the swordsman, the
exhibitionist, and the reindeer
have all arrived.
Huh? If they're all there,
then that just leaves
Robin and Brook and me!
Oh, the mighty Usopp can't
be the last to arrive!
Hurry up!
[FISH RIDER 387A]
What're you doing?
Quit thrashing around,
you moron! Stop it!
[USOPP]
I can't be last! C'mon!
Wow, the wind feels great! Wait.
[USOPP screaming]
[USOPP]
I owe you one.
[FISH RIDER 387A]
What the hell are you doing,
jumping off
mid-flight like that?
What? Your reckless
driving shook me off!
Thanks.
Happy to help.
Bye.
[BROOK] We'll see you
when you get there!
[BROOK laughing]
[USOPP screams]
Wait for me!
I should be in the
lead, you guys!
[PATRON 397D] Some suicidal
pirate hit a Celestial Dragon!
[PATRON 397E]
There's a warship on the way
from navy headquarters!
I can't believe this! Those
rude, inconsiderate pirates!
I didn't even get to
collect my slaves!
Watch where you're going!
Oh I was watching carefully.
All this money?
[RAYLEIGH] I think I can
find a more productive use
for it than trading
in someone's misery.
[LUFFY, SANJI grunt]
They keep on coming!
[SANJI]
Yeah, no kidding.
I'm gonna need a
cobbler after this.
[BLACK KNIGHT 397I]
Now you die!
[ZORO]
Duck! 36 Caliber Phoenix!
[LUFFY, SANJI grunt]
[KNIGHTS groan]
[LUFFY, SANJI]
Are you trying to kill us?!
Calm down. I told you
to duck, didn't I?
[BOTH]
Talk louder!
[DISCO whimpers]
[HACHI]
Camie!
[CAMIE]
Hatchin!
[HACHI]
Are you okay?
Those creeps didn't
hurt you, did they?
I'm okay. But you!
That Dragon shot you!
Nothin' to worry about!
C'mon, you oughta know
me better than that!
No measly bullet
can keep me down.
Just hang in there, Camie!
We're gettin' ya outta here!
Right! Hatchin! Thank you!
[KILLER]
So the rumors are true.
Yeah. He is crazy.
[LAW]
Straw Hat Luffy. 300 million.
That's some bounty.
[ROBIN]
My, we're missing the party.
Look at the entrance.
It's completely blocked.
Goodness. What a quandary.
Well then, let's
crash right through.
[FISH RIDERS]
You got it.
[USOPP] What? Can't we
just tiptoe in, instead?
[ROBIN]
Let's go.
[BROOK laughing]
[USOPP] My allergy to auction
houses is flaring up.
[CROWD screaming]
[PATRON 397E]
More flying fish?
[ROBIN]
Thanks a lot!
[FISH RIDER 388M]
Best of luck!
Cien Fleurs!
Wing!
[FISH RIDER 388A]
Take care, buddy!
[BROOK]
I'm off!
[ROBIN]
Clutch.
[MEN groan]
[BROOK groaning]
I think I fractured my spine.
Drink this.
Ah, that's right! I forgot!
Milk patches me right up
since I'm all bones!
Good as new!
Yes! Viva calcium!
It's time for feats of fancy.
[BLACK KNIGHT 397C]
Damn pirate!
[ROBIN]
Clutch.
[KNIGHTS groan]
Dammit!
Protect the mermaid!
She's my 500 mil future!
[SHALRIA] Do your jobs
and kill these pirates!
[USOPP laughs] There's
nothing to fear, friends!
The mighty Usopp has
arrived to save the day!
And you thought all was lost!
Well calm your timid hearts.
You know the hero always
arrives at the very last minute.
I am the headlining
act after all.
[USOPP gasps]
So high!
Maybe I should
just stand up here
and bravely pose a while longer.
[FISH RIDER 387A]
Get going already!
[USOPP screams]
Thanks for screwing up the
timing of my dramatic entrance!
These cretins will suffer
my wrath! I'll stuff the women
as trophies and starve the
men through a life of slavery!
[ROSWALD groans]
[SHALRIA shrieks]
You crushed Father!
Wait. That didn't
hurt that much.
[USOPP shrieks]
I'm so sorry, mister!
[BLACK KNIGHT 397D] They took
down Saint Roswald too!
You do know warships
are coming. Don't you?
[KNIGHT groans]
Usopp! Brook! Robin!
Hey, you guys
made it. About time.
Luffy! Where's Camie?
Right there! The thing is.
We gotta get that collar
off her before we can go!
We'd better hurry!
The navy is gonna
show up any minute now!
[USOPP screams]
[LAW]
I hate to tell ya this.
But the navy's already
here, Straw Hat.
Who the hell are you?
And what's with the bear?
[BEPO]
Bepo.
[LAW] You picked a
bad time to revolt.
The navy's had this place
surrounded since before
the auction even began.
They've got a base
on the archipelago, but I'm
guessing they're after someone.
[MARINE 397A] Please leave
in a calm and orderly fashion!
It's alright, we have
everything under control!
[MARINE 397B]
How's it look inside?
[MARINE 397C] We've finished
evacuating all of the patrons,
but the three Celestial Dragons
are still inside.
[MARINE 397B]
Then get them out of there!
Damn pirates! You're not
gettin' out of this alive!
[LAW] I don't know who
exactly they were hoping
to catch in here. But, I
sincerely doubt they were
expecting someone to go and
kick a Celestial Dragon's ass.
[LAW chuckles] That was a
hell of a show you guys put on.
I'm impressed, Straw Hat.
Ah. You're Trafalgar Law.
Luffy. They're pirates
just like us.
Huh? Even the bear?
[BEPO grunts]
[USOPP, BROOK whimpering]
Oh, and the guy
standing in back?
[ROBIN]
That's Eustass "Captain" Kid.
[BROOK gasps]
You mean the one who has
a higher bounty than Luffy?
[KID cackles]
[CAMIE gasps]
Enough of this.
If this worthless fish drove
them to such extremes.
I have no choice but to kill it.
[DISCO gasps]
She's not worthless!
Please! Don't!
I beg you to stop,
Saint Shalria!
Could you maybe at least
wait until the merchandise
has been paid for? I beg of you!
Please stop! Have mercy!
I just wanna be rich!
[SHALRIA]
Enough, commoner! Silence!
[DISCO gasps, grunts]
[CAMIE gasps]
Alright, fish. It's
time for you to pay.
[SANJI] Oh, crap! Camie!
[BROOK gasps]
[CAMIE whimpering]
I'm trying to aim!
[USOPP grunts]
[ROBIN grunts]
[ZORO grunts]
Now, die.
[CAMIE whimpers]
[ALL]
Camie!
Dammit! There's no time!
What? Saint Shalria?
[CAMIE whimpering]
[CAMIE gasps]
[LUFFY grunts]
[RAYLEIGH]
What'd I tell you?
[RAYLEIGH] I know a
ruckus when I hear one.
Looks like the auction's over.
I got the money I came here for.
Now guess I'll head back
to the gambling house
and throw it all away.
[GIANT 394A]
You are one messed up old man.
You got locked up just
to steal some money?
That was the plan.
And if it had worked out,
I was gonna rob
whoever bought me, too.
Ha. But I guess it
wasn't meant to be.
Oh, right, I forgot I'm out.
Time to find some more booze.
Now that I think about it.
That plan stinks. Who the
hell would spend money
on an old fart
like me for a slave?
[RAYLEIGH laughing]
Huh? Oh, boy.
I didn't realize we had
such a captive audience.
[BLACK KNIGHT 397E]
Where did that old man
and the giant come from?
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 397B] They
were supposed to be merchandise
for the auction but
they were locked up.
How in the heck did
they get out of there?
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 397B yells]
Their collars are gone!
There's no way they
could've gotten them off!
[KNIGHT 397C]
What do we do?
[BLACK KNIGHT 397F]
How should I know?
It's not our job
to capture slaves.
And we've got no chance going
up against an unshackled giant.
Ra-Rayleigh?
[PAPPAGU, CHOPPER gasp]
[CHOPPER] Wait, the Rayleigh?
The coating mechanic?
Which one is he?
Hey! Is that you, Hachi?
It sure is!
I'll be damned!
So, pal. What are
you doing here?
Did someone hurt you?
[HACHI grunts]
[RAYLEIGH] No, no, don't
speak, save your energy.
[RAYLEIGH] Hm.
[CAMIE gasps]
I see now. Plain as day.
A terrible situation.
Well, you were fighting for what
you believe is right, Hachi.
[RAYLEIGH] You must be the
good folks who stood by him.
All right.
Is he...
No way.
What? But how?
What'd you do to them?
Okay. Who is this guy?
[RAYLEIGH]
That straw hat you wear?
It suits a fearless man
like yourself quite well.
Yes. I've wanted to meet you.
Monkey D. Luffy.
[SENGOKU]
Straw Hat again?
And so close to the Holy Land!
Hasn't he given
us enough trouble?
[KIZARU] Yes, about that.
The World Nobles are the victims
this time, so we'd better
make a good show of things.
[SENGOKU]
Kizaru.
[KIZARU]
You take it nice and easy.
I'll take care of this.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece.
"Admiral Kizaru Takes Action!
Sabaody Archipelago
Thrown into Chaos".
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!