Damn you!
CP9 has finally
revealed themselves.
Their true identities are
Lucci, Kaku, Blueno, and Kalifa.
Luffy and Zoro stood up
to them in an attempt
to thwart their plans,
but were easily defeated
by Lucci and his
Cat-Cat fruit powers.
CP9 discovered that Franky
was actually Cutty Flam,
who most likely
holds the blueprints
for the ancient weapon Pluton.
Oh, did you just say hand?
Franky challenged them,
but was no match for the
power of Lucci and CP9.
Now that hurt.
All right, now time
for some payback.
We won't leave 'til we
get what we're after.
Make this easy on yourself.
There ain't no
blueprints in here!
Stay back!
Dammit! Where am I?
Oh, come on!
Not again! Stupid walls!
I have to hurry!
All right. Just as planned.
That's what the
government did to us.
They used your creations
to hurt a lot of people.
People we care about!
And now they're gonna
put the blame on us.
They want to back
Tom into a corner
so they can get
those blueprints.
After all this
you still think your hands
don't have blood on them?!
If Tom gets taken away,
if he hangs for this.
I swear on my life.
I will never forgive you!
Never! You unders--
Stop it!
Tom!
It's not his fault,
don't blame him.
He didn't do this.
You still believe that, after
everything that happened?!
Oh, no...
This is... This is one of
the special harpoons I made!
Once it pierces its target,
you can't pull it out!
I'm so sorry!
Haha. Don't apologize!
It's barely even
a scratch! Heh.
Over there! We found them!
Tom's been injured!
Wait, why is he hurt?
Weren't they the ones
behind the attack?
It doesn't make any sense!
The townspeople, they're here.
Now then.
I believe this is the part
where you come along quietly.
Damn you, Spanda!
Spandam, you fool.
Now let's get going,
you criminals.
The Day the Sea
Train Cried!"
These are the culprits
behind the attack!
Rest easy, everyone!
We, the men of CP5, have
destroyed their attack ships.
They'll cause
no more trouble.
I'm sure the judge would
have acquitted him
of those old charges today.
If so, then why did he
do something like that?
He was friends with
the King of the Pirates.
Who knows what
he's capable of?
Pleased to meet you,
your honor.
My name is Spandam.
I'm with CP5.
A pleasure.
And thanks, you saved us.
We can take over the
investigation from here,
if you don't mind.
We'll give them a
full interrogation.
Just try talking your
way out of this one.
The trust they had in
you has been shattered.
Soon, those blueprints for the
ancient weapon will be mine!
--Gerro, gerro!
--How could this happen?
First off, about the Sea Train.
Magnificent work.
With its help, Water 7 will
continue to grow and flourish.
For that, on the previous charge
of building Gold Roger's ship,
your acquittal today had pretty
much already been decided.
Knowing that, why in the
world would you commit
such a heinous crime
and erase that opportunity?
Please, explain yourself.
That's a lie!
It wasn't Tom or any of us
that attacked the Judicial Ship!
It was that
idiot, Spandam!
He's the one responsible!
Sure it was!
He's not serious, is he?
What kind of crap
is he trying to pull?
Why would a government agency
like CP5 attack a Judicial Ship?
There's no way!
You're gonna have to
come up with a better lie
than that, Mr. Apprentice.
Hahahah! Your name is
Cutty Flam, correct?
I believe that was the name
we took down from you
when we caught you red handed
on board one of those
treacherous raid ships.
And correct me if
I'm mistaken,
but weren't those
very same raid ships
all made by your company?
Ships that would do
such a horrible thing.
Something so awful,
are no longer my ships!
Tom tore off his chains!
He's on a rampage!
Take aim!
He just hit him.
Tom has never hit Franky before.
What'd you do that for?!
They are no longer
your ships, huh?
Don't you ever say that again!
What's wrong with saying that?!
I wish I'd never made them!
If those ships didn't exist,
then nobody would
have gotten hurt!
When a ship is built,
no matter what type
it's neither good nor evil.
I don't care what kind of ships
you choose to make for
the rest of your life.
Remember, even if the ships
you build hurt someone,
even if they destroy the world.
Even if no one else does,
their creator must love
them unconditionally.
The one who made them
must never deny them!
Don't place the
blame on the ships!
You must be proud.
Of every ship
you've ever created!
Iceberg.
Franky.
Whatever happens,
don't interfere with
what I'm about to do.
No matter what.
It's the World Government
who pinned this crime on us,
and it's the World Government
who will be the
ones to judge it.
There's no way for us to be
cleared of these charges.
It's over.
It must be tough for you to see
your innocent ships being used
for something as
horrible as this.
I bet you really wanna hit
that guy, don't you, Franky?
What are you doing?!
He's going crazy again!
Gerro!
What is he doing?!
Stop it, please!
You're making things worse
than they already are!
Can you even comprehend the pain
that you've put
that boy through?!
Fire!
They shot him!
Tom, no!
Tranquillizers, huh?
Not so tough now, are you?!
Serves you right, fishman!
Tom! Wait!
Why are you doing this?!
What are you
standing around for?
Get over there and
apprehend them!
We're going to take Tom
and every last one
of his villainous workers
down to Enies Lobby!
Who would have thought that Tom
could be such a dangerous guy?
What the hell was
he thinking?
Just what you'd you expect from
a man who sold his
soul to pirates!
He made those battleships and
waited around for a chance
like this to use them!
How dare you talk about him
like that, you bastards!
Stop it.
It's all right.
But, Tom!
I'd like to confess.
The raid on the Judicial
Ship was led by me.
That's not true!
Why would you say that?!
But I have a request.
Save your breath, fishman!
Nobody gives a
damn about your--!
Shut your mouth, CP5!
So, what is
this request?
If building the sea train was
supposed to be considered
a pardon for one
charge against me.
Then I'd like to be pardoned
for today's charges.
Even if that request
is granted,
you'll be right back to where
you were to begin with.
With a charge of building a ship
for the King of the Pirates,
which will result
in the maximum penalty.
Sounds good.
I like that better, anyway.
Giving a hand to that Roger guy
is something I'll never forget.
In fact, it's something
I take great pride in!
He's proud of that?
I can't believe he'd
make such a bold claim
about something so despicable!
Traitor!
Evil Fishman!
You'll regret that!
Why, Tom? Tell me!
It's for the best.
Now listen, don't
blame yourself for this.
I never thought the
World Government would go
to such extremes to
get the blueprints.
And the situation with Roger
only makes the matter worse.
Even so, it doesn't
have to be this way!
No, it's fine.
Look around you.
Even if I'm charged with
a crime from 14 years ago,
nothing else about this town
is the same now as
it was back then.
This island is alive and strong!
This is only
the beginning.
No matter what ends up
happening to me,
I was still able
to help this town.
My dream has
finally begun to run.
Tom! Don't! Please!
Tom, no!
Iceberg, Franky take care of
the blueprints.
Kokoro, Yokozuna thank you
for everything.
The tranquilizers
finally kicked in!
Capture those three for
the Judicial Ship attack!
Yes, sir!
Hold it!
I'm amending
the charges.
For the crime of designing
and building a ship
for Gold Roger, the
King of the Pirates.
Tom and Tom alone
will be apprehended
and taken to Enies Lobby.
That is all.
What in the hell got into
that old geezer's head?
Whatever, I don't
need his lackeys.
Release those
two apprentices!
Tom can't be saved from this.
It's the government
we're up against.
There's nothing we
can do! Endure it.
Tom traded his life for yours!
If you make them your enemy,
you won't be able to win,
no matter how many lives
you have to give!
Enies Lobby is the government's
personal judicial island.
Not one single person who's been
sent to that dreadful place
has ever been seen again!
The sea train is ready
for departure, sir!
We can leave
anytime you like!
Very good!
Kokoro.
Let's get moving, men!
Load up the prisoner!
I can't...
This bloated fishman is
going for a little train ride!
Endure this!
Hey!
Stop it!
Whoa! He really
messed up his face!
Now Tom's apprentice is
the one on a rampage!
No! Stop!
Gerro, gerro, gerro!
Capture that criminal!
The rest of you, take
Tom to the train!
That's not
gonna happen!
Nobody's taking
him anywhere!
Fire at will!
Tom's staying right here!
Are you okay?!
After him!
Hurry! Get out of here!
Fire!
Dammit! He got away!
I'll get that Cutty Flam brat
if it's the last thing I do!
That little criminal will
pay for what he's done!
Mark my words.
Once this case is over, I'll
have him sent to the gallows!
Spandam! He's here!
What now?!
It's-It's Cutty
Flam, sir!
What?! Where?
Standing out on the
tracks ahead of us!
And it appears that he's
holding some sort of weapon!
Stay right there, Yokozuna.
Gerro, gerro.
He's out of his mind!
What should we do, sir?
Are you out of
your mind, too?!
We keep on going!
That's what he
wants us to do, right?
Don't worry about him!
Right! Y-Yes, sir!
All right, Puffing Tom.
That's far enough!
What do you think
you're doing?
Where are you taking
your creator?
Gerro, gerro, gerro!
I won't let you pass!
Give me Tom back!
You hear me?!
Stop now, sea train!
I see!
So your parents just
abandoned you, huh?
That's terrible!
Hey! Stop laughing at me!
Fine then.
Come stay with me.
Tom.
I don't want to build
ships anymore.
I can't love ships that hurt the
people I care so much about!
I won't do it!
But even so, my goal in
life is to be just like you!
Come back!
Come back and
teach me once again!
Cause someday I want to
build my own dream ship!
A ship that will proudly
sail bravely over
uncharted waters all the way
to the ends of the world!
We've heard that Tom was
an excellent craftsman
and a creative
genius but he was also
an uncontrollable fishman
with superhuman strength.
When we ask the
citizens here about him,
they don't really
have much to say.
It must be difficult to
apprentice under
a man like that.
Right, Cutty Flam?
That ridiculous question
doesn't even deserve a reply.
You Government goons
are all piles of crap!
Easy, easy!
During that incident,
more than 100 people,
including Marines
and Navy officers,
were severely injured
here in Water 7.
And the culprit
behind it was you.
Causing the World Government
that much trouble
is a serious crime.
But because you were
confirmed dead
in a sea train accident
later that same day,
all of the charges against
you were annulled.
Since you're
actually still alive,
you'll be taken to
Enies Lobby as a criminal.
There, you can take your time
answering this one
simple question.
Where are the secret blueprints
for the ancient weapon
known as Pluton?
Now, Blueno.
Right, I was just able
to get a connection.
When I reported
our latest findings
on this case to our superior,
he said that he wanted to
speak with you directly
and immediately.
Superior, huh?
All right, Chief. Go ahead.
Hot! Hot! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I spilled coffee
all over myself!
Dammit! Stupid coffee!
What the heck?
So, you're still alive.
Greetings Cutty Flam.
Long time no see.
It's hard to believe you
somehow managed to
survive the "accident."
Hard to believe.
But good news, nonetheless.
Is that so?
Who are you?
For the past eight years,
every time my scars hurt,
I was tormented by
an unquenchable anger
that I couldn't take the
proper vengeance I deserved.
Because the criminal responsible
for those scars
was dead, you see.
I said who in
the hell are you?
Don't you remember me?
I'm the man from
Cipher Pol Number 5
that arrested Tom's Workers
when I caught them red-handed
for savagely attacking the
Judicial Ship 8 years ago!
I've been looking
forward to seeing you.
Wait is that you, Spanda?
Spandam! Spandam!
There's an "M" at the end!
Lucci!
Hurry up and bring them
to Enies Lobby already!
Yes, sir.
Hey! Hold on! Let him go!
What was that?
Uh, nothing! Sorry!
On the next One Piece:
"The Truth Behind
Her Betrayal!
Robin's Sorrowful Decision!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!