[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[KUREHA]
Now have a safe trip...
...my stupid son.
[LUFFY]
"Goodbye Drum Island!
I'm Going Out to Sea!"
‐‐[USOPP] Ooh!
‐‐Whoa!
‐‐[VIVI] It's beautiful!
‐‐[NAMI] Yeah.
Like a bunch of cherry blossoms.
Hey, do you think
Chopper's okay?
He's looking a little down.
He'll be fine.
Let's just leave him
alone for right now.
It's an emotional time.
He's going on his
first journey as a man.
It's a rite of passage.
[VIVI] And he's about to leave
Drum Island behind for good.
It's been his home
his entire life.
[USOPP]
Yeah...
I'm leaving them,
both Doctor and Doctorine.
My adventure is
finally starting...
...right now, on this ship.
[LUFFY, ZORO, USOPP, SANJI
cheering, laughing]
Oh, yeah! Partay!
And these cherry blossoms
are like party decorations.
Come on, Chopper,
snap out of it!
You can't just sit there in a
daze all night long, you know.
[LUFFY]
Woo‐hoo!
You wanna drink?
Come sing a song with us.
[LUFFY] Here! Shove these
chopsticks up your nose.
Go on.
[SANJI]
It's a great moonlit night
and cherry blossoms
are in the air.
How could we not party?
‐‐[CHOPPER gasps]
‐‐They're a handful.
I hate to tell you,
but your new friends
are about as crazy as they come.
My... friends?
That's right. These guys can
really be a lot to handle,
but now that you're one of us,
you're gonna have to
get used to it.
Karoo! What in the
world were you doing
frozen in the river like that?!
[squawking]
That bird! Ten Berries says he
slipped and fell into the river.
He's a clumsy one.
[VIVI]
Be quiet, Mr. Bushido.
‐‐[KAROO squawks]
‐‐[CHOPPER] Uh‐huh, yeah...
He said that the guy named Zoro
was swimming in the river
and disappeared.
He thought Zoro
was in trouble,
so he jumped into
the river to help
and ended up getting
frozen in it.
So this is all your fault!
[ZORO]
Ow...
So you were really
able to understand
everything Karoo was saying?
Yes. I'm still technically
half animal by nature,
so I can understand
what they say.
You can talk to animals?
Oh, wow, Chopper!
Between your medical skills
and talking to animals,
you've got some
amazing talents.
[gasps]
[CHOPPER]
Don't be silly, you jerk!
Flattering me like that
isn't gonna make me
happy or anything!
[LUFFY, USOPP]
He sure looks happy.
Hey, what did you mean about
Chopper's "medical
skills" anyway?
Well, Chopper here is a doctor,
and a first‐rate one at that.
Dr. Kureha taught him everything
there is to know about medicine.
[ZORO, LUFFY, USOPP]
Huh?
Impossible.
Chopper, are you
seriously a doctor?
How cool!
No way!
Really, Luffy,
if you didn't know that,
what did you think Chopper was
when you asked him to join us?
A talking, transforming
reindeer monster.
Back up food.
[CHOPPER gasps]
Wait! Oh, no!
I was in such a big hurry
I left my medical bag behind!
It had all of my tools in it!
Your bag? But isn't this it?
Huh?
That is my bag!
[NAMI] It was in
the back of the sleigh.
How is that?
[NAMI]
What do you mean?
Weren't you the one
who packed the sleigh
and got it ready for the trip?
[CHOPPER gasps]
[NAMI]
That's amazing.
Doctorine must have known
what you were planning to do
even before you had decided
to leave the island with us.
[NAMI]
What a kind woman.
Yes.
[SANJI, ZORO, USOPP]
Woo! Yeah!
[LUFFY laughs]
Here. Eat it! Usopp, eat it!
[LUFFY, SANJI, ZORO, USOPP
laughing, chattering]
Those guys.
Can't they see you're
having a sentimental moment
here? I'm sorry, Chopper.
Chopper?
You, too?!
[USOPP]
All right, Straw Hat Crew!
Attention!
Listen, all of you!
[BOTH yelling]
[USOPP] ...half man.
Introducing Tony Chopper!
Come on, Sanji!
Hey, you know...
Come on, you guys.
Listen up right now!
They're crazy.
[KAROO squawking]
[USOPP, ZORO, SANJI yelling]
But I've never had
this much fun ever!
Good!
I propose a toast to
our new friend, Chopper!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Chopper!
[ALL laughing]
[DALTON] I wonder if they've
made it off the island yet.
You know, that reindeer
friend of yours
is a first‐rate doctor
with a first‐rate heart.
I'm very glad to have known him.
[KUREHA] Those cherry
blossoms of Hiriluk's
really did lead to
something miraculous.
[KUREHA chuckles]
[KUREHA] But who'd have
thought the miracle would be
that clumsy reindeer
going out to sea
with a group of
pirates? That kid...
...acting like he's a
grown man all of a sudden.
I have a feeling he'll
make a fine ship's doctor.
So what are your plans
now that Wapol is gone
from the island for good?
For a long time...
...I worked as the
captain of the guard
under Wapol's tyrannical rule.
That's something that I still
need to make amends for.
I was thinking about
leaving this country‐‐
trusting the citizens to make
a better land for themselves
without me here as a reminder.
[KUREHA]
I see.
Is that what you've
decided to do?
[DALTON]
No.
I realize that leaving here
isn't the way to make up
for past mistakes.
This country is rid of
it's corrupt monarchy.
It's citizens are
preparing to build
a new country
that's all their own.
And I think if I stayed here,
I could find a way
to help them build it
into the country
that it's meant to be.
Maybe that will help...
...by washing away
some of the guilt
that I've carried around
with me for so long.
Well, seems to me...
...that you certainly do
possess the strength of heart
to take care of this country.
Strength of heart is needed
to look after a country.
And it can be
difficult to come by,
but I once saw it from a girl
who was no more than
ten years old at the time.
[WAPOL groans]
The World Summit again.
What a useless event this is.
I'm tired of coming to
this thing every year.
[KUROMARIMO]
You're absolutely right, sir.
[DALTON]
I wonder how much longer
Drum Kingdom can
continue like this.
The rift between the monarchy
and the citizens keeps growing.
[PERSON A gasps]
[PERSON A]
Look! It's the king of Alabasta!
[PERSON C]
Cobra Nefertari!
A king who is known
throughout the world
for his benevolence and wisdom.
[KING A]
The revolutionist, Dragon‐‐
this man's beliefs
are very dangerous.
As world leaders,
we should be aware
of the threat he poses
to our countries.
In as little as
five or six years,
he will likely become
a prominent enemy
opposed to our interests.
[yawns]
Well, I don't know about the
rest of your dumb countries,
but mine's governed too well for
my citizens to be lead astray
by some revolutionist. [yawns]
Go ahead and capture him if
you want, but leave me out.
it's ridiculous.
[COBRA growls]
Fool!
You are a selfish fool!
Why do you think we've
all gathered here
at the World Summit?
‐‐[WAPOL growls]
‐‐Just act responsibly for once!
No one talks to me like that!
Well, that summit
was as unenjoyable
as all the rest of them.
Huh? That girl!
She's that idiot
Cobra's daughter.
[chuckles]
Oh, no! My hand
must have slipped!
What are you doing?!
‐‐Sorry! Ha, ha, ha!
‐‐[IGARAM] Princess Vivi!
Oh, excuse me.
If I'm not mistaken, you're the
princess of Alabasta Kingdom.
Wow! it must suck to have
such a pathetic father!
Damn it! What do you
think you're doing?!
[VIVI]
No, stop, Igaram.
I'm fine.
My apologies.
I didn't look where
I was going, sir.
‐‐[WAPOL grunts]
‐‐[IGARAM growls]
That is quite a child.
At a World Summit like this
where all of the most powerful
leaders are gathered,
tensions tend to run high.
The slightest argument
can trigger an all out war.
Knowing that, she refused
to make a scene.
[DALTON]
She's so young to be so wise.
[WAPOL]
What an annoying little brat!
Let's go, Dalton.
Forgive us.
[VIVI cries]
[VIVI]
It hurts!
You made me so proud today,
Princess Vivi.
[DALTON] That princess had
great strength of heart indeed.
And that hasn't changed.
She's remained strong
all these years.
[DALTON]
She would make anyone proud.
[DOCTOR A]
Dalton, please.
The desire to care
for our country
hasn't faded from
within us either.
Allow us to do something.
We want to help
build a new country.
[DALTON]
Hiriluk.
This country will be reborn
as you always wished it to be.
Just like your son, Chopper.
[VILLAGER A]
Dalton! You need to hear this.
‐‐[footsteps]
‐‐[VILLAGER A panting]
I just remembered
something important
that I forgot to tell you.
What is it?
Take a look at this.
[VILLAGER B]
It's him!
That's the Straw Hat pirate
who defeated Wapol.
We're sure of it!
You mean he has a 30‐million‐
Berry bounty on his head?
Are you certain?
Goodness.
They're quite a band of rouges,
aren't they. [chuckles]
Where'd you find this?
Well, uh,
I completely forgot to
report this to you, Dalton.
I'm very sorry.
I guess it all happened
about a week ago.
A man who seemed to be
a random traveler
showed up one day
over in Robelle Town.
Strangely, it was a day
without any snowfall.
[VILLAGER B] We have no idea
where on the island he landed.
[VILLAGER A]
Anyway, he told us something.
The man said he was
hunting down Blackbeard,
the pirate who recently attacked
our island with his men.
And then, once he realized
that Blackbeard had
already left, he said...
In that case,
I have one more question.
Has a pirate wearing a straw hat
come through this area recently?
[VILLAGER B]
We didn't know so
he showed us the
wanted poster and said...
[ACE] Well, if the guy I
described does show up...
If he does?
[ACE]
Deliver this message:
I will wait for him in Alabasta
for ten days and no more.
Don't forget.
[gasps] Hey! Hold on a sec!
You didn't tell us your name!
[ACE]
Oh, yes, I forgot about that.
The name's Ace, gentlemen.
If you tell the
Straw Hat pirate,
then he'll know who I am.
[ACE chuckles]
Hey! Catch that guy.
He ate and didn't pay his
tab at the restaurant.
[ACE] Just give him
the message, thanks!
[BOTH]
Huh...
[DALTON] So he'll be waiting
in Alabasta for ten days. Huh.
Hm? Excuse me, Doctor,
but is there something wrong?
You look puzzled.
Tell me something, Dalton.
Have you ever heard of
the man Gol D. Roger?
Gol D.?
Do you mean Gold Roger?
I guess.
Is that what he goes by now?
[KUREHA]
From the looks of this...
...the guy Chopper
left this island
and headed out to sea with...
...is no ordinary pirate.
The spirit of D...
It still lives.
Whaddya know.
[CHOPPER]
This is amazing, Luffy!
The sea seems to go on forever!
Yeah, it's huge!
And pirates are the
ones who get to have
great adventures
on it all the time.
Incredible.
Being a pirate
must be really great!
[BOTH gasp]
[CHOPPER]
Whoa! What is that thing?
[LUFFY]
It's a seagull.
[NAMI] No way. There aren't
any seagulls that are that big.
Hey! Seagull!
[NAMI gasps]
It's coming!
[LUFFY] See, I was right!
It is a seagull.
That's really not
the point right now!
It's coming at us because
you called it...
Oh, yay! Adventure!
[screeches]
[NAMI yells]
[NAMI]
Hey, where'd Luffy go?
‐‐[LUFFY] Yahoo!
‐‐Huh?
You moron!
You're about to become
that bird's dinner!
[CHOPPER] Something horrible
has happened, you guys!
[yells] A bird's eaten Luffy!
This is no time
for playing cards!
We need to do something!
Luffy's in trouble!
Did Luffy ask for help?
[CHOPPER]
No...
[ZORO] Then there's no problem.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, but...
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
...Propeller!
Amazing.
[ALL yell]
[LUFFY grunts]
Hey, Sanji!
I got some meat for us. Look!
Why are you guys sleeping?
[USOPP, SANJI, ZORO]
We're not, you idiot!
You owe me for this, Luffy.
I had a really good hand!
Oh, yeah? Oops. [laughs]
Whoa, that's huge.
Does this mean we can start
having some decent meals now?
Can we eat it?
Hey, Chopper,
is something wrong?
Well...
...it's just...
...pirates really...
You guys really are...
...really incredible!
Why, yes we are!
Hey, listen up you guys!
We'll be landing
at Alabasta soon,
and this is no time to be joking
around like a pack of hyenas.
Come on.
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am.
[CHOPPER]
So what is Alabasta then?
[NAMI] It's the country
where Vivi's father rules.
[USOPP] Yeah, except there's
this guy named Crocodile
who's trying to take over
the country right now.
[SANJI] And Crocodile's one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Who're those guys?
[NAMI] They're pirates
who are given authority
by the World Government.
[CHOPPER] The government
actually supports pirates?
[USOPP]
Yeah. Pretty weird, huh?
And the Seven Warlords
are incredibly powerful.
You see, they go around
defeating other pirates,
one by one.
And that's why the government
supports the Warlords.
The idea is to have the pirates
get rid of all
the other pirates.
I'm really looking forward to
meeting this Crocodile guy.
Crocodile is considered
a hero back home.
He helps get rid of the pirates
who attack Alabasta.
However, his good deeds only
appear good on the surface.
He is an evil man.
In truth, he's manipulating
the citizens of Alabasta
to bring about a civil war so
he can take over the country.
No one has realized what
Crocodile's doing yet‐‐
not the people,
not even my father.
Right. Well, this should be fun.
All we have to do is
beat up that Crocodile guy.
Yes, but in order to do that,
we have to avert the
civil war in Alabasta
and get Baroque Works
out of the picture.
[CHOPPER]
Baroque Works?
[USOPP]
Oh, yeah.
You don't know anything
about them, either.
To be honest, I don't understand
what's going on
with them myself.
They have a really
complicated system
of agents, bosses, and partners.
The system is actually
pretty simple.
First, at the very top
of the organization
is the boss, Crocodile.
He's known as Mr. 0.
There are a total of 12
agents and one animal
who receive orders
from the boss directly.
For the most part,
these 12 male agents
operate as part of a pair
with a female agent.
Mr. 1 is paired with
Miss Double Finger.
Mr. 2 doesn't actually
have a female partner.
[ZORO]
Mr. 3 is the candle man
we ran into in
Little Garden, right?
[VIVI] That's right,
and his partner is the painter
Miss Golden Week.
[NAMI]
Oh, yeah, that little girl.
[VIVI]
Mr. 4 is next in line.
He's paired up with
Miss Merry Christmas.
I don't know much more than
that about those two, though.
[LUFFY]
Then there's that snot guy.
[USOPP]
Mr. 5.
[CHOPPER]
Snot?
[USOPP]
Yeah, his snot is explosive.
[VIVI] Mr. 5's entire body
can be used as a weapon.
[NAMI]
His partner, Miss Valentine,
has the Kilo Kilo Fruit powers.
[ZORO] That's the woman
who can change her weight
whenever she wants.
[VIVI] The agents with codenames
from Mr. 1 through Mr. 5
are known as officer agents.
They each possess one
of the Devil Fruit powers
and they are only sent on
the most important missions.
Agents Mr. 6 through Mr. 13
have the job of fundraising.
They make money
for the organization
by heading up the employees at
the entrance to the Grand Line.
[SANJI] Hey, what about that
weird monkey and chicken pair
I ran into?
[VIVI]
That's Mr. 13 and Miss Friday.
They're the agency's
punishment squad.
They punish any agent who
fails to complete a mission.
And there are more.
Under the officer agents are
200 men called "billions."
And there are another 1,800
men under the frontier agents
that are known as "millions."
Together they make up the secret
crime syndicate Baroque Works.
Let's see, 200 plus
1,800 equals, um, uh...
There are 2,000 of them?!
Two thousand?!
[LUFFY] All right.
I think I understand.
When are we gonna
get to Alabasta
so I can beat up Crocodile?
Uh, I don't think you
get it at all, Luffy.
If Baroque Works' sole objective
is to take over Alabasta,
then I can guess
what that must mean.
The rest of the officer agents,
as Vivi called them,
and their subordinates
are probably...
...on their way to
Alabasta as we speak.
Yeah.
[LUFFY]
I see.
So, in that case, we just
go beat up Crocodile...
[SANJI] That's enough,
Luffy. Just let it go.
[LUFFY]
Okay...
‐‐[MR. 2] Un...
‐‐[MAN A groaning]
‐‐Deux...
‐‐Trois...
‐‐[MAN A groaning]
[MAN A] I'm sorry, Mr. 2,
Mr. Bon Clay, sir...
Would you idiots
quit playing around?!
Damn it. Are you
completely clueless?
Do you even know who I am?
[groans]
[MR. 2] I am Bon Clay,
a Baroque Works officer agent.
I strike fear into the heart
of anyone who sees me.
Hey, you, navigator,
tell me something.
Y‐Yes, sir!
[MR. 2] Does that little
pea brain of yours
remember what the boss'
exact orders were?
Yes, Mr. 2.
The orders were to kill Mr. 3 on
his way along the direct route
between Little Garden
and Alabasta.
Okay, then.
Maybe you're not entirely
useless, now are you?
[MAN A groans]
Taking a direct route means that
you travel in a straight line,
doesn't it, navigator?
That's why we went straight from
Alabasta to Little Garden.
Isn't that right?
‐‐[thudding]
‐‐But then something seems to
have gone wrong with the plan
now, hasn't it, navigator?
We reached Little Garden
without so much as seeing Mr. 3
‐‐[thudding continues]
‐‐while on our way here.
Now to me that seems to
indicate that you fools
missed Mr. 3's ship entirely.
No, sir. That can't be true!
[MR. 2]
Hmm.
It sort of sounds like you're
questioning my intelligence.
Not at all, sir.
Be quiet, you.
All we have to do is
kill the pathetic Mr. 3.
It should be an easy mission
and one at which we have
no excuse to fail.
We must complete
the mission soon.
If we don't, then Mr. 1 and
his partner will be sent out
to make sure I end up dead.
‐‐Clear enough for you?!
‐‐[MEN gasp]
Now if you don't
want to answer to me,
then you'd better get to work‐‐
lookin' for that Mr. 3.
I want this ship going as fast
as it can, you imbeciles!
We're heading to
Alabasta immediately!
[MEN] Yes, sir, Mr. 2,
Mr. Bon Clay, sir!
[CROCODILE]
What's this?
Pirates are attacking
towns inside the kingdom?
Don't they know this country
is protected by Crocodile?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY] Who can
tell what they're thinking.
A country where riots
are constantly brewing
may be considered
an easy target.
[footsteps]
You'll go?
[CROCODILE]
Naturally.
I do have a public
duty to uphold.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
How very kind of you, sir.
Yes, I'm a kind man.
We Warlords are charged
with protecting the public
from pirate threats.
We are heroes to
these people, after all.
[CROCODILE chuckles]
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[ZORO] So, are you gonna
make us some food or what?
[SANJI] It's a little difficult
since a certain moron
ate all of our supplies.
[ZORO] What kind of
useless chef are you?!
[SANJI] Hey, you want me
to kick you in the face?
[LUFFY]
Shut up, guys!
[SANJI, ZORO]
This is all your fault!
[NAMI]
Look! We can see the island now!
[LUFFY] All right then.
We'll land and eat!
Oh, and help Vivi.
[ALL]
That's a side note?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Alabasta's Hero
and a Ballerina on the Ship!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!