Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
He escaped from the Hair Bind?
Rumble.
I'm sorry Doctorine. I can't
keep my word.
Maybe I am just like
the Doctor after all.
If he put his life on the
line to save his country,
then I want to put my life on
the line to save my friends.
If I'm going to die anyway.
I have to try it!
Everyone, please stay away.
I'm about to lose control.
"Bubble Master Kalifa!
The Soap Trap
Closes in on Nami!"
Yoyoi.
No one ever informed me
there was a devil fruit
that would actually
turn one into the devil.
But this side of you is
starting to impress me!
Perhaps you are
the devil himself,
or a demon, but a
true man never surrenders,
no matter the odds!
On my very honor
as the lion Kumadori,
I'll send you back to the fires
of hell from whence you came!
Mark my words. Shave!
Now! Finger gun Q, Q, Q!
Moon Walk!
Shishi Kebab!
Yo. Yoyoi.
You've given me no choice.
With this, you shall fall!
Once more Life Return!
Hair Bind!
Hair-- Hair Bind!
This is beyond belief.
Every inch of my being,
from my sub-consciousness
to the tips of my hair--
--is screaming that I must
escape if I wish to survive,
and they won't shut
up about it either.
But I refuse! I won't flee!
My body will obey! I will fight!
Once in a man's life.
Once in a man's life!
He encounters a foe that
his honor demands he face,
even though it might
result in his demise.
Shave!
Tempest Kick! Lotus!
Cry out! Song of Willow!
Crap.
Doesn't even matter
that I'm super right now.
This week has
kicked my ass ragged.
Oh, well.
I'm walkin' away with his key.
Number 4, huh?
Don't the swordsman and
the nose need number 2?
That's what the deer said.
If this guy had number 4,
and that guy had number 3.
Well that narrows
things down some.
That can only mean
that secretary lookin'
gal has the number two key.
I better hurry up and find her.
Those guys really need my help.
I was under the impression
that you were short on time.
If that were the case,
it would seem you
aren't trying very hard.
But perhaps this is
all part of your plan.
Don't you mock me.
You'll pay for this!
Sounds great.
I'm ready when you are.
You don't have to
wait for me, y'know?
The battle has already
started, after all.
Arrogant, aren't you?
I mean, you ate a devil fruit.
So that bath is
disabling your power.
If your body's half submerged.
I can't imagine you
can do much damage.
Oh yeah?
You think I'm so cocky
I'd drop my guard?
Don't worry about me.
Even without my powers,
I'm still better off than you.
Pardon me a moment.
Just what the hell
did you do to me?
It would spoil it
if I told you now!
Solving that mystery is part
of the fun of fighting
a power holder.
Whatever it was that
happened to Sanji,
she's obviously the
one who's behind it.
I've gotta be careful.
Otherwise I'll end
up just like him.
I'm finally starting to
get some strength back.
So you think I'm weak, huh?
Well, you haven't seen
the Perfect Clima Tact yet.
If you think I'm
just a pretty face,
you're in for a world of hurt.
I can move my legs.
Here it comes. Thunder Charge!
Swing Arm!
That's an impressive weapon.
Are those clouds?
Did you think I'd just lie there
and let you stomp on me?
Here's my Thunder Bolt Tempo!
And that's what happens when
you don't take me seriously.
What an interesting surprise!
I never thought I'd get
struck by lightning indoors.
Damn.
That barrier protected her,
but what was it made of?
It looked like it
turned into bubbles.
You better hurry
and figure that out.
It's your only
chance of defeating me.
I shouldn't tease you like
that--you'll never guess.
It was almost like soap
when you washed it away.
Did you eat some kind
of bubble-bubble fruit?
Is that it?
Well! Still!
Even if you do know
what my power does,
that doesn't mean you're
stronger than me or anything.
Understand?
Talk about defensive.
I almost feel bad for her.
To put it one way.
My power is cleanliness.
I'm a soap human thanks
to the Bubble-Bubble fruit.
So my entire body
produces a lather.
Lovely, isn't it?
Whoa. How sexy.
I wish I had a
secretary like her--
wait, I'm talking
like an old man!
Uh. It seems pretty
useless for fighting though!
So, what, do you
make people slip?
The sea of bubbles
that I create obey
my every command.
And I have quite
the imagination!
What the--?
I'll give you an example.
So she wasn't
just taking a bath!
Bubble Master Soap Sheep!
What?
Beautiful, huh?
Yeah, some imagination.
Don't let the fluffy
appearance fool you.
Sheep Cloud Relaxing Bubbles!
Oh. By the way.
Didn't you wonder why
you lost your strength
when you walked in here?
Of course.
That must have had something
to do with her power.
What else could it be?
Now that I think about it,
when I came through the door.
The floor was
covered with bubbles.
Oh, crap!
You took too long
to figure it out.
My strength is fading, again.
It's just like earlier
when I stepped on
that puddle of bubbles.
Give it some time.
You'll soon understand the
true horror of this power.
The bubbles that come
from my body are thorough.
They scour and clean
anything you can think of.
Dirt and general filth,
of course.
As well, as your strength.
Perhaps you need to be
reminded of something.
I'm not just a secretary,
I'm one of the world's
most deadly assassins.
I can move again.
Maybe it's because
the bubbles disappeared.
I'm done with your crap.
Thunder Ball!
That weapon is interesting.
But it won't be enough.
My strength is fading, again.
It's just like earlier
when I stepped on that
puddle of bubbles.
Give it some time.
You'll soon understand the
true horror of this power.
The bubbles that come
from my body are thorough.
They scour and clean
anything you can think of.
Dirt and general
filth, of course.
As well, as your strength.
Perhaps you need to be
reminded of something.
I'm not just a secretary,
I'm one of the world's
most deadly assassins.
I can move again.
Maybe it's because
the bubbles disappeared.
I'm done with your crap.
Thunder Ball!
That weapon is interesting.
But it won't be enough.
Golden Bubbles!
What're you doing?
My legs. I can't stand.
What'd you--
What'd you do to me?
Pretty, aren't they?
My lightest touch can
make anything glisten.
It's my gift to make
everything beautiful.
I'll give your skin a
luminescent sheen.
Every inch of your body
will shimmer from my touch.
Iron Bod--
I got no idea what kind
of junk is waiting for me.
As soon as I get back up,
I better get me some cola.
Oh, right.
I wonder if that deer's
still hangin' in there.
What's goin' on up there?
Wh--what the hell--
--is that?
Wait.
That's the CP9 guy that
got locked in the fridge.
That thing's holding
him like a ragdoll.
What the hell did I miss?
That hat.
I think it's the same style
that deer was wearing.
Hey! You!
You're not that
deer-gorilla, right?
This can't be real.
No, it's him, alright.
It's Kumadori!
His body came rocketing
over from the Tower of Law!
But who could've
done that to him?
Seriously. What the
hell is his problem?
A voice?
Hey! Keep movin'.
I don't remember telling
you to stop, Nico Robin.
Hey! Are you listening to me?
Don't forget
who's the boss here!
Alright, Lucci. Just drag her!
Pull her by the hair
if you have to!
It's an order. Now come on.
Start walking.
You're delusional, aren't you?
Oh, my. You're honestly
convinced that the Straw Hats
are still on their way
to rescue you. Moron!
I've never seen such
a weak-looking pirate crew.
If that's your only hope,
that's pretty sad.
That explosion we heard earlier
was probably the
pipes or something.
There's no way they
could make it this far!
While you're off in your
little fantasy world,
dreaming of being rescued,
we'll pass the Gates of Justice.
The Bridge of
Hesitation lies right
before the Gates of Justice.
We'll cross the first
elevated half of the bridge.
And once the gates
are within our sight,
the other half of the bridge
will rise from the sea.
And then we'll finally pass
through the gates themselves.
Once the gates have
firmly closed behind us,
every lingering trace
of your pathetic,
misguided optimism will
be dashed to pieces.
You'll forget what
hope even means.
The only feeling left
in your body will be
an overwhelming and
eternal sense of guilt.
You will spend your days
in ceaseless atonement
for your arrogant
crime of existing.
You know it's true. Nico Robin.
Now then. Hurry along.
Move your feet, wench!
Robin! Robin! Robin!
Wh-wh-what was that?
I heard someone!
Did you hear that?
Who was it?
You better take
Nico Robin and start moving.
Don't worry, chief,
I'll handle this.
A door!
At least it doesn't look like
it's made of iron this time.
It's big in here. Where am I?
I found you, Pigeon-bastard.
Glad you could make it.
Hey! Answer me! CP9!
One of the pirates caught
up with us somehow.
Come on! Are you even
listening to me?
Wait! No!
Look at what you're holding!
What?
I pressed the button on the
golden transponder snail!
On the next One Piece:
"Resounding Bad News!
Buster Call Invoked!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!