[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[FULLBODY gasps]
[FULLBODY groans]
[FULLBODY grunts]
[FULLBODY] What kind of
restaurant is this?!
It's almost as if... if...
...this were a pirate ship!
Sir, he's escaped!
Pirate Krieg's henchman
attacked us and vanished!
‐‐[FULLBODY] He what?
‐‐[gunshot]
Come on... This is a restaurant.
Of course, but how will you be
paying for your meal today?
Will a bullet be enough?
So you don't have
any money then.
[GHIN]
Huh?
[GHIN gasps]
I think I just found my cook!
[ZEFF]
Sanji...
[SANJI sighs]
Stupid geezer.
This is an opportunity
you don't want to pass up.
I have no need to keep you
here at my restaurant.
[LUFFY] "The Strongest Pirate
Fleet! Commodore Don Krieg!"
Hey, listen, pal...
I'm the Sous Chef in this place.
What do you mean you
don't need me any more?
You fight with customers
all the time...
You flirt with every woman under
80 who walks through here...
You can't even cook
a decent meal...
You're worth less to me than
the chum after brunch...
That's what I mean.
So... uh...
[COOKS laughing]
[SANJI growls]
[ZEFF]
Oh, and let's not forget about
how the other cooks avoid
you like you were poison.
So just run off and be
a pirate or whatever,
but get out of this restaurant!
That's how it is?
You shoot off at the mouth
and expect that I'm just
going to take it, old man?
[SANJI] I could blow
off everything you said,
but I won't listen to
anyone trash my cooking!
I'm staying here as a
Sous Chef, and that's final!
You hear me?!
[ZEFF]
What do you think you're doing,
grabbing your boss
by the collar?!
[SANJI grunts]
‐‐[ZEFF] You ingrate!
‐‐[SANJI groans]
‐‐[wood, glass shatters]
‐‐[CUSTOMERS gasp]
[SANJI groans]
Dumb... geezer...
[ZEFF]
Hm.
[SANJI]
Enough with the games...
You can try to kick me out...
But I'm here to stay. I'm not
going anywhere, old man.
Not till you're dead and gone!
[ZEFF]
Dead? Hah.
I got another hundred years
of kickin' your ass left in me!
[SANJI] He's always
gotta have the last word.
See? He said it's cool.
Now you can become a pirate!
Shut up!
My apologies...
I hope I can make it up to you
with this delightful fruit
Macedonia, my princess.
Wow! You're too kind!
It looks wonderful.
Good.
Hey! Don't forget about
us, Mister Casanova!
We'd better get some
kind of an apology, too!
This tea should be more
than adequate for you...
In fact, you should
be thanking me.
What?! You wanna fight?
You're gonna regret this!
Take him out, Zoro!
[ZORO]
You take him out!
Stop it! Please don't
fight because of me.
Of course, my dear...
Who said it was about you?!
I wanted to tell you that...
Yeah?
That all of the food
here is just delicious...
But it's a little
too expensive for me.
Relax, it's free.
‐‐[NAMI] Oh! Thank you!
‐‐[SANJI stammering]
You guys still
gotta pay, though.
What?!
[ZORO]
How very generous of you.
[LUFFY laughs]
[SANJI] What are you
sitting around for?!
You're not here
to lounge around.
[LUFFY]
Right...
[USOPP sighs]
We've been sitting around,
twiddling our thumbs
for four days now!
How long do you think we're
gonna be here, anyway?
Who knows?
He said he'll stay a year,
but I'm already so bored!
Quit whining,
this place is great!
Plus, all the food here is free!
[ZORO]
Yeah, for you it is.
[LUFFY grunting]
[USOPP]
Hey, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
What are we still doing here?!
Come on, let's just
get outta this place!
Just sit tight a little longer.
I'm gonna try to make
another deal with the owner.
[USOPP]
Ugh, well, hurry up!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Darling? Hey, What's the matter?
[CUSTOMER A gasps]
[CUSTOMER A screams]
[CUSTOMER B]
It's them... They're here!
The hourglasses
mean our time is up!
What are we gonna do now?!
That flag means death!
There's no doubt; it belongs
to the ruler of the East Blue...
...Don Krieg!
[CUSTOMERS scream]
[CUSTOMER C] But why? Why have
the Krieg Pirates come here?!
I told you! I knew those
goons would show up!
Now are you gonna get rid
of those guys or what?!
This can't be real! He's got
a whole fleet to command.
Why would Don Krieg come here to
get revenge for just one man?
I mean, doesn't he have
anything better to do?
He's here, all right! We're not
imagining that ship, are we?!
Guys, don't panic,
but I think this is our
cue to leave, right now!
Look at the sheer
size of that galleon!
What a huge ship!
You think Ghin came back to
repay you for your kindness?
I seriously doubt that's it.
‐‐It's something else.
‐‐[LUFFY] Hm?
Hey, look!
Yeah... Their ship...
[ZEFF growls]
Whoa, what'd they do?
Sail through a hurricane
or something?
Doesn't seem like damage
inflicted by cannons.
In fact, it doesn't
look man‐made at all.
[LUFFY] Hmm, then maybe
it was a tornado‐hurricane!
[SANJI]
There he is...
‐‐[footsteps]
‐‐[CUSTOMERS gasp, whimper]
[COOKS murmuring]
[SANJI]
Huh?
[KRIEG]
I beg you...
I need food... and water...
We have money...
Lots of money...
Please...
It's been so long, I don't even
remember the last time I ate...
Please, sir...
‐‐I need food and drink...
‐‐[GHIN groaning]
I'm begging you...
No, this can't be!
Where's the death
and destruction?
Is this really the Don Krieg,
Commodore of the
grand pirate fleet?
‐‐Guess he's hungry.
‐‐[footsteps]
[KRIEG groans]
[GHIN gasps]
[GHIN]
C‐Captain!
Don Krieg!
Please, help him! Our captain
is on the brink of starvation!
He could die!
He hasn't had a single
bite to eat for days!
He'll die if he doesn't
get some food soon!
[CUSTOMERS murmuring]
[GHIN gasping]
[PATTY laughs]
This is great!
I haven't laughed that
hard in a long time.
The great Don Krieg,
kneeling before us!
We have some money!
We're here as
customers this time!
Do you really think
I'm that stupid?
Hey! Get a hold of
the marines right away.
[GHIN]
What?!
He's finally weak
enough to be captured.
This may never happen again,
and I'm not gonna ruin it
by helping him get
his strength back!
[GHIN growls]
[CUSTOMER A]
He's right!
Who knows what he'll do if
gets on his feet again?
[CUSTOMER D]
He's done terrible things!
[CUSTOMER E] And as soon as he's
up, he'll keep on doin' 'em.
I say we let him starve.
Once he's back to normal,
he'll kill every last
person in this restaurant.
He won't get so much as
a glass of water from me.
[KRIEG]
I won't do anything...
[GHIN gasps]
[KRIEG]
I won't do anything...
Once I eat...
I promise I'll leave quietly...
So please...
Be merciful, and help me...
You're a king,
Don Krieg, stop it!
Please, don't reduce
yourself to this!
You're better than
the common beggar!
Please, sir! What
about your pride?
[KRIEG]
I promise...
Please... I'll take the scraps.
I'll take anything...
Anything...
[GHIN sobs]
Don...
Heh, boo‐hoo for
the cruel pirate.
[SANJI]
Hey, step aside, Patty.
[PATTY groans]
[PATTY grunts]
[grunts]
[LUFFY]
Whoa!
[COOK A]
Huh?
[GHIN gasps]
[GHIN]
Sanji...
[KRIEG]
Huh?
[SANJI] Here's something
for your captain.
Thank you, Sanji.
[KRIEG]
Thank you!
[COOK A groans]
You dimwit!
Get that food away
from him right now!
Don't you realize he's a cold,
heartless, killing machine?!
This is the man known as
the ruler of the East Blue,
the most treacherous
of all pirates!
It all started back in prison...
He pretended to be a Marine...
And when he decided to
declare his pirate ambitions,
he took command
of a Marine vessel
by killing the senior officer!
[CARNE] He would raise the
Marine flag to enter ports,
then lay waste to the
unsuspecting cities
and passenger ships there.
He even showed the white flag
before attacking enemy ships.
He did anything
to secure victory.
That guy fights dirty.
[CARNE] He's also unmatched
in physical combat.
You think he'll
just leave us alone?
Well, I've got news for you!
That's not possible with a
bloodthirsty killer like him!
He deserves death!
[CARNE gasps]
[SANJI]
Huh?
[KRIEG yells]
[SANJI]
Huh?
[KRIEG yells]
[SANJI groans]
[grunts]
[yells]
[SANJI grunts]
[GHIN gasps]
[KRIEG sneers]
[LUFFY gasps]
[gasps]
Sanji!
[CUSTOMERS gasp]
[screams]
[CUSTOMERS scream]
This is not what we agreed on!
You gave me your word! I only
brought you here because
you promised that you
wouldn't ruin this place!
Or hurt the man who saved us!
[GHIN groans]
[KRIEG]
Yes, that was delicious.
‐‐[bones cracking]
‐‐[GHIN screams]
[KRIEG]
I feel alive again.
[GHIN grunts]
[CUSTOMERS scream]
[USOPP]
Hey... You see that?
It looks bad...
What do you think is
going on in there?
Don't know. Let's
go inside and see.
What?! Are you serious?!
Sure am. You sound scared.
I am not scared!
[ZORO]
It's so strange...
The ship looks almost abandoned.
[KRIEG growls]
[COOK murmuring]
This is a pretty good ship...
I believe that I'll take it.
[gasps]
[SANJI groans]
Right... I see...
[PATTY groans]
[gasps]
As you can all see,
my ship is a wreck.
Naturally, I'll be
needing a nice new one.
After a few small chores...
Every last one of you
will leave the ship.
What?! No!
Don Krieg...
You promised... Please!
[KRIEG]
There are about a hundred men
left onboard my ship,
all are weak with hunger,
and many are seriously wounded.
If you value your lives, you
will prepare food and water
for every last one of them.
I've lost too many
men to hunger already...
[PIRATE B groaning]
Water...
[KRIEG]
Bring them over immediately!
You're telling us to
feed our executioners?!
Do you hear how stupid
that sounds?! We refuse!
You refuse?
I wasn't asking you.
Now make no mistake,
you wretched cook,
I'm not placing an order...
I am giving you one!
Do I make myself clear?!
Don't defy me...!
[COOKS scream]
[GHIN]
Sanji...
Sanji... Sorry...
I didn't mean for
this to happen.
You see?!
Look what you brought on this
restaurant, you stupid bastard!
[GHIN whimpers]
[GHIN whimpering]
[SANJI grunts]
[PATTY]
Hey!
Where do you think
you're going?!
[SANJI]
To the kitchen...
Looks like I'll be cooking
a hundred more meals today.
[PATTY, CARNE gasp]
[GHIN, LUFFY]
Sanji!
[COOKS]
What?! Are you crazy?!
Good... Hop to it.
Tell me the truth, Sanji!
Are you his spy or something?!
We can't let you go
anywhere near that kitchen.
[COOK D] We're fed up
with you acting insane!
[SANJI]
All right...
[COOKS]
Huh?
[SANJI]
Stop me if you wish.
I know...
It's no secret that Don Krieg
is a terrible, ruthless man.
[COOK A]
Huh?
[SANJI]
But that doesn't matter to me...
It doesn't matter!
After we feed all these men, who
knows what's going to happen...
I am just a simple cook,
no more and no less.
If someone's going hungry,
it's my duty to feed them.
That's all I know...
Whaddya say?
Is that wrong?
[SANJI grunts]
Patty!
Hey! Somebody grab him!
[SANJI groans]
[PATTY]
You bring free food to
the bums I kick outta this
place, over and over again...
And I'm not about to
argue over who's right
in that particular situation,
but this time, you're just
flat out wrong, Sanji.
I can't let you do things
like that anymore.
We're going to
protect this place.
Fortunately, we've got
numbers on our side.
It is Don Krieg, but what
could he do against all of us?
[KRIEG growls]
At a joint like this, pirate
scumbags come and go all day.
We're fully prepared to
serve any kind of customer!
Is that...?
I really hope you saved
some room for dessert...
...'cause I have
a secret recipe...
[KRIEG]
Huh?
...that is truly to die for!
Open wide! Here comes
the Meat Ball of Doom!
[GHIN, LUFFY gasp]
[KRIEG gasps]
[KRIEG screams]
[GHIN groans]
[LUFFY groans]
[GHIN]
Don!
[PATTY]
I might've broken the door...
I sure hope Zeff doesn't
yell at me again.
[CARNE]
He might go easy on you for
saving the restaurant and all.
So what are we going
to do about all the guys
left in Krieg's ship?
Fry 'em! Cover it in batter,
and fry the entire thing.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[USOPP, NAMI gasp]
[KRIEG]
Are you a chef or a comedian?
Because your jokes are lame!
[PATTY, CARNE gasp]
[KRIEG]
And that dessert was terrible!
The worst I ever had!
[COOKS gasp, scream]
[KRIEG]
So die!
[KRIEG yells]
[COOKS scream]
He's got 'em everywhere!
All those guns!
[GHIN whimpers]
[COOKS groaning]
You cooks should
not have defied me!
I am by far the
world's strongest man!
Arms, made of solid steel!
Wootz steel body
armor, impenetrable!
And a diamond fist that could
pound this entire world to dust.
In addition to the
weapons on my body,
I have a fleet of 50 ships
with five thousand pirates!
My record is perfect!
I've won every single battle
that I've ever been in!
I am Don!
And I'm the only one
fit to be called Don!
[ZEFF]
Outta the way, kid.
Wha‐‐ Uh! [groans]
When I give you
slime balls an order,
you will follow it
down to the last letter!
Don't you ever disobey me!
This is about a hundred meals...
Now take it to your
men right away.
[COOKS]
No, Owner Zeff!
Watch where you're
going with that.
I was standing there, you know?
You're... Red Foot Zeff.
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[NAMI] Think it's okay to
give Krieg food like this?
[USOPP] Yeah, do something
about that, Pops!
[LUFFY]
I will. Leave it to me!
[NAMI] Hey! Where are
you off to, Luffy?
[USOPP] Don't go picking a
fight with Krieg, you moron!
[ZORO]
A fight, huh? Sounds fun.
You fightin', Luffy?
Need a hand?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Protect Baratie! The Great
Pirate, Red Foot Zeff!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!