[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[CROCODILE]
Whatever it is you really want
can't be in this country.
Aren't I right? You're fighting
for somebody else's goal now.
And how can there be any
point in dying for that?
[LUFFY] Like I said, you really
don't understand anything,
do you?
Vivi...
Vivi is always telling people
not to risk their lives,
but she's the first
to lay down her life
in order to save others.
That's what makes
her such a burden.
So why not just ditch the
princess and save yourselves?
Because none of us
want Vivi to die!
Helping each other
is what friends do!
[PELL]
Princess Vivi.
I'm so proud that I've
been able to serve you
all these years;
protecting the Nefertari family
has been an honor.
[PELL] I am Alabasta's
guardian deity, The Falcon!
[PELL] And I am sworn to destroy
the enemies of the royal family.
[LUFFY]
"I Will Surpass You!
Rain Falls in Alabasta!"
[CITIZENS yelling]
[USOPP yells]
[VIVI]
Pell...
He's gone.
[NAMI]
He saved us all.
[USOPP grunts]
[CHOPPER gasps]
[USOPP coughing]
[USOPP]
This can't be happening!
Stop it!
All of you, are you
out of your minds?
[MARINE A]
Ma'am! No!
[REBEL A yells]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
What the‐‐?
[SMOKER]
Tashigi.
I need you to keep a
vigilant eye on this country
and where it ends up.
Whether it falls,
or whether it survives.
The dawn of a brand‐new
and historic age
is on the horizon.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[TASHIGI]
Madness.
Why aren't they stopping?
[VIVI]
Stop fighting! Please stop!
Stop fighting!
Stop!
Please stop!
Please stop fighting!
Stop fighting!
Stop it, please!
Please stop! Stop fighting!
Please stop fighting!
‐‐Stop it!
‐‐[ZORO] Vivi.
[VIVI]
Please stop fighting! Stop!
Please stop fighting! Stop it!
Please stop the fighting!
Stop! Please stop fighting!
Stop fighting! Please stop!
You fool.
You dopes!
Why are you just standing there?
Get your rears in gear!
It doesn't matter how,
just stop the rebellion!
We've got to keep
the casualties as low
as we possibly can!
[crying]
[VIVI]
Stop!
Stop it!
Stop fighting! Stop fighting!
Stop fighting!
Please stop fighting!
[CROCODILE laughing]
At last.
My time has finally arrived.
The day my grand
ambition is realized!
Alabasta now belongs to me!
[LUFFY] Because none
of us want Vivi to die!
Helping each other
is what friends do!
And that's why none
of us will leave her behind
or quit fighting you.
As long as she doesn't
give up on her country,
neither will we!
[CROCODILE growls]
[LUFFY]
You can't...
...defeat me.
[CROCODILE]
You finally manage to speak,
and that's all you
can come up with?
I suppose it's an acceptable
bluff from a loser
who's about to die.
But of course, like any bluff,
it's empty air.
[LUFFY] Except, I'm the man
who'll be King of the Pirates!
[CROCODILE]
Listen up, you damn brat.
If you really knew
anything about this sea,
you wouldn't make
such an idiotic statement.
I told you before.
There are thousands
of rookies just like you.
Every one of them chasing
their naïve little dreams!
The sooner you
understand the true level
of the grand line,
the sooner you'll give up
on your foolish dreams!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY] I'm the one
who's gonna beat you.
[LUFFY yelling]
[CROCODILE grunts]
[LUFFY grunts]
[CROCODILE grunting]
[CROCODILE] The scorpion's
poison should be working by now.
Where does this brat
get his strength from?
[CROCODILE]
Mr. 5's team was taken down?
Who the hell did it?
Monkey D. Luffy?
Never heard of him.
Huh. It must be a mistake.
[CROCODILE]
What?
You're saying that
they're still alive?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Crocodile, sir.
We've just received word.
Those pirates have arrived.
[CROCODILE growling]
[CROCODILE] You're just a
two‐bit nobody who comes from
who‐knows‐where!
You can't beat me!
Do you have any idea who I am?
I don't care who you are,
'cause it doesn't matter!
Whoever you are,
I will beat you!
[LUFFY yells]
[CROCODILE growls]
Now fall with this
ancient temple,
and let the desert
sands bury you!
Sables...
...Pesado!
[LUFFY inhales]
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
[CROCODILE]
Desert...
[LUFFY]
...Storm!
[CROCODILE]
...Spada!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY grunts]
Amazing!
He punched him straight
up through the bedrock
beneath the city!
[SANJI grunts]
Hey, you guys!
Look there!
[GROUP]
Crocodile?!
[VIVI] Now that this
conflict has escalated,
more blood will be shed
throughout the kingdom.
We're at war.
[sobs] You're trying to
get me home safely,
but there's no time!
I need to get home
as quickly as possible!
If I don't make it back in time,
a million innocent citizens will
give their lives needlessly!
[crying]
[LUFFY]
Right. Well, this should be fun!
All we have to do is beat
up that Crocodile guy!
[VIVI]
Luffy...
[SOLDIERS yelling]
I don't know how he got
there in the first place,
but I'm sure it can
only mean one thing.
I knew it! I knew it!
I never doubted it for a second!
It can only mean‐‐
[GROUP]
Luffy did it! He won!
[VIVI]
Please! Our enemy is defeated.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[VIVI sobs]
Don't shed any more blood.
[crying]
[VIVI]
Stop fighting!
Please stop fighting!
‐‐[KOZA grunts]
‐‐[REBEL B] Koza!
Hey, are you all right?
[KOZA]
Do you see it?
[TOTO]
Don't be so suspicious, Koza.
The rain will fall.
[KOZA]
The battle... will end.
[TASHIGI]
Rain.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[TASHIGI]
The madness has finally stopped.
They're beginning to hesitate.
[CHOPPER] The rain is
starting to clear the air.
Stop fighting!
Listen to me!
They've heard
Vivi's voice. Finally.
Vivi.
The princess.
Vivi?
I didn't know the
princess had come back.
[COBRA]
Hey! Are you all right?
[ROYAL SOLDIER B]
Sir Crocodile?
[ROYAL SOLDIER C]
How did he get here?
What happened to him?
Oh, so they're still
calling him Sir Crocodile?
We'll see if he's Sir Crocodile
after I tell them what's what!
Hold on. Just stay here.
[VIVI]
The rain has returned.
And will fall again,
as it used to.
Our nightmare is over.
Finally over.
I thank you.
No sweat!
♪Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!♪
[SANJI] That guy on your
back is one of ours.
I'll take him.
[ZORO]
Who are you, old man?
[VIVI]
Everyone, it's Daddy!
[SANJI]
Daddy?
You mean he's your father?
[ZORO]
Vivi, go to the Square.
[USOPP]
Of course!
The rebellion is over!
It wouldn't be right if
the king or the princess
didn't say a few words!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Farewell to Arms!
Pirates and Different
Ideas of Justice!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!