[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
[LUFFY]
"Sanji the Cook!
Proving his Merit at the
Marine Dining Hall!"
Is what they said
about this ghost ship
falling from the
sky really true?
I don't buy it.
But if Navarone
is supposed to be
this great
impregnable fortress,
how else could one
little pirate ship
have gotten in here if it
didn't fall from the sky?
I heard that there wasn't a
single crewmember on board.
[ALL]
Huh?
[MARINE E]
What the?
[MARINE D] But the table
was set for coffee,
and it was still warm.
Like people had been there
until that exact moment!
But that's not all.
Inside the cargo hold...
[BOTH]
They found gold?
[MARINE C]
Shh.
They found gold all right--
ancient gold dug up from
some old ruins somewhere.
[MARINE AA]
I don't know about you guys,
but that's the creepiest
story I've ever heard.
So--so it's a ghost ship?
[MARINE B] Those poor
saps must've been cursed
for stealing all that gold.
[MARINE H]
Attention units 4, 6, and 10
under Lt. Commander Drake!
Assume battle stations
for yellow alert...
[MARINE J] I don't care
what kind of a ship it is.
Nobody picks a fight
with our fortress.
--[MARINE I] Hurry it up!
--[MARINE J gasps]
[MARINE H] Commanding officers
of units 4, 6, and 10
are to report to Control Room 1
in the central building...
I think I know where we
are and it isn't good.
If I'm right,
and I hope I'm not,
then we landed right
in the middle of
an invincible fortress the
Marines call Navarone.
So what's our
next move, Captain?
[LUFFY snoring]
As usual, our captain
could care less.
[MARINE K] On the double, men!
This is an emergency order!
[DRAKE] We'll moor the
pirate ship to Dock 88
and run a full forensic sweep.
[knocking]
We have a situation!
Sir, some Marine vessels
outside the sea gate
are demanding entry!
Demanding?
[MARINE L] Since we're
in a state of emergency,
I advised them
to standby, but...
[OPERATOR] Sir, we barely
made it out of that storm
in one piece!
Please allow us to dock!
I don't know how much
longer we can stay afloat!
I don't care how badly
their ships are damaged.
There is a possibility
that pirates have
infiltrated this fortress!
So they'll have to
find help elsewhere.
If we let them in now,
it'll cause confusion that--
[JONATHAN]
Open the gate.
Huh?
[JONATHAN]
Permit their entry.
And immediately assign a
medical team to them as well.
Yes, sir!
Commander!
[JONATHAN] What a terrible
thing it is to be helpless
in the middle of the Grand Line.
Even someone like you can
understand that feeling.
Can't you, Lt. Commander?
Of course I understand.
To tell you the truth,
it's been quite some time
since I've gotten this
riled up about anything.
They can't get out
of the fortress,
so the problem
becomes finding them.
But why did they even
come to Navarone
in the first place?
Monkey D. Luffy.
[MARINE M]
We got ships comin' in!
[MARINE N] Proceed with caution,
we are now at red alert!
[MARINE O] Ready the
boarding inspection bridge!
[ZORO]
This base is huge.
Anyway, where the
hell am I? I'm lost!
[NAMI] Who decided that this
fortress should also be a maze?
It's so big I can't map it out.
[NAMI] We have to get
out of here, and soon.
But the more time that passes,
the more lost I get.
Now, where have all
the others gone?
[gasps]
[NAMI]
No way!
What in the world is that thing?
Jeez, it's enormous!
Hey, where's the Merry?
The Going Merry's gone!
What did they do with our ship?
And where's our gold?
All our precious gold is gone!
Gold, gold, gold, gold.
And after we went through
so much to get it.
[NAMI]
Battleships?
They weren't here before.
[MARINE O]
You must be unit 31!
Report to the
building in block 7!
[NAMI] Hmm. If there are
new ships coming in,
it means that this place isn't
a gigantic lake after all!
It is connected to the open sea!
All right!
Now I just gotta find the guys
and take back the Going Merry!
If I could somehow go
undercover as one of them,
I could find the guys,
and gather more information!
[MURRAY]
Where is it?
Luffy and Zoro are known by
almost everybody in the Marines.
But nobody knows
what I look like.
[MONTY]
I bet this is it.
[gasps]
Crap!
This fortress has
a terrible layout.
[MONTY]
It's like a maze.
[MURRAY] Excuse me. Do you
know where the kitchen is?
What?
Oh, the kitchen, of course!
I know right were it is!
We just arrived on the
battleships down there.
And of course the first
thing we do is get lost!
I'm sorry to hear that.
I got lost a lot when
I first came here,
but that must've been
at least five years ago.
--[MONTY] Five years you say?
--[NAMI] Mm-hmm!
[MURRAY]
Please take us to the kitchen.
We beg you. It would be
such an embarrassment
if we had to ask any of
the cooks here for help.
[NAMI]
Maybe I can just say no.
We just came from Marie Jois.
It wouldn't hurt you to
do us one little favor.
[NAMI] Well, it wouldn't
help me either!
Please say you'll help us.
Oh, sure, no problem!
So, do you two know anything
about our little fortress?
My brother and I know
much of the culinary arts,
but nothing about
this fortification.
As a matter of fact, we are
Marine chefs of some renown.
Wow! Celebrity chefs?
[chuckles] My brother
and I have been assigned
to take over as head
chefs of this kitchen.
On Marie Jois,
we satisfied the palates
of generals who expect
nothing but the finest.
We brothers are far
from the kind of cooks
who excrete insignificant meals
on a boat in the
middle of nowhere.
And we must prove to them that
we are in a different league.
[NAMI]
Oh, gimme a break.
I gotta ditch these guys and
find a disguise right now,
or we'll never get outta here.
Well! I guess that attitude
makes you guys the best!
Now, all you have to do
is go straight ahead
and take a right,
then take two lefts and your
first right and you'll be there.
--[MONTY] Merci.
--[MURRAY] Okay.
[NAMI]
See ya.
[MONTY] Wait, is this
the first right? Hm?
[MURRAY]
Huh?
[BOTH]
Huh.
This'll do just fine.
--[OFFICER A] Roronoa Zoro.
--[gasps]
That so called ghost ship
actually belongs to Straw
Hat Luffy and his crew.
We have been given
a secret mission
to track down and
apprehend the infiltrators.
Among them is one who
is considered to be
extremely dangerous.
You mean the Roronoa Zoro?
The great swordsman
who used to be
feared as a pirate hunter?
Doesn't he use the
Three Swords Style?
[OFFICER A] Well, we're gonna
make him and his friends
regret ever coming here.
[ZORO] You're gonna
make me regret what?
[groans] I'm definitely
going in circles.
[NAMI] How can you just stroll
around a hostile fortress?!
I am so gonna kick your--
Oh, hey, Nami.
You'll get caught in no time
if you keep walking around
wearing those things! [groans]
Hey!
You'll probably
get me caught, too.
[footsteps]
[BOTH]
Huh?
C'mon, Zoro,
you gotta hide, now!
Hey, wait! My swords!
Na-- [groans]
[MARINE R]
'Bout time to eat huh?
[MARINE S]
Yeah, I'm starving.
[NAMI]
All right. They're gone.
[ZORO groans] I'm tired of
all this sneakin' around.
Tell me again why can't
we just fight 'em?
[NAMI]
You idiot!
We don't know where
the others are.
If we did--
[ZORO]
Then they would show up, right?
[NAMI]
Hey, now there's an idea--
No, no, no!
The Merry's missing, too!
[ZORO]
Calm down, would you?
No need to shout.
Whoa. Would you
check out that view?
We landed in the dark so
I didn't get to see much.
[NAMI groans]
[ZORO]
Nice.
Hey, I bet if we wait here the
others will show up eventually.
Stop being so stupid
and listen to me.
What you're gonna
do is stay put,
'cause if you go anywhere
or do anything,
you're just gonna get lost!
Hey, stop that!
What do you think you're doing?
[ZORO groans, gasps]
[NAMI] I'll put this in
simple terms for you, okay?
You have no sense of direction
so I'm gonna find the others.
After that I'll come back--
[CHIEF CLEANER] Hey, you!
What are you doing over there?
[NAMI]
Oh, no! Game over!
Enough with the
slacking off, little missy!
Now get back to cleaning!
Aye, aye, sir!
I tell you what,
all those ghost ship shenanigans
have really got me beat.
[MARINE R] Better get some
chow and get back to work.
Ghost ship, huh?
[LUFFY] Did you find
us something to eat?
It sounds like the
dining hall is that way.
Dining hall!
[SANJI]
Hold on a second!
What are you doing?
Take it easy.
But my belly needs meat now!
[LUFFY groans]
I need meat now.
You just won't give up.
[MARINE T]
Who's there?
Halt!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MARINE U]
Strange.
Just hearing things.
It's no wonder.
We've all been on
edge since yesterday.
[MARINE T]
Let's get some grub.
We almost got caught
because of you, you dolt!
[SANJI gasps]
They'll never find us now
'cause we're gonna blend in
like chameleons of the kitchen.
Something smells good.
I guess this is it.
Could be interesting.
Hey, I heard that a couple of
battle ships docked today.
What? That means those
pompous brothers
will have arrived then.
[TOM] Yep, as a matter of fact,
they should be here any minute.
First impressions are important.
Show no mercy!
[COOKS]
Yeah!
[LUFFY]
Meat! I smell meat!
Keep it together, man.
Have you ever heard
the term "self control"?
Self co-what? Never heard of it.
Have you ever heard of the
terms "all you can eat meat"
and "unlimited refills"?
[SANJI gasps]
Hey! Luffy!
Need meat!
[COOKS]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Uh...
[LUFFY chuckles]
So you're the new chefs.
Well, are you the
Murray brothers or what?
Murray?
[SANJI]
Aw, man.
Hi!
So you are those arrogant fancy
pants cooks from Marie Jois.
Huh?
You're the guys who said that
you were doing us a favor
by coming out to this crap
fortress in the boonies!
And you said that we were
excreting insignificant meals!
You've sure got a lotta nerve!
This entire kitchen has
mistaken us for some other guys.
I don't know what you're
complaining about,
and I don't care.
Feed me! Give me food!
So you're here.
The world famous kitchen snobs
who made million-Berry
meals every night
for all the big shots
over in Marie Jois.
[BOTH gasp]
[JESSICA] I don't care
that headquarters sent you.
This is the most sacred
place in all of Navarone!
[SANJI chuckles]
Huh?
And if I don't approve of you,
you will never set
foot in here again.
Do I make myself clear?
[TOM, SHINPACHI]
Aw, yeah! She told you!
Tell 'em how it is, Jessica!
There are no less than
1,000 brave Marines
stationed at this stronghold.
And we show our respect to
each and every one of them
by preparing their meals
with all our might!
So they can stay strong!
In order for us to
achieve this great feat,
we work day and night.
And we never, even for
an instant, lose focus.
We're not like those cooks
who depend on expensive food.
We rely on skill.
Please tell me I can eat those.
Around here we can't forget...
...that great food...
...comes from a special
place in all of our hearts.
In other words,
you would presume to tell me
what real cooking is. Right?
No, I'm not trying
to say anything
quite as dramatic as that.
I just want you and your brother
to show us that pride
you talk so much of.
I'll give anyone a chance
to prove themselves,
no matter how pretentious
they might be.
However, there will be
trouble if I think you lack
anything at all in
skill or attitude.
Let me make this clear.
Unless you satisfy me,
you will never be able to call
yourselves cooks in Navarone!
I see.
That sounds like a
challenge, mademoiselle.
[MARINE V]
What is it? What's going on?
[MARINE W]
Well it looks like the cooks
are gonna have a cooking fight!
[MARINE T]
I gotta see this!
[MARINE S] Is that the chef
that came from headquarters?
You are allowed to use
any ingredients you like.
The rules are simple.
Each will prepare
meals for 100 people.
And the Marines themselves will
decide the contest's winner.
Whoa! I have no idea
what's going on,
but it sounds exciting!
[SANJI]
Start whenever you're ready.
[horn blows]
We can't lose this one, boys!
Cook as if your
life depended on it!
We'll cook using only the best
parts of the ingredients we got!
Huh?
[JESSICA] Is he admitting defeat
by not preparing anything?
--Finished!
--One hundred meals!
Ya like that?
This food looks so good!
Keep you hands off!
Of course, we normally prepare
1,000 servings of each meal.
And we're fast,
like sharks darting for prey!
That is the essence
of being a chef here!
[JESSICA]
Hm?
How terribly wasteful
you all are.
What's that guy up to?
He can't be.
No way.
He's using all our
leftover parts. Whoa.
Pulverize the tuna's bones
along with it's head.
[SANJI]
Next mix in the guts.
[SANJI] Add veggie scraps
and roll the paste into balls.
Then they'll be deep-fried.
Boiling fat trimmed
from the meat
until it becomes
soft and tender...
[SANJI] ...provides the
perfect compliment
to a sauce made from shellfish.
The bitterness of the
guts whets the appetite.
And the powerful flavor gives
new life to a tired body.
This brings us
to the preparation
of the vegetable dish.
The skins of burdock
roots and potatoes
contain more vitamins and
minerals that their insides,
which makes them an
ideal nutrient source.
Finally, broccoli
stems can be used
to create a soft,
sweet scented dressing.
[MARINES gasp]
[SANJI grunts]
Voila!
Cuisine, a la carte!
This is a battlefield, right?
It's important that
the food taste good.
But more important than that
is making sure your
food stores last.
[gasps]
It doesn't matter if you spend
1,000 Berries or a million.
You should never waste
even a single scrap of food.
It is our duty as
cooks to utilize
every bit of our ingredients
with love and skill.
Just like loving
everything about a lady.
A wise old geezer
once taught me that.
[MARINES gasping]
[MARINE X] I've never
tasted anything so good!
[MARINE Y]
This is delicious!
[MARINE Z]
Amazing!
How stupid of us!
We tried to impress the famous
cook and he turned around
and beat us at
working class cuisine!
We did exactly what we shouldn't
have and tried to show off.
The food in
Navarone is different
from the food prepared
for the officers.
It's food for Marines
who live day to day.
That was Jessica's
belief, anyway.
To think that we,
the cooks at Navarone,
were picky about
the ingredients!
[LUFFY]
...87! 88!
--[JESSICA] Hm?
--[LUFFY] 89! 90!
[LUFFY]
91! 92! 93! 94...
Incredible!
Have you guys ever seen anyone
with such an insatiable appetite
for the food we've made?
One hundred!
[ALL gasp]
Are you okay?
[LUFFY panting]
[SHINPACHI]
What's wrong?
Just hang in there!
[LUFFY grunts]
So good!
Heh. Man, I'm stuffed!
Satisfied!
[JESSICA chuckles]
[SANJI]
Let's go.
Yeah. I guess it is
about time we leave, huh?
Thanks for all the
food. Sure was good!
If it had been up to me,
I never would have battled
a woman as beautiful as you.
Until we meet again,
mademoiselle.
Hold it!
[LUFFY] Hm? Did you think of
something else for me to eat?
[JESSICA] Were you planning on
leaving me humiliated like this?
I won't stand for it.
I like your spirit
and your appetite.
As of right now,
you two are part of the team.
[COOKS]
Yeah!
[LUFFY giggles]
My sweet Jessica.
Oh, thank you.
[JONATHAN yawns]
If there's one thing fishing
teaches, it's patience.
Patience. Right, sir.
A valuable attribute.
They may be ignorant pirates,
but don't you think
they would be hiding
somewhere a little
less conspicuous?
This place is in plain
sight of everything.
There are some who
would choose to hide
when there is no
possibility of escape.
But among pirates
of that caliber,
it is certain there
will be one or two
who find the act
of hiding cowardly.
[SERGEANT]
You think so?
[JONATHAN]
Hmm...
Well, it looks like we have
our first catch of the day.
[SERGEANT]
Huh?
Stupid navigator!
Doesn't she understand that a
swordsman needs his swords?
[ZORO grunts]
So close.
[ZORO gasps]
No!
[gasps]
[ZORO gasping]
[ZORO groaning]
[ZORO gasps]
[gasps]
[coughs]
[ZORO]
Nami's got it comin'.
[JONATHAN]
Welcome to Navarone.
[ZORO growls]
A fine catch indeed.
What's going on here?
Beats me.
A future lies before us
waiting to begin
Let's take to the wind!
and search the world for answers
to all the questions
in our minds
Exploring day and night we'll...
...live out our
dreams in paradise!
And that's why...
We're running, and running,
traveling along an open road
Never letting go of
what we came to do
We're here to see this through!
We can't lose, can't lose,
nothing on earth
can stop us now
'Cause we're not afraid
of our own destiny
We Dream and live
our lives free!
[NAMI]
Ugh! You stupid moss head!
[ZORO]
What'd you say?
[NAMI] Getting caught
wasn't part of the plan!
You know what, forget it!
You stay there and
cool off for a while!
Where is everyone else?
Am I the only one that knows
what kind of dire
straits we're in?
Chopper, this is no time to be
playing doctor in the infirmary!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Captured Zoro!
Chopper's Emergency Operations!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!