[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other.
Luffy and the others
found themselves
trapped inside
Raindinners Casino,
but thanks to Sanji's
brave actions,
they were able to
make their escape.
Marine Captain Smoker,
having been saved by
Luffy and company,
allowed them to flee unharmed.
Will Alabasta fall?
Or will it find true peace?
Moment by moment, the sands
of the hourglass of fate
run down towards the final hour.
[LUFFY]
"Merciless Mortal Combat!
Luffy vs. Crocodile"
[MARINE A]
I see them!
After them!
[LUFFY chuckles]
[MARINES shouting]
Captain, aren't you coming?
You go. I'm tired.
You're tired?
Listen.
Sir!
There's no point
pursuing them now.
Have the men call off the chase.
I want everyone
assembled here.
And contact Headquarters.
Tell them to mobilize every
military vessel in the vicinity
and route them here.
I want Alabasta surrounded.
You're calling for
reinforcements, sir?
But, sir, if I may point out,
our superiors may not be willing
to move that many ships
against such a small
number of pirates.
And since when do I care
what the superiors might think.
[MARINE B]
Sorry, sir.
I'll get right on it!
Hey! The pursuit has been
called off! Come back!
Hurry!
Yeah! This way!
The scent of Nami's perfume is
getting stronger and stronger!
[grunts]
[USOPP]
Hey!
Please tell me you
guys aren't planning
to run all the way to Alubarna.
[NAMI]
We've got Eyelash.
Just where the hell is that
stupid camel, anyway?
[LUFFY]
Close, I hope!
Doesn't this town have a stable?
Let's get some horses.
[VIVI] But the whole town
is crawling with Marines!
Not to worry. Look ahead.
Hey, guys! Hop on!
[screams]
A crab!
Chopper!
That's a Moving Crab!
Yummy!
[LUFFY]
Whoa! Awesome!
I can't believe my eyes!
I bet it's delicious!
[CHOPPER]
All aboard!
We get to ride it?!
Pleased to meet ya!
Is it just me, or does its
face look kinda shady.
Who cares? At least
we have a ride.
Say hello! He's
Eyelash's friend!
[EYELASH grunting]
Eyelash has lots of
friends in this area.
Because it's his hometown;
he was born and raised here.
He's nice, but kinda pervy.
[VIVI]
I can't believe you found one!
Moving Crabs are always
submerged under the sand,
so it's nearly
impossible to spot one!
Judging by his size, I'd
say this guy's pretty fast.
Okay! Time to move out!
Hang on, everyone! Here we go!
[screams]
[NAMI, USOPP gasp]
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[screaming]
Chopper, stop the crab!
[LUFFY yelling]
It's him!
[yells]
Hey! Luffy!
That damn idiot!
Luffy, no!
You guys go on ahead!
Don't worry about me!
Make sure you deliver
Vivi home! Safe and sound!
You have to promise me!
[chuckles]
Good luck, you guys.
Idiot.
Hey!
Let's go, Chopper. Just
keep goin' to Alubarna.
Right! Okay.
Let's go, Crab!
[USOPP yelps]
[USOPP]
H‐Hey, hold on!
Wait, Zoro! That's cold!
Stop the crab!
You're not actually gonna
leave him behind, are you?
I can't believe you'd do
something like this.
Well, if Luffy's gone, then you
better protect me damn it.
We gotta go back!
It's all right, Vivi!
He'll be fine!
You have to trust
me on this, okay?
I certainly feel sorry
for the other guy.
Luffy shows no
mercy to his prey.
And there's not a single
person he's gone after
that was able to walk away.
Crocodile will fail.
Luffy will win.
It's that simple.
The moment that the rebel
army started running,
this land's final hour was set.
Once the royal army
and the rebel army meet,
this country, the Kingdom of
Alabasta, will be gone forever.
If you truly are the
one and only hope
for preventing that tragedy,
then you must survive,
no matter what.
So, from this moment forward,
what happens to Luffy,
or any of us for that matter,
isn't the least bit important!
But...
[SANJI]
Vivi.
This is a fight that you
and you alone started.
You're the one who bravely
left this land years ago
and made the decision
to stand up
against a corrupt and
evil organization.
However...
Don't make the mistake of
thinking you're alone anymore.
Yeah, that's right!
Don't worry, because...
...because Captain Usopp
is going to protect you.
[VIVI]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Listen! We'll be
waiting for you.
We'll be in Alubarna.
Yeah!
[MISS ALL SUNDAY chuckles]
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
You could say Princess Vivi
slipped through our fingers.
No matter.
The Agents are still scheduled
to gather in Alubarna.
Contact them at once.
Straw Hat, I'd say you've taken
this nonsense a little too far.
[LUFFY] Nonsense?
Vivi doesn't see it that way.
Ya see, unlike most people,
she genuinely cares
about others.
[CROCODILE]
Huh.
[LUFFY] I guess, deep down,
she's an optimist,
even if it's not too realistic.
Take this revolt, for example.
She believes no
one needs to die.
Nobody needs to die?
The problem with idealistic
fools like Princess Vivi
is they take a stand without
any comprehension
of what is truly involved
in a real fight.
Wouldn't you agree?
Yep.
[LUFFY]
But that doesn't change the fact
that as long as you're around,
Vivi's gonna fight until she
either wins or dies trying.
So, I figure...
...I'll take you down,
right here!
[laughs]
Such a foolish boy.
Despite what the
idealists cry about,
there's one constant truth.
On the rough battlefields of
life, you either kill or die.
That's why I'm more than
happy to shoot a bullet
through every bleeding
heart I meet.
Yeah. Which proves you're
the bigger fool here.
[growling]
[chuckles]
You think something's funny?
Perhaps you'd like to die
as well, Nico Robin.
If you wanna try,
go right ahead.
And didn't you promise not
to call me by that name?
[CROCODILE]
Where are you going?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY] I'm headed
to Alubarna. See ya there.
Damn woman. I'll
never figure her out.
I've got three minutes to spare.
[CROCODILE]
After that,
I'm certain your time
will've run out as well.
[CROCODILE] Your three
minutes are counting down.
I don't have any more time to
waste on the likes of you.
It's your move kid.
[LUFFY]
With pleasure.
Gum‐Gum...
...Pistol!
[growls]
And Gum‐Gum...
...Stamp!
[growls]
By now it should be quite
obvious, but I'll warn you.
You cannot defeat me.
This is an exercise in futility.
Gum‐Gum... Gatling!
[LUFFY yelling]
[chuckles]
Listen to my warning
and take heed.
If you continue this
senseless attack,
you will have
accomplished nothing.
And wasted what little
time you have left!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
...Bazooka!
[LUFFY yells]
Good riddance! You lousy
old sand gator!
Your wasting your time, boy.
[LUFFY growls]
You bastard!
No matter how hard you
fight against the truth,
there's no way a
rubber freak like you
could even hope to rival me.
[growls]
[CROCODILE]
You'll‐‐
I'm sorry. My fist
interrupted you!
Now what was that?
[growling]
[CROCODILE] I've had my fill
of your pathetic fun and games.
Let's end this. Now.
Fun and games?
Trust me, I'm dead
serious! Jerk!
Damn it, he's right though.
He's got an answer for
all of my attacks.
What do I do now?
We may both be pirates,
but you fall grossly
short on skill.
Desert Spada!
[CROCODILE]
Nice reflexes, boy.
A full‐on hit from that
attack would've killed you.
What the‐‐?!
That's one deep hole!
You may have Devil Fruit powers,
but you lack discipline
and training.
With that, your skills could
be as formidable as any.
But you're not there yet.
Like so many fools,
you waste time obsessing
over your abilities.
Gimmicks get you only
so far in a fight
without the skills‐set
to back them up.
Desert Girasole!
[LUFFY screams]
What in the‐‐? What's going on?
[LUFFY yelling]
The sand... It's
sinking! What is this?!
[LUFFY grunting]
What is this stuff?!
Let me out, let me out,
let me out, let me out!
[CROCODILE] What's wrong?
Never heard of quicksand?
It makes for a convenient
desert burial
when you need to get rid
of someone in a hurry.
The sand is drawn down into
underground waterways.
And I have the good fortune
of being able to detect
exactly where they are.
That advantage alone is enough
to make me unbeatable
when fighting in the desert.
[LUFFY] If you think I'm gonna
let myself be buried alive
in this sand trap, you
got another thing comin'!
You bastard!
Gum‐Gum...
...Bazooka!
If I can't slug you,
then maybe...
...I can catch you instead!
Gum‐Gum... Net!
Haven't you learned
anything, moron?
Predictable.
Shut up.
Gum‐Gum... Whip!
This is really getting old.
[LUFFY screams]
[LUFFY]
Let me go! I'm warning you!
[CROCODILE]
Crescent Cutlass!
My‐My arm!
[screams]
[LUFFY]
What did you do?!
It's all shriveled‐up!
Like a mummy!
You turned my arm into a mummy!
[CROCODILE]
Stop whining.
This is the price you pay.
The sand has absorbed all
the moisture from your arm.
You're lucky. All I decided
to attack was your arm.
I can do this all day long,
until you're a pile of dust.
You gotta be kidding me!
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
That's it! Water!
[CROCODILE]
Hm?
All in vain.
You're wrong, Sandy!
You see, that old guy in Yuba
gave me this barrel of water.
He spent all night digging
it up just for me!
Luffy, here, take this with you.
He's not scared,
and neither am I.
I'm not about to give into
the sand... without a fight!
Gum‐Gum...
This is getting ridiculous.
[LUFFY]
...Munch‐Munch!
Enough! This ends now!
[LUFFY coughing]
Vermin. It is time to die.
Both you and the
accursed land of Yuba.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[CROCODILE]
Your three minutes are up.
Like I said at the start,
I don't have time to fool
around with you any longer.
Now, Sables!
[LUFFY yells]
Ah, the sand's so
soothing and dry.
[TOWNSFOLK A]
Look out! Sandstorm!
Right ahead! In the sky!
[TOWNSFOLK B]
Take shelter!
[TOWNSFOLK C]
Wait a minute!
No, it's not coming this way!
It's headed south!
Captain Smoker, look! Up there!
[USOPP]
Vivi? What's wrong?
[VIVI] There's a giant storm
moving toward Rainbase!
It's Crocodile.
Luffy, no.
[CROCODILE] Listen carefully.
Can you hear it move?
In this land, the
prevailing winds
always blow from north to south.
And so, if this infantile
sandstorm of mine were, to say,
catch one of these winds,
it would grow exponentially
until it became a monster.
And, following its
trajectory south,
where do you think
it would strike?
Tell me!
In Yuba.
[gasps]
No, not there!
Dammit! Why the hell are
you doing this?! Stop it!
Look, it started.
It's headed south.
That nice old man has
nothing to do with this!
Do you hear me?!
Stop it, or I swear
I'll kill you, you bastard!
You leave that old man alone!
[yells]
[CROCODILE laughs]
[CROCODILE]
You cannot alter fate.
That sandstorm is going
to pick up strength.
And eventually, it will
become strong enough
that even I can't stop it.
I don't believe you! Liar!
Yuba is finished.
If you don't end
this now, I will!
[thud]
[CROCODILE] Did you really
think you were my equal?
[CROCODILE] There have been any
number of rookies like you
who've challenged me.
And you've all shared a common
trait: Fatal ineptitude.
And in the end,
the only thing you are truly
qualified for is death.
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[USOPP] What? The crab
can't cross this river?
[VIVI] He's a desert creature,
so he can't handle the water.
[USOPP]
But it's still a crab.
Make it work!
[NAMI]
Do something. C'mon, Scissors.
[CHOPPER] I know!
Scissors loves dancer girls!
[NAMI]
Will this do?
[SANJI, EYELASHES gasp]
[ZORO] You're messing him
up with all this nonsense!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Dash For a Miracle!
Alabasta Animal Land."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!