Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the next
King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use
any means necessary
to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue.
The crew will cut a path
across the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison, Impel Down!
Now he's racing down
to Level 5 with the help
of escaped prisoner
Buggy the Clown.
[BUGGY]
I got the key to the treasure,
I got that chump off my back
and soon, I'll be free!
I robbed you, got my revenge.
And you thanked me for it!
[BUGGY laughs]
Stupid! You can't chop me!
What do you think the
Chop-Chop Fruit is for?
[LUFFY]
The Strongest Man in the Prison!
Poison Man Magellan Appears!
[BUGGY screams]
I busted out of
my cell to escape,
not to end up in an even
worse hell than before!
[BUGGY groans]
[MONSTERS growling]
Creepy!
But...
[BUGGY] At least now I
have this! Which puts me
that much closer to finding
Captain John's treasure.
All I have to do is
find my way out of--
[BUGGY groans]
Okay, let's go!
Just tell me the way!
What the--?
Hold on a second!
[MONSTERS growling]
[LUFFY panting]
It's a dead end.
So, Level 2, huh?
[BUGGY grunts, pants]
That's right.
They call it the Wild Beast Hell
and it's even worse
than the Crimson Hell
on Level 1.
Damn it. Don't run off with
my head, I can't catch up!
Anyway, this floor is
swimming with giant monsters
that'll swallow you
up in one bite!
[LUFFY]
Oh yeah? Wow.
[BUGGY]
All right, focus.
Until I can find a way
out of this dump,
I gotta take advantage of
Straw Hat any way I can.
[LUFFY]
Is that one of them there?
[BUGGY] You're kiddin' me--
It found us already?
[growling]
[HIPPO whines]
Looks like a hippo to me.
[BUGGY]
Yeah, it does.
[LUFFY] He's a lot smaller
than a regular hippo.
That's really a "wild beast"?
[BUGGY]
That's funny.
I always heard Level 2
was full of big, savage--
What the hell?
What is this thing?
Run!
[BUGGY, LUFFY panting]
Awesome! Look! Little guy's
pretty fast for a hippo!
Stop admiring it!
Turn left! Quick!
[LUFFY, BUGGY panting]
[BUGGY laughs]
Nice one, you runt!
You run fast,
but you're not too hot
when it comes to turning, huh?
[LUFFY, BUGGY yelp]
Uh, hey, are you
sure it's all right
for him to eat
your body like that?
Yeah. It's no big deal.
Keep running-- I'll show you
what a Chop-Chop man can do!
[HIPPO yelps]
[LUFFY, BUGGY grunt]
[HIPPO groans]
Whoa! How did you manage that?
[BUGGY cackles]
Even if my body parts are
chopped into tiny pieces,
I can still move them
around however I want!
[BUGGY]
That'll teach you! Stupid hippo!
[BUGGY cackling]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL buzzing]
Who is that? The other guy.
Standing there behind Buggy.
[LUFFY, BUGGY panting]
[BUGGY] There's gotta be
some way out of this
crappy situation. I can't
just run around forever.
[BUGGY, LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY]
What's wrong?
[BUGGY]
I thought I saw something.
[LUFFY]
Maybe it was a bat.
[BUGGY screams]
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
It's some kind of
monster mantis!
[LUFFY]
I think you're right.
Way too big for
a regular mantis.
[BUGGY, LUFFY gasp]
Whoa! He cuts like a champ!
Stop admiring the enemy!
If I get chopped up
much more than this,
it's gonna be a big problem!
He's cool. You think
we could be friends?
Ugh. What's wrong with you?
Can't you see we're in danger?
[MANTIS yelling]
[MANTIS grunting]
Hey, look at that.
I think he's stuck.
[LUFFY]
What should we do?
[BUGGY]
Maybe we should, uhh...
[LUFFY]
Eh, Let's just go.
[BUGGY]
Mm-hm.
So are these things really
the "Wild Beasts of Hell"?
They just don't seem like
that big of a deal to me.
You're right, they aren't
as bad as I'd heard.
Everything on Level 1 was
way more terrifying than this.
Maybe they're just called that
to dissuade anyone
from trying to--
[LUFFY, BUGGY grunt]
[MANTIS yelps]
[LUFFY]
What the heck was that?
[BUGGY gasps]
[BOTH] Holy crap! Now that's
a Wild Beast of Hell!
Wait. I know that face.
[BUGGY, LUFFY screaming]
[BUGGY]
Dammit! The rumors are true!
This thing's gonna eat us
whole! Why am I even here?
I didn't wanna go to Level 2
in the first place!
I was trying to escape
and leave you behind!
You're bad luck!
Everything that sucks in
my life is all your fault!
[LUFFY]
What? Did you say something?
And what is this
thing chasing us?
From the looks of it,
I'd say it's the rarest kind
of monster in existence.
A snake born from a chicken egg.
A Basilisk!
[LUFFY] That thing
came out of a chicken?
[BUGGY] I said it was
a monster, didn't I?
These things shouldn't
even be allowed to live,
let alone run free!
They eat people like snacks,
So they locked 'em up here where
they can only eat criminals!
[BUGGY, LUFFY yelping]
What are you doing? Run!
I don't have time
for this, snake bird!
[LUFFY]
I'm gonna kick your ass!
You're the one who's gonna
get your ass kicked, moron!
Hey, wait a second.
Now I can escape!
I'll leave the rest
to you. Sound good?
See ya, Straw Hat!
Third Gear!
[LUFFY yells]
[SKINNY GUARD] Attention,
jailers on Level 2! Attention!
We've identified the man
with Buggy the Clown!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
The Straw Hat Luffy?
What's he doing in Impel Down?
[SKINNY GUARD] Just capture
them both immediately!
Dead or alive,
it doesn't matter!
Let's go!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[GUARDS]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Giant Pistol!
[GUARDS scream]
[SKINNY GUARD]
What was that? What happened?
Aw crap. This cannot be good.
It's getting hot.
[DOMINO] Well, as the
Vice Warden told you before,
the Warden's office
is located on Level 4,
which is known as
the Burning Heat Floor.
Aside from his office,
the whole floor is an inferno.
There. We've finally arrived.
[MOMONGA]
Well, where is he?
Where is this Warden?
[DOMINO]
Warden Magellan suffers from
terrible digestive problems,
so he stays in the bathroom
an average of 10 hours
a day, seven days a week.
Of course, he sleeps
about 8 hours each night.
So once you factor in
mealtimes and breaks
he only works about
four hours a day.
Is that really enough
time to do his job?
When the need arises,
he's the right man.
Oh. We're in luck.
Sounds like he's coming out.
And I forgot to
mention it before,
but the Warden ate
the Venom-Venom Fruit.
So he's a poison man.
Poison man?
[DOMINO]
Yes. Please, be careful.
[GUARDS]
Excellent work, Warden.
[GUARD 425F] You showed those
bowels who's boss, sir.
[MAGELLAN groans]
[MAGELLAN] As always,
it was a rough battle in there!
You must be our guests.
I'm Magellan, the Warden here.
[MAGELLAN]
This room is too bright!
For the record,
I much prefer places
that are dark, cold, and
closed off. Just like my heart.
[HANNYABAL]
Stop being ridiculous.
Now, listen.
Vice Admiral Momonga and
the Warlord Boa Hancock
are here on important business.
And our time is short,
Warden Magellan.
[MAGELLAN]
Ah! My apologies!
I have a bad case of
the runs, I'm afraid.
The poison soup I had for
breakfast this morning
isn't quite agreeing with me.
[HANNYABAL] Well, what do
you expect? It's poison!
Oh, come on-- I'm a
poison man! I love poison!
It's just like
the old saying goes.
"Poison kills poison" I believe?
[HANNYABAL] Well, that's why
you have venomous diarrhea.
Yes, and I'm afraid that you
have a venomous
tongue, Hannyabal.
[HANNYABAL] Hurry up and retire
so I can become Warden.
Oopsie! I mean, uh, please hurry
and show our guests
to "Fire Fist".
Yeah, right!
Like that was a
slip of the tongue!
It saddens my heart to
know that my colleague
thinks so little of me.
[HANNYABAL groans]
[DOMINO]
Put these on.
[HANNYABAL] Warden! Please,
be careful when you exhale!
Your breath is poisonous gas!
Are you trying to kill everyone?
[MAGELLAN laughing]
Hey! What the hell is so funny?
Serves you right.
Stupid Vice Warden.
And I have the venomous tongue?
Fool! You dare breathe
your disgusting poison
in the face of an
empress? How rude!
Ugh! She's stepping on me!
And I think I like it!
[HANNYABAL]
Lucky punk.
[DOMINO]
Vice Warden.
You realize that's the
Warden's seat you're in.
It'll be mine soon enough.
[MOMONGA]
We don't have time for this!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL 425B rings]
Yes? This is the
Warden's Office.
Hey! Don't answer my phone!
Oh, no! I'm dying...
[HANNYABAL] Damn it.
I just wanted to be Warden.
[DOMINO] Retrieve an antidote
for the Vice Warden.
[GUARD 425E]
Right!
What's that?
You say someone
broke into the prison?
Absurd! This is Impel Down.
No one has ever
infiltrated its walls.
Our defenses are flawless. How
could we possibly allow this?
It is indeed a travesty.
And it was on
your watch, Warden.
[HANCOCK]
Have they found us out?
Transfer the video
footage to my chambers!
[HANCOCK]
Warden?
[MAGELLAN]
Hm?
I was wondering.
Would it be possible
to see the prisoner? Now?
Sure! Let's go! Like. Right now!
Warden! Wake up!
We kind of need you
to deal with this!
[GUARDS clamoring]
Now that's odd.
It appears that we've lost
contact with Warden Magellan!
I want a report on
every level of this place
sent to the jailer's room
and Navy Headquarters now!
I don't know why he's here,
and I have no clue
what he might be up to, but,
that guy who's wreaking so much
havoc with Buggy the Clown
on Level 2 is definitely
Straw Hat Luffy!
Something's up.
We lost contact with the
jailer's room on Level 2!
What?
[GUARD 425H]
Damn it!
This whole place
is going to hell!
What's going on?
Well, don't give up yet!
Stay on the line until
they reply, got that?
Sir!
[SKINNY GUARD]
Jailer's room on Level 2!
What's going on down there?
What's wrong?
[BUGGY sputters]
Got 'im!
His fist! It was huge!
Gum-Gum...
Giant Pistol!
[LUFFY panting]
Why in the hell
are you so small?
[LUFFY]
'Cause I used Third Gear!
Heh. Takes care a' him
There we go! I'm back!
Okey dokey. Let's get moving.
[PRISONER 425A]
The God of Salvation
has descended into Hell!
[PRISONER 425B]
He beat the Basilisk!
I saw it myself!
[PRISONER 425C]
Yes! The monster is down!
He got him!
[PRISONER 425D] You did it!
You guys are amazing!
[PRISONER 425E] They destroyed
the jailer's room, too!
It's a miracle!
They must be angels
sent from heaven!
I don't know who you
two are, but thank you!
Hey, could you hand
us those keys, too?
They're for these
cuffs and the doors!
[PRISONER 425H]
They're right there!
See them? Over there
on the ground!
[PRISONER 425I]
What's he doing?
C'mon! We gotta get goin'!
Don't be in such a rush!
We're supposed to be
saving my brother!
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
What is he doing down here?
[MR. 3] He's not in a cell,
nor in a prison uniform.
And it looks like he's
on his way out of here.
Alright! An opportunity
like this one
simply won't happen again!
It's now or never!
As much as I thought otherwise,
it seems heaven hasn't
forsaken me just yet!
[BUGGY] Heh. Hey, boys!
Is this what you're looking for?
[PRISONERS cheer]
[PRISONERS]
Yeah, that's it! That's it!
--Give it to me!
--Let us outta here!
Hm? Now is that any way
to ask someone for a favor?
[PRISONERS]
We're sorry! We're begging you!
That was inexcusable!
We apologize!
[BUGGY] Hm? What was that?
I couldn't hear you.
[LUFFY] Yes, you could.
What the heck are you doing?
[PRISONERS]
Please, sir!
[BUGGY]
Alright! You got it!
One set of keys,
coming right up!
Complements of Captain Buggy!
Accept it with gratitude!
[PRISONERS cheering]
[PRISONER]
We're free! We're free!
We're finally out
of those damn cells!
[PRISONERS clamoring]
[BUGGY cackles]
That's right! Now I ask you.
What's the glorious
name of the man
who has given you
your sweet freedom?
[PRISONER 425J]
It's Captain Buggy!
And we're in your debt forever!
[PRISONER 425K] Anybody
talking bad about Buggy's
gonna answer to us!
[BUGGY cackles]
That's me! And don't you scum
ever forget it! Now!
Unlock the other cells!
Set everyone free!
[PRISONERS cheer]
[BUGGY] Once these morons start
wreaking havoc on this place,
I'll finally have a chance
to sneak out on my own!
[BUGGY groans] Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
[LUFFY] You done?
Good! Then it's my turn!
Back to the plan! Lead me
down to the next level!
Isn't there a hole like
last time, or something?
[BUGGY] How should I know?
This place is like a maze!
You expect me to remember
the details of every floor?
Find your own damned
way to Level 3!
[PRISONERS laughing]
[PRISONER 425L] Thanks for
everything, Captain Buggy!
[PRISONER 425M]
I can smell freedom already!
[MONSTERS growling]
[PRISONERS gasp]
[PRISONERS scream]
[BUGGY grumbling]
Stop it, Straw Hat! Put me down!
[LUFFY]
Why should I?
You said you'd lead me
all the way down to Level 4,
and now you're gonna do it!
[BUGGY] I lied, okay?
I just wanted the treasure,
so I lied to get it!
With all those prisoners free,
the chaos will be immeasurable!
And when that happens, I'll--
Wait, what was that? You lied?
[BUGGY laughs]
[footsteps]
[PRISONERS screaming]
[LUFFY, BUGGY yelp]
[BUGGY] What are you
idiots doing? You're free!
This is your chance to raise
hell and get outta here!
We, uh. We just remembered
why we never tried to do that.
Escape is impossible.
Especially with those wild
beasts running around.
Yeah. Dying is for the birds.
We're way better
off in this cell.
[BUGGY screams] Okay! I've
changed my mind, Straw Hat.
I'll show you the way
to Level 3. Let's go!
What?
But you just said you didn't
know the way, Big Nose!
My nose is perfect! How rude!
[MR. 3] I couldn't help
but overhear you.
If you're having trouble
on this floor, I can help.
[BUGGY]
Is that so. Who're you?
[MR. 3 laughs] Long time
no see, Straw Hat Luffy!
You helped me out
without noticing.
How fortunate.
I am a man who always
pays back his debts.
[LUFFY] Do I know you?
[MR. 3 gasps]
Wait! It's the "3" hair!
Holy Crap! Look at his hair!
[MR. 3]
You just shut up!
It's a three! And, it's on fire!
Candle Lock!
Oh yeah! This should be perfect!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
Mallet!
[MR. 3 laughing] Why, just a
little game of hide and seek.
Can you figure out
which one is me?
You're just another buffoon
who acts on blind instinct
and uses brute force
to solve all his problems.
I am a Baroque Works agent.
Every assignment
that is given to me
I see through to its end.
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
Stamp!
[MR. 3 groaning]
How'd you know
which one was me?
Hunch.
Oh, yeah! You were on the island
with the giants, right? Three!
[MR. 3]
Mister Three, you fool!
[MR. 3 laughing]
[MARINE 425A]
Fleet Admiral!
We've just received an emergency
report from Impel Down!
[SENGOKU]
Huh? What's going on now?
Tell me! Is it Whitebeard?
[MARINE 425A]
No, sir.
Straw Hat Luffy has
infiltrated the prison.
[SENGOKU]
What? Straw Hat?
What is he doing there?
I thought Bartholomew Kuma
had taken care of
that little troublemaker!
Yes. That's the same report
that I had heard as well, sir.
But what bothers me
even more is why a pirate
would sneak into Impel Down.
Do you have any clue
what he might be planning?
[MARINE 425A]
Sir?
Well, regardless of
what Straw Hat's
got up his sleeve, it's the end
of the road for him this time.
That is to say, he picked
the wrong place to break into.
[SENGOKU]
Impel Down has successfully held
hundreds of thousands of
criminals over the years.
Many of them notorious
pirates with powers
as fearsome as
their reputations.
Their defenses are legendary
and they're prepared
for almost any situation.
[SENGOKU] Of course, it was
the guard's incompetence
that allowed him to enter.
But either way,
Straw Hat will never
leave that place alive.
Only one man has.
[MARINE 425A]
Really?
20 long years ago.
He became the first
and only person.
In the history of
Impel Down to escape.
A pirate named Shiki,
the Golden Lion.
[MARINE 425A]
Shiki? The Golden Lion...
[NARRATOR]
In the history of Impel Down,
only one man has ever managed
to escape from its walls.
His name is Shiki,
the Golden Lion.
20 years later, in what
we now know as the present,
the Straw Hats encounter a giant
beetle and find themselves
wrapped up in Shiki's plans.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
A Special Presentation
Related to the Movie:
A Gold Lion's
Ambition on the Move.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!