Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Those fools braved
Aqua Laguna to get here.
They're determined,
if nothing else.
Humph.
Either that,
or they're just lucky.
Remember, we have
permission to kill this time.
But if we kill them, it'll be
over before we have any fun.
The drawbridge?
Yeah.
The Franky Family's trying
to get that under
control right now.
Once they bring it down,
we should be able to get to
the other side, no problem.
What a pain.
She's right there and
all we can do is wait.
CP9.
I tried to leave
everything behind.
The last thing I wanted
was for you to come after me.
Why did you do it?
But for now, I want to
talk about Nico Robin.
What do you know?
When you first came to Water 7,
did she start acting strangely?
Yeah. She did.
She went into town that day
and then never came back.
By the next morning,
she was the prime suspect
in your attempted murder.
When Sanji and Chopper
finally saw her again,
she said this was goodbye
and wouldn't be a part
of the crew anymore.
Of course, none of that
made any sense to us,
so, we decided to
break into your mansion,
in hopes that we'd be able
to see her one more time
and find out the truth.
I did it to make
my wish come true.
One that can't happen
as long as we're together.
If you can't accept
that, I'm sorry.
What kind of wish
would force her
to give up all
of her friends?
I think I know the
answer, actually.
This probably started
shortly after you lost sight
of her for the first time.
CP9.
The government had begun
its operation the
moment she arrived.
In other words,
there's a good reason
why your friend
did what she did.
But before I go
into the details,
I want you to understand
that both Nico Robin
and I have the means to
revive an ancient weapon
that is capable of
destroying the entire world.
A weapon?
That's right.
Click.
It's me. We've hit
a snag in the plan.
Everyone head to the
bedroom immediately.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
Do you understand now?
The blueprints that
they found are fake!
I don't care.
I would rather die than
hand over that information
to the government.
But now it's not that simple.
If you've decided that
you're going to help them,
and you're searching for
the Poneglyphs yourself,
then I have to do everything
I can to stop you!
I understand your concern,
but I'm only studying the
Poneglyphs to learn more
about the history of the world.
I don't care about the weapon.
You have to take responsibility!
I told you this would happen.
But you don't listen.
Franky, even if
you weren't trying to.
Weapons are made to hurt people.
Whether you want them to or not,
they can hurt your friends.
Even if you don't
have malicious intent,
your actions can
still hurt people!
If your curiosity
for history leads
to the destruction of the world,
then you're better off
dying right here and
right now, Nico Robin!
Even after seeing what happened
to the devils of Ohara, you
still want to walk this path?
You don't know a
damned thing about Ohara!
You have no idea how
much the World Government
has warped my life,
do you hear me?
If you hate the government
so much, then why help them?
Because I have a wish that
I would sacrifice anything for.
When I came to this town,
CP-9 presented me
with two conditions.
The first was to
pin your assassination
on the Straw Hats
and leave their crew.
The second was to turn
myself over to the government
and follow their every
order without question.
You realize, they
won't let you live.
You escaped them for 20 years.
Why would you agree to
something like that now?
In this particular instance,
CP9 has been given permission
to activate a Buster Call
against the Straw Hats.
A Buster Call?
It's an emergency order that
summons five vice admirals
and ten battleships
to the same location.
No matter how strong you are,
no one can survive a full-scale
military attack of that caliber.
Under normal circumstances,
only the three admirals
and the head of the navy,
the fleet admiral,
are allowed to exercise
that kind of authority.
However, this is a special case.
Just this once,
Admiral Aokiji has given
CP-9 the right to make the call.
When I heard his name,
I surrendered.
If I hadn't agreed to their
conditions, then me and the rest
of the Straw Hats
would've been annihilated.
For the past 20 years, I've been
able to run away and survive,
no matter what the circumstance,
but that's only because
I had nothing to protect.
Because I was willing to betray
others and use them as a shield.
But not now.
For the first time in all
these years, I can't do that.
They picked up the
life I gave up on.
Returned the heart I lost.
And continued the dreams
that I no longer believed in.
Even after all I've done,
I've found friends who
will still believe in me.
I see, but then
what is your wish?
That excluding me, all of
the other Straw Hat pirates
will be allowed to
leave this island safely!
And as long as you can
have that, you don't care about
what happens to
the rest of the world?
I don't.
Luffy!
You idiot!
What the hell are
you doing up there?
Nami? Where are you?
I can't see!
Okay, listen, listen,
it's not my fault.
That pigeon guy sent me flying
and I got stuck between these
buildings, so I can't move.
I'm trying, though!
Is this a joke to you?
We don't have time for this!
Those guys from the
government took Robin away
and you weren't
even there to help!
She did it all for us, you know!
She's going to
sacrifice herself!
The government was planning
an on attack on us,
but Robin turned herself over
to CP9 so we would be safe!
She knew they would kill her,
but she didn't care!
Then, Robin was
lying this whole time?
I'm glad.
Whoa-hoa! Awesome!
Check out the face!
That's so cool!
Unlike the Puffing Tom,
this one here's a crazy train.
Its name is "Rocketman."
Comes with no guarantees,
so board at your own risk.
Good! Now, let's take off!
Now Departing Water
Seven for Enies Lobby!
Here comes Rocketman!
Yeah! Full speed!
Let's go! We'll get it all back!
Cool!
Take this!
Every man and every nation in
the world must answer to me!
All that power at
the tip of my fingers!
I don't understand.
Why would Aokiji allow you
to invoke the Buster Call?
What gives you any
right to question me?
You shut your mouth!
You get to play a part in
the rebirth of this world!
Isn't that enough for you,
you insolent witch?
Why, you should
even be thanking me!
Yeah? Huh?
I'll cleanse this world
of Ohara's legacy
by bleeding you dry.
Nico Robin.
Hurry!
Run to the evacuation ship!
Save those books!
Someone take these!
We weren't trying to
uncover some dark secret.
We simply wanted
to hear the voices
of the past and protect them.
Stop it! I wanna stay with you!
Mommy! No!
You must live, Robin!
Now you listen to me.
You may be lonely at first.
But one day you'll
find true friends.
True friends?
Yeah.
The sea's a vast place,
so I guarantee.
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
Monster!
She's so scary her mom ran away!
No matter who you are,
ain't no one born into
this world to be alone!
Someday, you'll know.
They said she's one
of the devils of Ohara.
You know, those scholars who
were plotting to end the world?
Don't let her get away!
Now, give me my money!
I told you where
she was hiding, didn't I?
A devil like you
shouldn't even exist!
Your friends are out there
at sea waiting for you, Robin.
All you gotta do is find them!
Sniper King.
Hm?
Shoot down that flag.
Roger.
This my new weapon, a massive
slingshot by the name of Kabuto!
Behold its awesome power!
Special Attack Firebird Star!
No way!
Mission complete.
You're all going to die!
You morons can't challenge the
entire world and expect to win!
Yeah? Bring it on!
Robin! There's still
something I wanna hear you say!
Tell me you wanna live!
I can live?
Face it!
Your whole existence
is nothing but a crime!
The whole world's
against you Robin!
You can't be allowed to live!
I never dared to wish
for something like that.
The world had
denied me that hope.
The sea's a vast place,
so, I guarantee.
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
But now.
If I'm allowed to say
my wish, just this once.
Then I--
I want to live!
Take me with you!
Take me away from here!
Let's go!
All right, move it!
As long as I've got CP9 here,
I'm practically invincible!
What? What the hell is it?
Let's go!
The reason she's
wearing sunglasses is
because anything she
looks at will turn to stone.
Such is the life of a Gorgon.
But on this particular
day, Rodusa has
an entirely different reason
for not looking at anyone.
Found you, monster!
All right, Dragon.
Hand over your legendary horns.
Oh, give it up already!
That hurts!
And anyway, who are
you calling a monster?
C'mon, help me fish instead.
There's supposed to be a
legendary fish in these waters.
This is what life is like in
the carefree monster village
found inside Monster Forest.
Its name, is Monstown.
Looks like you gotta bite!
I can't believe I fell
for that delicious bait!
Come on! You again, Choppaken?
What were you doing at the
bottom of the ocean, anyway?
I was looking for
the legendary treasure
that's supposed to be
down there somewhere.
Anyway, think you could give
me some more of that bait?
Hold it, Choppaken!
Don't put one single tentacle on
that legendary treasure, got it?
If I grab it first,
it's finders keepers, right?
Of all the nerve!
You wanna fight about it?
Scary.
Is one of you slimy bastards
giving my Stronami a hard time?
Cause I'll crush you!
Hey. Why the hell are
you trying to catch me?
You're the legendary fish.
I'm a kappa, dammit! Not a fish!
Yeah, a perverted kappa
that lives under the sea.
Now prepare yourself!
Says the minotaur
that looks like a cow.
Nice spots, tough guy.
Shut your hole!
And while I'm here,
I'll be taking
that legendary saucer
you got on your head.
No way, Bessie.
This thing keeps me alive.
But since we're talking
about legendary things,
those iron clubs you've
got are just what I need.
Just try to take 'em!
Stop it! That's enough!
All of you!
Legendary this, legendary that.
Don't you get it?
You're all legendary creatures!
Wait a minute, Rodusa!
We're only looking because
we all saw you crying
when you lost your
legendary earrings earlier
and wanted to help you
find something even rarer!
Hey! That was a secret!
And so the reason she
wouldn't look at her friends,
was not because
she was a Gorgon,
but because she was
hiding her tears of joy.
Oh, you guys. Thank you!
Such is life in Monstown,
the carefree monster village.