[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
Golden bells and birds, huh?
Do you think they
might be symbols
of some ancient
Jayan civilization?
[exhales] I really
couldn't say for certain,
but I'm pretty sure all
these pieces were part
of the same casting.
This creature is
called a South Bird.
You can still find them
on this island today.
Wow, and they
have a peculiar call?
Uh‐huh. Just like
in the logbook.
Sailors have used
South Birds on ships
since ancient times
to help them na‐‐
[CRICKET, MASIRA, SHOJO]
Oh, no!
[CREW]
What's wrong?
You guys gotta get to the forest
on the south side of
the island right away!
How come? Why?
[SANJI]
What do we need the bird for?
Now listen carefully!
Tomorrow you're going
to sail for the Knock‐Up Stream.
It lies directly south of here.
How are you gonna get there?
Have you forgotten
this is the Grand Line?
You're heading for open sea!
You won't be able
to get your bearings.
Wait, he's right.
Without a land
mass to lock onto,
the Log Pose will be useless
and there'll be no way
for us to navigate.
There is if you
can lay your hands
on one of these birds!
[BELLAMY]
I heard the sad story
of the Montblanc family
back at the tavern.
It moved me to tears.
But stealing another man's
treasure moves me even more.
I'm a pirate.
Cricket!
Maybe you'd like to
know what people call me
before I take your
whole life's work.
The Hyena!
[laughs]
[LUFFY]
"Dreams Don't Come True?!
Bellamy Versus
the Saruyama Alliance!"
[SOUTH BIRD]
Duuuuu!
[LUFFY, CHOPPER scream]
[LUFFY]
Chopper! Watch out!
Duuuuu!
[LUFFY] Something's wrong
with these things!
They aren't normal!
[screams]
What's wrong with this forest?
Duuuuu!
[CHOPPER]
It's his fault!
[LUFFY]
Whose?
[CHOPPER]
The South Bird!
It's him! He's
controlling the bugs!
[LUFFY] He can control
bugs and guide ships?
Shh! Quiet.
You guys hear anything?
Somethin'.
But it sure doesn't
sound like any bird to me.
Up there!
[SANJI]
What the‐‐?
What are they? Boulders?
Yeah, it looks
like an avalanche!
No, you're wrong! They're bugs!
[SANJI]
Ladybugs!
[USOPP]
Big ones!
Heh heh heh! Heh heh heh!
[ZORO]
Ugh.
There's no end to them!
They just keep popping up!
Stupid crickets!
Oh come on!
You think you can beat me?
Do ya?
[SOUTH BIRD]
Duuuuu!
[ROBIN]
I wish those birds
were as easy to see
as they are to hear.
[SANJI] A slug that
size needs a lot of salt!
How can you think of
cooking at a time like this?
[SANJI] I'm not,
salt dissolves slugs, idiot!
Duuuuu...
I'm sick of all this running!
Let's stand and fight!
Come on, you bugs, bring it on!
[CHOPPER]
No, Luffy!
Just one sting
and you're history!
[USOPP]
Fireflies!
[NAMI]
Pretty!
Eww! Roaches!
[USOPP]
Pigs!
[USOPP, NAMI scream]
[SOUTH BIRD]
Duuuuu!
If you're looking for a fight,
you've come to the right place.
You're gonna regret mockin'
the Saruyama Alliance!
[ROSS]
Get 'em!
[SARQUISS]
Hand over the gold, old man!
Do it quickly and
we may even let you live!
You forgot to say "please."
Huh? Old man.
[MASIRA]
Monkey Punch!
You know it's dangerous
for a kid like you
to be playing
with such a big knife.
Looks like the boys
might actually need a hand.
Guess I better
show 'em how it's done!
Spring
Sniper!
Huh?
Huh?!
[LILY]
Way to go, Bellamy!
Yeah!
[giggles]
[laughs]
So whaddaya think about
our captain's "Spring‐Spring
Fruit" powers, old man?
Aw, he's speechless!
[laughs]
[BELLAMY]
Clean up this trash!
Now!
And be quick about it!
[SARQUISS laughs]
Well, so much for the
Saruyama Alliance!
Just an old man
and two smelly apes!
What a joke!
[EDDY]
Hey, Bellamy!
We hit the jackpot!
Oh! I'll say!
Look at this!
That's a fine piece of gold!
And so are these!
Oh, wow!
And now, it all belongs to us.
[CRICKET]
Huh? No way.
You punks have no
right to take that gold!
[SARQUISS]
Huh?
No right?
I'll show ya what
gives us the right!
Big Chop!
Oh, you damn fool!
[SARQUISS laughs]
We're way stronger than you
and your pals, old man!
I'd say that alone gives us
the right to take what we want,
when we want, don't you?
Come on!
Let's dance!
If you don't mind,
I'm cutting in!
Havoc sonar!
[wails]
Lousy!
[BELLAMY]
Sarquiss, no!
I'm going to finish him
off my way!
It's him again.
The one with those
Spring‐Spring fruit powers.
Shojo, run,
get out of there now!
[BELLAMY]
Spring...
[wails]
[BELLAMY]
...Sniper!
No! Shojo!
[SHOJO]
Old‐timer! Look what we found!
Gold! A bell‐shaped ingot!
[laughs]
[MASIRA] Look! It's just like
it says here in the logbook!
Gold bells!
The story's true!
[BELLAMY]
We're done here.
Load up!
Let's go!
And as for you,
old man, grow up!
[laughs]
This "City of Gold"
is just a fairytale!
That liar, Noland,
dreamt it all up!
If you want to be
a pirate in this new era,
you've got to wise up.
Your dreams will
never come true! Ever!
[laughter]
[MASIRA] The City of Gold
does exist! Hehe!
[CRICKET laughs]
Hey, guys! Take it easy!
My house is pretty small!
Ya know something, junior?
[coughs]
A worthless little punk like you
who is too afraid to believe
in dreams doesn't have the
right to call himself a pirate.
What was that?
[ZORO] It's like trying
to find a needle in a haystack.
We didn't even see one.
[LUFFY] Well, we did, but we
could never get close enough
to grab it thanks
to all those stupid bugs.
All we did was run.
So seven people
couldn't catch one bird?
That's pathetic!
C'mon would you
get it together, guys!
You're one to talk.
[sighs]
We've been doing this for hours!
I don't think I can run anymore!
Duuuuu!
Du du du du du! Duu duu!
He just said, "You
morons think you can catch us?
Hah! Good one!"
Morons? What nerve!
Hey, birdbrain,
I'll give you a "good one,"
right between your eyes!
Duu! Duu!
[ROBIN]
I can grab it if I can see it.
Duuuuu!
[LUFFY]
Hey, Pops!
We caught one of those birds!
Pops! What happened?
[USOPP]
Masira!
[SANJI]
Shojo!
[NAMI]
What the‐‐?
What happened here?
[SANJI]
I've got a better question.
Who did this?
Hey, gimme a hand!
[USOPP]
Aahh! The Going Merry!
What happened to her?
Who did this?
When I find out,
they're gonna be sorry
they ever laid a finger
on her, the savages!
Dammit!
[CRICKET]
Sorry, kid.
You're alive!
‐‐Don't try to move, okay?
‐‐I'm really sorry about this.
‐‐Just take it easy!
We did everything we could to
stop them, but it wasn't enough.
They made us
look pretty pathetic.
We gotta get movin' though.
Your ship's not
gonna patch itself up.
Hold on, Pops. Wait!
Tell us what happened first!
Who did this to you?
Calm down.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Did you have any
luck finding a‐‐
Duuu.
Look at that,
you got yourself a South Bird.
Nice job.
They're hard to catch.
[NAMI]
Luffy!
Huh?
Cricket's gold! It's all gone!
That stuff?
It's junk.
Just forget it.
It doesn't matter.
Your dream is more important.
We have to get
you to the Knock‐‐
Forget it?
How can you say that?
Think about what it
took to get that gold!
Ten years of diving to
the bottom of the ocean!
Subjecting your body to all
the pressures of the deep!
Come on, you can't just‐‐
Shut up!
I'm serious.
That gold, and what
happens to it, is our problem.
Got it?
Your ship's in no shape to
make it to the Knock‐Up Stream.
If we can get all the
Saruyama Alliance crew here,
they'll have it fixed
and reinforced by morning.
You'll still be able
to set sail tomorrow.
Listen.
Everything will be all right.
We will send you to the sky,
I promise that.
Old‐timer.
Hey, Luffy.
That's Bellamy's mark!
You want any help?
I'll handle this one alone.
[NAMI]
Luffy, don't be stupid!
We don't have time for this!
We have to set
sail in three hours!
[LUFFY]
If I follow the coast,
will that take me all the
way back to Mock Town?
Yes, I believe it will.
Hey, where are you goin'?
Don't be an idiot!
You can't possibly take on this
Bellamy guy all by yourself!
If you wanna stop him, use this.
Kid. Don't do it.
I'll be back by morning, guys.
[DRUNKARD taking a leak]
Well, lookee there!
Wow! Looks like the ole moon's
right out there under the water!
Guess my eyesight's
really gettin' bad!
I better get my eyes checked
or I'm gonna end up
fallin' off this dock!
Hahah!
Imagine that!
A pirate with bad eyesight!
Me?
I think I'd rather lose one eye
than have two bad ones!
Hahah.
'Least I'd get an eyepatch!
[laughs]
A fancy one, too!
Hey!
Whadda ya know!
A newspaper!
It must be the
really early edition!
Huh? This ain't no paper!
It's a stack of wanted posters!
Oh, boy.
What is this town comin'
to when low‐life scum outnumber
the fine, upstanding
citizens like myself?
Huh?
It's those spineless guys
from this afternoon!
Hah!
That looney kid talkin'
about the island
in the sky was a riot!
What was he worth?
Thirty million?
Hmm?
[laughs]
I guess my eyesight really
is gettin' pretty bad!
So one, ten, one hundred,
one thousand,
ten thousand,
one hundred thousand?
I think I'm gonna need
some reading glasses!
One hundred thousand.
O‐One million.
One hundred million?
[NAMI]
Three hours, Luffy!
That's all you've got!
If you take any longer...
[NAMI] ...we're going to lose
our chance to go to sky island,
and it's going to
be all your fault!
He's in bad shape!
It looks like he's been diving
dangerously like this for years,
coming up too quick,
and not giving the gas bubbles
enough time to fully dissipate!
All I'm doing is
following what I believe
to be my destiny.
This is a battle
between me and Noland.
I'm really sorry kid.
We did what we could to stop
them but it wasn't enough.
[LUFFY]
Bellamy!
[SARQUISS]
Those apes really cracked me up!
It was hilarious when they
were all bloody and had tears
and snot runnin'
all down their faces,
and started cryin', "Old‐timer!"
[laughs]
If he really meant so much,
they should have done a
better job of protecting him!
Right?
Yeah, those guys were so lame!
[laughs]
Hey, what did you expect?
The same thing would
have happened
to anyone else
as stupid as them!
Taking on a big‐time pirate
worth 55 million Berries
like Bellamy?
That's just insane!
[DRUNKARD]
Bad news!
[PATRON A]
This better be good.
Those guys!
The ones that were
here this afternoon!
They...
Bellamy!
What on Earth are
you still doing here?
You... You've gotta get
outta here this instant!
I'm serious!
You're in terrible danger!
Tch! What are
you talking about?
How am I in danger?
Sixty?
One hundred?
Those two together
are worth a 160 million!
Their bounties are higher
than yours, Bellamy!
Know what that means?
You're dead meat!
And so are we!
We were laughing at them!
I think we messed
with the wrong people!
They'll kill us!
Ya think they
remember what we look like?
We should get out of here!
Now!
I've never heard of anyone
having a bounty
worth 100 million before.
[BELLAMY laughs]
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
All it takes to scare
you big, tough guys
are some little scraps of paper?
What, do you all have
empty sockets for eyes?
You saw their
scrawny, little leader!
[LUFFY]
Made it!
This is nothing but a sham!
Here, I'll explain
it to you morons!
See, there are pirates
like these losers who fake
their own wanted posters just
to make a name for themselves!
The fakers win fights
without throwing a single punch!
Their enemies take one look at
the bogus bounties, turn tail,
and run just like
you sorry excuses for pirates
are doing right now!
You saw them! They're weak!
They didn't even fight back!
But now you're all scared.
Pathetic!
Thanks, Bellamy!
Hey, they almost pulled
one over on us, huh?
Yeah, he's right!
Besides, someone with a
bounty of 100 million would
have had to have pulled off
some pretty big capers.
He looked pretty young,
if you ask me.
And if that kid's so wanted,
how come we've never seen his
picture in the papers before?
Good point.
I've never heard of any kid
in a straw hat, have you?
[PATRON A]
I got to admit!
I was pretty scared
there for a moment!
[PATRON H]
All right! Back to the party!
Cheers!
[LUFFY]
Bellamy!
Where are you?
Heh. Excuse me, gentlemen.
[LUFFY]
Hey!
Well, speak of the devil.
We were just talking about you.
You got something
you wanna say to me, kid?
I do.
Give back Pops' gold!
Every bit of it!
Right now!
[BELLAMY snickers]
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...♪
[BELLAMY]
I thought you were headed
to your island in the sky?
[LUFFY]
Oh, I'm still going there.
After I kick your butt!
[BELLAMY] All you ever
say is dream‐like crap!
Here, how 'bout I help
you dream forever, kid?
In the afterlife!
So long, Straw Hat!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"100 Million Man!
World's Greatest Power
and Pirate Black Beard!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!