It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
Forget about it--I won't even
let an ant through this gate!
While fighting to
open the Front Gate
on Enies Lobby's Main Island,
the Franky Family were stopped
in their tracks by the giant
gatekeepers Oimo and Kashii.
Timber Hitch Tug!
However, Paulie and Zambai
reversed the tide of battle,
and began to
force the gate open.
Luffy had already passed
over the gate himself,
but was unable to make
any progress thanks
to the overwhelming
number of Marines
that hounded him at every turn.
Five men?
We've only lost
five of our guards?!
Jeez!
How in the world could you
make such an obvious mistake?!
Five hundred.
Lucci's party escorted Franky
and Robin to the Tower of Law,
where Spandam was
eagerly awaiting them.
It's good to have you back,
Lucci, Kaku, Blueno, Kalifa.
That's harassment.
All I did was say your name!
Needless to say,
I'm extremely pleased with your
performance in this mission.
By the way, although it
isn't exactly a reward for all
your hard work, I do have
something I want to give you.
But we can take
care of that later.
For now, let's
meet them, shall we?
The hope of the entire world.
Nearby, the Straw Hat pirates
sat on the sea train Rocketman,
anxiously awaiting their moment
to charge onto the island.
You ready, ladies and gents?
The time has finally arrived.
I'm gonna need you
to take out that iron fence,
okay Samurai Man?
Just leave it to me.
Hurry up!
Move it!
You too, big guy!
Coo-Coo?
Chapapa-papa!
I couldn't be happier!
Amazing work.
You survived the "accident"
eight years ago, Cutty Flam.
And now, I have you as well.
The world's most dangerous
woman, Nico Robin.
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
What a fantastic feeling!
It's so unfortunate.
The rest of the
world may never know
what a glorious accomplishment
CP9 achieved today.
One of the drawbacks of being
a secret agency and all that.
Yes, a pity.
Honestly, the news of your
capture could take years
to reach the public.
The "justice" those old geezers
in the current World Government
dole out is far too lenient!
Without sacrifice,
goals cannot be achieved.
I mean, this is world
peace we're working for--
it's not easy!
Surely there can't be
an issue with sacrificing
a few fools along the
way who hinder our work
for the sake of
the greater good.
Right?
You know, if everyone
would just give us
what we ask for obediently
and without question.
Then we wouldn't need to
go to such extreme measures.
Like we had to with poor Tom!
That traitor deserved it!
Crazy bastard!
Tom put his life on the line
to protect those blueprints!
Because idiots like you exist!
What are you doing?!
Don't just sit there, help me!!
Kumadoriii!
Yoyoi!
What is your desiiiiiiire?
Isn't it obvious?!
Help me!!
Make him stop!
Saa. Saa.
Saa!
Yoyoi!
Uhhh.
No need to thank me, Chief.
Nooo neeeeeed.
Now Gum-Gum Gatling!
Now Gum-Gum Whip!
Giant Sickle!
Bell!
Hammer!
Bazooka!
Gum-Gum Stamp!
This is Main Island,
calling the Chief.
Spandam, come in!
I repeat! Come in!
It's no good!
No signal!
Is that so?
Maybe he's got the
receiver off again.
Awww, seriously?!
Could his timing be any worse?!
Hey!
Anyone see where Straw Hat went?
He's right beneath you!
What?!
He is?!
Everyone attack
him from all sides!
Now!
There he is!
We got him!
Damn!
I'm cornered!
Now Gum-Gum Volcano!
What?!
No way!!
The walls are falling!
Run!
Now Gum-Gum Gatling!
Oh, no!
Chief Spandam!
Please, come in!
We need your orders, sir!
We can't stop Straw Hat Luffy!
Get ready!
He's heading towards
the courthouse!
We need those defenses lined up!
Move it, men!
Shut up, already!
What's with all the yelling?
You guys woke me up!
Chief Justice!
Yep!
You got it!
That's me!
Chief Justice of Enies Lobby!
On the left!
My name is Left Baskerville!
On the right!
I am Right Baskerville!
And, located in the center,
I am known as Central Freeway!
Say what?!
Uh.
Chief Justice.
We've got a problem.
There's a pirate on a rampage
on the Main Island, sir.
But we can't get in touch
with Chief Spandam to get
an update on our orders.
Please, sir, take
command on his behalf!
A pirate, you say?
All pirates are guilty!
There hasn't been a trial yet!
Even so, I think he's innocent!
Then.
I'll be neutral.
Death!
Say what?!
Chief Justice!
There's trouble, sir!
I just received a report.
The Straw Hat's accomplices
have taken out Kaahii
at the Front Gate.
Oimo's still fighting,
but won't last much longer!
Say what?!
That gate must not be breached!
Send one hundred Watchdogs
to that location immediately!
Sir!
We're in trouble!
Our 5 minute window is up!
Damn!
Hurry!
We've got to get that
gate open for Rocketman!
I will never let you through!
Okay guys!
We picked the gate's lock!
All you have to do
now is push it open!
What?!
Oh, crap!
Nice work!
You heard her!
Move it!
You stay away from that gate!
Rope Action!
Top Knot!
Whoa!
Those Galley-La
foremen are incredible!
You think this puny
rope is gonna hold me?!
Franky Family!
Pull!
Yeah!
No problem!
Gomorrah!
Sodom!
Grab that rope!
Move it, Franky Family!
Don't stop until that
gate is wide open!
Oi, oi, oi!
Hold on!
Slow down!
I'm getting dizzy!
Push the gate!
No!
Impossible!
The gates are opening!
What the hell is Oimo doing?!
A little more.
They've breached the gate!
Hey! Hey!
There's no way.
Is that a sea train?
What's going on here?
It is!
Look at it!
A sea train!
And it's not the Puffing Tom!
It's another one, and it's
headed this way at full speed!
They're crazy!
What're they trying
to do--jump the fence?
Hurry!
Close the gate!
We can't let them through!
Come on!
Get those doors shut!
Hey, granny!
Yeah? What is it?
There's been a change of plans.
I need you to give me as much
speed as you've got, okay?
Roger!
It seems we've had to
switch up our plans a little.
Your green-haired
samurai friend says
you all should find
something to hold onto.
Better hurry!
Find something to hold onto?
But why?
Hey! Moss-for-brains!
What's going on out here?
They, uh, they
closed the Main Gate.
They what?!
This is bad!
We're gonna crash!
What are we gonna do?!
Dodge it, Kokoro!
I've got a plan.
Don't worry.
All right, Zoro!
Hey, Frog!
See fence?
Smash!
What?!
Gero!
Gero, Gero!
Gero, Gero, Gero, Gero!
That's his plan?!
Does he realize
what's gonna happen
when we run into that fence?!
Impossible!
That seatrain!
It's flying!!!
No!
We're gonna die!
What?!
But I don't wanna die!
Nami! This way! I'll
save you! Fall into my arms!
Shut up, you idiot!
I've got enough
problems right now!
Zoro!
You'd better have
thought long and hard
about how you're
gonna land this thing!
Of course I have!
We fall.
Gero!
I hate you!
We'll find out if luck's
on our side soon enough.
Oimo's going down!
Whoa!
What a crew!
Are you Straw Hats?
Damn straight!
Is that so?!
That doesn't matter.
Let's move. Time's a' wasting.
We've gotta clear a path.
And fast.
All right!
You heard him, guys!
We need to go deeper!
Let's make a hole!
Yeah!
Paulie! No!
Who in the hell are you?
Who, us?
I'll tell you.
The First-Class
Guards of Enies Lobby.
The Watchdogs of the Law.
By order of Chief
Justice Baskerville.
For your crimes,
you're sentenced to death!
Damn.
They just keep coming!
One after another.
Oimo!
What are you doing?
How could you let this pirate
riff-raff open the gate?
What's wrong with you?
Can't believe I passed out!
Oh crap!
That giant's back up
and on his feet!
Little jerks!
You're dead!
You'll pay!
Whoa!
What the--?!
Rocketman fell from the sky!
We opened those
gates for nothing?!
Huh?!
What the hell just happened?
Man, that was some landing!
Do you think that they're okay?
They're not coming out.
Hey! You guys all right?
What?!
Impossible!
Who are those two?
Huh... Maybe we should have
introduced ourselves first.
Nah.
I'd rather let
my feet do the talking.
The Straw Hats are here!
We've been waiting for you!
Excellent.
Just like I planned it.
Whoa!
Really?!
Now Gum-Gum Storm!
There he goes!
That way!
Dammit!
Don't let him escape!
Get back here!
You're cornered!
Give it up!
Hey!
C'mon!
There's nowhere left to run!
Move it!
Now!
Get the hell out of my way!
So, our idiot captain rushed
off by himself again, huh?
Well, we're the ones
following that idiot around.
So what does that make us?
Then again, thanks to Luffy,
the Marine forces are
scattered all over the island!
Good!
More for me!
I'm not gonna let
Luffy have all the fun.
On the next One Piece:
"Catch Up with Luffy!
The Straw Hat's All-Out Battle!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!