[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
Fighting alongside Whitebeard
and his associates,
he continues to push
toward the scaffold.
Although Whitebeard himself
is critically injured,
he entrusts Ace's
future to Luffy,
who is aided by
a team of pirates
forging a path for him.
Stop and listen to me!
What's wrong?
There's a new plan!
I'm either gonna live
or I'm gonna die.
So back up Straw Hat with
everything you've got!
[gasps]
They did it!
They cleared a path!
[MARINES gasping]
[ACE gasping]
We did it!
I'm here!
[LUFFY gasps]
Grandpa!
Get outta the way!
I'm not moving a damned inch!
I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting pirates
since long before you were born
and I ain't stopping today!
Old man!
You're not my grandson here.
You are the pirate,
Straw Hat Luffy.
And I'll fight you to the death.
[LUFFY gasps]
This is the path that
you chose to take!
You and your brother alike.
[LUFFY]
"Each on Different Paths!
Luffy vs. Garp!"
Come on. Grandpa!
Let me by, please!
[ACE gasping]
Luffy!
[PIRATES yell]
Hey! Coby!
Stay with me, little buddy!
You'll make it!
[MARINE A grunts]
[HELMEPPO crying]
[HELMEPPO] How could you
do this to my friend?
Coby looked up
to you, Straw Hat!
I'll make you pay for this!
I'm too weak.
[gasps]
I have to get stronger.
Coby! You're alive!
Don't scare me!
[HELMEPPO crying]
[COBY]
Where's Luffy?
[HELMEPPO]
Who cares? He ran off!
Wait.
Garp is facing him
right at the scaffold!
Are those two
really gonna fight?
That's crazy!
[COBY]
Luffy.
[LUFFY panting]
I can't believe nobody
could stop that kid!
Damn it!
Don't worry about it.
It should be easy to
hit him from here.
Take aim and fire at will!
[HANCOCK]
Impertinent boors!
Stand back!
Taste my Slave Arrow!
[MARINE C]
I--
[MARINE D]
Love--
[MARINE E]
You!
[MARINE F groans]
We almost had him!
Who's side are you on anyway?
Not yours, fool!
What if you had hit Vice
Admiral Garp with a stray shot?
Uhh...
Yeah, but--
[HANCOCK]
I must protect him!
Because Vice Admiral Garp
is my beloved grandfather!
Wait, that's not right!
Yeah, that's news to me, too.
Well, he will be if
I ever marry Luffy,
and I'm sure I will someday.
She's crazy.
But cute.
The bridge is gonna
give out, Straw Boy!
You gotta move it or
lose it, whatever it takes!
[PIRATES]
Don't give up!
Almost there.
[PIRATES yelling]
[GARP]
A pirate... has the gall...
...to ask a Marine
to step aside?!
You want to pass me?
Then treat me like any
other Marine you've faced
and fight for your life!
[LUFFY panting]
[MONKEYS whooping]
[LUFFY]
Oww!
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY yells, groans]
[LUFFY]
Grandpa!
This kinda hurts!
Why do you want me to fight
these dumb monkeys all day?
[MONKEY D grunts]
Huh?
It's your training.
Training sucks!
For one, I have to
get hit all the time,
and for two, I'm hungry!
[MONKEYS grunt]
Huh?
Don't be a baby!
You're gonna be a fine
Marine someday, just like me!
[LUFFY]
Nuh-uh!
I'm gonna be a pirate!
Marines are all lame!
Huh?
You little punk!
The monkeys hit hard,
but you're even worse, Gramps!
[LUFFY panting]
[APE A whooping]
[LUFFY grunting]
Now, Gum-Gum... [yells]
[gasps]
[sighs] You're
killin' me, kiddo.
Hey, ya wanna know a secret?
[GARP]
Huh? What is it?
Turns out, I'm not
gonna be a pirate.
Now that's my boy,
you finally get it!
Uh-huh! I'll be way
cooler than any pirate!
I'll be King of the Pirates!
[LUFFY giggles]
[GARP] This is Shanks'
influence, isn't it?
You're dismissed, ape!
I'm gonna teach you
to be a proper Marine
if I have to beat it into you!
Not this again!
The only way you will
ever be a pirate
is if I'm six feet under, boy!
[LUFFY screams]
[LUFFY snoring]
[stomach growls]
[snoring]
[GARP]
You're all tuckered out,
but I see your stomach's
as lively as ever,
or as noisy at least.
[GARP] You probably
don't care for me much,
since I'm so loud and rough
with you all the time.
Can't blame you, really.
[GARP] But I'm not harsh
'cause I don't like you,
and I don't want you to be a
Navy man for my sake, either.
I just want you to have the
strength to do the right thing
and walk the right path.
[GARP]
That's my one and only wish.
[GARP] By the way, I swiped
some food from the Navy,
so you can eat all the
meat you want for once!
I figure they owe me a favor
and they'll probably think
pirates stole it anyway.
[laughs]
[LUFFY]
Grandpa...
I'm not hurting you!
Just move!
If you don't strike me dead,
then you'll lose Ace!
[LUFFY]
Shut up!
[GARP] You can't just cry
till you get your way!
I won't show you mercy!
[GARP]
You're a pirate, Luffy.
That makes you my enemy!
[GARP grunting]
[GARP yells]
[GARP]
Luffy!
[GARP gasps]
[SENGOKU]
Garp!
[yelling]
[ACE gasping]
[ACE]
Damn it, this all wrong.
How the hell am I
supposed to feel?
Pops. Luffy. My friends.
They're here to save me, but
they're pushing through a sea
of their own blood to do it!
I'm sick.
These are tears of joy!
Even after all I've done,
I want to live!
[PIRATES gasping]
He took down Garp?
[BOTH gasp]
[ACE gasps]
Old man!
[LUFFY yells]
They're family, after all.
Damn it.
Ahh. Look at that!
I believe he just might make it.
Change your mind?
I thought you said
he couldn't do it?
I didn't say he could save Ace.
Now that he's at the top,
they'll die together.
That's all.
[WHITEBEARD]
Shut your mouth!
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
You let your guard down.
[PIRATES]
Pops!
[WHITEBEARD groans]
[LUFFY grunting]
[ACE gasps]
[LUFFY panting]
Finally, I'm here!
I told you I'd do it!
Luffy!
Hmph. You really are crazy.
Yeah, well... [giggles]
[LUFFY]
Hold on!
[HANCOCK]
Take this.
It's the key to your
brother's handcuffs.
I've got the key right here.
That's great, but how?
[SENGOKU growls]
[pants]
[PIRATES gasping]
[PIRATE AA]
What the hell is that?
That's Sengoku's power.
I've never seen it!
Damn, he's huge.
Struggle all you like,
but you're trapped in
the palm of my hand!
[ACE]
This is insane!
[PIRATE BB]
A gold statue?
[MARINES gasping]
That's not something you
should have, Straw Hat.
Let's fix that, shall we?
No! The key!
Now take aim!
Wait until I give the order,
but prepare to fire!
[LUFFY gasps]
Oh, crap! I lost it!
You've dug your own grave.
You're a criminal
as well, Straw Hat.
I've had enough.
I will execute the both of you
right here and with
my own bare hands!
[MR. 3 groaning]
[gasps]
[MR. 3]
My goodness.
I think I must have passed
out for a moment there.
Straw Hat? What?
Wait. 3?
Why are you here?
[MR. 3 gasps]
[screams]
What is that thing? [screams]
3! Quick!
Protect Ace with a wall!
I'm not losing now!
Gum-Gum Giant Balloon!
[MR. 3]
Candle Wall!
[LUFFY grunts]
[SENGOKU]
What's he doing?
[LUFFY groans]
The whole scaffold's
coming down!
What happened up there?
Ace is still alive?!
This is awful!
[MR. 3]
I'll make a key!
Get those cuffs
off him and hurry!
You got it!
Look, Captain Buggy!
That's where Brother 3 went!
Holy crap!
I thought he hightailed
it out of this dump,
but now he's right
in the middle of it!
Also, what the hell
is he wearing?
[MR. 3 grunting]
[MR. 3]
Not that one.
This isn't about
putting down a pirate,
it's about maintaining the
integrity of our institution!
We must carry it out properly!
Wait a sec.
[MR. 3]
Those are the executioners!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL rings]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
Excellent.
They said that Admiral
Borsalino stopped Straw Hat.
They're in the plaza right now.
[MR. 3]
Oh, no!
[BON CLAY]
I know you can do it!
And you have lots of
friends to help you!
[MR. 3]
Mr. 2!
Okay. That's that.
Now what do we do?
Rescue Straw Hat
before it's too late!
[BON CLAY growls]
Because I'm his friend!
I don't need any other reason!
[BOTH]
That's... it?
[LUFFY]
This is it.
The gate's about to close.
We have... to go...
So thank you!
Straw Boy!
I'm here!
[BON CLAY]
Straw Boy.
Find Ace! Save him
and don't look back!
[MR. 3] He wouldn't run
away if he were here.
He honored his friendship with
Straw Hat to the bitter end.
[MARINE L] Get ready and we'll
finally put an end to this.
[EXECUTIONERS]
Yes, sir!
[EXECUTIONER B gasps, groans]
[MARINE O]
Where's the replacement?
What could possibly be
taking him so long?
[EXECUTIONER A]
Well, it was short notice
and we don't do this very often.
Hey, you ready?
Fine! Let's move!
[MR. 3] Frankly, I couldn't
care less about your brother.
I'm here out of respect
for my late comrade!
Laugh at me if you like,
but here's your key!
Why would I laugh at that?
[MARINE AA]
Fire!
Blow them to bits before
they hit the ground!
Here! Good luck!
Thanks, 3!
[SENGOKU gasps]
Damn it!
That doesn't look good!
Luffy!
[PIRATES]
Ace! No!
[PRISONERS]
Brother 3!
That is an ugly way to go!
[MARINE BB] Those handcuffs
are Sea Prism Stone.
Fire Fist's power won't
be able to save him.
[MARINE CC] Pretty sure we
got Straw Hat in there, too.
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINE DD]
What is that?
It looks like a
tunnel of flames!
[ACE]
Ever since you were little,
you've never listened
to a word I said,
have you?
Then you run off and
do something crazy.
Like old times, huh, Luffy?
[PIRATES cheering]
They're alive!
Well, of course!
[PIRATES]
Ace!
It's... a true miracle!
Hey, I see them!
Look there, in the flames!
[BOTH gasping]
Let's go!
[NARRATOR]
Ace is free at last,
and the pair of brothers
are unstoppable.
Although the Whitebeard
Pirates are emboldened
by their teamwork,
their captain is not
convinced that their escape
will come so easily.
With his eyes on a new age,
Whitebeard makes a
difficult decision.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Ace Rescued!
Whitebeard's Final Order!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!