[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[NARRATOR] After a long
and arduous adventure,
Luffy and his crew
finally reached
their mystical island
destination of Skypiea.
[NARRATOR] However, when Nami,
Zoro, Robin, and Chopper
were carried off to face
Heaven's Judgment,
Luffy and his remaining crew
set out to Upper Yard
to rescue their friends.
Fortunately, their
new friend Conis
was there to show them the way.
Presenting the Crow!
Ah! You're kidding me, right?
[SANJI]
Wait, uh.
Crows don't even swim.
[CONIS]
Your exit is Gate Number Two.
It leads right to
the Milky Road,
and that will take you all
the way to Upper Yard.
Just follow it
and you'll be fine.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Conis.
Yes?
You've been trembling
ever since we left.
Is everything okay?
[PAGAYA] Oh, Conis,
please forgive me.
But it's every citizen's duty.
[CONIS]
Just run away. Please.
I called the Super
Express Lobster!
It was all my fault!
Once we know
someone's a criminal,
we must lead them to Upper Yard.
If we don't, then
the penalty is death!
[PIERRE]
Pi-e!
Conis! Look she's safe!
I-I know who you really are.
We-We all know.
Please come back to us... God.
[LUFFY] "Onward, Crow!
To the Sacrificial Altar!"
I really hope Conis
is all right.
You know she's gonna
have hell to pay
when the White Berets
catch up with her
and it's our own stupid fault.
She'd be okay if she
hadn't helped us.
And I'm not sure she can
trust that Sky Knight.
He pretty much
gives me the creeps.
He's kinda old and weird,
but he doesn't seem like
that bad of a guy.
There was no other choice.
I wanna protect her,
but it's not like we could've
brought her along with us.
Well, then she probably is
in less danger without us.
"Sacrificial altars," "ordeals."
And the sound of it,
I wish I was the one flying
off with the old geezer.
Man, this piece of junk is slow.
Of course it is.
It's gotta be several times
heavier than a standard waver.
What'd you expect?
Uh, guys! Where did that
huge forest come from?
[SANJI]
Is that the Upper Yard?
[LUFFY] I don't remember
this being on the map.
Wait.
No, there is supposed
to be a forest ahead,
but I don't see any warning
about how big it is.
This cannot be right!
[SANJI]
Who knows how old that map is.
We know it can be traced back
a couple hundred years,
but who's to say it hasn't
been around longer?
The forest may have been
a fraction of its size
when that map was made.
[USOPP]
Ah, that's true.
[LUFFY] All I know is, I gotta
climb one of these trees!
Ha! They're enormous!
[LUFFY]
Look, the entrance!
[SANJI]
Well, this is it, Usopp.
If you're gonna chicken out,
now's the time.
[USOPP]
Actually, if you don't mind,
I was kind of thinking
I'd like to go back.
[LUFFY]
Too late!
[USOPP]
Then why did you ask me?!
[caws]
[USOPP]
Wh-What was that?
[LUFFY]
Would you calm down?
[SANJI]
Yeah, take it easy.
[USOPP]
Open your eyes!
Don't you notice
anything strange?
Look at all these shipwrecks!
[LUFFY]
It is a forest.
[SANJI]
He's right.
[USOPP]
That doesn't make any sense!
Besides, they didn't
run aground--
they were sliced in half!
[rustling]
Did you hear that?
The woods are full
of noises. Relax.
[SANJI]
I heard that.
[USOPP screams]
[USOPP]
Full speed ahead!
All ahead full!
Stroke! Stroke!
[LUFFY]
What's going on?
Hm?
[ALL scream]
A sickle monster!
Hang on tight, here
comes another one!
No. Not just one.
Paddle like crazy!
[ALL yelling]
[USOPP screams]
[SANJI]
What the hell is this?!
[USOPP]
Watch where you're going!
Luffy! No, wait! Slow down!
This isn't working.
Usopp, take the wheel!
Gum-Gum...
[USOPP] What are you doing?
It's in front of us!
[LUFFY]
I know, just hang on!
...Bazooka!
Ha-ha! Dodged it!
[USOPP]
Whoa! That was close!
Great, there's more?
Spears? Are you kidding me?
[LUFFY]
Usopp, right!
[SANJI]
No, left!
[USOPP]
Which one?
[SANJI]
Just dodge 'em!
They won't stop!
One of  'em's bound
to hit us eventually!
All right, guys, get ready.
Gum-Gum Pinwheel!
[sighs]
That was close.
I hope that's all over with.
I can't take any more scares.
[USOPP]
Eh? Oh, now what?
[USOPP screaming]
It's gone!
Not yet!
[USOPP]
It's coming back!
--[SANJI] Move it!
--[LUFFY] Dodge!
I can't believe that
overgrown crustacean
just dropped us out in
the middle of nowhere.
Does anybody know
where we are?
[NAMI]
One thing's for certain,
we're definitely somewhere
in the middle of Upper Yard.
[ROBIN]
Hmm.
This seems to be some sort
of altar for sacrifices.
[NAMI]
Altar? Wait, sacrifices?
Nami, what's a sacrifice?
[NAMI] You know, like,
an offering to the gods.
Oh, is that all?
I thought it meant
being boiled alive
in a big stew or something.
[screaming]
Actually, that's about right.
But regardless of the method,
the thing being offered is
generally someone's life.
[CHOPPER screams]
Are you tryin' to tell me
we're all gonna die here?!
Whoa!
[NAMI]
Chopper!
Damn it.
[sighs]
[CREATURE roars]
[screaming]
Oh, no! What's that?
A shark. In the sky.
A "skyshark"?
[CHOPPER screaming]
Zoro! Zoro!
[ZORO]
I can't see anything down here.
Where the hell is it?
[ZORO]
Way out of my element.
Can't maneuver like
I can on land.
[LUFFY screaming]
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
[LUFFY yelling]
[USOPP]
It missed us.
Oh! Not again!
[USOPP]
I'm sick of this place!
We're never gonna
make it outta here!
I'm going back! I don't
care what you say!
[LUFFY]
No, you're not!
[USOPP] Shut up!
I'm captain of the Crow!
[LUFFY]
Since when?
[USOPP]
Since now!
Even if we do turn around,
there's no guarantee we'll
survive the trip back.
Damn.
[USOPP screaming]
[USOPP]
Doesn't that thing ever quit?
Let's see how you like
a little Gum-Gum, huh?
[USOPP]
Yeah!
[SANJI]
Get it, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
I got nothin'.
[USOPP screams]
[SANJI]
That only leaves us one choice.
Try and outrun it!
[yells]
I think we finally outran it.
Aw, but this is bad.
Now it's too late to go back!
Oh, I can't even see
the entrance anymore!
[LUFFY]
Then stay here.
[USOPP]
I'd die, you idiot!
[SANJI]
More than likely
[yelps]
[screams]
Was that a big snake?
[SANJI]
Looked like a giant lamprey.
A "Sky Lamprey" I guess.
One that big will do more
than just suck a little blood.
Neatest forest ever, huh?
Neat forest my butt!
If this is our so-called
ordeal, then I quit!
You can't quit yet.
We just got here.
We've got to keep moving.
We can't spend any more time on
this Milky Road than necessary.
Otherwise, we're asking
for certain death.
[ALL gasp]
What happened to him? No.
There he is!
Zoro!
[CHOPPER]
It's all my fault!
What if he gets swallowed?
Wait. Why hasn't
he come back up?
Zoro, please be okay!
You don't think he
got eaten, do you?
[CHOPPER screams]
Zoro's fish food!
If he had been eaten, the clouds
would've turned red by now.
How can you stay so
calm at a time like this?
[ZORO]
I am so done with you!
[ZORO
I can tell you one thing.
We are not gonna make
it across by swimming.
What kinda swordsman
punches a shark
'stead of usin' his blade?
I'm so glad you're okay!
Whatever happened to your
precious swordsman's pride, huh?
Would you give it
a rest for once?!
[CHOPPER] Ah! There's an
entire school of 'em!
What are we gonna do?
[ZORO]
I'm not sure.
But if that first one
was any indication,
we're not gonna have much
luck fightin' 'em off.
[ROBIN]
We've got to do something.
We can't stay here forever.
If leaving us here was that
lobster's idea of a joke,
it's not very funny.
Perhaps this is the
"Heaven's Judgment"
we've been hearing
so much about.
[ZORO] 'Cept you'd think this
"God" would try something
a little flashier, ya know?
Eh. Couldn't say,
never met the guy.
[ZORO] I'm not sure
what the solution is.
We definitely can't set sail
with the hull looking like this.
Hey, Chopper, try to figure
out a way to fix the ship.
Uh, me? Okay!
Why should he fix it?
Are you going somewhere?
[ZORO] I'm gonna find
a way into the forest.
We should probably make
this our base of operations.
You guys can keep a lookout.
I'm sure Luffy and the others
are headed this way.
Like they say,
if you get lost,
you should stay
where you are, right?
[NAMI] Shouldn't that
apply to you, too?
[ROBIN]
Hm.
Zoro, if you wanna
go into the forest,
well, I guess that's
okay with me.
But you haven't really
told us what for.
There's supposed to be some
kinda God on this island--
I wanna meet him.
Wait. That's a terrible idea!
I mean, what are you gonna do
when you actually find him?
I don't know. Depends on
if he behaves himself.
Zoro, you're the
bravest person I know.
And what about his priests,
you gonna beat them up, too?
Hello? The last thing we need
is you pissing off a God!
It's kinda not smart!
[gasps]
By the time I'm done with him...
...this "God" is gonna
bow before me.
Ah-ha! Go, Zoro!
I don't believe in him anyway.
What do I care about
pissing him off?
[CHOPPER screams]
O powerful one,
I just wanted you to know
I don't agree with
my idiot shipmate.
I don't even like him that much.
Okay, bye.
[CHOPPER] Don't listen to
her, Zoro! You're awesome!
[ROBIN]
Hm?
Come on. Can't this little
cruise be over already?
Are you kidding? That was
probably a warm up for later.
Supposedly we're gonna
have to go up against
a boat-load of
super-deadly priests
that are already waiting
for us on the island.
So you're telling me none
of what we've gone through
has anything to do with
our actual ordeal?
I dunno. I kinda doubt it.
Especially considering the
magnitude of that attack
back at the docks.
I couldn't tell you
how it all works,
but it's serious power.
Take even one hit
and you're a goner.
This "Eneru" shouldn't be
taken lightly, that's for sure.
And I get the distinct feeling
he's watching us, even now.
[LUFFY] That's weird. So you
think he was in that town?
[SANJI] I'm guessing
he's must have been,
to attack as
accurately as he did.
[USOPP] Not necessarily! This
is a God we're talking about.
I bet he could see us from
a thousand miles away!
Heck, he's probably
watching us right now.
Yeah? Since when did you become
such a devoted follower?
You're not even
from around here.
You're missing the
point completely.
People say "God
is great," right?
I was taught to show
respect to those with power.
You don't have to mean it.
It's self-preservation.
Fine.
But you do realize
that not every "God"
in the world is "great."
Like the God of poverty.
Or the God of pestilence.
[USOPP, LUFFY]
Oh, what do you know?
[SANJI] We can continue
that debate later.
That is, if we live through
being eaten by that thing.
[USOPP whimpers]
[screams]
Not another one!
That vine looks pretty sturdy.
[ROBIN]
Ah. Excellent idea.
Mind if I tag along, swordsman?
[ZORO] Sure. Long as you
promise not to slow me down.
[NAMI] Wait a minute!
Where do you think you're going?
Look at this.
At least a thousand
years have passed
since this altar was built.
[NAMI, CHOPPER]
A thousand years?
The sense of history
here is amazing.
It gives me chills. You feel it?
[BOTH]
Uhh...
[ROBIN] A place as ancient
as this is sure to be filled
with all kinds of old relics.
Imagine all the valuables
we could discover.
Just think: The
possibilities are endless.
[NAMI]
Hm.
In that case, I'll join you.
Nami! I thought you
were too scared!
It's for history.
[CHOPPER]
Yeah, sure it is.
[ROBIN]
That work for ya?
[ZORO]
It's perfect!
[clearing throat]
[NAMI groans]
[ZORO yelling]
It's official.
He's lost his mind.
She made it!
[NAMI]
Looks easy enough.
This is higher up
than I thought.
[ROBIN]
Be careful.
If you fall, you'll
most certainly die.
[NAMI] That supposed to
be your idea of helping?!
Whoa. She's right.
I'm dead if I fall.
Nami?
All right, fine! I'm going!
Is that what you want?
[squeals]
Help me! It's too fast!
I'm gonna crash!
[NAMI screams]
Look at that,
you're not gutless.
[NAMI]
Thanks for catching me.
Anytime.
[ZORO yells]
[ZORO]
...is what you should've done.
[NAMI]
That had nothing to do with it!
[ROBIN] This forest is even
bigger than I thought.
Okay, Chopper! You're
in charge of the ship!
[ROBIN]
We're counting on you!
We'll be back soon!
[CHOPPER]
Bye! Everyone be careful!
Don't take too long, okay?
I guess Nami will be all right
since she's with Robin and Zoro.
My friends are all so
brave and adventurous.
I'm too scared to go,
but maybe someday,
if I'm really lucky,
I can be brave like them, too.
[CHOPPER]
Oh, well. If I can't be brave,
I can at least
make myself useful.
Being left alone in the middle
of a dangerous forest
to fix our ship is proof that
everyone must trust me,
so I have to do my very best.
It's just little old me, all by
myself in the big scary forest.
[gasps]
[CHOPPER]
Oh, no! Who's gonna protect me?
[screaming]
Sky lamprey!
Hey. What do you think?
Would that thing taste good
with some salt and pepper?
Never thought I'd say it,
but I don't think now's the
time for trading recipes.
Damn.
Then Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
[yelling]
[USOPP] I hate sky islands,
they're scary!
[SANJI]
Wanna get out here?
What kinda question is that?!
You want me to die?!
I'm allowed to be scared,
cut me some slack!
[LUFFY chuckles]
Uh. Hey, look!
There's a giant head
blocking our way!
Not quite. It's a statue.
Oh, right. But it looks
like a total dead end.
No, look, there's
four entrances.
Of course.
And how much you wanna
bet all four of 'em
lead to different places?
[USOPP]
Ordeal of Swamp, Ordeal of Iron,
Ordeal of String,
and Ordeal of Spheres.
Ha-ha! You think we
get to take our pick?
Is it me, or do none
of these things
really sound like much
of an "ordeal"?
[LUFFY chuckles]
[USOPP]
Uh. I don't know, guys.
Which one should we choose?
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[USOPP]
So, any suggestions?
[LUFFY]
Spheres are like balls, right?
That sounds fun!
[USOPP]
This isn't a game, you know!
[SANJI] Okay, Spheres it is.
Just don't let your guard down.
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Whoa!
[SANJI]
What is this place?
[LUFFY]
Look at all the balls!
[USOPP]
You call this an ordeal?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"10% Survival Rate!
Satori, the Mantra Master!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!