Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[LUFFY] We're gonna
make you regret you
even thought about
taking our food.
You hear me, Moria?!
We'll make him give back
twice the amount he took
from us, and before dawn!
[CREW] Yeah!
This is not good at all,
I gotta tell the master
before this gets serious.
What? Impossible!
No one wakes up that quickly
after their shadow's taken!
I... I didn't see it myself,
but their friends seem
to have beaten them awake.
We need Absalom!
What the hell is he doing?
[HILDON] Uh, well, um...
I'm pretty sure his wedding
ceremony just began,
and I'm also pretty sure that
all of the Zombie
Generals are attending.
Horo horo horo horo.
Just let the stupid
animal have his wedding.
[HOGBACK] What?
[PERONA] I'll be in my room
if you need anything else.
Come on, Kumacy.
[KUMACY] Right. Sorry.
Well I'm not bored
enough to bother standing.
I'll just wait here
for Oars to get back.
Well then, may I ask
a simple request?
Moria! Where the hell are you?
Oh, crap!
[LUFFY] Give us back our food!
[OARS] Huh?
Ah ah ah! I'm falling!
Usopp! Sanji!
[CHOPPER] Something
came crashing through.
They all fell down
with the stairs.
[ZORO] Their legs are twitching
so I'm sure they're fine,
nothing to worry about.
What I'm curious
about is this thing.
Well, whatever it is,
it's blocking our path.
Sure is a weird lookin' wall.
It's not made of rock.
What the hell
are you guys doing?
That thing's Luffy's zombie!
[FRANKY and ZORO]
What?!
[LUFFY] "Usopp's the Strongest?
Leave Anything Negative to Him."
Usopp and Sanji fell,
are you sure it's okay to
just leave them down there?
Don't worry about it,
those two can take
care of themselves.
And besides, if we're
gonna go after Moria,
we'd better hurry it up.
We gotta take that big onion
by surprise while we still can!
You said it!
The faster we beat him,
the faster we can get out
of this creepy place!
[CHOPPER] Up ahead is
that big dance hall place
where you lost your shadow.
If we keep going
forward after that,
we'll hit a giant refrigerator
that was the last
place we saw Moria.
Sounds good!
I thought
Perona was supposed
to take care of you miscreants!
Doctor Hogback!
Uh? A reindeer?
But why is it talking?
The infamous
Dr. Hogback, I presume.
[LUFFY] That guy was
hanging out with Moria.
Guess I'd better
kick his ass, too.
[HOGBACK] Let's not be hasty!
[CHOPPER] Don't do it, Luffy.
I have a bone to pick with
this guy, let me fight him.
You see that big,
metal door behind you?
[CHOPPER] That leads to
the refrigerator. Go on ahead.
Okay, you got it!
How rude, you can't
just ignore me
and waltz your way to Moria!
Get them, Cindry! No Mercy!
As you wish. One. Two.
[LUFFY] She's throwing plates?
Fasfas! Keep it up,
Cindry! Good!
I'm not going
to miss this time.
Three.
Huh? What's that
coming out of you, Cindry?
It's you!
Go on ahead, Captain.
[LUFFY] You got it!
Thanks a lot, Robin!
[HOGBACK] I told you
to stop ignoring me!
Hey, Hogback!
You have no right to call
yourself a doctor anymore.
I've lost all respect for you.
Huh?
Fasfasfasfas!
I didn't recognize you
at first, Doctor Chopper!
So you're have zoan type
devil fruit powers, do you?
I must admit, you're
a fascinating creature.
I don't know how
you managed to escape
after they carried you
through Perona's garden,
but that's irrelevant now.
I've found you again and I won't
let you get away a second time.
Your shadow will be mine.
No, rather. I should have
that interesting body
of yours turned
into a marionette.
And I'll have your friends help!
[CHOPPER] That penguin. That's
the zombie with Sanji's shadow!
Then the one with
the sword must be.
Hey, wait a sec,
if you put someone's
shadow in a zombie,
they act like them right?
Then I think I've seen
your Zombie, Zoro.
Oh yeah? What
kinda guy was he?
Hmm... Well,
he looked just like you.
They say scars on the back
are the shame of a swordsman.
It's nothing like him at all!
You don't think?
Fasfas! Now, mop the
floor with their faces!
Of course,
Doctor Hogback.
So, which one is first?
The crappy reindeer.
[panting heavily]
Could this stupid
hallway be any longer?
Gimme a break!
All right, finally!
What is this place?
[LUFFY] There you are!
Oh, you again.
Uhh... Ahh... Gah...
This thing is too
frickin' huge, brother!
[FRANKY]
And look at those horns!
Did he climb up
from hell or something?
I've never seen
anything like this!
It's really a zombie?
Holy crap.
Luffy.
It's all over!
He's gonna grind us up
and make meat pies out of us!
[USSOP screams in panic]
What is he gonna do?
IYAAAAAAAA!!!
Ahhh. There we go.
[USOPP] Huh?
Okay, now I look
like the real thing!
Can't be the King of the
Pirates without an awesome hat.
Man,that sure was scary
when that building fell down.
What just happened?
Are you telling me that
thing didn't even notice us?
It's hard to believe,
but it really does act
like Luffy, doesn't it?
Something that huge
with his fighting power
is gonna give us hell.
'Cmon, let's just
get out of here.
You guys don't need
your shadows, right?
Like hell we don't!
Even if I did give
up on my shadow,
which is stupid, by the way,
we'd still have to rescue Nami,
so get your ass up!
[SANJI] The problem right now is
that we're all stuck down here.
The stairs were the
only sure fire way to get
where we're going and
they're completely destroyed.
And even if we changed our
route and take this passage.
We're still screwed, since
the bridge got taken out too.
In other words,
we can't get to that mansion
with the mast either way.
[ZORO] And it's way
too far for us to jump.
[USOPP] We had a
shortcut laid out for us,
now we're gonna have to go
some scary way full of zombies.
[FRANKY] Just gimme
30 seconds, I got this.
[FRANKY] I'm not happy with
how this railing turned out.
You built a bridge?
There was wood and
scraps everywhere.
If I couldn't throw
together a bridge or two,
I'd be a damn disgrace.
I mean, if you say so,
but for a makeshift bridge,
you sure put a lot of
effort into the details.
You sayin' you want me
to do a half assed
construction job? Huh?
Nah. Don't hear
me complaining.
Anyway, thanks a lot. Let's go.
What, does a
princess live here?
Dunno what I was
expecting, but it wasn't this.
What the...?
Horo horo horo horo!
[PERONA] I was going to
have my zombies grab you
at the stairs by the bridge,
but I suppose that
plan fell through.
[PERONA] Oars was just reborn
and he's already a nuisance.
My patience is running
very thin tonight.
[ZORO] It's those ghosts again.
So it was her controlling
them all this time?
What the hell are
those things, anyway?
Horo horo horo horo!
Oh, my. Is that fear
I sense in your voice?
I wouldn't blame you after
what happened last time.
[PERONA] I can create
ghosts at my command
with the power of the
Hollow-Hollow Fruit.
You can think of them as a
sort of extension of myself.
They can empty your heart
and crush your spirit.
Horo horo horo horo!
This should be fun,
for me at least.
I can't believe
this little cutie
is the one making those
annoying ghost creatures!
Save your comments
for another time--
if we get hit by even
one of those things,
it's all over for us!
He's right, we gotta run!
I don't wanna
lose my dignity again.
[FRANKY] Retreat!
Negative Hollow!
[NEGATIVE GHOSTS]
Horo horo horo horo!
Horo horo!
[SANJI] I'm dumber than a
mackerel. I should just die.
[FRANKY] I know, bro. I wish
a stray dog would step on me!
[ZORO]
I should just crawl around
on the ground like
a worm, and eat dirt!
[USOPP]
It's all over.
[FRANKY sobs]
Capture them.
Well, that was easy.
All that's left are
the three above us.
[USOPP] Gatling Salt Star!
Who did that?
That's my crew, you know.
I won't let you hurt them!
Tricky punk.
You acted like you got hit
just so you could surprise me!
But don't worry,
I won't miss a second time.
Negative Hollow!
What?
[USOPP] My name...
is Captain Usopp.
[PERONA] I don't get it!
Why don't my attacks
do anything to you?
I know I didn't miss
that time! What is this?
What kind of power have you got?
Power has nothing to do with it.
I just naturally have
a negative personality!
What?
He's even more negative
than the Negative ghosts!
He's a real piece of work!
No, Mistress Perona!
[PERONA thinking]
It can't be!
No human is immune
to the Negative Hollows!
They have the power
to empty your heart!
Perona!
[PERONA thinking]
So long as humans are alive.
They're always
looking toward the future,
moving forward
one step at a time.
But this man, he...
[USOPP] Huh?
Don't give up.
Don't give up!
Don't give up!!
[WILD ZOMBIES]
Don't give up!
Don't give up! Do your best!
Don't pity me!
Come on you guys,
time to snap outta this!
You gotta go rescue Nami
and get the shadows back
before it's too late!
[USOPP] No matter
how strong you are,
you don't stand a
chance against her.
All you can do is run.
But don't worry.
I'll take care of her for you!
I can't believe it.
Usopp actually
looks cool for once.
Is his heart
really that empty?
Little turd!
[USOPP]
Oh, but please defeat
all of the zombies
before you go.
Valiant though I may be,
I must conserve my energy for...
[SANJI] All right, see ya later!
[USOPP] Hey, wait! No, uh...
The zombies.
You gotta beat the zombies.
I can't do that
part on my own! Wait!
That's fine. I'll just
pound you to death.
[ZOMBIE PRIEST] Do you, Absalom,
promise to take Nami,
as your lawfully wedded wife,
to have and to hold
in good times and in bad,
in sickness and in health?
Damn straight.
[cheering]
[ZOMBIE PRIEST] Do you,
Nami, promise to take Absalom
as your husband, to have and to
hold, in good times and in bad,
in sickness and in health?
[ZOMBIE 356A] Oh, yes I sure do!
I think he's so cute!
[cheering]
Then you may now
kiss the bride.
[OARS] Hey, what's this thing?
Whoa, when I pull it,
the boat moves!
That's pretty cool.
Which way is right again?
Ah, I forgot. Oh well.
Just tell me where the meat is!
Set sail for meat!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"The General Zombies
are Down in a Flash!
Oars Feels like an Adventure!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!