[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue.
The crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
Separated from his crew,
Luffy and his newfound cohorts
have hijacked a Navy ship
in order to rescue
his brother, Ace,
who's been transported
to Navy HQ for execution.
[BUGGY] Screw you!
Nobody is that crazy!
Surely you guys heard
about the war brewing
between Whitebeard and the Navy!
Uh. War?
Navy Headquarters?
Well, we passed through the Gate
of Justice. Isn't that right?
Our destination is
Enies Lobby or Navy HQ.
This Tub Current is restricted
to Government passage only.
It's one giant whirlpool
that connects
the Government's
three major facilities.
[PRISONERS]
No one told us about this!
Buggy! Buggy!
That's enough!
Don't get too flashy!
You guys are high on power
and acting impulsively.
So listen. I want all of you
to live out a dream with me.
For today... I'll
conquer Whitebeard,
and thus, rule the world!
[PRISONER GG] I'll follow
you anywhere, Captain Buggy!
[PRISONER HH] To hell
with living a peaceful life!
[BUGGY]
All right then!
Now let's win this war,
you guys! To Navy HQ!
[PRISONERS cheer]
So, I guess the mutiny's over?
Let them have fun
while they can.
[LUFFY]
"The Friends' Whereabouts!
The Weatheria Report
and the Cyborg Animals!"
[LUFFY]
Huh?
I know you're worried about Ace,
but standing vigil won't help.
You should rest and prepare
yourself for the battle.
[JIMBEI] The war that approaches
us will be a trying one,
and one that changes
the tide of the times.
Having just escaped from the
greatest prison in the world,
we may take heart.
But the fortress that lies
before us is ever more imposing.
[NARRATOR]
Far away, but not long ago,
on a Sky Island
known as Weatheria.
A weather wizard, or
rather a weather scientist,
continued his studies.
Hey, hey, hey, young lady!
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, young lady!
Hey! Hey!
Yes, hey!
What do you want now?!
Ah! My face! What is this thing?
Why, it's my famous
cloud candy of course!
Well, I suppose
it's not famous yet.
It's taken many
hours of research
to get it tasting like
cotton candy, you know.
But I think it's all
been worth it, don't you?
[NAMI shouting]
[HAREDAS yelps]
Are you nuts?!
Violence won't do, young lady!
Let's just calm down!
I could've died!
Oh, wow. That does
taste like cotton candy!
Yeah! Weren't you listening?
Wow. Really is an island
of wonders, huh?
[sighs]
Hey. I'm just checking,
but are you positive
we're still heading to
the Sabaody Archipelago?
[HAREDAS]
Of course.
I said I would grant you
a favor, and I meant it!
'Kay, but it was quite a long
time ago when you told me that.
Not to be rude, but
when will we get there?
Uh? What do you mean?
Hm? Ah! When do we get there?!
Impossible to say since
Weatheria travels on the winds.
So, if a typhoon hits,
we'll get there pretty fast.
Then how far did
we get yesterday?
My guess is about
600 feet or so.
--[NAMI grunts]
--[HAREDAS laughs]
[HAREDAS groans]
[NAMI] Seriously,
if this stupid island
wasn't floating in the sky,
I would've bailed already!
That's silly.
Even if we were on land,
you'd still be too far away
for it to do any good.
If you stay here, you'll get
there someday at least.
I know, but I'm not going
there for a vacation.
This is urgent business, okay?
We could go down for a bit.
Frankly, I could stand
to stock up on some
funding for my research.
Huh? Go down where?
On the ground.
[NAMI]
Uh... You can do that?
[HAREDAS] My research is
actually quite costly.
Thankfully, my weather
expertise is valuable
to the land dwellers, so I can
turn a profit pretty handily.
Wha.... is this?
[HAREDAS]
Young lady!
[NAMI gasps]
Over here!
[NAMI]
A ship?
Whoa. What the heck? It flies?
[yelps] Uh, no! No!
Here we go!
[NAMI]
Huh? [screams]
That's the island I was
looking for, let's land there!
[NAMI]
It's so dry.
Wow, that's rough.
[MAYOR] You can save our island?
And we're to believe that?
[HAREDAS]
Why not?
Your problem is straightforward
enough, I think.
Just a bit of rain should
set things right in no time!
Thankfully, I'm an
expert with the weather.
I'll gladly summon
a shower or two!
--[VILLAGERS gasp]
--[MAYOR] You jest!
So, how about we make
a little deal?
Does a hundred million
berries sound fair?
That's a lot!
--[VILLAGERS gasp]
--[MAYOR sighs]
Alas, even for the rain,
it's too much.
[HAREDAS]
Hm? Did I highball it a bit?
Are you kidding me?!
Do they look rich to you?!
I see. Well, how does
a hundred sound?
--[NAMI] Huh?
--[VILLAGERS] So cheap!
[NAMI]
Ugh!
You've got some pretty awful
business sense, old man!
[HAREDAS laughs]
It's fine.
That aside, can you
really do this?
Aren't you being
a bit optimistic?
Just watch and believe,
my dear lady. This'll be easy.
What's that?
Soap bubbles, maybe?
Looks like there's
something inside.
[HAREDAS laughs]
One more thing.
Could you take this and generate
some wind for me, please?
Oh, I see... Do you
want it full power?
[HAREDAS]
But of course!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Rain clouds? But that can't be!
[VILLAGERS cheer]
[VILLAGER B]
It's raining!
[VILLAGER C]
Yeah!
[CHILDREN laugh]
[HAREDAS]
What did I tell you?
[laughs]
They sure are happy,
aren't they?
[HAREDAS] The science of weather
has many wonderful applications!
[NAMI]
Hm...
Well, I suppose this
is goodbye, young lady.
I already spoke with the
mayor about your journey.
He said he would be happy
to help you along the way.
[NAMI]
I'm not going.
Huh? Why not?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Because, I want to learn
this science of yours!
I'm pretty impressed!
Really?
Since it's still
a while to Sabaody,
would you mind teaching
me along the way?
Ha. I'd be thrilled!
Oh, great! I can't wait!
Anyone with a passion
for the weather
is welcome to learn from me!
[BOTH laugh]
There's still one left.
Perfect. Now look.
This here is what
we in the business
call a soap bubble thundercloud.
[HAREDAS]
Oh, that's not good at all.
[groaning]
[NAMI growls] You old fool.
What are you doing?!
[HAREDAS] Science exacts a
price on its learner, my dear!
[NAMI] I'll exact
a price out of you!
[HAREDAS]
Help! Assault!
[NARRATOR] This is
the Mechanical Island,
Future Land Baldimore,
also known as the
birthplace of the Genius.
Super relaxed.
[KITTON sighs]
Aw, man!
He was so much fun before
and now he's just lame.
Grampa, tell me
you have a plan!
We've gotta turn
Franky back somehow!
[TAROIMO whines]
I ordered some cola for him
but it hasn't arrived yet.
I'm afraid he's beyond
our help, without it.
I'm sure a bottle or two
will bring him back
to his perverted
old, uh, I mean,
charming old self, but we
can't make him go wild.
Or can we?
[TAROIMO howls]
[TAROIMO howling]
[FRANKY]
It's cold!
How on earth I did I end up
out here in the elements?
Ah! How lovely, a scarf
for me? Thanks.
[FRANKY]
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my!
Goodness!
This... This is the nightmare!
[FRANKY]
"Keep Out,
this is an enclosed forest
of mechanical animals."
[CYBORG ANIMALS clamor]
[CYBORG ANIMALS growl]
Ready for plan A: Surprise
Awakening in the Jungle!
[TAROIMO pants]
[KITTON] Nothing's more
wild than mecha animals!
This'll get him back on
track for sure! [laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Don't try this at home, kids.
Now, now, let's all calm
down, shall we friends?
Because you seem
agitated this morning.
Did you remember to
eat your breakfast?
It is the most important
meal of the day, you know.
Let's work on getting those
blood sugar levels up!
[CYBORG ANIMALS growl]
Huh? Hold on a second,
that means it's breakfast
time for me, too!
Ahhh, you silly
goose! Ha, ha, ha.
Delicious! No better way
to start the day than with
a cup of tea! Ha!
Would you care for
some tea, too?
Ah! Let's cherish
every moment, friends!
[KITTON]
Ah... It's not working!
[KITTON, TAROIMO gasp]
--[CYBORG APE whoops]
--[KITTON screams]
[KITTON screaming]
Someone help us!
Ah, my friends, good day!
It's Franky!
[TAROIMO barks]
That's not proper. How about
"Mr. Frank" from now on?
Violence is never the a--!
[FRANKY groans]
I know that you're at an age
when you want to be naughty.
But listen... we can...
sort this out...
like gentlemen, right?
Nothing-- good-- ever
comes-- from violence!
Come on, just fight
back! Please!
You can't reason with gorillas!
Rela--
Listen to--
Listen to what I
to what I have to--
If you'd let me talk-- I
have-- wisdom to impart!
My friend-- we must-- not--
We--
[APE]
Huh?
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[CYBORG ANIMALS growl]
[FRANKY]
Ohh, yeah! Super!
[FRANKY yells]
Who do you think I am,
you punks, chopped liver?
You can't step to Franky!
He's back! You were seriously
starting to scare me!
[FRANKY]
Oh yeah, wow!
[KITTON]
What's wrong?
[FRANKY] I cooled off a bit and
ran out of steam, literally.
Huh? You mean... you're
gonna turn back?
Oh, I know just
the place to go!
[FRANKY]
Huh?
Where are you takin' me, kid?
[KITTON] To the house of Dr.
Vegapunk! It's not far and I bet
we can find a machine
that makes cola there!
[FRANKY]
Say what now?
[KITTON] Baldimore's
famous for its technology
and this guy is the genius that
cooked up a whole ton of it!
Like, all those mechanical
animals you just fought
were made by Dr. Vegapunk
ages ago!
I heard he was
kind of an oddball,
and he did leave the island
overrun with dangerous cyborgs,
but that doesn't make
him any less of a genius!
My Grandpa told me there's
some dangerous stuff in there.
But it's an emergency and
I have you to protect me,
so it should be okay.
[thud]
[FRANKY]
Lessee.
[ALL]
Huh?
[ALL whimper]
This is not good.
[NARRATOR] Sanji is pursued by
people of undetermined agenda
after he runs and runs, he finds
himself face to face with
a mysterious queen
and a frilly dress.
Meanwhile, Chopper finds himself
face to face with something
soft, round... and huge.
[LUFFY]
On the next, One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts!
The Chick of a Giant Bird
and a Pink Showdown!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!