Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR] With their
journey to Fishman Island
temporarily on hold,
the Straw Hats agree
to help the mermaid Camie
rescue her friend, Hachi.
As a result,
they soon found themselves
locked in a deadly battle
with the Flying Fish Riders.
When their leader, Duval,
was suddenly
unmasked by Luffy,
his strange and shocking
connection to Sanji
was revealed.
[SANJI]
You shut your damn mouth!
[LUFFY]
Explosion!
Sunny's Super-Secret Weapon,
Gaon Cannon!
[NAMI]
That face.
I see it,
but I don't believe it!
Whoa.
I thought Sanji's wanted poster
was just a bad drawing,
but here it is, in the flesh.
That's rough.
Black Leg Sanji.
You ruined me!
This is all your fault!
Hey, Sanji,
where are you going?
[DUVAL] Can you imagine
how scared ah was,
being hunted like an animal,
the Navy headquarters
hounding me at every turn?
Famous bounty hunters
knockin' at mah door.
I didn't wanna hurt nobody--
ah just wanted a life of peace
and quiet, and you destroyed it!
Uh, hey.
Just 'cause
you become a pirate
and got that bounty poster that
doesn't even look like you,
I gotta go into hiding
or someone's gonna
put my arms in shackles
or deliver my head
to the government!
What did I ever do to you?
Give me back my life!
Black Leg Sanji!
Who cares?
Ah! Head!
Listen up, you punk!
If you don't take responsibility
for this, then who will, huh?
[SANJI]
Shut the hell up!
I'm more pissed off about
the stupid wanted poster
than anyone!
So he's a victim, too.
Poor guy.
I guess.
But now I kind of wonder
which one of them
hates that poster more.
Who is that?
[LUFFY] You've been
depressed for long enough.
Shut up!
Why is mine the only
one with a drawing?
--Does this look like
--I thought it was a photo
--my handsome face to you?
--'til you said something.
[ZORO] Who has a
handsome face, again?
[SANJI] All the women in the
world are gonna laugh at me.
In a way, I guess
they've both got it bad.
Wasn't expecting that.
What a crazy world we live in.
I dunno if it's a lucky
one or an unlucky one,
but he must have been
born under some kinda star.
Whether this is a
miracle or a tragedy,
it's entertaining either way.
Hey guys, do you think we
can make friends with Duval?
[HACHI] They really do look
the same, don't they?
[ZORO]
Two peas in a pod.
Yohohohoho!
Yoho! Yohohohoho!
[coughing]
When I'm done with this guy,
I'm gonna flatten you!
Well, you go ahead
and take care of things!
We'll sit this one out.
Don't act like it's my fault!
If you didn't want to look
like the stupid wanted poster,
then why didn't you just cut
your damn hair or grow a beard
instead of trying to kill me?
Huh! I didn't think of that!
If you're that stupid,
you can only blame yourself!
Just shut up
and listen to me!
[SANJI]
Hm?
[DUVAL] You know, Black Leg,
me and my boys--
We just wanted a simple life.
Nothing fancy.
We weren't so bad.
[DUVAL] We were running a
humble little criminal outfit
in these parts,
just trying to make ends meet.
Hey, brat!
What d'you think
you're doing to our boss?
[DUVAL]
This little girl yours?
I... I'm sorry, sir!
[FATHER 389A]
Please, forgive her!
[MOTHER 389A]
Put my husband down!
[LITTLE GIRL 389A]
Daddy!
These are my best pants!
How are you gonna pay for this?
Huh?
[LITTLE GIRL 389A]
Daddy!
[MOTHER 389A]
Darling!
[DUVAL] We didn't
do anything wrong.
We just extorted
some money from people.
It was a simple life,
but a happy one.
[DUVAL] But one day,
it all came crashing down.
My innocent little dream
turned into a nightmare!
Oh man,
what d'you think he did?
It seems like a pretty
big bounty, doesn't it?
I guess the Navy really thinks
Duval is dangerous, huh?
[RANDOM GUY 389D]
Here he comes!
[RANDOM GUY 389E]
Don't go anywhere near him!
[RANDOM GUY 389F]
They're gonna arrest us, too!
[RANDOM GUY 389D]
Get away!
[DUVAL]
That's weird.
Why'd everybody run away?
[DUVAL] I didn't think
much of it at the time.
I just figured the village
had finally learned to fear me.
You know, on account
of me being so tough.
[DUVAL] But that
was wishful thinking.
[MARINE CAPTAIN 389A]
I don't know what you're doing
all the way out here,
but we found you.
Now surrender and save
us all some trouble.
Wait, why's the Navy here?
[MARINE CAPTAIN 389A] Don't play
dumb with us, Black Leg Sanji!
No way!
You mean I'm a wanted man?
77 million berries?!
But wait, that ain't my name!
Attack!
[DUVAL screaming]
[DUVAL] I ain't Sanji!
I ain't even met the guy!
[DUVAL]
They're gonna kill me!
Understand, Black Leg?
It's not my fault.
I never wanted to cause
any trouble, and suddenly,
I get a bounty of 77 million
because you don't
know how to behave.
[DUVAL]
A small town guy like me
can't stand up to all
those powerful Marines.
They hunted me down,
and now I gotta hide
behind that iron mask,
so nobody will
recognize my face!
My whole life is ruined
because you decided
to be a damned pirate!
I'm gonna chase you all
the way to the end of hell
if that's what it takes!
And if you got
a problem with that,
then why don't you just
kill me and get it over with?
Help me! He's killing me!
You're telling me you put
Nami and Robin in danger,
even though they have
nothing to do with this,
because some moron
drew a crappy picture of me?
'Cause they're part of the crew
that made you a famous
pirate in the first place!
[DUVAL]
If I'm gonna take revenge,
I might as well wipe out
the rest of your crew
while I'm at it, right?
None of you are
makin' it out alive!
[SANJI]
Poison harpoons?
Convert to trap mode!
Huh? Pervert?
If the Head says
you die, you die!
Take him down!
You suckers don't know
when to quit, do you?
You couldn't resist, could you?
This looks bad.
Sanji!
They're gonna pull him
into the ocean and drown him!
Sanji! Get outta there, quick!
It's no use!
It's made of iron!
Say hello to a watery grave!
Oh no!
Hang in there,
Sanji, I'll save you!
We don't need
both of you drowning.
Let me handle this one!
[HACHI]
I'm on it!
You humans are
too slow underwater!
You'll never catch up in time!
You're right.
But you don't stand a chance
against the speed of my men.
--[HACHI] Nyuu?
--[DUVAL] C'mon,
even you should know
that Flying Fish
are the fastest
creatures in the sea!
And my men have oxygen tanks,
so they can take
their sweet time
making sure
your little friend
is nice and dead
by the time he comes up!
See? I thought of everything!
Nyuu!
I wish I could've
crushed the life
out of that bastard
with my own two hands,
but at least I know
he'll die suffering!
What did you say?
[laughing]
This is what happens when
you piss off the Head, pal!
[SANJI]
I'm gonna pass out.
[CAMIE]
It's all right.
Camie, no!
Hey! Cowboy!
I think you may have forgotten
about a little someone.
Like you said,
flying fish are definitely
faster than fishmen.
And when it comes
to sea creatures,
they're in the top class.
But, just to let you know,
there is one creature
that's even faster than that.
Mermaids.
[PAPPAGU] In every sea
in this wide world,
there's nothing great or small
that can outswim a mermaid!
[CAMIE]
Don't worry, Sanjichin.
I'll be there real
soon, okay? Hold on!
She's really that awesome?
I never knew.
Yeah, and if she wasn't
spacing out all the time,
nothing would ever
be able to catch her.
It is what it is.
I see!
Camie! We're counting
on you! Good luck!
[NAMI]
Uh-oh. What is that?
[FRANKY] Looks like an anchor,
but crap, that's huge!
[FISH RIDER 388A] Aim for
the center of the ship!
Once we drop this,
they'll sink like a rock!
[FISH RIDER 388A] Some of 'em
have Devil Fruit powers,
so that'll take out
half the crew!
This bites.
No way we can survive that.
Then dodge it--
use the Burst or the Paddle!
Is there time?
No, it's too late.
[FRANKY]
Usopp, hurry. Come with me!
[USOPP]
Huh? O-Okay!
Go to the bow
and stay on standby!
[USOPP] I don't get it,
but whatever you say!
We're gonna bust out
our super-secret weapon!
What super-secret weapon?
They're gonna sink the Sunny!
Somebody do something!
Anything!
[FISH RIDER 388A]
Drop it!
No...
We seem to be
in quite the pinch.
Now die!
[USOPP]
Franky, hurry!
They're gonna sink the Sunny!
Somebody do something!
Anything!
Sunny won't die. Believe it.
The mane is spinning!
Is that supposed to happen?
Now die!
[USOPP]
Franky, hurry!
[CHOPPER screaming]
[FRANKY] Emergency
Evacuation Secret Weapon.
Chicken Voyage!
[FISH RIDERS]
They dodged it!
Hey, that's cheating!
How the hell do you make
your ship go backwards
in the first place?
Usopp, get inside the prow!
[USOPP]
Get inside?
Whoa! It opens!
[USOPP]
I thought I'd seen it all,
but Franky really
outdid himself!
[FRANKY]
Don't worry, brother.
We're not just running away.
The Sunny's got another trick
that's about to
knock your socks off!
Awesome!
[FRANKY]
Cola Energy charging!
What is that?
Uh-oh.
[USOPP]
Charging complete!
Hey! What am I
supposed to do now?
[FRANKY] Get as many
as you can in the circle!
[USOPP]
The circle? Like this?
'kay, they're in!
[FRANKY] Lock on with the button
below you, then pull the lever!
Below me, huh?
Ah!
Hey, look, it's glowing!
[FRANKY]
Gaon Cannon...
...Fire!
[NAMI]
Amazing!
[HACHI]
Nyuu?
You are way too
impressed with this.
[FRANKY]
How d'you like that?
Now you've seen the
Sunny's true power!
[CHOPPER] You got almost all the
flying fish guys in one shot!
[FRANKY] Well, you can
thank Usopp for that one.
Not bad for a first try, huh?
Yes! Go me!
Sunny!
Good show, Mr. Lion,
my eyes nearly
popped out of my head!
[BROOK] Or they
would have, if I had any.
Chicken Voyage uses
3 barrels of cola up front,
but right after, it also fires a
2 barrel Coup de Burst in back
to stop the ship
from getting blown away.
In other words, it uses
a butt-load of cola,
so it's not something
we can do often.
[FISH RIDER 389B]
She tied us up in the net!
[FISH RIDER 388M]
Damn it, that mermaid's fast.
Hold on, Sanjichin,
we're gonna make it.
We're almost there.
It's Camie!
Oh, thank goodness!
Is Sanji okay?
[CAMIE] I don't know,
but something's wrong!
He's losing a bunch of blood
for some reason!
[CHOPPER]
Is he dying?
I thought he was okay at first,
but blood started
pouring out of his nose!
A... nosebleed?
Eh, he's fine.
If he wants to die
like that, then let him.
Yep. It's what
he would have wanted.
[CAMIE]
Hang in there, Sanjichin!
[SANJI] Did I die
and go to heaven?
You little punk!
If you weren't friends with
a mermaid, you'd be dead!
[LUFFY] Looks like you lost
a lot of men back there.
Shut your mouth!
[DUVAL] I don't need
the Flying Fish Riders
as long as
I've got Motobalo.
You think I ride this guy
cause he looks cool?
Ha!
Countless have
fallen prey to his horns!
He poked holes
in the village dam back home
and if you try putting him
in a cage, he smashes the bars!
The Marines keep hounding me,
but I escape them every time
'cause this guy is always ready
to bust some heads!
[DUVAL]
They don't call his horns
the "Heart Rippers"
for nothing!
Okay. Let's rock.
Gooo... Motobalo!
Luffy! No!
The horns can't even reach him!
There's no point
in fighting, you big cow.
Stop it.
[DUVAL]
Motobalo, what's wrong?
Cow's acting weird
all of a sudden.
[FRANKY]
What happened?
[USOPP]
Guess it passed out.
Did I just miss something?
Hey Luffy! What was that?
I didn't do anything, I think.
[DUVAL]
Motobalo!
Why does my life suck so much?
Whatever he did, it didn't
seem like an attack.
It's more like he
won the animal over,
or at least knocked it over when
he spoke to it face-to-face.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you saying he
psyched the thing out?
Sure, Luffy's tough,
but that ox doesn't know that.
Maybe it's just a scaredy cow.
[DUVAL]
Straw Hat.
I'm gonna murder you!
[SANJI]
Hey. Hold on, Luffy.
Sanji!
Glad you made it out okay.
[SANJI] Stand back and let me
take care of this whiner.
I just met him and he's
already been a pain in my ass
for too long.
[DUVAL]
Your ass?
Look who's talking, Black Leg!
Until you're dead,
an innocent guy like me
can't find a moment
of peace in this world!
You're the criminal here!
And ah'm sick of
paying for your crimes!
That's enough.
[SANJI]
How do you think I feel
seeing that crappy
picture come to life?
A stupid face like that
shouldn't exist in this world!
You don't wanna see it?
Then just die!
[SANJI]
Oeil! Nez! Joue!
Bouche! Dents! Menton!
[DUVAL]
Please stop it.
Parage Shot!
Now eat this.
That's a full course
of my best techniques,
served up free of charge.
And it's the last
you'll ever taste,
you piece of crap.
[PAPPAGU]
Attention!
Since you guys seem
completely clueless,
I'll tell you how to
reach Fishman Island!
First, your ship needs to
be coated at a certain location.
The name of that location--
[CAMIE]
Look! There it is!
[LUFFY]
Awesome!
Look at all the bubbles!
[PAPPAGU] Camie,
I wasn't finished talking...
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Disembarking with Sights
Set on Fishman Island!
The Sabaody Archipelago!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!