The government was
planning on attacking us,
but Robin turned herself over
to CP9 so we would be safe!
Then Robin was lying
this whole time?
I won't let Robin die!
One-Sword Style!
Thirty-Six Caliber Phoenix!
It's Paulie!
Hurry!
Only one thing to do.
We set off and rescue
them right away!
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Let's go.
Hey, help us out, Rope Guy.
We need a boat.
Actually, we need a sea train.
Do you have
another one of those?
There is no "other" sea train.
The Puffing Tom
is one of a kind.
The man who made
that train's a legend.
It's miracle it
got finished at all.
So, sorry, I can't pull another
Sea Train out of my ass.
Okay, then lend us a ship!
The strongest and fastest
one you guys've got!
Damn it, would you
give it a rest already?!
Are you stupid?!
You saw what just happened!
You barely survived
that wave on land
and you wanna go out to sea?!
I don't care how
good the ship is...
you wouldn't last five minutes!
No kidding!
You idiot!
Even during a normal Aqua Laguna
no ship has ever made
it through the storm.
And this year,
it's anything but normal.
Just look at what happened
to the backstreets.
This is the first time the waves
have ever done damage like that.
Water Seven was built to last.
If it starts shaking, then
we damn well better listen.
I'm telling you,
even if you went out there
in our biggest galleon,
you'd be smashed to smithereens.
I'm not gonna let
you sail out there
if I know you won't
make it back alive.
Wait 'til morning.
We'll lend you a ship as
soon as the storm passes.
The rest of you head to
the evacuation shelter.
We're done searching
for missing people.
We can't stand around
like idiots waiting
for a wave to hit us.
Right!
Hold on.
If we wait until
after the storm settles
we won't make it in time
to save Robin, will we?
I heard about Enies Lobby
long before we came here.
When you said it was
a government island,
it made me remember something.
It's not just a base.
It's also where the Gates of
Justice are located, isn't it?
Well?
I'm not mistaken, am I?
Gates of Justice?
Enies Lobby is known
as a "Judicial island."
But that's all a lie.
The court they have
there is only for show.
The truth is, if
you've been taken there,
then you're already
considered guilty.
When you arrive the
government walks you
through an empty courtroom,
leading to a pair of
cold, steel doors that
tower above the entire island.
Those doors are known
as the Gates of Justice.
The criminals who
walk through them
must abandon all hope.
Once they reach the other side,
they'll never see the
light of day again.
Once you set sail
beyond those doors,
there are only two
destinations you can reach.
Neither of which you
are ever likely to leave.
One is Navy Headquarters
where the strongest
military powers
in the world gather
in the name of justice.
The other is Impel Down
an underwater prison,
filled with torture chambers
and execution blocks.
No matter how
vicious they may be,
the criminals imprisoned
there can only wait for death.
In other words
going to Enies Lobby
is no different than
a death sentence.
There's no trial, no justice
and no hope of escape.
Am I right?
Robin has a bounty on her head.
No matter where they take her,
she'll face death, or worse.
Every second we
sit here talking,
she gets one step closer
to the Gates of Justice.
Don't you dare tell us
to wait until tomorrow!
If you know that much already,
I've only got one thing to say.
Even if the sea was
calm and you were able
to set sail that's the last
place you should ever go.
Don't forget, you people are
wanted criminals just
the same as your friend.
Just like you said,
Enies Lobby is the front door
to the World Government's
own personal playground.
They've drawn battle lines
around that place that
should never ever be crossed.
Regardless of how they
feel about their crewmates,
no pirate would be stupid enough
to launch a
rescue mission there.
They know what would happen.
Picking a fight in that place
is like declaring war
on the entire Navy!
Hey. I know how you must
feel, but Paulie's right!
You can't leave during
Aqua Laguna, anyway!
You'll be dead before
you even get there!
There's no point in throwing
your lives away over this!
Luffy.
Fine then.
We'll steal a ship!
Our crewmate is counting on us!
Don't try to get in our way!
We're leaving now!
Whoa, even the waves got mad!
Whoa!
Is he gonna fight us?
That sure was scary!
Fine, then.
You want a fight, you got it.
All of you.
Stop it!
Kokoro?
Stop bein' such a
damn fool, Straw Hat.
Like it or not,
Paulie's right on this one.
Shut up granny,
it's none of your business!
You sure about that, boy?
Either way, these
folks are just trying
to stop you from
killing yourself.
The point is no
matter how mad you are,
no ship can handle Aqua Laguna.
Only a sea train made by a
legendary man stands a chance.
I know that, but
I don't have any choice,
since the only sea train in the
world has left town already!
If you're prepared to
die, then that's fine.
Just come along with me.
We'll brave the storm
on my sea train.
Who's that guy?
I dunno.
You idiots!
Don't just stand there!
If he's not wearing a uniform,
then he must be an intruder!
Get him!
I guess playing innocent
doesn't work in here.
And here I thought
I could get out of a fight.
Oh well, it's not my funeral.
Sanji?!
Hold it!
You think we're gonna
let you get away with that?
If you're smart.
Collier Frit!
Wait, you didn't
hijack the Sea Train
just to rescue me, did you?
I don't even know
what you're doing here.
Also, what's your name again,
I don't believe we've
actually met before, have we?
Oh, are you kidding me?
You jerk.
Bingo!
Transponder snails!
Hmm, okay.
This must be a communications
room or something.
Lucky I ran into
this place so soon.
Those guys I beat
up in the last cart
only had a bunch
of useless crap.
Masks and
costumes and stuff.
Anyway, now that I have this
I can get in touch with Nami.
Let me guess.
He's one of your
pirate friends, isn't he?
EX friend.
The question is, who are you?
I'm the face of
Water Seven's underworld.
The ship dismantler, Franky.
So you're the bastard
who beat up Usopp, huh?
He may be dead to me now,
but he was part of
our crew, back then!
How many pieces you
want me to cut you into?
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
It's not like that now, a lot
of stuff has changed since then!
Hey, punk!
You're lucky I'm tied up!
C'mon man, that
line's getting old.
Seriously, he's a good guy.
He saved the Merry
at least for a while.
Oh yeah.
The Merry was--
Whoa.
C'mon buddy, you can't get
all sad n' mopey on me now!
Hey! Blondie! Untie me!
Pretty Please?
You can spend the
rest of your life
in that potato
sack for all I care!
Screw you!
I said "pretty please" what
the hell else do you want?!
Stop it!
No more fighting, guys!
Look!
If we keep yelling, then the
marine's are gonna come!
Yeah? Then shut up!
Say what?!
They shoulda gagged both of you!
Whatever!
Just untie me, okay?
Don't order me around!
Stop fighting already!!
Captain T-Bone?
What are you--?
Franky's with them too?
Yes, sir.
But I'm afraid that the Sea
Train has already departed.
Paulie and the other
guys are out looking
for Straw Hat and
his friends but no luck.
Now that we all know that
Robin needs saving then
there's no limit to
what we can accomplish!
A secret base?!
It's been more than 8 years
since anyone's set foot in here.
And nobody's touched the
sea train for more than 12.
Let's go, Chopper!
Right!
I'm warning you, the thing
might not run anymore!
What?
You better be kidding me!
Now now, settle down, boys.
You can run as fast as you like,
but you're not getting
inside without the key!
Huh?
Now that's weird.
It's open-
Whoa-hoa!
Awesome!
Check out the face!
It's so cool!
Unlike the Puffing Tom,
this one here's a crazy train.
Its name is "Rocketman."
Comes with no guarantees,
so board at your own risk.
Rocketman!
Sounds fast!
Neat-o!
Did you have to add the face?
Don't worry, it may be
mean, but it won't bite.
Hey look, it's Ice Pops!
Hello there, Straw Hat.
So you're okay after all.
It seems your friend's
faith was well-founded.
I assume you brought
them here, Kokoro?
The question is,
what are you doing here?
You've been through a
lot today, you need rest!
Mmwell let's just say you
and I were thinking
the same thing.
We have a soft spot
for idiots, don't we?
Go ahead.
I just finished servicing it.
Water and coal have been loaded
and the steam's building up now.
Thanks for getting it ready
for us, we owe you one!
I wouldn't celebrate
yet, if I were you.
You might not even
survive the ride.
This was our failed prototype
before we made the Puffing Tom.
No matter how you tune it,
you can't control its speed.
In other words,
it's a runaway train.
That's fine!
It can go as fast as it wants!
Hurry up, let's go!
Get on already!
We're leaving as soon as
Nami gets here, Granny!
Ah man.
Luffy, are you okay?
You've been kinda shaky on
your feet since we found you.
He probably just
lost too much blood.
Maybe.
I am feeling kinda dizzy.
I think I need some meat.
Hurry, this way!
Wait!
I don't see why you have to go
all the way down here
just to eat your dinner!
He's right!
If you're hungry, eat now!
You think all that
food is for me?!
What?!
Sorry I took so long!
Nami.
Hey, save the
small talk for later!
Get on board so we can go!
Wow, amazing!
So there's another
sea train huh?
It was hiding here all
this time and we never knew!
This is a real surprise!
You're the one who
told us we have to hurry.
Why are you the
last one to get here!
And what's with that big bag?
I brought you food and drinks.
I'm sorry I just yelled at you.
He's ready to go!
You'll shoot out of
the canal into the ocean.
If you can latch onto
the railway after that,
it should be a good start.
Don't you worry a bit!
I like to drink,
but I take my job seriously!
You just stay here
and give that body
of yours a good rest!
Sounds fine to me.
And while I'm taking
care of these pirate folk,
I hope you don't mind watching
Gonbe and Chimney for me.
Yes, that's fine.
Don't go troubling
yourself over him, either.
That boy got hit by
a sea train, you know.
If he can survive that,
I'm sure he'll be okay!
Besides, we've got the
King of Pirates on our side.
We can't lose.
Straw Hat!
Who's there?
The Franky Family!
We're kind of busy right now.
Please! Straw Hat.
You guys gotta take us with you!
The people from Galley-La said
you were gonna take a
sea train to Enies Lobby!
Those government
bastards took Franky!
They took our bro away from us!
We wanna go,
but we can't get through
Aqua Laguna alone!
You sure you wanna
pick a fight on their turf?
I'll fight anyone, anywhere!
We gotta get our bro back!
I don't care what happens
to us as long as
we can save him!
We're begging you!
Please help us, Straw Hat!
We'll do anything!
If we don't hurry,
bro is done for!
You've gotta be kidding me.
You steal our money, beat up our
friend, then ask us for help?!
I don't care.
Even if it's wrong,
I'm still begging you.
I'll give up my pride
if I can save him!
C'mon.
Hurry up!
Thank you so much.
Are you sure about this?!
Eh, it's fine.
Thank you.
Thanks, Straw Hat.
Well, let's go!
Ah we don't have to
get on the train, though.
We'll just hop on our king bulls
and head out to sea the
same time the train takes off.
All you gotta do is let the
bulls catch a ride on your tail.
What're king bulls?
Anyway, we're off!
Thanks!
See ya, soon!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Let's show those bastards
what we're made
of and save our bro!
We're comin', bro!
How's that?
Good!
Now let's take off!
All right boys and girls.
Hold on tight,
so you don't fall off!
Now Departing Water
Seven for Enies Lobby!
Here comes Rocketman!
Yeah!
Full speed!
Let's go!
We'll get it all back!
Come on, Rocketman!
Don't let Aqua Laguna beat you!
I don't know about
these stowaways, Luffy.
All 50 members of the Franky
Family thank you, Straw Hat!
The more the merrier!
We all have the
same enemy, right?
Let's beat 'em up together!
On the next One Piece:
"Rescue Our Friends!
A Bond Among Foes
Sworn With Fists!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!