[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[USOPP screams]
[LUFFY gasps]
[BOTH whimper]
[WYPER]
If you don't want to die,
then go back to your
Blue Sea immediately.
Because I promise, if
you do anything stupid
on this island...
...we'll execute you.
Now leave.
I wonder why they're up here.
[SHANDORIAN M yells]
[SHANDORIAN E screams]
He's willing to
sacrifice this much for us
even though he gave us
that whistle for free.
Well, we wouldn't
be very good pirates
if we turned our backs
on gold. So let's not.
It won't be easy.
You know everybody up
here already hates us.
[laughs]
Gold! And it's all
waiting for us!
[LUFFY] "Festival on the Night
Before Gold-Hunting!
Feelings for Vearth!"
[FUZA screeches]
[SHANDORIANS screaming]
[SHANDORIAN B grunts]
[HOLY THE DOG growls]
Together, those two
are a problem.
[KAMAKIRI] We have to find
some way to separate them.
[GENBOU]
Hey, I got an idea.
[bellows]
[SHANDORIAN A yells]
[OHM whistles]
[OHM]
Three attackers.
[SHANDORIAN P growls]
[SHANDORIANS groan]
[LAKI grunts]
[HOLY THE DOG growls]
Laki!
[LAKI whimpers]
[OHM]
You look so sad dangling there
while all of your
hope drains away.
Heh. That stuff important
enough to die for?
[growls]
[grunts]
[LAKI growls
[OHM grunts]
[LAKI gasps, yells]
[KAMAKIRI]
Laki!
Kamakiri, you've gotta move!
Thanks, I owe you
one after that Kamakiri.
[gasps]
Ah!
Kamakiri!
[SHANDORIAN A]
Wyper! Kamakiri's taken a hit!
Huh? What happened?
[SHANDORIAN A grunts]
[WYPER growls]
Damn. So close to victory.
Heh! But you never
even had a chance.
When night falls, we'll have
an even greater advantage.
[chuckles]
[SHANDORIANS panting]
[WYPER growls]
We're moving out!
Grab all our wounded and meet
back at the rendezvous point!
Now!
[OHM growls]
You're not getting away!
[GEDATSU]
Ohm, wait.
What is it?
We have been summoned
by God Eneru.
[bird chirping]
[CHOPPER]
Hmm?
[ZORO]
Why'd you stop?
[CHOPPER] All that racket seems
to be getting farther away.
Well, maybe all those
guerillas and priests decided
to call it quits for the night.
Which sounds like
the right idea. Let's go.
Ah! Don't leave me behind!
[ZORO]
If you'd keep up, I won't.
[CHOPPER] But you don't know
how to get back to the camp!
[SANJI]
Hmm...
[LUFFY growls]
Ah! Boring!
[SANJI] Nobody told you
to watch the boiling water.
You have one job
and one job only.
Take the distilled water
and fill up the canteens,
so make sure that happens.
We'll need fresh
drinking water tomorrow.
[LUFFY]
Hmph. Whatever.
[CHOPPER] Sanji, we found
tons of great stuff.
[SANJI]
Excellent. Let's see the haul.
We found walnuts,
aloe, bananas, garlic.
[ZORO]
Rats and frogs, too.
Nice. It all goes in the pot.
[NAMI]
Disgusting!
You don't expect us
to eat that mess, do you?!
Oh, silly me.
Nami, I promise,
I'l take the garlic out.
The garlic's
the only good thing!
[ROBIN] Is our navigator
having another meltdown?
[NAMI]
Now that's what I call a gem.
It's huge!
[ROBIN chuckles] Big, yes,
but it's not a gemstone.
Hey, that's a big salt crystal.
Nice find, Robin dear.
I found it on the shore.
And I figured we'd
find some use for it.
Not only is salt
vital to survival,
but without it, my food
would taste awful!
[cackles]
If I take half of
the garlic and aloe,
then I can make antiseptic
and burn ointment
and use it to heal
the Sky Knight.
Yeah? You need any frog?
[CHOPPER]
No. No frog.
[SANJI]
Zoro, you're not doing anything.
I got a little job for you.
[ZORO groans]
Sanji, my swords were not
meant to be used like this.
[SANJI] Yeah, but disobey the
chef and you probably won't eat.
So it's your call.
[LUFFY] Ah! You just
dropped a rock in the stew!
--Is it good?
--We don't eat it.
It helps the pot cook.
The stone's heat cooks
the stew from the inside out.
[CHOPPER]
Ah...
Trust me on this one.
You'll need all the nutrients in
this dish to survive this place.
[CHOPPER]
Perfect, then.
[LUFFY]
Smells like we got a winner--
--[CHOPPER gasps]
--[LUFFY grunts]
Keep your hands off!
[LUFFY groans]
Sanji. I'm hungry.
Well, it's not ready yet!
Weren't you just
cramming a skyshark
down your gullet not
ten minutes ago?
Yeah. But that
was just an appetizer.
I figured you knew that.
He must have
a rubber stomach, too.
Yeah, tell me about it.
[ZORO]
What are you doing Usopp?
Sanji's almost got
dinner laid out for us.
[USOPP gasps] I figured, since
I wasn't doing anything anyway,
I'd start hauling this wood
over to the ship for repairs.
You're gonna
swim over there, huh?
Yeah.
So you don't have a
problem with the giant sharks?
[USOPP] The ship will
still be broken tomorrow,
I'll fix it then.
Let's eat, Zoro!
[ZORO]
What a moron.
[NAMI]
Yes! Finished!
[SANJI] Soup's on,
but it's ladies first. Got it?
[CHOPPER]
Sure.
[SANJI] If you would all
please take your seats,
I'll be around with
your meals shortly.
And eat up--I don't
want it getting cold.
[NAMI] Now, if you would all
listen up while you eat,
I'll explain how we're going
to handle this tomorrow.
[USOPP]
Oohh, it looks tasty!
You said it. Thanks.
Hey, this is important,
you guys.
[SANJI]
Then I am all ears, Nami-sweet.
[LUFFY]
Me, too!
Wow. Check out the
heart-shaped carrots!
You really go
the extra mile, Sanji.
You're welcome. Yes.
I did all that just to
impress you, Usopp.
[USOPP]
Uh... All right.
Anyway... Let's review
Noland's book first.
He discovered the
City of Gold 400 years ago.
However, after leaving the
island and returning with
his king, he found the
gold ruins had vanished.
Luckily, we now know what
happened to these ruins.
Keep the ladle handy,
I'll be back for more after I--
[bong]
Sanji, pay attention!
[SANJI] I was, but he
was interrupting you!
[LUFFY] I compliment his food
and this is the thanks I get?
Sheesh!
[NAMI growls]
The point I was getting at
is that the gold didn't sink
into the ocean, but was
shot up here into the sky
by the knock-up stream
just like we were.
Do you really
think a whole island
could have done that?
[NAMI] Well, it's the only
thing that makes sense.
Remember? Cricket
said that every time
this phenomenon occurs it's
in a different location.
Yeah, that explosion
was enormous.
I'm not surprised
it lifted an island.
[ZORO] Hmm. It's just hard
to believe that the forest
we're sitting in is the same
one we saw back on Jaya.
[ROBIN] I believe that
has something to do with
the odd composition of
the island clouds up here.
Look at all the trees,
fish, and wildlife.
Something about this
environment dramatically
increases growth rates.
Which explains how
a society here could have been
swallowed up by these
burgeoning forces.
[SANJI sighs]
So tragic.
[CHOPPER] That also explains
why the South Birds
who saved us were so huge.
I couldn't believe it.
Yeah, 400 years of
growing will do that to a bird.
[SANJI] Then why-- Here.
Why did those South Birds
go to such great lengths
to save you guys?
Um... I don't know.
But, when they saw him,
they referred to
--the Sky Knight as God.
--[BOTH gasp]
He's god? So if we
beat the crud out of this guy,
then our job here is done!
[USOPP]
No, genius!
How did you get that out
of what he's saying?!
[NAMI] Would both of you
loudmouths just pipe down?!
[USOPP]
Yeah, shut up!
[LUFFY]
Yeah. Wait, who's a loudmouth?
--[USOPP] You are!
--[NAMI] You both are. Can it.
Now does anyone recall
what Noland's log said
about the City of Gold?
[LUFFY]
I do! It's a city of gold!
[USOPP]
You're such a dumbass!
Do you ever think
before you talk?!
I think he wrote
about South Birds
and a giant gold bell.
'Course there
could be a lot more.
The last thing
he wrote in the log before
he died was something odd.
It's something
I can't figure out
even after seeing this island.
It says "The City of Gold
is in a skull's right eye."
That's it! Check it out.
I matched up Robin's map of
Jaya with the old Skypiea map
that we found in the shipwreck.
Of course, this isn't
exact and there may be
some incorrect overlap, but
when you match up the location
of Cricket's house with the
broken part we found up here,
this is what Jaya looked
like 400 years ago.
Neat! It's a skull!
It is a skull!
Well?
[LUFFY gasps]
Way to go, Nami!
[CHOPPER]
We did it!
[USOPP] Okay. But where
in the skull's right eye?
[NAMI] Hmm...
I'm thinking right here.
It's the one structure
that's actually inside the eye.
And no one's found it yet
because of all the people
who have tried, we're the
ones who had both maps.
[USOPP] Ah. Of course.
We must be lucky pirates.
It kinda makes sense.
Hidden treasure!
[CHOPPER]
Treasure! [laughs]
The only thing left
to do is make our way
to the skull's eye.
But since we can't
leave the ship unguarded,
tomorrow morning, we'll split
the crew into two teams.
This is our time.
On the other side of
this island waits more gold
than we've ever dreamed.
Wyper--
[WYPER] How serious are
Kamakiri's injuries?
[GENBOU] Well. They're
tending to him right now.
He's back there.
Is he going to make it?
[GENBOU]
See for yourself.
[WYPER] I didn't expect him
to be defeated like that.
[GENBOU] What can we do?
Ohm will not easily be beaten.
It's me.
[WYPER]
Hmm?
[gasps]
[LAKI whimpers] It was my fault.
He's dying because of me!
[LUFFY sighs]
Now that's what I call gourmet!
Tomorrow, we get the gold!
[NAMI]
You got it! [giggles]
You think it'll be sunny again?
We are above the clouds
so I'd guess "yes."
Let's put out the fires
if we don't need them.
It's beginning
to get late, you guys.
We don't want
to announce our location
to our enemies.
[LUFFY]
Hmph. What a rookie move.
You hear that Usopp?
She wants us to douse the fire.
What are we gonna do?
Huh?
[USOPP]
I don't know.
It's not really
her fault though.
She's never been exposed
to this kind of living before.
We should be tolerant.
[ROBIN] Huh?
What are you two saying?
[LUFFY sobs] You're always
supposed to have a campfire when
you camp that's what
makes it camping!
[USOPP sobs] 'Cause it's
the warmth of the flame
fighting through
all this wilderness
that reminds us
that we're human!
[NAMI] It's never-ending
with those idiots.
Hey! Lay off the sob stories!
You know how dangerous
this island can be.
Let's not give it
any help in killing us.
Don't care.
We're in the middle of
a war between priests
protecting their god and
guerillas forging a coup!
Not to mention the giant,
bloodthirsty monsters
that wait around
every corner to eat us
[CHOPPER]
Not monsters!
Sky island scary.
Luffy, take a look!
Is this enough
wood for your fire?
Can you idiots
think for one second?!
[SANJI] Heh. Don't worry.
Wild animals are afraid of fire.
They'll stay away.
But they're surrounding us.
We have to run or we'll die!
[WOLF A growls]
[screamin]
[barking]
Chopper. I think
it's trying to talk.
You mind translating?
[CHOPPER whimpers]
[barking]
[CHOPPER] "You jerks are being
so loud we can't even hunt!
Why don't you dumbass humans
go to hell and sleep already?!"
[BOTH]
Who's a dumbass?
[CHOPPER] I didn't say it!
It was the wolf!
[barking]
[CHOPPER] "You rotten
two-leggers better not be trying
to muscle in and take
what doesn't belong to you!"
No. We're not like that.
We were brought here
against our will.
"This is our forest!
You think you can just come in
and start building fires?"
Sorry.
"Everything here belongs to us!
The land, the trees,
and the air!"
--[bonk]
--[WOLF A yelps]
[screams]
Nothing's keeping
me from that treasure!
[WOLVES growling]
Great. Everything's
gotten worse again.
Now we get eaten by wolves.
Didn't see that coming.
[NAMI]
Do something!
[USOPP]
What can I do?!
--[WOLF A barks]
--[USOPP whimpers]
[WOLVES whine]
[CHOPPER]
"Back down, boys.
We may have the numbers,
but they got the raw power.
It's not worth it.
Girl, you pack
one mean punch there.
Gotta say, you're
my kind of angry."
So, uh, that's what
a happy ending looks like.
[ZORO]
I guess so.
[LUFFY]
Then... I have an idea.
Campfire!
[cheering]
[WOLVES howling]
[ALL howling]
[USOPP] It's the Festival on
the Night Before, Gold-Hunting!
[LUFFY howling]
[howls]
This is fantastic!
And you guys
really make this stuff?
That's great! More please!
[ZORO gulps]
Hmm?
--[CHOPPER, SANJI laugh]
--[ROBIN chuckles]
[howling, laughter]
[BOTH laugh]
I love you guys.
Tomorrow the treasure's ours!
Our treasure!
Tomorrow!
[howling, laughter]
[GAN FALL] I'm surprised
you're getting along so well
with the cloud wolves.
[chuckles]
I know of no one else
who could have such
raucous festivities
on Eneru's land.
[ROBIN] It's good to
see that you're awake.
Are you feeling any better?
[GAN FALL] I apologize for being
such a burden to you all.
Hey. You're too hard
on yourself old man.
You saved Chopper, and you
kept our ship from being blown
to a thousand pieces.
[GAN FALL]
That's my duty.
[ROBIN] There's still
plenty of stew left.
Would you like some?
[GAN FALL]
Thank you, no.
Not right now.
Hey! Thanks for everything,
Sky Knight guy! Let's dance!
[CHOPPER]
C'mon, dance with us, Gan Fall!
[ZORO]
Chopper, you been drinking?!
[WOLF E howls]
Hey, old man, I gotta question.
Conis. Is she okay?
[GAN FALL]
Very much so.
I've sheltered her and
her father at my house.
They're fine.
[SANJI] Great. I was worried
she'd never see me again.
I'm so happy that
both of them are safe.
Now. Let's celebrate
by tossing Chopper.
[CHOPPER]
Why me?!
[laughs]
[BOTH whopping, laughin]
[GAN FALL]
I'm sorry for eavesdropping,
but I heard your earlier
conversation about how
this island was known
long ago by the name Jaya.
[ROBIN]
Yeah, that's right.
[GAN FALL] But I believe you
have yet to hear the story
of how this island
on which we sit...
...came to be known
as such holy ground.
[LAKI gasps]
Is this what was
so distracting for you
in battle, Laki?
Are you here to sabotage us?
Get in our way and slow us down?
No, I'm not.
I feel awful for Kamakiri.
[WYPER]
We were fighting the priests!
We can't afford to be
off task at all if we want
to make it to God's Shrine!
Apologizing won't
fix anything--I know that!
So give that back to me. Now!
It belongs to Aisa! It's hers!
I promised I would bring
back some vearth for her!
Give it back to me! Please!
--Shut up!
--You have to let me have it--
Kamakiri. You shouldn't
even be standing right now.
[KAMAKIRI]
I can still fight.
[KAMAKIRI] You're right about
this being our best time
to strike the Upper Yard.
With Satori gone,
we proved today
that we can defeat
the remaining priests.
I say we attack
again tomorrow, at first light.
[GAN FALL] The ground of
the Upper Yard must remind
you Blue Sea people
of your home far below.
It is similar, right?
[ZORO]
It is.
[GAN FALL]
Yes. You're lucky.
What you see all around us
and beneath our feet
is something that does not
naturally exist in the sky.
[GAN FALL] Island cloud
can support plant life,
but it cannot generate its own.
Greenery and soil are both
foreign things to our life here.
[GAN FALL] Our people have
our own name for this.
It's vearth.
[GAN FALL] Those living among
the clouds hold this sacred.
It's what they all desire.
[KAMAKIRI]
Once we kill Eneru...
...there will be no need
for you to sneak around
obsessing over a
single bag of vearth.
The time is now.
[KAMAKIRI] We will return
after 400 years of exile--
to the true home
of the Shandorians!
[WOLF A howls]
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[LUFFY] Finally, we get
to chase down the gold!
[USOPP] I am Usopp, Chief
Operating Officer of
Operation Get the Going
Merry Off that Stupid Altar!
[CHOPPER]
Well, help me, sir.
[USOPP] Of course!
There's nothing I can't do!
[ZORO]
Then get to it, Chief.
[GAN FALL] You know
you're mortal enemies
of Eneru by now, right?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Enter God Eneru!
Farewell to the Survivors!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!