[thinking]
There's no mistaking it.
This is my handwriting.
Sky Islands, Marine
Base G8, and this gold.
If what's written here is true,
could everything they
said be true, as well?
If I can just get back
to Cocoyashi Village,
I'm sure I could
figure it all out.
But without a decent ship,
how am I gonna get there?
And, I'm on the Grand
Line, of all places!
According to this map,
it's impossible to sail directly
from this sea to the East Blue.
[USOPP] Wait, what's that?!
You're the captain?!
Aw, man! That was a lucky break!
If I hadn't gotten
my memory back,
I would have been stuck
"aye-aye-ing"
Captain Usopp forever!
Shut your mouth!
I'm never gonna believe it!
No matter what anyone says,
I know that I'm the
great Captain Usopp!
I have an army of 8,000 pirates
who obey my every command!
Hahahaha!
That's the Usopp I know,
through and through!
But you're not the captain.
You're Usopp, the sniper
of the Straw Hat Pirates!
[USOPP thinking] Crap! The
tables have turned against me!
[CHOPPER thinking] This guy's
a monster, just like me.
And yet he's the captain?
Hey, Chopper!
Ahhh! Keep away!
Aw, come on!
How long are you
gonna act like that?
Let's play like we always do!
So, I'm the ship's doctor,
and this is
something I always do?
Yeah! You do it every
time we have a party!
It's like your "thing"!
Come on, Chopper!
That rubber monkey said
he got his memories back,
yet he's acting like just
as much of an idiot as before.
That's right.
The captain never ever changes,
no matter what happens to him.
[USOPP thinking]
Even if I am a pirate,
I'm nothing compared to
these freaks of nature!
I'd never survive sailing
with the likes of them!
How'd I get myself
into this mess?
[ROBIN]
Now it's clear what happened.
Everyone didn't miraculously
lose their memories overnight,
they were stolen.
And so the
obvious culprit is.
The only person we
all remember: That brat!
What would that
freaky kid want
with our memories anyway?
Beats me.
Wait a sec!
We have to get
Nami and Zoro back!
Come on! Let's go! Hah!
[ROBIN] You're right, but
we should wait until morning.
Hmm?
Why can't we go right now?
Searching for two people
on an unknown island
in the middle of the night
is a recipe for disaster.
Guess you've got a point.
Let's get some rest
and then we'll begin our
search when the sun comes up.
I don't think that boy
will be back tonight.
We gave him a lot of trouble.
He'll think twice before
showing up here again.
Hmm...
Right! It's settled!
We'll rest up
and start the search
first thing in the morning!
[SANJI]
Hold on a sec.
I'm all for bringing that
lovely lady Nami back,
but not that Zoro guy.
He can just stay
gone for all I care.
I agree! If you two
wanna go look for him,
you can do it on your own!
I, uh.... I'm not sure.
What the?!
What're you saying?!
We're saying,
"Why look for Zoro?"
He's a pirate
hunter, remember?!
Why should we go
through all the trouble
of chasing down
a guy like that?
Isn't it obvious?
Because he's our friend!
Just because you said
it doesn't mean it's true.
Come on!
That guy sure didn't act
like he was our friend.
Surely you noticed that.
The way he left is
proof enough for me.
Usopp is the sniper.
Sanji is the cook.
Chopper is the doctor.
Robin is the archaeologist.
Nami is the navigator.
And Zoro is the swordsman.
We are the Straw Hat Pirates
and we don't leave
any man behind.
[ROBIN] Then we'll have to get
Mr. Swordsman's memory back.
No problem!
All I have to do is kick
that brat's butt again!
That's how I got mine back!
Sound good, Chopper?
Well, it looks like tomorrow's
gonna be a really busy day.
All right, let's all get
some sleep while we can.
[ROBIN thinking] The key
to unraveling this mystery
is somewhere on that island.
[DRIM thinking] It seems
that I underestimated you,
Monkey D. Luffy.
You're a formidable enemy.
Still, you won't stop me
from making my wish come true.
But, in order to do so,
I'll need an ally.
An ally like a certain
skilled swordsman.
Hmph!
[sighs]
[thinking]
That's right!
He's different than
he was yesterday.
This man is Pirate Hunter Zoro.
If I try to approach him,
things could go bad quickly.
Okay then. I'll cut
my losses for tonight.
There'll be other
chances soon, anyway.
Oh, yes. And when
that time comes,
your work will truly begin.
[thinking] It is said that
fish from around the world
gather together in the All Blue.
I've dreamed of
reaching that sea...
Why'd you help me?
It doesn't make sense to
sacrifice so much for me!
You old fool!
Tell me!
Because for my entire life,
I've had the
same dream as you.
A restaurant?
I was thinking that if I make
it out of this mess alive,
I'd could build a restaurant
as my final purpose.
Great! And I'll
even help you do it.
So don't die okay?
Ha! A weak little
brat like you
couldn't be much
good for anything!
Then I'll become strong!
[thinking] That annoying
old geezer saved my life.
There's no way I would
have ever left him.
So why? What the
hell happened to me?
[thinking]
Pepper, Carrot, Onion.
I wonder what happened
to the Usopp Pirates?
It's go time,
Brave Usopp Pirates!
We do have a village
that we need to protect!
[KAYA] So what adventure are you
going to tell me about today?
[USOPP]
Well let's see. Oh I know!
What about the story of me
fighting a giant goldfish,
at the south pole, when
I was only five years old!
Goldfish?
[USOPP]
A giant goldfish!
What first astounded me was
the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that
when I landed on it
I thought it was solid ground.
Usopp! Hahahha!
[thinking] I've always
dreamed of being a pirate,
just like my old man.
Did I actually
become a real one,
leaving everyone
behind to do so?
[CHOPPER thinking]
Why am I here?
Why am I here
with these humans?
The only ones I've ever trusted
were Dr. Hiriluk and Doctorine.
Even among my fellow reindeer,
I had no friends.
I was always alone.
[HIRILUK] I promise you I'm
not going to shoot you, see?!
Listen, my name is
Hiriluk. Doctor Hiriluk!
And if that's true there's
no disease that can't be cured.
Let them all laugh
at me, I don't care.
My medical skills will save
this country yet! You'll see!
I raise this skull
and crossbones
to challenge all
diseases of the world.
A skull?
This symbol represents
my conviction
and belief that there is
nothing that's impossible!
I will save this country
with my doctor's skills!
[thinking] And now I have
friends? Six of them?
How am I supposed to
believe I'm out here
with them as a doctor
on a pirate ship?
But what if it's true?
None of that's
gonna happen.
Nothin' can take
away my dreams.
And I know it's the
same for you guys too.
Nami, Zoro.
Sit tight and don't worry.
We're coming for you.
Hey! Wake up!
[ROBIN]
We're already up and ready.
Mr. Cook and
Mr. Doctor are here, too.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
There's no way I'd ever
leave a lady like that behind.
And besides, Robin's going
to need herself a bodyguard.
And if anyone gets injured,
then they'll surely need the
assistance of a doctor, right?
Which means that I should
stay behind and guard the ship.
You're coming too, Usopp.
Well, actually I've got this
"My Heart'll Stop If I
Go On the Island" disease.
Just come with us!
I know one thing:
Usopp, the brave
warrior of the sea,
is a man who always comes
through when things get rough!
That's me!
All right then! We're all going!
Aw, crap! I got caught
up in the moment!
So how are we gonna get
across the bay to the island?
I think a raft is
the most viable option.
Good idea! Hey!
Make us a raft, Usopp!
Why should I?!
I'm Captain Usopp, remember?!
Yeah, yeah.
At the very least,
I'm a sniper!
Either way, I can't properly
do the job of a shipwright!
To make a raft, all you do
is tie some logs together!
Problem solved!
Are you sure those are the
right kind of knots to use?
Well, yeah! A knot's
a knot, right?
[thinking]
You've gotta be kidding!
That thing's gonna break apart
as soon as it hits the water!
But mine looks
a whole lot cooler.
Check this baby out!
No way!
Mine is the coolest!
Sorry, but there's no
comparison. Mine rules.
[USOPP]
Oh, come on! Seriously?!
How can you call
yourselves pirates
when you can't even
make a decent raft?!
[SANJI]
Ooo!
Such amazing workmanship!
See? Usopp's a man who
always comes through!
Hm?
[thinking] Wait, how did
I know how to build this thing?
I don't get it.
All right! Let's Go!
Thanks for the room.
What do I owe you?
[OLD INN MAN]
Sorry, who are you?
Huh? What? I'm a
guest of the inn.
I stayed here last night!
[OLD INN MAN]
Do you recognize her?
[INN WOMAN] No,
I've never seen her before.
[YOUNG INN MAN]
Wait, she might be a thief!
What? A thief?!
Hey, now hold on a
second! I'm a customer!
I just met all
three of you yesterday!
Do you seriously
not remember me?
I mean, surely
you do, Mr. Manager.
Manager? You mean me?
Uh... He is the manager
of this inn, right?
[YOUNG INN MAN and INN WOMAN]
I don't know.
[thinking] It's nice that I
got to stay for free and all,
but what in the
world is going on here?
Could this mean that--
Who're you?
Don't tell me you
lost your memories, too?
It's just like what
happened to me yesterday!
[VILLAGE MAN A]
Yesterday?
[USOPP]
Yeah, that's right.
They might have
come through here.
There was a swordsman
with green hair
and a woman
driving a weird boat.
So did you see them?
[VILLAGE MAN A] Yesterday...
Now what did I do yesterday?
Not you, too?!
What is wrong with the
people on this crazy island?!
Not a single one of these
nitwits remembers anything
about what they did yesterday!
Hahahahaha!
What carefree people!
I think it's a little more
than being "carefree."
And we're not
really ones to talk.
We're just like them.
It might be more
than just coincidence.
So what's the plan?
What do we do?
It'll be kinda tough finding
them in this situation.
Right! Back to
the ship then!
No good thing is
gonna come from us
wandering around
on this creepy island.
So, what do you say?
Hey, Nami!
Oh, crap!
Hey! Wait!
What a day.
Why'd you run
away from us, Nami?
You'll never get this
away from me, got it?
You'd have to kill me
before I'd let it go.
Don't say that!
There's no way I'd hurt
a beautiful lady like you!
That's ridiculous!
I promise, I won't
lay a finger on you!
Though I'd really like to!
Hey doc, what kind of
disease does he have?
Can't you do anything for him?
It's definitely a
serious condition,
but I'm pretty sure
there's no cure.
Fine, let's make a deal.
What kind of deal?
I promise to give you
10% of my treasure,
if you promise to take me
back to Cocoyashi Village.
No way.
Okay, then 20%.
Nuh-uh.
Fine! 30%!
Can't do it.
It'll kill me, but 50%!
Sorry.
Nnnn... Gah!!
Just how much
of this treasure
are you trying to
swindle me out of?!
Come on, Nami!
You love that treasure! Hah!
There's no way that you'd
ever give it up to anybody.
Hey, how the
heck did you know
that I was gonna
double-cross you?
Ha ha ha!
Because we're friends,
Nami! How else?
Gimme a break!
Why would I ever be
friends with the likes of you?
This is ridiculous.
The negotiations are over.
I'm leaving. See ya!
Step aside, please.
Not happening.
Nami, you are going
to come along with us.
You're out of
your freakin' mind.
Why would I go
anywhere with you guys?
Now move it, jerk!
I won't.
[ROBIN]
Miss Navigator.
Huh?
You've been feeling that
there's something odd
about this island ever
since you set foot on it.
Am I wrong?
You look perplexed.
What's the matter?
There was a boy
holding a strange horn.
Yeah, last night I got
a good punch in on him.
And then some smoke
came out of his horn
and then it
went into my body
and then I could
remember stuff!
That's right.
The captain has all
of his memories back.
Preposterous, are you
sure you weren't dreaming?
No, it's true!
I saw the whole thing
happen with my own two eyes!
I also seem to
remember seeing
that little brat the
night before last, as well.
What I wanna know
is why he came back.
It's just a theory,
but maybe he
wasn't able to steal
all of your
memories in one shot.
Even with just what I know,
you all seem to have
experienced numerous
incredible adventures
during your journeys together.
It was too much
to take all at once,
so he starved himself
and returned yesterday?
The theory seems
logical enough.
Hey, Robin! Do you think
that memories taste good?
So then that little boy.
Bye! See ya!
[LUFFY]
All right then!
Let's go kick that
little runt's butt again
and get everybody's
memories back!
Then Zoro will
rejoin our crew!
I doubt that it's gonna
be as simple as that,
but we definitely need to give
that brat some painful payback.
Look, can't we just
forget about Zoro?
Even if we get
our memories back.
It's kind of unsettling
to be in a pirate crew
on a pirate ship with a
pirate hunter, you know?
Zoro's the swordsman
and Nami's the navigator.
They're our friends
and part of our crew.
It still bothers me when
you say that, you know!
How can I be a pirate, much
less friends with pirates?
Look, I'm the one who's
gonna be bothered without you.
Without a navigator,
the ship can't go anywhere!
Understand?!
[LUFFY] Robin! Do you
have any idea where
that little runt is hiding?
[ROBIN] Well, there is one place
that I'd like to check out.
[LUFFY]
Okay then! Let's go!
Hey, wait! My gold!
Don't worry!
I'll carry the lady's stuff!
If doing so means
I get to be with you,
then this is no trouble at all!
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
[thinking] Even with
everything that's happening,
they all follow Luffy.
I wonder if it's true
that I have friends now.
[LUFFY] Hey, Chopper!
What are you waiting for?
Let's go!
Aye-aye!
If you wanna eat, help yourself.
Well, it's true that
I am rather hungry.
But this isn't the
kind of food that I eat.
Oh, yeah?
Tell me, why haven't you
asked me who I am yet?
Ah! That's right.
The people that live on this
island don't remember anything.
Not even their
own names, huh?
No point in asking.
You're on a quest to become the
strongest in the world, right?
Hmm, if that's the case,
then I think that
Monkey D. Luffy
would be the perfect
opponent for you.
Huh?
Hi, I'm Luffy!
So what's your name?
Talking about that
idiot in the straw hat?
I'm actually
surprised that someone
like Roronoa Zoro couldn't
see that man's strength.
See his strength?
What do you mean?
I mean that
Monkey D. Luffy
destroyed the
vicious Arlong along
with his fishman pirate
crew in the East Blue.
Then, in the Grand Line,
he managed to bring
down Crocodile,
one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea, all by himself.
Warlords of the Sea?
Yeah. And that's not all.
On the sky islands,
he beat up a powerful
god named Eneru!
And after that, he went on
a rampage in a Marine Base!
Against Luffy, even the Marines
had to throw in the towel!
I've never seen
another pirate like him!
Don't screw with me!
I'm not in the
mood for any more
of these cock-and-bull
stories, you got it?
So after hearing all that,
you wanna fight
Luffy, don't you?
[chuckles]
What are you doing?
Huh? Where are we?
Is this where that
weird kid lives?
This place is
giving me the creeps.
[CHOPPER thinking] Did I
catch a cold or something?
I've been shivering
for a while now.
If only we had a doctor here.
Wait! That's me!
[NAMI thinking]
I bet these pirates
are trying to take me out
to the middle of nowhere
so they can steal my gold!
I won't let them do it!
[SANJI thinking] Nami's
been shooting glances
at me this whole time!
That can only mean one thing:
She's fallen in love with me!
Back atcha!
[NAMI thinking]
Is that some kind of signal
that he's about
to steal my gold?
He's freaking me out!
Now I see.
[LUFFY]
Butterfly!!
What's up, Robin?
Did you find something?
I just determined the culprit
that stole your memories.
Consequently, it's not
the one we thought it was.
Wait a second, you mean
it's not that little brat?
Now, let's make our way
to the Sea God's Palace.
Sea God's Palace?
Okay, but why?
Eh-heh! Just a hunch.
♪ ending song ♪
[NAMI] This was
a terrible idea!
Why did I go
along with you guys?
[USOPP] She's right! Hey!
Let's go back! Come on!
[LUFFY] No way.
Not without Zoro.
[SANJI] That damn swordsman
is coming right for us!
[LUFFY] Oh, hey!
You're right!
[SANJI] Hold on!
He's acting strange.
[LUFFY] Really?
Zoro is always like this!
On the next One Piece:
"Zoro Bares His Fangs!
A Savage Animal
Stands in the Way!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!