[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
And Impact.
[KAMAKIRI]
Burn... Blade!
[ENERU] Think you're
faster than lightning?
[KAMKIRI]
Wyper!!
[AISA screams]
[AISA] The voices,
they're disappearing!
[ENERU] I guess my electricity
traveled down the Milky Road.
The stupid fools.
[LUFFY] "A Mystical City!
The Grand Ruins of Shandora!"
It's amazing.
You're incredible, Nami!
She's all yours now,
and as good as new!
[NAMI]
Yeah! Thanks!
I don't know what
you did, but I love it.
This thing is
so fast it's crazy!
[PAGAYA]
It's true,
and Jet Dials went extinct
hundreds of years ago.
It's really quite astonishing.
Imagine how shocked I was
to find one onboard
the waver you left.
I fear we're running out of
things to occupy ourselves with.
We had planned to lead all
of you to the end of Skypeia,
but it seems our
circumstances have changed.
[NAMI]
Hmm...
I guess the best thing to do
is get the ship to the coast
where we all agreed to meet.
There's really
no reason to worry.
I'm sure they're fine.
You know, when the four of
those goofballs get together,
there's practically
no stopping 'em.
[AISA] There aren't
any four-man groups.
[NAMI]
Huh?
At the most there's maybe two.
If there were a four-man
group on the island
I'd know about it, and I don't.
It's Mantra.
That's the power that Eneru
and his Priests use, huh?
I was born able to use it.
That's why...
That's why I'm so afraid.
You have no idea how scary
it is to hear voices disappear!
You're not crying
again, are you?
No, I'm not crying!
You stupid Blue Sea person!
Her waver had broken down.
Luckily our boat
happened to pass by.
If we hadn't gotten
to her when we did,
she would've been
eaten by a sky shark.
What were you thinking
coming out here by yourself?
I dunno.
But... I couldn't keep
sitting around doing nothing.
[AISA]
Laki, and everbody.
[distant crash]
[NAMI]
I hope everyone is all right.
[LUFFY's stomach growls]
Ugh! What a day.
This is crappy.
I'm starving and I left
my bag outside this stupid cave,
and all the fruit trees
around here are rotten.
And all I can think about
is eating that yummy
breakfast Sanji made.
What kind of messed up cave
did I wind up in anyway?
Can't seem to find
an exit anywhere.
[LUFFY] I wonder if
everybody's already made it
to the City of Gold.
I bet it's all pretty and
shiny and golden and stuff.
And they probably make all
kinds of good food there too.
I can't wait to
get there and find out.
[ZORO grunts]
Feels like I've been
walking forever.
I think I'll have
that lunch now.
This stuff ain't too shabby.
Who's there?
Aww.
Sorry, fella,
but I don't speak bird.
And if it's
my food you're after. Hey!
Aww.
You're not getting it!
Stop staring at me!
Would you stop following me?
Aww.
Listen feather brain,
I just ate all my food.
I don't have anymore, okay?
Besides I wouldn't give
you any even if I had some,
so get lost before
I lose my temper!
Aww.
What is your problem anyhow?
Walking all weird with
your big fat melon head
facing the wrong direction.
I don't want to have
to fight you bird, but I will.
Got it?
Aww.
[ENERU] In three hours,
a mere five of the 81 people
on this island will
be left standing.
[ENERU]
There's only one hour left
until my proclaimed time is up,
and 25 survivors
currently remain.
[SHANDORAN]
This can't be!
What's Eneru doing here?
[SHANDORAN]
He's going down!
Huh?
[ENERU]
And now, 24.
[YAMA laughs]
Well, it seems all your
talk doesn't amount to much.
Stomach Mountain!
[ROBIN]
A runic statue!
Veinte Fleurs! Calendula!
[YAMA] How long
are you going to insist
on protecting this withered,
good for nothing old city?
Indefinitely.
Why must you disrespect what our
ancestors had held so sacred?
[YAMA]
Huh?
The past has nothing to do
with me so why should I care?
That doesn't surprise me.
Only the foolish
say such things.
[YAMA growls]
How dare you insult
someone so powerful!
Super Punch Mountain!
[ROBIN] I've got to get
away from these ruins
before this simpleton
destroys what's left of them!
[ROBIN] Back then, I believed
my quest had been lost.
My dreams were buried
along with the underground
temple of Alabasta.
Having lost everything,
I chose to travel with Luffy.
But these ruins
could hold the clues
to an unspoken history that's
been lost to the world below!
[YAMA]
How long do you plan on running?
I don't understand it.
You've finally
decided to face me?
[ROBIN]
Yes.
It's too late for you.
[YAMA]
Huh? Too late?
Even if you choose to repent.
I won't forgive you.
Oh, you won't forgive me? I see.
All because of these
shabby old ruins you adore.
A pile of rubble that doesn't
even belong to you?
[ROBIN] That's right. Those
ruins don't belong to anyone.
I've grown tired of this,
and I'm tired of talking to you.
Well, not to worry.
In just a few short moments,
you won't have to
talk to me ever again
because unfortunately,
you're going to be crushed
to death underneath me!
Drop Mountain!
I can unleash all of
my power on you in this place!
Treinta Fleurs!
[ROBIN] All you do is charge
around like a clumsy bull.
With no regard for
the weight of the history
that you've destroyed!
Hang!
His body's too heavy.
I'll chop you to ribbons!
The Ten Axe Mountain!
My eyes! I can't see!
Ah! What are you doing?
Why did you turn the
dials around backwards?
You're gonna kill me!
What you have
carelessly destroyed
were priceless treasures.
Relics so rare it would
be next to impossible
to measure their actual worth.
It's true that history
may repeat itself,
but people can't
go back in time.
A stupid brute like you
wouldn't understand that.
I, uh... I... I understand.
Please. Please, I'm sorry.
Won't you forgive me?
That's out of the question.
Ah... Ah...
Well, in that case,
I'll have to kill
you then, won't I?
[screams]
My fingers! My fingers!
Cien Fleurs!
[ROBIN]
Delphinium!
[YAMA]
No! No!
Stop!
I'm afraid it's far
too late for that.
Can't... breathe.
[ROBIN]
Clutch!
That was certainly unpleasant.
[ROBIN] This should be
the center of the city.
But it doesn't match up at all
with the map on the monument.
I wonder if the entire
city was broken up
when it was thrust into the sky?
[COBRA]
I don't understand.
Then why did you come here?
I don't really know anymore.
Chasing a dream, I suppose.
An empty dream.
The last remaining
Poneglyph in the world
that still carries
the "true history."
[ROBIN]
The Rio Poneglyph.
What do you mean
by the "true history"?
Nothing.
It doesn't matter now.
For 20 years I've searched,
and I've never had
a better lead than this.
This was my last hope.
And it didn't work out.
So if I'm going to die here,
it's the perfect time.
I'm tired of this
fool's crusade.
It's over.
All I wanted, was to
learn our true history
and to share it
with the whole world.
[ROBIN]
It's so strange.
Could this really
be the City of Gold?
The size and the topography
are all completely different.
Hmm...
[ROBIN] And what's
most unnatural of all.
The only entrance is at the top!
[ROBIN]
Could it be?
I think I can go below.
[ROBIN]
It's so vast.
The ruins really
do go much deeper.
I thought it was bizarre
that all these Blue Sea Ruins
had Island Clouds for ground.
[ROBIN]
The ruins above are nothing more
than the upper
parts of the city,
eaten up by Island Clouds.
There's still more below.
[ROBIN]
Light!
It's all so incredible.
The ancient city collapsed
eight hundred years ago.
But I can hardly believe
it's been that long.
It's still so majestic
and grand.
I've actually found it.
This really is
the great Shandora.
The City of Gold!
[ROBIN]
It can't be!
So then you're saying,
that it's possible
our lost history
could actually be uncovered?
And the Poneglyphs are the
key to unlocking these records?
The ancient Poneglyph symbols.
So the Shandorians
were familiar with them.
But only the ones
who made the Poneglyphs
were able to read them.
We shall know the true meaning
and utter it to no one.
It's our legacy to be the
inheritors of history.
With the sounding
of the grand belfry.
That's right.
I remember Noland's
old logbook mentioning
a giant gold bell being here,
but if that's true,
where could it be?
All of the city's ancient
writings were burned in a fire.
[ROBIN] The entire history of
this place was eradicated.
They'll all manage
somehow, right?
They've come through
this kind of stuff before.
Quit following me!
Aww.
Sure goes down a long way.
[ROBIN] A Poneglyph
was carried into the city!
There's no question about it.
The city faced great hostility.
Shandora. The mystical
City of Gold.
Fought and fell to
protect that Poneglyph.
And that means,
the grand belfry located in
the center of the four altars.
It could contain the
text of the true history.
It could be, the Rio Poneglyph!
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[ZORO]
Hey!
Where are you taking me,
you stupid bird?
[LUFFY]
What's with this goofy cave?
And where's the exit?
[ZORO] Something really
ticked that snake off!
[NAMI screams] Why's this
crazy snake chasing us?
[ZORO] Hmm. All these
guys seem pretty tough.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"0% Survival Rate!
Chopper vs. Ohm,
the Sword Wielding Priest!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!