Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Wait!
You didn't press
that button, did you?
The silver transponder
snail has received a signal!
It's an emergency!
A Buster Call has been requested
under the authority
of Admiral Aokiji!
What's the location?
Enies Lobby!
Contact the five Vice Admirals
closest to that location!
All things considered,
it may be faster to reach
there from headquarters.
How long, then?
No more than
thirty minutes, sir.
In that case, prepare ten
battleships for departure
and inform the Vice Admirals
of the situation.
Make it quick!
Yes sir! A Buster Call
has been requested!
The destination is Enies Lobby!
Prepare ten battleships
for sail immediately!
Hello? Hello?
What is it, Chief?
Oh, now I get through.
This is the one
I was trying to use.
Not that it matters anymore.
There's no turning back now.
I pushed the button.
Of all things! I triggered
the Buster Call!
Everyone get off
the island! Hurry!
A Buster call has been
invoked on Enies Lobby!
If you don't get away
from here immediately,
you'll die!
Hey!
Don't tell them things
they don't need to know!
We're gonna get hit
with a Buster Call!
Battleships are coming!
Get away from Enies Lobby!
Hey, wait a second!
If that was Robin talking,
then where is she?
Right behind these
doors, of course.
As you seem to have surmised,
you'll have to go
through me first.
Outta my way.
I'm not gonna let you keep
me from Robin any longer.
Say what you like.
This is the end.
You'll never see her again.
I made a promise, and
I'm not gonna break it.
I'm coming for you, Robin!
"Five Namis? Nami Strikes
Back with Mirages!"
Hey. Get up.
I don't have time
for this. C'mon.
Don't you dare
give me that look!
Swallow your pride and
cancel the Buster Call!
Now, before it's too late!
Give it up!
You're still going
on about that crap?
As the Chief of CP9,
I have a reputation to uphold!
"Whoopsie, silly me!
I take it back!
Cancel the Buster Call!"
Oh yeah, that's gonna
go over real well!
I don't care how many
useless peons die out there.
All I know is one thing,
once I hand you
over to the World Government,
I'll get a nice,
pretty promotion!
That's all that matters, right?
You're a fool.
You've already lost.
Excuse me?
Luffy, and everyone else,
they're coming for me.
Rather optimistic,
wouldn't you say?
Even if I hadn't
made the Buster Call,
you'd still be finished!
Your little friend is
up against Rob Lucci.
Do you really think he can win,
against a CP9 Agent with
a power level of 4000?
In other words,
he can completely
crush what little
hope you have left.
So I don't care how
many friends you've got.
I don't even care
about the Buster Call.
The point is you're screwed
no matter what happens!
Do you understand?
I won't give up.
Robin!
It's a Buster Call!
The battleships are coming!
If we don't get moving,
they're gonna
burn us to a crisp!
Run away!
Look, it's all crooked!
Hey, where is everybody, anyway?
I was excited about showing
them the secret passage.
Sounds like they're
having a party over there.
Chimney, Gonbe!
There you are!
What're you up to?
Oh, hey Granny!
Guess what, guess what!
We found a weird
hole in the wall,
and then we took the pirate
guy there to check it out,
and then he blew a
hole through a door
and got super duper tiny!
He what?
But before that he
was all like kapow!
Kapow?
Right?
Wow, that's some story
you've got there!
Well, I can't say
I quite understand,
but either way it sounds like
things're getting pretty crazy!
Seems we've finally
reached the climax.
I'd better hurry.
If I stay here,
I could die as well.
If you're gonna run, then
leave the key here with me.
Shave! You must forgive me.
Alas, I fear the
game must end now.
Hey! Let me go!
At the very least, please
accept this parting gift.
Golden Bubbles!
Damn it.
It's the same thing
she did to Sanji.
I can't pick up the Clima Takt.
I'm too slippery.
I can't even stand up!
Look at this mess!
What did you do?
Well, I admit this
look doesn't exactly
do wonders for your curves,
but your skin is quite nice.
Although there is one catch.
Your already pathetic
strength has been cut in half.
I'd give up on the
key if I were you.
Yeah right. You wish!
Cool Charge!
Stop wasting
my time. It's no use.
Tempest Kick!
Huh?
I call it "Mirage Tempo".
I'm over here, by the way.
How dare you!
Don't toy with me!
Finger Pistol!
They're all fakes?
Where did you go?
I'm right here!
What is that?
She turned into a monster?
Huh?
So you have devil fruit
powers as well, do you?
What a ditz.
Hurry, before the
Buster Call starts!
You don't gotta tell me twice!
I'll make you face the wrath
of the mighty Nose Storm!
Tempest Kick!
Finger Pistol!
Good. Now keep it up.
Tempest Kick!
Not again!
Hey, no offense, but this
plan of yours is awful.
Let's call it quits before
I get dismembered, okay?
Hmph. No, wait.
Huh?
Look.
Our enemies are
afraid to attack.
They fear the wrath
of the Nose Storm.
Yeah? You think so? Alright!
That swordsman is more
ruthless than I imagined.
How cruel.
Turning his own
partner into a weapon.
Nah. He's just desperate.
They're trying to buy time.
Zoro, your trusty blade
is prepared at last.
My heart is tempered in steel!
Attack them without reservation.
I shall not falter! To victory!
That's more like it.
Mighty Nose Storm
Killer Attack Allure.
Allure? Oh!
That captures the beauty
of Nose Storm perfectly!
I admit, I am quite alluring!
Excellent work, Zoro.
Hm? Is he asking us to
come over there and kill him?
Wait, what're you--?
Don't mind if I do!
Not if I get there first!
Shave!
Damn it.
I can't believe I fell
for that stupid trick.
Now he's just using
his friend as bait!
So when you said
"allure" you meant
the kind that you
catch fish with?
I taste terrible!
What am I to you, huh?
Just bait? Not even
a sword, anymore?
One more time.
Killer Attack A Lure.
Have you no shame?
By the way, I think you've got
this whole "Killer Attack"
thing totally wrong.
The only one dying is me!
I see, so you have zoan-type
devil fruit powers, do you?
Are you dense?
I told you, that's not me!
But this isn't some
random monster, is it?
Those are reindeer antlers,
and I'd recognize
that hat anywhere!
But what happened?
Is that giant thing
really Chopper?
Even so, I've never
seen a beast like this!
Moon Walk!
Tempest Kick!
Stop it! Leave him alone!
Hey, Chopper!
It's you, isn't it?
What's going on?
Did you do this?
Maybe he just doesn't
recognize me now.
I must look strange.
You are Chopper, aren't you?
I was kidding, all right?
I didn't think you actually
turned into that thing!
Don't treat me like I'm a fool!
Chopper!
She ignored me! So rude!
Chopper! What's wrong with you?
It's me! Nami! Look!
Stop it!
Why are you doing this?
Oh no. Sanji's down there!
I don't know where
that awful thing
wandered in from,
but I'll make it pay.
Don't you lay a finger on him!
I won't let you hurt my friends!
What the heck happened to him?
This isn't good.
I need to find a
way to stop him.
That thing is your friend?
How amusing!
You pirates keep strange
company, don't you?
Chopper!
She ignored me again!
How rude can you get?
I'd love to have
you take care of
that monster for me,
but I've been given an
order to eliminate you.
And time is running short.
Tempest Kick!
Uh-oh. I don't think I can dodge
when my legs are
slippery like this!
Huh? I'm still okay?
One of my legs
is back to normal.
But why? Did I miss something?
It's wet.
It must've happened when
Chopper threw the bathtub.
Wait!
I get it!
All I have to do is wash
the soap off with water!
Let's not be hasty.
Even if you can
counter the effects
of my Golden Bubbles with
water, that doesn't mean
I'm going to stand by
and let you do it.
Sheep Cloud! Relaxing Bubbles!
No problem.
This is nothing a
little wind can't fix!
Now. Cyclone. Damn it!
Oh no. My strength is--
Supple Finger Pistol!
My Takt--
Whip!
That was helpful.
Helpful?
If you blow me away
with an attack like that,
then those annoying bubbles
of yours get blown away, too.
Aren't you tough!
Well, if you like,
I'll blow you away until
there's nothing left!
The forecast is cloudy!
Cloudy Tempo!
This sure beats
that magic show stuff
this thing used to do.
Clouds? Fighting
with lightning again?
These clouds aren't
for lightning.
They're way too thin for that.
This time, I have
something else in mind!
I see. Damn. I should've known!
The forecast is rain! Cool Ball!
Shave!
Pour down! Rain Tempo!
And I worked so hard.
How rude to wash
everything away.
If your idea of "nice"
is getting my ass beat,
then I'll pass.
Cool Charge!
Mirage Tempo!
She's gone!
I've watched your every move.
I know your strengths.
And I know all your
weaknesses, as well.
What's-- What's happening?
Mirage Tempo Fata Morgana.
What? Chopper!
Why the hell doesn't
he recognize us?
I've got no idea,
but that is Chopper!
Who else has antlers
and wears a hat like that?
Step aside, you guys!
Hey, hold it!
What do you think you're doing?
That deer monster
is on our side!
That's the last straw, Franky!
You're not going
to get away with this!
Nobody treats
my friends that way!
On the next One Piece:
"Nami's Decision!
Fire at the
Out-of-
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!