[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[NARRATOR]
In the land of oases,
a dry cloud of sand blankets
the people with anguish.
Some cling to hope, and
others seek to destroy it.
As their paths cross,
they mark an era in
the country's history
that will forever be
overshadowed by sadness.
Nami engaged in mortal combat
with Miss Doublefinger,
whose Spike Spike Fruit powers
quickly turned their brawl
into a losing battle.
That is, until Usopp's
invention, the Clima Takt,
gave Nami a fighting chance.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Crocodile
appeared at the palace
before Vivi and a
captive King Cobra.
He finally revealed the ultimate
goal behind his ambitions:
A mysterious object
known as the "Pluton."
[LUFFY] "Secret Passed Down
in The Royal Family!
The Ancient Weapon Pluton!"
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[VIVI]
What is he talking about?
Pluton? What is that?
I don't have a clue.
Pluton.
According to legend,
it can completely obliterate
an island with just one shot.
[CROCODILE] An ancient
weapon whose power rivals
that of a god.
It's somewhere in this country,
but you already knew that,
didn't you, Your Highness?
An ancient weapon?
Alabasta has such a thing?
And father knew about it?
Perhaps it is a secret
passed down with the throne.
Acquiring Pluton has
always been my goal.
With it, this peaceful country
will become a military power to
be reckoned with under my rule.
Your rule?
You're not this
country's monarch!
[CROCODILE]
Oh, but I soon will be.
And once I'm on the throne,
it will be easy to bring all
the pirates in this area
under my umbrella.
With such influence,
eventually I'll gain more power
than even the World
Government itself.
No one will dare cross me.
The World Government
would never allow you
to wield that much power!
[CROCODILE]
You're right, they wouldn't.
So where is the Pluton? Tell me.
I don't know where you heard
that name, Crocodile,
but I don't have
the slightest idea
as to where it could be found.
I'm not even certain
it ever existed,
let alone if it's hidden
in this country.
It could be a myth
for all I know.
What you say probably
isn't a complete lie.
I have considered that
possibility for a while now.
That Pluton may
have never existed.
There are those who
believe it's just a fable,
but I believe that it's real.
[ROYAL SOLDIERS yelling]
[CROCODILE]
What noisy insects.
[SOLDIER A]
I heard that King Cobra's
been crucified by
Crocodile up there!
[SOLDIER B]
We've got to save His Majesty!
[SOLDIER C] If we can break
through those doors,
we can save the king!
How? We can't do anything
because of those strange
hands coming out from them!
[SOLDIER B] It's impossible
unless we find a way
to stop those things!
[CROCODILE]
If my timing's correct,
the rebel army should break
through the defenses
and reach that square in
approximately 20 minutes,
where they'll clash
with the royal forces.
And then, in just half
an hour, at 4:30...
[CROCODILE] ...their battle will
be interrupted by a bomb
I've ordered to be
fired into the square.
[gasps]
Please don't! I'm begging you!
Oh, and it's no ordinary bomb,
but one so powerful it
will destroy everything
within a five kilometer radius.
If you do that, everyone‐‐!
[CROCODILE]
That's right.
No one from either
the royal army
or the rebel forces
will survive.
They'll be wiped out and
the battle will be over.
[grunts]
Aren't you happy? You should be.
After all, you're the one who
wanted them to stop so badly.
Since I'll be ruling
from this palace,
there's no need to blow it up
just to end their fight.
It's easier just blow
both armies up instead.
This land's worth
more than they are.
How can you be so
callous toward them?
What did these people ever do
to you to deserve this, huh?
They have lives and families!
Princess!
Who cares?
[VIVI] You don't have to
kill them, Crocodile!
[CHAKA]
Princess!
[CROCODILE]
Perhaps I'll change my mind
if the king answers
another question.
There's a Poneglyph in
this country, Your Majesty.
Where is it?
Poneglyph? What are
you talking about?
If you promise to spare them,
I'll tell you where it is.
[chuckles]
I'll... even show you.
Father.
[CROCODILE laughs]
Just what I'd expect from
a king. You're a wise man.
[CHAKA]
Enough.
I cannot take...
another second of this!
[NAMI]
No!
[USOPP] Listen, Nami,
the Clima Takt is a weapon,
but you have to rely on
a stronger one to use it:
Your brain!
You gotta think to
survive a battle!
Remember: Your mind
is the real weapon.
[NAMI]
Right! Think!
Let's see, I've got Heat
Balls and Cool Balls!
All I need to do
is take advantage
of their characteristics
and combine them!
[USOPP]
One last thing.
Tornado Tempo!
This is the centerpiece
of the whole weapon!
Tornado Tempo?
Okay, here's the deal:
As long as your enemy is human,
they won't be able to stand
after being struck by it.
But it's a last resort,
and you only get one shot.
If you miss, it's over.
If I miss, it's over.
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Pay attention.
[yelps]
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER] That little
gadget of yours is interesting,
but it's not a weapon.
Here's some advice, sweetie:
If you can't use it to attack,
it's nothing more than a toy.
The day that thing can
be called a weapon
is the day you can finally
hurt someone with it.
Now...
Stop running.
If I don't do something quick,
I'm gonna get skewered!
The only chance I've got is
that Tornado Tempo thing!
If I can do it!
[chuckles]
Hey! Give that back!
Did you seriously think you
could kill me with this toy?
[chuckles] Oh, please.
A sweater can produce
more electricity
than this little thing.
Well, we won't know unless
I try, so give it back to me!
[NAMI yells]
[NAMI]
Come on, think!
I have to distract her somehow
so she can't dodge
the Tornado Tempo!
What do I have to work with?
Uhh...
There are the three different
types of air bubbles,
and the extremely dry weather of
this country, but that's all!
If only there was just a little
more moisture in the air.
Wait! Moisture!
That's it! This thing
has a rain technique!
Rain Tempo!
Water tricks?
[NAMI]
Rotating Sprinkler!
Desperate.
No, I'm not! I've got
a plan, you'll see!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
I don't think so.
I've had enough of
your party tricks.
And speaking of parties,
time to end this one.
Uh‐oh!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Sea Urchin Stinger!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER yells]
Now why don't you be a good
little girl for me and die?
[gasps]
If that'd been me instead
of the wall, oh, man!
Since you showed me something
interesting earlier,
it's only fair that
I return the favor.
[NAMI]
Now's my chance!
[chuckles]
[NAMI] Hot air rises while
absorbing moisture.
When it collides with cold
air that's descending,
it rapidly cools, and the
moisture gets frozen.
And then...
Now Spike‐Spike... Doping!
[yells]
[gasps]
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER] I told you
your life was over, didn't I?
Stinger Flail!
[screams]
[USOPP groans]
[USOPP] These wounds
are nothing, Chopper.
Just point me in the
direction of the battle.
Nothing can stop Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea.
I'll keep fighting even if
my arms get ripped off
or my nose gets broken
If you keep talking so much,
you're gonna cause
internal bleeding.
I'll shut up then.
[SANJI]
Huh.
Well, well. You're alive.
Huh?
Oh, man.
[USOPP, CHOPPER]
Sanji!
[CHOPPER]
You're hurt!
So, does this mean
that you beat up Mr. 2?
Better believe it!
Here.
My‐My goggles!
So you got 'em back for me
from that creep, huh?
Thank you, Sanji!
Oh, you're the best!
Wait a minute. They're broken!
In that case, I take back
everything I said!
Thanks for nothin', ya jerk!
And they were the
latest models too!
Do you have any idea what I had
to do to get these things?
[SANJI]
Hey, look at that.
[USOPP]
Look at my poor goggles.
[CHOPPER]
Whoa!
[SANJI]
That must be the auxiliary force
for the rebel army.
[CHOPPER]
There's more of them?
Looks like it.
I guess Vivi wasn't able to
stop the fighting in time.
This is just great!
[EYELASH grunts]
Eh? What the hell?
Hey! Eyelash! It's about
time you showed up!
Where've you been hiding?
Let's hurry to the palace.
Maybe there's still a way
we can help Vivi out.
Come on!
[CHOPPER]
Right!
[SANJI]
Usopp, move it!
[USOPP]
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Hey, Eyelash, gimme a lift!
Wait! Stop! Don'tcha
see the bandages?
Help an injured
man out, would ya?
At least you've proven that
you're a first‐class expert
at something, even if
it is running away.
[gasps]
[NAMI]
Oh, right! The air bubbles!
[gasps]
[NAMI]
A cloud!
It's small, but it formed!
Just what are you
babbling about?
It's still not large
enough, though!
I've gotta make it bigger!
Cool Ball!
Heat Ball!
I've had about enough of this!
Time to die!
Stinger Flail!
Tell me. Are you
prepared to die?
How 'bout you?
You're just bluffing, girl.
Am I?
[screaming]
[growls]
You're dead meat!
[gasps]
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER yells]
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
What?
[NAMI] Today's forecast
calls for pleasant weather
with stable humidity
and mild winds.
However, a high‐pressure
system will be moving in
sometime during the afternoon.
This could create
some strange weather
in one particular area,
so people in the vicinity need
to watch out for mirages.
And more importantly,
for tornados.
This is a centerpiece
of the whole weapon.
But it's a last resort,
and you only get one shot.
If you miss, it's over.
[NAMI]
If I miss, it's over.
A tornado watch has been issued!
[NAMI]
I'll make it work. I have to!
Vivi's been there for all of us,
so I'll be there for her!
[VIVI]
Nami, please. Don't die.
Well, you can at least try
putting all of our lives
on the line together!
Aren't we friends, Vivi?!
[LUFFY]
There, now you see.
Now you understand.
[LUFFY]
I know how much you hate this.
You wanna get
Crocodile the most.
[NAMI]
Sometimes, it summons clouds!
Other times, it makes rain fall!
It can even produce wind!
But there's one more special
technique of the Clima Takt!
And I'm going to unleash
it for Vivi's sake!
[NAMI groans]
Something the matter?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Oh, dear, it looks like
that left leg of yours
is pretty injured.
So much so, in fact, that I
doubt you could run away.
Sea Urchin Stinger!
[screams]
This is... It's nothing!
It doesn't hurt at all!
Do you have any idea
what kind of pain
she's been going through?
Compared to Vivi....
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Huh?
[NAMI] It doesn't matter if I
lose a foot or a leg or two,
or even an arm....
I don't care!
[NAMI]
Now!
Take this! Tornado..
...Tempo!
[gasps]
Huh?
What? What? What? What? What?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
What have you done to me?
[screaming]
[yelling]
[gasps]
It worked! I did it!
Usopp! Vivi!
[ZORO]
Ya know...
That face of yours,
it sorta looks familiar.
And if I'm not mistaken,
you used to be one of the most
infamous bounty hunters
in the West Blue, didn't you?
Not to mention an
assassin, as well.
So what happened to you?
You went from top of the heap
to one of Crocodile's dogs.
Did you do it just to
get some nice scraps
by lickin' his hand like
a good little lapdog?
Shut up.
[ZORO]
Here, let me show you...
...the difference
in pride between...
[ZORO]
...your swords and mine!
Three‐Swords Style...
...Bull Needle!
Spider...
...Defense.
[yells]
[ZORO]
Huh.
So basically, your body
is as hard as steel.
Unless I can cut steel,
I can't defeat you.
[MR. 1]
That would be correct.
Smashing and cutting
attacks won't work on me.
Well, that bites, doesn't it?
I'm not capable of
cutting steel yet,
so I guess there's only
one thing left to do.
[MR. 1] Hmph. And what's
that, swordsman?
[ZORO] I'm gonna learn how
to cut it right here and now.
Really?
[ZORO] I've been waiting for a
challenge just like this one.
I've been telling myself
for a while now
that it's time to take my
skills to the next level.
When I defeat you, Mr. 1,
I'll be the swordsman
strong enough
to cut through anything,
including steel.
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[ZORO] I swore on that day
I'd never lose again.
But the wall in front of me
now may be too large
for me to break through.
[MR. 1]
When you can't even scratch me,
there's only one way this
battle will end for you.
And that's with your death.
[ZORO] What the hell do
I lack to beat this guy?
What is it?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Secret of Powerful Swordplay!
Ability to Cut Steel and
the Rhythm Things Have!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!