Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Bastard... you
taking this seriously?
Of course! I'm
quite impressed...!
But you said you were
in a hurry... didn't you?
My new power should
speed things up for you.
What's going on?!
Damn...! I was trying to
use my man-beast form,
but I messed up on the man part!
There's a talking giraffe
falling through the ceiling!
Your... power is so
awesome... I love it!
A wolf...?! What the...
Is this place some kinda zoo?!
You're going to pay for this!
You're all going to pay!
I'll show you the power
of my devil fruit...
Then you'll be sorry!
Tempest Kick...
Oh boy...he's mad now!
Sky Slicer!
This isn't good.
Usopp, get down!
"I Won't Kick, Even
If It Costs Me My Life!
Sanji's Chivalry!"
I see...
That long neck has
improved your reach.
The centrifugal force coming
from a body that size
makes for a very fast...
and very deadly attack.
W-wait a sec.
It doesn't look like
he cut anything to me.
Try taking a
look at the ceiling.
Huh...? The ceiling...?
All I can see is the sky.
The sky...?
But that must mean...
He... he just cut the Tower
of Law in half, didn't he?!
It's slidingggg!
Hmph... You should be ashamed...
A professional doesn't let his
emotions get the better of him.
I don't want to
hear it anymore...
For the last time, giraffes
are awesome... I love giraffes.
Fine... whatever you say, man.
Humph... You can show off
all you want-doesn't
matter to me...
I came here expecting a fight...
your powers don't
scare me one bit.
H-hey! Cut it out,
Zoro! That hurts!
What're you doing...?!
Why are you pulling
my arm like that?!
Wait... My arm...
Whoa... that's not coming off.
Nope. Don't think so.
What the hell did you do?!
I swear, this is not my fault!
If you hadn't tackled
me back there,
this never would've happened!
You were about to
get your head lopped off
and you're blaming
this on me...?!
You trying to get us
both killed, or what?
If you don't get me
out of these things,
I'm using you as a shield
the next time he attacks...
Now they're completely
ignoring us...
What happened?
Fix this mess...!
You fix it!
It's your fault!
Okay, okay let's
think about this...
In short... we're in the same
situation as Robin, right?
Right?
Then, to get the key...
We're gonna have to
fight them and take it...
So nothing has changed, really.
Being handcuffed to someone
is just business
as usual, then?!
Damn, I guess
they're stuck together.
Fine... Then it's settled...
I'll put those two idiots
out of their misery...
You stand over here and watch.
What...?! Screw you...!
I'm not letting you steal
my prey, you bastard!
Our only other option
is working together
and I know you don't want that.
Oh, hell no.
That's how I feel.
Hey! You guys!
Can you check the
number on those handcuffs?
Number?
Each pair of
handcuffs and each key
is marked with a
matching number...
Otherwise, we wouldn't know
which key we'd need
to use to unlock them.
At any rate, if either
of us have the key
to those handcuffs we'll unlock
them for you.
Oh! Okay, thanks...!
Let's see, where is it...
Here! It's number 2! Unlock us!
Nope, not mine.
It's not mine, either...
That's a shame.
Damn it! Then don't get
our hopes up like that!
Even if we ran away,
it's not like
we could fight the rest
of CP9 in this state.
That settles it, then...
Guess it's
first-come-first kill.
That's only fair, I suppose.
Crap!
That's weird...
what happened...?!
The stairs are all split up!
I should've known...
It must've been that
big rumble I felt earlier...
Whoever's fighting
sure must be tough!
Hey, are you guys okay in there?
Zoro...! Sniper King!
Hey! Chopper!
Huh...? What's going on?
They've waving at me...
Maybe it's a game?
Yay!
Handcuffs!
We're stuck together, stupid!
If you can't find
key number two,
they're gonna murder us!
Oh... okay.
What the hell is this...?
I kinda figured there'd be
a bridge here or something.
Man, those whirlpools
are really huge...!
I can see the Gates
of Justice from here...
but I don't know if
I can get there on a boat.
I don't have time to
stand here and think...
I gotta give it a shot at least!
Here goes nothing!
I'm on my way, Robin!
Whee...! Yay!
I found a secret way
to get to the gates...!
I'm gonna tell the pirates
and then they'll save the day!
Huh? What's this...?
That's awful fishy...
Could it be...?
Click.
What's going on?!
All right! We found
another secret passage!
Pow...! Where are we now?
Whoa...! Are you okay,
Pirate Guy?
You're not looking so good!
I get it... So the keys
and the handcuffs
have matching numbers on them.
If you can't fight, then that's
okay-I didn't find anyone,
so I can just beat
these guys for you.
Sorry, but there's no way
in hell that's gonna happen-
and besides, if you get taken
out, we'll still be stuck
in these handcuffs
with no way to fight.
Please! We're counting on you!
You're our only hope!
Only hope...?
Flattery doesn't work on
me at all, you big dummies!
Between Sanji, Nami and Franky,
someone has to have the #2 key.
Get it, and bring it here.
Hurry, okay?!
Hmm... If anyone
has a key already...
it's probably Sanji.
I've gotta find him...
I'm their only hope!
Yooooo...! I've... caught...
you... now... girl!
Let go...
Yoyoi...! You... are...
far... too... weak!
Now perish!
I'm no match for him at all!
Franky...
Iron Body!
Boxing!
Shave!
Why are your
punches so strong...?
Wait -You're not human, are you?
It's cute how you CP9 guys
can make your
bodies hard like iron...
but these fists of mine are
the genuine article, brother.
What am I doing...?!
This is no time for me
to be drinking tea!
Witchcraft...! You put
me under a spell...!
One more sip and
I'd be finished...!
Damn it! I almost got
captured in your love trap!
So you say, after three cups.
Shut up, you witch!
Don't you dare play
innocent with me!
I haven't forgotten what
happened on the Sea Train...
I won't forgive the way
you people treated Robin!
Now... Give me your key.
What a shame...
It seems you're in a hurry.
Well, I won't keep you...
If you want the
key then take it.
So where is it?
Who knows...?
You'll have to search my body...
And find out for yourself.
Think you're up to it?
You bet I am!
You are off to a bad start.
Damn... that was stupid...
Might I remind you...
Even as we speak...
your friend Nico Robin
is drawing closer
to the Gates of Justice.
Although in her case
"closer to hell" is
probably a more accurate
way of putting it.
Yeah, fine, I get it already-I'm
screwing around in here,
while Robin's life
is on the line.
But I'm warning you,
I won't make the
same mistake twice.
I don't care if
you're a woman...
If you don't give me that key,
you're gonna get hurt.
We've gone from sweet talk
to petty threats, have we?
Do you think I care if you treat
me like a woman or not...?
I'm an assassin...
A professional.
Keep your chivalry.
I've been ordered
to take your life
and that's exactly what I'll do.
Take my life, huh...?
'Fraid that's not gonna work.
'Cause I'm not leaving here
without the key to
those handcuffs.
I suppose tea
time is over, then.
Shave!
You CP9 folks are every
bit as strong as you say.
Got you!
Score one point for me.
You... How could you?!
Sorry, but... that's how you
score a point.
You're gonna...
pay for that one.
Moon Walk!
He's fast!
There. It's over--you're
pinned to the ground...
I beat you fair and square...
now give me the key!
Finger Pistol!
Tempest Kick!
What a sad little man...
You call yourself a pirate...?
You're afraid to even touch me.
Hey... you shut up...!
Give me the damn key!
I've had enough of your
empty threats, you coward.
I'm growing bored,
so let's try something new...
If you can't withstand this
attack... you won't survive.
He's not coming after me...
I was lucky enough
to get away once.
I'd be dead for
sure, next time...
I need to find the others...
before he finds me.
Life Return!
Yoyoi! Yoi! Yoi! Yoyoi!
Damn...
Let's... see...
what... comes next...?
Shall I pierce thee to death...
or choke thee to death?
A fragile life... a wintry wind.
Now... before spring can come...
a flower succumbs...
to the cold.
But in its end...
let it bloom in red...
if only for an instant...
This is my compassion...
as the petals
gently fall...! Yooooo!
A final request...
When you reach the other side...
I ask that you deliver a message
to my poor, deceased mother.
Let her know that I am well...
and that my killer's
instinct is as strong as ever!
Now die... Die! Die! Die!
No!
Song of Spring Feelings!
Cloven... Roseo!
Nami! Are you okay?!
I'm fine...
Thank you for saving me.
Did he eat a Devil Fruit...?
What's up with his hair?
I don't know--it's like he's
got an octopus on his head.
Once he grabs you,
you're done for.
Come on... this is our
chance to get away...
The less we see of
that guy, the better.
Hey, wait... but how are
we supposed to get the key?
Oh, this little thing?
Stealing the key
was the easy part,
I just couldn't deal
with that hair of his...!
Anyway, have you
seen the others?
Before I get to that,
could you tell me
what number your key is?
It has a number? Oh, it's three.
Wrong one.
You're gonna have
to explain this to me.
This place is falling apart!
Wait... what? Is that a doll?
No... It's Sanji...!
What the heck happened to him?
Sanji! Can you hear me...?
What's going on?
Who did this to you?
Are you all right?
Say something!
Sanji!
I'm sorry... I lost...
I couldn't... get the key.
Hold on, okay...?
I'll see what I can do.
Sanji lost?
I can't believe it...
Hey, Sanji... You
really couldn't win...?
You really gave it your all?
You fought that blonde
woman, didn't you...?
I see... You must've
gone easy on her.
I'm sorry I couldn't
get the key.
Forget the key...!
This fight is a matter
of life and death!
You can't stick to your
stupid code of honor, okay?
Is chivalry really
worth dying for?
People are counting on you!
I don't want this...
I don't want to die...
But I was raised to
never hit a lady...
no matter what...
So even at a time like this...
Even if it kills me...
I won't... kick... a woman...
I see... That's stupid!
He was coughing up blood,
Nami--don't hit him!
Is running away against
your code of honor, too...?
Because that's not worth
dying over either...!
Nobody wants to see you
throw your life away in vain.
Leave that woman to me...
You try to get better.
And by the way...
Even if it's dumb, I like
that chivalry of yours.
What...? Did...
she say she loved me?
Not even close!
For the record...
I won't play nice.
Neither will I...
We'll get along fine.
Hey! You wanna save Nico Robin?
Get me some cola!
I still haven't forgiven you!
I don't need
forgiveness, brother...
I need cola! Now hop to it!
What kind of idiot
uses cola to power up?!
The kind of idiot that kicks
a lot of ass, okay? Just watch!
On the next One Piece:
"Fukurou's Miscalculation!
My Cola is the Water of Life."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!