She was willing to
sacrifice the lives
of everyone in this
world, even her own.
As long as she could
save the six of you.
Robin, wait!
We're coming for you, Robin!
Please, don't go!
I don't care who you're up
against. We'll help you!
Wait!
Robin!
Looks like we were too late.
Ow!
Seriously!
What was that guy
trying to pull, anyway?
Whatever the case,
it really doesn't matter.
That was a Government train.
He'll be captured, and
that will be the end of it.
Hey, isn't he with Galley-La?
Hey, Paulie!
Try to act
professional, will ya?
It looks like there's something
going on between them.
This is a train station!
People say hello and
goodbye here every day!
It's our responsibility
as employees here
to silently oversee
things like this.
Yeah, you're right!
Keep quiet!
Got it?
Quiet. Got it.
Train left a little early, huh?
Uh, yes! That's right!
All of the passengers
were already on board,
so they decided to--
The weather's getting
rougher by the minute, too.
At this rate, Aqua Laguna
could hit at any moment!
With all of these factors
in mind, it was decided
that the departure time
should be pushed forward!
It's not safe here right now.
You should take shelter
on the Shipbuilding Island
as soon as possible.
That goes for the
young lady, as well.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey listen, the train's gone.
There's nothing we
can do to stop it.
I hate to say it,
but Enies Lobby isn't the
kind of place where--
Are you crying?
Hey, look I-I understand
how you must feel, but--
After them!
She's pissed!
I'll never forgive those
World Government idiots!
Listen, I need a ship!
What in the hell are
you talking about?
The strongest and
fastest you've got!
You wanna set sail in
the middle of all this?
Don't be an idiot!
Do you have any idea how
dangerous this storm is?
Lay off!
I can handle it!
Look, this isn't some
regular run-of-the-mill storm
we're talking about!
It's about to be hell
at sea around here!
It's impossible to sail out now!
Doing so is nothing
short of a death wish!
Listen to me!
Robin is throwing her life away
for our sake and I'm not gonna--
That was close.
Thank you!
Yes, thank you!
You saved us all!
If it wasn't for you,
we would've all been
swept out into the sea!
Look at that.
That huge fixture with the train
schedule on it was torn apart.
Nothing like that has ever
happened here before.
Not even with Aqua Laguna.
This thing's power
is unbelievable.
And the actual storm
isn't even here yet!
Aqua Laguna is
different this year.
These waves are coming in fast!
Hey, is that sea train that they
took Robin on in any danger?
It should be able to make
it out of this rough patch
before the actual
storm makes landfall.
Unless it takes a direct hit,
that train's capable of cutting
through these big waves.
Um, excuse me.
Are you Nami?
Huh?
Yes?
Someone left you a note
out in front of the station.
Must've been one
of your crewmates.
A note?
From who?
And how did you manage to
notice something so small?
It was right here.
Whoever it was
made it easy for us.
That dimwit!
So, what does it say?
Give me a second.
The first half is just
a hopeless love letter.
Did she say "love letter"?
It seems there's a love
triangle going on here.
No.
Considering the situation,
I'd say the other
man is most likely--
What are you staring at?
The important part starts here.
P.S. I saw Robin get on
the 11 o'clock train.
I'm gonna hop on
board and follow her.
Sanji got on board that train?
Usopp's there, too?
"And some arrogant thug with
a ducktail." Who's that?
That must be Franky.
Yeah, must be.
She mentioned another man!
And it sounds like Franky, of
all people, must be the fifth!
Poor Paulie doesn't
stand a chance.
Maybe it'd be better if
he just threw in the towel.
What in the hell
is with you guys?!
Oh, and there's something else.
This was left on the
ground alongside that letter.
There should be at least
one transponder snail
somewhere on that sea train.
I'll contact you
as soon as I can.
Keep this portable one close
to you at all times, my darling.
Just pretend it's me
and hold it lovingly against
your soft, beautiful--
I get it.
He left this one to
communicate with us.
Wow.
He must have anticipated
Nico Robin's movements.
Pretty impressive!
I'll say!
At least for the time being,
Robin has Sanji with her.
The rest of us will
just have to catch up
with them at Enies Lobby.
Man, can't even manage to light
up a single smoke out here.
Really?
So after that, Sanji
went to the train station?
Yep!
And Usopp's on
the train with him!
Thank goodness!
At any rate, no matter how
we're going to follow them,
we can't do anything until
we find Luffy and Zoro first!
Understand?
Right!
I got it Nami.
I'm a hundred percent certain
about which way they flew
so head in that direction
and start looking!
You guys help look, too!
Let's do this!
Are you with me?
Yeah!
We won't let you down!
Now, what would be the best way
for one to sneak
inside this thing?
Whoa!
This storm is insane!
Collier Shoot!
Who in the hell are you?
Hey, hold it!
Where do you think you're going?
Don't move!
Whoa, did you see that kick?
He's not some
run-of-the-mill civilian!
Come on, now.
If you keep saying
things like that...
...I'll blush.
It wasn't a compliment!
He's making fun of us!
Hey!
Go let Rob Lucci know
that we've got a suspicious
intruder on board!
Wait a minute!
This insignificant little
matter isn't something
we need to bother CP9 with.
No matter how violent
or unruly this man is,
it won't do him any good.
Because, in this car, you've
got... Whoa, it's smoky!
In this car, you've got me!
Jerry!
That's right.
You're looking at the champion
on a South Blue island
renowned for its martial arts.
The undefeated Boxing Champion!
I prefer karate.
If you can handle my punches
then maybe I'll show you some!
Easy!
No need to overdo it!
Jerry Aurura Flicker!
Hey, Jerry!
Your target's behind you!
You're a sneaky one!
Now, listen!
Don't think you have me
at a disadvantage just
because I'm so very tall and
this train car is so very tiny!
This is the first time
I've ever talked to someone
whose head is where
their crotch should be.
My boxing technique
is more effective
in tight places like this!
Prepare for annihilation!
Go, Yoga Style!
One-two!
You just shortened your reach!
That's what you think!
All part of the plan.
Screw!
Drop Kick!
That's totally against
every single rule of boxing!
This is a waste of time.
Brochette!
I'll start with the
seventh and last car.
All of the World Government
officials are there.
In order of increasing strength,
the fifth car is next.
That car holds 40 marines
and the man who leads them,
a Navy Headquarters Captain
and former knight named T-Bone.
Next, in the 4th car,
we have Wanze,
an accomplished martial artist
from Cipher Pol number 7
who also happens to be
the head steward on this trip.
Standing by in the 3rd car is
Nero, the newest member of CP9,
and a force to be reckoned with.
Anyway, though we
are escorting criminals,
with government personnel
as trained and powerful
as the ones I mentioned,
we needn't worry about
the possibility of a raid.
Our military might
is represented
throughout this train.
Straw Hat!
Zoro!
We're here to help!
Come out!
Where are you?!
Mister Foreman, it must be
hard for you to even move.
Maybe you should
take a little break.
Don't be stupid!
This is nothing!
Hurry up and find them!
Yes, sir!
Has anyone gone to
bring Iceberg up to speed?
Two men went to
give him a report!
Hey, where are you
going, Mr. Iceberg?
Sir?
Hey, Zoro!
Where are you?
Answer us, Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Zoro! Luffy!
Come on guys, answer me!
Where the heck are you?
What's that?
Food, you say?
Yes, that's right.
We need meat.
All the meat you can find!
And hurry!
We're running out of time!
How did we end up being a couple
of errand boys for that girl?!
We're not doing this for her!
We're doing it for Paulie!
He's so devoted to
that crazy woman,
even after she dumped him!
We've gotta give this our all!
Yeah, you're right!
Keep going!
In any case, she
must be really hungry!
She's still a growing girl!
Right?
I guess!
It's no use.
None of the stores are open.
Everyone's evacuated.
Hey, wait a minute!
What about the kitchen
back at the train station?
No way!
Think about it!
The backstreets are
probably already flooded!
Then we've got no choice but
to keep looking around here!
But--
Let's get moving!
What do you think will happen
if we show up empty handed?!
Rain.
This is bad.
The strong winds are
already interfering
with my sense of smell.
Man, I'm beat.
It feels like we've been
calling for hours,
but there's still no answer.
You think that maybe they're--
Don't be ridiculous!
Just keep trying!
Luffy, Zoro!
Where in the world are you?
There's no way that
leopard guy took you out.
We finally know
why Robin left us
and we need to do
something about it!
Straw Hat, where are you?!
Answer us!
Please!
Hang in there, Robin.
Luffy and the rest of us
are coming to save
you no matter what!
What's going on here?
Oh! Paulie!
Quick, come see for yourself!
The more the tide recedes,
the bigger the
returning waves will be.
If you pay attention
to the ebb of the tide,
you can measure the
magnitude of the storm surge.
I'm flying!
Meow!
And, if you
consider how much lower
the water level's
going to be this year.
Hey, Chimney!
Take a look!
Whoa!
Amazing!
Meow! Meow! Meow!
It's almost as if
the sea has dried up.
I haven't seen anything
like this in my entire life.
The power of the
sea is astonishing.
No way.
How can the tide be so low?
I've never seen
anything like it!
Just how big of a wave
is coming this time?
All of the backstreets are going
to be completely swallowed up!
I hope nobody's
still down there.
If there is,
they'll die instantly!
The roar of the ocean.
It's gone.
Look-ee, look-ee,
look-ee, look-ee, look-ee!
Meow, meow, meow!
Hey, Granny!
Take a look over there!
I see something!
You do, do you?
Yeah!
There's something
between those two buildings!
Come on, Granny!
Look! Look!
Kokoro!
Oh!
If it isn't the pirate girl!
Hey!
Miss Pirate Lady!
Look!
Look over there!
I see something!
Like what?
Just what are you going
on about, Chimney?
No way!
What happened to the sea?
It's dried up!
Luffy!
That straw hat.
Isn't that your "King
of the Pirates" captain?
Well?
That idiot!
Hey, hold on!
Where do you think you're going?
Don't go down
to the back streets!
It's dangerous!
"To the backstreets"?
Hey! Wait!
Somebody stop that woman!
Are you trying
to kill yourself?!
Aqua Laguna is gonna hit
at any moment! Come back!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
Oh!
Hey, Nami!
I kind of got stuck here when
that leopard guy sent me flying.
Listen!
Robin was lying to us!
She was?
About what?
She's sacrificing herself
in order to protect us!
Then let's get going!
We gotta protect her!
On the next One Piece:
"Nami's Soul Cries Out!
Straw Hat Luffy
Makes A Comeback!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!