[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[NARRATOR]
Luffy and his crew have managed
to avoid the White
Beret's demands,
but Eneru's Super
Express Lobster
dragged away the Going Merry
with Nami, Zoro, Robin
and Chopper aboard.
So you're saying, if we want
our friends and ship back,
we have to walk right up
to their front door
and march on it.
This is part of the
challenge you mention?
Part of Heaven's Judgment?
Yes.
In Upper Yard, there are
four powerful Priests
of unimaginable strength
who await you.
[LUFFY] Hmm. Sounds
like a piece of cake.
I mean, all we have to do
to get our friends back
is beat up these priests, right?
You make it sound easy.
[laughing]
Finally! A little action.
[LUFFY] "A Trap on Lovely
Street! The Almighty Eneru!"
[USOPP]
Hey! Luffy!
[SANJI]
Wait up a minute, will ya?
[LUFFY]
Yeah? What is it?
[SANJI]
What's the big idea?
Why'd you just up and
leave all of a sudden?
You heard Nami.
If we stay we'll just cause more
trouble for Conis and her dad.
[SANJI] All right, so where
are we goin' then?
Where do you think?
The sacrificial altar.
[SANJI] And how are you
planning to get there?
[LUFFY]
Hm.
[SANJI]
You have to think about it?!
There you go.
We can just swipe one of
those boats out there
and head up the Milky Road.
Easy.
[SANJI]
Easy, huh?
Do you see any boats out there?
[LUFFY]
Um.
[SANJI]
Oh, just stop trying to think!
A boat wouldn't do us
much good, anyway.
Not if all we have to
go on is this old map.
I can't even tell where
we are on this thing.
And look, the Milky Road
isn't even on here at all.
Man, what a pain in the butt.
[SANJI]
Uh. Hm?
[CONIS]
Excuse me.
[SANJI]
Conis, sweetheart!
You came all this way to give
me a goodbye kiss, huh?
Well, actually, I'm here
because of my father.
He asked me to help
you find your way
to the sacrificial altar.
Aw! That's sweet!
[CONIS] I can accompany you as
far as the Angel Island docks.
We should be able to find
you a suitable boat there.
You got a definite plan.
Unlike a certain little
scatterbrain I know.
Yeah, right?
I meant you!
[SANJI] You're gonna be
our escort, Conis? Great!
We'd be delighted to
have you. Right, Luffy?
Of course we would!
Lead on, lady!
[CONIS]
Great!
[chuckles]
There's no way
I'll let you escape.
I'm going to send all
of you to Upper Yard
to receive Heaven's Judgment.
[SUU]
Suu-suu.
[LUFFY]
What's that?
[CONIS]
Oh, that's Lovely Street.
If you want a closer look,
you're in luck.
We actually have to pass
through it to reach the docks.
[MEMBER A] Captain, aren't they
already headed for Upper Yard?
[MEMBER B] Yeah, what're
we sneakin' around for?
[MCKINLEY]
Idiots!
You both know how these
Blue Sea people are.
They're all the same.
Oh, sure, they talk about
excitement and adventure,
but when they actually
face danger,
they cry and run
for their lives.
Exciting, huh?
Upper Yard here we come!
You realize there's a chance
you'll all be killed up there.
Well, everyone's
gotta go sometime.
So you're not worried at all?
Are you serious?
Why would I be worried?
[SANJI, USOPP shouting]
'Kay, I'm sorry.
[LUFFY]
Wow! This place is great!
[CONIS] Lovely Street is
the center of commerce
on the Island.
It has everything.
[LUFFY laughs]
Check it out! Floating stores!
[CONIS] It takes a special
variety of island cloud
to build those.
[LUFFY] So where's all the
floating restaurants?
[ISLANDER I]
It's them.
[ISLANDERS murmuring]
Hey, guys. I notice everyone's
avoiding us. Again.
[SANJI]
Can't say I blame 'em.
Word's probably already gotten
out that we're criminals.
So what else is new?
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
Ah, let 'em be that way!
That means we've got
downtown all to ourselves!
All these gorgeous angels
and they're avoiding me.
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Huh.
Sure is a lot of weird
stuff for sale here.
[gasps]
[LUFFY] Aw, man. Too bad
I don't have any money.
Hey, mister, do you
take treasure?
[screaming]
[LUFFY]
Ooh!
This must be a Dial shop!
Wow, these Breath
Dials are huge!
I should put a couple
on the Going Merry--
we'd be as fast as a waver!
[LUFFY chuckles]
[screaming]
Hey, Luffy, when you're
done foolin' around,
there's still the matter of
rescuing Nami and the others.
If you don't get
serious, and soon,
they're gonna be sacrificed,
do you know that?
[LUFFY] You worry too much!
They're fine!
Don't forget, Zoro's with them!
Yeah, like we can really
count on that guy!
I just hope the ship hasn't
sustained any more damage.
I mean, she's had more than
her share of abuse lately.
[LUFFY] Huh. There's something
in the middle of the street!
[CONIS]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
What a weird face!
What's it supposed
to be? A seal?
[SANJI] Looks like a figure
made outta mud.
Knowing this place, I bet it's
some kinda religious statue.
[USOPP]
Oh, you're both morons.
This is art! I can tell!
[CONIS]
This is "vearth."
You might say it represents
the eternal yearnings of
the people of the sky.
Vearth, huh?
Really?
So what, you guys like,
pray to this thing?
That's pretty crazy.
[CONIS giggles]
[CONIS] Well, I guess it would
be difficult for someone
from the Blue Sea to understand.
Oh! We're almost to
the docks! Right this way!
Aw! We're leavin' town already?
[USOPP]
Already?
We were never planning
on stopping here
in the first place!
[LUFFY]
I know, but I don't see why
we couldn't stick around
a little bit longer.
[ISLANDER L]
Phew! Looks like it worked.
[ISLANDER M] Yeah, they're
headed straight for the docks.
[ISLANDER N]
We're saved!
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Look at all these boats!
Yes, you'll notice
there are boats
of all shapes and sizes
anchored in this harbor.
From luxurious hotel ships
where you can spend the night
to sleeker models that
are made for speed
and loaded up with giant dials.
If you look over here,
there are even more types.
Whoa!
That one! It's perfect!
[LUFFY] I always wanted a
gondola! We'll take it!
Ooh! Look back there!
I bet those dials make this baby
move quicker than lightning!
This is gonna be
a whole lotta fun!
Come on! Let's go for a spin!
[SANJI]
You idiot.
We've got to rescue the
crew first, remember?
Get serious, will ya?
[CONIS] Actually, your boat
is right over here.
[SANJI]
Great!
[LUFFY]
Ooh! Ha!
Is it even awesomer
than the gondola?
Oh, man, I can't wait to see it.
Presenting: The Crow!
Ah! You're kidding me, right?
[SANJI]
Wait, uh, crows don't even swim.
[CONIS] I only learned
to ride a waver recently.
Before then, I used the
Crow to get around.
It's not as fast as
a waver of course,
but it has two Breath Dials,
and is quite reliable.
Please, feel free to use it.
Wait. I'm not going.
[gasps]
[MCKINLEY]
Aha!
I knew he'd finally
show his true colors.
No one in their right mind
doesn't value their own life!
Oh!
Unless I can take that.
He's not scared; he's selfish.
That one, huh?
You don't like the Crow?
I'm sorry.
The only thing sorry is this
guy! Apologize, you ingrate!
She goes to the trouble
of getting us a boat
and all you do is complain!
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry he doesn't appreciate
your help like I do, Conis.
I'm sorry.
[CONIS]
It's okay.
[USOPP]
Hm?
[CONIS]
Your exit is Gate Number Two.
It leads right to
the Milky Road,
and that will take you all
the way to Upper Yard.
Just... Just follow it
and you'll be fine.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Conis.
Yes?
You've been trembling
ever since we left.
Is everything okay?
Ugh. Can't hear.
What're they talkin' about?
[CONIS]
I-Is it that noticeable?
Yeah. It's like you're
scared or something.
No, wait. She wouldn't!
[SANJI laughs]
Don't you get it?
She's worried about us!
Oh, Conis, that is so
sweet of you, my dear!
[USOPP]
Speaking of being worried,
are you and Pagaya
gonna be all right?
I mean, everyone in town
is avoiding us like the plague,
but you're leading us around,
lending us your boat,
giving us directions.
Is helping us gonna
get you in trouble?
Doesn't that make you,
like, our accomplices?
Conis, don't cry.
You'll gonna be fine, 'kay?
You should've told us
you were scared.
Really. We could have just
come here on our own.
No, it's--
It's not--
[CONIS]
It's not what you think!
She wouldn't dare.
Don't say anything
you'll regret.
Don't you get it?
Even after I told you how
terrifying Upper Yard is,
I still led you here.
I even got you a boat and
told you which route to take.
Don't you find that odd?
Isn't it obvious
what's going on here?
[growls]
Watch your tongue, little girl!
Don't say anything foolish!
[USOPP]
Huh? You hear somethin'?
Huh?
[SANJI] Don't tell me
they're all in on this.
[CONIS]
But why? We shouldn't do this.
They're not like the others.
Besides, there's no need
for me to guide them.
They're already headed
for Upper Yard.
Conis, if that were truly so,
I would not have to burden
you with this task.
But we must face facts.
You've seen how other
Blue Sea dwellers act
when they come here, these three
are probably no different.
Once the initial
excitement wears off,
the reality of what
they're facing sets in.
They get scared and begin
to value their lives
over their dreams of adventure.
That's why we must lead them
to the Milky Road's end.
All the way to Upper Yard.
[PAGAYA]
Oh, Conis, please forgive me.
But it's every citizen's duty.
You know what will happen
if we don't follow
almighty Eneru's will.
[SANJI, USOPP gasp]
[CONIS]
Just run away. Please.
I'm so sorry, you guys!
No, no, stop!
What do you think you're doing?!
I called the Super
Express Lobster.
It was all my fault!
You mean that thing that took
Nami and the others away?
You called it, Conis?
[CONIS] While you three were
inside talking to my father,
I went aboard and lied to
your friends about a current
that leads to Cloud End.
They believed me.
And I had them raise anchor.
[CONIS] That was the signal that
summoned almighty Eneru's
Super Express Lobster.
[MCKINLEY]
What? Do you want to die?
You stupid girl!
[CONIS] Once we know
someone's a criminal,
we must lead them to Upper Yard!
If we don't, then
the penalty is death!
[ISLANDER S]
You idiot!
You're gonna bring his
wrath down upon us all!
[ISLANDER R]
This is outrageous!
[ISLANDER Q]
Somebody stop her!
[CONIS] It's our duty.
The duty of every citizen.
That's crazy!
[CONIS]
I know!
I-I'm sorry. I should've
told you sooner.
Wait a sec.
You're saying they forced
you to lead us all here?
If that's true...
[ALL] ...then why even
tell us at all?!
[LUFFY] Are you nuts?
Now your life is in danger!
[ISLANDER M]
It's all over!
[ISLANDER N]
We're too late!
[ISLANDER S]
Get away from the girl!
[ISLANDER J]
The judgment is coming!
[yelling]
It's too big!
[USOPP coughing]
[gasps] What in the
world was that thing?
It did that?
[USOPP]
Luffy!
[SANJI]
Conis! Where are you?
Conis!
Luffy! Conis!
Hah!
[ISLANDER W]
That's what happens to those
who defy almighty Eneru!
[GAN FALL] Do not fear.
They are both safe.
[PIERRE]
Pi-e!
It's him! Gan Fall!
[gasps]
Oh! The weird old man!
Me, "weird"? No.
I am the Sky Knight, friend.
And this one's on the house.
Conis! Look she's safe!
[GAN FALL] And she will
remain so under my watch.
You have my word. I shant
allow Eneru to harm her.
Thanks!
Now that you've seen the scope
of Eneru's power and anger,
what are you going to do next?
The same thing we were
gonna do from the start.
Go to Upper Yard and
rescue our friends.
I see. May luck be with you.
[PIERRE]
Pi-e!
[CONIS]
What about them?
[GAN FALL] They have chosen
their own course.
Do not blame yourself, child.
I-I know who you really are.
[GAN FALL]
Of course! It's no secret.
I am the Sky Knight.
No. We-We all know.
Please come back to us... God.
[USOPP]
Good luck, fellas!
Hop aboard. Get comfy.
I'll give you good shove off!
[SANJI]
Get on the boat!
[USOPP]
I don't wanna!
All right, Upper Yard,
here we come!
[USOPP crying]
[USOPP]
No!
They-They went.
Without any fear or hesitation!
[LUFFY laughing]
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[USOPP]
Will Conis be all right?
[SANJI] All we can do
is count on the old man!
We gotta save Nami
and Robin right now!
[USOPP]
And the other two!
[LUFFY]
Hey! What's that?
--[SANJI] Is this it?
--[USOPP screaming]
--Heaven's Judgment?
--Shut up!
--[USOPP screaming]
[LUFFY]
Just keep moving forward!
[USOPP]
Oh, I just wanna go home!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Onward, Crow!
To the Sacrificial Altar!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!