[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[NARRATOR] Luffy and his crew
have finally arrived in Skypiea.
However, following
a confrontation
with the local authorities,
Nami, Zoro, Robin, and Chopper
have been carried away to
face judgment in Upper Yard.
In pursuit of their friends,
Luffy and the others
must now face the dangers
of the forbidden land.
[USOPP screams]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Zoro and his group
have their own problems
at the sacrificial altar.
[ZORO]
I am so done with you!
And what about his priests,
you gonna beat them up, too?
Hello? The last thing we need
is you pissing off a God!
It's kinda not smart.
[ZORO]
By the time I'm done with him,
this "God" is gonna
bow before me.
[NARRATOR] Zoro, Nami, and Robin
have now made their way
into the forest, leaving
Chopper to repair the ship.
[CHOPPER]
Oh, no! Who's gonna protect me?!
[LUFFY] "10% Survival Rate!
Satori, the Mantra Master!"
Enough is enough.
Where is this "God"?
It may not matter.
If he really is a God,
chances are he knows
exactly where we are.
Well, if he would
just come to us,
I could get this
thing over with.
[NAMI] You say that because you
haven't seen the things I have.
There is someone or
something on this island
with the ability to destroy us.
O powerful one,
we're but simple sailors.
Please leave us in peace.
Oh!
And also, please help us find
lots and lots of treasure.
Nice prayer, Nami.
Look, you can sit on your
knees all day if you want,
but it's not gonna
get us outta here.
I say we cross the river and
see what's on the other side.
[ROBIN]
Yes, I agree.
[NAMI] And how do you plan
to get across this time?
I don't see any vines handy.
Hey, Zoro, maybe you could
throw Robin across and she--
[screams]
[ZORO]
Those things are everywhere!
[NAMI] If you think
I'm crossing that now,
you're outta your mind!
We may as well just hop in and
give the sharks a free snack.
Calm down, it'll be fine.
We'll just keep walkin' upstream
and hope we find a safe
place to cross over.
Give up! I'm not going!
If you wanna go so badly,
just leave me here.
[ZORO]
Ugh. I just might!
If you're so scared, why'd you
even come in the first place?
[BOTH growling]
Hey, guys. Look at this.
[NAMI]
Look at what, exactly?
It's dirt.
Yeah. Am I missing something?
Of course it's dirt.
This is a sky island.
You're right.
The ground's not fluffy.
Huh? Oh, right!
I almost forgot, I noticed
that the first time
I saw this island.
Sky islands are made of clouds.
It feels like it's been a year
since I've touched dirt.
So why's this island
different from the others?
Not sure, but the fact
that it is different
might be what makes
this place so special.
At any rate, it's reason
enough to start exploring.
Prepare for judgment, criminals.
You have no choice
but to receive it.
Select a gate.
Select from four ordeals.
For you, there can be
no turning back.
You may choose your own trial,
but we will decide your fate.
[GEDATZ]
Swamp!
[SHURA]
Iron!
[OHM]
String!
[SATORI]
Spheres!
[GEDATZ, SHURA, OHM, SATORI]
Choose your path, criminals!
So what do we do?
Um, let's go with spheres.
Why do you like that one?
[LUFFY]
Spheres are like balls, right?
Sounds fun.
That's your only reason?
They're ordeals, they're
not supposed to be fun!
Not that I'm
disagreeing with you.
Spheres is definitely the one
that doesn't sound too violent.
At least to me.
I mean, all swamp
makes me think is...
[USOPP] Help! I'm sinking!
Somebody help!
And I'm talkin' 'bout
the kind of "sinking"
you don't come back up from.
[LUFFY]
Okay, so what about iron?
[USOPP]
Ah! They're gonna smash us!
[screaming]
No thank you! Way too scary!
[LUFFY]
Fine! String, then.
[USOPP] This isn't so bad.
One hand in front of the other.
[screams]
[USOPP]
Where's the ground?
No way.
It sounds so harmless,
it's probably the worst!
Big ball! Incoming!
[USOPP]
Splat.
Come to think of it,
spheres doesn't sound
all that safe either.
Maybe we should
think this over.
[SANJI] We don't have time
for a debate here.
We're right on top of it.
[LUFFY]
All right, spheres it is!
Okay.
I guess we'll have to trust
Luffy's instincts on this one.
Then it's decided. Just don't
let your guard down, guys.
Remember, these
are God's Islands,
10,000 meters above sea level--
anything can happen.
Ready! Let's do this!
[chuckles]
Driver, would you mind
not shutting your eyes?
[USOPP] No. It's just as
dark with them open.
[LUFFY] Hey, guys, what if this
is like one of those games?
[USOPP]
Like a what?
[LUFFY] You know,
if you pick the right door
then you get a prize.
But if you pick the wrong one--
What are you talking about?
What if we picked wrong?
Why couldn't you have
mentioned this before, Luffy?
Well, let's see here. Um...
If you pick the wrong one...
then you fall off the island!
[USOPP] How can you say
something so stupid?!
We're thousands of
meters in the air!
I don't know how
many times your life
can flash before your eyes
during a fall like that,
and I don't wanna know!
[SANJI]
You guys are both being idiots.
Nothing like that's gonna--
[ALL screaming]
[USOPP]
You've gotta be kidding me!
[SANJI]
We're alive?
I seriously thought
we were falling
all the way back
to the Blue Sea.
[LUFFY laughing]
That's because somebody
had to make up
a lame story to scare us!
I was scared! I thought
I was a goner, too!
[LUFFY laughing]
All right, so what
is this place?
A forest. With balls.
[SANJI] They're balls
made of Island Cloud.
[LUFFY]
Ha! Awesome!
They look like really
big snowflakes.
Now what could be
scary about that?
See, Usopp? It's okay.
Heads up, the Milky Road is
leading us up into the trees.
I just don't see how this
is an ordeal. Do you?
[SANJI]
Not yet.
It'd be great if there
was nothing ahead,
but somehow I doubt it.
[LUFFY] What if it was
like one of those games,
and we picked the right door,
and now all we have
to do is float around
in this giant snow
looking for the others?
[USOPP]
Y-Y-Yeah! M-Maybe that's it!
You're still being idiots.
They think we're criminals,
I doubt they'll let
us off that easy.
Use your brains for once.
I wouldn't be surprised
if there were more traps
like the ones earlier.
We have to stay sharp.
[SANJI]
Let's just keep moving.
[LUFFY]
What, are you the captain now?
Can we at least have a snack?
[USOPP] Ooh! Yeah!
Whatcha got in your bag, Sanji?
[LUFFY]
Come on, gimme!
[SANJI]
No! No snacks!
[LUFFY] But, Sanji, we need
to keep our strength up!
[USOPP]
Just a little somethin'?
[SANJI]
I said no!
Now listen, it's really simple:
I'm going to keep steering,
you guys keep watch
out the sides.
[LUFFY, USOPP groan]
Whoa. I didn't realize how
high up we were getting!
[SANJI]
Something's not right.
It's too quiet.
There are four priests,
so I assumed each
tunnel would lead to one.
Why haven't we seen
any of them yet?
I got a bad feeling about this.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Usopp! Catch!
Okay, I got it,
I got it. Pass!
I thought I told you
to keep watch!
[USOPP, LUFFY groan]
[USOPP, LUFFY scream]
A snake!
Stupid... snake ball!
Okay, didn't see that coming.
Ah! Sanji! Cloud ball!
Kick it away!
I do not like the idea of
being surrounded by snake eggs.
[ALL]
This can't be good.
[USOPP] For cryin' out loud!
What's with these things?
[USOPP crying]
[SATORI laughs]
[SATORI] Silly children,
these are Surprise Clouds.
[SATORI] You never know what's
going to come out of them.
Hey? Where's that
voice coming from?
[SATORI]
Ha-ha! Heso!
Who--?
I'm so glad you picked
my challenge--
the Ordeal of Spheres!
[laughigng]
[SANJI] Yeah, is that
a talking dumpling?
[USOPP]
Eh. Uhh...
[SATORI laughing]
This guy is one of
Eneru's priests?
[SATORI laughing]
[LUFFY]
That's the ordeal? Ball guy?
Stop with the dancing!
And tell us who you are!
[laughing]
Gotta say, he's not as
bright as I expected.
Didn't Nami and the old guy
say these priests were strong?
'Cause I'm not seein' it.
[SATORI laughing]
[SANJI]
Hey! Dumpling!
Nami and the others
better be safe!
[SATORI]
The sacrifices?
They'll escape or they won't.
Doesn't really matter which.
If they escape, they'll die.
If they're sacrificed,
well, they'll die then, too.
What's that mean?
[SATORI] But I'd be more
worried about yourselves.
You'll have to beat me if you
plan on going any further.
And I really don't see
that happening.
[SATORI laughing]
He's comin' right for
us, Luffy! Get him!
I hope you're ready for this!
Gum-Gum...
Ooh! You gonna stretch?
...Pistol!
[laughs]
[LUFFY yelling]
[USOPP]
No way!
Luffy!
[USOPP]
You're okay, aren't you?
A hit like that couldn't
have hurt you that much!
[SATORI]
Well, you see,
it's not what you'd
call a... normal hit.
I'll show you not normal!
[SATORI]
Right foot, high kick.
Boulette-- Uh.
[SATORI]
Only the most well-trained
are granted the power of...
..."Mantra."
[SANJI]
Impossible!
How could he have
predicted my attack?
Ah!
No! Sanji!
[SATORI]
I warned you, didn't I?
Impact!
The shock destroys the
body from the inside out.
[LUFFY]
Sanji. Usopp.
[SANJI]
Yeah, I'm fine.
Ugh. What did that
bastard do to us?
I got no idea.
Who is this guy anyway?
[laughs]
My name is Satori.
I am one of the four priests
of the almighty Eneru,
who watch over Upper Yard
and see to the judgment of
criminals like yourselves.
I own the vearth
in this Lost Forest.
The Lost Forest?
Why, yes.
My forest, in all its glory.
And now...
...your boat will be
lost in its illusions!
Ah! We're using that!
[SATORI] She will now speed
along the Milky Road,
eventually weaving her way
to this forest's only exit!
I'm sure I don't
need to tell you this,
but if you lose a
dial boat in here,
it's the same as losing your
way to the sacrificial altar.
That means you will
have to find the boat
and board her
before that happens.
Of course, my hundreds
of Surprise Clouds and I
will never allow
you that chance.
Does that seem unfair
to you boys?
Welcome to the Upper Yard!
[SATORI laughing]
The Ordeal of Spheres.
There's a ten percent
survival rate, so good luck.
Survival rate. Just ten percent?
[SATORI laughing]
[CHOPPER wailing]
Zoro! Nami! Robin!
Why did you leave me all alone?
Please come back! I don't
wanna stay here by myself!
What will happen if I'm
attacked now? I can't fight!
There'll be no one
here to save me.
Huh?
[screams]
This is all because of Luffy.
If he hadn't wanted to
come to Skypeia so bad,
then I wouldn't be stuck here.
[gasps]
[ZORO]
You guys can keep a lookout.
I'm sure Luffy and the others
are headed this way.
That's right. Luffy and
the others are coming here.
So, really, all I have to do is
stay alive until they show up!
It shouldn't be long now
before they get here.
I just need to keep busy.
I know!
I'll work on fixing the ship
like Zoro asked me to.
I can do that.
[chuckles]
They'll be so surprised
when they see how well
I'm taking care
of the ship all alone.
[chuckles]
[CHOPPER screams]
[CHOPPER]
The hammer!
I-I have to get it back.
Aww... Oh, dear.
[SATORI laughing]
[SATORI] You boys had better
catch her pretty soon.
She's getting away.
He's right, you guys.
We need to get moving now,
before we lose sight of her.
Ugh. If we lose her
in this forest,
finding her again
could be impossible.
Usopp, wait. Finding each
other won't be easy either.
Luffy, you coming?
You two go on ahead without me.
I'm gonna take care of ball guy.
Ha-ha! This should be amusing.
Do you really think you can
beat me, rubber boy? Ha-ha!
[SANJI]
I guess someone needs to deal
with this potbellied freak.
[SANJI]
Don't do anything reckless.
He has weird powers.
Back as soon as we get the boat!
[LUFFY]
Great.
It's just you and me now, fatso.
[laughs]
He'll grab that branch.
And Gum-Gum...
Same move as before.
[LUFFY]
...Pistol!
[gasps]
[SATORI laughs]
[LUFFY screaming]
[laughs]
What's the matter? I thought you
were going to take care of me.
I am. I said I would, didn't I?
And this time I won't
miss! Gum-Gum...
He'll feign a punch,
but follow with a kick!
[LUFFY]
...Whip!
[SATORI laughs]
And again!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[groaning]
[LUFFY screaming]
[laughing]
[USOPP panting]
Where is she? Where's the Crow?
If we don't get her back,
we'll be stuck here forever!
[USOPP] I can't see
anything from down here.
Up I go!
[SANJI]
Watch yourself, Luffy!
These priests are
far from ordinary.
Now to find the boat,
and get the hell outta here.
Fast!
[LUFFY]
Darn it! My head's stuck!
[laughs]
Aren't you stubborn?
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[USOPP] Aw, man! It looks like
we're going to lose the boat!
[LUFFY] This ball guy is tough!
And what's with these clouds?
Fighting on sky
islands is weird!
[SANJI] This is no time
for crappy ordeals!
We've got to save
Nami and Robin!
[CHOPPER]
Zoro! Nami! Robin!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Ordeal of Spheres!
Desperate Struggle
in the Lost Forest!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!