[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!
[NARRATOR]
In the land of oases,
a dry cloud of sand blankets
the people with anguish.
Some cling to hope,
and others seek to destroy it.
As their paths cross,
they mark an era
in the country's history
that will forever
be overshadowed by sadness.
There are those in Alabasta
who hope to prevent war,
and those who seek to incite it.
Many different people
have gathered
at the capital, Alubarna.
Among those now
in the heat of battle
are Chopper and Usopp.
Their struggle with Mr. 4
and Miss Merry Christmas
continues to unfold.
Will Alabasta fall?
Or will it find true peace?
Moment by moment,
the sands of the
hourglass of fate
run down towards the final hour.
[LUFFY]
"Big Opening Day Today!
The Copy‐Copy Montage!"
[USOPP] Don't lie to us,
you dirty mole woman!
We aren't gonna listen to you!
There's no way Luffy can
be dead, do you hear me?
He'd never lose to
that alligator bastard!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] And what
makes you think that scrawny
little captain of yours
could even last five seconds
against our boss?
You stupid long nose!
Because someday
he's going to become
the King of the Pirates!
So there's no chance that
he would let himself die here!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS laughs]
Did you hear that, Mr. 4?
He'll be the pirate king.
Pi king. Pi king. [laughs]
That's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard!
[laughing]
King of the Pirates!
Only idiots like you
and your pathetic friends
would believe
a ridiculous story like that.
I'm glad that pathetic
captain of yours is dead.
He was a moron who
didn't know his own place.
He was a 'ron! [laughing]
A 'ron! [laughing]
Chopper! Listen!
[USOPP]
A real man‐‐[gasps]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] It's
about time you die, long nose!
Molehill Highway!
Listen to me.
A real man,
no matter how terrifying
or hideous or corrupt
his enemy might be...
I'll see you in hell, 'ron,
ya long nosed 'ron!
[USOPP yelling]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Mole‐mole impact!
You okay?!
No... No matter
how slim the chance,
a real man will still fight!
[MR. 4 laughing]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Mr. 4!
You're up!
Now take your batting stance!
Ready your four‐ton bat!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
This is it.
Molehill...
[USOPP yelling]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Intersection Number Four!
Usopp, no!
[USOPP grunts]
[BOTH laughing]
The weak are always weak,
even if they
pretend they're not.
How sad.
[CHOPPER]
Damn you!
What did you do to him?
Oh, look, the blue nose
wants to play now.
Well, no problem at all.
We'd be happy to
take care of you.
Just like we took care
of your long nose
freak friend over there.
‐‐[laughing]
‐‐[MR. 4 laughing]
[CHOPPER]
Shut up!
Damn mole woman.
Usopp's not a coward,
do you hear me?
[USOPP grunts]
[USOPP]
There are times when...
When a real man
must stay and fight
instead of running.
No matter what.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
You're still standing?
Like now,
when a friend's true dream
is laughed at by someone.
No way.
You were hit in the head with
a bat that weighs four tons!
You shouldn't even
be alive, ya damn 'ron.
You shouldn't, no ya shouldn't,
shouldn't even be alive, no way.
What sort of sneaky trick
are you using this time, huh?
[USOPP]
Luffy is not dead.
He's going to be King
of the Pirates someday.
I know he will!
That is one thing
that I will never let
you laugh at! Never!
Ha!
I guess the long nose hasn't
learned his lesson yet.
Let's go again, Mr. 4!
I'm not gonna let that happen!
Let me show you
a transformation point
I've been saving.
[yelling]
[CHOPPER]
Horn point!
I'm coming, Usopp!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] You get
an "A" for determination,
but no matter how hard you try,
you'll have no chance
at defeating me!
Chopper!
Chopper, just... just
get behind me, okay?
Yeah, got it!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
All right, Mr. 4, get ready!
[MR. 4]
Four!
Take this special attack.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Now here we go!
‐‐Molehill!
‐‐[MR. 4] Four!
[USOPP]
Special Attack: Smoke Star!
[MR. 4 yells]
[USOPP] All right, Chopper,
the rest is up to you!
[CHOPPER]
Right!
That stupid brat
took off his shoes
and jumped right off!
[yelling]
[USOPP]
Now, Molehill!
Intersection Number Four!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
No, don't do it, Mr. 4!
Don't do it! It's me!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS screams]
Four?
[USOPP]
Hey, you guys!
Why don't you take
a look over here?
Now! Usopp‐Chopper Attack!
Hammer Comet!
[MR. 4]
Huh?
[yells]
[MR. 4]
Four!
We did it!
Are you okay?
[ball ticking]
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
Just hang in there, all right?
Don't die on me!
We need to find a doctor!
A doctor! [cries]
[USOPP]
That's you.
[CHOPPER]
Oh, yeah.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[ROYAL SOLDIER F yelling]
[REBEL SOLDIER A yelling]
Are you all right?
[REBEL SOLDIER A]
Yeah.
[REBEL SOLDIER B]
Koza! Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
That bullet from Nanohana
is still in you.
[KOZA]
None of that matters now.
This is a battlefield we're on.
We have to stay focused
on what's happening.
Got that?
I'd like to get to
one of their horses.
If we can make our
way down this street
and through the center of town,
then we'll be at the north block
where the royal palace is.
[REBEL SOLDIER B, KOZA grunt]
What are you planning, Koza?
Why go to the palace?
To reach the king and
demand that he surrender to us.
But that's insane!
The main force of the royal army
is stationed in the north block!
And what's more,
they're led by Chaka and Pell.
Think of the danger!
And we haven't even
managed to gather
all of our forces together.
Don't you think it
would be a better idea
to wait until reinforcements
arrive here to help?
We can't.
It's already too late for that.
Now come on!
[REBEL SOLDIER B]
Wait! Koza!
Halt! Are you aligned
with the rebel army?
The only thing ahead
of here in the north block
is the royal palace.
Do you understand me?
[ROYAL SOLDIER C] If you
aren't a part of the battle,
leave this area of town at once!
[ROYAL SOLDIER A]
Hey! Are you listening?
This place is no
playground, you get it?
[VIVI]
I know that!
[ROYAL SOLDIER F]
Princess Vivi?
[ROYAL SOLDIER G]
It can't be!
[ROYAL SOLDIER H]
Is it really her?
[VIVI]
Where's my father?
I need him now!
Well, Princess...
[VIVI]
Never mind.
If I can't see him,
then take me to Chaka.
There's something
that he must do!
[MR. 2]
Deux!
Un! Deux! Un! Deux!
[MR. 2]
Trois!
[SANJI]
Bastard!
[MR. 2]
That was quite a kick.
This one can compete with
my Ballet Kenpo moves!
You! Out of my way!
[SANJI]
I already told you.
If you want to get by,
you'll have to defeat me first!
I hope you realize all your
efforts will be in vain.
All my life I have practiced
these dance moves.
I have perfected the
dancer's graceful art
of Ballet Kenpo
and it is unbeatable,
even by the likes of you!
[MR. 2] Just give up!
It's no use trying to escape!
Ballet Kenpo!
[swans honking]
My Degenerate Swan
Dance Recital!
This dance isn't
getting me anywhere;
it's time to settle
this once and for all.
‐‐Collier Shoot!
‐‐[MR. 2] Un!
‐‐[SANJI] Epaule!
‐‐[MR. 2] Deux!
‐‐[SANJI] Cotelette!
‐‐[MR. 2] Ora!
[SANJI]
Selle!
[MR. 2]
Un!
‐‐[SANJI] Poitrine!
‐‐[MR. 2] Deux!
‐‐[SANJI] Gigot!
‐‐[MR. 2] Krah!
[MR. 2]
Ballet Kenpo!
[SANJI]
Mouton Shoot!
[MR. 2]
Swan Arabesque!
[SANJI yells]
[MR. 2 yells]
[SANJI] My Mouton Shoot...
blocked by that clown?
[MR. 2]
My ultimate Swan Arabesque,
stopped by that stupid,
insignificant cook?
You've gotta be kidding me here!
Okay, it's time to get serious.
From now on, I mean business!
Do you hear me?
Let's see it, then.
Hah!
You don't know the true extent
of my power yet, do you?
My most impressive
feature is my ability
to remember faces.
Using that, I can
construct and display
an incredible montage!
When you see this,
you will laugh helplessly
until you collapse.
To begin... The world's
most ridiculous hair.
Then, the world's
most ridiculous eyes.
The most ridiculous nose.
And then the world's
most ridiculous mouth.
[laughs]
Now, take a good, long look!
Experience the grand unveiling
of the Copy‐Copy Montage!
[MR. 2 laughing]
About ninety percent of that
was your own ridiculous face.
I'll help you.
Stop playing dress‐up,
you ugly freak!
Don't you have a heart? I'm a
brilliant artist, you big jerk!
I don't have time to
mess around with your
childish little tricks anymore.
Tricks, huh? Not so fast!
They aren't just tricks!
Just wait until you see!
Within my art there
lies the power
of the greatest friendships
and the truest loves!
Right, I get it.
I see what you're planning now.
[MR. 2]
We all need love! And friends!
It really just isn't
going to work, though.
Now let's see you hurt me!
[yells]
How could you do that?
You just attacked
your little friend
with the long nose!
Well, then, clearly you
don't value friendship much,
do you?
You're a real idiot.
No matter what you
transform your face
to look like,
you're still only you.
I'm not the kind
to be fooled by images
and façades like that.
No way! A person is their soul!
[MR. 2 whimpering]
Is their soul?
[MR. 2 crying]
That's so...
Wow!
[crying]
I am so embarrassed to
have been so caught up
with appearances!
I understand,
even if I was to become...
...her, for instance.
It wouldn't make any
difference to you at all,
because images don't matter.
[MR. 2]
Well he's easy to read...
Really easy to read.
[MR. 2]
Incredibly easy to read.
You are such a fool.
‐‐[ROYAL SOLDIER I] What?
‐‐[ROYAL SOLDIER A] It's Vivi!
[ROYAL SOLDIER B] It's true!
Princess Vivi has come back!
[ROYAL SOLDIER C]
But why now?
But Princess Vivi,
that's insane!
We can't do something like that!
What are you afraid
would happen if we did?
That the kingdom
would simply die?
You're wrong, it wouldn't.
This palace is not
Alabasta, after all.
Alabasta is...
It is the people who are
out there hurting each other.
They're the ones who
made Alabasta a country
in the first place!
If there's any chance
at stopping this war,
then we must take it.
Please, Chaka!
We only need to draw
everyone's eyes over here
for a few seconds!
If you can do that,
then I will take it from there!
I swear, I can do this!
[VIVI] For now, please,
destroy this palace!
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[ROYAL SOLDIER A] But you can't
be serious, Princess Vivi!
[ROYAL SOLDIER B] The palace
has stood in the same spot
for four thousand years!
[ROYAL SOLDIER C] Please don't
go through with this plan,
Princess Vivi!
[ROYAL SOLDIER D] Chaka! You
have to use your best judgment!
[ROYAL SOLDIER E]
The king isn't even here!
You can't possibly do
this without his approval.
[CHAKA]
Sire! We must take action
against the rebels quickly,
before it's too late!
[COBRA]
This is not some little quarrel.
If we strike first,
they will strike back.
Are you suggesting that
we attack our citizens
before we determine
who's behind all this?
Because that would
be the true destruction
of our kingdom.
But we will act‐‐
we will head out for Rainbase
and Crocodile.
[PELL] Your Majesty,
attacking Crocodile now
will only make things worse!
It will only add fuel
to the rebel army's fire!
If we leave for Rainbase now,
the rebel army will
use our absence
as a perfect chance
to attack the palace.
[COBRA] It doesn't matter
if the rebel army
destroys this palace completely.
It's only a building.
You see,
even if our royal army
does fall in the end,
if we can just defeat Crocodile,
this country can still
be reborn as long as
its people are safe and whole.
If we battle the
rebel army instead,
then that will all change.
Remember...
...the people are the country!
[CHAKA]
Princess Vivi.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[CHAKA]
I will do as you say!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[NAMI yells] Why did these guys
decide to come after me?
[ZORO] That dumb woman!
Where did she go?
[MR. 2] This guy may
be a first‐class cook,
but he's nothing special
when it comes to fighting!
Let me show you some
more of my Ballet Kenpo,
the true art of the dance!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Transformed into Nami!
Bon Clay's Rapid‐Fire
Ballet Kenpo!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!