[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
The battle of Marineford
ended with a Navy victory.
Unable to save Ace's life,
the injured Luffy was
taken to Amazon Lily,
where he fell into despair.
[NARRATOR] But this is a
story from another time.
Ten years ago, in the East
Blue, the brothers ran wild
with dreams of a world
full of adventure,
as well as the pirate flags
they would someday fly.
[NARRATOR]
Tucked away in Mount Corvo,
with Dadan and her
mountain bandits,
Ace and Luffy took
a vow of brotherhood
with their friend and
co-conspirator, Sabo.
[ACE]
We'll always be brothers
and nobody can take that away.
Heh. From now on, we're
honest to goodness brothers.
Cheers to that!
[ALL]
Brothers!
Too bad I'm gonna
become a pirate
and recruit the best
cook before you do.
Yeah, you wish!
I'm gonna be a pirate
before either of you dopes!
[GARP clears throat]
You little bastards are still
spouting that pirate crap?
You're both gonna be
Marines someday,
even if I gotta beat
some dignity into you!
[BOTH groan]
[DADAN]
"We will stand on our feet."
[screams]
Now this is how you live!
Uh-huh, no kidding.
[LUFFY giggles]
What an awesome hideout!
So, that's where they are?
[LUFFY]
"Luffy Becoming an Apprentice?!
A Man Who Fought Against
the King of the Pirates!"
[NARRATOR] Seasons came and
went, giving way to winter.
[ACE]
Sabo! He's coming at you!
Don't let him escape!
[SABO]
No problem! I got this!
Good! He's running
straight for the bay!
[giggles]
Okay, Luffy! You're up!
Hello, food.
[LUFFY yells, groans]
[BEAR A gasps]
[BOTH chuckle, gasp]
You can't get away!
[panting]
[BEAR A groaning]
I got him! You see that?
Ha, ha. Wow, nice one, Luffy.
All right, that's
two in one day.
We're gonna have a ton
of danpa soup tonight!
Uh-huh!
I did it! [laughs]
I can hunt, too! Yay!
Uh, hey, Luffy?
[TIGER A growls]
Behind you! Look out!
Huh? Behind me?
Whoa, he's big!
[ACE] He must've smelled our
dinner and came running.
[SABO]
He just wants the danpa, Luffy!
Get away from there!
[TIGER A growls]
[LUFFY gasping]
I've never hunted
anything so big.
This one is special to me!
So, go get your own food!
[SABO] Luffy, cut it out,
he's way too tough!
We can get another one!
[LUFFY]
No! I said this one is special!
Get away, cat!
I'm gonna bonk you!
[LUFFY gasps, groans]
That looks bad.
You okay?
[LUFFY]
I'll show you!
Gum-Gum...!
[LUFFY gasps, groans]
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY]
Round two.
Now, Gum-Gum...
[SABO, ACE]
No, you don't!
Hurry! Hurry!
While he's busy!
[SABO]
I know!
[LUFFY]
I'll get you next time!
[sighs]
[SABO] Sorry. I know that was
your first big kill and all.
[ACE]
He'll get over it.
Which is something we
couldn't say if he got eaten.
[LUFFY]
Yeah, but that tiger cheated!
He can't steal from me!
I gotta teach him a lesson!
[ACE]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
If you wanna die that bad,
don't take us with you!
Huh?
[LUFFY laughing]
[SABO]
C'mon! That's not funny!
[ACE]
Luffy!
[LUFFY gasps, screams]
[SABO grunting]
[ACE grunting]
Hurry! Pull!
He's slipping!
Okay.
[LUFFY giggles]
Sorry!
[SABO groans]
Well, today sucked.
Let's go to bed and hope
tomorrow is better.
[LUFFY] You mean going to
"bed" makes it "bedder"?
[LUFFY chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Ugh. I'm hungry.
[ACE]
Who's fault is that?
--[thud]
--[LUFFY] Ow!
[SABO]
The bridge thing was stupid,
but I don't blame
Luffy for being mad
about losing his catch.
He did pretty good
out there today.
Yeah. Except for the
part where he almost
got eaten by a giant tiger.
Oh, you would do the same thing!
Whatever! Good night!
[SABO, ACE yawn]
[LUFFY yawns]
[LUFFY giggles]
Having big brothers
sure is cool.
I hope they'll join
my pirate crew someday.
[ACE] Don't waste your time
on these guys, Captain.
[SABO]
Yeah, we got this one.
[LUFFY]
I may be the captain,
but we're still brothers!
[ALL yell]
[LUFFY giggling]
Awesome.
This had better be
a really good joke.
I'd rather have something
to eat, but let's hear it.
I'm happy, that's all.
I made up my mind!
You guys are joining my crew!
'Kay? Promise?
I'm not promising anything!
Shut up and go back to sleep.
I said we'd figure it
out later, didn't I?
Aw! Come on!
It'll be way more fun
if we're together.
And you guys need
my help, you know.
You do!
Uh, yeah, you're the one
who needs help, buddy.
Also, stop bobbing like that.
It's weird.
[LUFFY]
You're not listening!
We gotta be a crew, we gotta!
Okay, I get it,
we make a good team.
Let's work together,
but I'm the captain.
[BOTH]
No, it's my ship!
I see. Well, that's too bad.
We're back to square one.
You sure you can't budge?
[ACE]
Yep.
What about you?
I wanna be free--I'm not gonna
serve as somebody's lackey.
Sorry.
[LUFFY]
Come on! It'll be fun!
Oh, wait, I know!
Let's go fight that
big 'ole tiger
and whoever beats it
gets to be captain.
Screw "captain."
We'll all be tiger food.
Even if we could beat that
thing--which we can't--
the chances of you
doing it are, like, zero.
Yeah, if I fought it by myself.
That's why we'll
fight it as a team
and just see who
lands the final hit!
[ACE, SABO]
Now that's a plan!
You guys are goin' down!
[ACE, SABO]
Yeah, right!
[ACE]
Everyone ready?
Uh-huh.
These were hard to catch.
This is a waste of fish.
You knew they were bait.
We gotta think bigger if
we wanna fight a monster
like that tiger.
[BEAR B roars]
[SABO gasps]
It sounds like he's on his way.
You greedy jerk--I'm beating
you and I'm keeping my fish!
[BEAR B roars]
[LUFFY gasps]
[BEAR B growls]
Let's do it.
[BEAR B roars]
[SABO]
Oh, oops.
That's not a tiger.
[LUFFY, ACE]
Huh?
[roars]
So now what?
Do we fight him instead?
We didn't invite you,
bear, go away!
Shoo! Go on!
[BEAR B growls]
Actually, this guy might be
nearly as strong as the tiger.
Either way, if we
can't beat him,
we can't beat our kitty friend.
All right then, let's see
if big, hairy, and ugly
makes for a good warm-up.
[ACE] Keep yappin',
I'm gonna beat him!
[SABO]
Hey, no fair!
[LUFFY]
You big cheater!
[yelling]
[ACE grunting]
[ACE]
Heh.
[ALL gasp]
[BEAR B roars]
[ALL screaming]
[ALL panting]
[BEAR B roars]
[LUFFY whimpering]
He's not gonna stop
chasing us, is he?
[LUFFY, ACE, SABO panting]
[LUFFY]
We're gonna die!
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
Whoa. Who's that guy?
Better move, whoever he is.
His name's Naguri--I've seen
him around Gray Terminal.
Hey! What're you doing, old man?
You got a death wish? Run!
[BOTH gasp]
[BEAR B growling]
[NAGURI grunts]
[gasps]
Leave these boys alone.
It's time to return
to the forest.
I said turn around
and leave us be!
[ALL gasp]
He stopped it.
Just like Shanks. So cool!
[SABO] What? You used to
be a pirate, Naguri?
And a captain?
Indeed.
Yeah, I knew that already!
I mean, you did
that cool thing--
only a pirate captain
could be that awesome!
What "cool thing"?
[LUFFY giggles] You know
what I'm talking about--
you made the bear go away.
And all you had to do
was look at him!
Just like Shanks!
Oh, I see. [chuckles]
He never seemed tough
enough to be a pirate.
Not to me.
He was just weird.
[SABO] 'Course, lots of people
at Gray Terminal are weird,
but this guy would
grab junk all day
and then hammer it
together and make--
well, I don't even know what.
The other guys or Bluejam's
crew would pick on him,
but he'd just sit
there and take it.
Never fought back
or said a word.
Seemed pretty pathetic
if you ask me.
Shows what you know, dummy.
All captains are like that!
Now you're just making stuff up!
Since when are you
the pirate expert, huh?
Captains don't get worked up
over losers--Shanks told me!
It's always "Shanks" with you.
Hey, here, eat.
[LUFFY, SABO gasp]
Ow, ow, ow!
Hey, you gave him more than me!
[SABO]
Better luck next time, shrimp.
Hey, don't hold back, Naguri--
you did save our lives.
Thank you. But it
was no trouble.
So... You're obviously
no pushover.
What are you doing in a
dump like Gray Terminal?
[NAGURI]
Hmm.
It's hardly a charming story.
Well, if you don't want
to talk about it,
it's not like I can force you.
[NAGURI]
No. I don't mind.
I assume you know the
famous pirate, Gold Roger?
[ACE gasps]
Uh-huh?
'Course I know! He was the king!
My men, at the height
of our strength,
challenged Roger to a fight.
Really?
A fight that we lost.
Put in our place,
we all split up.
[NAGURI] Everything went
downhill after that.
One thing led to
another, and here I am.
Frankly, it makes me wonder
if I was worth
anything to begin with.
You fought the King of the
Pirates--that means you're cool!
Win or lose!
Well, I'm not so sure.
We got beaten pretty badly,
and at any rate, we certainly
didn't feel very "cool." So...
Oh, really?
So Gold Roger was
as tough as they say?
Or tougher, even?
Yes. But one man alone
can only be so strong--
it was his crew that made
him truly unstoppable.
Or rather,
it was their teamwork,
their comradery
that impressed me.
It was an honor to
see them in action.
[SABO gasps]
[LUFFY] Aw, man. I guess I
still got a long way to go
before I'm tough like that.
Is that so? You planning on
being a pirate someday?
I sure am!
And a captain? Like me?
[LUFFY]
Mm-hm! And the king!
Oh, wait, you can help me!
Do you have any
good pirating tips?
[NAGURI]
Hm?
How do I get super strong?
I gotta beat Ace and Sabo
so I can be captain.
Is that how it works?
Uh-huh, sure is!
So, can you train me?
Well, all right.
Really?
[LUFFY]
Heh. That's great!
I'll start my
training tomorrow!
[SABO sighs]
[LUFFY]
Where did Ace go?
[SABO]
Uh, yeah, about that.
[LUFFY]
What?!
Gold Roger is Ace's dad
and he never told me?
[SABO]
Yeah, well, it's a big secret.
So, keep it that way.
And while you're at it,
don't mention it to Ace, either.
He'll kill the both of us.
[LUFFY]
I don't get it.
It's a mystery to me, too,
but I do know he hates Roger.
Why? I mean, that's his dad.
Doesn't mean he has to
like him, does it?
[gasps]
[SABO] I know you guys
still have it worse,
but even if I did have parents,
I was still all alone.
Sorry, I guess you're right.
Family or not, I guess
some people in this world
just aren't meant to get along.
[LUFFY]
Yeah, but most people don't have
the King of the Pirates
as their dad.
I know you want to
ask him about Roger,
and to be honest,
I'd love to know, myself,
but just lay off, okay?
Do you promise?
[LUFFY]
Uh-huh! No problem.
Oh, and you, too, Naguri.
I won't say a word.
[NAGURI] But to think
that Roger had a son
and he was right
here all this time.
[SABO]
All right, there he is.
Looks like he calmed down,
but play it cool
just in case, got it?
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
[SABO]
And do not mention Roger--
[LUFFY]
I know! I know, I know!
Hey, Ace, there you are!
Didn't know you
came home already!
Hey, Ace, there you are!
Didn't know Roger was
your dad and you hate him!
[screams]
[SABO]
He didn't last five seconds!
Remember when we were
gonna drown you?
'Cause I'm kinda regretting
that we didn't right now!
Luffy.
Yeah?
Who told you all that?
U-Uh...
Sabo did!
So, tell me, was Roger
awesome or super awesome?
Stop it! Be cool!
This is the exact opposite
of what I told you to do--
You're gonna get us killed!
[BOTH groan]
Ow.
Don't you ever speak that name
in front of me again, got it?
[LUFFY]
Don't be stingy!
I bet you got cool
stories to tell!
[SABO]
You could've let me explain
before you clobbered
me over the head!
That's enough!
There.
[LUFFY] I wanna hear
pirate secrets! Please!
Yeah! We're brothers--we can't
hide things from each other!
Shut up!
You're both dead to me!
[LUFFY]
Roger, Roger, Roger!
He's your father,
father, father!
[SABO] Stop! His anger's
making him stronger!
[LUFFY screams]
[ACE] This is your fault
for running your mouth
in the first place, Sabo!
[SABO]
Ow! He had to learn someday!
[LUFFY]
Stop hitting me!
Let me say it again.
From now on,
you bastards're dead to me!
[SABO, LUFFY]
Oh, yeah?
Took the words outta my mouth!
[ALL gasp]
Don't let me down.
I'll be counting on you.
[BLUEJAM] Got it.
I'll leave no stone unturned.
Well, you heard the man.
[BLUEJAM PIRATE A]
We'll get right on it, boss.
Hold on. When you find him,
don't do anything yet.
[BLUEJAM PIRATE A]
What?
[BLUEJAM]
The longer we make him wait,
the more gratitude we
can wring out of him.
Money's fine, but I
want a favor, too.
He can wait for his
dear Sabo a bit longer.
I see.
[BLUEJAM]
Keep an eye on him,
but until I give you the order,
don't snatch him up.
[DADAN] "We will have
a visit this spring."
Dogra! Magra!
What is Goa? A country?
[DOGRA] Uh, that's
the country we live in.
Mount Corvo, Windmill
Village, and Gray Terminal
are all part of Goa.
[DADAN]
Hmph. I knew that.
It must be the end of the world.
I wasn't even sure
you could read
and now you're
reading the paper?
Frankly, it's kinda
creeping me out.
--[thud]
--[MAGRA] Ow!
[DADAN] Anyway, they're making
a big deal about this visit,
but it's not like they're
gonna haul their asses
all the way to our mountain.
Not that I'd want to see
those pompous bastards anyway.
Celestial Dragons?
No thanks.
[NARRATOR]
Ace and Sabo visit Naguri
to see how Luffy is fairing
in his new apprenticeship.
As the three boys compete to
decide who will be captain,
Naguri reminds them that
it takes more than strength
to be a leader.
Facing off with a massive tiger,
they must find their
answer in battle.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Battle Against
the Big Tiger!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!