[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain
has fallen in the desert
kingdom of Alabasta,
the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
Having escaped from
the trap at Raindinners,
Luffy and the others set
out toward Alubarna,
where they hoped to
plead with a rebel army
numbering two million soldiers.
However, a waiting
Crocodile ensnared Luffy,
and the two began
a vicious duel.
Unable to find a foothold
against Crocodile's
overwhelming power,
Luffy fell victim
to a near lethal blow.
Can Luffy discover his
opponent's weakness in time?
Or is it the end for the
mighty Straw Hat pirate?
[LUFFY]
"Dash For a Miracle!
Alabasta Animal Land!"
[TOTO] Water!
I can hardly believe my eyes.
Th‐There's so much!
Precious water.
The water is coming forth!
Didn't I tell you, Luffy?
This land is strong.
Through it all, Yuba lives on.
[CROCODILE] This sand storm
will deal Yuba a final,
destructive blow.
Fanning the flames of anger
within the rebel army
until an inferno ignites.
But in the end,
the bleeding hearts
which infest this land
are what's killing it.
And you, Straw Hat Luffy,
are the worst of them all.
If only you had purged
yourself of such weakness,
you may have lived
a little longer.
Water.
I assume you don't feel so
indebted to this water now.
[CROCODILE groans]
[LUFFY grunting]
What's this? You're still alive?
[CROCODILE grunts]
[LUFFY yelling]
That looks like it hurts.
But you'll be out of
your misery soon enough.
[laughing]
[LUFFY grunting]
[CROCODILE]
Goodbye.
That was a complete
waste of my time.
[TOTO]
Not so bad.
Once we've weathered this storm,
the rain will bless
us with sweet relief.
Just like always.
Your winds will never
vanquish us, you cowardly storm!
Yuba will never
give in to the sand!
[USOPP]
And that's when it happened!
I looked him straight
in the eye and yelled,
"You bowlegged bastard!"
And ever since that day,
crabs throughout
the world have been
self‐conscious about
being bowlegged.
[CHOPPER]
Oh!
That's the reason
they walk sideways?
[USOPP] Yep.
And at that pivotal moment,
a lobster happened
to be within earshot
and heard the whole thing!
[CHOPPER]
Oh.
So lobsters are crabs too?
Better believe it!
[CHOPPER]
Oh!
[USOPP laughs]
Zoro. Why don't you relax?
You're just wasting
your energy doing that.
Who asked you?
[SANJI]
Excuse him, Nami. He's hopeless.
Guys like Zoro‐‐
they gotta keep moving
or they won't stay focused.
They have one‐track minds,
'specially...
...our own resident
muscle‐freak, here,
now that he's had a taste
of the Seven Warlords.
Stop whining.
Just say what's on
your mind, or shut up!
[SANJI]
Ah, you need me to spell it out?
All this tough‐guy bluster
is just a sad attempt
to mask your fear that
Luffy might lose this one.
[ZORO]
Who, me?
You sayin' I'm scared? Huh?
Is that what you're sayin'?
Look at me!
Fancy eyebrows!
[SANJI] That's it!
I've had enough of you!
Ya damn moss‐head!
[ZORO]
What'd you call me?!
You wanna go at it?
Cut it out! This is pointless!
[CHOPPER]
She's strong!
[USOPP]
Look at 'em.
They're at each other's throats.
Everyone's worked up.
It's up to me, as vice‐captain,
to take charge.
[VIVI]
Calm down! All of you!
Everyone's frightened, yes,
but we mustn't turn
on each other!
Luffy's counting on us
to meet him in Alubarna!
Yeah, well, you seem more
on‐edge than any of us!
Keep your mind on the rebellion
and leave the rest to us.
[SANJI]
Sorry about that, Vivi.
If we tear each other apart,
we've already lost.
[NAMI]
All right, that's settled.
Now, let's devote our
attention to Alubarna!
Full speed, Scissors!
[USOPP]
Huh?
"Scissors"?
[NAMI]
Name for the crab.
[CHOPPER]
Oh!
[USOPP]
You just make that up?
[NAMI]
Got something better?
[USOPP]
No, not really.
[CHOPPER laughs]
[TASHIGI]
Me, go to Alubarna?
Are we chasing after
the Straw Hat pirates?
Or, uh, reinforcing
the royal army?
[SMOKER]
That's up to you.
You'll have to decide
which is more important
when you get there.
But Sir. I don't understand.
What's going on?
[SMOKER]
Rely on your sense of justice.
Whatever happens,
I'll accept responsibility.
Captain, where are you going?
I have to head out to sea.
Something unforeseen
has come up.
Be on alert to receive
communication from me
at any time.
Right!
[SMOKER] I need you to keep a
vigilant eye on this country
and where it ends up.
Whether it falls,
or whether it survives.
The dawn of a brand
new and historic age
is on the horizon.
[engine starts]
[MARINE A]
Sergeant Major. Sergeant Major!
‐‐Your orders?
‐‐[TASHIGI] Yes.
[SMOKER] Whether it falls,
or whether it survives.
The dawn of a brand
new and historic age
is on the horizon.
[TASHIGI] Our target is the
pirate Straw Hat Luffy,
and everyone who
serves under him!
All hands reinforce your gear!
Prepare to depart for Alubarna!
[MARINES]
Right!
Straw Hat Luffy.
What?!
What do you mean we
can't cross this river?
[VIVI]
Think about it.
Moving Crabs are
creatures of the desert.
They don't take to water.
[USOPP]
Has everyone gone nuts?
It's a crab! They can exist
on land and water!
Guys, this is not good!
This is a serious problem!
Look!
If we just carelessly
spend our energy
swimming across the river,
we're not gonna make it in time!
See here?
After the river,
there's tons of desert
to deal with!
So, if this crab can't make it
to the other shore,
are we supposed to run
the rest of the way on foot?
We don't have a choice.
We won't make it in time!
It's absolutely impossible!
Uh‐oh. Hey, I can see it!
Sandora River straight ahead!
Oh, great.
Help us, Scissors!
Pretty please!
I know.
Scissors loves dancer girls.
Will this do?
[CHOPPER]
Probably.
Wow! I can't take it!
[CHOPPER]
He's looking this way!
We're accelerating!
[SANJI]
Nami swan!
[ZORO] Great! Now we've
got two animals in heat!
[CHOPPER]
All right! We're moving now!
[USOPP] And what exactly
has this solved, Chopper?
Nothing!
Go faster!
[CHOPPER]
He did it!
[SANJI] I'm seeing it,
but I don't believe it.
This crab is incredible!
[USOPP laughs]
Way to go!
Now, don't you stop!
Just keep on going. Hurry!
Run, run, run all the way!
Go! Keep moving!
Nothing can stop us now!
Oh! I love this crab!
Hey, wait a minute!
What's going on?
If I didn't know better,
I'd think we were sinking!
You stupid crab!
[ZORO]
It's over.
No use whining about it.
Keep moving.
[USOPP]
Hold on a second!
Are you sure there aren't
any boats around here?
How long will it take us
to reach the shore?
[VIVI]
The rest of the night.
That's insane!
Thanks a lot!
Thanks for the ride.
Bye, Scissors.
Oh, shut up! He's the reason
we're in this mess!
[USOPP]
What the‐‐?
[GROUP yells]
[VIVI]
It's a Sandoran catfish!
They're rarely seen by humans!
Doesn't seem that rare to me!
[VIVI yells]
[VIVI] Did I mention they
love to eat human flesh?
[USOPP] You could've
told us a bit sooner!
[GROUP yelling]
Get off of me, dammit!
I can't see a thing
with you hanging on
so tight! Chopper!
[USOPP yelling]
[USOPP]
Kung Fu Dugongs?
[CHOPPER] They say they
were just looking out for
their fellow pupils.
[USOPP]
Pupils?
What, they think Luffy's
our master? Please.
[VIVI] You really want
to argue with them?
[USOPP]
Hang in there, little guys!
Just a little further!
Thanks a lot!
[CHOPPER]
Bye‐bye!
Now that things
are going smoothly,
can we make it in time?
[VIVI]
I don't know.
Even riding Eyelash,
I'm not sure when
we would get there.
[USOPP] Not to be pessimistic,
but Eyelash can only
carry two of us.
If Baroque Works
is going to attack us,
it'll be from here on,
so we can't split up.
Isn't there any way
for us to stick together?
Damn. This isn't good.
Look! Over there!
What is it now?
Is it the enemy?
Don't tell me they're
here to kill us already!
No wait! That sound!
Karoo!
[KAROO squawks]
[VIVI] And the Supersonic
Duck Squadron!
[VIVI] You've come to
help us, haven't you?
[KAROO, DUCK SQUADRON squawk]
[VIVI]
Karoo!
[LUFFY coughs]
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
Meat!
[LUFFY coughs]
[CROCODILE]
We may both be pirates.
But you fall grossly
short on skill.
This sand storm will
deal Yuba a final,
destructive blow.
Fanning the flames of anger
within the rebel army
until an inferno ignites.
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY grunts]
Thank... Thank you.
Why do you fight?
Those of you with
the name of "D."
"D"?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Who are you people?
What are your intentions?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY] Apparently,
you don't have a clue
what I'm talking about.
[PELL]
I found you!
Where is Vivi?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
My.
Awake already?
[PELL] Now that I've
studied your ability,
this won't turn out
like it did last time!
Be careful, Pell.
Don't wanna overexert yourself.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Perfect timing.
Why don't you save
the boy before he dies?
[LUFFY grunting]
After all, if it weren't
for his courage
and selflessness, who knows
if your precious princess
would've made
it back alive at all.
It must please you
to know Vivi's safe.
That even as we speak,
she's on her way to Alubarna.
Though it's a long trip,
and anything could happen.
Guess the situation
is what it is.
[ALLIGATOR growls]
[PELL] If I'm not able to
stop her, then who can?
Vivi must be protected
for everyone's sake!
[LUFFY growls]
Meat!
[KOZA]
Damn you, Cobra!
My brethren and I are
willing to defend Alabasta
with every last drop
of blood in our bodies.
We will die before
turning it over to you!
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[ROYAL SOLDIER E]
Hurry! Step lively!
Stack it up higher!
[ROYAL SOLDIER F]
Get the cannons ready at
the southern gate!
Stop dawdling around and focus!
[ROYAL SOLDIER G] We need
more cannonballs over here!
[ROYAL SOLDIER A]
Chaka!
The enemy's number is said
to be well over two million!
Tell me, soldier, what do
you think of His Majesty's
attack on Nanohana?
I have served his Majesty
for over ten years
and I was quite surprised.
You're right.
There's really no way
anyone could rationalize it.
Logic would suggest something
has happened to the king.
If true...
It is all the more reason
why we must not
lose this fight.
Bury your fear deep.
For your King's sake.
As well as that
of Princess Vivi!
We will defend this
country at all cost!
[ROYAL SOLDIER A] Everyone
who is not prepared to fight
take shelter outside the city!
We cannot guarantee your
safety if you elect to stay!
[TOWNSFOLK A]
Run!
If we don't get outta here,
we'll be in the line of fire!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] Things
are getting hectic down there,
I see.
But it's still moving too slow.
Hurry up and fight already!
I can't stand waiting!
[MR. 4 laughing]
I can't take this.
I really don't care if he is
or isn't the king.
I'm gonna go outta my mind
if I have to stand here
guarding him any longer.
Cant. Can't. Can't take this.
[MR. 4]
Four!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
I mean, sure, slipping past
the palace guards
and kidnapping this royal
pain‐in‐the‐rear is a
mission which only a team
of our accomplished
skills could pull off.
But, now that it's over,
this assignment has
become a tedious bore!
Right, Mr. 4?
Did anything I said
manage to seep through
that thick head of yours?
Slow, you're so slow.
[MR. 4 groans]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
My back is killing me!
[COBRA]
Chaka. Koza.
You mustn't fight.
The two of you embody the
spirit of this great country.
Divided, you only
weaken her resolve.
[NARRATOR] There are those
who lament war...
[REBELS, SOLDIERS yelling]
[NARRATOR] ...and those
who race towards it.
Just go ahead and run away.
[MR. 4]
Four!
[NARRATOR]
Still, others incite war.
But for the very few
who know the truth,
they strive to prevent it.
These widely opposing viewpoints
all have one thing in common.
They are about to clash,
here in the capital
city of Alubarna.
[IGARAM]
Ma! Ma‐ma!
So, the final revolt has begun.
There was a lone ship.
Hopefully that means
Princess Vivi and the others
were able to make it
to Alabasta in one piece.
I must hurry.
I pray there's still time.
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[USOPP]
I see it! There's Alubarna!
[ZORO]
Let's go! Everyone ready?
[CHOPPER]
Yeah!
[NAMI] The rebel army
is all yours, Vivi.
[VIVI]
If I don't stop them now,
then all that we've done
will be for naught!
Please, everyone!
You must listen to what
I have to say! Leader!
[KOZA]
I thought I just heard a voice.
Am I imagining things?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Rebel Army vs. Royal Army!
Showdown at Alubarna!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!