Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[YORKI]
Laboon!
Once we travel the world,
we're comin' right back here!
You just wait for us!
[LABOON vocalizes]
[BROOK] Laboon, thank you
for waiting for us.
I know that 50 years
is a long time.
But please, do you think
you could be patient
for one or two more?
[BROOK]
I have my pride as a pirate.
I promised you I would see you
again after circling the globe.
I intend to keep my word and
return from the right direction.
[LUFFY]
A New Crewmate!
The Musician, Humming Brook!
[ROLLING PIRATE 381A]
Hey, Skeleton!
[ROLLING PIRATE 381B]
You ain't singing anymore?
[ROLLING PIRATE 381C]
One more song!
Come on!
[BROOK]
Yoho!
When this was recorded,
my comrades and I
knew the end was near.
But we sang our hearts out
because this would be the
Rumbar Pirate's swan song.
For over fifty years
I sailed alone,
drifting aimlessly
in that dark, misty sea.
Hearing this song
was my only comfort.
All alone on that giant ship.
This made me feel human.
In that sad and lonely place,
it was my only link
to other people.
But now, I will
proceed with a new strength
and I can seal
this Tone Dial away
until it can finally
fulfill its original purpose.
Goodbye!
Whoa!
He did that weird
head thing again!
[LUFFY laughing]
[piano music]
I'm glad to hear
that Laboon is well
and still waiting for me.
My shadow has returned, and
we're leaving the Devil's Sea.
And although
the voices in this dial
kept me sane all those years,
I must remember that
it was not for my sake
that they were first recorded.
This is a song for Laboon
to remember his old friends.
[BROOK] Every day on
that boat was difficult,
and there was no end in sight.
Frankly, I'd given up all hope.
But Luffy, you know what?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
I'm... so...
I'm so glad
to still be alive!
[BROOK sobbing]
[BROOK] I'm so glad
I never gave up.
No matter how hard it was!
Well, of course, right?
[BROOK] I've waited so long
for this day to come!
[BROOK sobbing]
Ah...
So does the offer to join
your crew still stand?
[LUFFY]
Yeah, welcome aboard.
What? Just like that?
For real?
[screaming]
[laughing]
[USOPP]
But good to have you!
We finally got our musician!
[LUFFY] He may be all bones,
but he sure knows how to play!
I've been wanting a
musician since forever!
[CHOPPER] He had a heavy heart,
but he's light as a feather!
[USOPP] By the way, what do
you call a singing skeleton?
Yeah, tell us, Brook!
A natural bone singer!
[laughing]
[BROOK]
"Bone," get it?
--It's funny because...
--[LUFFY] He's so funny!
Do you get it?
It's funny!
[NAMI]
Yeah, I got it.
The crew certainly
is lively now, huh?
Why do we always
have to attract those types?
So noisy.
[LOLA] I don't know
what's going on,
but congratulations, Namizo!
Uh, thanks, I guess.
I don't know
what's going on, but...
Cheers!
I'm confused, too, but...
45 degrees!
[laughing]
[BROOK]
Laboon.
[LABOON vocalizing]
[BROOK] I won't turn back,
not after coming so far.
I may have been
sidetracked for a while,
but I'm headed
straight forward again.
All the way around the world,
back to Twin Cape, so far away.
Because I know
you'll be waiting for me,
and I have to keep my promise.
Both to you and my crew.
So I will see this
to the end no matter what.
So wait for me.
Just a little bit longer.
[LABOON vocalizing]
Huh?
Hey, Laboon. What's wrong?
[cheering]
[LABOON vocalizing]
Well you seem to
be in high spirits today.
I wonder why.
[LABOON vocalizing]
Yohohohoho!
[BROOK]
Take a look at this.
[FRANKY]
Huh?
A wanted poster?
You mean you already
have a bounty on you?
[BROOK] Pardon me for
not introducing myself
properly before.
I am known as Dead Bones Brook,
and I'm a wanted man.
My nickname is
"The Humming Swordsman."
I have a bounty of 33
million berries on my head.
I was the leader
of a battle convoy
in the kingdom of my origin.
Afterwards, I served
as a musician and swordsman
in the Rumbar Pirates,
later succeeding Yorki
as captain of the crew
until their demise.
But now, I pledge
my life and my services
to Captain Monkey D. Luffy
of the Straw Hat Pirates.
I shall do my best
to make you proud.
That is to say...
I shall work myself to the bone!
Yohohohoho!
All right!
One more toast!
Raise your glasses!
[BROOK]
Yohohohoho!
How splendid!
Thank you Franky, Usopp.
It's perfect!
No prob, bro.
I can make one of these
any day of the week!
But it was my design,
just so ya know.
Yeah, but I picked
out the flowers!
Thank you so much, Chopper.
They're lovely.
Oh you boney bastard!
Flattery won't get you
anywhere with me!
[BROOK] But truly.
It's a beautiful memorial.
And this is
certainly for the best,
since I could scarcely
bring all of those bones
onto Mr. Lion with me.
[FRANKY] Okay, but
it's "Thousand Sunny,"
not "Mr. Lion!"
[BROOK] You know,
by happy coincidence,
Thriller Bark originally
came from the West Blue,
just like the Rumbar Pirates.
Despite the troubles
this ship brought me, I...
I hope my friends
will rest peacefully
in the soil of their homeland.
[USOPP] We're gonna
head back now, Brook.
We'll see you soon.
[FRANKY]
Glad you like it.
[CHOPPER]
Bye-bye.
[BROOK]
Thank you.
[violin playing 'Binks' Brew']
[violin continues]
Goodness, you gave me a fright.
You were out for quite a while--
are you feeling better?
[ZORO]
Yeah.
I overslept a bit.
[BROOK]
And what is that?
[ZORO]
A dead sword, Yubashiri.
I'm laying it to rest here, too.
Luffy is the man who will
become King of the Pirates!
[BROOK]
Uhm...
[ZORO]
What is it?
No, nothing.
Oh, uh, in case
you hadn't heard,
I officially joined the crew.
[ZORO]
Heh, I see.
Well, that's too bad
for you, now, isn't it?
[BROOK]
Huh?
This crew can be
a real handful, that's all.
Yohohoho!
So it would seem,
but I'll give them my blood
and sweat all the same--
except I don't have any,
since I'm a skeleton.
[LUFFY] Zoro's up,
so on to our next adventure!
Come on, it's time to set sail!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Hey!
Zoro, you took off
your bandages!
[ZORO]
Of course I did!
They made it hard to move.
That's the point!
You're supposed to
sit still and heal!
--[CHOPPER] C'mere!
--Setting off already?
I'm sorry you can't
stick around.
Whenever you feel like leaving,
you can take Brook's ship.
I fixed the rudder
and the sails for you.
[LOLA]
It's wonderful.
I can't thank you enough
for all you've done.
It might take
the rest of my life
for me to pay you back,
but I'm willing to try.
In other words, what do you
say you and I get married?
Sorry babe, you're
a gem, but it won't work out.
I'm afraid I'm just
too super to settle down.
I really hate
to see you take off.
You sure you don't wanna
stick around and party
--for a few more days?
--[LUFFY] No way!
We're off to Fishman Island and
it's gonna be totally awesome!
Fish dudes!
There's gonna be fish dudes!
Screw the fish dudes!
There're gonna be mermaids!
I'm gonna flirt
with all of them!
Ah, I wonder if the
mermaids we encounter
would be so gracious
as to show me their panties.
Hey man, don't be dumb.
Think about what you're sayin!
Mermaids don't wear any panties!
[RISKY BRO BROWN HAIR]
And I'm tellin' ya.
Mermaids are so gorgeous,
they even give the
Pirate Empress Hancock
a run for her money!
[SANJI and BROOK]
Mermaids, yeah!
Mermaids are fish
from the waist down.
Why do you guys know
so much about Fishman Island?
Oh, well,
couple 'a years back
before we got stuck in this
hellhole, we took a trip there.
You are gonna love it!
Wow Lola, I didn't realize
you went to the
New World already!
[LOLA] We didn't go there,
you big silly,
we came from there
in the first place!
My Momma's a pirate
just like me, y'know!
Oh. That reminds me.
Here, you should take this.
It's my momma's Vivre Card.
[NAMI]
A piece of paper?
Whoa, hang on to that one.
One of the greatest pirates
I've ever met in my life
is Lola's mom!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[RISKY BRO MASK]
That'll come in handy someday!
Not just anybody
gets one of those!
Sorry, but what's
a Vivre Card again?
What? You guys don't know?
C'mon Captain,
don't be insensitive.
They only make Vivre Cards
in the New World!
Oh, I forgot about that.
Anyway, this is no normal paper.
You can wet it or burn it
but it won't change.
If you take a
piece of your fingernail
to the shop
where they make these,
they'll use it to create
a personalized piece of paper.
Just like this one.
Because of their use,
they also call Vivre Cards
"Life Paper" sometimes.
The idea is to tear off a piece
and give it to your
family or friends
when you go on a journey.
Uh-huh? And then what?
[LOLA]
Take a look.
This is the Vivre Card
I got from my momma.
[NAMI]
Ah! It's moving!
[LOLA] No matter where in the
world these scraps of paper are,
they're drawn to each other.
So long as I have this,
I know what direction
Momma is in.
It doesn't tell you the
distance, though, I'm afraid.
Whoa, that's so neat!
I bet there's a bunch
of crazy stuff like that
in the New World, huh?
Well, I don't know
about "crazy,"
but it certainly is handy.
Anyway, I'm signing the
piece of my Momma's Vivre Card,
so if you're ever in trouble,
you can use it to find her
and she'll help you out.
If that ever happens,
be sure to tell her
that I'm doing fine, okay?
Wow, thanks, Lola.
Hey, hold on, don't I have
one of those already?
Huh?
I almost forgot, but Ace
gave you something like this
a long time ago.
You remember that, right?
That scrap of paper
will reunite us someday.
[LUFFY]
So that's what it was.
This is it, but...
Huh, that's weird.
I thought you said
these things couldn't burn.
[yelling]
Are you kidding?
Let me see that!
[LOLA] This is definitely
a Vivre Card,
but there's something I
neglected to tell you before.
The life force of the owner
is also reflected on the paper.
Does this belong
to someone close to you?
Yeah!
It's my big brother's.
Lola?
[LOLA]
I'm sorry to say this,
but your brother's life is
in terrible danger right now.
--Bye!
--Bye bye!
See ya! Good luck!
We owe you our lives!
We won't forget what
you've done, Straw Hat!
Thank you
for giving us the sun!
Take care!
Don't get annihilated out there.
That would be very bad!
Yohohohoho!
Why would you
even say that?
Are you out of your mind?
Bye Lola, and thanks
for the Vivre Card!
I'll miss you!
I hope we
meet again someday!
If you see my momma,
tell her I said hi, Namizo!
[LUFFY]
Set sail!
Well, I guess
they're gone now.
Yeah.
[LOLA] Hm? Looks like
the fog's come back.
We set sail tomorrow!
[ROLLING PIRATES]
Roger!
[NARRATOR] No one knows
the truth behind
what happens in this Sea of
Mysteries, the Florian Triangle.
Each year, over 100 ships sail
into the mists, never to return.
The giant ship, Thriller Bark,
first dropped anchor in these
dark waters 10 years ago,
but the tales of terror
and disappearances
came long before then.
Perhaps it is fortunate
that the thick mist
is abundant
on this day as well,
cloaking the terrors of
these mysterious waters
like a white veil.
[NAMI]
Luffy...
Huh?
You sure you're okay with this?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Oh right,
you mean Ace's paper.
Eh, he'll be fine.
Don't worry about it.
Luffy, we can take
a detour, if you like.
I wouldn't mind.
[BROOK] Time has proven
to be no obstacle
to either me or Laboon.
So long as I draw breath, I
know we'll be reunited someday.
[USOPP]
Yeah, it's fine!
You do what you want, Captain,
we don't care one bit!
Yeah, I'm ready to go anywhere!
I wanna meet Luffy's
bro and the big whale bro!
Seriously, it's okay.
Even if Ace was
in some kinda trouble,
he wouldn't want his little
brother to come bail him out.
That'd drive him crazy.
He hates to show his weak side
and he never asks for help.
If I saved his life,
he'd probably just get mad.
[LUFFY] As pirates, we're
supposed to be rivals anyway.
His adventures are his business,
even if they turn out bad.
Well, keep your hopes up.
Lola's pals were saying
the card doesn't just shrink
when someone's in trouble.
It also grows bigger
if things get better for them.
Good.
Then I'll see him again when
he's back to full strength!
I'm sure that's
what he was thinking
when he gave me
that card, right?
Oh yeah, Zoro.
You were asleep
for the big party
so I guess you
missed out on this.
Well, no harm in doing it
one more time, right?
Let's all raise our mugs
in celebration
of our newest crewmember,
the musician, Brook!
[ALL]
Cheers!
[BROOK]
Really, you're too kind!
[LUFFY]
Full speed ahead!
Let's get moving
with a Coup de Burst!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[FRANKY]
Coup de Burst!
We're flying!
What's going on?
[NAMI] Blue water
and a beautiful sun!
This is the life!
[LUFFY] Cool! They got
a bunch of neat stuff here!
[FOXY]
Fehfehfehfeh!
[LUFFY]
Hey! It's splithead!
[FOXY]
Who you calling splithead?
I'm gonna put an end
to your wise cracks
with my amazing new technique!
On the next One Piece:
"The Slow-Slow Menace!
Silver Fox Foxy Returns!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!