[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
Luffy has returned to Marineford
with Rayleigh and
Jimbei at his side.
For what reason
did they go back,
and why did Luffy
ring the Ox Bell?
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[NARRATOR] On a certain
island along the Grand Line.
[BUGGY PIRATES crying]
[MOHJI] Times have been rough
since you got locked up!
We couldn't even sleep at night,
but we knew we had
to get you back somehow!
[CABAJI] We sailed all
over in search of you,
surviving countless hardships
along the way, but then!
We saw our very own captain
a hero in the newspaper!
[RICHIE crying]
[BUGGY PIRATES crying]
Welcome back!
Finally!
[CABAJI]
We're with you till the end!
A little wait like
that is nothing!
Our very own Captain Buggy,
leading us into the New World!
I didn't know you guys
cared about me so much!
I missed all of you, too!
[BOTH]
Captain!
[ALL crying]
Buncha liars.
I seem to recall you
giving up on him.
[CABAJI, MOHJI, RICHIE]
Shh!
[BUGGY]
Eh?
[PRISONERS cheering]
[MOHJI]
Welcome to the crew, fellas!
I'm the first mate of the Buggy
Pirates, Beast Tamer Mohji!
[PRISONERS]
Brother Mohji!
And I'm the Chief
of Staff, Cabaji!
[PRISONERS]
Brother Cabaji!
And this here's my buddy,
the one and only Richie!
[RICHIE roars]
[PRISONERS]
Richie!
Impressive. Looks like
what the paper said
about your new followers
turned out to be true.
Though I'm almost
afraid to ask how
you got so many infamous
criminals to follow you.
[BUGGY laughs]
Give me some credit!
Clearly, when it
comes to scoundrels,
I'm a natural born leader!
Oh, by the way, I picked
up a little something
on my trip that you
might find interesting.
Huh?
[BUGGY]
Ta-dah!
It can't be.
Very nice! You finally found
Captain John's armband, huh?
Sure did!
Don't leave me in suspense.
How did you get
your hands on this?
[BUGGY] That idiot
Straw Hat gave it to me
without a second thought!
[BUGGY laughs]
Everything's comin' up flashy.
The wind is blowin' my way!
Could it be? Buggy was meant
to be King of the Pirates?
Oh, speaking of Straw Hat--
He's still making a name
for himself after the war.
[BUGGY snorts]
Hah?
[ALVIDA]
You didn't know?
He caused quite a stir
returning to Marineford.
[BUGGY gasps]
You're kidding me!
He was barely alive when
I last saw him, and now this?
Huh. Let's see.
"'First Son of the Sea' Jimbei
teams up with Straw Hat.
Dark King Rayleigh joins them."
Rayleigh?
[screams]
This is a joke, right?
Since when did Rayleigh get
involved with Straw Hat?
[BUGGY sputtering]
This just keeps
on getting messier.
I can't wrap my head
around this at all!
Wait a sec.
If I'm remembering it correctly,
Straw Hat's pop is the
Revolutionary, Dragon.
On top of that,
his grandpa's Garp.
It could only mean one thing.
[snorts] Rayleigh, must be
Straw Hat's long-lost uncle!
Hey, Buggy!
[gasps]
[BAT squeaks]
A carrier bat brought a message
for you from the government.
How did they find me?
Did someone rat me out?
The Navy must be
trying to strike me down
before I'm too strong!
Which means the message
is my final warning!
Hey! Give me that letter!
[MR. 3]
It can't be!
This is simply unbelievable!
Hey, that's for me! Stop it!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
at the Sabaody Archipelago,
along the Grand Line,
the Thousand Sunny
waits for its crew,
anchored at Grove number 44.
[COFFEE MONKEY A]
Either you hand over the ship,
or we bust your faces in!
You can't fool us.
We know it belongs to Straw Hat
and we know he's Dragon's son!
The Navy's bound to pay
good money for it,
so walk away and
we won't hurt ya!
[GROUP gasping]
Since you and I are in
the same line of work,
give it up now and you'll
get a cut of the profit!
Easy, right?
How about it,
Flying Fish Riders?
[DUVAL]
Hmm.
What? I'm handsome?
I didn't say that, weirdo!
We're through with
playin' around!
[DUVAL] You punks ain't
gettin' nothin' from me!
[COFFEE MONKEYS groans]
[DUVAL grunting]
Ugh. Enough of this!
[COFFEE MONKEYS gasping]
[COFFEE MONKEY A grunting]
Listen up, ya losers.
I, the very handsome Duval,
refuse to let a bunch of ugly
fools like you become popular!
Uh, I mean try to steal our
friend's ship on my watch!
Stay unpopular!
Well, as long as he protects
the ship, we're okay.
[DUVAL] You won't touch
this ship as long as I live!
And before I die,
I'm gonna touch a girl!
I mean, if you touch it,
you're gonna die!
The ship, I mean, not the girl.
The bottom line is you're
not getting near the Sunny!
But if you want a fight,
come and get it!
[FLYING FISH RIDERS]
Yeah! Tough guy!
[COFFEE MONKEY A]
C'mon, let's book it!
Wow, Duval! Nice one!
[DUVAL gasps]
Girls won't leave me alone
because I'm so handsome!
[FLYING FISH RIDERS]
Woo, woo!
Thanks for the support.
I love you, too--
Mermaid Café should obviously be
the first stop, don't you think?
It's so in style!
Nah. Once they get back, the
first place they'll wanna see
is the Fishman Karate
training hall!
[PAPPAGU]
Wait a minute!
I already promised Brook
I'd introduce him
to the Mermaid Princess!
Hey, Boss, it's like she doesn't
even know you're there!
I can wait. That's cool.
Oh, I almost forgot to ask.
The Straw Hats can
use their Vivre Cards
to get back here, right?
Now that we all know Luffychin's
alive, they should be here soon!
Maybe.
If they're far away,
it might take them a while,
but Ray found Monkey easy
enough with his Vivre card.
[SHAKKY] Until then,
we have to protect this ship.
Don't you worry, 'cause we're
here to do exactly that!
Whether it's the Navy
or somebody else.
Nobody is gonna take the ship!
[SHAKKY chuckles]
So far you're doing great!
--[FLYING FISH RIDERS yelling]
--[GROUP] Hmm?
[FISH RIDER B] Hey Duval,
we've got a huge problem!
Kuma's heading this way!
Kuma?
Do I know a Kuma?
Oh, right!
[FISH RIDER B screams] It's the
Warlord, Bartholomew Kuma!
[DUVAL grunts]
[HACHI growls]
Relax, everyone.
That man...
He came to speak
with Ray before.
So tell me, Kuma,
whose side are you on?
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, on Sandy Island,
part of Alabasta Kingdom
on the Grand Line.
[NARRATOR]
The capital city, Alubarna.
[COBRA]
What happened to the pirates?
We chased them away.
The city is virtually undamaged.
[COBRA]
I see. Good job.
[PELL] We're strengthening
security across the country.
Ever since Whitebeard's death,
pirates around the world
are more active.
Our region is no exception.
We have to careful
for the time being.
[COBRA] If only all pirates
were like Straw Hat Luffy
and his crew.
But such is not the case.
[PELL] Speaking of Luffy, have
you read today's newspaper?
[COBRA]
Yes, I did.
[IGARAM gasps]
Vivi was ecstatic when she read
about Luffy and the others.
Heh. Of course she was.
But...
[VIVI]
Karoo!
[squawks]
[VIVI]
Take a look at this!
[KAROO squawks]
[VIVI]
Thank goodness!
Luffy is still alive!
I'm so glad! I just
knew he'd be okay!
Huh? What?
Within a single moment,
her entire demeanor changed,
and all of her joy
suddenly vanished.
She took the newspaper
and ran towards her room.
[VIVI] Huh... What's that
on Luffy's arm? Numbers?
Is it a code?
Well, it's not a tattoo, right?
That doesn't really seem
like Luffy's style, does it?
[KAROO squawks]
[VIVI grunts]
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, in another city,
in another country,
along the Grand Line.
[CROWD gasps, murmurs]
Whoa! Hey!
What's a hard-core pirate
like him doing on our island?
Hush! He can hear you!
[CROCODILE] It's only been
three weeks since the war.
They were lucky to escape
death at Marineford.
What the hell would
bring them back there?
Straw Hat's probably
cooking up some plan.
Either that, or he's just crazy.
That sounds about right. Heh.
[MR. 1] He was badly injured
in the fight, though.
Takes someone pretty special
to get back on their
feet so quickly.
[chuckles] You sayin'
I'm slower than Straw Hat?
Trying to challenge
your old boss?
[CROCODILE]
I'm done resting, don't worry.
There's no point in
stayin' here any longer.
It's time to set out
for the New World.
Are you comin', Daz?
Of course I am.
[NARRATOR] The news of
Luffy's latest exploits,
as well as his return
to Marineford,
quickly spread to each
crewmember's hometown.
[DADAN]
Get a load of this, Ace!
You saved your
little brother's life.
Luffy is alive!
[crying]
Rest in peace, you brat!
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, on the Grand Line.
[LUFFY] Really sorry you had
to go so far out of your way.
It's nothing. We're pretty
used to being away from home.
[LUFFY]
Um, what are you doing?
Huh? We're making sure
that you're resting properly,
of course!
Orders from the
Snake Princess herself!
[RAN]
But she couldn't stay because
she collapsed from a severe
case of heart-fluttering.
So here we are,
keeping a close eye on you!
[AMAZONS giggle]
I hope they get the message...
wherever they are.
They'll understand if
they see the article.
Obviously, this isn't something
you would do on a whim.
Would you stop, please?
That said, your swordsman
can be a bit daft.
Still, I think he'll
figure it out somehow.
They are your crew after all.
If anyone can understand
you, it's them.
[NARRATOR] Above the
Grand Line, high in the air.
[gasps, yells]
[BIRD A squawks]
[CHOPPER]
I got it, Luffy! Don't worry!
A change of plans, then!
Yeah, okay, okay!
[NARRATOR] On the giant bridge
reaching across the East Blue.
So, that's it. Very well, then.
Something in the paper again?
Good news, I hope.
[ROBIN]
Hm.
Interesting as always.
Luffy.
[NARRATOR]
And in Kamabakka Kingdom.
[QUEENS laughing]
Roger that, Captain!
[IVANKOV]
What's going on?
[IVANKOV gasping]
[NARRATOR]
The Bowin Islands.
[USOPP panting]
[USOPP]
I...
I gotta find a way off.
I gotta find a way
off this island!
[USOPP grunts]
[USOPP]
Ouch!
Oh! I'm so sick of this!
[USOPP groans]
[panting] Get away from me.
I don't care what
you have to say.
One way or another,
I'm gonna get to Luffy,
even if it kills me!
Look at that! I think I made it!
Is that the shore?
[HERACLES]
You've barely gone 50 feet.
[USOPP]
No!
Damn it!
Why does everything here
have to be so delicious?
I'm still hungry!
[HERACLES]
Stop it, Usopp'n!
You're already
dangerously obese'n!
Don't give in to
the island's trap!
Can't you see I'm busy?
[BOTH gasp]
Huh?
[USOPP]
I've got it!
[HERACLES]
What is it this time, Usopp'n?
Yes, Luffy! Yes!
[USOPP crying]
[NARRATOR]
The Sky Island, Weatheria.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, young lady!
Where ya running off to?
[NAMI]
Shh! Not now!
[HAREDAS] Well, I thought
you should know that
they closed the Balloon Terminal
after you tried to escape.
And since the island's so small,
there's nowhere to run.
Well, you better come up
with something quick then!
I have to get away from here!
I know I'm your hostage,
but why don't we go back
to my place for a while?
[NAMI]
Huh?
[gasps]
[HAREDAS grunting]
Hey, hey, why don't
we go inside already?
[NAMI]
Shh!
Now that is interesting.
But honestly, Luffy!
How about how I feel, huh?
You're so selfish!
Better hurry, young lady,
they're coming this way!
[NARRATOR]
Future Land Baldimore.
Hey, Grandpa,
think something bad
happened to Mr. Frank?
I'm sorry, Kitton.
It's too late now.
Just forget the whole incident.
You'll be better off.
That explosion was massive.
There's no way he's still alive.
And I told him not to press that
self-destruct button repeatedly.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasping]
[FRANKY]
One, two, three!
[KITTON'S GRANDFATHER,
KITTON yell]
[FRANKY]
Whoa, heh, that was a doozy!
[KITTON yells]
You're alive!
[FRANKY]
Huh... Uh-huh.
[KITTON giggles]
I gotcha, boss.
[BOTH screaming]
[NARRATOR]
The Tehna Gehna Kingdom.
[CROWD cheering]
I don't have time
to dawdle around
while my friends
are still out there.
--[LONGARM A] Hey!
--Huh?
Are you done eating yet?
Lemme have those plates.
[BROOK]
Oh, go ahead.
Also, I think I asked you
gentlemen for the newspaper.
There might be a follow-up story
about my friend
that I'd like to read.
Surely you understand?
Real funny!
You don't even have eyes
in that empty head of yours.
How the hell are
you supposed to read?
I may joke about my appearance,
but it's hurtful when
someone else does it!
Too bad, freak show!
You're up soon, so get ready.
Here.
[BROOK gasps]
It's Luffy!
Greetings! Feast your eyes,
ladies and gentlemen,
on these magnificent
living bones!
[CROWD cheers]
Ah, hah. How very clever of you!
No need to worry, Luffy.
I understand. [chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
The ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
[PERONA]
You gonna sleep there forever?
Would you get up!
Quit trying to leave!
Do you like getting stomped
by a bunch of baboons?
Look at it from my side.
I've got to take care of you!
Leave me alone, will ya?
[gasps] Very well!
I guess you don't need this!
I brought today's newspaper
from the News Coo
because I thought you
might wanna read it!
[ZORO grunts]
[PERONA]
Aren't I considerate?
There's an update
on your captain, too,
but you don't care.
What?!
[ZORO groaning]
The paper! You have
to give it to me!
[PERONA yells]
Okay, okay!
You're freakin' me out!
[PERONA]
Hey, are you done yet?
My hands are getting tired!
[ZORO]
Hold on a sec!
There's something going on here.
Normally, Luffy wouldn't
do something like this.
Rayleigh's with him, so it
must be some idea he cooked up.
There's gotta be a catch here.
I don't care, just
hurry it up, will ya?
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO groans]
[NARRATOR] Luffy's crew
receives his message.
Meanwhile, a battle to become
one of the Four Emperors
breaks out among pirates
now in the New World.
As the fighting intensifies,
a Navy admiral appears
to wipe out the pirates.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Pirates Get on the Move!
Astounding New World!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!