Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR] The Straw Hat
Pirates left Water 7
and set sail for the New World.
While en route,
they came across a strange ship
with a tired and hungry crew.
The Straw Hats took them in,
but were met with a surprise.
[JIRO] There's someone else
I need you to take a look at!
[CHOPPER] Is--Is that him?
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
[CAMPACINO] What is it?
[SALCHOW] The trophies are
being cornered as we speak.
[CAMPACINO] Oh?
[CAMPACINO]
Well, well, well!
What fortunate timing.
To hell with the mission!
We won't do it!
We'll take this ship
and launch a counterattack!
If we don't, Vigaro's
death will be in vain!
[FRANKY] Hey, guys!
I'm not really the type to go
looking for an apology, but...
...you should
probably give me one
after making up that lame story.
[LUFFY]
Sunny in a Pinch!
Roar, Secret Superspeed Mecha!
[STANSEN] Whoa! Whoa!
Let's just calm down here, okay?
Look, we're not a bunch
of criminals or anything!
We're just some common,
ordinary fishermen!
Right, guys? Right?
[laughs nervously]
And you really expect
us to buy that crap?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but trying to drug
a bunch of pirates
doesn't sound like something
"common, ordinary fishermen"
would do, now does it?
[FRANKY] You better
get your story straight,
because it's time to tell us
what the hell's going on here.
[STANSEN]
Please! Let's not be hasty!
If we discuss this
like civilized people,
I'm sure we could work this out.
Or not.
--"Or not"?
Uh... I mean--
Hey! What are you doing?
Get back here!
[STANSEN] Guyle! Stop it!
[GUYLE] There's no point in
negotiating with these people!
There're only three of them!
Let's take this ship by force!
Yeah!
Then we could finally
be a proper crew again!
I'm sick and tired of being
a pawn for those bastards!
No! Wait a minute!
These guys helped us out
when we were tired and hungry!
He's right!
There's no need to--
Shut up!
If you aren't going
to help us fight,
then we'll do it on our own!
All right, but at least
leave the lady out of this!
Yeah!
She's too pretty to hurt!
--Yahhh!
So much for "discussing
this like civilized people".
Glad we've got
everything out in the open!
[yelling]
I said stop it, dammit!
Whoa!
What the hell?
Sorry about that!
I know all this must look
very underhanded and shady,
but, uh--I assure all of you.
We have the very
best of intentions!
Right? Right? See?
[laughs nervously]
Cut the crap!
What are you guys
trying to hide?
Our patience is starting
to wear pretty thin here.
I'm freezing!
Come on, haven't you guys taken
care of these morons yet?
[NAMI] I knew there
was something suspicious
about all this.
Seriously.
You look more like a bunch of
thugs than some fishermen.
Geez!
[NAMI] Did you really
think you could fool us?
We're way too smart for that!
Well, most of us are.
So what now, Stansen?
[RACE] We're screwed!
Now. You better start talking.
It seems you've
left us no choice.
[STANSEN] Retreat!
What?!
[splash]
--[FRANKY] Get back here!
--[SANJI] Cowards!
[FRANKY] Dammit!
If you guys don't wanna talk,
then I'll just have to blast ya!
Forget about it.
Just let 'em go.
We have other things
to worry about.
Like Chopper.
I can't find him anywhere.
[SANJI] What? Chopper?
Wait. Yeah, where is he?
You don't think something
happened to him, do you?
He may have been abducted
by those fake fishermen.
I hate to say it,
but I think you're right.
Sneaky bastards.
It's just a hunch
at this point,
but boarding their ship
will be the fastest way
to get to the bottom of this.
Let's get moving.
The wind's starting to pick up.
We'll be getting
a storm anytime now.
Before we go,
we need to figure out
what to do with these two.
[NAMI]
Ugh! Those nitwits!
--[NAMI] Wake up!
--[punching noises]
[LUFFY] Man! I'm freezing
my butt off out here!
Cold...
But that doesn't explain
why my head hurts so much.
Ah... ah... ah...
Ah-choo!
[SALCHOW] What?
I told you not to
underestimate those pirates!
Imbecile!
Our plan was going so
well and you ruined it!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to--
[sneezes]
We'll get 'em next time!
[SALCHOW] Whatever!
It doesn't matter anymore.
--I want you to stand down.
--[STANSEN] Huh?
[SALCHOW] You heard me.
I said to stand down.
From the start,
you useless cowards
haven't done anything but
screw up and get in the way.
So stand down.
Are we clear?
[STANSEN] Yes. Crystal.
Right! You got it!
[laughs]
Yes. Yes.
Roger that.
Very well then. Standing down.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Click.
[SALCHOW] Listen up, men.
There's been a change of plans.
It's time to use Trap Seagull.
[STANSEN'S MEN] Yes, sir!
[USOPP sneezes]
Sneaky crybabies!
We lend them a hand,
then all they do is kidnap our--
[USOPP sneezes]
Chopper!
A-ha! There you are!
What have you done with Chopper?
[STANSEN] Straw Hat Captain!
I sincerely apologize for
abusing your hospitality.
But this is where we part ways!
We what?
Hey! Hold on!
What do you think
you're doing? Stop!
[SANJI] This is bad!
He's gonna cut the tow rope
that connects our ships!
[ALL] What?
Dammit! Wait!
Now, Gum-Gum Pistol!
The wind!
[LUFFY yelling]
Oh, crap!
Devil Fruit powers!
Sorry, but it's time
for you to go!
What the--?
Nice, Robin!
Way to go!
Another crewmember
with Devil Fruit powers?
[ACCINO HENCHMAN 327A]
Mr. Salchow.
Preparations for Trap Seagull
are now complete.
[SALCHOW] Good. Good.
Then let's get
this started, shall we?
Showtime!
What the--?
Music?
Hey, you guys hearing
what I'm hearing?
It's coming from this way.
I hear it, too. Weird.
Something's coming.
[USOPP] What's that?
No way!
The Marines are here!
[ALL] What?
How the hell'd they
track us down so fast?
Perfect! Just what we need!
[USOPP] Gahh! No!
[LUFFY] Get us outta here, Nami!
[NAMI] Right! I'm on it!
[USOPP] Go away!
[ACCINO HENCHMAN 327B] The Straw
Hat ship is on the move, sir!
[SALCHOW]
Let's shake things up a bit.
Do it!
[ACCINO HENCHMAN 327A]
Sir!
[explosions]
We're under attack!
They're shooting at us!
Nami, hurry!
They're gonna blow us to bits!
I know, I know!
Stop yelling!
Sanji!
[SANJI] Aye-aye!
[SALCHOW]
Hahaha!
And now...
...light 'em up!
Light 'em up! Light 'em up!
More Marines dead ahead!
Nami! Do something!
Quick! Turn left!
Right!
Good! Keep it up!
Next!
Number 67!
Light 'em up!
What? No way!
[NAMI]
There, too?
They're everywhere!
[USOPP screams]
You're kidding!
We're screwed!
[LUFFY] That's a lotta boats!
No... We're surrounded.
Yes. Just as planned.
So... What now?
[screaming]
Holy crap!
Nami, help us! Do something!
Gah! Shut up, already!
I'm doing the best I can!
Nami! Take a look! Over there!
[NAMI]
What is it? An escape route?
[USOPP] A what?
Where? Where? Let me see!
Hey! Yeah, you're right!
Think we can we make it?
Go for it!
[SANJI] Roger!
[USOPP screaming]
Hey! What's wrong?
The wind!
It changed direction!
We can't hold the helm!
[USOPP]
Whoaaa! We're done for!
Damn! I can't get her to turn!
[FRANKY] Move it!
Bastard!
What are you doing?
Forget already?
It's like I told you before.
The Soldier Dock System was made
for situations like this!
Channel Zero...
...Activated!
Cola Engine...
...Paddle Ship Sunny!
[FRANKY] Go!
What the--?
What's going on?
Jiro! Help me!
We've got to keep him still or
his wounds will open up again!
Right!
[LUFFY] All right! We got away!
[USOPP] Yeah!
And all the Marines can do
is sit back and watch!
Nyah, nyah!
You got that right!
This boat's faster than
anything they've got!
[FRANKY] Super!
[ACCINO HENCHMAN 327C]
Mission accomplished, sir.
The Straw Hat Pirates are
heading straight towards
the Frozen Highway, as planned.
[SALCHOW] Of course they are.
They're morons and I'm a genius.
They've fallen into our trap,
just like I said they would.
Report this to
Campacino immediately!
Chopper! Where are you?
Hey! Chopper!
--We're here to take you back!
--Who's that?
[LUFFY] If you can hear me,
say something!
It's Luffy!
I'll be right back!
Hold on, Doctor! Wait!
Hey! Stop hiding! Chopper!
[GUYLE] Don't move!
If you take one
more step, I'll--
Enough!
Captain Straw Hat...
[STANSEN] Please!
Please forgive me!
[GUYLE] Stop that!
Why are you begging to them?
Shut up!
My apologies.
I'm sorry I was so rude,
and for deceiving you.
On our behalf,
I beg your forgiveness!
I don't care
about any of that.
We came here for one reason
only: to get Chopper back.
--Right?
--[NAMI] Mm-hmm.
Grow a backbone already.
I haven't seen him,
but I'd be more than happy
to help you look for him.
If he's not on
your ship, then he's--
[CHOPPER] Luffy!
[LUFFY] Chopper!
We've been looking
for you everywhere!
Come on! Let's get outta here.
But I--
Hold on!
We still need him here!
If the doctor leaves now,
he's done for!
[LUFFY] Huh? Who is?
I won't let you take him,
no matter what!
Hold on.
[CHOPPER] Jiro, wait!
[RACE] Stop it, Jiro!
Just calm down!
You'll get yourself killed!
I don't care!
I'm not afraid of dying!
You hear me?
I'm not a coward
like the rest of you!
I'll fight 'em!
No matter how strong the
enemy is, I'll keep fighting!
I'll win or die trying!
Let me go!
Chopper? What's going on?
What's his problem?
[CHOPPER] Listen, Luffy.
I hate to ask,
but I'd like to stay on this
ship just a little bit longer.
There's someone here
who's badly wounded.
I treated him and he's stable,
but he still needs my attention.
Please.
Let me look after him until he
regains consciousness, at least.
Sure. You got it.
We can wait a bit.
[snoring]
[JIRO] Doctor.
I appreciate you staying.
[CHOPPER] Jiro.
I don't really know what
the situation is here.
It seems like you and your
friends are in some kind of jam.
But for what it's worth, even
though I'm a pirate, first--
I'm a doctor.
If there's someone
who needs my help,
I do whatever I can
to save them.
Believe it or not,
we're pirates, too.
Wow, really?
I had no idea.
And the man you see
lying here is our leader.
"The Phoenix".
Captain Puzzle of the
Phoenix Pirate Crew.
The Phoenix?
[JIRO] Yeah.
He's called that
because no matter how bad
the situation might be,
even if he's on
the verge of death,
he always finds the
strength to rise up.
Just like a phoenix.
[JIRO] Captain!
[GIANT PIRATE 327A]
Hahahaha! He's dead!
Burnt to ashes!
What? But how?
[PUZZLE] Give it up!
You won't kill me so easily!
[GIANT PIRATE 327A]
He's some kind of monster!
[PUZZLE]
Actually, I'm a phoenix!
Just like the
rest of my crew,
I thought this was
the man who would become
King of the Pirates.
But things are
different out there.
The New World is
a league of its very own.
You've been there? Really?
[JIRO] Yeah, we have.
But we didn't stand a chance.
Even Captain Puzzle
had to retreat
from the enemies
we met there.
Me and the rest of the crew
escaped before we got hurt,
but it was a close call.
We were totally outclassed.
[JIRO] But either way,
I still believe in him!
Captain Puzzle has the courage
to resurrect himself again,
just like a phoenix!
[GUYLE] Dammit. I've had enough!
I'm sick of Stansen's crap!
Shh! Hey, careful!
He's still our commander
right now, you know!
If he hears you,
you'll get in trouble!
Huh. Like I care
what that coward thinks.
He has no right to
lead any one of us!
[GUYLE] You guys feel
the same way, don't you?
Guyle's right. This sucks!
We can't just keep
going on like this!
Yeah!
Haven't we suffered enough
humiliation from those bastards?
Not only did they
steal our flag,
they conned us into working
as their little lapdogs!
[GUYLE] What the hell
is wrong with you?
I'm not joining up with them!
I'd rather die! You hear me?
[STANSEN] You fool!
Vigaro went so far as
to sacrifice himself
to protect you!
He gave his life for you!
I won't let that
sacrifice be in vain!
[GUYLE] I believe that if
our captain recovered,
he would lead our crew
to recapture our flag.
He'd take back our dignity,
make us pirates again.
[GUYLE] But Stansen
doesn't think like that.
He's different.
"Different" how?
What do you mean?
He only cares about saving
his own skin at any cost.
Didn't you see
the look on his face
when he was talking
to that hunter?
[GUYLE] Ever since our
defeat in the New World,
he's lost his spirit.
We have no choice.
We need to wait for
our captain to recover.
But that doesn't mean
I have to accept
what's going on
in the meantime.
[GUYLE] Ever since
our captain was injured,
Stansen's forced us
to serve the hunters.
That ends now!
As a proud pirate of this crew,
I will stand up to the hunters
and fight them to the death!
The Phoenix Pirates
will rise again!
Then I'll fight beside you!
As will I!
What about you?
I became a Phoenix Pirate
because of how much
I admired Captain Puzzle.
You can count on me!
Yeah!
No matter what happens
to the captain,
I won't let anyone
sully his good name!
I'm a Phoenix Pirate, too!
Agreed.
I don't think Vigaro would
like to see us in this state.
We can't let it end like this.
Right.
Then it's settled.
We'll fight them together.
Even if our captain can't
fight alongside us,
we still have to
show these bastards
what the Phoenix
Pirates are made of.
Whoa!
Nothing but giant icebergs
in every direction.
[NAMI] What's going on?
Something's wrong here.
It's almost as if
the direction we sail
is at the whim
of these icebergs.
[NAMI] What the hell?
[SANJI] That was close!
Sanji! Look out!
Oh, crap!
[NAMI] Hard to port!
Damn these things!
[SANJI]
Whew! An even closer call!
What's up with these icebergs?
How can they move so fast?
I don't know.
But I do know that
something fishy's going on!
It's almost like these
things are moving
of their own free will!
[CAMPACINO] What's that?
[SALCHOW] Well, to
tell you the truth, sir,
I was a little careless.
But everything's
under control now!
The trophy is heading
to the usual place!
Don't worry, my brother!
[CAMPACINO] Let's lay off this
"brother" business, shall we?
[SALCHOW] Sorry!
I was just trying to...
[ARBELL] Campacino! Honestly!
Are you bothering him again?
Salchow.
You haven't failed in your
mission, now have you?
Do you still have
the target in sight?
[SALCHOW] Well, not exactly!
But it's not like they've
escaped or anything!
Everything's still
going according to plan!
You believe me,
don't you, honey?
What? I'm so
disappointed in you!
[SALCHOW] Don't say that!
Your approval is
all I seek, my dear!
Please, forgive me!
[ARBELL] No. Not yet, anyway.
[CAMPACINO] Let's end
this party with a bang.
Once they arrive,
we'll claim our trophy
as a last-minute
birthday present.
[BRINDO] This is going
better than I thought!
To think--
The whole family coming together
to get a perfect gift for Papa!
[ARBELL] Just wait a
little bit longer, Papa!
[LIL] Hey, Arbell.
Can I go with you?
[ARBELL] No, Lil. You can't.
I'm paired with my
darling. You know that!
Don't be silly!
I hate that man.
[laughing]
A total bounty
of over 600 million.
Hurry up and show them to me!
Don't get a chance
like this every day.
[CAMPACINO] A toast!
To our beloved Papa, Don Accino,
and to the rest of the
Accino Family as well!
May fortune bless us all!
And to the present
for our Papa,
the bounty of the Straw Hats!
[ALL] Cheers!
Well then, my beloved
sons and daughters.
Time to move out.
Let the hunt begin!
[NAMI] Whoa! Look out!
Quick, Sanji! Turn!
[SANJI] Aye-Aye, Nami!
What the hell is wrong
with this place?
[NAMI] It's like we're
being surrounded.
This is bad!
Turn the rudder! Hurry!
[SANJI] It's not responding!
Why aren't Luffy
and Chopper back yet?
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
The Dream Sinking
in the New World!
The Disillusioned Pirate,
Puzzle!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!