[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY]
We made it!
So, this is it gang!
Our second island
in the Grand Line!
A tiger?!
[roars]
[USOPP] What's up
with this crazy island?!
Collier coup...
[ZORO growls]
[NAMI]
This is Little Garden?
What's little about it?
[NAMI] Seriously!
That guy's not little!
Ahh! Somebody help us!
It's a big dinosaur!!
[VIVI] This place must
be millions of years old!
Somehow this whole island
has been frozen in time.
Stuck in the age
of the dinosaurs.
I've fought Dorry every day for
more than a hundred years now.
I can't remember why,
but I guess that
doesn't really matter now.
[VIVI]
Why do you keep fighting?
[BROGGY]
For honor!
Oh.... Oh boy... He's huge!
[DORRY groans]
[pants]
[DORRY] I now know
that this was a judgment.
A judgment from Elbaf.
[DORRY]
The god of war.
[DORRY] I didn't have
the god's protection...
...and that is all.
[LUFFY]
Who was it?! Who did this?!
These guys messed up
the best duel ever!
They're in some serious trouble,
and they're gonna answer to me!
I'll kill you!
Hah hah! Good luck...
Because it's no use, your
friends are well on their way
to becoming the perfect wax
figures in my collection,
and there isn't anything you can
do about it, Straw Hat Luffy.
[USOPP]
Hold on, Luffy, I'm coming...
[gasps]
[LUFFY sighs]
This really is some nice tea.
Luffy! Hey! Wake up!
[tea pouring into cup]
This is such good teeeeaa...
Luffy!
Why are you sitting there...
...and drinking tea?!
Huh?
Run all you want. It's all over
for you and your friends.
Here comes my best trick so far!
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
[LUFFY]
"Time to Fight Back!
Usopp's Quick Thinking
and Fire Star!"
Huh?
[BOTH scream]
[MISS VALENTINE]
Ahahahaha!
What an idiot!
He missed the target
and hit his friend instead.
Good that was the
last of his bullets.
[MR. 5 chuckles]
Breeze Breath Bomb!
[BOTH scream]
Did I forget to mention that
my breath is also explosive?
[USOPP]
Damn. I can't believe this guy!
He didn't have any
bullets to begin with?!
Hey, Karoo... Are you all right?
[KAROO groans]
[coughs] Luffy...!
You snap out of it yet?
[LUFFY]
Yeah. I'm good now, thanks.
[gasps] So he didn't miss!
His plan this whole time
was to burn the Color Trap
on the Straw Hat's shirt.
[pants]
I'm tired of your stupid paints.
You're through...
I'm not gonna let you hurt
any more of my friends...
[growls]
Now, I'm really mad!
This is getting weird.
It's been a long time,
and no one's come back.
I wonder what's going on.
This island's crazy.
Anything could have happened
to Nami, Vivi, and the others,
which means that
cooking this lizard
may have to wait for a while.
Hey, Nami! Vivi!
Can you hear me?
Hey! Beautiful ladies!
If you can hear me,
please just say something!
Hmm?
That's strange. What's this?
[MR. 5 laughs]
Oh, you're mad, are ya?
Look at your friends. Being
mad won't do them any good.
Oh, yes, it will!
They're still alive!
[MR. 5 laughs]
Are they, now? Look again...
All they need is some of
Miss Golden Week's paint,
and they'll be
perfect wax statues.
Face it: You're too
late to save them...
They're gone, and you know it!
[growls]
[MR. 3]
Mr. 5 is right about that.
Your friends are finished
because you were too late
to help them, and now,
it's your turn to die.
[MR. 3]
It's time for...
...Candle...
...Champion!
[MR. 3 laughs]
[screams]
What the heck is that?
That thing...? That is
what he used one time
to take down someone with a
forty‐two million berry bounty.
That's Mr. 3's most
dangerous work of art.
Time to use your talents,
Miss Golden Week.
I need an extra special
paint job for my armor,
and don't forget to be artistic.
After that, can I take a break?
[MR. 3] Why, yes,
you can go get some tea.
I'd prefer it if you stayed
out of this, actually.
When I'm in this armor,
I'm utterly impervious to harm.
This suit is as hard as iron.
It may be made of wax,
but it fits like a glove,
and it's impossible
for anyone to pierce.
And you don't stand
a chance against it.
[MR. 3]
This artwork is flawless.
Wow...! That's so cool!
Why are you
admiring him?! Fight!
Quaaaaack!
Just a little more
laughter yellow...
Right! Gum‐Gum...
[MISS GOLDEN WEEK]
Paint job complete!
And now...
[LUFFY]
...Pistol!
...Champion Fight:
Harvest Field Maneuver.
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
...Stamp!
Hehe! Nice try!
Not good!
Luffy's attacks don't work
against that guy's armor!
[coughs]
The wax is choking me! Huh?
Wax... Huh...
[USOPP] Of course...! Why didn't
I realize it before now?
It's all wax,
which means that
it must be able to melt!
[USOPP]
Luffy, we need to use fire!
No matter how hard it is,
wax is still wax!
The others only hardened
a few moments ago...!
We should still be
able to save them!
Quack!
No way! Seriously?!
[MISS GOLDEN WEEK]
Yeah, that's correct.
Aaaaah! You idiot!
Don't tell them that!
But it doesn't really matter
if you realize that now,
you have no
hope of saving them.
They have thirty
seconds left, at most.
After that, their hearts
will slow to a stop.
As we speak, they're
writhing in silent pain,
barely conscious...
They're hanging onto
their lives by a thread,
terrified of
their impending doom
and unable to move or
even scream for help...!
And they know that you were too
late to save them! Hahahaha!
I'll save 'em right now.
I don't need thirty seconds.
Breeze Breath Bomb!
[USOPP screams]
Usopp! No!
Quaaaack!
When we say you
don't stand a chance,
it's best to believe us.
Ahaha!
[grunts]
[LUFFY] Damn it!
We're running out of time!
[MR. 3]
Just give up.
Listen, I need you to grab
a hold of this rope, Karoo.
[MISS VALENTINE]
Well, this looks like a party.
Now what are
you two planning...?
Do you think I could
join in on the fun?
Karoo, run now.
Get going!
[USOPP] Just run around
all the candle sticks!
And move as quick as you can!
Come on.
I don't know why you bother.
[MISS VALENTINE
'Scuse me.
Ah, jeez.
[MISS VALENTINE] Can you
handle my Crescendo Stone?
I wonder just how many kilograms
you'll be able to endure.
[KAROO]
Quaaaaack! Quack!
[MISS VALENTINE]
Ten kilograms.
[USOPP groans]
[MISS VALENTINE]
One hundred kilograms.
[USOPP groans]
[MISS VALENTINE]
Two hundred kilograms.
[USOPP grunts]
[MISS VALENTINE]
Three hundred kilograms.
[groans]
[MR. 5] Damn it!
Hold still, you quacker!
Hahaha! Give it up! It's no use!
Your friends are a permanent
part of my collection now!
Accept it. Hahahahaha!
They're not!
There's no way I'm gonna let
you have my friends, candle boy!
I don't have any fire,
so I'm gonna have
to borrow yours.
I hope that's okay!
That hurts! Quit pulling!
Stop it!
Hold on!
That tiny little flame isn't
gonna work quickly enough!
[USOPP]
The rope that Karoo has...
Light that on fire!
A rope? How's that
supposed to help us?
Just trust me on this!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
I covered the
whole thing in oil.
[LUFFY] Okay, everyone,
it's time to wake up!
It'll be hot,
but it's the only way,
and they should be all right.
Stop it! Let go! Aaaaaa!
[LUFFY roars]
Aaaaah! Ahhh!
Uh, whoops...!
Hope the others don't
get all burned up!
[MR. 3] Oh, curse you,
you stupid Straw Hat pirate!
You destroyed
my precious candle set...!
How dare you show such disregard
for artistic integrity!
[MR. 3]
You'll pay for this!
No! You're not getting
away with this...
Quaaaaack! Quaaaaack!
[MR. 5]
Damn it...
How dare you mock
Baroque Works agents?!
I'm sick and tired of you
and your friends! Got that?
Okay, playtime
is really over now!
I'm going to break
that scrawny little neck
of yours into a million pieces!
Ten Thousand...
...Kilogram Guillotine!
Not good!
[NAMI]
That was really hot!
Couldn't you have
thought up another plan?
You're being a little
picky here, don't you think?
Aren't you at least
a little bit grateful...?
You have a point there. Thanks.
It's amazing! I can't
believe we're actually alive!
Got out of the wax, did ya?
Well, I've had enough...
We simply cannot afford for you
to screw up our mission anymore.
[USOPP]
Hey, Mr. 5!
Special Attack...
Exploding Star!
You fool!
Haven't you figured out
that your pathetic explosives
don't affect me at all?
They're nothing to
an exploding man!
You took the bait!
I'm sorry.
I just told a little lie.
That wasn't an Exploding Star...
That was a Special Tabasco Star.
[MR. 5]
Spicy!
Hahahahahaha!
I had to learn how effective
that thing was the hard way!
[MR. 5 grunts]
Damn, you stupid pirate!
[coughs]
I refuse to let you
make a mockery of me!
[USOPP gasps]
[MR. 5]
Time for a full body explosion!
There'll be nothing
left of you.
[USOPP]
Ow... Ow, let go of me!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please let go!
Let him go!
I'm too young to die...
Ahhh! Let go!
[ZORO]
Flaming Oni Giri...
[MR. 5]
Huh?
Oh!
[ZORO grunts]
[MR. 5 screams]
[ZORO] You know these
flaming swords aren't too bad.
[NAMI]
Zoro!
[BROGGY grunts]
Hey, there. Glad to see
you made it out alive.
Heh. Yeah.
Master?
So now it seems...
two foes are left.
[LUFFY]
Bird guy! Lets go!
[KAROO]
Quack! Quack!
Real men don't interfere
with someone else's fight!
[MR. 3 laughs]
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[MR. 3] So good of you to come,
I've been expecting you...
Welcome to my Wax‐Wax Manor.
[LUFFY]
What's going on?
[MR. 3] Why, just a little game
of hide and seek...
Can you figure out
which one is me?
[laughs]
I'd say it appears you picked
the wrong group of people
to go up against.
You're no match for
my intellectual prowess
and artistic abilities.
You're just another buffoon
who acts on blind instinct
and uses brute force to
solve all his problems.
You can't hope to catch an
intellectual giant like me!
[laughs]
I am a Baroque Works agent.
Every assignment that is given
to me I see through to its end.
So if you think you're ready,
then just step forward.
[laughs]
That's right;
just take a little step.
And as soon as
your back is turned,
I'm going to stab you...
[laughs]
...right through that
pathetically noble
little heart of yours.
[laughs]
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum... Stamp!
[MR. 3]
Ahh!
[grunts]
[MR. 3]
How could you have known...
...that... this...
is where I was...?
[groans]
Instinct.
Quack!
Quaaack!
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[clinking glass]
[sniffs]
[SANJI] Earl Grey is a perfect
addition to the afternoon.
Aaah! Hold on!
What am I doing...?!
I shouldn't be sitting here
all relaxed just casually
sipping tea without a
single care in the world!
Nami, Vivi, and the others
could be waiting out there
right now for me
to come and help them!
I am still curious about
one thing, though...
What is a nice,
relaxing place like this
doing smack in the middle
of an ancient, creepy jungle?
[SNAIL ringing]
Huh?
[SANJI]
What?
Hmm?
A transponder snail.
Yeah, hello...
You've reached the crap café...
Can I take your order...?
You can quit fooling
around now, jackass.
Now then...
Your report's a little bit late,
don't you think?
[SANJI]
Huh...? My report, you say?
And to whom exactly
am I speaking, please?
Me.
Mr. 0.
[SANJI]
Hmm...
♪If there is a treasure
out there to be found,
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big place,
the oceans are wide,
Dumb luck alone
won't help you find it,
Just give up, it's astronomical.
Even so.
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on,
The laughter behind our
backs, it keeps us strong
It's too bad 'cuz we're still
sailing forward, so bon voyage!
Just leave us alone!
It may be foolish
chasing impossible things,
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream,
the more ambition
I'm gonna need!
It may be foolish
travelin' on, but I know
That I just gotta fight!
The farther the sea,
the greater paradise
We're gonna find!
Don't give up,
just keep on trying,
And you'll see that
you're closer to...
The horizon of your dreams!♪
[SANJI] Hey guys, look
what I got my hands on.
[LUFFY] That's an
Eternal Pose to Alabasta!
[USOPP]
Aw, yeah!
[ZORO]
Now, we can get going!
[LUFFY] All right! It's
time for a rice cracker party!
[USOPP]
Aww, we only have two left.
That's not nearly
enough for a party.
[NAMI]
This is no time for a party!
Come on, let's get going!
We don't have time
to waste sitting around.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Farewell, Giant Island!
Head for Alabasta!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!