[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
Pathetic.
[CROCODILE]
Let me tell you something.
You're never going
to save this country.
Goodbye, Princess.
[yelling]
Luffy.
[growls]
It can't be!
[screams]
It's Luffy. He's alive!
[LUFFY]
I'm gonna put an end to this.
For good!
[LUFFY growling]
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Once you touch water,
you can't turn into sand.
You took away all
the rain in Alabasta
because you're afraid
of water, didn't you?
I know how to defeat
you, Crocodile.
Our real fight is starting now.
[LUFFY]
"Sand Croc and Water Luffy!
The Second Round of the Duel!"
Get up. It's time to fight.
Now, Crocodile!
[chuckling]
[chuckling continues]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[USOPP]
Are you serious?
In ten minutes, this place
is really gonna blow up?
Yes, 4:30 is when it goes.
That soon?
[VIVI] According to
what Crocodile said,
if the cannon is shot,
no one within five kilometers
of here will survive.
[NAMI] Five kilometers?
Then that means‐‐
[CHOPPER]
Both the rebel and royal armies
will be completely wiped out!
[SANJI]
That damn Crocodile.
[USOPP] What the hell
are we supposed to do?
[ZORO]
We find the cannon.
[OTHERS]
Huh?
We stop the cannoneer
from shooting.
The cannoneer?
[USOPP]
Okay, but how do we find him?
And in ten minutes.
[ZORO] Well, not by
standing around here.
[USOPP] But if everything in
this area's going to explode,
then the cannon guy has to
be far away, doesn't he?
Or else he'd just blow
up with the rest of it.
No way. No. He's close.
The cannoneer is
almost certainly
near the Palace Square.
[USOPP]
What? Are you serious, Vivi?
But that means he's gonna be
caught in the explosion too!
I guess that shouldn't
be too surprising.
It is Crocodile.
What?! He's just gonna
let his own man die?!
He's just plain evil.
Come on, let's go.
[gasps]
[screams]
Looks like we found
ya, Princess.
I wonder how big a promotion
Crocodile will give us
for killing you.
[BILLIONS laughing]
[VIVI]
Billions!
It looks like we'll
lose some time.
He's right, so let's not waste
all of it jibber‐jabbering.
[BOTH]
Let's go.
I'll go ahead.
[USOPP, CHOPPER]
Yeah, us too!
[BILLIONS yell]
Well, that's two seconds.
Your counting is not helping.
Just keeping track.
Let's split up.
We need to get out
of this dust devil
if we're gonna find anything.
[VIVI]
Ten minutes!
[ZORO]
All right, now let's go. Hurry!
[SANJI]
Yeah.
[VIVI] This is really it.
This is the last chance.
[VIVI]
In ten minutes,
the country's fate could
be decided for good!
[CROCODILE laughing]
Come on, you think
you can defeat me?
Sure do.
Now that I figured out how to
stop you from turning into sand.
I'll admit I'm impressed
you figured it out.
Especially since you
were about to die.
But I hope you realize
something like that
isn't nearly enough to
make this an even fight.
I am one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea.
So what if you're one of
the Seven dumb Warlords?
I guess that makes me...
...the eighth Warlord.
Really? Who is that guy?
He's a pirate. I'm surprised
you haven't heard about him yet.
He's helped your
darling Princess Vivi
escape from death
a few times now.
So then, he is the
one responsible
for bringing Vivi back?
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
...Pistol!
If I dodge it, then it's no use.
My hand can still absorb
any fluid on you.
For that matter,
my hand can absorb
all the water in
your body as well.
Ah, crap, forgot
about that trick.
[LUFFY yells]
All right, not bad.
[LUFFY] But remember
how you told me...
...Devil Fruit Powers
get stronger?
Gum‐Gum... Pistol!
[LUFFY]
Shotgun!
[CROCODILE]
Stupid brat!
Desert Spada!
Uh‐oh.
Just barely!
Now, Gum‐Gum...
You just keep using the
same move against me.
Do you wanna win?
[LUFFY]
Yeah! And I'm going to!
[LUFFY] That's been my plan
from the beginning!
Time for you to get wet!
[CROCODILE] Of course
your plan was obvious!
Sables!
[LUFFY screams]
[growls]
[gasps] Barrel!
[laughing]
You're struggling so
hard, Straw Hat Luffy.
You can't do anything at all
without that barrel of
yours, now can you?
This isn't any different
from my first fight
against you after all.
Yeah, you're right, Crocodile.
It isn't any
different like this.
[LUFFY gulping]
[growls]
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
How about this?
Now I'm not the same
as I was, huh?
You gotta be kidding me.
Water Luffy. Ha‐ha!
Oh, no! A leak.
[CROCODILE] He can't be
serious about this, can he?
[yelps]
I guess I shouldn't
drunk that much water.
[laughing]
[growls]
[CROCODILE] Does this idiot
really not understand
what's going on here?
[growling]
Damn it, stop your
messing around!
[CROCODILE]
Damn that brat!
Who said I was messing around?
[CROCODILE]
My body...
[LUFFY] I'm always serious!
Let me show ya!
Now Gum‐Gum...
...Bazooka!
[chuckles] How was that,
Sand Croc?
That's amazing!
He beat Crocodile?
That kid is weird,
but incredible!
There's no time now for
all this admiration.
We have other things to do.
[screams]
[MISS ALL SUNDAY] Get up.
It's time for us to get moving.
You are going to show me
the way to the Poneglyph.
What're you planning to do?
How could looking at
it possibly help you?
[groans]
Just stop asking questions.
All you have to do is
show me where it is.
Your luck's beginning
to run out.
You certainly did try, but
there's not much time left.
[CROCODILE] You should get
going now, Nico Robin.
Unless you want to be dried
up along with this brat.
Go. Now. I'm done playing games.
Nico Robin?
Yes, as you wish.
[CROCODILE growls]
[CROCODILE]
Listen up, Straw Hat.
I'm going to destroy every
last rock on this ground.
And you along with them.
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
All the grass is dying.
[screams]
[growls]
[CROCODILE]
Ground Secco!
[yelping]
[screaming]
[LUFFY]
Falling!
Ah! That was close!
All right.
Water‐Water... Pistol!
Ah! His hand sucked it up.
[CROCODILE] You actually
thought you could
kill my powers, didn't
you, Water Luffy?
[CROCODILE] That was a very
foolish mistake to make.
The true power of sand is
drying things out. Watch.
My right hand can suck the life
out of anything by
turning it to dust.
Its power is limitless.
[gasps]
[laughs]
[LUFFY]
He wasn't exaggerating.
Even the statues are crumbling!
[LUFFY]
Everything is just dying.
[gasps]
My sandal!
Everything that is connected
to the ground is done for.
Including you.
Ground Death!
[laughing]
Okay, where is he?
Where's the cannoneer?
Only eight minutes left
till the cannon goes off!
Well, it's gonna have
to be enough time
to find the cannoneer.
We have to stop Crocodile's
attack from happening,
no matter what.
If we don't, then a million
people are gonna die here today!
[SANJI]
If there's a cannonball
that can blow up
that big an area,
it's got to come
from a big cannon!
Maybe it's in a building!
[SANJI]
Damn it!
Oh, crap, I just
thought of something.
If this entire area is gonna be
blown up in eight minutes,
then doesn't that mean
we're gonna be blown up
right along with it?
I don't like blowing up.
[ZORO]
No time to think about that!
[USOPP]
Look! Up there!
That's it!
But do you think we'll be able
to get up there quickly enough?
Hey!
[USOPP]
Why does he do this?!
[gasps]
Are you from the rebel army?
I can't waste any
time with you.
Goodnight, pal.
[screams]
Now cut it up, Zoro.
[growls]
[ZORO] This isn't it!
It's covered in moss!
[PELL]
I don't see it anywhere.
There's no sign at all of
a cannon or cannoneer.
I don't understand. Where is it?
[VIVI]
Only seven minutes left!
I'll stop it somehow!
I will!
Your name. He called
you Nico Robin.
Is that really your name?
What does it matter if it is?
Don't you have more important
things to worry about?
[COBRA]
Nico Robin.
That name was known throughout
the entire world 20 years ago.
Tell me, what did
you come here for?
Just show me to where the
Poneglyph is being kept.
That's all you need to
worry about right now.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
What impeccable timing
you Marines have,
showing up right now.
Get out of the way.
We're in a hurry.
No chance!
Thanks to one of the soldiers,
I know everything that's been
going on here in Alubarna.
We're not moving.
That man, do you have
any idea who he is?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Yes, and I don't care.
I'm not listening to him, you,
or anyone else from
the government,
and I would strongly recommend
that you and your men
get out of my way.
We have no intention
of giving way to you!
Well then, you may not
live much longer.
Please hold on!
Don't be worried about me!
We've been warned that at 4:30,
a bomb is going to be shot
into the Palace Square
where the fighting's going on.
Please, you have to
go stop it now!
That's only... minutes from now!
If this attack happens,
it'll cost a million
citizens their lives!
[TASHIGI]
Well.
All right. We'll save you and
then we'll stop the attack.
[COBRA]
Wait! You don't know who she is!
Ready, men?
Move out of my way.
Treinta Fleurs!
Strangle!
A Devil Fruit.
I said I was
in a hurry, didn't I?
Don't make me angry with you.
That's her! It's
really Nico Robin!
I'm sure of it.
I looked up her old
wanted poster
because Captain Smoker
had asked me to do so.
That's really her.
She has a bounty.
Twenty years ago, the whole
world was talking about her.
I still remember the articles
that appeared in the
newspaper around that time.
In a terrifying incident, six
Marine warships were destroyed.
They said that an eight‐year‐old
girl was responsible
for sinking them.
The government classified
her as a first‐degree risk,
and they put an incredible
bounty on her head.
Seventy‐nine million Berries!
It's still an amazing sum!
But after that, she just
suddenly disappeared.
Stop your pointless rambling!
Either move out of my way
or you're all dead. Okay?
[TASHIGI] It's useless having
this many soldiers fight her.
[TASHIGI]
Sergeant!
Take the men and head to the
Square to stop the explosion.
But, Sergeant Major‐‐!
Just do it! There's
only minutes left!
[SERGEANT]
Right!
[TASHIGI]
Now, let that man go right away!
I've already warned you to move!
[LUFFY]
That was bad.
That right hand of his is
gonna be a big problem.
The entire lawn has been
turned into a desert.
Oh, great. Where'd he go now?
I'm quite tired of wasting
my time with you.
Missed me.
[LUFFY]
Croco‐‐
[chuckles]
You have lost to me...
two times now,
Straw Hat Luffy.
[CROCODILE chuckles]
♪Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!♪
[CROCODILE] This is a good
way to die, Straw Hat Luffy.
[SANJI] There's hardly any
time left until the attack!
[USOPP laughing]
[USOPP]
You're dead now!
[ZORO]
What are you doing, idiot?!
[USOPP] Putting myself
in Crocodile's shoes!
[ZORO]
Just keep looking, will ya?!
[VIVI] This is my last chance
to save Alabasta!
I have to hurry and stop this!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"That Looks Croc‐ish!
Luffy, Run to the Royal Tomb!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!