Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Sniper King.
Hm?
Shoot down that flag.
Roger.
This my new weapon, a massive
slingshot by the name of Kabuto!
Behold its awesome power!
Special Attack Firebird Star!
No way.
Mission complete.
You're all going to die!
You morons can't challenge the
entire world and expect to win!
Yeah? Bring it on!
Robin! There's still something
I want to hear you say!
Tell me you wanna live!
Robin.
I can live?
I never dared to wish
for something like that.
The world had
denied me that hope.
The sea's a vast
place so I guarantee--
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
But now, if I'm allowed to
say my wish, just this once.
Then I--
I want to live!
Take me with you!
Take me away from here!
You guys! You're so
awesome! I love you!
Let's go!
Look! The drawbridge
is lowering!
Our reinforcements pulled
it together after all.
And just in time, too.
Hey, Robin! We'll save you!
No matter what!
That got it! Go, Straw Hat!
The rest is up to you!
Damn you, pirate scum!
We'll never let you through!
Prepare the mortar cannon!
Don't let 'em cross the bridge,
even if you have to destroy it!
Yes, sir!
What happened? Why'd it stop?
Damn those marines!
They really piss me off!
Stop getting in the way!
Hey! Straw Hats! Listen up!
Huh? Granny Kokoro?
I heard everything.
Why are you all
just standing around?
We're not "standing around"!
The bridge broke -
there's no way over!
Jump into the waterfall!
Give it all you've got!
Trust me!
Look, it's the sea train!
Hey. What's up with
that devious chuckle?
Let's go!
I wouldn't take
you with me anyway.
You'll never
make it as a pirate.
No! I will make it as a pirate!
Someday, I'm gonna gather
a crew even better than yours
and I'm gonna find the greatest
treasure in the world,
and then I'll be
King of the Pirates!
I'll show you!
When I was little, I made
an oath to gather a crew
and become King of the Pirates.
It was a promise I made
to the man who protected me.
Robin.
You're not only
a part of my crew.
You're my friend.
I'll protect you,
just like he protected me.
I swear. I'll always be there!
"Jump Towards the Falls!
Luffy's Feelings!"
Hey!
You gotta take me with you on
your next adventure, Shanks!
I wanna be a pirate,
just like you!
Right. As if you could
ever be a pirate!
Why couldn't I?
Look.
You might be a
good swimmer and all,
but that doesn't mean you'd
make a good pirate, Luffy.
But I'm a great fighter, too!
My punches are like two pistols!
Are they now?
What's that supposed to mean?
He means that you're
too much of a kid, kid!
And he's right, you know.
I got boys older than you.
I'm not a kid! I'm a grown up!
Here, have some
juice and calm down.
Wow! Thanks, Shanks!
I don't know one
pirate who drinks juice!
Hey! You tricked me!
Stop laughing!
That was a cheap shot!
Excuse us.
So these are what pass for
pirates around these parts.
Looks rather sad to me.
Welcome, gentlemen.
What can I do for you?
We're mountain bandits,
but we didn't come to
tear your place apart.
All we want is some sake.
I'd say ten barrels should do.
I'm sorry, but actually we're
fresh out of sake right now.
Interesting. These other
pirates seem to be drinking.
Is that water in their glasses?
No. That just happens to be the
last of what I had stocked up.
My apologies, gentlemen.
Looks like me and my friends
drank the whole place dry.
But, you can have
this if you want.
It hasn't even been
open yet. Go ahead.
I'm wanted.
There's an eight million
berry bounty on my head.
One bottle isn't enough for a
nightcap. So don't insult me.
Just great. Now the floor's wet.
Sorry about that, Makino.
You got a rag I can
clean this up with?
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
Since you like to clean things
so much maybe you'll find
this mess more fulfilling.
A place with no sake is a
place not worth our time, men.
Let's get out of here.
See you later, pansies.
Captain, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Not a problem in
the world, Makino.
That fella really
got you good, boss!
Talk about a loser!
Why are you all laughing?
What's so funny?
You should have
fought back, Shanks!
It doesn't matter
how strong they look
or how many of them there are,
if you just laugh it off,
you're not a man, or a pirate!
Look, Luffy,
I know how you feel,
but the guy just
spilled some booze on me.
It's not worth getting
bent out of shape.
Whatever!
You shouldn't eat out
of frustration, Luffy.
Shut up!
Wait! What are you eating?
No! You didn't!
Don't tell me you ate the
fruit that was inside that box?
Spit it out right now!
Every single bit!
What are you doing?
Why are you shaking me?
What's going on?
Luffy, you just ate
the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Part of a group
called the Devil Fruits.
Eating any of them takes
away your ability to swim
for the rest of your life,
but the one you ate also
turns your body to rubber!
No way! It can't!
You dumbass!
What is this?
We were drinking and having a
nice time, until you showed up.
You apologize!
No one messes
with Shanks's crew!
I don't think I said anything
to offend you directly.
You think wrong! Now apologize!
Mayor! Help me!
Did you see the looks
on those pirates' faces?
Yeah! They got doused in liquor
and didn't even say a word.
How pathetic.
Pirates are a bunch
of wimps, nothing more.
They're all talk, no action.
Stop it!
Stop making fun of Shanks
and his men right now!
They're not wimps at all!
Luffy, no!
You better stop right now,
you stupid bandits!
You should watch
your flapping gums, kid.
No one who's ever
made me mad has lived
to tell the horrifying
and painful tale.
Wait! Hold on!
Let the boy go! I beg you!
I don't know what he's done,
and I certainly don't
intend to fight you over it.
If you'll accept, I'll
even pay you to stop this.
Just spare the poor
boy's life, please!
Mayor!
While the oldest
generation may know the way
of the world better than us all.
I'm sorry, but this rotten
kid's already made me angry.
Nothing can save him now.
You're the rotten
ones around here!
And you're a lost cause.
Which you can
regret in the next life.
No!
Please, you have to let him go!
I was wondering why the bar
was empty on such a fine day.
So, it's the
mountain bandits again.
Captain Shanks!
Shanks!
Pirates. You're just
now showing your heads?
Have you been spending all
this time scrubbing the village?
Luffy! Didn't you say
earlier that your punches
were stronger than pistols?
Shut your mouth!
Listen. I don't know what
you think you're doing here,
but you might wanna leave.
You wouldn't want
something bad to happen.
And I have just the man
to deliver this message.
I'll blow your
head off if I have to.
But that's up to you, my friend.
Would you risk your life?
Now that' you've
drawn your pistol,
are you willing to use it?
What the hell are
you talking about?
I'm saying that guns aren't for
threats. They're for actions.
You! You're a dead man!
These guys fight dirty!
Dirty?
Who did you think
you were dealing with?
We never claimed to
be saints or anything.
You fellas are staring
down a crew of pirates.
Shut up! We just
want the boy! Not you!
Listen up bandits.
Whether I'm sprayed with
alcohol or doused with food.
Hell, even if I'm spit on,
most of the time I'll just laugh
it off and forget about it.
But if you hurt
a friend of mine,
you'll pay for it,
regardless of your reason.
Shanks.
So we're gonna pay?
Lousy pirates.
Kill 'em all, men!
I'll take care of this.
Shouldn't be a big deal.
You shouldn't get too cocky.
If you really wanted to fight
us, looks like a battleship
or something bigger
would have been more useful.
Wow.
Hold on, please!
It was the kid who attacked us!
I thought you were a wanted man.
A smokescreen!
Luffy?
Looks like I made
a clean getaway.
They'd never think to look
for a mountain bandit
escaping onto the ocean.
Dammit! Let go of me,
you dumbass idiot!
I really hope you die!
Yes. I know that's
what you want.
But you're the one dying today.
Remember what I said
about making me angry?
Dammit! Dammit!
Filthy bandit scum and
I couldn't squeeze off one hit!
Sorry, kid, but I don't seem
to have a use for you anymore.
What the--?
What the hell is that?
Shanks!
Get lost.
I'm in your debt, Luffy.
Makino told me everything
about how you stood up for us.
How you were willing to fight
and put yourself on the line.
You can't cry. You're a man now.
But Shanks. Your arm!
Your arm!
Luffy. It's just an arm.
I've got another one.
I'm just glad you're alright.
So you're leaving?
Yeah. It was a nice
extended vacation,
but we have to part ways now.
I bet you'll miss me, right?
Yeah. But this time's different.
I won't beg you
to take me with you,
'cause I'm gonna become
a pirate all on my own!
I wouldn't take
you with me anyway.
You'll never make
it as a pirate.
No!
I will make it as a pirate!
Someday, I'm gonna gather
a crew even better than yours
and I'm gonna find the
greatest treasure in the world,
and then I'll be King of
the Pirates! I'll show you!
You think you'll surpass us?
In that case.
I'll leave this hat to you.
It means more to me than
anything in the world,
so you better take good
care of it. You hear me?
It's been ten years
since that day.
I set out to sea
to become a pirate.
I'll protect my
friends and my crew
the same way that
Shanks protected me.
Robin! Wait for us!
Bastard!
That vile Chopper Man!
He will thwart my plans for
world domination no longer!
This is Dr. Usodaba:
Evil Incarnate!
He leads the evil Usodaba Gang
and plots to take
over the world!
This evil scientist
produces evil monsters,
evil robots, you name it!
Those are some of his
evil minions behind him.
Did I mention he was evil?
I'll lure Chopper
Man to my base.
Here, I will patiently await
his arrival, ready to strike.
Then, I'll crush him with
my gang's full fighting power!
His weakness, and my bait,
will be his lovely
assistant, Namifia!
This is Namifia,
his lovely assistant!
She efficiently manages all
of Chopper Man's missions.
All right, minions!
Go out and kidnap my hostage!
Sir! Here you go, evil one!
What's up?
Why'd you bring him?
This is Chopper Man! Our
hero and champion of justice!
Donning his Chopper cape, he
flies around doing good deeds,
and fights for world peace!
His weapon is his cuteness!
Using the power
of his "Cute Spark",
he can render any enemy
helpless by melting their heart!
And if that doesn't work,
he uses the power
of his "Chopper Violence"
to beat the crap out of them!
Tea, please!
Hey! You can't relax
at my base of evil!
What's that big thing
out in the garden?
My secret weapon!
Stop peeking at
it, you little jerk!
Can I take you for a test drive?
Sure! Go ahead!
Don't make friends with
my nemesis, Luffybomber!
This is the giant robot
and secret weapon
known as Luffybomber!
It stands 50 meters tall!
With Usodaba at the controls,
it becomes your worst
and strongest enemy!
Special Skills: It can speak!
Personality: It does
whatever it feels like!
This is the Rice Ball
Monster, Zorokiller!
If you don't have
rice balls, he gets mad
and says, "Make sure
you have some next time!"
Robiflowern, the flower monster!
This evil woman is defeated
by Chopper Man's "Cute Spark"
time and time again!
And, the naughty
monster, Sanjiropus!
He insists that
he isn't naughty,
but he's always thinking
about naughty stuff!
To men, he will show no mercy!
They are the Usodaba
Gang's "Evil Three"!
But, they don't
really have anything
to do with this story, so.
Conveniently enough,
this evil gang was blown away!
Whoa! That was amazing!
You're the coolest, Luffybomber!
Hell yeah, I am!
Hey, Chopper Man!
There's trouble in one
of the eastern towns!
Right!
I'll fly over there with my
giant robot Luffybomber
and see what's going on!
Where'd he go?
Oh, I sold him.
Go, go, Chopper Man!
Continue your noble
fight for world peace!