[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[BROGGY]
Well, there's the signal.
It's really been active today.
You're really going?
But your wounds from the
last battle haven't healed!
Please! Dorry can't be
doing any better than me!
[BROGGY laughs]
A few scratches won't
take me out of a duel!
That would surely be a poor
excuse for a brave warrior.
[laughs]
[pants]
[LUFFY]
Wait, giant guy!
Don't!
[VIVI] You can't fight,
Dorry! You need to rest!
You'll die if you
push yourself too hard!
I will fight... I am Dorry...
I will‐‐ [sputtters]
...fight... for Elbaf's
pride and die as a warrior.
[LUFFY] "Broggy's Bitter
Tears of Victory!
The Conclusion of Elbaf!"
[rumbling, explosions]
[gasping]
[DORRY grunting]
[sighs]
[pants]
What is he...?
[growling]
Woah, look!
He picked up that huge
rock. That's so cool!
[VIVI]
Luffy!
[gasps]
[LUFFY yells]
Come on! What are you doing?
‐‐Get this rock off me!
‐‐[DORRY] It can't be
‐‐helped now.
It's been over a century...
...since we started
the battle... this duel.
Injured or not,
I cannot allow myself
to run away from this fight.
To do so would be like running
from the title of warrior.
And if I was no longer
a warrior of Elbaf,
then I would no longer
know who I am.
[DORRY] I'm sorry I suspected
you of causing the explosion.
I now know that
this was a judgment.
[DORRY]
A judgment from Elbaf...
The god of war.
I didn't have the
god's protection...
...and that is all.
Listen to me: Gods and
protection and judgments
have nothing to do
with what's going on!
If a god told you to just
run off and die, would you?!
Someone has interfered
with your duel!
And a duel that's
been interfered with
isn't a fair fight anymore!
Isn't that right?
[DORRY]
Silence.
What can you know about this?
You're a human who can't have
been living on this earth
for more than two decades.
How can you possibly
hope to understand
the ways of the
warriors of Elbaf?
[LUFFY]
Who cares about that stuff?!
Now get this damn thing off me!
Hey! Old guy! Listen to me!
Move this rock already! Come on!
Come back here!
You can't leave me
trapped like this!
[BROGGY]
All right then.
Now, Master Broggy,
go and show this guy!
[laughs]
[USOPP mimics BROGGY]
You bet, Usopp!
I'm gonna beat him
for sure this time.
He hasn't got a chance.
[USOPP] Go get him,
you great warrior of Elbaf!
The mighty Broggy always
defeats his opponent!
‐‐[BROGGY laughs]
‐‐[USOPP] You can do it, Broggy!
You're the mightiest
warrior in the world!
You can destroy him any day!
You're gonna crush him!
Go, Warrior Broggy!
‐‐Fight like the...
‐‐[NAMI] Why does he continue
this pointless fight?
How can you say something
like this is pointless?!
Broggy is a brave warrior,
just like I'm gonna be someday!
You have no right to
say anything, you idiot!
‐‐If you weren't a girl...
‐‐[NAMI] Well now we can
think about getting
back to the ship.
Waiting for a year...
There's no freakin' way.
It's completely unacceptable.
We need to get everyone
back on the ship
and come up with a plan.
[USOPP]
Now hold on a second!
I for one don't think
we stand a chance
in a fight against dinosaurs!
Cutting through the jungle
in order to get back
to the Merry won't do us
much good if we get killed
on the way, will it?
What happened to all that
"brave warrior of the sea"
stuff you've been
going on about?
I said that someday
I would be a brave warrior
of the sea. Besides, even
a brave warrior has to have
enough sense not to
get himself killed.
[NAMI]
We don't have a choice here.
Luffy's group is over at
the other giant's place.
We should probably
head that way first.
Nami, listen.
Even if I should lose everything
someday, and I must face
a horribly tragic death‐‐
alone on a deserted island‐‐
I, will proudly say this
about how I have lived:
I am Captain Usopp,
and know that I have been a
great, brave warrior of the sea!
[NAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
But for now, do you
think you could just
try to be a dependable warrior?
Right. Let's go.
[rumbling]
[BROGGY laughs]
Dorry, how was your drink?
Hit the spot, didn't it?
Yes. It tasted almost godly.
[laughs] Well, I'm glad
that you enjoyed it.
Let's go!
[BROGGY yells]
[laughs]
[BROGGY growls]
[yells]
What's... wrong?
You... seem... weak.
[DORRY]
Don't count on it.
I'm as strong as ever.
[BOTH growling]
[LUFFY growling]
[LUFFY]
Move, you stupid rock! Come on!
Of course.
Just when I meet a great
warrior, this happens!
Just calm down.
[VIVI] I don't understand
why he's so upset
over someone that he just met.
He sure doesn't seem much
like a hardened criminal
with a bounty on his head.
Who was it?! Who would
dare to interfere?
I'll kill them!
Hey, Luffy...
Karoo's missing!
[footsteps]
[panting]
[MISS VALENTINE]
Hey! Isn't this the ugly bird
that the princess is always
hanging around with?
[screams]
[Mr. 5]
Yeah.
[laughs]
[MR. 5 chuckles]
[screams]
Don't leave.
[KAROO screams]
Well now, we're happy
we ran into you.
In fact, there's a little
somethin' we'd like
to ask you to do for us.
Oh, yeah.
[ZORO grunting]
This isn't good.
I'm lost.
This tree looks familiar,
but it's kinda hard
to tell in this place.
I think I was supposed to
take a left at the tree
wrapped in vines.
[ZORO]
Oh. Hey, Nami, it's you!
Seems I got lost.
Looks like you got
some pretty good timing.
I wasn't sure what
I was gonna do.
So what are you doin'
in this area anyway, huh?
Uh... Nami?
[USOPP screams]
Oh, crap, it's another dinosaur!
Get away, get away,
get away, get away,
get away, get away!
Usopp, wait up!
[panting]
Luffy!
[NAMI]
Boy, is it a relief to see you!
So what are you
doing here, anyway?
[gasps, yelps]
[USOPP screaming]
[USOPP]
Uh, Nami?
[DINOSAURS squawking]
[USOPP]
Nami! Nami! Nami! Nami!
Where did she go?!
Luffy!
[screaming]
[USOPP]
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
[USOPP groans]
[USOPP] I have terrible news:
A dinosaur ate Nami!
What? No way!
We were running through
the jungle to get away
from the dinosaur, and then
suddenly, I turned around
and she was gone!
It must've gotten her!
I got my friend killed!
How can I live with myself now?!
[screaming]
[VIVI]
Hey, you guys, calm down.
Just listen to me for
a second, will you?!
If she was there one
moment and gone the next,
then... you can't know
for sure what happened.
Well, no, it's not like
I could stop and check!
I would've been eaten, too!
It was either a dinosaur
or some other wild beast.
What else could it possibly be?!
I don't know for sure.
But, if Baroque Works followed
us from Whiskey Peak,
it would make sense for
them to capture Nami,
and not you. I think we
may be in great danger.
We should go.
[gasps] You mean
that Baroque Works
is here on the island with us?!
Wait. But why capture
Nami and not me.
[VIVI] Because you haven't
gotten in their way.
Most likely, you aren't
on their assassination list.
[USOPP]
Oh, okay.
[VIVI]
Now that I think about it...
I bet that booby‐trapped alcohol
was meant to get us instead.
[gasps]
Huh? What did you
say about alcohol?
Broggy gave Dorry
some of your alcohol
that must have
been tampered with.
Because, when Dorry drank
the barrels, they exploded.
No way!
They actually exploded
inside the guy?!
Wait! He was injured that badly,
and he still ran
off to go fight?
[LUFFY]
I tried to stop him, and that's
how I ended up like this.
[BROGGY, DORRY grunting]
[USOPP]
This is horrible.
Those two have been
fighting as hard as they can
for 100 years! And they
always ended in a draw.
[DORRY, BROGGY grunt]
[groans]
[laughs]
[pants]
Plus...
Their duels are fought with
the most honor and pride
in the whole world!
Yeah.
There's no way
they can settle it
once and for all like this!
[BROGGY laughing]
What's... wrong... huh?
[DORRY, BROGGY grunting]
Well, he keeps fighting.
He certainly is stubborn...
That Dorry the Blue Ogre.
[giggles]
Yes. Well...
I should lend some assistance.
[DORRY groans]
[BROGGY cackles]
[BROGGY]
A whole century.
[BROGGY] This has been a long
and difficult battle, indeed.
[LUFFY gasps]
[USOPP gasps]
[screams]
[panting]
[DORRY] I now know that
this was a judgment.
A judgment from Elbaf...
The god of war.
I didn't have the god's
protection... and that is all.
[LUFFY growling]
Stop it, Luffy.
Calm down.
[LUFFY]
Who was it?!
Who did this?!
Hey, Mr. 3.
I think I heard something.
[laughs] Some pathetic
animal yelping helplessly
in the jungle. Amusing.
[laughs]
[BROGGY panting]
All... these fights...
[panting]
Seventy‐three thousand
four hundred sixty‐seven duels.
[BROGGY]
Seventy‐three thousand
four hundred sixty‐six
draws... and...
...one win!
[BROGGY sobs]
[BROGGY pants]
[BROGGY whimpers, sobs]
[MR. 3 cackles]
Do I see tears of joy?
I doubt that happiness
will last long.
But... For now, I offer
you my congratulations.
Did you say "happiness"?
You... know nothing.
Who are you, little man?
I am Mr. 3.
That's a codename, of
course, which is necessary
in my line of work.
I am an artist of sorts.
And this is my assistant.
All the best artists
require assistants, you see.
Her name is Miss Golden Week.
I tell you all this
because I've already
caught you in one
of my art works.
What... What have
you done to me?!
[BROGGY growling]
[yelling]
Right, Luffy!
I don't know what
we're dealing with here,
but I'm gonna take
care of them myself!
I'll come, too, Usopp.
Good.
Having you along with me
will be reassuring.
[MR. 5]
You're not goin' anywhere.
[USOPP, LUFFY, VIVI]
Huh?
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
You guys again!
[gasps]
You can have 'im back.
We don't need him.
[laughs]
Karoo!
Why, you...! Wait.
Who are these guys?
The bullies from
the last island.
Karoo never did anything to you!
Why did you have
to do this to him?!
You're right.
We had no need to retaliate
against your ugly bird... but...
We needed to get our
hands on that little
straw hat friend
of yours, you see.
The plan was simple.
We wanted to lure you
both into the jungle
by having your dear birdie here
squawk pitifully for help.
But the idiot
refused to cooperate.
Now...
You just call out for
your owner real loud.
Give us a really loud squawk
and we might even let you go.
All right...
Then we'll make you squawk.
Just call for the princess.
[MR. 5]
Call for help now!
Let's hear it, bird!
Call out to your beloved
princess and this will all end!
Just open your mouth,
you damn creature!
[MR. 5] But then we realized
that little Straw Hat
was already neatly trapped here,
just waitin' for us.
In which case...
...we didn't need
that thing anymore.
[VIVI]
Karoo...
[groans]
[laughs] What a dumb bird.
I'll kill you!
And were you the ones
who planted a bomb
to injure the giant Dorry?
Yeah. That's us.
Who is this new guy?
Is he on the list?
No, but he's clearly
a friend of theirs.
Let's just get rid of him.
How dare you interfere
with a proud warrior duel?!
It was you?! I'll
kick your... asses!
How about I get
rid of you instead!
Aw... It's just so cute when
you fight, Miss Wednesday.
[laughs] What's more,
she really thinks
she stands a chance
against agents like us.
Taste my Peacock Slasher!
[USOPP]
I'll get you, too!
Exploding Star!
Yeah, got ya!
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
Wrong!
Huh?
[MR. 5]
Nose Fancy Cannon!
[USOPP gasps, yelps]
[USOPP coughs]
[MISS VALENTINE laughs]
Did you get burned?
Usopp!
Ten Thousand Kilogram Press!
[VIVI yells]
Now, now.
‐‐[screams]
‐‐[MR. 5] Just calm down.
[MR. 5 chuckles]
There's no need to get so upset
right now, Princess.
We aren't plannin'
to kill you yet.
[grunting]
[MR. 5]
We only came here to abduct you.
Those were Mister Three's
explicit orders.
[gasps]
Mr. 3? The Wax Wax Fruit man?
He's here on the island with us?
[MR. 5]
That's right.
Mr. 3 the "candle man."
His body creates wax, which he
can then control as he likes.
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
A candle man?
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I wrote you a
love song to let you
Know that I wanna be with
you 'til the end of time
Even when the sparkle fades
The doubts in vade our
once so trusting minds
Promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies
We built a castle of sand
And now we're watching
it wash away,
It doesn't have to end
We'll start again,
this time 'round,
we'll build a stronger love
Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I just wanna hold you
and not let go
You know that I'll be with
you 'til the end of time
Oh, you've got me heart and soul♪
[LUFFY] Usopp! We can't let
them get away with this!
[USOPP coughs]
No, we sure can't!
[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY]
You can't stand this either?
[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY]
All right! The three of us
will beat them
senseless together!
Come on, Usopp. Bird, let's go!
‐‐[USOPP] Yeah!
‐‐[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"The Devilish Candle! Tears
of Regret and Tears of Anger"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!