[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated
from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
With help from Jimbei,
Luffy makes his way
to the scaffold,
only to be halted by the
Navy's three admirals.
When it seemed
all hope was lost,
Whitebeard and his men
joined the fray.
Now, an all-out
battle has broken out
between the Navy's elite and the
strongest pirates in the world!
Go Ice Block: Partisan!
--[AOKIJI] Hm?
--[JOZU grunts]
Go, I'll fight.
[WHITEBEARD]
I'm counting on you, son.
[pants]
[gasps]
[LUFFY groans]
[KIZARU]
Hmm.
You're full of
courage, aren't you?
But take this word of advice.
If you're simply
not strong enough,
you won't even come
close to saving him.
[panting]
[LUFFY groaning]
He's nothing but
a big-mouthed kid
who goes looking for trouble.
Dumb and clumsy.
Careless, too.
[WHITEBEARD] But I've got a
soft spot for fools like him.
[WHITEBEARD yells]
You. You're always sailing
around wreaking havoc.
But here, you're through!
[chuckles]
That's what you think.
[MARCO]
Hang on, Ace! I'm comin' for ya.
[MARCO grunts]
[GARP grunts]
[MARCO groans]
[GARP]
If you wanna reach the scaffold,
you're gonna have to
make it through me first!
[LUFFY] "The Power That Will
Shorten One's Life!
Energy Hormone, Redux!"
We're up against him, too?
The legendary hero, Garp?!
[PIRATES gasping]
He may be over the hill
now, but 20 years ago,
that guy went neck-and-neck
with Gold Roger!
He might be the strongest
Marine the Navy has ever seen!
[PIRATE AA]
He didn't just fight Gold Roger,
he beat his rival, too.
When Shiki the Golden Lion
launched his attack
on Marineford,
Garp was the one who
locked him up in Impel Down!
[PIRATES gasping]
We didn't make it
all the way here
just to lose to an old man!
Legends ain't nothin' but words!
[GARP chuckles]
I might say the same
thing to you, Whitebeard!
[grunts] Your glory days are
just a dying memory now!
Hound Blaze!
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[MARINES gasping]
Damn. Are you gonna
destroy this entire city?
Send me the bill for
repairs when we're done.
This is ridiculous!
Just execute him!
All right, go and get a
substitute immediately!
[MARINE B]
Sir!
[PIRATE BB]
Make a path!
Keep pushing toward
the scaffold!
[PIRATES shouting]
[PIRATES gasping]
Ironic, I know, but I
forgot about those things!
No more lasers for
today! That's enough!
Did you think we were weaklings?
We're from the New World!
[PIRATE CC]
Now's our chance!
[PIRATE DD]
Get to the scaffold!
[IVANKOV]
How is he?
He is'nt good!
First aid isn't going
to cut it, I'm afraid.
We gotta get him
outta here, and fast.
[IVANKOV] The odds were
against him from the start,
but this is too cruel.
He's so close.
[SENGOKU]
Hm?
A final moment of regret?
[GARP grunts]
[GARP]
Poor boy.
[THUG A]
Gold Roger?
[THUG A] Yeah, of course I know
who he is, but who gives a crap?
People talk like he's
something special,
but what did he even do?
He just riled up
a bunch of criminals!
And thanks to that bastard,
the entire world is screwed up.
And what does that mean?
There's no way
you're that stupid.
Everyone knows before
he was executed
he told some BS story
about hidden treasure
to give the middle finger
to the Government.
But either way, it worked,
'cause a bunch of dumb pirates
bought into the whole
thing and went nuts.
Don't you get it?
He left behind a stain
people still can't clean up.
Even killing the
bastard wasn't enough.
Now, thanks to him,
we gotta put up with a
bunch of human garbage
pissing on everyone else,
following his lead.
He's the biggest piece
of crap who ever lived.
He stinks even after
we flushed him!
Just like you, kid!
[THUGS laughing]
[ACE grunts]
[THUG A]
Huh?
[ACE growling]
Aw, did I hurt your
wittle feelings?
Are you in the Roger Fan Club?
You got something
you wanna say, kid?
[ACE grunts]
[THUG A gasps]
[THUGS gasping, groaning]
[DADAN]
You startin' trouble again, Ace?
What was it this time?
[DADAN] Everyone's making
a fuss about some thugs
that got beat near
to death by a kid.
That's too bad.
I was hoping they would die.
[DADAN]
Don't gimme that!
You realize when you
pull this kind of crap,
I'm the one who gets
chewed out for it, right?
Hey, are you listening?
[DADAN]
Honestly!
I don't know what that
old fool was thinkin',
leavin' a boy like you with me!
What?
You want me to
tell you about Roger?
[SUIT A]
Huh.
He was a liar.
And a murderer and
miserable thief to boot!
Only jackasses believe his crap.
[SUIT B] King of the Pirates,
King of the Chumps,
he's dead either way!
[SUIT A]
Got that right!
[SUITS laugh]
[MAN B grunts]
Roger, huh?
I'm trying to enjoy a
drink over here, kid.
The man was a hack.
Now piss off!
Hear me? Beat it, kid!
Huh? [groans]
[CROWD gasps]
[MAN A] Hey! What do think
you're doing, you little punk?!
[GARP laughing]
[GARP] "I should see
the other guy," right?
Look, Ace.
You can't keep
doin' this, kiddo.
So your grandson.
He's around my age, huh?
Huh?
Do you think he's
happy with himself?
Luffy? I think he is.
The boy's growin' up
in fine feather.
Old man.
Yeah?
[ACE]
Tell me the truth.
Did I deserve to be born,
or was it just a mistake?
[GARP]
Hm?
That's not for me to say.
You just keep livin'
and hope you find out.
[IVANKOV] Quick, carry
Straw Boy back to the ship!
[IVANKOV]
It's not ideal,
but we'll have to save
Ace Boy without him.
[LUFFY grunts]
[IVANKOV]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Iva...
[IVANKOV gasps]
Calm down, take it easy!
[panting]
I need one last favor from you.
[IVANKOV]
Huh?
[PIRATE FF]
We're coming for you, Ace!
We're taking you home!
[PIRATE GG]
The Navy never stood a chance!
[ACE]
This is wrong.
Dammit!
[JIMBEI grunts]
[MARINE D groans]
My friend. Don't lose hope.
I swear I shall save your life,
no matter how much
blood is spilled!
We're almost there!
[HARUTA grunts]
There's no stopping us now!
[PIRATES shouting]
[PIRATE HH] Don't let
them get you down, Ace!
[PIRATE II]
Yeah, we won't leave you!
[PIRATE JJ] We're brothers!
We stick together!
[PIRATES yelling]
[ACE]
Damn it, this all wrong.
How the hell am I
supposed to feel?
Pops. Luffy. My friends.
They're here to save me, but
they're pushing through a sea
of their own blood to do it!
Don't say "one last" anything.
We're getting out of
here alive, darn it!
[panting]
You know what I need.
[IVANKOV]
Hm?
I'm sick.
These are tears of joy!
Even after all I've done,
I want to live!
[LUFFY grunts]
Iva... Help me...
You realize what the
repercussions of this would be,
don't you?
[panting]
[PRISONER AA]
Captain Buggy!
[PRISONER BB]
He's awake!
[PRISONER CC]
He's alive!
[PRISONER DD]
I knew it all along!
Huh? Aw jeez,
what happened? We okay?
Aokiji just froze you solid!
It was really freaky!
[PRISONER A]
Captain Buggy!
[PRISONER EE]
Oh, no! It's too late!
[PRISONER A] No! He was
so beautiful! So perfect!
He was gonna conquer
the world, damn it! The world!
[PRISONERS yelling]
Oh, no!
[PRISONERS shouting]
[screams] Hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot!
[PRISONERS gasp]
He got hit by the ice
attack on purpose
so he could show us how to
unfreeze everyone else!
Even when he's frozen solid,
he's still thinking
of his friends!
Quick! Let's thaw out the other
guys before it's too late!
Okay!
Hey, drowning over here!
Might want to rescue
your savior first!
Remember, I can't swim! Help!
[PRISONERS]
Captain Buggy!
We were blinded by
your godlike glory
and forgot about the
whole Devil Fruit thing!
[PRISONER B]
You've saved us so many times.
And we almost let
you down! I'm sorry!
Sue me, I'm not omnipotent.
But as long as you still
worship me, we're good!
[BUGGY laughs]
[BUGGY] Looks like I've still
got my luck and my lackeys.
By the way, where did
Mr. 3 run off to?
I'm not sure. The last
time we saw him was
before those walls
trapped us in here
and everything went to hell.
[BUGGY] That little rat!
He made it out, didn't he?
Huh? You mean these walls?
With the cannons?
[PRISONER A]
The Navy lured everyone in,
then trapped them
with these things.
After that, it was ice and
meteors and boiling water
and, well, we're trapped.
Oh, are we?
Because the Great Captain
Buggy wouldn't have made it
this far in life if he'd
surrendered every time
he ran into a
measly wall or two!
Do you hear that, Navy?
Buggy's comin' for ya!
No walls, ice, or giant
magma fists can stop me!
Awesome!
You've only been defrosted,
like, a couple of minutes,
but you're like,
"Bam! Let's do it!"
That's how I roll.
[BUGGY]
Okay, seriously, now what?
Better move, magma punk!
[WHITEBEARD groans]
[MARCO gasps]
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
Son of a--
[HARUTA, PIRATE F]
Are you okay?
The ravages of time
humble us all.
Yes, even you!
Screw the fight, this is
what I was afraid of!
I don't want no sympathy--
There's no way I'm wearing this
crap in front of my enemies!
[MARCO]
Damn it, Pops!
[KIZARU]
Huh.
Wouldn't turn your back
on me, if I were you.
[MARCO groans]
Marco!
You gonna make the same mistake?
[JOZU groans]
Jozu!
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
[AKAINU]
Someone has to see you off.
And that duty seems
to have fallen on me.
[AKAINU grunts]
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
Pops, no!
Whoa, not good.
Aw, crap.
[COBY pants]
[HELMEPPO]
Hey!
It's a little late for
a change of heart now!
No offense, but they
don't need you anymore.
I mean, I think we all know
the Navy's got this one.
Akainu got Whitebeard,
Kizaru took out Marco,
and Aojiki froze Jozu.
You wouldn't kick a
man while he's down,
so don't run out there
just to pick up scraps.
And if you were looking
to test yourself
against Straw Hat
again, he's out, too.
Even the strongest pirates
in the world got stomped.
Good to know we're on the
winning team this time.
Because I promised myself
that I'll keep trying...
...till...
...till I become
a Marine admiral!
[COBY gasps]
[COBY]
No.
I-I'm sorry, I got carried away!
This is so embarrassing.
I just wanna dig a hole
and bury my head in it!
That was really arrogant of me.
I got worked up after
seeing you again and I just--
[LUFFY]
Coby.
You said you're gonna
fight me, right?
Then you will
become that strong.
You'll have to.
[COBY] I'm so ashamed of
myself, even thinking that.
It was obviously a pipe
dream from the start.
Even with all his strength,
Luffy couldn't make
his dream come true.
But at least he fought.
All I've done is run!
I don't even pass as a Navy
soldier, let alone an admiral!
It's useless!
I'm useless!
C'mon, you should be happy!
Our team just scored
a massive victory!
I bet they'll throw a party!
[COBY growls]
[HELMEPPO gasps]
[IVANKOV]
Another hormone shot?
Do you want to die?
You're past your limit!
I'm sorry, kid, but you've
been burning your candle
at both ends for too long!
Have you forgotten that
poison you suffered through?
You cheated death once!
I didn't save you so you
could destroy yourself!
I told you this last time.
My hormones aren't
a magic fix-me-up
you could take every time
something goes wrong!
I want to save Ace Boy
just like you,
but If you keep misusing my
power like this, you'll die!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY panting]
[IVANKOV gasps]
[LUFFY] As long as I
do everything I can...
[pants]
...I don't care if I die.
[IVANKOV gasps]
I'm begging you,
you have to let me fight!
Guys, I think Pops is down!
Marco! Jozu!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
If I don't keep fighting...
...and they kill Ace 'cause
I wasn't there for him...
...then I'd rather
be dead anyway!
[IVANKOV gasps]
Right now is the only fight
that matters--live or die!
[IVANKOV gasps]
You dummy!
Whatever would I tell
your dear old dad, Dragon,
if I let you die like a dog due
to my deadly Devil Fruit power?
This stubbornness of
yours is not cute at all!
[panting]
[MARINE E]
Where's the replacement?
What could possibly
be taking him so long?
[EXECUTIONER A]
Well, it was short notice
and we don't do this very often.
Hey, you ready?
Fine, let's move!
[LUFFY]
Ace...
[IVANKOV grunting]
Oh, fine!
[LUFFY groans]
It's your life!
Give us a good show!
[groans]
Wait, what are you... doing?
[gasps]
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY yelling]
He got back up!
[COBY gasps]
[LUFFY yelling]
No way!
Kizaru hit him dead-on.
It's a miracle he's even alive,
let alone getting up
and screaming like that!
[COBY grunts]
Wait! Where do you
think you're going?
You'll get hurt!
Coby...
[COBY panting]
[COBY]
I won't run away.
[LUFFY yelling]
Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[NARRATOR]
Empowered by Ivankov's
Energy Hormone technique,
Luffy dashes forward,
heedless of his injuries.
Yet even with his
sudden strength,
he still faces a wall of Marines
blocking the path to Ace.
Among them, an old friend
appears for a reunion
neither of them expected
to come so soon.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"To Live Up to a Promise!
Luffy and Coby Collide!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!