Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[HOGBACK] He is one of
my "Zombie Generals."
His body is quite special.
It hearkens from the country
of Wano in the New World.
Wait. What happened?
I thought he was
going to cut us.
Whatever, you guys! Come on!
Let's get out of here
while we still can!
Look, the door is wide open!
[NAMI] Good point.
[CHOPPER] Uh, right!
[RYUMA] Three-Verse Humming:
Arrow Notch Slash!
[LUFFY] This sucks!
Stop it! Lemme outta here!
[FRANKY] What the--?
[LUFFY] Lemme go, you bastards!
Open up this box and let me out!
Is that a coffin?
[ROBIN] That voice.
What are you
doing in that box, dumbass?
Why'd you go and get
yourself caught like that?
Straw Hat!
[ABSALOM] We'll hold the
wedding ceremony immediately.
All the preparations
have already been made.
You're that
invisible pervert from the
shower, aren't you?
Let me go!
[ABSALOM]
You may call me Absalom.
It's the name of your future
husband, so remember it well!
[NAMI] I don't keep
myself in shape
so some sick voyeur
can drool over me!
So don't treat me like a
piece of meat, you animal!
[USOPP] We gotta get
out of this forest!
[LOLA] You're not getting away!
Monkey monkey!
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
Zombie Generals in the front.
Zombie Generals behind.
I'd give up if I were you!
Hey! Don't do that--
have you lost your mind?
Coup de Vent!
[TARARAN] You can't break
the friggin' bridge, man!
That's cheating!
Now, Cien Fleurs...
...Wing!
[ROBIN] A fall like
that won't stop a zombie,
but at least they're trapped
in the courtyard for now.
Aaaaaaah!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE GENERAL 347A]
You guys see that?
[BROOK] What do you
call a flying skeleton?
Air bone!
[LUFFY] "Appearing from the Sky!
That Man is the
Humming Swordsman!"
I dunno what your
deal is and I don't care!
She's our friend and
I won't let you hurt her!
I'm warning you!
I won't stop punching
'til you stop running!
[USOPP] Get away, Nami! Hurry!
[LOLA] I'm gonna crush you,
you filthy cat burglar!
[LOLA] The only woman Absalom
is allowed to marry is me!
Get lost!
[LOLA] Now. Prepare to die!
[NAMI] Wait!
You've got it all wrong!
I... I'm...
The truth is: I'm a man!
[LOLA] What? What?
What?
[USOPP] Oh, come on.
You... You mean it?
[NAMI] Yeah, crossdressing
is just a hobby of mine.
I'm not joking!
And uh--I think you and that
Ab Guy make a super cute couple.
You two should totally
hook it up, girlfriend!
Huh? You think?
Of course I do!
You were made for each other!
[LOLA] To be completely honest,
I was beginning to lose hope.
All this time, no one
has ever offered me
a single word of encouragement.
You don't know
how much it means.
Thank you. Thank you.
[NAMI] Raise your head up high.
It's okay.
You don't have to
thank me for saying that.
We're friends.
My name is Namizo.
But you can call me Nami.
[LOLA] We're friends? Nami!
She bought that?
[LOLA] I, like,
just don't get it!
I always tell him
how much I love him
and I hug him so tight
I nearly crack his ribs!
And he's just like,
"oh whatever" about it.
I've tried being
as sweet as I can,
but he just won't notice me!
Well of course not, Lola!
You're going about
this all the wrong way!
You need to be more aggressive!
Huh? What?
Is that the problem?
I'll put it this way.
If you want to get married, you
can't do it while he's awake!
That's just silly!
You knock him out and get him
to sign while he's sleeping!
Wait, is that really ethical?
I mean, like, as a human being?
[NAMI] Lola, sweetie,
you're a zombie!
[LOLA] A loophole!
A rotting zombie loophole!
[NAMI] Remember,
if you can't knock him out,
you can always drug him!
Hey. Namizo.
Weren't we gonna run away?
Oh, by the way, Lola.
I dropped something
important back
when I visited
the treasure vault.
I'd like to go pick it up,
but I don't remember the way.
Can you give me directions?
Of course! You big silly!
Just go through
Mistress Perona's room,
it's right next door!
Can't miss it.
Take the stairs
over to your left...
[USOPP] Wow, Nami.
That warthog bought
that hook, line, and sinker.
[CHOPPER thinking]
So Nami was a guy all along.
No wonder she acts so manly.
[USOPP] Hey, Nami,
he caught up to us!
All right then.
Lola, this is your
chance to attack!
I'll never see him again
and that's perfectly
fine with me!
There's nothing stopping you!
You'll make a beautiful couple!
I'll give it my best!
[LOLA] Thank you
for everything, Nami.
You gave me the
courage to fight!
Absalom, I'm coming for you!
Aaaaah! Lola?
All right you two,
this is our chance!
A non-violent
solution--for us at least.
Wow, Nami, that was awesome!
[NAMI] She's not
such a bad girl.
You just have to get
to know her a bit!
I know what you're thinking--
I can see it in your eyes!
[GYORO] Master, we're back!
We've done it! We've done it!
[LUFFY] Shut up about
your stupid master
and let me outta here!
I can't see anything!
Where am I?
Stop ignoring me!
[LUFFY] Who are you guys?
Hey! Lemme go! Stop! Stop it!
[LUFFY] You're lucky
I'm in here,
'cause when I get out,
I'm kicking your asses!
Little jerks!
What do these
things want from me?
[PERONA] What kind
of stupid pirate ship
doesn't have any treasure?
[ZOMBIE 348A] They have
a few chests and such,
but all of them are empty.
We did pick up some money
they had lying around at least.
[PERONA] What a waste of time.
I have to look at
your un-cute faces
and there's not even treasure?
I thought this was the
guy who beat Crocodile--
you'd think he'd have a
bit more to show for it!
[sighs] Whatever.
They've got plenty of food.
Let's take that back
with us at least.
[ZOMBIE 348A] Aye-aye!
[HILDON] Mistress Perona!
Hm? Hildon.
[HILDON] The Master
is calling for a meeting
with the Mysterious Three.
What is that about?
Did something bad happen?
It would appear
that Straw Hat Luffy
has just been captured.
This will be the
debut of number 900!
Number 900? For real?
You sure are fat.
What the heck do you eat?
How rude of you!
You can't speak to
our master like that!
So, this is the famous
Straw Hat Luffy, huh?
Well, you're energetic
if nothing else.
Kushishishishi!
[LUFFY] And you must be Moria.
I hear you're a real jerk.
Kushishishishi!
I gotta admit,
I admire your confidence!
I'd expect nothing
less from a man
with a bounty of 300 million.
You'll make an
outstanding underling.
You're just perfect
for what I had in mind!
[LUFFY] Underling? Screw that!
Who do you think you are?
Who do I think I am?
Are you asking
me that ironically?
Kushishishishi!
It's obvious!
I am the man who will
become King of the Pirates!
Aaaauuughh! Master Ab!
Get out here and marry me
right now, you big jerk!
You turned invisible and
ditched me again, didn't you?
Did we lose them?
I think. Lola should
keep him busy.
It's him.
Guys, he's coming this way,
what should we do?
[USOPP] Over here!
Hurry! Get inside!
[NAMI] What the heck is that?
[USOPP] I don't know,
just get in here and hide!
[KUMACY] What was that?
This is strange.
There shouldn't be any
place left for them to run.
[ABSALOM] Hey! Kumacy!
[KUMACY] Perv-salom.
I mean, Master Absalom,
this is bad!
It seems intruders have--
[ABSALOM] Hold on,
this is important.
Did you see three
pirates run past here?
They just disappeared.
[KUMACY] Well, actually,
that's the thing--
[PERONA] Absalom!
What do you want?
I told you, I don't
like you in my room!
[ABSALOM] Perona.
[KUMACY] Welcome back,
Mistress Perona.
Is there anything you need?
[PERONA] Yeah,
I need you to stop talking!
How many times do
I have to tell you that?
[KUMACY] All right, but just
this once, there's something--
Can it. Nobody cares!
Don't you think you're being
a bit too strict with Kumacy?
Or rather, way too strict?
[PERONA] He's my underling,
what's it to you?
[PERONA] Anyway, did you hear?
Master is calling for us.
[ABSALOM] Did something happen?
[PERONA] I suppose
you could say that.
Number 900 is
making its big debut.
[ABSALOM] Number 900?
Then he must have
found a powerful shadow.
I wonder who--
[PERONA] It's Straw Hat Luffy...
[NAMI] It's a miracle
they haven't found us yet!
What were you thinking,
hiding in here?
We were better off before!
[USOPP] What do
you want from me?
You were freaking out
about that invisible guy
and I found something
to climb inside.
How was I supposed to
know it was a zombie, huh?
We'll run away as soon as
we get the chance, okay?
[HILDON] Master Absalom!
That's where you're hiding!
There's something important
I needed to tell you!
[ABSALOM] Yes?
[HILDON] In addition
to the pirates,
I'm afraid that we have
another unwanted guest.
[ABSALOM] Go on then.
It's him!
The Humming Swordsman!
He's back?
Did someone
just fall from the sky?
Hey. Is that what
I think it is down there?
It can't be.
[FRANKY] Actually,
looking at the shape,
I don't think it
could be anything else.
I don't get it.
Just where did that weirdo
fall down from, anyway?
Guess we better go save him.
What a pain in the ass.
Hey, hey!
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
You think I'm
gonna let you get away,
just cause you broke
some measly bridge?
I'm a spider!
I can climb wherever
the hell I want!
Monkey! Monkey!
Looks like we're gonna have
to pound the crap
outta this guy first.
You think you could
keep the spider busy for a sec?
[ROBIN] What for?
Perfect. There's an open
section right over there.
Anyway, I'm gonna
build a spider smasher.
Hey, I'm right here,
don't ignore me!
I'll show you
what's what! Bastards!
[TARARAN] Sticky Spider Net!
[ROBIN] He has a
spinneret on his hand.
Time for Seis Fleur.
[ROBIN] Slap.
You slapped my eye,
you awful woman!
No! No! Damn it!
You're playing dirty,
this isn't fair!
[FRANKY] Good work partner.
I'm ready to rock. Step aside.
[ROBIN] Hm? My! What's that?
[FRANKY] This here?
I just stuck my steel nunchucks
into some stone
columns, that's all.
'Cause when
a monster is this big,
you gotta smash him extra hard!
Heavy Nunchuck!
[TARARAN] Where did all
that power come from?
There's no way
this guy is human!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE GENERAL 348A]
Tararan's not looking so good.
[RANDOM ZOMBIE GENERAL 348B]
Who are these guys?
[ZOMBIE GENERAL 348B] At any
rate, we'd better go help him.
Come on.
I said stop it already!
[TARARAN] Sticky Spider Net!
[TARARAN]
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
No more smashing
me in the face!
Too bad for you! Looks
like it's time for revenge!
[FRANKY] Weapons Left!
[ROBIN grunts]
[FRANKY] Nico Robin!
What the hell are those things?
Mousey mousey mouse mouse!
I was careless. I'm sorry.
I didn't think there'd
be other spiders here.
[FRANKY] Damn it.
[TARARAN]
Ah-ah-ah...
Serves you right.
Monkey! Monkey!
That's what happens when
you let your guard down!
These guys
are my minions.
They're called Spider Mice.
There's more than 500 of
them here on Thriller Bark!
Once we set our eyes on you,
there's no escape!
We've never once failed
to capture our prey!
From the shadows,
from your blindspot,
from where you least
expect it, we attack!
And thanks to
Dr. Hogback's modifications,
our silk webs are unbreakable!
We picked off your
friends one by one,
silently carrying them through
the ceiling of the mansion
without anyone
noticing a single thing!
It doesn't matter
how strong they are,
once they're wrapped in
our webs, they're helpless.
One little mistake
and they become nothing
more than another
offering to our Master!
Don't worry about your friends.
As soon as we carry you off,
you'll all be reunited!
Hope you enjoy the ride!
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
[BROOK singing]
♪ Yo hohoho, yo hohoho.
Yo hohoho, yo hohoho. ♪
What's that?
[BROOK] ♪ Gather up
all of the crew, ♪
♪ it's time to ship
out Binks' Brew. ♪
♪ Sea wind blows,
to where, who knows? ♪
♪ The waves will
be our guide. ♪
♪ O'er across
the ocean's tide. ♪
♪ Rays of sunshine
far and wide. ♪
♪ Birds they sing,
of cheerful things, ♪
♪ in circles passing by.
♪ Yo hohoho, yo hohoho.
Stop it!
Who the hell is singing that?
[BROOK] ♪ Yo hohoho, yo hohoho.
Yo hohoho, yo hohoho. ♪
♪ Yo hohoho, yo hohoho.
[BROOK]
Yohohohoho!
My goodness, it looks like you
came to this island after all.
[ROBIN] How did you
get all the way up here?
I jumped, of course.
I'm quite light.
Since you're here already,
I suppose there's
no point in holding back.
I'll tell you everything
I know about this island.
Who are you?
Huh? You're not a zombie!
Does that mean you're
with these pirates?
Hold on. What're you--
[BROOK] Worry not, my friend.
I'm not going anywhere. I'll
put an end to this promptly.
[BROOK] Three-Verse Humming:
Arrow Notch Slash!
[LUFFY] Cut it out,
you big onion!
Let me go!
[MORIA] Kushishishishi!
Put the spotlight on him!
[LUFFY] I said stop it! Wait.
That's my shadow. No!
[MORIA]
Kushishishi!
I know just what do you
with you, my little friend.
You'll make a fine zombie!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Luffy's Emergency Situation!
The Ultimate
Shadow's Destination!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!