[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR] While trying
to escape the Upper Yard,
Nami's group was
confronted by Eneru
who displayed
his fearsome power.
Meanwhile, the four search team
members became separated
and Luffy clashed
with the leader of the
Shandorian Warriors, Wyper.
[LUFFY]
Gum-gum...
Now you die!
[LUFFY, WYPER]
...Bazooka!
[NARRATOR]
Then, Nami's team encountered
a deadly new pair of enemies.
Ha! You can call me Hotori!
Ha! And you can call me Kotori!
And you guys killed
our beloved big brother Satori.
Ha-ha!
[NARRATOR] And after
becoming hopelessly lost,
Chopper came face to face
with Sky Punk Gedatsu.
Come out right now!
[CHOPPER shrieks]
[LUFFY]
"The Ordeal of the Swamp!
Chopper vs. Sky Punk Gedatsu!"
[ROBIN]
A memorial to the city itself.
Its descendants built it.
After the great city fell.
[ROBIN]
Shandora.
That was the name
of this ancient place.
[ROBIN]
402 S.E.
The city, was at its
peak 11 hundred years ago.
But then it toppled
around 800 years ago.
That time frame
almost perfectly matches
the hundred years
of history that vanished
from the rest of the world.
Perhaps this
island holds the key.
The key to a
long-forgotten history,
that was veiled
from the world below.
[ROBIN] This is a complete
map of Shandora.
Perhaps I'll learn more
about this "Blank Century"
if I go to the
center of the city.
Who's there?
Well, aren't you a
beautiful young lady?
[ROBIN] Are you another
one of Eneru's henchmen?
Henchman?
You had better watch your mouth.
I am Yama, Divine Commander
in the service of
God Eneru himself.
And what exactly
do you want from me,
Divine Commander Yama?
I don't want to talk.
[roars]
Where did you go?
[GEDATSU] A concealment
technique no doubt.
[CHOPPER] His eyes
are rolled back in his head.
And it's really spooky!
Gedatsu, you can't see the enemy
with your eyes
rolled back like that!
[gasps]
So careless!
[CHOPPER]
What a dimwit!
An enemy huh?
Oh, I get it now.
You must be one Eneru's priests.
[GEDATSU]
Indeed, I am.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Gedatsu, priest in
the service of Almighty Eneru.
Huh?
[GEDATSU]
And I command the Upper Yard's
Ordeal of the Swamp.
Huh?
C'mon, say something you jerk!
[DIVINE BAA]
Gedatsu, he can't hear you
unless you start
speaking out loud!
So careless!
You don't normally forget that.
[GEDATSU]
Hmph!
I advise you to watch
where you step.
See.
This entire area is
my territory to control!
All around us are swamp clouds.
And once you find
yourself trapped by one
there is no hope of escape.
The survival rate
here is 50 percent.
It's almost tragic.
Ordeal of the Swamp!
"The swamp"?
Best of luck.
Hey, you're sinking!
Fool! It has no effect on me!
Swamp cloud.
[GEDATSU]
Milky dial!
[CHOPPER gasps]
No way!
[CHOPPER] He's shooting
something out his feet
that makes him fly!
That's so cool!
Something's coming
out of his hands.
[GEDATSU] One stinking,
matted raccoon dog
is hardly worth
my precious time.
Take this!
Swamp cloud burger!
A deadly swamp
with the weight of a cloud.
Once touched,
nothing can survive!
[DIVINE BAA ]
Wait, no, Gedatsu!
Don't aim it at me!
Please, stop!
[CHOPPER]
He can't escape!
I see!
It's a cloud,
so if you try to lift it,
your hands will just
pass right through it!
The more you
struggle to get free,
the deeper you're
dragged inside of it!
[CHOPPER]
I have to help him!
[GEDATSU]
There you are, raccoon dog!
Swamp cloud burger!
[screams]
If one of those things hits me,
I'll be dead for sure!
If you're still alive, hang on!
Hey!
You gotta breathe!
Don't die!
[coughs]
Oh good, you're alive.
Thank you.
You saved my life.
[GEDATSU]
Ha!
Being saved by the enemy.
Pathetic!
[CHOPPER]
Uh-oh!
[GEDATSU] And you call yourself
one of the Divine Warriors.
You're not worthy
of such a title.
[DIVINE BAA growls]
How dare you, Gedatsu.
You're gonna pay!
I'll never serve you again!
[GEDATSU]
Hmph!
Watch, as my axe dial
drains the life from you!
Haa!
Yes. We'll team up.
And together we'll defeat him.
Waa!
Bring it on!
We're not scared of you!
[GEDATSU chuckles]
Very well.
This one is called
my jet punch!
[GEDATSU]
The lethal jet dial.
Punches accelerated with it
allow you to destroy an enemy
before they even realize
the fight has begun.
It's only real defect is that
it also destroys my clothes.
[CHOPPER]
This is a Priest?
If I don't get out of here right
now, I'll end up like that guy!
[shrieks]
[CHOPPER] I gotta keep
my feet off the clouds!
Those swamp trap
things are everywhere!
If I run on top
of the ruins only,
I can make it to the
forest and solid ground!
[CHOPPER screams]
Just where do you think you're
running off to, raccoon?
Here's another jet punch.
[CHOPPER]
Rumble... jumping point!
[CHOPPER] Rumble balls
last for three minutes.
If I don't escape within
that time, I will be killed.
[GEDATSU]
So, you have Zoan-type powers!
[gasps]
[screams]
Too bad. How about another one?!
Oh, yeah?
Weight point!
Swamp cloud burger!
[CHOPPER]
That again?!
Guard point!
Why that insolent little--!
[CHOPPER]
Brain point!
Rumble Scope! A weak point!
He's got to have
some weak point!
Anything'll do!
I need to find
a weakness and escape!
Jet Punch, contact!
[CHOPPER] Even with
my guard up, it's useless.
[ROBIN]
You big oaf!
Can't you see you're destroying
valuable artifacts?
[YAMA laughs] You should
probably concern yourself
with preserving your own life
instead of this
crumbling heap of rubble.
Punch mountain!
Oh no!
Stop this, you fool.
Ugh!
It seems like this
stupid cave goes on forever.
No matter how far I walk
I can't find the way out.
[stomach growls]
Oh, man I'm getting hungry.
I don't see anything
to eat around this place.
I wonder what Chopper and
the others are up to right now.
I hope they're not headed
to the city of gold without me.
[CHOPPER]
His feet.
[chuckles]
That's the weak spot.
[CHOPPER]
Walk point!
Can I escape?
I can't even see straight.
Still think you can win?
[CHOPPER]
My legs are shaky at best.
And the rumble ball
is about to wear off.
[CHOPPER] All right.
It's time to stop running.
[CHOPPER]
You can beat him!
[GEDATSU]
What do you think you're doing?
Swamp cloud burger!
[CHOPPER] I'm always
the first to run away,
so everyone thinks
they have to protect me.
[CHOPPER] That's why
they can't rely on me.
I'm going to raise
a pirate flag right here!
Don't you know
when you've lost?
Even the air is
my territory to control.
You can't escape.
[CHOPPER]
C'mon.
Oh no! He took it off.
That raccoon dog took my shoe.
So careless!
I'm coming, racoon dog
Ahhh! I'm a monster!
I'm strong!
[laughs] The weakest
beast roars the loudest.
One last jet punch!
I let myself get carried away
and nearly lost control
of my mantra.
[CHOPPER]
He only grazed me!
That was close!
Arm point!
I'm alive!
[CHOPPER]
My turn.
Cloven.... Cross!
[screams]
Finally, I'm one
of the pirates, too!
[CHOPPER] It looks like he
fell right into a swamp cloud!
Good. Now if he
would just stay there.
You hear me? Don't come up.
Just keep on sinking, you jerk!
[gasps]
[screams]
He's moving!
He's still alive.
[GEDATSU] I can't believe
I lost to a raccoon dog.
Of all the things,
I could never live down.
And how did I get stuck
in my own swamp cloud?
This isn't supposed
to happen to me!
[shrieks] Please, oh,
please, just stay down!
Sink! Sink!
[GEDATSU]
I can escape with a milky dial.
Wow he really sank!
[GEDATSU]
So careless!
[CHOPPER]
Did I? I did. I really beat him!
[GEDATSU]
So careless!
[AISA] Another one
of the priest's voices
just disappeared.
Something terrible
must have happened!
This is bad! I have
to get to the others!
Oh, no! Of course,
you just had to break down
at a time like this, didn't you?
No! Work!
I barely know how
to ride this thing.
How can I fix it?
There's no way.
Huh?
[shrieks]
[AISA]
Help! Help me, please! Help!
[horn trumpeting]
[AISA]
Don't eat me!
I don't want to die!
[horn trumpeting]
Please hurry, Father!
[PAGAYA]
I'm trying,
but I don't know if
we'll make it at this speed.
I'm about to gun it so hang on!
Right!
[SUU]
Suu Suu!
[AISA screams]
[PAGAYA]
Now, Conis!
[CONIS]
Right!
Grab on! Reach out
and take my hand!
[PAGAYA]
That was a risky move.
Don't worry, you're safe now.
You're a Shandorian
child aren't you?
You don't have
to be afraid little girl.
We're friendly.
[AISA]
I'm not afraid!
I'm one of the
brave warriors of Shandora.
I'm not afraid of you Skypieans!
[SUU]
Suu Suu!
Her name is Suu.
And she seems
to like you quite a bit.
[SUU]
Suu!
You can call me Conis.
[PAGAYA]
I'm Pagaya, Conis's father.
Pleased to meet you little girl.
We're very glad
you're all right.
So, can you tell us your name?
Everyone calls me Aisa.
Look, I know you just saved me,
and I hate to ask
any more favors.
But I need to go
to the Upper Yard,
and I was wondering
if you would take me.
Because right now
there are all kinds
of people's voices
disappearing more and more.
It's the truth!
I can hear their voices,
even from very far away.
Then they're gone.
Actually, we're already
on our way to Upper Yard,
so you can ride with us.
Yeah?
We're trying to find the pirates
from the Blue Sea World
because we thought we should
guide them safely out of Skypiea
and get them
where they need to go.
You mean all those
people on the ship?
Ah. Yes.
They're probably
still trying to escape
from the Upper Yard.
Do you know where
their ship could be?
It's very important.
[AISA]
Mm-hmm.
[CONIS]
Father!
[PAGAYA]
I understand.
All we need is for you
to lead us there, little one.
[AISA]
Sure.
[CHOPPER]
I'm finally a pirate!
I think instead of
looking for the others
I'll just look for the gold!
That would sure shock everybody!
That place over there
seems like a good spot
for gold to hide.
[CHOPPER]
Who knows.
Maybe the others
will end up there too.
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[LUFFY]
Aww!
I'm hungry!
There's gotta be something
to eat around here.
Or not.
[CONIS]
Are you all right?
You've been shaking
for a while now.
[AISA] I've never felt
this afraid before.
Everyone's voices
just keep disappearing.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Unbeatable Powers!
Eneru's True Form is Revealed!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!