[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
[screaming]
[LUFFY]
...Bazooka!
[LUFFY grunting]
I got that jerk right
where I want him!
Time for me to end
this, right now!
[KRIEG grunts]
[groaning]
[ZEFF] Even with a hundred
thousand more weapons,
our chore boy can still
bring him to his knees,
because he does not know fear.
Krieg may have more
pirates at his command,
He may have terrible weapons
that cause mass destruction
to every thing in his path,
but he will never have
that kid's heart.
[SANJI]
The All Blue...
I'll fight until
victory is mine!
[KRIEG groans]
[GHIN]
Don Krieg...
We lost.
[PIRATES]
Commander!
Thanks for everything, Sanji.
When he wakes up,
give him a message.
Tell him that I'll
see him again.
Somewhere out there,
on the Grand Line.
Heh. It's my silly dream.
With this poison in my veins,
I may only have a
few hours to live.
But I feel free somehow,
like now, I can live those last
few moments on my own terms.
Pursue your dreams with every
last fiber of what you are.
Then you will never again feel
lost, or hopeless, or afraid.
I learned all of that
from a brave chore boy.
Well then. We gratefully
accept this boat.
Am I right to assume there's
no need to return it?
[SANJI] It yours, don't
ever come back here.
Not for anything.
Not even to return this boat.
[PATTY]
He's right!
And don't you ever forget,
This is the restaurant
where the cooks fight!
The Baratie!
[GHIN] Hm. The cooks
there sure mean business.
[LUFFY]
"Set Sail!
The Seafaring Cook
Sets off With Luffy!"
[LUFFY snoring]
[booming]
[LUFFY grunts]
Waa! My hat!
Where's my hat?!
It's right there, calm down.
[LUFFY]
Oh good, here it is.
[SANJI]
Have a good nap?
[LUFFY]
Hey... Those pirates...
[SANJI] They're gone now,
all thanks to you.
[LUFFY]
Me?
[SANJI] Yeah, and Ghin asked
me to tell you that he said,
"See you on the Grand Line".
Huh, he did?
To you?
[SANJI]
No, to you!
So, I guess I don't have to
do anymore lame‐o chores,
since I got those pirates
off your back, right?
That's the deal.
Hey, I was wondering...
[SANJI] No, I'm not
gonna run away with you
to become a pirate.
[LUFFY]
Aw...
I've got some unfinished
business here.
I'll stay until Zeff
acknowledges my skill.
Okay then, I give up.
That means you let go!
[grunts]
I can't just leave...
These bozos don't
know the first thing
about how to run a restaurant.
But still, I promised myself
that one of these days...
I'll go to the Grand Line.
[laughs]
Well, let's go right now!
It just isn't the
right time. Not yet.
[SANJI]
There is one place.
Say, have you ever
heard of the All Blue?
[LUFFY]
Nuh‐uh.
You've got to be kidding me!
That sea is a miracle.
[gasps]
[SANJI]
In the All Blue,
there are fish from the
East Blue, the West Blue,
the North Blue,
and the South Blue.
That one stretch
of ocean has it all!
[ZEFF]
Hmph.
To us cooks, it's a
culinary dream come true.
A place that fantastic
has got to be on the Grand
Line somewhere, right?
I mean, where else...
[ZEFF] The little brat
looks truly happy.
Heh. What an idiot.
[PATTY]
Alright guys! Soups on!
[COOKS chatter]
[SANJI huffs]
Really?
Oh good, they saved
us some seats.
They did?
No chairs left for you.
[COOK O laughs]
Just sit on the floor and eat!
There are no chairs?
That doesn't seem right.
This is a restaurant.
[SANJI]
All right, fine.
They sure are acting strange.
[SANJI grumbles]
Well, that's nothing new.
Bunch of jerks.
[PATTY]
Hey! What is this?
Who prepared the
soup this morning?!
Oh! I did!
This stuff is pretty good, huh?
I think I really out did myself!
[PATTY]
Is that a joke?!
I can barely hold this
slop down! Bleh! Bleh!
[SANJI growls]
[SANJI] I thought someone
like you, would like slop.
It makes sense to me, seeing
as, that's what pigs like.
Ha! Just face it Sanji, your
soup sucks. It's disgusting!
Bleh, bleh, bleh!
That soup is nothing
short of a delicacy.
There's something wrong
with your taste buds!
Ugh! That's gross!
[COOK A]
I can't eat this!
Bleh, bleh! Revolting!
[COOK D coughs]
This soup is horrible!
[COOKS murmur]
What the hell's going
on, you bastards?!
We're sick of the
way you run things!
You're a sham of a Sous Chef
and everybody knows it!
You can't just settle every
single little disagreement
with violence!
If the food's bad,
then we're gonna say so!
[growls] What'd you say?!
Don't forget that
we're seafaring cooks.
So, you'd better not waste
one single drop of that soup!
[ALl gasp]
[SANJI gasps]
[COOKS]
Boss!
Geezer!
That wretched little dish
tasted like stewed garbage.
If we ever served that
kind of trash here,
we'd go out of business!
[SANJI]
Are you really this stupid?!
Just how is my
soup any different
from the stuff you make? How?!
You think they're the same?
[SANJI grunting]
[ZEFF growls]
Don't flatter yourself!
[COOKS gasp]
[PATTY]
The Boss punched him!
[CARNE]
He didn't kick him!
[grunts]
You think you can lecture me
on the art of cooking, do ya?
Fat chance!
I'm a man who has
cooked on more seas
than days that
you've been alive!
[SANJI grunts]
[growls]
[SANJI]
Damn it!
That worthless old man...
[SANJI]
I'm not a little brat, anymore!
[LUFFY slurps]
Gah! What's all the fuss about?
This soup's totally awesome!
All of us know the soup is good.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
I know he's an outstanding chef.
Everyone here on
the Baratie does.
Yeah, he's great.
Aside from Chef Zeff,
he's the best we got.
[COOK D]
That was scary wasn't it?
He seriously snapped.
[COOK O]
Yeah...
[ZEFF] But that
thick skulled idiot
wouldn't listen to us if
we tried to reason with him.
[growls]
Hey, listen.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[ZEFF] You were saying
that you needed
a cook for your ship, right?
Well, this isn't something I
want to be asking anyone,
but... would you mind taking
that little brat along with you?
Take him to the Grand Line.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
That would be best for him.
The Grand Line is his dream.
Geez, Boss, you sure made
us put on a hell of a show.
Oh man, I was worried he
was gonna figure it out
'cause of your bad acting!
[laughing]
C'mon, Your acting was
way worse than mine!
[COOK D] I'm gonna get
some more of that soup!
[COOK O]
Yeah, that stuff is good!
[SANJI grumbles]
[SANJI] I can hear
everything, Dumbasses.
[ZEFF]
So, what do you say, Kid?
No way.
But earlier, you mentioned you
needed a cook for your ship.
Just what are you trying to say?
That he's suddenly not
good enough for ya'?
Oh, he's good.
And I'd love it if he joined
my crew and came with us.
But, it seems like he
really wants to stay here
and cook with all of you guys.
You can ask me all you want,
but I'm just not gonna take him.
So you're saying you
can't agree to it
until he tells you
himself, s'that right?
That's right! More food, please!
Well, I suppose
that's fair enough.
But, who knows if that
hardheaded little brat
will ever agree to
join up with you.
[PATTY] Yeah, Once that
guy makes up his mind,
there's nothin' anybody
can do to change it.
[LUFFY]
More, please!
[gasps]
[YOSAKU screams]
[screaming continues]
[SANJI yells]
[SANJI grunts]
Sanji!
What is that? A fishman?
[COOK D] Did he come all the
way from the Fishman Islands
‐‐to eat here?
‐‐ [COOK E] You dolt!
It's a human and a panshark!
[LUFFY]
Huh? What's this?
Whoa! It's Yosaku!
Oh, hey... Big Bro Luffy.
How come you're alone?
Where are the others?
‐‐Did you find Nami?
‐‐[YOSAKU groans]
[YOSAKU] We never
actually caught up to her,
but, from the direction
Big Sis is headed,
we think we've figured
out where she's going
and what she plans to do.
[LUFFY] I see.... Then we
can bring her back.
Maybe... It's just...
IF our suspicions
turn out to be true,
then the place she intends to
go could mean certain death
for all of us, if we follow her.
[LUFFY grunts]
[YOSAKU] The point is, we really
need your help, Big Bro Luffy.
Please! Come with me!
Okay... I don't really get it,
but I got it. Let's go.
[SANJI]
Wait.
Your dream is foolish.
Then again, so's mine.
Now is as good a time as any.
Why not start my
quest, right now?
[LUFFY]
Sanji...
I'll be joining
your little crew,
on your journey to be
King of the Pirates.
[gasps]
[SANJI]
You hear me?
I want to be the
cook on your ship.
[PATTY, CARNE]
Huh?
All right, whadya' say?
Yeah!
Of course!
[YOSAKU]
This is great, Big Bro Luffy!
[BOTH]
Woo hoo!
We got a cook!
Now we'll get the tasty food!
[SANJI] Are you guys
happy now, or what?
Sorry. Really, I'll leave now.
Ha! I don't like it!
To tell ya' the truth,
I was hopin' to
give you the boot
from this restaurant personally.
But, it seems that you
don't have a problem
with straight up abandoning us.
I'm especially sorry
for making the lot of
you resort to bad acting.
Hey, wait! How'd you know?
[SANJI]
I heard everything!
You bunch of jerks!
What?!
Was stomping on my pride
the best plan that you
could come up with?
Was it?
You damn geezer.
Every little thing has
to be a fight with you!
Well, I'm sick and tired of it!
Bring it on! Huh?
[ZEFF] Hmph. I never
have liked children.
As a matter of fact,
I hate children.
There wasn't a day passed
when I didn't regret
letting a useless little
brat like you live, Sanji.
Ha! Fine by me,
you rotten old man.
Enjoy the rest of
your miserable life.
[YOSAKU] Whoa!
This is a nice ship!
You sure it's okay to use her?
[COOK A] Of course!
It's Sanji's ship!
[COOK B]
You still need more?
[LUFFY]
Yup! Gonna need more meat!
All right, well how many days
are you gonna be out at sea?
[LUFFY]
I don't know...
[ZEFF]
Kid?
[LUFFY]
Hm? Hey, Pops!
Would you like this?
It's my logbook,
a detailed record of my one
year journey to the Grand Line.
No thanks.
He. He. I knew it!
[laughs]
[LUFFY] Oooh‐ ooh! I want
some more of that marbled meat!
That's enough meat for you!
[SANJI] It's the nicest sea
restaurant I've ever seen!
That's for sure!
[ZEFF]
Hey, Sanji, listen...
[SANJI]
Hm? What is it?
[ZEFF] It doesn't matter
what sort of person
walks through our doors.
If they're hungry...
Then they will be fed...
Every starving wretch who comes
to us will get a fine meal.
We can make that happen.
It doesn't matter
how much we fight,
because we share the same dream.
[SANJI laughs]
Yeah!
[ZEFF]
Are you ready?
'Cause we're gonna be busy!
[SANJI] You bet! It won't be
a problem with me around!
[SANJI yelps]
Ow...
Awful!
‐‐[ZEFF grunts]
‐‐[SANJI yelps]
Is that what you call peeling?!
[SANJI]
That hurt, you old fart!
I'm trying to cook here!
Just stay outta my way,
and we won't have any
problems! Got it?!
[ZEFF]
What?!
You better watch your
mouth, you little brat!
[SANJ] I'm not a little brat,
you crusty old geezer!
[SANJI]
Heh! Try this.
[ZEFF] Did you make
it all by yourself?
Uh‐huh!
[SANJI]
How is it?
This is the worst soup I've
ever had, you little brat!
[SANJI whimpers]
You mean, old geezer!
[YOSAKU] Big Bro Cook
sure is taking his time.
[LUFFY]
Yeah...
Now, it's payback time!
Here it comes, Sanji!
[PATTY, CARNE yell]
[PATTY grunts]
[CARNE yelps]
Really guys, that was just dumb.
Let's get going.
[LUFFY]
You don't need to say goodbye?
No, it's fine.
[ZEFF]
Sanji?
Take care of yourself, okay?
[SANJI whimpers]
[whimpering continues]
Chef Zeff!
Thanks, you geezer!
I'll never forget your kindness!
I owe my life to you, Old Man!
So, thank you!
[sobbing]
[ZEFF whimpers]
[sobbing continues]
[PATTY whimpering]
You asshole!
I'm gonna miss you so much!
I'll miss you too!
[COOKS sobbing]
You damn wusses!
Real men should part without
a word, let alone tears!
[LUFFY]
Let's go! Set sail!
I will see you again!
I'll come back someday!
‐‐[COOKS] Bye!
‐‐[PATTY] Bye, Sanji!
[COOKS]
We're gonna miss you!
[PATTY]
Good luck!
[ZEFF] As long as you sail with
enough faith in yourself,
that you have no fear...
not even of death...
You will find the All Blue.
I'm sure of it.
[ZEFF]
All right, men!
Customers will be here soon!
Get to work already!
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[SANJI] Sounds like Nami's
headed to Arlong Park.
[LUFFY]
What's that?
[SANJI] It's a place over
run by fishman pirates.
[LUFFY]
She couldn't be...
[SANJI] With her looks,
she might be a mermaid.
[LUFFY]
Maybe a water imp.
[SANJI]
I'll kill you!
[LUFFY]
Maybe she's half fishman.
[SANJI]
No meals for you!
[LUFFY]
Why?
On the next One Piece,
"The Worst Man in
the Eastern Seas!
Fishman Pirate Arlong!"
I'm gonna be
King of The Pirates!