Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[LUFFY]
You don't recognize me?
The name's Monkey D. Luffy.
Gum-Gum...
...Rifle!
Aaaa...
Huuuhhhh?
[LUFFY] There's only
one Luffy. It's me.
You got a problem with that?
Now Gum-Gum Storm!
Wait, we're not
dreaming, are we?
I never thought
I'd see this day.
It's true. Straw Hat
really is our savior!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372H]
Oars is down!
The battle is over!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 372I]
We're finally gonna get
our shadows back!
Thriller Bark has fallen!
[LUFFY] "The End of
the Battle is Nigh!
Pound in the Finishing Move."
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373A]
Straw Hat! You're amazing!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373B]
You beat Oars!
[cheering]
Hey! C'mon! Pull it together!
Luffy!
Can you hear me?
Say something!
I think all those
shadows we gave him
were too much after all!
Even someone as powerful
as him still isn't invincible.
He absorbed the strength
of a hundred shadows.
He pushed his body
to the absolute limit.
Unless we want all
of this to be for nothin',
we gotta get those
shadows back right now!
He's right! We gotta hurry!
Take a look to the east
and see how bad it is yourself!
The sun will be up soon!
So what now?
What do we have to do
to get the shadows back?
[USOPP] He took four
of them from our crew!
We had a plan,
but there's a little snag.
Straw Hat was the one
who was gonna make
Moria give them back.
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
I don't think he can move
in his condition.
Much less make
anybody do anything.
[LOLA] Moria took the shadows
and placed them into zombies.
As the lord of the shadows,
he and he alone must
order them to return
to their former masters.
Otherwise, they'll stay
right where they are.
[RISKY BRO. BROWN HAIR]
Less talk, more action!
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
Right!
We gotta force Moria to give
the order to release them,
no matter what!
If we don't get the shadows
back, beating him was pointless!
This is bad!
Oars is back on his feet!
That's impossible!
How the hell is he able to move
after a beating like that?
[RISKY BRO. BROWN HAIR]
That's it.
We're done for!
Most of the Straw Hats are down
for the count--
they were our last hope!
And the shadows!
We already used them against
him and it wasn't enough!
That was the best shot we had!
Even if the Straw Hats
could fight, he's too strong!
That didn't hurt at all.
Damn you!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373C]
He really is a demon!
There's no way we can win!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373D]
We're completely out of options.
We never stood a chance!
We'll be stuck living in this
darkness forever! Forever!
We gotta retreat.
If we stay here,
we're all gonna die!
Yeah.
Let's head back to the forest
where the sun never shines.
Back to the night forever.
[ROLLING PIRATE 373A]
I don't believe it!
I'm not sure how
it was for Luffy,
but Oars took
one hell of a beating.
Whoa, hold on,
you need to take it easy!
You don't wanna die, do ya?
[LOLA] After Oars
pounded him mercilessly.
He can still stand?
How can that be?
Is he some kind of zombie, too?
Wha--What happened to the
bodies of the Straw Hat crew?
They were right here!
Where'd they go?
What the--?
Hey, you're right! They were
here just a second ago!
They're unconscious!
They can't move
around on their own!
What happened to these two?
Huh? They're gone!
That long-nosed guy and
the woman just disappeared!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373E]
They couldn't have gotten up
and run away on
their own, could they?
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373F]
How could they all disappear
at the same time?
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373G]
We can't worry about it now.
We gotta run!
I'd love to give 'im
just one more punch.
[RISKY BRO. BROWN HAIR]
Straw Hat!
You too? What are
you guys made of?
[LUFFY]
But I can't move, dammit!
My body's too worn
out to get up right now.
Hey, Robin!
[ROBIN]
Yes. I'm right here.
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373A]
Hey! They didn't run away!
I wanna get up there.
I understand. I'll provide
some footholds for you.
I, too, am still
willing and able to help.
Ahh! A living, breathing,
talking skeleton with an afro!
Huh? No way!
Good to hear!
I've already got a plan.
[NAMI]
Just as I thought!
[ROLLING PIRATES]
Huh?!
[NAMI] Everybody's back up
and ready for the next round!
[RISKY BRO. BROWN HAIR]
She's back!
And how did she get up there?
Wait.
You mean these guys didn't
even think about running away?
From the second that
Oars stood back up again?
They were all just getting
ready for the next round!
Just wait.
Chopper! We gotta hurry!
The sun's coming up!
Right!
Do ya think we can
still use this thing?
[FRANKY]
It's fine! Come on!
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
I don't believe it!
And to think we were all
about to throw in the towel!
Hey, it's about
to get real ugly here,
so get outta the way!
[ALL] Okay, gotcha!
We'll leave it to you, then!
Now Pierna Fleurs!
[BROOK]
Yo ho ho ho!
--[BROOK] Here we go!
--[LUFFY] Let's do it!
[BROOK]
Yohohoho!
Hey! Come back!
The heck is this stuff?
Some smoke? Clouds?
The forecast calls for rain!
Cool Ball!
Rain Tempo!
[gasps]
Where'd that rain come from?
Yeah, is she some kind
of wizard or something?
[USOPP and FRANKY]
All right!
"Emergency Plumbing"
Construction complete!
Cut it out!
Now! Coup de Vent!
What the--?
Come on, Usopp!
Give it all you've got!
I am!
[FRANKY]
If you wanna freeze a giant,
nothing beats a Supersize
Subzero Wind Cannon!
Now! Fire!
Crap! I'm frozen!
I can't move!
Awesome!
They froze him
with the rainwater!
Now it's my turn!
What?
Suck on this!
Stupid chain!
You did it!
Get this thing off me!
Nice! Good shot!
[SANJI]
Thanks!
Now! Toss me!
Are you sure about this?
Yes, I'm sure!
I'll be fine!
My body's made of rubber!
[BROOK]
Take care!
Time for Third Gear!
Bone Balloon!
Zoro! Your turn!
Go for the stomach!
Leave it to me.
Three-Sword Style,
Ultimate Attack:
[ZORO]
3,000 Worlds!
[SANJI] My turn again.
Take this!
Good one, Sanji!
We got his back nice
and straight now!
What in the hell
are these guys doing?
His structure's the
same as a human's,
which means his
spine is S-shaped,
designed to carry weight as well
as soften impact to the body.
But when the spine is
pulled into a straight line
it won't be able
to absorb impact,
and he'll have to bear the
full force of Luffy's attack!
Do it!
Best of luck!
Get ready for
a Special Bazooka!
Huh? So what?
I'll just knock you back
with my own Special Bazooka!
Gum-Gum...
My arm's bein' all crappy!
I can't stretch!
His inability to feel
any pain turned out
to be a weakness.
Time to finish him off
and take back your shadow!
[LUFFY]
Now Gum-Gum...
[cheering]
Take him down, Straw Hat!
[USOPP and FRANKY]
Do it!
Here's my Giant Bazooka!
Yo ho!!
[RISKY BROS. and LOLA]
He did it!
[panting]
I don't care
if you're a zombie.
No one could get back up
after something like that.
He lost. He really lost.
Even though he was so big.
What's gonna happen
to Thriller Bark?
They really did it.
I knew they could.
That Straw Hat crew
is something else.
It seems like I invited nothing
but trouble to the island.
[GYORO] What happened
to our master?
Can anybody see him?
They did it!
They really did it this time!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373H]
Thank you so much!
You guys are the best!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 373I]
They really were
our shining stars of hope!
[LOLA] I told you,
Straw Hat is our savior!
Let's hear it for--
[LOLA] What the hell?
I don't understand!
Why'd you get so tiny?
It doesn't hurt,
but I can't move.
[CHOPPER] He's still conscious.
Even with his bones
crushed, he can't die.
These zombies really do
make a mockery of life.
The sun's coming up!
What is this?
This strange sensation
coursing through my bones.
[cheering]
Hey, Luffy! Hurry up
with those shadows!
The sun is coming up!
What are you cheering about?
Unless you get
your shadows back,
you're all gonna burn to ashes!
Wow, you're right!
I forgot! We gotta hurry!
[LOLA]
All right, then.
Let's go wake
Moria with a beating
and make him
release the shadows!
Morning's almost here!
No need. I'm awake.
[ROLLING PIRATES]
Moria?!
Master's alive!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Of course, I wasn't
worried about him at all!
Fine.
That just saves us the trouble
of waking you ourselves.
Now, unless you want
another serious beating
from the Straw Hats,
you'll do what we say!
Give the order!
Return all the shadows! Now!
[RISKY BRO. BROWN HAIR]
Yeah!
Give 'em back, you bastard!
Kushishishi!
What do you think this is,
a playground brawl?
A true pirate would never
bow to demands like that,
not even if his
life depended on it!
So you teamed up
with those losers
from the forest, did you?
What a joke.
Now I see how Straw Hat got that
ridiculous increase in power!
How desperate you must be
to use my own shadow
abilities against me!
You shut your mouth!
Return the shadows at once!
Straw Hat Luffy!
You've got some nerve making
a mess of Thriller Bark!
You'll pay for what you've
done to my glorious ship!
You're the one
who's gonna pay!
It's your fault for
picking a fight with my crew!
Now give back those shadows
before the sun comes up!
Kushishishi!
Why, when at this point,
all I have to do is sit around
and wait for you all to die.
I'm afraid you're not cut
out for the New World, kid!
I admit you've got
some good underlings,
but it doesn't matter.
All will be lost.
And do you know why?
Straw Hat!
This isn't exactly the time
to sit around and chit-chat!
Take a look at the sky!
It's getting brighter!
Focus on getting
the shadows back!
We're almost out of time!
Because unlike me,
you've yet to realize
the weakness of your crew!
I trusted my
underlings as you do,
but despite their talents,
do you know why
I ended up losing them?
Because they were mortal!
That's what makes things
different this time!
Had they been zombies
from the beginning,
I would have
had nothing to lose!
Zombies are fearless,
eternal, relentless warriors
that can be replaced,
even if they fall!
Now, with my army
of the undead,
there's nothing in the
world that will stop me
from becoming
King of the Pirates!
You and your crew
should be grateful
for the chance to
serve as my slaves!
[ZOMBIE 373A]
It's got me!
[MORIA] Now, every last
shadow in Thriller Bark.
Come to me, and become my power!
Shadows Asgard!
What's happening?
His shadow came out!
All these shadows.
No way!
He's gathering up every
shadow on this island
and pumping them into his body!
Tell me, Straw Hat Luffy.
From your strength,
I'd say you absorbed about
a hundred shadows, right?
Then I shall take--100!
[MORIA]
200!
300!
[MORIA]
400!
500!
[MORIA]
600!
700!
[MORIA]
800!
900!
Kushishishi! Kushishishi!
1,000!
[RISKY BRO. BROWN HAIR]
We are so screwed!
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
There's no way we can win now.
He's a thousand times bigger
and stronger than before.
[LUFFY] I don't care how
big or strong he gets.
I won't quit till he spits out
every one of those shadows.
I'm going to the
New World no matter what!
On the next One Piece:
"Our Bodies Vanish!
The Morning Sun Shines
on the Nightmarish Island!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!