[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see
And we know that our
hearts have brought us here
Where the compass
points our destiny
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
We know we'll get there
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true
You and those dreams
are precious in my life
A glimpse of the sun rising
on our tomorrow!
[SANJI]
Now's our chance!
[JONATHAN grunting]
[JESSICA]
We almost had them!
[LUFFY]
See ya 'round, fortress guy!
You don't know me?! [screams]
[DRAKE]
Lock him up, men!
You should be more
grateful to Robin.
[gasps] I see.
Robin knew that I would really
be safer here with you.
[ROBIN] We may have had a chance
for a clean escape earlier.
Looks like there's only
one way out of this place.
[LUFFY] "Luffy and Sanji's
Daring Rescue Mission!"
[OFFICER B]
Listen up, men!
Among the Straw Hats
we've captured,
one was impersonating
a Marine officer!
So in the future, do not worry
about reports or paperwork.
If you see an
unidentified person,
arrest him immediately!
[MARINES]
Sir!
[WORKER G]
Did you hear?
That long-nosed guy that
was snooping around here
is a crewmember
of the Straw Hats.
[WORKER E]
I wonder what he was doing
nosin' around this dock?
Yeah, there's an
entire harbor here
full of ships that
are way better than
this sad little hunk of junk.
He could've hopped in
any of these ships
and sailed away.
[WORKER G] Pirates are
dumber than I thought.
[WORKER E]
Me too, and I already thought
they were pretty
dumb to begin with!
[WORKER G, WORKER F laughing]
Hey, already callin' it
quits for the day, Mechao?
[MECHAO] Cut this old geezer
some slack, will ya?
Did he say "geezer"?
[WORKER E]
We must've heard wrong!
[BOTH laugh]
[SANJI]
You numbskull!
At least try to be careful!
[LUFFY]
Oh. Sorry.
[SANJI] This fortress is really
starting to drive me nuts!
[LUFFY] Hey, Sanji,
where are Zoro and Usopp?
[SANJI] Well, detective,
since they were captured,
they're probably in the brig.
[LUFFY]
Awesome! To the brig!
[SANJI] Do you know where the
brig is, oh fearless leader?
[LUFFY]
No, I thought you knew.
[SANJI]
How would I know that?
[LUFFY]
Hmm.
That big bellybutton island
with the guns looks suspicious.
Yeah? Why's that?
I dunno.
[SANJI grunts]
In any case, you might
just be on to something.
It's surrounded by the sea.
And the only way to get there
is to cross that bridge.
It won't be easy,
but we gotta try.
[LUFFY]
All righty!
[BOTH]
Hm?
Damn. This plan is already
a pain in the neck.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[MARINE A] Sir! I'm in
section 4 of block F.
Nothing unusual to report.
[OFFICER D]
Good work! Keep searching!
[MARINE A]
Yes, sir!
Crap.
The patrols are using
mini-transponder snails
to communicate.
This'll be tough.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Sanji.
[SANJI]
Hm?
Secret missions are
fun, huh? [giggles]
[SANJI]
Get a move on, monkey boy!
[MARINE X humming]
[MARINE X grunts]
[SHEPHERD groaning]
What the? [gasps]
[MARINE X]
Don't move!
[ROBIN]
This is strange.
There's times when no
ships enter or leave.
Why is that?
[ROBIN gasps]
[ROBIN]
I'm being watched.
[SHEPHERD] What do you think
you're doing, soldier?
Do you peons know who I am?
Hah. Oh, yeah, you made sure
to tell us over and over.
You're Special Inspector
Major Shepherd from HQ, right?
[SHEPHERD] If you know who
I am and you value your job,
then get me out of here!
I have to speak to Commander
Jonathan immediately!
[USOPP]
Major Shepherd?
This must be the Marine bigwig
that Robin was pretending to be!
Those guards think
he's one of us!
[USOPP]
In that case...
[USOPP] That's enough!
You're embarrassing yourself!
A man's gotta know
when he's done for.
Struggling will only
make it worse.
Good to see you, Condoriano.
C-Condoriano? Who is that?
What are you talking about?
Hey, now.
Stop kidding around,
ole' buddy, ole' pal.
Don't tell me you've already
forgotten your own name,
and my beautiful face!
[SHEPHERD grunts]
Get away! I'm not your buddy!
Soldier! I don't know this man!
What happened to you?
Did the fall damage
your fragile brain?
Oh, no, say it ain't so!
How--how sad!
I'm begging you!
Please let this wretch with
the broken mind out of here!
He's not the same Condoriano
that I once knew!
[MARINE A]
Well, that settles it.
Yep, no point in
interrogating him.
What do you lemmings
mean "that settles it"?
Wait! Where're you going?
I'm ordering you!
Come back!
I'll have you all
court-martialed!
[ZORO]
Condoriano.
Huh?
Condoriano?
I think we've had just
about enough of that crap.
[USOPP]
Nice move, Zoro!
[USOPP giggling]
It worked!
You owe me big time, Robin!
[ZORO] Stop it, Usopp,
you're creeping me out.
[LUFFY groans, chuckles]
[DRAKE]
Commander.
We haven't received
a single report
on the whereabouts of Luffy
or the other Straw Hats.
[JONATHAN]
Hmm...
Have you decided on a
course of action yet?
[JONATHAN]
My guess is that they're
having a hard time
finding the brig.
Maybe we should
guide them to it.
Huh?
[JONATHAN] Take your men to the
brig and wait for them there.
But be careful not to
spring the trap too soon.
Uh--sir!
[JONATHAN chuckles]
[JONATHAN]
This is a battle of wits, Luffy,
and you are simply
out of your league.
What are you waiting for, Sanji?
Hush.
Dammit.
We're gonna have to
fight our way through.
[SANJI]
Hello.
The underside of the bridge
is completely unguarded.
C'mon, Luffy! That's our way in!
Huh? Cool!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[JONATHAN]
This is Commander Jonathan.
[MARINE F]
Reporting in, sir!
The suspect we took
into custody earlier
was identified by
the long-nosed man
as a Straw Hat named Condoriano.
Condoriano?
[MARINE F]
Yes, sir!
He has repeatedly claimed
that he is Special
Inspector Shepherd.
[JONATHAN]
Hmm.
[MARINE F] But we now
know that he was lying.
[JONATHAN]
Very good. Keep me updated.
There are two Shepherds, huh?
[JONATHAN]
Your move, Luffy!
Hey, Zoro.
You get the feeling
something's not right here?
There's tension in
the air. I feel it.
[MECHAO gasps]
Huh? Mechao?
Yeah. The guy from the docks!
What?
What are you doing here,
you crazy old fart?
[MECHAO] I came down here to
ask a question, that's all!
There's no need
for those swords!
Put 'em away!
[ZORO]
Hmph. It's a trap.
So. The question.
[MECHAO]
It's not for you.
I need to talk to Long-nose
in that cell over there.
[growls] Wait!
You can't just walk in here and
start talking to the prisoners!
[MECHAO] It won't take long.
I'll be gone before you know it.
Hey!
Uh, you're that guy from--
[DRAKE growls]
[USOPP] Did anything
happen to the Merry?
Is she all right?
Don't worry, she's in good hands
for the time being, I promise.
Your ship is okay.
[sighs] What a relief!
You're the one who does the
repairs on that ship, right?
Uh? Yeah, well...
You gotta to do something
about those mast plates.
[USOPP]
Hm?
If you nail steel plates down
without applying
a proper splice,
the mast will snap like a twig
at the first sign
of a strong wind.
A splice?
Really? You don't know
what a splice is?
Actually,
I have to admit I'm not
really a bonified mechanic.
The one who fixed
the ship, uh...
Did he do all the repairs
in just one night?
[USOPP] Yeah! It happened
in a place called sky island
that's miles and miles
above the ocean!
[MECHAO]
Miles above the ocean?
Yeah, yeah, it's okay
if you don't believe me,
I mean who would?
[MECHAO] Hmm... Well,
come to think of it,
your ship did fall out
of the sky, didn't it?
What? You're not
gonna call me a liar?
[MECHAO] I might've thought
you were pulling my leg
if I didn't see it
with my own eyes.
But considering the
angle that it came down,
it looks like your ship fell
from a considerable height.
It was crazy!
There were gods and angels!
We saw things up there
I never even dreamed of!
[MECHAO]
Gods and angels? Ha, ha, ha.
Sounds to me like you died
and came back to life!
[USOPP]
There were close calls,
but I don't think
I actually died.
[USOPP, MECHAO laughing]
[MECHAO]
Oh, right!
About what you were
saying earlier.
Think back to the night
that the mystery man
repaired your ship.
Tell me, did he appear from
the mist late in the night?
Yeah, he did! How in the
world did you know that?
Hold on, do you know
who this guy is?
I think I know what
you saw that night.
[MECHAO]
Huh? Hey, what's goin' on?
Times up, old man!
We've got business
to attend to here.
Show him the way out.
--[MARINE G] Yes, sir.
--[MECHAO] No, stop!
Wait! Mechao, tell me what
it was I saw that night!
Please, tell me!
I didn't get a
chance to tell you
the most important thing of all!
When you make repairs
to the ship,
always pay special
attention to the parts
that you normally
wouldn't bother with!
Those are the areas
that need it most!
If you treasure that ship half
as much as I think you do,
you'll do well
never to forget that!
Did you get all that?
Yeah! I got it, old man!
And I'll always remember that!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Someone came out.
[SANJI]
I don't like it.
Something definitely seems
fishy about that place.
Well, let's do it!
Hold on.
Let's take a minute
and think this through.
The path we took to get here
was completely unguarded.
It's like they're
showing us where to go.
That can only mean one thing.
[LUFFY]
I know!
The boss of this
fortress is a nice guy!
They're planning to ambush us.
If anything, it saves
time for those jerks.
We'd literally be
walking into a jail cell.
What are we waiting for?
So it's a trap, big deal.
We won't get any rescuing done
if we don't go in there.
Are you saying you want us
to run headlong into a trap?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[SANJI] Barging into a Marine
brig is never a good idea,
but it's better than
doing nothing at all.
I'm also worried about
Nami and Robin.
Sanji, it's not such a bad idea.
[SANJI]
Yes it is!
[LUFFY]
But you like it, huh?
[SANJI]
No, I don't!
Um, there's nothing in here.
Just get moving, all right?
Can do!
[LUFFY]
Hey! Zoro! Usopp!
Where are you?
Wait. That sounds
like Luffy's voice!
[LUFFY]
Hey!
It is Luffy!
Hey! Luffy, down here!
Usopp. The guards can
hear him coming, too.
[USOPP gasps]
No! Turn back!
But then who's gonna
come rescue us?
I'm confused.
Tell me what to say.
I don't know.
They can rescue us
if they want to.
[USOPP]
Rescue us if you want to!
[SANJI]
I heard someone!
[LUFFY]
This way!
Uh-oh, they're here now.
Please be careful, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Found 'em!
Hold on! We'll get you outta...
[USOPP gasps]
No! These bars,
they're Sea Prism Stone!
[DRAKE]
We've been waiting for you!
Surrender peacefully and
I might let you live!
Heh. You're kidding me, right?
Do you seriously think
that's enough to stop us?
[SERGEANT]
Is this enough for you?
Heh. Now I'm
shaking in my boots.
[SANJI]
Okay, now what do I do?
First things first!
What the?
[SANJI grunts]
Oh, this is good.
It would take nothing
short of a cannon
to break those bars down.
[SANJI grunts]
Oh man, that's one tough cage!
A cannon? That's it!
Sanji! I think I know
what will do the trick!
Reach into my pocket!
What for?
I have an impact dial in there.
You can use it to
blow up these bars!
Hold on, an impact dial?
Isn't that supposed to
hurt whoever sets it off?
Yeah, no time to be wimp though.
Hurry up and get it!
What could those Straw
Hat Pirates be up to now?
This is your last warning!
Shut up, gorilla man.
I'm gonna show you something
you might find interesting.
A shell?
[SANJI] That might not be
the best place to stand.
[USOPP]
Oh, right, right, right.
Here goes.
[USOPP]
Who? This well-mannered snake?
[DRAKE]
Hm?
[USOPP gasps]
You moron!
Was that your super
awesome secret weapon?
'Cause it's kinda lame.
Shut up or I'll gut you!
[SERGEANT]
I believe him. I'll shut up.
Oh, uh, sorry, Sanji,
I forgot it's on the
other side. Sorry.
It's, ah, this side here.
Right here...
[USOPP gasps]
Stinky.
[DRAKE]
Ahh! This smells like--!
So bad!
[gasps] What kind of
juvenile barbarian
would store a fart
in my odor dial?
I... thought it would be funny.
Why did I even have to ask?
[SANJI gasps]
Watch out! It's gonna blow!
Get down!
[MARINES gasp]
[siren blaring]
[OFFICER B] There was
an explosion in the brig!
This is not a drill. Let's move!
[SANJI grunting]
Hey! You guys okay?
Mission... accomplished?
Yeah, I guess
you could say that.
[USOPP screams]
[LUFFY]
Help me...
[SANJI]
Every time I turn around.
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO] Well, there's no
point in standing around.
Let's get outta here!
[USOPP]
Uh, thanks!
Let's go, Luffy!
Right! Everybody run!
[USOPP]
Hey! Hey! Wait a sec!
Don't let Zoro lead,
he'll get us lost!
Oh, would you just shut up?
[LUFFY laughs]
[DRAKE groans]
Is everyone alive?
[MARINE G groans]
Yeah. I think so.
[DRAKE]
Good!
Those of you who can
move, come with me!
We're going after
the Straw Hats!
No escape!
Reinforcements are already
waiting for them outside.
We'll catch them again and
execute them on the spot!
Huh.
[USOPP]
I told you! Now we're lost!
[SANJI]
Yeah, where are we?
[USOPP] How do you get lost
going to the front door?
That's almost impossible!
[ZORO]
I said shut up!
[DRAKE]
Commander! I failed.
Straw Hat Luffy has
managed to escape the trap!
What about his crewmembers?
Roaronoa and the
others with him?
[DRAKE]
Yes, sir! I mean, no, sir!
Well, uh, witnesses
reported that they didn't
see Condoriano with them.
[JONATHAN chuckles]
Well, Lt. Commander,
the bridge is still
guarded, is it not?
[DRAKE]
Uh, yes, sir!
[JONATHAN]
Very good. Then don't panic.
We still have plenty of
opportunities to capture them.
[ROBIN]
Well.
Sounds like the boys
made their move.
A future lies before us
waiting to begin
Let's take to the wind!
and search the world for answers
to all the questions
in our minds
Exploring day and night we'll...
...live out our
dreams in paradise!
And that's why...
We're running, and running,
traveling along an open road
Never letting go of
what we came to do
We're here to see this through!
We can't lose, can't lose,
nothing on earth
can stop us now
'Cause we're not afraid
of our own destiny
We Dream and live
our lives free!
[USOPP]
A trap?
[LUFFY] That means
something fun might happen!
[ZORO]
Traps schmaps.
Worrying about annoying
stuff is annoying.
[SANJI] We'll see what
kind of trap it is.
[JONATHAN] So, you think you
can escape from Navarone?
And from me?
[LUFFY] We won't get
caught! We're pirates!
On the next One Piece!
"Enter the Hot-Blooded
Special Forces!
Battle on the Bridge!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!