Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison, Impel Down.
[NARRATOR] Along the way,
he ran into Buggy,
as well as former Baroque Works
agents Mr. 3 and Mr. 2.
Together, they fell from
Level 3 down to Level 4.
[LUFFY] Hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
That smells so good.
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Oh boy, I can't wait
for yummy food time.
[LUFFY grunting]
[BON CLAY screaming]
[MAGELLAN]
It's time to put an end
to your buffoonery,
once and for all, boy!
Who're you?
It's... Magellan!
[gasps]
I've got you now,
you criminal scum!
[LUFFY]
"Mighty Magellan!
Bon Clay Bugs Out"!
[GUARD A groaning]
[yelps]
[GUARD A] Oh, crap!
I gotta get outta here!
It's truly quite hot down here.
[GUARD B]
W-Warden! Wait! Please!
Give us a second!
[GUARD C]
Don't start fighting yet!
[GUARD D]
Everyone, clear out!
The Warden's poison
will get us, too!
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
You suck!
I was finally gonna make it
to all that awesome-smelling
food over there!
I'm hot, I'm mad,
and I'm hungry!
Get the hell outta my way!
Food is your concern?
Very well, then.
Soon, you'll never have
to worry about eating again.
What's that supposed to mean?
Straw Boy, whatever you do,
don't fight him!
Listen, that's Magellan,
the Warden of Impel Down!
He has the power of
the Venom-Venom Fruit!
He's the last person
you ever wanna fight!
Make a run for it!
[LUFFY]
Venom-Venom fruit? He's poison?
[MAGELLAN]
Indeed I am.
You're a bit out of
your element, Straw Hat.
Even though you're a rookie,
I expected more from a pirate
with a bounty of 300 million,
especially one who has caused
the World Government
so much trouble.
Speaking of trouble,
I can't imagine how you managed
to worm your way through
security, but here you are.
[MAGELLAN]
Rest assured, you will suffer
for tarnishing my reputation.
I know why you're here,
by the way.
You came to rescue
your brother, Portgas D. Ace,
second division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates.
An ambitious endeavor,
if a foolish one.
Though struggle as you might,
both his fate and yours
were sealed the moment
you set foot here.
You've had quite
the little rampage,
but all of that will
come to an end now.
And one final thing,
I will find out exactly how
you broke into my prison.
You will spill every last,
juicy detail to me.
[HANCOCK]
It's safe now, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Wow, that was close!
Even so, I'm afraid
that this is as far
as I'll be able to accompany
you. They're quite insistent
on placing me in those
Sea Prism Stone Handcuffs.
And, once they take my cloak,
you'll have nowhere to hide.
I just wish-I wish I could
do more to help you, but--
Aw, don't talk like that.
You got me in
this place, didn't ya?
That's more than
I coulda done alone.
[sighs]
Luffy.
[LUFFY]
I'll die before I say a word.
Ha. You criminals always
spout that sort of nonsense
before your interrogation.
But listen, Straw Hat,
when you face the torment
I have in store for you,
you'll say anything
for the mercy of death.
[LUFFY growls]
Listen, please!
Magellan's whole body
is poisonous!
Crazy, terrible poison!
If you so much as
touch him, you're finished!
You can't beat a guy like that!
[LUFFY]
I will!
[BON CLAY] Ughh! Let's
go back the way we came.
To the Pool of Blood!
This way! Give up
on that stupid food
and let's hightail
it to Level 5!
There's no escape.
[MAGELLAN]
The staircase to Level 5
is protected by three Demon
Guards and their commander.
Hehh?!
[MAGELLAN]
Every exit on this floor
has already been accounted for.
There will be no more running.
Now, should I stop them,
or should I let
the Warden take the blame?
This is your grave!
Nooo! I won't believe it!
I can't believe it! Ah!
Hydra!
[gasps] What the heck is that?
A venom monster?
The whole thing is poison?
--[LUFFY yelps]
--[BON CLAY screaming]
Gum-Gum!
Pistol!
Don't do it!
[BON CLAY groaning]
You can't!
Why did you--?
[BOTH grunting]
Don't get in my way!
Didn't you hear me?!
You can't fight him!
Listen, if you touch
that poison anywhere,
it'll be the last thing you do!
What a buncha crap!
How am I supposed to fight him
if I can't even touch him?
You don't! That's what
I'm telling you!
Dammit! Can't you give me
some options here?!
[BON CLAY] Magellan is
only aiming for Straw Boy.
--Un, deux, trois!
--[LUFFY yelps]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Now Gum-Gum!
I said Gum-Gum!
[MAGELLAN]
Hmm?
[BON CLAY (LUFFY)]
Lovely Pistol!
Cross-Dresser Gatling!
Ballerina Giant Scythe!
A bit confused, aren't you?
"I wonder which one's
the real Straw Hat."
I'm sure it's very difficult
to tell us apart.
Hey, Bon.
You forgot the clothes.
Now that I've so cleverly
drawn the Hydra's attention,
it's time for you to
get away, dear friend.
Huh?
[BON CLAY (LUFFY)]
Here, Hydra, Hydra, Hydra!
Come on! I'm waiting for you!
[BON CLAY]
I've got you now!
I said there's no escape,
and I meant it!
It got bigger!
Wuh-oh!
"Oh, Come My Surprise"!
[BON CLAY screaming]
Warden Magellan! Wait, please!
We're still evacuating!
[GUARDS gasping]
[gagging]
[LUFFY screams]
That Warden guy's
poisoning his own people!
[BON CLAY screaming]
The Hydra's venom is
a paralytic neurotoxin!
It makes its way
through your body
causing horrific pain
before you finally die!
It's killing me!
Give me the antidote, hurry!
Uhh. Boss, why?
Stay out of the way when
I'm fighting, you damned fools.
You got that?
[GUARD H]
W-We're terribly sorry, sir!
Stop chasing me!
I just wanna eat! Hungry...
How can he think about food
at a time like this?
Either way, you gotta respect
a man that knows what he wants.
I admire your bravery,
dear friend.
It just sucks that
we're both gonna die!
[groaning]
[LUFFY]
Catch me if you can, Hydra!
[yelling]
[grunts] I forgot
it's really hot!
All right!
One of the heads is gone!
How clever.
You have some of your
brother's cunning after all.
Still, this is the end.
[GUARD I] Ah, crap!
Get ready! Here it comes!
Chloroform Ball!
[gasps]
[LUFFY yelps]
[LUFFY]
That was close!
[LUFFY grunts]
[GUARD J]
Put your gas masks on!
Stay clear! The Warden's
in the middle of a battle!
[PRISONER A]
What is this, tear gas?
[PRISONER B]
No! It's Magellan's poison!
[PRISONER C] Go somewhere else
to fight, you bastards!
[PRISONER D]
Who's he up against, anyway?
[PRISONER E]
I don't know.
Maybe that intruder
they were talking about?
So, Hell Heat plus poison gas?
Give me a break!
[LUFFY]
Achoo! What the--?
Achoo-choo!
Aw, my eyes itch like crazy!
What's happening to me? I can't
fi--Achoo! Fight like this!
Achoo!
[LUFFY]
Whoa!
The Hydra-Achoo! Stopped moving!
Down the Venom Road!
Try as you might.
[grunting]
You won't escape from me!
--[LUFFY sneezes]
--[MAGELLAN grunts]
[LUFFY]
I can't see!
Could I offer you some of this?
[LUFFY groaning]
One touch and it's over.
[LUFFY gasping]
[LUFFY]
He's melting through the stone!
First, the wall and then you!
[LUFFY]
I gotta rescue Ace.
[MAGELLAN]
Surely, even you must know
that your death is imminent.
Achoo!
Just like Ace.
[GUARD K] Please, give me
the antidote! I'm dying!
You mean they were all
poisoned by the Warden?
Yeah. They got caught up
in the crossfire
between him and
that Straw Hat kid.
At this rate, he'll end up
poisoning all of us!
[GUARD L]
Oh, man, I hope not!
Did you hear that? Sounds like
Straw Hat's in a tough fight.
Well, too bad for him,
but good for us!
What?
In all the awful things
that Impel Down has to offer,
Warden Magellan
is by far the most deadly.
Right now, he's focused
on Straw Hat.
So, while there are
likely guards posted
at the staircase to Level 3
preventing an eventless escape,
at least we can
take comfort in knowing
we won't face the worst terror!
What I'm saying is
this is our chance!
[BON CLAY]
Straw Boy's in trouble!
Worse yet, there's nothing
I can do while my dear friend
is being subjected
to that dreadful poison!
Well, there is
one thing I can do.
[BON CLAY]
Straw Hat! Hang in there!
I'm here! Spinning for you!
[BON CLAY sighs]
What's the use?
That won't help at all!
I'm a fool! Such a fool!
[grunts]
[BON CLAY] If I can lay down
my life for a friend,
then death is
a small price to pay.
In the name of
"Oh, Come My Way,"
Bon Clay will
stand up and fight!
Having said that...
I'm too scared to move!
[screaming]
Ouchie.
[BON CLAY]
Look at him.
He's fighting so hard
and you can't help him?
Can't you do something?
Calm down. Think this through.
[BON CLAY]
Swan! Arabesque!
The outcome? The swan is dead.
I'm pulling my own tail here!
That would never work!
Wait for it. Fouetté!
[BON CLAY]
The rose withers and wilts.
Oh, come on! That's even worse
than the other idea!
[BON CLAY] I bring you
"Memoirs of a Winter's Sky"!
I did it!
[BON CLAY] The garden of
"Oh, Come My Way" is calling me.
It's useless!
I'm all out of ideas!
I can't even think
of a cool way to die!
Straw Boy, my dear friend,
I can't help you!
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY yelping]
Now Gum-Gum! Stamp!
[LUFFY grunts]
[panting]
[BON CLAY]
Warden Magellan guards
the most dangerous criminals
in the most infamous prison
in the entire world!
He's the lord and
master of hell itself!
You're not going to let Straw
Boy face him all alone, are you?
[whimpering]
Forgive me!
[crying]
[BON CLAY]
There's just no way to beat him!
I tried to warn you,
but you wouldn't listen!
Running is the only answer!
I'm sorry, Straw Boy!
I'm a coward! Forgive me!
[MR. 3] I'm telling you,
we have to make a move
while Magellan is busy
with Straw Hat!
[BUGGY]
Are you out of your mind?!
Look how many guards there are
down there! It's nuts!
That doesn't matter.
Just think about it.
They assigned the more
powerful Demon Guards
to protect
the staircase to Level 5.
It's more important to them
to not let Straw Hat get down
to the lower levels.
Meaning they are the crappiest
security they have here.
If we miss this chance,
soon after, they'll
tighten their defenses.
Straw Hat will lose
at some point.
Once he does,
this window is closed.
We must get to Level 3
before that happens!
[BUGGY]
Actually, maybe you're right.
I've never heard anything about
Vice Warden Hannyabal
having any Devil Fruit powers.
If I can take out those guards
with a Muggy Ball... Heh.
We can do it. Hannyabal
can't be that tough, right?
Now you're thinking.
All right, let's do it.
I don't want to stay in
this heat one moment longer.
It's now or never.
[BOTH]
Ready?
[BOTH yelling, laughing]
[GUARDS gasping]
Nothing is going to stop us
from getting through!
That's right!
Vice Warden Hannyabal, look,
it's Buggy the Clown and Mr. 3!
Looks like they're
trying to get to Level 3!
We can't let those bastards
go any higher! Let's go!
Now, Muggy!
Candle!
Wait a minute!
Guards, stand down.
[GUARDS gasping]
[BUGGY, MR. 3]
Huh?!
Vice Warden, why?
That's right, I'm the Vice
Warden and I'm in charge here.
Yes, yes, yes!
Here's my chance.
It seems fortune has
finally favored me.
On top of Straw Hat
Luffy's invasion,
if these two managed to escape,
I'm sure the officials
wouldn't tolerate
this magnitude of incompetence.
[BOTH]
Huh?
And since he's
the one in charge,
they'll blame Warden Magellan
for everything that happened.
After that...
I will be promoted to Warden,
as I so richly deserve.
Uh, Vice Warden,
are you sure you don't
want us to stop those two?
--[Hannyabal laughing]
-- Please, give us an order.
Anything, sir!
Okay! Everybody move.
[GUARDS]
Huh?
Uhh.
Uh, we've been expecting you.
So please, come right this way.
You heard me, men! Move it!
Make way! Don't be rude
to our guests!
No way. Is he serious?
Maybe this is all part of
the Vice Warden's secret ploy.
There you are! Please,
go right on ahead.
[BOTH]
Uhh?
[BOTH growling]
[BUGGY, MR. 3]
Screw a bunch of that!
Can't fool us! We see right
through your sneaky little plan!
There is no way our escape
could be that easy!
You could at least
make it less obvious!
Huh?
Suck it, freak! Muggy Ball!
Take this! Candle Lock!
[GUARDS screaming]
What the hell is wrong
with you two idiots?
I said, you could go!
[BOTH grunting]
[MR. 3]
Oh, crap.
[BUGGY]
This isn't good.
[MAGELLAN] I suggest you put an
end to this nonsense and submit.
[panting]
I'm gonna rescue my brother.
And we'll escape
from here together!
I won't die without
even seeing him!
[LUFFY] And I'm not going to let
you execute him, you hear me?
[MAGELLAN]
Hm? What's that smoke?
I don't have time
for your tricks.
[LUFFY]
I'm not getting anywhere.
I can't win
without touching you.
I'll make a sacrifice.
[LUFFY] You can take
my arms, but I won't lose!
Huh? Why would I need your arms?
You want me to take you apart
piece by piece?
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
Now, Gum-Gum!
Jet Bazooka!
[groaning]
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY screaming]
[NARRATOR]
Magellan's venom proves to be
an impenetrable wall, chipping
away at Luffy's strength
and destroying any hope
of a counterattack.
With nowhere to run,
Luffy's desperation to save Ace
forces him to make
a very grim sacrifice
as he prepares for one final
attack against his adversary.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"The Showdown Has Come!
Luffy's Desperate Last Attack!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!