[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue.
The crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy makes his way to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother
Ace from execution.
Meanwhile, the other
Straw Hat Pirates
have adventures of their own.
[LUFFY]
"The Friends' Whereabouts!
A Huge Tomb and the Panty Debt!"
[NARRATOR]
Far away, but not long ago,
Zoro found himself trapped
on a certain gloomy
island with Perona.
[ZORO] I can't take this
anymore. I gotta hurry.
[PERONA] Where did that
sword-swinging simpleton
run off to this time?
[ZORO pants]
Oh, come on, gimme a break!
I can't find the
stinkin' bedroom!
[ZORO panting]
[ZORO] It's like I'm
stuck in a maze!
This way!
What am I even doing?
This is a waste of time.
[PERONA] "Hide his sword!
It'll be fun!" I thought.
"Use your Negative Hollow
to make him depressed!"
That'll be hilarious!
Only I had to tell him where
his sword was, and two days
later, he still can't find it.
Wow Zoro, I guess
you sure showed me.
Great, now I'm depressed.
[screams]
Why're you here?
Are you tryin' to use your
power to mess with my head?
I live here!
And you're depressing
enough without my help!
Besides, I told you
where your sword was!
[ZORO grunts]
[PERONA] Climb the stairs
directly behind me,
follow the hallway and get your
stupid sword back, okay?
Do you need me to hold
your hand, little boy?
You keep giving out crappy
directions to trick me!
Uh! Have you got brain
worms or something?
That's the wrong way.
[ZORO growls]
Behind me! Come on!
What, is your sense of
hearing messed up, too?
I shouldn't have
taken his sword away.
I didn't think he'd
be so sad without it.
This isn't funny at all.
In fact, it's a tragedy!
[PERONA]
Poor thing.
You're the one who
did this to me!
Keep at it, buddy,
you'll be okay!
[ZORO growling]
Go, Zoro!
That's enough!
[PERONA]
Here, just take it.
[ZORO]
Why the change of heart?
I'm bored of your
antics, that's all.
And it's not like you're
any threat to me.
This form is no different
than one of my ghosts.
You'd have to attack my
real body to do any harm.
And the chance of you
finding it is like, zero.
And besides, you're not cute
enough to be one of my servants.
[laughs]
[PERONA] You really
think I'm doing this
out of kindness, dingbat?
If this plan works out,
I get back to my life
on Thriller Bark.
If you're going to
be this stupid,
I'm almost required to
take advantage of you.
This spooky little vacation
has been fun enough,
but you're my ticket out of
here and I'm going to use you.
Lucky me, huh?
[PERONA] What? Why didn't
I see that coming?!
I've gotta stop freaking
out and follow him!
He'll just get lost
again! What is he thinking?
I gotta get
back to Sabaody.
It's been too long already and
we were in pretty bad shape
when I got sent away!
I just hope everyone
made it out all right.
Everyone start running and
look after your selves!
We can't win this one!
We're too weak!
Get moving!
[BROOK]
Wait, do I-- Ah!
[USOPP]
Sanji!
[LUFFY groans]
--[USOPP screams]
--[ZORO whimpers]
I can't just stay here,
doing nothing!
They could be hurt. Or worse!
Ah-ha!
[ZORO] That castle looks
familiar. I think.
Hm... Oh, I get it!
Ha, ha. It's like the other
one. Why'd they build two?
[PERONA groans]
So that's how your head works?
How did you ever
survive for this long?
[sighs] I really have
a kind heart, don't I?
I don't have to guide him
to the sea, but here I am!
Well, he'll be doing me a favor
in the end, so no biggie!
You sure this is
the right way to go?
[PERONA] Don't you dare!
You're gonna get us lost!
You aren't allowed to complain.
No more talking, just
follow in silence!
Sounds good.
[PERONA] Agh! Stop!
You're drifting off already!
[ZORO]
Huh. So much for silence.
[PERONA] So much for you
following me, you idiot!
[ZORO]
What's that?
[PERONA] Did you forget that
I'm leading the way, or what?
[ZORO] I dunno.
Guess you're just a bad leader.
[PERONA gasps]
Oh, it's my fault, of course!
[sighs] I'm not even really
here and he's wearing me out.
[ZORO]
What's the deal?
[PERONA sighs]
[ZORO] Don't act tired.
You're not even walking.
[PERONA]
It's you! I'm tired of you!
[ZORO]
What did I do?
[PERONA] Just ignore him,
Perona. Don't lose your cool.
[ZORO] Huh. This tree
looks kind of familiar.
[PERONA]
We're in a forest!
What was that?
[PERONA] Maybe that Kuma guy
sent someone else here, too!
I'd better go check!
Hey, where are you going?
I'm getting out of here,
'cause I just found out
that I don't need your
useless hide after all!
[PERONA] You can walk
in circles till you die!
I wonder who it is?
I just hope it's someone
a little cuter this time.
[laughs]
Hey. Ya came back, huh?
[screams] Wha... What're
you doing here?
Why wouldn't I be here? The
ocean is this way, isn't it?
[PERONA]
Well, I mean, yeah,
but it's not like you
could figure that out!
He isn't human.
He's a god of trickery
sent to torment me!
Or something.
[ZORO] Looks like someone
did that recently.
[PERONA] Ugh, what a letdown.
It was just a tree falling.
Guess it's back to
my original plan.
I was really looking forward
to dumping him, though.
Y'know, I do cherish these
abandoned battlefields!
Delightfully morose!
Maybe that fallen tree was
the work of tortured souls,
trapped in their place of death!
I've got a different
theory on that.
[PERONA]
Uh?
Uh! Hey, don't go! Wait!
The heck is this?
It looks like a grave.
The question's who made it?
[ZORO] Whoever they are,
they've got some skill.
It was carved straight
out of that tree.
[PERONA] I dunno if this is
"good creepy" or "bad creepy."
[ZORO] There it is again.
I knew someone was here.
[ZORO growls]
[ZORO gasps]
They're fast.
Damn it. He's strong, too!
Uh-oh! Look out!
[ZORO grunts]
[PERONA gasping]
What are those things?
[growls, roars]
[NARRATOR]
This is Lazy Bones Island
in the Land of
Poverty, Hungaria.
Sent here by Kuma,
Brook was mistaken for Satan
by the island's inhabitants.
[yawns] How lovely!
Another perfect day!
[BROOK]
And yet, so lonely.
[BROOK] If only I could share
the sunrise with my friends.
Yes. I'm sure
I can, someday!
Because whatever happens,
the sun will always rise!
So long as I stay alive,
I have hope.
We will all meet again.
[BROOK]
My goodness, this island
certainly is in an unfortunate
state, though, isn't it?
And such a strange place.
I didn't think about
it much yesterday.
But that house was full
of oddities. Those dolls.
And the strange tapestries
adorning the wall.
Not to mention all of the
macabre-looking decorations.
It seems they were performing
some sort of ritual,
but I can't guess the purpose.
It's rather foreboding.
Even if they were kind to me.
[PEKKORI]
Oh, good! You're awake.
We were just about to bring
you an offering of breakfast,
as I'm sure you must
be quite famished
after your journey to
the realm of humans.
My, how considerate of you.
[PEKKORI] Oh, it's
the least we could do!
[laughs] Such kindness,
and from total strangers!
You have my gratitude!
Forgive me. I should've
introduced myself, first.
I am the leader of
this humble country.
You may call me Pekkori.
Well, Pekkori. Thank you, I
shall relish this gift of yours.
[gasps]
Young lady.
[whimpers]
Would you be so kind as
to show me your panties?
[GIRL A gasps]
It shall be! Everyone
show him your underwear!
[BROOK] Oh no no,
that's quite all right,
just the young lady will
be more than adequate!
Please, there's no
need to be bashful.
We have plenty to go around!
[BROOK] Ah! Really,
I've had my fill!
Ah, thank you so much
for this generous feast!
My stomach's so full,
I can scarcely move!
[stomach growls]
[BROOK]
T-That was a joke, you see.
I-I clearly don't have
a stomach, after all!
[groans]
[WORSHIPPER B] That food was
supposed to last us all week.
[WORSHIPPER C]
Shh! Be patient for now!
[PEKKORI]
Uh. Lord Satan.
I believe you mentioned that
you wanted to ask us a favor.
Yes, I need to set sail right
away. Do you have a ship?
But... my Lord?
Has one of us done something
to displease you?
N-No!
[PEKKORI] Ah! Everyone, quickly!
Show him your underwear!
[BROOK]
Enough with the under-- Whoa!
[panting]
Is our underwear not
good enough anymore?
[BROOK grunts] No, your
underwear is perfectly fine.
I've been separated from
my friends, you see.
I'm afraid I must return
to them, whatever the cost.
"Return to them?"
[BROOK]
Yes.
A-At any cost, you say?
Yes. I must go. I'm truly sorry.
Then we're finished.
If our undergarments
no longer satisfy you,
we have nothing else to give!
Our beloved country will die.
The suffering will
only get worse.
We should just take
our lives now.
[BROOK]
No need to overreact!
I'm sure we can come
up with something.
[WORSHIPPERS]
Like what?
For starters,
could you tell me a bit
more about your situation?
Why do you call me
"Satan," for example?
And what was it you mentioned
about the Longarm
Tribe last night?
I may be able to help you yet.
[PEKKORI whimpers]
Our dear country has
long been overrun
by the cruel and vicious
members of the Longarm Tribe.
Not only do they take our money,
our food, our belongings,
but they also strike down or
enslave our sons and daughters.
As you can see,
it's left us devastated.
We scarcely have the
clothes on our backs.
[BROOK gasps] Then, the
food that you gave me...
[PEKKORI] I'm ashamed
to say it was all we had.
We felt we should make
some sort of offering.
Oh, no.
There was nothing we could do
to escape our terrible fate.
Except pray to every god
and goddess we could name,
and many who were
long forgotten.
And when that failed us,
we called upon the powers
of witches and sorcerers,
in the hopes that they could
curse our enemies to death.
[gasps]
And then, in the end,
we turned to the blackest
magic of all and called you!
So desperate was our plight,
we would summon even
the Lord of all
evil into our midst!
Lord Satan, we can
take no more!
Our people are doomed
without your aid.
Face the Longarm Tribe and
deal them a bloody blow!
We beg of you!
[WORSHIPPERS]
You... think I can?
Yes!
Preferably curse them to death,
although at this point,
just about anything will do.
[WORSHIPPERS]
Please, my lord!
[BROOK gasps]
I, uh...
[screams]
[WORSHIPPER D]
It's the Longarm Tribe!
Oh, no.
[WORSHIPPER E groans]
[WORSHIPPER F gags]
[GIRL A]
No! Help me!
[SATAN WORSHIPPER G screams]
[BROOK gasps]
You're in trouble this
time! You hear me?
[WORSHIPPER I]
Put her down now!
[WORSHIPPER J]
We're not gonna warn you again!
Let my daughter go!
We've had enough of this!
We'll give you a taste of hell!
[BROOK gasping]
[screams] Don't let
them take me away!
Uh, they're really kidnapping
her, aren't they?
[WORSHIPPER L]
Uh-huh.
[PEKKORI]
Unless you curse them!
Yes, now is the time!
[WORSHIPPERS]
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
[BROOK] Never mind that!
Shouldn't we be chasing them?
[GIRL A]
Lord Satan!
[BROOK]
Uh?!
We're too late.
[BROOK] But why didn't
they do anything?
She's their friend!
Their family!
Is the situation
really so hopeless
that they can't
even fight back?
Did you hear us, Satan?
[BROOK]
Huh?
[PEKKORI] Did you?
We were cheering extra hard!
You can save us
now, oh Dark Lord!
[WORSHIPPERS]
Give it your best!
[BROOK] Oh... I see what got
them in this situation now.
They're lazy!
[BROOK] But that young
lady is still a victim.
I can't allow her to
suffer such a cruel fate.
I will save her.
At the very least,
I owe for you the food.
Not to mention the panties.
[WORSHIPPERS cheer]
[WORSHIPPERS]
Lord Satan! Lord Satan!
[BROOK] You must forgive me,
Luffy. Everyone.
Right now I'm rather busy being
Satan in a sea of underwear.
I'm afraid our reunion
will have to wait.
I owe my odd new friends
a debt of gratitude.
But I am confident that I
shall resolve this quickly,
and I hope you keep
safe until then.
[JIMBEI] It's been almost an
hour since we've left Impel Down
and the winds are strong.
It's odd that we haven't reached
Navy Headquarters yet.
Don't think you could hurry
it up a bit, do you? Huh?
At this rate, there won't
be any carnage left for me
by the time we get there.
Calm yourself.
Those Navy bastards
better not kill Whitebeard.
'Cause that's my job.
You still insist on that?
If you wanna piss
and moan about it,
I'd be happy to kill you first.
[JIMBEI growls]
[CROCODILE]
Huh?
[JIMBEI]
Hm?
What's wrong, friend?
I'm comin' for you, Ace.
It's not over. Not yet!
[NARRATOR] Luffy and company
continue on the tub current
with Marine Ford looming
on the horizon.
Staring impatiently at his
brother's vivre card,
Luffy's reminded of
more innocent times.
Then, in nearby waters,
Ace is haunted by a
recollection of his own.
[LUFFY]
On the next, One Piece!
"Retrospective
Before Marineford!
The Vow of Brotherhood!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!