[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[HENCHMAN A chuckles]
Another big haul today!
That's two in a row!
[HENCHMAN C]
All of this should keep Buggy
from getting too mad at us.
[HENCHMAN B]
Hey..
What's with that boat out there?
[HENCHMEN]
Huh?
We should check it out.
[HENCHMEN chuckling]
Oh... It's a lady.
[HENCHMAN A chuckles]
Hey, wake up little girl.
[GIRL]
Uh.
Please tell me I'm not
dreaming this time...
...finding help out here
in the middle of nowhere...
If you're real, then please,
could you get me some water?
I'm so thirsty.
I'll give you as much jewelry
and valuables as you like,
if you could just give
me one little drink.
No sweat. We'll help ya.
But not until we see what kinda
treasure you're holding on to.
[HENCHMAN C]
Yeah, don't mind us.
‐‐We'll just be a minute.
‐‐[HENCHMAN B laughs]
[HENCHMAN A]
Can't get the damn thing open.
Uh. Hold up, here we go.
[HENCHMEN scream]
[GIRL laughing]
If you want, you can
keep the whole thing.
It's not my style.
[HENCHMEN scream]
But that's our boat!
You tricked us!
From the look of those clouds
moving in from the south,
I'd say a cold front's coming.
So you can probably
expect strong winds
and squalls any
time now, really.
Also, in that small a boat,
you run a bit of a
chance of capsizing.
[HENCHMEN gasp]
[HENCHMEN screaming]
[GIRL]
Bingo!
See ya!
I'll just take whatever
treasure you guys got here.
[HENCHMAN A]
Get back here, you bitch!
[HENCHMAN C]
We'll get you for this!
[LUFFY] "Luffy's Past!
Enter Red‐Haired Shanks!"
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY]
I'm so hungry.
[ZORO] When the hell are
we gonna reach land anyway?
[LUFFY]
Who knows?
We're just sailin' on
the wind and the waves,
goin' where they take us.
We might not ever
even reach the land.
Nah, I guess we will someday.
[ZORO grunts]
Don't you find it dumb
that someone trying to be
King of the Pirates
doesn't have a single
navigational skill?
Not really...
I just drift around...
What about you?
Aren't you some famous bounty
hunter who's sailed the seas?
I don't have any recollection
of ever calling myself
a bounty hunter.
[ZORO sighs]
I set out onto the open sea
in search of just one man,
but then I couldn't
get back to my village.
By that point, I had no choice
but to go after pirate
ships to earn a living.
Oh, I see. So you're just lost.
Hey, don't put it like that!
[gasps]
[ZORO gasps]
Oh no, not my Shanks hat.
This straw hat means more to me
than you could possibly know.
It's been with me
in many a fight.
It's something so precious
that I couldn't even
give to you, Luffy.
[BOTH gasp]
[LUFFY yells]
[PIRATES cheering]
Hey!
You gotta take me with you on
your next adventure, Shanks!
I wanna be a pirate
just like you!
[laughs]
Right, as if you
could ever be a pirate.
[LUFFY]
Why couldn't I?
Look.
You might be a good
swimmer and all,
but that doesn't mean you'd
make a good pirate, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
But I'm a great fighter, too!
My punches are like two pistols!
[SHANKS]
Are they now?
What's that's supposed to mean?!
[laughs] He means that
you're too much of a kid, kid!
And he's right, you know.
I got boys older than you.
I'm not a kid!
I'm a grown up!
[SHANKS] Here, have some
juice and calm down.
[LUFFY gasps]
Wow! Thanks, Shanks!
[laughing] I don't know one
pirate who drinks juice!
Hey! You tricked me!
[PIRATES laughing]
Stop laughing!
That was a cheap shot!
[HIGUMA]
Excuse us.
[HIGUMA] So these are what pass
for pirates around these parts.
Looks rather sad to me.
[SHANKS]
Hm?
[MAKINO]
Welcome, gentlemen.
What can I do for you?
We're mountain bandits.
But we didn't come here
to tear your place apart.
All we want is some sake.
I'd say ten barrels should do.
I'm sorry,
but actually we're fresh
out of sake right now.
[HIGUMA]
Hm, Interesting.
These other pirates seem
to still be drinking.
Is that water in their glasses?
No, that just happens to be the
last of what I had stocked up.
[SHANKS]
My apologies, gentlemen.
Looks like me and my friends
drank the whole place dry.
But...
You can have this if you want.
It hasn't even been opened yet.
Go ahead.
[MAKINO gasps]
I'm wanted.
There's an eight million
berry bounty on my head.
One bottle isn't
enough for a nightcap,
so don't insult me.
[sighs]
Just great...
Now the floor's wet.
Sorry about that, Makino.
You got a rag I can
clean this up with?
[MAKINO]
Ah... Oh, don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it...
[glass shatters]
[gasps]
[HIGUMA] Since you like
to clean things so much
maybe you'll find this
mess more fulfilling.
[HIGUMA]
Ta.
A place with no sake is a place
not worth our time, men.
Let's get outta here.
See you later, pansies.
Captain, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Not a problem in
the world, Makino.
‐‐[SHANKS chuckles]
‐‐[PIRATES laugh]
That fella really
got you good, boss!
[PIRATE Q]
Talk about a loser!
[SHANKS laughing]
Why are you all laughing?!
What's so funny?!
You should've
fought back, Shanks!
It doesn't matter
how strong they look
or how many of them there are,
if you just laugh it off,
you're not a man
or a pirate!
Look, Luffy, I know
how you feel.
But the guy just
spilled some booze on me.
It's not worth getting
bent out of shape.
[LUFFY]
Whatever!
‐‐[MAKINO, SHANKS laugh]
‐‐[chomp]
[SHANKS laughs] You shouldn't
eat out of frustration, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Shut up!
[gasps]
[SHANKS]
Wait! What're you eating?
[LUFFY gasps]
No! You didn't‐‐
Don't tell me you ate the fruit
that was inside that box?!
[LUFFY]
Uh... I...
[LUFFY screams]
[SHANKS] Spit it out
right now! Every single bit!
[LUFFY]
What're you doing?
Why're you shaking me?!
What's going on?
Luffy, you just ate
the Gum‐Gum Fruit,
part of a group called
the Devil Fruits.
Eating any of them takes away
your ability to swim for
the rest of your life,
but the one you ate also
turns your body to rubber!
[LUFFY]
No way! It can't!
[SHANKS]
You dumbass!
[MAKINO panting]
[LUFFY groans]
[HIGUMA]
What is this?
We were drinking and
having a nice time...
...until you showed up.
You apologize!
No one messes with Shanks' crew!
[MAKINO panting]
[HIGUMA] I don't think I said
anything to offend you directly.
[LUFFY]
You think wrong!
Now apologize!
Mayor! Help me!
[MAYOR]
Hm?
[BOTH panting]
[BANDIT A laughs]
[BANDIT A] Did you see the
looks on those pirate's faces?
‐‐[BANDIT A laughing]
‐‐[BANDIT B] Yeah!
They got doused in liquor
and didn't even say a word.
How pathetic.
[HIGUMA] Pirates are a
buncha wimps, nothing more.
They're all talk, no action.
[LUFFY]
Stop it!
[HIGUMA]
Huh?
[LUFFY] Stop making fun of
Shanks and his men right now!
They're not wimps at all!
[MAKINO]
Luffy, no!
[LUFFY growls]
[LUFFY] You better stop right
now, you stupid bandits!
[MAKINO, MAYOR pant, gasp]
[HIGUMA] You should watch
your flapping gums, kid.
No one who's ever made me mad
has lived to tell the
horrifying and painful tale.
[MAYOR]
Wait! Hold on!
Let the boy go!
I beg you!
[LUFFY gasping]
[MAYOR]
I don't know what he's done,
and I certainly don't intend
to fight you over it.
If you'll accept, I'll
even pay you to stop this.
Just spare the poor
boy's life, please!
Mayor!
While the oldest generation
may know the way of the
world better than us all,
I'm sorry, but this rotten
kid's already made me angry.
Nothing can save him now.
You're the rotten
ones around here!
And you're a lost cause...
...which you can regret
in the next life.
‐‐[MAKINO] No!
‐‐[MAYOR] Please!
You have to let him go!
I was wondering why the bar
was empty on such a fine day.
[MAKINO gasps]
So, it's the mountain
bandits again.
Captain Shanks!
[HIGUMA]
Eh?
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY]
Shanks...
Pirates.
You're just now
showing your heads?
Have you been spending all this
time scrubbing the village?
Luffy. Didn't you say earlier
that your punches were
stronger than pistols?
Shut your mouth!
Listen, I don't know what
you think you're doing here,
but you might wanna leave.
You wouldn't want
something bad to happen.
And I have just the man
to deliver this message.
I'll blow your head
off if I have to,
but that's up to you, my friend.
[BANDITS laughing]
[HIGUMA chuckles]
Would you risk your life?
Huh?
Now that' you've
drawn your pistol,
are you willing to use it?
What the hell are
you talking about?
I'm saying that guns aren't for
threats; they're for actions.
[BANDITS gasp]
[MAKINO, MAYOR gasp]
[LUFFY gasps]
You! You're a dead man!
These guys fight dirty.
Dirty?
Who did you think you
were dealing with?
We never claimed to
be saints or anything.
You fellas are staring
down a crew of pirates.
Shut up!
We just want the boy, not you!
[SHANKS]
Listen up, bandits.
Whether I'm sprayed with
alcohol or doused with food,
hell, even if I'm spit on,
most of the time,
I'll just laugh it off
and forget about it.
But if you hurt
a friend of mine,
you'll pay for it,
regardless of your reason.
[LUFFY]
Shanks...
[HIGUMA laughs]
So we're gonna pay?
Lousy pirates.
Kill 'em all, men!
[BANDITS yell]
[BEN] I'll take care of this.
Shouldn't be a big deal.
[BANDITS yell]
‐‐[BEN grunts]
‐‐[BANDITS grunt, groan]
[HIGUMA gasps]
[BEN]
You shouldn't get too cocky.
If you really wanted to fight
us, looks like a battleship
or something bigger
woulda been more useful.
Wow.
[HIGUMA stammers]
Hold on, please!
It was the kid who attacked us!
I thought you were
a wanted man.
[HIGUMA whimpers]
[HIGUMA yells]
A smokescreen.
[SHANKS]
Luffy?!
Oh no!
I let that guy take him!
What're we gonna do?!
Boss, calm down.
Quit freakin' out.
We'll find him in no time.
[BEN]
Heh. What a guy.
[HIGUMA laughs]
[HIGUMA] Looks like
I made a clean getaway.
They'd never think to look
for a mountain bandit
escaping onto the ocean.
[LUFFY] Dammit! Let go
of me, you dumbass idiot!
I really hope you die!
[chuckles] Yes, I know
that's what you want.
But you're the one dying today.
Remember what I said
about makin' me angry?
[LUFFY]
Ah!
Dammit! Dammit!
Filthy bandit scum and I
couldn't squeeze off one hit!
‐‐[LUFFY choking]
‐‐[HIGUMA laughing]
[HIGUMA]
Sorry, kid,
but I don't seem to have
a use for you anymore.
[HIGUMA laughing]
[HIGUMA gasps]
[HIGUMA]
What the‐What the hell is that?!
[choking]
[HIGUMA screams]
[LUFFY screams]
[LUFFY]
Shanks!
Get lost.
[MONSTER whines]
[SHANKS]
I'm in your debt, Luffy.
Makino told me everything
about how you stood up for us.
How you were willing to fight,
and put yourself on the line.
[sobbing]
You can't cry.
You're a man now.
But Shanks... your arm...
You're arm!
Luffy.
It's just an arm.
I've got another one.
I'm just glad you're all right.
[PIRATES chattering]
So, you're leaving?
[SHANKS]
Yeah.
It was a nice extended vacation,
but we have to part ways now.
I bet you'll miss me, right?
Yeah, but this time's different.
I won't beg you to
take me with you.
'Cause I'm gonna
become a pirate...
...all on my own!
I wouldn't take you
with me anyway.
You'll never make
it as a pirate.
No!
I will make it as a pirate!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a
crew even better than yours
and I'm gonna find the
greatest treasure in the world,
and then I'll be
King of the Pirates!
I'll show you!
Ha. You think you'll surpass us?
[SHANKS]
In that case...
[LUFFY gasps]
[SHANKS]
I'll leave this hat to you.
It means more to me than
anything in the world,
so you better take
good care of it.
You hear me?
[PIRATES cheering]
[SHANKS] I want you to bring
this hat back to me someday...
...in good condition.
And only once you've
become a great pirate.
That's our promise, Luffy.
[ZORO]
Luffy!
Hey. You're gonna
drop that again.
I thought it was important.
[LUFFY]
Heh.
It is. Thanks.
[ZORO] Uh. I am so hungry.
It's killing me.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[ZORO]
Hey, look, a bird.
I know! Let's eat it!
Huh? How do we catch it?
[LUFFY]
Leave that to me!
Gum‐Gum... Rocket!
Makes sense...
[LUFFY yelps]
[groaning]
[LUFFY screaming]
[LUFFY]
Help me!
You moron! What the
hell's goin' on now?!
[HENCHMAN A]
Huh?
[HENCHMAN A gasps]
Hey, you there! Stop!
Please! Men overboard!
Stop! Men overboard!
I can't believe
I find ship‐wreckers
at a time like this!
I can't stop, you're just
gonna have to jump in!
[HENCHMEN]
What?!
[HENCHMEN screaming]
I'm actually impressed
you made it onboard.
[HENCHMEN]
Are you trying to kill us?!
[HENCHMAN A]
Stop the boat now!
The three of us are members of
Buggy the Clown's pirate crew.
This boat is ours now!
[ZORO]
Huh?
[HENCHMEN laughing]
I'm sorry we had no idea
you were the famous
Pirate Hunter Zoro!
[HENCHMEN]
Please forgive us!
Thanks to you three idiots,
I lost sight of my friend.
So just keep paddling.
[HENCHMEN]
Yes, sir!
Knowing Luffy...
he'll probably pull off
something once he spots land.
[HENCHMAN C] So, any ideas
about what we do now?
[HENCHMAN B]
Good question.
If Captain Buggy finds out
a girl stole our boat and
our treasure, we're history.
[HENCHMAN A]
I know...
[ZORO]
Huh? So who is this Buggy guy?
[HENCHMAN A] Uh. You've never
heard of Buggy the Clown?!
[ZORO]
Nope.
He's the ruthless captain
of our pirate ship.
And he's eaten one
of the Devil Fruits.
Above everything else, he is
a one truly terrifying man.
[GIRL panting]
[GIRL]
Yes, I've finally got it!
Hey girl, get back here!
You better give us
that map back or else!
[HENCHMAN D] We just stole
that chart of the Grand Line!
It belongs to us!
Dammit!
If we don't get that thing back,
then we're as good as dead!
We'll be killed by one of
the Captain's cannonballs!
[HENCHMAN G]
Captain Buggy!
I've spotted something high
in the sky above the port.
[BUGGY]
Well, shoot it down.
[cannon fires]
[GIRL panting]
[GIRL]
Ah!
[gasps]
What's that?
[LUFFY screaming]
[GIRL screams]
What... was that?!
What the hell?!
A guy fell from the sky.
[LUFFY] Dammit, why were there
cannonballs flying at me?
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
At least I'm safe now.
And...
...what just happened
to me was awesome.
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[LUFFY]
How can any human being
be alive and chopped up
at the same time?
[ZORO] You're a rubber guy.
How human do you think that is?
[GIRL]
Nothing makes sense anymore.
A rubber guy,
some chopped up guy,
who are these people?!
[LUFFY]
Uh... Pirates!
[GIRL]
No! That's not what I meant.
Come on!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"A Terrifying Mysterious Power!
Captain Buggy,
the Clown Pirate!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!