[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR] With only one hour
left until Eneru's deadline,
time is quickly running out,
and only 24 survivors remain.
Cien Fleurs!
[YAMA]
Stop!
I'm afraid it's far
too late for that.
[NARRATOR] After finally
defeating the rotund Yama,
and discovering Shandora,
the fabled ancient city of gold.
Robin stumbled across
something even more astonishing.
[ROBIN]
Could it be?
[ROBIN] A Poneglyph was
carried into the city!
There's no question about it.
And that means,
the grand belfry located in
the center of the four altars.
It could contain the
text of true history.
It could be the Rio Poneglyph!
[LUFFY]
"0% Survival Rate!
Chopper vs. Ohm,
the Sword Wielding Priest!"
Almost there.
I can't wait to see the
look on all their faces
when they find out
I discovered the gold first.
Look at those ruins.
[CHOPPER]
What's up with this place?
The ground's all crooked.
Guess I'll go this way.
Gold! Gold!
[growling]
[OHM]
No Holy. Stay.
I said stay!
[screams]
[CHOPPER]
What was I thinking?
I'm too little to do
this all by myself!
I should've gone back!
[OHM]
Interesting.
You're the third one
to make it this far today.
[CHOPPER]
Who are you?
[OHM]
I can't believe
that spider-headed fool
was so careless.
You killed Gedatsu, didn't you?
[CHOPPER] I guess he
means that guy from earlier.
[OHM]
I suppose it's for the best.
The world is better off
with one less imbecile.
Wouldn't you agree?
What the...? I tripped over...
[screams]
[OHM]
Calm yourself.
There's no need to be so afraid
of Holy, he's merely a pet.
He won't bite you.
[CHOPPER]
But what about this guy?
It looks like he's been
chewed up and spit out!
[OHM]
Heh. I assure you.
Holy is a very well-trained dog.
He would never bite anyone.
It was I who attacked that man.
Huh?!
Are you crazy?
Who are you?
Why would you
do something like that?
I am Sky Breeder Ohm.
Now would you please be quiet!
[OHM]
Do you think I'm not saddened
by what's taken place here?
Huh?
[OHM]
I don't understand.
Why do men choose to fight?
when they must know
how fragile their lives are?
I'm not really sure.
[OHM] Man was put here
to find happiness.
Yet time after time, they
throw themselves into battle,
only to lose their lives along
with the joy they've
struggled so hard to find.
What a strange and tragic
thing is man's nature!
There's only
one way to be redeemed!
And that is for all men to die!
Ah!
Oh, please, sir, you don't
really mean that, do you?
This is bad!
[OHM]
What have you come here for?
Oh. I was just trying
to find the city of gold!
[OHM]
Greed only leads to ruin!
Huh?
[OHM]
You must be rescued.
You wanna rescue... me?
Only losing your
life will save you
from all your earthly desires!
[CHOPPER gasps]
He doesn't want
to resuce me at all!
[LAKI]
But why?
Why was everyone charred black?
It was almost as if they...
...they'd all been struck
by a bolt of lightning.
[LAKI]
Kamakiri! Kamakiri!
Ha... Ha...
Laki, is that you?
[LAKI]
Yes!
[KAMAKIRI]
Go. Get out of here, Laki!
Why? Tell me.
[KAMAKIRI] Wyper,
he's headed for god's shrine.
But Eneru isn't there!
There's still time Laki.
Stop Wyper.
All right.
I understand.
Now quiet, save your strength.
Nobody can beat Eneru.
[ENERU]
I am living lightning.
[laughs]
Laki.
Hear me!
[KAMAKIRI]
He comes as lightning.
An element that man has
feared from the beginning
and rightly so.
He can't be conquered.
[LAKI]
Don't worry, I'll stop Wyper.
You just wait here
and save your energy.
I'm going to leave
Aisa's bag with you.
[KAMAKIRI]
Nobody can beat Eneru.
He can't be conquered.
[LAKI] Kamakiri is so strong,
yet his will has been broken.
If what he said is true,
then Eneru's eaten
a Logia-type Devil Fruit.
The most powerful kind of all!
I've got to stop Wyper
before its too late!
[ZORO]
Hmm...
I've been here.
It looks familiar.
Or have I?
Maybe.
Or maybe not.
Huh. I'm not sure.
[GIANT SOUTHBIRD]
Pfft.
Are you laughing at me, huh?
[squawks]
What are you so
worked up for anyway?
The only reason you came
along in the first place
is to get some food.
My bad sense of
direction shouldn't matter!
Ya dummy!
[ZORO]
Huh?
Aah!
No! No! No!
Hey!
Let go, you big
featherbrained jerk.
There's no more food in there.
Hey!
Where are you taking us?
[LUFFY] Of all the
weird places to end up.
Exit, exit, where is the exit?
Here it is!
Ooo. Huh?
[LUFFY]
It's a dead end.
Hmm...
Huh?
You can't be serious;
I walked all this way.
Maybe...
Maybe it's a trick door.
Let's find out.
I can always try busting
through the stupid thing.
Gum-gum...
...Bazooka!
But it... it didn't even budge.
[rumbling]
[LUFFY]
Hmm?
Huh? Huh?!
[screams]
Not again!
[CHOPPER screaming]
[CHOPPER panting]
He didn't follow me.
I'm okay.
I bet he's a Priest too,
but it looks like there's a lot
of places to hide around here.
If I can just stay hidden
long enough to escape,
I can try to meet up
with the others.
I have to make sure
he doesn't see me.
He looked like a swordsman,
so if I keep my distance
I should be okay.
[OHM]
He's run quite a long way.
But running from
salvation is futile.
Attachment to this life
is a result of evil desires.
Therefore...
...the path to peace,
leads to but one place.
This is the Ordeal of Iron!
The survival rate is zero!
[AISA]
Another voice disappeared!
[NAMI]
Aisa?
[AISA]
I can't just sit here!
I've gotta go find Laki!
[NAMI]
Oh, no, you don't!
Wait! Aisa!
[NAMI groans]
Get back here!
Leave me alone!
I've got to save Laki! Let go!
I've gotta get out
of here right now!
Let go!
This isn't any of your business!
Maybe it's not
any of my business,
but there's no way
I'm gonna sit back
and let a little kid
get herself killed!
I'm a warrior!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Kid warrior.
Hey! Those dirty looks don't
scare me, so knock it off.
Nami? Is everything okay?
[NAMI]
We're fine.
All right, stop messing
around and get in the waver!
You don't understand!
You have to let me go,
so I can save my friends!
I have to help them!
You better knock it off right
now, or I'm gonna slug you!
[NAMI]
And no crying!
Look, you don't want to end up
like Sanji and Usopp do you?
Well do you?
Come on, I'll help
you in the boat.
[screams]
Oh no!
[LUFFY coughs]
Okay. That was scary.
What's with this
lame cave anyhow?
First there was an earthquake,
then a flood of ocean clouds!
I could've drowned!
You hear me?
Open up!
[roars]
[screaming]
Why's it going crazy?
[LUFFY roars]
Let me out of here!
Gum-gum...
...Gatling!
[screams]
Nami, no!
That way leads to the forest!
[NAMI screams]
[CONIS]
Nami!
[PAGAYA moans]
[CONIS]
What do we do?
They've gone into the forest!
Missed.
Ha!
You're lucky.
[distant rumble]
Huh?
[DIVINE SQUAD MEMBER]
Hmm? What's that?
Who's that?
I dunno.
Something's coming!
Go that way!
That way!
Lord of the Sky!
No way!
Aisa!
[NAMI]
We're inside the forest!
[ZORO]
Um.
Hey! What's the idea?
Are you even listening to me?
Aww.
I gonna pluck you,
and cook you up in a stew!
[rumbling]
Huh?
Wha?
[screams]
[ZORO]
Hey, come on!
Fly higher!
I don't wanna
be giant snake food!
[ZORO] Can't you fly any
faster you dumb bird?
[ZORO]
It's still coming after us!
Something must have
really pissed it off!
Why you!
[screams]
To make it to god's shrine,
I have to climb to
the top of Giant Jack.
And if Eneru is there.
It's time I brought an end
to our terrible history,
once and for all!
Now.
Wyper.
If you climb that
vine any further,
you'll reach god's shrine.
What makes you think you
have permission to pass?
[WYPER growls]
Damn you.
It doesn't matter.
Heading for that shrine
is no longer useful.
[WYPER]
Gan fall?
What business do you have here?
Still can't let go
of your old position?
[GAN FALL] No, but I still
have responsibilities
I've yet to fulfill.
I thought you might be
interested in knowing
I've recently come
from god's shrine.
It's tragic, the entire thing's
been utterly destroyed.
Naturally.
Eneru was nowhere to be found.
Perhaps it means he no
longer has any need for it.
[ENERU] It appears that their
years of hard labor are over.
You see, this island is
no longer useful to me.
I've simply come
to bid you farewell.
I demand to know, Ohm!
What is it you and
your master seek to do?
Hold on.
You saying Eneru's not up there?
[ZORO screams]
One of Straw Hat's friends?
[groans]
Ow. That bird's gonna pay.
[GAN FALL]
It's you!
Where am I?
[ZORO]
More ruins?
Hmm.
These guys all
look pretty tough.
Oh well. Hey!
Hand over the gold!
[OHM]
Look what we have here.
If it isn't another greedy
infidel, seeking his salvation.
[WYPER]
Enough!
Get out of my way, or I'll
destroy every one of you!
[GAN FALL]
The time has come, Ohm.
Tell me where Eneru
and the Divine Squad are!
Ya stupid cave!
Just let me out!
[OHM]
I'm sure you each feel
what you have
to say is important,
but there's only one way
for your voice to be heard.
You must survive
or find salvation!
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[OHM] It appears the Upper Ruins
are getting awfully crowded.
[GAN FALL]
What is it you're after?
Where is Eneru?
[ZORO]
We don't care about all of that.
Just hand over the gold!
[WYPER]
You're all getting in my way!
So you can die together!
[LUFFY]
Come on, where the heck am I?
On the next One Piece!
"Climb Giant Jack!
Deadly Combat
in the Upper Ruins!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!