[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY]
My hat!
Wait!
[LUFFY]
Stop hat!
Good! My hat.
[LUFFY] So this is what the King
of the Pirates saw when he died.
[laughs]
[BUGGY] Ugh! I hate
that damn Straw Hat
and I want to crush
him like a bug
the next time I see
his ugly face.
So he finally showed up.
It took him long enough.
[TASHIGI]
Captain Smoker!
Is there something wrong?
Come with me, Tashigi.
Sir!
[thunder rumbles]
[LUFFY]
"Buggy's Revenge!
The Man Who Smiles On
the Execution Platform!"
[TOWNSMAN 7] Whoa! Someone's
on the execution platform!
[TOWNSMAN 8]
Who the heck is that?
That old man said this is the
place where it all happened.
Twenty‐two years ago,
the King of the Pirates
was executed right here.
[POLICE CAPTAIN]
Hey! You! Up there!
Get down from there immediately!
[LUFFY]
But why?
You are standing on
an execution platform
that belongs to the
World Government!
Now get down from
there right now!
Fine.
I'll come down but first you
gotta say the magic word.
And smile too.
I'm not playing!
I'll arrest you if
you don't come down!
[ALVIDA] Now's not the
time for such trifles.
Long time no see, Luffy.
I've been looking for you.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Now that's just rude.
Do you mean to tell me
that you, of all people,
have forgotten my face?
Wow, she's absolutely gorgeous!
Oh, wow.
I've never seen
such pure beauty!
Her skin looks so
deliciously soft!
Forgot? I'm pretty sure
we haven't ever met.
Who are you?
[ALVIDA]
I'll never forget you.
You were the first man
who ever truly struck me.
[LUFFY]
What? I never hit you!
[CROWD chattering]
[ALVIDA] When you struck me
with your passionate fist...
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum!
Pistol!
It felt good.
Listen up, boys.
What would all of you say
is the most beautiful sight
in the whole East Blue?
[CROWD]
That would be you!
[ALVIDA]
That's correct.
I am quite breathtaking,
aren't I?
There isn't a man alive
who wouldn't crumble
before my beauty.
But I prefer strong men.
Like you. I'm going to make
you all mine, Luffy. Just wait.
Aw, gross! No way.
Just who the heck are you?!
[ALVIDA] You still haven't
figured it out?!
[ASST. POLICE CAPTAIN]
This is the police!
Put your weapon down
and come quietly!
I am placing you under arrest
for assaulting a police captain!
As for you up there!
Get off that platform!
Hold on. Who did you
say you were arresting?
We're arresting you!
[ALVIDA] Are you really
going to arrest me?
[chuckles]
We've got a big
problem here, sir.
She's too beautiful!
I really don't give
a damn! Arrest her!
[OFFICER A]
Do we have to?
[OFFICER B] Can't we just
stand here and look at her?
[BUGGY]
Surprise!
[OFFICER B]
A terrorist bombing!
[TOWNSMAN 8]
Watch out, miss!
Did that just‐‐?
It slipped right past her!
Oh man. That's weird!
[BUGGY laughing]
That little stunt was
dangerous, you know?
[BUGGY]
I'm flashily sorry.
But your smooth skin
is unharmed, of course,
so there's no need for
trouble, fairest Alvida.
[chuckles]
Alvida?
[LUFFY]
I don't see Alvida.
Don't be so dense,
you nimwit! I'm Alvida!
Are you sure? 'Cause I
don't think you're her.
I guess I really did change
after eating the fruit called...
...Smooth‐Smooth Fruit.
No attack can hurt my skin
because it slides right off.
Unfortunately, a lowly fruit
couldn't improve upon
my already stunning good looks.
One big change you
may have noticed
was that I
lost my freckles.
[LUFFY]
Sure, that must be it.
After becoming a
whole new person,
I decided to join
forces with someone
who shared my goal
of finding you.
[BUGGY laughing]
Now that I've flashily
made my entrance,
behold the real
star of this show.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Ever since the day
you sent me flying,
I've been obsessed with
exacting my revenge on you.
That alone led me to finally
finding my crew!
My travels are an epic saga.
I went through hell,
found friendship,
I even lost parts of my body.
I call this tale:
"Tiny Buggy's Great Adventure"!
The first thing that
happened was‐‐
Why the hell am I
telling you a story?!
Don't know. Now...
what was your name again?
Boggy? Boogie? Behie? Baggy?
Ah! I know! It's Buffoon!
Buffoon?! You got a lot
of nerve you rubber bastard!
And now Buggy the Clown is
gonna make you pay for that!
Hey, that's Buggy the Clown!
Pirates!
[CROWD]
It's the Buggy Pirates! Ah!
[BUGGY] You people flashily
stay where you are!
I want every single one of you
to see exactly how
scary I can be.
Oh yeah! Buggy, right?!
You mean you just now
remembered it?!
Hey! What gives?!
Long time no see,
you rubber freak.
How's your pal Roronoa Zoro?
[BUGGY]
Got 'em. Good job, Cabaji.
[laughing]
[BUGGY]
To all of my followers,
hundreds of billions of
them around the world,
we will now super flashily
begin the public execution!
You're trapped Monkey D. Luffy!
You can't move so
much as an inch!
[BUGGY laughing]
Tell me, Straw Hat,
feel honored?
You'll die in the same place
as the King of the Pirates!
[laughing]
The barometric pressure
is falling fast.
I've never seen such
a sharp drop before.
You know, I thought
I felt something strange.
[NAMI] There's a storm headed
straight for the island.
[USOPP]
A storm?
[NAMI] Yeah, we'd better
hurry back to the ship
or we'll be in trouble.
Is it gonna be big?
[ZORO]
Hey!
[NAMI]
Zoro!
Where is he? Have you
guys seen him around?
You mean Luffy?
[ZORO] Yeah. We got separated.
And I keep gettin' this feeling.
It's not good.
It usually means that something
bad's gonna happen.
[TOWNSMAN 7 screams]
[TOWNSMAN 8]
Pirates are here!
[TOWNSMAN 1]
Holy crap!
[TOWNSMAN 2]
Run!
[TOWNSMAN 3]
It's Buggy the Clown!
What'd they say?
I think they said Buggy.
[SMOKER]
Hmm. And then what?
[GENERAL]
Well, sir,
it isn't just Straw Hat Luffy,
it's also Buggy the Clown,
and Iron Club Alvida.
They're all there! Wanted
pirates from the East Blue
have taken over
our town square!
They do all of this
right in front of me?
Why those arrogant scumbags.
Captain Smoker, sir,
what are your orders?
Send unit number one
out to the sea,
and have unit number two
surround the pirates
from the streets.
The rest will stand by within
shooting range of the square.
See that it's done.
[GENERAL]
Sir!
[SMOKER]
And give this order to unit one.
They are to crush any pirate
ships as soon as they see them.
I don't want a single one
of those wretched pirates
to get off this island.
Not a single one.
[TOWNSMAN 5]
It's time for the execution!
[TOWNSMAN 4] Buggy the Clown
is gonna kill Straw Hat Luffy!
Yeah!
They're gonna execute him?!
That freakin' idiot!
[ZORO]
Let's go!
[SANJI]
Hold this.
[USOPP yelping]
[USOPP]
San‐‐ Sanji!
[SANJI] And treat it like
a lady, you got that?!
[NAMI]
Come on, we gotta hurry!
[USOPP]
Where're we goin', Nami?!
[NAMI]
The harbor, you numbskull!
[USOPP] Harbor?
Oh yeah, I knew that!
[MARINE A]
Captain Smoker. Look!
[MARINE B]
Things are getting weird.
[SMOKER]
It's that kid.
What's he doing out there?
Well, if I didn't
know any better,
I would say that Monkey D. Luffy
is about to be executed.
[SMOKER]
That kid looks pathetic.
Personal quest. To see where
the King of the Pirates died.
Huh...
[SMOKER] For some reason
that kid caught my attention.
I thought he was different
from the others.
Looks like he's nothing
but pirate scum after all.
Captain, we are
ready to attack.
Don't be hasty.
But we've got them
surrounded, sir!
I'm in command! You got it?
Yes, sir.
[SMOKER] One pirate is
about to kill another.
Let them fight it out first.
That'll save us the trouble.
Listen, once that
Straw Hat loses his head,
we surround Buggy,
Alvida, and their gang.
And do it fast!
[BUGGY laughing]
[BUGGY]
Pirate Monkey D. Luffy...
...of the Straw Hats,
will be flashily executed..
...for the crime of being stuck
up and making me angry!
Now live it up flashily!
Oh boy, I've never
seen an execution.
Well, you're about to kid.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
What?! Stop joking!
It's no joke.
[LUFFY] Take this
board off, you bastard!
[BUGGY] All right!
I hereby flashily begin
the festivities of this
public execution!
[BUGGY laughing]
[NAMI] I saw a massive cumulus
cloud in the eastern sky!
That means an unimaginably
big storm is headed our way.
And it's coming in fast!
If Buggy and Luffy
have caused a scene,
the Marines are sure
to come out.
And if our ship is washed out
to sea when we need to escape,
we're done for.
That is a big deal!
As a matter of fact,
I bet the Marines have already
started taking action!
And they'll destroy the
Going Merry if they find it!
[USOPP]
Hold on!
So you're telling me the
Going Merry's in danger?!
[USOPP]
C'mon, Nami! Hurry up!
[NAMI]
Wait for me!
[UNIT LEADER]
Okay, men, double time!
We have to get to the
harbor immediately
and destroy every
last pirate vessel!
[MARINES]
Yes, sir!
[MOHJI] ♪ Riding around
on a Ritchie bike! ♪
♪ Who's that man?
Who's that man? Who? Who? ♪
♪ Who's that man riding
around on a Ritchie bike! ♪
Oh yes, it's me!
So this is the rubber
guy's ship, huh?
[RICHIE]
Uh‐huh.
Would ya look at that?
He's got a bigger ship. He
won't need it where he's going.
Cause it's almost time for Buggy
to flashily finish him off.
However, just in case
the rubber guy,
who has absolutely no chance of
escaping, happens to escape,
we need to burn this ship down.
Burning wood smells so good.
[grunting]
I'm so sorry. Really, I am.
Please spare my life.
Why would I spare your life?!
This is what happens
when you go against us.
I guess this is it for
the man I had my eye on.
You've got quite a big audience
here today, Straw Hat.
You wanna say a few
words before you die?
Oh? Cat got your tongue?
That's all right. Stay quiet,
or say a few words,
it doesn't matter,
you're still gonna die!
Listen! I'm the man who'll
be King of the Pirates!
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!
[TOWNSMAN 6]
What?
[TOWNSMAN 7]
He said... King of the Pirates.
[TOWNSMAN 1]
In this town of all places?
[TOWNSMAN 2]
That's a crazy thing to say.
We're finally getting to
the best part of the show.
Bye, bye now.
[chuckles]
[ZORO]
Stop the execution!
[ZORO, SANJI]
Now!
Sanji! Zoro!
Zoro!
Luffy, you idiot.
Guess all that foolin' around
finally caught up with ya, huh?
[SANJI]
You startin' a sideshow?
Or is that just how
you look? Pretty sad.
Now what we gotta do is
drive these goons away.
[TOWNSMAN 1]
N‐No! It's pirate hunter Zoro!
[CROWD screaming]
Hey, guys! Heh!
You made it, Zoro! But you're
just a little bit too late.
[ZORO] We gotta bring
down the platform
Roronoa... Zoro.
Okay, boys! Get 'em!
[PIRATE A]
Let's do it!
[PIRATE B]
Yeah!
[ZORO]
Outta our way!
[laughing]
Not even the great Zoro
can stop me now!
There's nothing you two can do!
It's the end for your captain!
Bastard!
[ZORO] If I can just cut
down the platform...
[MARINE C]
Listen.
The moment Monkey D.
Luffy's head falls,
we all attack together.
Prepare for battle.
[MARINES]
Sir!
[BUGGY laughing]
[LUFFY]
Zoro! Sanji!
Usopp! Nami!
Sorry.
[LUFFY]
But... I'm dead.
[ZORO]
Idiot!
[SANJI]
Don't say that!
He smiled.
[laughing]
I'm still alive! That's nice!
That was divine intervention.
[ZORO] Stop talkin' nonsense.
We gotta get outta this town.
Our troubles are not over.
[LUFFY laughing]
Attack! Surround all
the pirates now!
[MARINES yelling]
[SANJI]
Here they come!
Oh wow! So cool!
Everybody here went
crazy so quickly.
[ZORO]
Luffy!
[LUFFY screaming]
Zoro!
We don't have time for this.
We have got to get outta here.
We'd better hurry back
to the Going Merry
or we'll never be able
to leave this island.
And we sure as hell
won't get to the Grand Line!
Really? Well,
that's no good. Run!
The Straw Hat Gang
is getting away!
[MARINE C]
Capture them!
[SMOKER]
Why did he smile?
Did he know he'd be saved?
No.
At that moment, he was certain
that his life was about to end.
He simply accepted death,
and smiled after
preparing himself.
Captain, we have to
pursue the pirates.
Lieutenant, think back.
Have you ever seen
any pirates who smiled
on the execution platform?
[LT. COMMANDER]
No, sir.
It doesn't matter how
tough the guy is.
At the moment of death, they all
turn pale and die in despair.
[SMOKER] That Straw Hat
man smiled. I saw it.
He smiled just like
Gold Roger, 22 years ago.
Just like the old King
of the Pirates did
on that exact
execution platform.
Captain.
Where's the Straw Hat man now?
Sir.
He slipped past us and is
heading towards the harbor.
[SMOKER] Unit one should've
destroyed their ship by now.
Well, sir. They had to return
to port for a refitting.
See, they couldn't light their
powder due to the sudden rain.
[SMOKER]
What?!
But a reserve unit
is currently making preparations
to attack the ship instead.
Captain Smoker,
if we let them sail now,
they'll be able to
get to the Grand Line
before we can capture them.
[SMOKER] The wind is blowing
towards the west.
It's a tailwind for that ship.
[SMOKER]
Is this just mere coincidence?
It's as if heaven itself
has special plans
for this young pirate.
[ZORO] We'd better pick up
the pace or we're toast!
[SMOKER]
I am White Hunter Smoker.
On my honor as Marine Captain,
I won't let that man
leave this island!
[MAN] Blow, winds!
The storm of fate has arrived!
♪All that's in my
heart confuses me,
I cannot understand,
As I face what I must do,
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand.
I'll set sail alone,
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near,
As I drift away,
I pray you watch me
as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise,
I began to wonder,
What could be the reason,
It's so hot inside.
No answer has come,
But I can't get away
from what's true,
It's because of you...
Show me how to
catch those feelings,
Get 'em to come back to me,
I'll do what I must,
Because they're
everything I wanna be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back
from yesterday,
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we
can make the way.♪