Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of
pirates go to battle
across the seas in search
of the One Piece,
the legendary
treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will
cut a path across
the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison Impel Down.
With the assistance of Ivankov,
the Queen of New Kama Land,
Luffy was finally able
to make it to Level 6,
only to discover that
Ace was already gone.
[MAGELLAN] I assure you,
resistance is futile.
[ACE groaning]
[ACE groans]
Luffy!
[MAGELLAN]
Your brother's a pirate.
His fate was sealed the moment
he stepped in this prison.
[ACE sighs] Damn it, Luffy.
I'd hoped Hancock was lying.
[INAZUMA] It was a simple plan,
but it defeated us nonetheless.
As much as I hate to admit it,
we're trapped here on Level 6.
At least for the time being.
As far as Ace Boy
and the Navy goes,
that ship has already sailed,
literally. Give up on him, 'kay?
Or rather, put your
faith in Whitebeard.
There's no way he'd give
up on one of his own!
He'll come up with something.
I'm leaving.
Huh?!
I'm going to Marineford
Look. If I give up now,
I'll regret it.
[INAZUMA] You can do as you
like, but first of all,
how do you propose we
get off of this floor?
[CROCODILE chuckles]
[IVANKOV, INAZUMA, LUFFY]
Uh?!
If you want out that
bad, then set me free.
I'll make a hole in the ceiling
and you'll be free to go.
--Sound good?
--[chains rattling]
[CROCODILE chuckles]
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Crocodile!
[chuckles]
Just like old times, huh?
Did ya miss me?
[LUFFY] "The Ultimate Team Has
Formed! Shaking Impel Down!"
[CROCODILE grunts]
You know, for the life of me,
I couldn't think of a good
reason to break out of here.
But Whitebeard and the Navy
are gonna start a war?
This is my chance to bring down
that old man once and for all.
This clash of powers
has piqued my interest,
and I've just the
tools at my disposal
to get us a front row
seat to the action.
You scratch my back,
and I'll scratch yours.
Not a bad proposition, is it?
[LUFFY growls]
[inaudible]
Screw that crap! You messed up
Vivi's whole country, you jerk,
--you can rot down here!
--That was a long time ago.
That place is no longer
of any interest to me.
[LUFFY growls]
--[footsteps]
--[CROCODILE] Hm?
However you may feel,
we still need his help.
If we have an opportunity
to escape from here,
then we're obliged to take it.
What? Are you crazy, Iva?
Do you know what this guy--
It's no time to be hoity-toity.
Sandy Pants here is our
only ticket outside.
[CROCODILE growls]
Hello, Ivankov.
My, my, it's been a long
time. Eh, Croco boy?
Hey wait, you two
know each other?
Just a passing acquaintance.
I met him when he was a rookie,
all wet behind the ears.
I wouldn't worry. If this guy
tries to double cross us,
I'll whip him into shape in
a jiffy. As long as I've got
an eye on him, then he
should behave just fine.
[IVANKOV chuckles]
He is a scoundrel,
but he's a scoundrel with
a weakness I know well.
Hey! If you so much as mention
a word of that, I'll--
Easy there!
Sure you want to take that
snippy tone with me, Croco Boy?
Because I'd be more than happy
to reveal your sordid
past right now.
[CROCODILE growls]
[IVANKOV] Or, you can shut that
mouth of yours, help us out,
and keep your dirty
little secret. Heehaw!
[CROCODILE growls]
Cocky bastard!
Hey, you guys!
While you're at it,
you should let me
outta here, too!
Me, too! Me, too! I gotta
bone to pick with Whitebeard!
Yeah, let me out, too!
[PRISONERS chanting]
Shut up! Death Wink!
[PRISONERS groan]
[JIMBEI]
Please, have mercy on me!
I beg you to take me with you!
I will be of great service!
I've known your brother Ace
since he first joined
the Whitebeard pirates!
He's a good friend!
And I know you too,
from all the stories he's told!
I'm not like the
others down here.
I was arrested because I
objected to his execution!
I wanna help save Ace, too!
I swear, I will put my
life on the line for him!
[IVANKOV] Mm... Jimbei,
"The First Son of the Sea".
If they imprisoned him here,
then he must have relinquished
his title as one of
the Seven Warlords.
That would mean his
self-proclaimed bond with Ace
has merit indeed.
--[LUFFY] All right then.
--[INAZUMA] Wait, are you sure?
You've never even met this man,
and he's most
assuredly dangerous!
It'll be fine.
Just let him out, okay?
You have my gratitude.
Me next! I like Ace, too!
I'll die for him and stuff!
You boys are asking
for a Death Wink!
[PRISONERS yelp]
[CROCODILE]
Mm.
Two Warlords. Or two
former Warlords, that is.
Wait a sec. Fish guy? For real?
You won't regret this.
I will fight to protect Ace,
even if it means my own end.
Ha. If you think you
can stop the war
between the Navy and
Whitebeard, go ahead and try.
I don't give a damn, either way.
As long as I get a shot
at that crusty old bastard,
it's worth it for me.
If you think I'll let you lay
a single finger on Whitebeard,
you're wrong.
Well then, why don't
you just try and stop me?
Croco Boy.
Your secret past, remember?
[CROCODILE growls]
It's settled then.
Let's get moving. We don't
have much time.
With a team this formidable, not
even Impel Down can hold us!
Hee-haw!
All units, Load up, move out.
Use your Prison Bullets!
Prepare to deal with
Devil Fruit powers!
[GUARD B]
We've reached Level 6, sir!
[GUARD A]
Move in!
[GUARDS]
Huh?
[GUARD F] What the heck?
Is that the ceiling?
[GUARD G]
Worry about that later!
Spread out and search the floor!
[SHIRYU] Do you really think
they stuck around here,
after making that gigantic
hole, you morons?
[GUARD F]
Huh?
S-Shiryu, the Jail Manager!
Pathetic. It's as plain as day,
you can't do anything
right without me.
What a bunch of sorry
excuses for jailers.
Let me give you a hint, so maybe
you can clean up this disgrace.
While you were picking your
noses, the three prisoners
you're looking for released
Crocodile and Jimbei.
And then climbed up through
that hole to Level 5.
I want you to pass along
a message for me.
Tell Magellan I'll
help him, if he wants.
[GUARD F]
No, that's... Uh!
What?! What did you say?
They've escaped with
Jimbei and Crocodile?!
[GUARD F] Yes, sir!
They're not in their cells!
No! Are you saying that even
after my brilliant plan,
they somehow wormed
their way out of Level 6!
And that now they're a
group of 5 roaming wild
and not sleeping like
they're supposed to be?
[GUARD F]
Yes, sir! That's correct!
[HANNYABAL yelling]
Do you think I might
be held responsible
for any of this nonsense?
Warden Magellan is currently
transporting Portgas D. Ace
to the Navy. So I'm afraid you'd
be responsible for all of it.
[HANNYABAL] I knew you were
gonna say that! Ah! Ah...
All right, I'm gonna get
out there and fight, too!
All jailers report to
Level 4 immediately!
Mistress Sadie! Saldeath!
Gather your forces and head
to Level 4 this instant!
I'll be Warden even if
I have to risk my life!
Wait, what am I saying?!
Stop those criminals, even if
you have to risk your lives!
[IVANKOV]
You ready to boogie, Bon boy?
Yes. Yes, I am, Iva!
[IVANKOV]
Are you sure?
Emporio Energy Hormones only
give you strength for one day.
There will be side effects.
I know. Go ahead and do it.
I mean, what choice do I have?
If I don't, I won't even be
able to get off the floor.
Yes, good point!
Unless I wanted to carry you.
Which, for the record, I do not.
Emporio Energy Hormone!
[BON CLAY groans]
[IVANKOV] Yikes!
Right in the jimmies. Oopsie!
[BON CLAY]
New Kama Power!
[LUFFY]
Bon! Please, don't die!
Is everybody ready?
Just so you know,
even if we do make it
to the top of the prison,
we'll still be in for
one hell of a fight.
We're completely
surrounded by the Calm Belt,
which is impassable
in any normal ship.
We'll have to steal
a Navy vessel
if we want to go anywhere
near their headquarters.
That means we need more
people to join our team!
I know what you're thinking,
we have lots already.
But to be honest, some of you
won't make it out alive.
By the time we
reach the top floor,
many of you won't
be there to see it.
If you're captured,
you'll be tortured to death.
There will be no mercy.
So, if we want to survive,
we need to set free as
many prisoners as possible
while we make our way from
here to Level 1.
Whether we like them or
not, we'll need their help.
If we can cause enough
chaos to start a riot,
it'll help keep those
jailers occupied.
That means our first step on
each floor is to open the cells
and let our new friends
clear the way for us!
So let's give these
boys hell!
New Kama Land is gonna
rattle this big cage
the likes of which they've
never seen before!
Hee-haw!
[ALL cheer]
Are ya ready to rock this,
Straw Hat Boy? Huh?
He went on ahead of us.
A free spirit! Hee-haw! Let's
catch up with him, candies!
[ALL cheer]
[BON CLAY] Wait! Somebody,
please! Stop me!
I'm going too fast! It's never
been this fast before! [screams]
Huh. The hormone seems to
be working a bit overtime.
Indeed. But check out those
amazing moves! Very nice.
[BON CLAY] It's not nice!
I'm getting sick! Ooh!
At least the Navy will remain
blissfully ignorant
of this disaster.
[sighs] All right!
Back to your posts and
clean up the mess inside!
[GUARDS]
Yes, sir!
[LUFFY panting]
It's just before
ten in the morning.
The execution is at
three in the afternoon.
We can be certain that they'll
do everything in their power
to stay on time! So if
Whitebeard is going to
make an attack, it's most
likely that he'll do it
as soon as possible. Ace
should already be on the ship
and en route. The war could
break out at any second.
But they won't kill him
until three o'clock, right?
That means we still
have a chance
to get there and save him!
--[CROCODILE grunts]
--[LUFFY] Huh?
[CROCODILE] Is this
supposed to slow me down?
I'll use my right hand
and turn this into sand.
[NARRATOR]
Let's go over
how Crocodile's Sand-Sand
Devil Fruit power works.
He can turn into sand,
as well as control it.
His right hand can suck
out any type of moisture.
People and plants
will wither away,
while rocks and earth will
turn into sand.
[CROCODILE grunts]
[GUARDS gasp]
[GUARD I]
They're-They're here!
Uh. Level 4, reporting in.
Jimbei, the Warlord who escaped
from Level 6, has been sighted.
Seems we've reached
the Burning Heat Hell.
[GUARD I] Alongside the
intruder, Monkey D. Luffy.
Man, it's hot!
[GUARD I] The former Warlord
Crocodile is here as well!
We're prepared to
engage the enemy! Fire!
[GUARDS scream]
Idiots! Use the Prison Bullets!
[CROCODILE yells]
[GUARDS scream]
[GUARD K screams]
[GUARD L]
Fire the Prison Bullets!
[LUFFY grunts]
Here we go! Gum-Gum Rain!
[GUARDS groaning]
Fishman Karate!
[GUARDS whimper]
[JIMBEI grunts]
[GUARD M screams]
[GUARD M]
Huh? Hey, what just happened?
[GUARDS]
Uh...
[GUARD N groans]
[GUARD Q groans]
[GUARDS groaning]
[GUARD S]
Ah! What the hell is this?
Feel my Arabesque Brick Fist!
[GUARD U]
Straw Hat and two Warlords?!
What are we supposed to do?!
We don't stand a chance!
[GUARD V] Don't give up!
We outnumber them, at least!
We need to hold out until
the reinforcements arrive!
[GUARDS whimper]
Move it. We're in a rush.
Should be fun.
[GUARD W] Don't just
stand there! Shoot them!
[gun shots]
[SECURITY SNAIL A beeping]
[HANNYABAL]
Huh?! Talk to me!
[GUARD X]
Vice Warden, this is Level 4!
You got 'em?!
[GUARD X]
Uh, about that.
[GUARDS scream]
[GUARD X]
Please! Come help us, sir!
[grunts] Come on boys!
[MANTICORE A]
Camisole.
[MANTICORE B]
Long johns.
[MANTICORE C]
T-back.
[MANTICORE A]
Pantyhose.
[MANTICORE B]
Briefs.
[MANTICORE A]
Leggings.
[MANTICORE C]
Bra.
[MANTICORE D]
Bloomers.
[MANTICORE C]
Bloomers. Briefs. Briefs.
[MANTICORE B]
Briefs.
[BUGGY] All this
waiting around sucks!
[MR. 3]
It's not funny anymore.
[BUGGY] Damn! Why're they
hanging out right here?
Stupid underwear fetishists!
[MR. 3] Just cleaning their
butts. Must be nice.
We finally make it to Level 2,
and this is what stops us?
If the guards come,
it's all for nothing!
Also, these things won't
stop farting. It's awful!
Ain't that the truth!
[BUGGY, MR. 3 gagging]
[farts]
[BUGGY]
That was you!
[MR. 3]
I'm sorry.
[BUGGY groans]
Smells like burdock.
[MR. 3]
I know.
Holy crap! The keys!
Now we can get out!
Thanks, buddy,
you don't know how... Oh!
It's... You're Crocodile!
I'm thinkin' about
breaking outta here,
but I might need a
bit of assistance.
And you, you're a man of action.
Aren't you, Mr. 1?
Now that you mention it,
things are a bit boring here.
I think I might take you up
on that offer, old friend.
[NARRATOR]
Luffy and his companions
battle their way up to Level 4.
Meanwhile, the
prisoners on Level 2
cause a massive riot. Plunging
the prison into utter chaos.
Suddenly, another infamous
pirate breaks into Impel Down.
But what could be his mission?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Even More Chaos
Blackbeard Teach Invades"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!