[thinking]
That scent! Is it?
Huh?! Chopper, what is it?
Chopper!
Oo... Waaah!!
[tumbling sounds
followed by a thud]
Are you all right?
[SANJI]
Chopper! Did you hurt yourself?
There you are!
Don't run off like that!
What in the hell is
the matter with you?
One second, you're
right beside me.
I knew it! Look!
[CHOPPER] Robin!
[SANJI] It's Robin!
Stay where you are.
Because I won't be coming
back to you and your crew.
We're parting ways
here, in this city.
[ROBIN]
Inside me,
I carry a darkness that
none of you know about.
One day, that darkness
will be the end of all of you.
[ROBIN] I'm afraid you'll
be taking the fall
for last night's attack
while I escape.
And let me warn you.
The situation
will only get worse.
Robin! What happened?
You're not making any sense!
This isn't like you at all!
Please! We'll work
this out together!
Although I only spent
a short time with you,
from this day forward.
We will never see
each other again.
Thank you for all of the
kindness you've shown me.
Know that I'll never forget it.
Goodbye.
[SANJI]
Wait...
No... please...
This can't...
This can't be happening.
Hey!
Come back!
[SANJI] Stop! You don't know
what you're saying! Robin!
Robin!
I lost track of her scent.
I see.
Hey, Chopper.
Hm?
[SANJI] Go meet up with
Luffy and the others
and tell them everything that
happened between us and Robin.
I don't want you to
leave out a single word.
Sure.
As for me, let's just
say I have a plan.
I'll try to be careful.
We'll meet up later.
♪ opening song ♪
[LUFFY]
[CRAFTSMAN A]
Hold it right there!
[CRAFTSMAN B]
Don't let 'em get away!
This is all your fault, Zoro!
The whole town is
out looking for us!
It was gonna happen
sooner or later, wasn't it?!
[CRAFTSMAN A]
You can't run forever!
[LUFFY]
This way!
[NAMI]
Right!
[CRAFTSMAN A]
Over here!
[CRAFTSMAN B]
Where'd they go?
[CRAFTSMAN C]
Check the alleys!
[CRAFTSMAN D] You don't think
they're on the rooftops, do you?
[CRAFTSMAN F]
Damn it! We lost 'em!
[CRAFTSMAN G] I don't get it.
I'm sure they went this way.
[CRAFTSMAN H]
We'd better keep moving.
[CRAFTSMAN I] All right,
but we should check
inside the buildings, too.
[CRAFTSMAN J] Good.
We'll split up. Let's go!
Yeah!
[LUFFY]
Is it okay now?
Wait a sec.
[CRAFTSMAN K]
Where'd you last see them?
Just a little longer.
Aaah!!
[NAMI shrieks]
Uhhh...
I'm begging you.
[SHOP OWNER A]
Are you crazy?
I've gotta evacuate!
Stop pestering me!
Come on.
I have money, okay?
Here take it.
I need as much lumber,
tar, and rope as this'll buy.
Oh, and also some nails,
latches and tin plates,
if you don't mind.
[SHOP OWNER A]
I said I'm closing the shop.
[USOPP] It'll just
take a second, please.
[USOPP's stomach growls]
[sighs]
Okay, kid.
But I'm afraid this money
ain't gonna buy much for ya.
Uh. Then... how
'bout I sell my tools?
Will that make
up for the rest?
Hey, hey. Come on! Stop it!
We don't do barter.
This's the big city, you know.
I'm sorry, but it's cash only.
[stomach growling]
You win. But
let's make it quick.
[SHOP OWNER A] You sure
you're okay carrying that
with all those injuries?
Can't you get some friends
to help you out? Hey!
[USOPP grunts]
[SHOP OWNER A]
I knew this was a bad idea!
Wait! This isn't gonna work!
I'm fine. I got it.
This is nothing.
[SHOP OWNER A]
Hey!
Don't worry. I can do it.
[SHOP OWNER A]
No, look.
Here, take these.
You're hungry, right?
[stomach growls]
[USOPP]
Th-Thank you.
[SHOP OWNER A] Sure thing.
Try to be careful.
Good luck out there, kid!
[USOPP]
Mm-mm.
These are good.
Really good.
Guess that guy was
pretty nice after all.
The waves sure are
getting high, aren't they?
Don't worry, Merry.
You're gonna be just fine!
After all, you flew
in the sky, remember?
You've got nothing
to be afraid of!
[loud crashing]
Oh ho ho! Whoa, what's
got you riled up, big guy?
C'mon Franky,
you can tell us!
What's up, bro?
AARRGH!
I got so much rage inside me,
I feel another rampage
comin' on right about now!
[MOZU] Hey, wait for me, bro,
don't rampage alone!
As always, thanks
for the drinks, Blueno!
Hahaha!
What got into
him all of a sudden?
Is there something going on?
Beats me.
Never can tell with that guy.
Only idiots know what
idiots are thinking.
Looks like the
crowd cleared out.
Yeah, no thanks to you!
I'll have you know that Luffy
and I had a perfectly good
hiding place until you lead
that angry mob straight to us!
Like I said, with that
many people looking,
they were gonna
find you anyway.
Oh yeah, that reminds me.
How did you know we
were down there, Chopper?
Your smell.
Ah... I shoulda known.
But wait, wasn't Sanji with you?
Well, he was.
No way! That doesn't
make any sense!
Did Robin really
say that to you?!
[ZORO] We were prepared
for this, weren't we?
After all, Robin was our enemy
before we let her join the crew.
This might be our only
chance to find out the truth.
So we shouldn't run away.
There's still lot of things
we don't know about Robin.
Now it's time to decide
if she's a friend or a foe.
[ROBIN]
The situation will get worse.
From this day forward we will
never see each other again.
[ZORO]
You're sure?
That's all she said, Chopper?
Mmm.
If she says she won't
see us after today
and things are gonna get worse,
maybe that means
the attack on Iceberg
was just a warm-up
and she has something
even bigger
planned for tonight.
I don't know why
Robin's doing any of this,
so it's hard to make a guess
as to what she's planning.
But seeing how much
commotion her first attack
on the mayor caused,
there's only one way
to make things worse.
In other words,
she'll murder him.
[ZORO] I think that's what she's
trying to tell us, at least.
Also since she told Chopper
that she'll be pinning
the crime on us,
it could be that she's feeding
us all these little hints
to try and lure us out
to the crime scene tonight.
Think so?
If that is her plan,
it would be convenient
for her if we did
happen to show up.
Since that would put us
at the scene of the crime.
You say you don't
know what she's thinking,
but it sound to me like you've
already decided
that she's our enemy!
I'm talking about
possibilities here, that's all.
We should always be prepared
for the worst-case
scenario, understand?
If I get locked into a
single line of thinking,
it'll only slow me down.
If she's my friend,
I have to be ready to forgive
but if she's my enemy
I have to be ready to fight.
Our best chance to settle
this is tonight. Are we going?
Of course.
It's not that
I object to the plan
but we're still
forgetting something.
Sanji said he saw Robin walking
with someone in
a mask, remember?
Obviously that wasn't one of us,
but Iceberg said
exactly the same thing.
That he was attacked by Robin
and a large man in a mask
that he didn't recognize.
Whoever he is,
I bet he's the reason
Robin is doing
all of this stuff.
Yeah! That means
it isn't her fault
and we just need to beat
the real bad guy. Right?
That's the ideal situation.
But on the other hand,
it's also possible that this
guy is one of Robin's friends.
The problem is we
don't have much to go
on other than
"a big man in a mask."
So where do we even start?
I mean, what is our goal here?
We find Robin and capture her.
[LUFFY] That's the only way
we'll ever know the truth.
[ZORO]
You're right.
We're wasting time here
trying to figure it out.
Just one thing.
Robin won't be easy to catch.
After all, the World
Government's been trying
for 20 years and it
still hasn't happened.
Like he said, it's the only
way we'll really know for sure.
Yeah. Let's settle
this right now!
[LUFFY]
Right.
Come on. Galley-La's waiting.
Damn. It's late.
Where'd Straw Hat run off to?
[CRAFTSMAN C]
Paulie! We gotta go!
All these streets are
gonna flood before long!
All right. Let's head back.
I'm going to the main office.
Sounds good, boss.
You heard him, guys,
time to move out!
[FRANKY] Get out here and
fight me, Straw Hat!
Where are you?! Stop hiding!
I thought that little
turd had some backbone,
but I guess I was wrong.
Won't even show his face.
I know what you're saying, bro,
but to be fair, the whole
island is hunting him down
right now, you know?
Exactly! I bet he's hiding,
if he hasn't been
caught already.
By the way, what's
with this weird crab
walk thing all of a sudden.
If we face the front,
then the wind catches
our hair and we blow away!
Speaking of which, the
weather isn't the only thing
that's out of control today.
[MOZU]
Tell me about it.
It's like you've got a rampage
going on inside you, too.
Shut up. I'm just like
that this week, okay?
[ZAMBAI]
Hey bro!
[GROUP]
Hey, it's bro! Hey, bro!
[MOZU]
Well, if it isn't Zambai!
Tell me, tell me that you
beat up those stupid Straw Hats.
No, but I tried to.
Some angry mob showed up,
got in the way,
then Luffy took off.
[GROUP]
Huh?
Are those guys lucky or what?
When you're on a rampage,
nobody survives!
That's weird. I wondered
why that weak dude
with the long nose was
fixing the ship on his own.
I figured that you'd wrecked
up the rest of the crew
so bad that he was the only one
left who could do anything.
Wait. You found one of 'em?!
Yeah, on their ship.
[FRANKY chuckles]
Well, that's just fine,
'cause all we need is one.
In other words,
we'll use that loser as bait
to lure out the rest of 'em.
Whoa, Bro's got his
bad guy face on, guys.
All right, you
good-for-nothings,
I want you to march
through the town
and spread the word for me.
Say "we've got Long-Nose
and if you don't want him
swimming with the fishes,
then come to the
warehouse under the bridge."
Tell 'em Franky sent ya.
[chuckles]
In the meantime,
I'll go nab Long Nose
so we can make good
on our little threat.
You got it, Bro! I swear
we won't let you down!
Hey, you. Yeah,
you with the luggage.
What's all that stuff you got?
It's my special bed.
[CHILDREN]
Aqua Laguna! Agua Laguna!
Aqua Laguna is coming for you!
[CHILD A]
Here comes a big wave!
[laughter, play shrieks]
So do you know
what's going on
with those Straw Hats?
I'm not sure.
I don't think they've
caught them yet.
Tsk! Still on the loose!
Ah... That's no good!
And with everyone so
worked up about the storm,
they'll have the perfect
chance to attack again.
[CHILD B] Aaah!
Aqua Laguna's gonna get me!
And what I heard,
is that tonight,
all the craftsmen from
the Galley-La Company
will be guarding the main
office to protect the mayor.
Whoa, that's a really
big deal, isn't it?
[CITIZEN F] How many people
have the Straw Hats got, anyway?
[CITIZEN G] Some say 50.
Some say 100 or even more!
Remember, the captain's got a
100 million bounty on his head.
For all we know, he could be
sending an army of 3,000 men
to fight the
shipwrights as we speak!
Are you kidding?!
That sounds really bad!
[CRAFTSMAN M]
All right, men,
hold your formation
and don't give an inch!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
Don't even let a single
fly get through, got it?!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
Bring it on!! Wahahaha!!
What's wrong with you?!
Would you please
be quiet, Tiletone?!
[LULU]
I heard the Straw Hats
weren't spotted on
the sea train.
That means they're still
here on the island somewhere.
Still. They'd be complete
idiots if they tried
to show up with all
of these guards around.
Yeah, you'd think,
but that didn't
stop the dumbass
that barged in
here earlier, did it?
We gotta be ready for anything.
[ICEBERG] Mwell, this is
reassuring, but it's a bit much.
They wanted to
do this for you.
I'm not royalty.
Pardon me sir,
but why on earth
did you put Nico Robin's
wanted poster up on your wall?
It bother you?
A bit.
Hmm...
It's better if you don't know.
That girl is a demon.
[CHOPPER] There sure are
a lot of people out there.
It's a little far, too.
It'll be fine if you rocket
through the window, right?
After Robin shows up, I mean.
That' right. If we
make a commotion first,
then they'll just sneak in while
we're dealing with the guards.
Let's be patient.
[CRAFTSMAN M]
Get ready!
Strike at anything
that moves, men! Got it?
[GROUP]
Yeah!
♪ ending song ♪
[NAMI] What was
that explosion?!
[ZORO] Looks like
they're on the move.
[NAMI] Uh oh, who are those
weird people in the masks?
[LUFFY] All I know is
that Robin's in there, too.
[ZORO] Remember,
if we miss her here,
we may never see her again.
[LUFFY] I know.
We'll catch her for sure.
We're gonna settle
this tonight, Robin.
On the next One Piece :
"Cannon Fire is the Signal!
CP9 Goes Into Action."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!