Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[HILDON] The night
has just begun,
but already the shadows
in the forest are deep.
Soon, it shall be transformed
into a world of terror,
far beyond your
worst nightmares.
Might I recommend
you take a ride
with me in my carriage?
We could go to
the mansion together.
Mansion?
[HILDON] Of course.
Dr. Hogback's abode
is just up the way.
Huh?!
Huh? What?
Do you know him Chopper?
Doctor Hogback?
[LUFFY]
"The Man Called a Genius!
Hogback Makes His Appearance!"
[distant howling]
[NAMI] Hey. I didn't
get a good look at them,
so maybe it's
my imagination,
but don't those horses
seem a bit strange?
[HILDON] It's dark.
Your eyes are
playing tricks on you.
[chuckles]
[NAMI] Well, if you say so.
I'm sure it's fine.
Anyway, thanks for
saving us back there.
We were in bad shape
before you showed up.
It was nothing.
Have a drink to
calm your nerves.
Now, this forest is filled
with frightening creatures.
It's dangerous to
pass through on foot.
I was surprised.
I thought Cerberus
was just a legend,
but there it was, three heads
gnashing and everything!
That thing musta
been some kind of mutant.
It just wasn't natural.
We were lucky we
got up in that tree,
but I was afraid I'd
never come down again
with that thing around!
If you're hoping to
wait for your friends,
the mansion's the safest place.
Besides, they couldn't
possibly miss it.
[CHOPPER]
Not only that.
We're gonna get to meet
Dr. Hogback, too, right?
Is this hog guy
really that famous?
Are you kidding?
Every doctor in the
world knows his name!
He's one of the
greatest surgeons ever!
He can perform
real miracles!
They say his operations
have saved more people
than there are stars in the sky!
He has fame
and fortune,
and every other honor a
doctor could ever hope for!
The entire medical community
looks up to him as a true hero!
But then, he just
disappeared without a trace.
Some people thought
he had an accident,
and others thought
that he was kidnapped.
But in the end, since
no one could find any clues,
everyone gave up
on looking for him.
And bit by bit they
started thinking of him
as nothing more than a legend.
That is the Hogback
you're talking about, right?
Yes indeed. He's
studying in seclusion.
The doctor came to this island
to conduct research beyond
the scope of mankind.
Ah! Do you think I could
get an autograph from him?
[HILDON] I'm sure
he could be persuaded
to spare a moment
for one of his fans.
No way.
This island
has lions, too?
Aaaaaahhh!!!
What's wrong with you?
Don't scare me like that!
Come on! What happened?
[NAMI] There was a lion!
But he--his face was...
[NAMI]
Ugh. It looked like this.
Oh yeah, right!
Wanna see?
Then take a look
for yourself! Here!
[laughter]
Huh?!
Eh?!
Oh?!
[sighs]
[laughter]
Aaaaah!
[ALL THREE] That is not right!
That is definitely not right!
Please, stop the carriage!
We need to turn around, Hildon.
My goodness, whatever
could've upset you so much?
Perhaps you all saw an illusion?
What do you mean "illusion"?
There was something
out there for sure!
This forest is freakin' strange!
That much is true.
It is a bit odd here.
The fog, for example,
has strange qualities.
It can even cause
hallucinations for some.
So you mean
it was just the fog?
[sighs] That's good!
Illusion? The fog?
No, that doesn't make any sense.
Listen Hildon, I'm sorry,
but I really do need you to take
us back to the coast right away.
Even if it's dangerous,
the three of us
can manage somehow.
But I wanna meet Dr. Hogback!
It's not fair! I have to!
[USOPP] I know how you feel,
but my "Something Freaky
is Going on Here"
Sensor is on high alert.
You've gotta trust
my powers on this one.
Either you can
go see the doctor and die,
or we can turn
back now and live.
Which one will it be?
Well, of course
I don't wanna die!
That's scary!
Oh, that's too bad.
Then, as you wish,
I'll have the driver turn
the carriage around for you.
Wait a moment
and I shall return.
[HILDON] Stop the carriage!
[chuckles]
Listen Chopper,
I'm sorry.
I know what this means to you.
No, I understand.
If I was strong
and brave like Luffy,
I could just walk
there by myself instead
of sitting here and crying.
How long does he plan
to make us wait here?
Dunno, but I'm too scared
to look outside again.
He's just turning around.
It should only take a sec.
Gaaaah!!
There's nobody here!
Not even the horses!
Not only that, they left us
in the middle of
some scary graveyard!
Are you kidding me? But why?
What? No, That can't be right!
Please, someone tell me
he just left to go pee!
Hildon! Hey! Where'd you go?
[USOPP] Leaving us alone at
night is one thing, but come on!
In a graveyard?
[NAMI] Yeah, I get it!
Just-- just stop, okay?
I'm trying to think here.
What should we do?
I'm scared!
[NAMI] Chopper.
[NAMI] What is it now?
[USOPP] Is that? No.
Aaaauuuggghhh!!
This is a dream, right?
[ALL THREE] Z-Z-Zombies! Nooooo!
[USOPP] It hurts! Help me!
Usopp!
These things are strong!
Usopp, no!
[CHOPPER] They're gonna
flip over the carriage!
He was right--
they're crazy strong!
[USOPP]
Aaaaaaugh!!
It bit me! Damn it!
It's all over! I'm gonna
turn into a zombie now!
Usopp! Hold on, I'm coming!
No! Get away
from me! Stop it!
Somebody help me! Ah!
Let Usopp go!
Eat this!
I'm sorry!
[ZOMBIE 340F] Here,
you dropped this.
[ZOMBIE 340D] Oh, thanks.
Don't let them bite me! Hurry!
Nami!
I said get off me! Get away!
My Exploding Star should work!
Zombies hate fire!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 340A]
Dude! Fire!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 340B]
Get back man, that'll burn you!
I figured it would work,
but I wasn't expecting this.
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 340C]
That's dangerous, you idiot!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 340D] Didn't
your parents raise you right?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 340E]
You little turd!
All right, that got the
zombies out of our way.
C'mon, Nami!
[USOPP] Let's get outta here!
Right!
[USOPP] At this point,
we might as well make
a run for the mansion, since
it's closer than the shore.
[CHOPPER] That sounds
like a good idea to me!
[NAMI] That was so scary!
Don't worry, we're fine.
As long as we're able
to keep up the pace,
there's no way those
things can catch us!
Even if they're strong
and don't get tired,
they shamble along
really slow when they move.
Shamble slow.
Shamble slow. Shamble slow.
Turbo shamble!
[USOPP] What,
were they just lazy?
[USOPP] No! No--
Hey, wait a sec.
They're tired now?
[CHOPPER] Keep running, Usopp!
[USOPP] Uh, right!
[ZORO] We're drifting away!
Do something, stupid!
[SANJI] You got
any ideas, genius?
The steering wheel
won't move an inch!
[FRANKY] Even if
we used the paddle,
those waves are too high.
Eh, no big hurry--
I'm still having fun.
The waves'll take us to the
island sooner or later.
Yeah? And what
about Nami, huh?
You forget about her?
What is that?
Hmm?
Is that a spider web?
[ROBIN] At this rate
we're going to be trapped.
[FRANKY] Hurry!
Use the paddle! Quick!
It's too late.
We're already caught.
Damn it. Now what?
The ship didn't take any damage,
but it's not like
we can sail it anymore.
And by the way,
I'd hate to see the
spider that spun this thing.
It's frikkin' huge!
[howl]
They aren't
following us, right?
[USOPP] Man, what
is with this island?
Half the stuff here isn't
even supposed to be real!
And by the way, if I start
turning into a zombie
and go after your brains,
then just kill me!
Where'd that come from?
If you get bit by a zombie,
you turn into one
and eat brains--
I read it in a book,
so it must be true.
I don't think you're mature
enough for horror novels,
you should stick
to children's books.
[sighs] Well, here we are.
I sure could go
for a glass of water.
I can see him after
all! Lucky me!
If he's crazy
enough to live here,
I have a feeling he's not going
to be quite as welcoming
as you hope, but fine.
[NAMI] Excuse me?
Is this the mansion of
Dr. Hogback, by any chance?
We're traveling pira--
Uh, traveling traveler people.
We've lost our way,
so could we take shelter
here until morning?
Hello? Is anyone there?
[USOPP] Well, there's nothing
stopping us from going in,
though this tunnel
is kinda scary lookin'.
[CHOPPER] I can see the
courtyard on the other side.
[NAMI] Is the doctor home?
What if no one
lives here?
Beats the zombies!
I say we give it a look.
[CHOPPER]
The lights just turned on!
That's a good sign, right?
[USOPP] But why would they shine
a spotlight on this old well?
It's weird.
Oh no. What is it now?
Welcome.
[CINDRY] One. Two. Three.
[CINDRY] And four, five.
Ah, ow! This crazy
woman is throwing plates!
[CINDRY] Six. Seven.
Why are you only attacking me?
Why, you ask?
Because you alone are not
allowed to enter the mansion.
You two are just fine, though.
Uh. I'm confused.
[CINDRY] Now you,
get out! Eight! Nine!
[USOPP] I don't get it!
[MALE VOICE] Stop it.
That's enough!
What?
Please! Nothing scary!
Ehhh... Hope he
doesn't throw plates.
[MALE VOICE]
We can make an exception
just this once,
can't we, Cindry?
Forgive me if we startled you.
You must excuse her.
You see, she was once
engaged to a wealthy man,
but to test his love,
she shattered ten plates
from his cherished dining set.
Sadly, he then called
off the engagement.
Cast out of her
home in disgrace,
she has become
my personal servant
with a boundless plate grudge.
Yeaaah... I don't really care.
[MALE VOICE] And as you
may have already surmised,
I am the long-missing, world-
famous surgeon, Dr. Hogback.
A genius, in the eyes of many.
[CINDRY] Ten!
[NAMI] Usopp!
Hey, Cindry!
We went over this!
I said he could come inside!
When you don't listen to me,
then I look like a fool
in front of our guests!
Uh-oh.
[CINDRY] I wish every last plate
in this world would disappear.
I got it! You don't
have to tell me!
I mean, I just got done
explaining it, didn't I?
So Chopper, that's who
you were talking about?
D-Doctor Hogback!
It's really him!
Doesn't look like
a genius to me.
Shut up, Nami!
[CINDRY] I'll make
an exception this once.
All three of you may enter.
We'll continue our
conversation inside.
Follow me.
[HOGBACK]
Uh, and there you have it,
please make yourselves at home.
I still don't get
why she hated me
so much,
but whatever.
I guess, at least,
we get to go in now.
Right. Anything's better
than that creepy forest.
Oh! Ah. Hey, wait!
I'm still here...
[HOGBACK]
Fasfasfasfasfas!!
It's quite rare for
me to receive guests,
but my, you
certainly are filthy.
Was it a stressful trip?
[NAMI] Well, yes, but it's
sort of a long story. We, uh--
[CHOPPER] Go ahead, Nami.
I can talk to him about
doctor stuff later.
We were attacked by a bunch
of zombies in the forest,
so we ran away and
came here to take shelter.
Zombies, huh?
We also saw a bunch
of crazy monsters
that were straight
out of a horror story!
What the heck is up
with this creepy island?
I mean, you live here, right?
You gotta know something!
So these beasts were
chasing you, were they?
And yet you still made it here
in one piece. Quite impressive.
But to answer your question,
I don't know much about
those creatures either,
which is precisely why I'm here.
Oh! You mean you're
studying zombies?
It's a brand new realm
of medical research!
Yes, indeed!
Although most people
associate zombies with fear,
what if you think
of them in terms
of "someone who has
come back from the dead?"
Then it's a miracle!
The dream of all doctors!
Everyone in this
world has a loved one
they'd like to see
come back to life!
Why, that's human nature!
And yet the medical
community condemns it.
Madness, they call it!
I'm trying to
play God, they say!
That's why I disappeared
from society,
so I could continue
my research in seclusion
on this island
without interruption!
Oh, wow! So I finally
found out the truth!
But just think-- If your
research here is a success
then you're going
to bring happiness
to thousands of people
all over the world!
As a doctor, myself, sir,
I'm behind you all the way!
How open minded!
Why, thank you, Doctor Chopper.
[CHOPPER] Even if you
acknowledge me as a doctor,
you won't get on my
good side, you big dummy!
[CHOPPER] C-Could I
have your autograph?
Oh, of course!
"To my dear, Doctor Chopper."
So do you think
you could give me
a little tour of your lab later?
No one, and I mean no one,
can look inside my lab!
[splat]
Ahhh!
Come on here, Cindry!
Can't you at least put
the flan on a plate?
Is that too much to ask?
I wish every last plate in
this world would disappear.
Fasfasfasfasfas!
Well, this sort of
thing does tend to happen,
so rest assured,
I'm always quite adamant
about keeping the
table cloth clean.
Okay. I'll eat, then.
You could still use
a spoon, you idiots!
[CHOPPER] It's so sweet--
I love it!
[CINDRY] I've prepared
a bath for you.
Since you're all filthy,
you should take one
before you go to bed.
I almost forgot to ask you.
There's someone else who
came to this island before us.
This may sound crazy,
but have you seen a
skeleton roaming around today?
A skeleton?
[USOPP] Yeah, he had an afro
and he was in a really
good mood for a dead guy.
[clack, clack, clack]
Yohohoho!!
'Course, even for this place,
I know it'd still be weird
to see a skeleton walking
around and talking.
So you're sure
he didn't come by?
[HOGBACK] Never seen him.
All right then.
It's no big deal.
[thinking] Is it really him?
No. It couldn't be.
[USOPP] Nami, are you
done in the bath, yet?
I'm getting bored out here.
[NAMI] No! And stop peeping!
Anyway, we're leaving
this place at sunset.
[USOPP] At night?
But what about the zombies?
[NAMI] What, you think
we're safe in the mansion?
Also, what's that noise?
Are you keeping watch?
[USOPP] Um. Uh-oh.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Nami's in a Major Pinch!
The Zombie Mansion
and the Invisible Man!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!