[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[NARRATOR]
In the land of oases,
a dry cloud of sand blankets
the people with anguish.
Some cling to hope, and
others seek to destroy it.
As their paths cross,
they mark an era in
the country's history
that will forever be
overshadowed by sadness.
[NARRATOR] At the southeastern
gate of Alubarna,
Usopp and Chopper faced
the mole‐woman,
Miss Merry Christmas,
and clean‐up batter Mr. 4
in a life or death battle.
Combining their skills,
Usopp and Chopper were finally
able to defeat the pair.
Meanwhile, Sanji and
Mr. 2, Bon Clay,
were engaged in a vicious
foot‐to‐foot struggle.
Sanji found himself
in great danger
from the Clone‐Clone
Montage put on by Mr. 2.
[chuckles]
Ah! Oh, how cute!
[LUFFY]
"Transformed into Nami!
Bon Clay's Rapid‐Fire
Ballet Kenpo!"
[NAMI laughs]
[NAMI]
You're just what they mean
when they say "he's
nothing but talk."
I bet you don't have enough
strength left to get up!
[SANJI]
Don't think for a second
that I'm just gonna
lie down and give up!
You may look like
Nami on the outside,
but you're still the same
idiot on the inside!
You bastard! I'll show you.
[screams]
I'm gonna...
[laughing]
[SANJI]
I can't do it! She's too cute!
Oh, no! This desert air
is so stifling!
It just makes me wanna
rip all my clothes off!
Ah! I'll help you!
[NAMI]
Ballet Chop!
Ow! My eye!
Lovesick fool!
Kick Point!
[laughing]
So! Nothin' but talk, are ya?
I'll show you talk.
[BON CLAY]
Hm?
[chuckles]
Nobody messes with me!
Now, Mascara... Boomerang!
[screams]
Eat this!
Please, don't kick me!
[gasps] Oh, no!
Why?
The "eyes" have it!
[laughs]
Well, this has been a treat,
but alas! I must be off.
Duty calls, and I've got
a princess to kill!
I really hate to rush things,
but I'm gonna have to
finish you off now!
Stand right there, lover boy,
and I'll make this quick!
Ha!
Round and round and round
I go, and when I stop...
[laughing]
Wait a minute, did you just say
we're supposed to blow
up the royal palace?
I know that it sounds crazy,
but those are the orders
that just came down
from high command!
[GUARD C] We've been ordered
to blow up the palace!
[GUARD D]
They can't be serious!
[GUARD E]
That palace is 4000 years old!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[CHAKA]
Nothing I can say
can express my sorrow
at all of this.
It's all right. I know.
You really had no choice when
it comes right down to it;
it was your duty to
intercept the rebel army.
In spite of what
happened to Igaram,
you've done well by managing
to keep the rebellion in check
for the last two years.
But... I wasn't wrong.
I've met some true friends who
are going to save Alabasta.
You guys go on ahead!
Don't worry about me!
Make sure you deliver
Vivi home! Safe and sound!
You have to promise me!
Crocodile will fail.
Luffy will win.
It's that simple.
The moment that the rebel
army started running,
this land's final hour was set.
Once the royal army and
the rebel army meet,
this country, the Kingdom of
Alabasta, will be gone forever.
If you are truly
the one and only hope
for preventing that tragedy,
then you must survive,
no matter what.
So, from this moment forward,
what happens to Luffy,
or any of us for that matter,
isn't the least bit important!
[VIVI] All of you, who were
willing to give your lives,
how are you faring now?
[CHAKA]
Princess Vivi.
In the two years since
we've seen each other,
you've grown into a
beautiful young woman.
Once this war is behind us all,
I'd like very much to
hold a grand banquet
to honor your pirate friends.
Chaka.
Okay, then give me food.
After I beat up Crocodile,
give me food.
I'll eat till I explode!
[VIVI]
Yes. I believe in you, Luffy.
You must be all right. You
must've defeated Crocodile.
[door opens]
My lord Chaka!
Yes, report.
Is it really true that they're
gonna blow up the royal palace?
The soldiers are getting
explosives ready.
Surely this must be a mistake!
There's no mistake, gentlemen.
That order was given by me.
[BOTH gasp] Princess Vivi!
Use every ounce of explosives
that you can lay your hands on.
The only way to stop
this senseless fighting,
and to save the lives of
the people of Alabasta,
is to blow up the royal palace.
[CHOPPER]
Hang in there, Usopp.
It's only a flesh wound,
nothing serious!
It's just a shattered femur,
no problem at all!
It's true you've busted
your nose, your humeri,
and both your clavicles,
but you only lost a
little bit more blood
than is normally fatal
for a man your size!
Your blood pressure is slightly
better than a zombie's,
but otherwise you're
in really great shape!
[USOPP]
Right now, I feel fantastic.
I see a beautiful
field of flowers.
[CHOPPER] Ah! You don't
mean Heaven, do you?
Can you see Heaven?
[USOPP chuckles]
No matter how great
a pirate you may be,
in the end, no one can escape
death's cold embrace.
No, don't die, Usopp!
Keep fighting! Don't give up!
Au revoir, Chopper.
I leave all my vast treasure
hoard to you, little friend.
All 15 gold and silver pieces.
Become a good doctor.
Usopp, no!
Open your eyes!
You can't die yet!
I have to apologize to you
for something first! Please!
This sticky bun.
This is the sticky bun
that you wanted
and I hid to have
all for myself.
If I'd known you were gonna die,
I would've saved half for you.
Honest, I would've.
Now I'll have to eat
the whole thing,
but I know I'm not
gonna enjoy it.
My bun.
My precious!
That brainless little fool,
where did she manage to
lose herself this time?
This is why I told her to pipe
down and hide, but no!
She has to go running
off on her own
and make me waste time
looking for her.
Stupid Nami!
[NAMI]
That's it! I can't run anymore!
I'll have to fight!
[NAMI]
Like hell!
[MR. 1]
This is taking too long.
So hasty.
[screams]
Zoro!
That stone column just
split into pieces!
[ZORO]
It didn't split.
It was sliced.
Only a swordsman could've
done something like that.
That's right.
[ZORO]
You cut it, didn't you?
With those arms, huh?
You've got a rather
unusual body, don't you?
[MR. 1]
You noticed.
I ate the Dice Dice Fruit,
making blades of my entire body.
You're him.
The swordsman who
supposedly cut down
a hundred men at Whiskey Peak.
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
He's also the pirate
who turned down an invitation
to join Baroque Works
several years ago at East Blue,
and cut down our
Mr. 7 at the time.
That was you too?
Ha! That's a story
that takes me back.
That little misunderstanding
was your Mr. 7's fault
for not accepting the
terms I offered him.
As I remember it, I made a
very generous proposition.
I said, "Sure, I'll join, as
long as you make me your boss."
[chuckles]
You're quite a
comedian, aren't you?
Instead of meeting my terms,
he rather rudely took
a slash at me,
so naturally, I put
him in his place.
Now would you like
to invite me too?
'Cause right now, you guys
look so ridiculous,
I wouldn't even accept the job.
[MR. 1 yells]
You think you can make
a fool out of me?
You, some swordsman from
an upstart pirate crew?
[ZORO] Maybe I am, but what
do you think you guys are?
Puppets with no
will of your own
being manipulated by Crocodile
into building his fake utopia.
Or maybe you're all just
little tin soldiers.
All shine and no steel.
Miss Doublefinger.
I know, I know, you want to
eliminate him, don't you?
You do as you please.
I'll take care of the girl.
Uh! Nami, be careful‐‐
Okay... she's gone.
[MR. 1 growling]
[NAMI]
Twirling, twirling!
A 320,000‐spin finishing
Grand Fouette!
What's this?
[BON CLAY]
Ballet Kenpo!
Memoirs of a Summer's Day!
I see your weakness.
There's a flaw in your attack.
[BON CLAY]
Memoirs of a Summer's Day!
[SANJI]
Joue Shoot!
Sure enough, I was right.
You've seen through it,
you say? Through what?
What part of my ability could a
philistine like you appreciate,
let alone see through?
Only this.
That you can't use your
precious Ballet Kenpo
while you're assuming
Nami's form.
[grunts]
It's true, I can't bring
myself to attack you
while you look like Nami,
but it's pretty clear you have
to return to your normal self
before you try to attack me.
And it happens whenever
I see you touch your cheek
with your left hand.
[BON CLAY laughing]
Eh? What? I can't hear you!
Hey! I'm right, aren't I?
Well‐‐ Well, so what
if you are right, pal?
All right, all right.
It's only with this magnificent
godlike physique
that I've patiently developed,
putting in day after day of
rigorous and brutal lessons,
that I am able to perform
my Ballet Kenpo.
But so what?
You're still plenty black and
blue, aren't you, Mr. Big Talk?
Now, take a look at
the prima of Ballet Kenpo!
I'll say this much about it,
then you're dead.
The one on your left is the pen
and on your right is the cob.
[SANJI]
Who cares?
[laughs]
Whether you see through it
or not doesn't matter!
Now! Prepare to die!
Behold the power of
my Ballet Kenpo!
Bombardier!
[SANJI] What? He punched
a hole in the wall!
[laughing]
You dodged it! Smart thinking!
At the end of their bent
necks are steel beaks!
[SANJI] He didn't even crack
the plaster around the hole!
True power, when
compressed and focused
into a single point of contact,
will not destroy
anything needlessly.
It might be best if you were to
try thinking of one of my kicks
like a shot from a
high‐powered rifle.
Of course, in this case,
the bullets are of a
drastically higher caliber.
I'm going to perforate you!
Un!
Deux!
Collier.
No good!
[SANJI] Damn! His reach
is longer than mine!
[laughing]
Looks like the fight is over!
I'm flying like a swan!
Ballet Kenpo!
Memoirs of a Winter Sky!
[SANJI]
But the longer his reach is,
the longer it takes
him to recover.
If I can avoid his kick,
I'll have that much
more time to attack.
[BON CLAY]
Say good‐bye!
[laughs]
And just what do you think
you're gonna do now, lover boy?
Hey, something's stuck
to your left cheek.
Huh? Really?
Basses... Cote!
[SANJI]
Longe!
Tendron!
[growls]
Flanchet!
Un!
[groans]
[chuckles]
Deux!
‐‐[BON CLAY] Ora!
‐‐[SANJI] Quasi!
[BOTH yell]
‐‐[SANJI] Tendron! Quasi!
‐‐[BON CLAY] Un! Deux! Ora!
‐‐Collier! Flanchet! Cuisseau!
‐‐Un! Deux! Krah! Un!
‐‐Jarret! Tendron! Quasi!
[SANJI]
Collier!
[yells]
‐‐[SANJI] Jarret! Collier!
‐‐[BON CLAY] Un! Deux! Ora!
‐‐Quasi! Flanchet! Gigot!
‐‐Un! Deux! Krah!
‐‐Selle! Queue! Jarret!
‐‐Collier! Quasi! Flanchet!
‐‐Un! Deux! Ora!
[BON CLAY]
Un! Deux! Ora! Un! Krah!
[BOTH yell]
[BON CLAY]
Bombardier Arabesque!
[screaming]
I... I give up.
You've gotta be kidding.
You mean you're still alive?
What's the matter?
All you have to do is
turn into Nami again
and I won't be able
to finish you off.
[BON CLAY]
Nonsense.
I can't move, with
the shape I'm in.
There's no point trying to
avoid the outcome of this.
I congratulate you.
Now kill me.
You may as well. Baroque
Works will do it anyway.
Don't just stand there,
get it over with.
Come on, finish me.
[gasps]
It was a good fight,
and beyond that,
we don't need anymore
words, do we?
[BON CLAY chuckles]
[BON CLAY]
This is, without question,
the deep respect that arises
between rival, but I won't cry!
[SANJI]
Bye now!
Oh, and I'm takin' back our
sharpshooter's goggles.
[BON CLAY groans]
[BON CLAY]
Well, he did finish me.
[SANJI grumbles]
I think I cracked a
couple of my bones again.
Uh, everything is ready
as you ordered, Princess!
[GUARD H]
Everything is set here, too!
[VIVI] This castle has been
a part of Alabasta's history
for 4,000 years.
‐‐[VIVI laughing]
‐‐[KAROO squawking]
[VIVI] It's been a great
source of pride to me.
[VIVI] But if we destroy
the royal palace,
the people will have to stop
fighting with each other
and pay attention!
I'll finally be able to
tell everyone the truth
about this horrible conspiracy
in my own words!
All right, light your fuses!
[gasps]
[yells]
[screams]
What is this?
[VIVI]
You okay?
It... was him.
[CROCODILE]
We can't have this.
That was rather treacherous
on your part, wasn't it?
Huh, Miss Wednesday?
After all, my dear, this is
about to be my house.
No, I'll never let you!
[gasps]
[CHAKA]
Your Majesty!
[VIVI]
Uh! Father!
This is lovely. To
have a palace like this.
[CROCODILE laughs]
It's a marvelous place
to look down
on all the filth
and rabble below.
Where‐Where is Luffy?
Who's that?
Oh, you mean Straw Hat?
That miserable young rookie?
My dear, he's dead.
[CROCODILE laughing]
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[ZORO]
I hope Nami got away.
She hasn't got much of a chance
against someone like that!
[USOPP] Nami, it looks like it's
time to finally use it, huh?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
I've found you, girl.
[USOPP]
Your new weapon. Ugh...
[CHOPPER]
Usopp, stay with me!
[NAMI]
Take this, Miss Doublefinger!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Nami's Cyclone Advisory!
Clima Takt Burst!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!