[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[ZORO grunting]
Take aim and fire!
[gasps]
[ZORO grunts]
[LUFFY laughs]
[ZORO gasps]
[COBY]
Luffy, no!
[MORGAN]
Straw Hat!
[MARINES gasping, murmuring]
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
Hah!
[MARINES screaming]
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY] That won't work on me!
I told ya I was strong!
Wha‐‐? You wanna tell me
just who the hell you are?!
[LUFFY laughs]
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
And I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates.
[LUFFY]
"Morgan versus Luffy!
Who's the Mysterious
Pretty Girl?"
[ZORO] You're gonna be
King of the Pirates?
Right...
You must be completely
outta you rubbery mind.
You have any idea
what that means?
King of the Pirates means
King of the Pirates.
How could it mean
anything other than that?
[MARINES]
Huh? Eh?
Yeah, when he first
told me, it was shocking,
but he's completely serious.
That's how he is, I suppose.
'Cause he actually seems
to have every intention
of becoming King of the Pirates,
and obtaining the world's
ultimate treasure,
the One Piece.
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
Here's what I promised you.
There's three.
I couldn't tell which was yours,
so I just took all of them.
All of them belong to me.
I use Santoryu, the
Three‐Swords Style.
[LUFFY]
Hmm.
Take 'em already!
Just know that if
you fight with me now,
you'll be a
government‐defying villian.
So it's either that...
...or you're left out here,
and killed by the
marines execution‐style.
What are you, the
son of the devil?
It doesn't matter. 'Cause if
I don't choose your side,
I'll just end up
dead on these sticks.
So let's do it.
[laughs]
So you're finally
gonna join my crew!
This is the best thing ever!
‐‐[LUFFY laughs]
‐‐Would you quit
‐‐All right!
‐‐celebrating already
and get these ropes off me?!
What the‐‐?
What is he?
Bullets just bounced
right off him!
Straw Hat's no ordinary
human like the rest of us.
He must have eaten one
of those Devil Fruits
that we've heard all
those rumors about.
Devil Fruit?
The hidden treasure of the sea.
[MORGAN]
The Devil Fruits.
Those who eat them are said
to gain extraordinary,
otherworldly abilities.
[MORGAN]
The power to breathe fire.
The power to cause tsunamis.
Rumors persist that there are
many types of these fruits,
but next to nothing
is known about them.
It is said that
the secrets to them
lie somewhere in the Grand Line.
And there's no
question about it.
The Straw Hat has just
showed us his Devil Power.
[COBY]
Come on! Hurry!
They... got... these...
things... on here tight!
Come on! Quit screwin' around!
It doesn't matter what
abilities they have,
all who oppose me are executed!
If the guns won't work, we chop!
[MARINES yelling]
[COBY screaming]
[LUFFY]
That's funny.
The knots got tighter,
instead of looser.
Gimme one of my
damn swords, now!
[COBY screams]
Luffy look!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
‐‐[MARINES yelling]
‐‐[COBY screams]
[swords clang]
[MARINES grunting]
Roronoa Zoro.
‐‐[COBY gasps]
‐‐Wow! That's so cool!
[BOTH gasping]
Make one move and you die.
[BOTH sobbing]
He's scary!
[ZORO] Today I officially
become a criminal,
having fought the Marines.
So, I'll become a pirate.
That, I can promise you.
But I want you to know one
thing, while I'm with you,
the only thing I dedicate myself
to is fulfilling my ambition.
[LUFFY]
Which is?
To be nothing less than the
world's greatest swordsman.
If somewhere along the way
I have to give that up,
then I want you to
accept responsibility.
After which you get
to apologize to me.
The world's greatest swordsman.
Sounds pretty good.
The King of the Pirates
wouldn't have any less
than the best on his crew.
Big talker.
From this point on, no matter
if I'm a criminal or not,
I will spread the name
Zoro throughout the world!
What're you standing
there frozen for?!
I want you to kill all
three of them right now!
[MARINES whimpering]
You might wanna duck.
[ZORO gasps]
Gum Gum...
Whip!
[MORGAN gasping]
Yes!
You knocked 'em all down!
Wanna tell me what you are?
I'm just a guy who ate
the Gum‐Gum Fruit.
What's the Gum‐Gum Fruit?
A rubber person?
It looks like he does have
the Devil Fruit powers.
Captain, we don't stand
a chance against them.
Yeah, just look at them!
They're insane!
We couldn't even take
on Zoro by himself!
This is a direct order.
Every marine that
just spouted weakness,
pull your gun out,
and shoot yourself.
I can't do anything
with weak soldiers!
What babies.
This'll be easy.
[COBY]
Luffy!
Bring those Marines
crumbling to their knees!
[MORGAN grunts]
[LUFFY growls]
‐‐[LUFFY yells]
‐‐[MORGAN groans]
[MORGAN]
Rankless, low‐life bums!
You have no right
to defy my superiority!
I am Marine Captain
"Axe‐Hand" Morgan!
And I'm Luffy.
Nice to meetcha.
[MORGAN yells]
‐‐[LUFFY grunts]
‐‐[MORGAN yells]
[COBY screams]
[LUFFY grunts]
[MORGAN groans]
Look. He's been hit!
You runt...
[LUFFY grunts]
[MORGAN growls]
Now, die!
[LUFFY]
I don't think so!
‐‐[LUFFY grunts]
‐‐[MORGAN groans]
The captain's getting
pummeled out there.
It's embarrassing.
Call yourself a Marine.
But you destroyed my
friend Coby's dream.
[MORGAN groans]
‐‐[LUFFY growls]
‐‐Straw Hat!
Stop right there!
Look at what I got!
‐‐[LUFFY grunts]
‐‐[MORGAN groans]
[HELMEPPO]
Are ya stupid or something?!
I said stop!
If you would pay
attention to me,
I have a hostage here
you might wanna look at!
Helmeppo's crazy.
Hey.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
If you value your squatty
little friend's life,
you won't move a muscle!
I'm serious! One move and
I'll shoot him! I swear!
[COBY whimpers]
[whimpers]
[LUFFY laughs]
[gasps]
Luffy, listen!
Don't let anything that happens
to me stop you, no matter what!
Even if I die!
Of course. You got it.
You hear that, you big idiot?
Coby is ready to
die by your hand.
Don't you move!
I said don't move or I'll shoot!
I swear it!
Luffy!
‐‐[COBY] Behind you!
‐‐[LUFFY] Gum Gum...
[MORGAN]
Time's up!
For I am fearless Marine
Captain "Axe‐Hand" Morgan!
Daddy, hurry up
and kill him already!
[LUFFY]
Pistol!
[HELMEPPO screams]
Nice one.
[MORGAN groans]
Thank you.
I'm Just doing my job, Captain.
[LUFFY laughs]
[COBY whimpering]
[MARINE A]
Captain Morgan's been beaten.
[MARINE E]
Unbelievable!
[MARINE C]
Those guys are unreal!
If there's anyone else
who wants to step forward
to fight us, then do it now.
[MARINES gasping, murmuring]
[MARINES cheering]
[MARINE B]
We're free!
[MARINE F]
Finally!
[MARINE H]
Morgan's reign is over!
[MARINE I]
It's really happening!
[MARINE G]
Glorious day!
That's weird...
Looks like they're all happy
that their captain was beaten.
They must've been afraid of him
for a long time
before we showed up.
[ZORO groans]
[LUFFY, COBY gasp]
[COBY]
Zoro! Are you okay?!
What's wrong?!
I'm just...
...hungry.
[GIRL]
Sorry, you two.
You just have to suck
it up for a while.
[MARINES muttering]
[GIRL] I can't find
this sucker anywhere.
Hmm.
[gasps]
[GIRL grunting]
[GIRL]
That's it!
A maritime chart
of the Grand Line.
I knew they were hiding it.
[GIRL]
This isn't the map.
What mark is that?
So, it's Buggy.
Also known on the seas...
as Buggy the Immortal.
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[ZORO]
Whew! I am stuffed!
[ZORO sighs]
Having not eaten
for three weeks,
I was ready to gnaw
through my boot straps.
[GROUP laughs]
I can't believe you're finished.
Lightweight.
How the hell can you
have a bigger appetite
than a guy who hasn't
eaten in weeks?
[LUFFY] It just tastes too
good, I guess. Right, Coby?
Uh, yeah, It's great.
Thanks for fixing it for us.
My pleasure.
After all, you guys
did save the town.
You're the most amazing
man I've ever met!
Yeah, I am, I know.
I'll be more amazing...
...when I'm King of the Pirates,
and I have the One Piece.
Oh, and the best
crew on the seas.
So.
How many others
have you gathered
for your crew besides me?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
You told me that you
were in the middle
of gathering together
the crew for your ship.
And if you're gonna be
King of the Pirates,
I gotta assume you already
have some waiting in the wings.
[LUFFY]
Nope, just you.
[gasps]
Just...?
Yep. It's just us.
So you and I are what amounts
to an entire pirate crew?
[LUFFY]
What's wrong with that?
We're a couple of strong guys!
Okay...
But please tell me
you have a ship.
[LUFFY]
Sure do. It's right there.
You're kidding.
Nope. But we'll have an
enormous one before long.
Just you wait and see!
[laughing]
And how's that?
With a great big
pirate flag on top.
[LUFFY laughing]
I can't wait!
I think Luffy was born
without that part of the brain
that allows the rest of us to
plan out what we have to do.
I can't believe I let
myself get suckered
into having him as my captain.
Hey! We'll have a ton more
crewmembers in no time.
[RIKA]
Luffy?
Where are you and your
crew planning on traveling
when you leave here?
You mean it's not obvious?
We're headed straight
for the Grand Line.
No! Have you completely
lost your mind?!
You have two crew members!
There's no way you're equipped
to handle the Grand Line, Luffy!
I've heard about it,
but I never knew it was
such an awful place.
It's worse than you think.
You know that this world
has two oceans, I'm sure.
There is an enormous landmass
that cuts across both of them.
This is called the Red Line.
Legend tells of a town that sits
dead center on the Red Line.
The Grand Line is said
to cut through this town
at a right angle and
stretch all the way
around the rest of the world.
The story goes on to say
that Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
had once obtained everything
this world had to offer.
Before he died, he said
that he left the great One Piece
treasure at this location.
Ever since, pirates have
set sail for the Grand Line.
Today the place is
nothing but a battlefield,
and some even call it
the pirate graveyard.
I heard stories about it
from people passing through.
The customers say that no one
who has ever entered
the Grand Line
comes out of
that place alive.
Which is really too bad,
'cause that's where the
One Piece is said to be,
and that's exactly
where we're going.
I guess we have to live with it.
No! You can't agree!
[ZORO] What do you care, you're
not going with us are you?
No... But I still worry...
Is it so wrong to care
about the two of you?
Luffy and I haven't known each
other for years or anything,
but I'd still consider
him a friend.
Wouldn't you say?
Of course.
We may have to part ways but...
...we'll always be friends.
[gasps]
[COBY] When I was a just little
kid, I never had any friends,
much less anyone who would
bother fighting on my behalf.
So I always tried my hardest
never to fight for anything.
[COBY] But the two of you
have taught me a lesson
I could never learn on my own:
How to live for
what I believe in!
So I've decided to make my
one childhood dream a reality,
and I'm going to
join the Marines!
[ZORO] Then don't you think
you should be a little more
concerned with your situation?
[gasps]
I mean, you did spend two
years on Alvida's pirate ship,
even if you were nothing
but her cabin boy.
[COBY]
Uhh...
The Marines' information
gathering is top‐notch.
They'll find out about
your time with Alvida,
and you'll never join.
I... never thought of that...
[LIEUTENANT]
Hey! You there.
[COBY, RIKA gasp]
We heard that you fellas
are actually pirates.
Is this rumor true?
Right, and I just added the
first member to my crew.
So pretty much the whole
thing just became official.
We appreciate everything you
did to save our town from
that horrible tyrant who
terrorized us all for so long.
However, now that we know that
you're pirates, as Marines,
we cannot sit idly by and watch
you go about your business.
Therefore, you and your crew
will need to leave
this town immediately.
But out of respect for
what you've done,
we will not report
you to headquarters.
Are you crazy?
How do you find the
nerve to talk like that?!
[MAN B]
Before these pirates came along,
you guys were as scared
of Morgan as we were.
[WOMAN A] Without them,
we'd still be under his reign.
We owe them our lives!
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
Well, time to go!
Thanks for all
of the food, lady.
Hey, wait a second.
You're leaving already?
Yeah.
[COBY whimpers]
[LIEUTENANT] Aren't you
part of the crew, as well?
[COBY gasps]
Uh, well, I... uh... I...
[LIEUTENANT]
Hold it!
Is he with you or what?
What I can tell you
is what he's been busy
doing up to this point.
[COBY]
Luffy! You wouldn't!
Yeah, there was this
fantastically fat pirate lady.
I think her name was Alvida.
Luffy.
[COBY] If they find out
I ran with a pirate crew,
I'll never join the Marines.
She carried around this
huge iron club and, boy,
she was the nastiest looking
woman I've ever seen.
For two years, this wimpy kid
was her own private cabin boy.
[COBY]
Please stop!
You can't do this!
Luffy, no!
[COBY yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[MARINES gasp]
[ZORO]
Hm.
[COBY whimpers]
[gasps]
[LUFFY chuckles]
Now that was a dumb move.
[COBY, LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Bastard!
Damn you!
Get out of here now!
We can't have you pirates
ripping up this town any more
than you already
have, you hear me?!
[ZORO]
Enough.
You made your point.
Now let him fall to the ground.
[COBY groans]
[COBY panting]
It's obvious you're not
crewmates so stop badgering
the poor kid and take your leave
of our town this instant!
[LUFFY]
Heh.
[COBY]
Huh?
That was on purpose?
Luffy did that
just to help me out.
[COBY] He worked me
up and got me so mad
that I'd hit him and look
like I wasn't on his side.
[COBY] Even at the very
end of our journey together,
I wound up continuing
to rely on him.
I couldn't do
anything for myself.
Nothing's changed
for me at all.
[COBY]
I am such an idiot!
‐‐[COBY] Sir!
‐‐[LIEUTENANT] Hm?
Please, sir.
Please, you have to let
me join the Marines.
I'll clean and scrub and do any
chores that you'd like me to.
I'll do anything
to become a Marine.
[LIEUTENANT]
Hm.
Lieutenant. I can't say
I fully trust this kid.
I wouldn't be against the idea
if there weren't clear cases
of certain Marines
actually being pirate spies.
I say, we should conduct
a background check first.
No matter what you say, I am a
man who will become a Marine!
[reaction missing]
[LIEUTENANT] I can't tell
you how many of our comrades
have been killed by
pirates over the years.
This is a big step
you're taking.
So...
[LIEUTENANT]
Permission to join granted.
Sir!
[GIRL]
Hmph.
[ZORO] That was a thin act
you put on back there.
I wouldn't be surprised if
they see right through it.
[LUFFY laughs]
Coby should be able
to handle the rest on his own.
I have faith in him.
[ZORO] It is a fitting
way to leave this place,
unable to turn back 'cause
everyone here hates us now.
Very pirate‐like.
[laughs]
Yeah. It sure is.
‐‐[COBY] Luffy!
‐‐[LUFFY] Huh?
I can never thank you enough.
You've done more for me
than anyone ever has!
I've never heard of a Marine
thanking a pirate before.
That's one for
the history books.
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
We'll meet again, Coby!
Someday!
Bye, Luffy.
Hope to see you again someday!
All hands, salute!
[COBY gasps]
See ya!
[LIEUTENANT] That's a good
friend you have there.
[COBY gasps]
Yeah!
[LIEUTENANT]
Men!
Seeing as our current salute
is in violation of Marine law,
we will all go without
food for three days!
Do we all understand this?!
[MARINES, COBY]
Yes, sir!
[COBY] I know that we'll
meet again someday.
Deep inside, I feel it as much
as I've ever felt anything.
even if we are divided
as pirates and Marines,
I still look
forward to that day.
At last, our pirate
crew finally sets sail!
I got the feeling some
interesting adventures
are waiting for us.
[LUFFY laughs]
I'll be King of the
Pirates. I know it.
You seem more than obsessed
with this King of the
Pirates business.
Is there some kinda
story behind it?
Or any kind of reason at all?
[LUFFY]
No. No reason.
It's just...
Just what?
I promised someone...
a while back...
[LUFFY] I swore that
I would gather a crew,
find the world's
greatest treasure,
and become King of the Pirates.
And this straw hat
knows the whole story.
I see.
Now! Let's go!
It's time for us to
set our heading...
...for the Grand Line!
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[ZORO]
You're kidding.
You don't even know how
to navigate correctly?
[LUFFY]
Well, do you?
[ZORO]
No!
[LUFFY] Ah! Would you
stop rocking the boat?!
You'll knock my hat off!
[ZORO] Is that straw hat
that important to you?
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
It's my treasure,
and I have to return it to him
after I'm King of the Pirates.
[ZORO]
Who's him?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Luffy's Past!
Enter Red‐Haired Shanks!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!