Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison, Impel Down.
[MAGELLAN] Consider this
your punishment, child.
There's no way to neutralize
the amount of poison
your body has absorbed.
[BON CLAY screams]
[LUFFY] What do you think
you're doing to my friend, Bon?
Leave him...
...alone!
[NARRATOR] After fighting
off the Army Wolves,
Luffy and Bon Clay
lost consciousness,
and were carried away
by the mysterious Inazuma.
When Bon awoke, he found
himself in a most queer place.
[IVANKOV]
I bid you welcome.
To Impel Down
Level 5.5, bitches!
A secret garden
for all y'all prisoners! Ahh!
This is New Kama Land!
[ALL]
Hee-haw!
[LUFFY]
"Luffy's Treatment Begins.
Iva's Miraculous Power!"
--[CROWD cheering]
--[IVANKOV] Yeah, work it.
Yeah, work it down low. Work.
[CROWD cheering]
[IVANKOV]
Left side, right side, wow!
Front side, back side, wow!
Wild side all night, wow!
Aahh...
[BOTH chuckling]
[PATRON B]
Move it, sister!
I said, Hee-haw!
[IVANKOV]
Hee-haw!
[BON CLAY]
It's him.
Hee! Haaa...
[BON CLAY]
Iva?!
...aaw!
[CROWD cheering, applauding]
[IVANKOV] I guess I got
a little too excited
dancing and cutting loose.
I-I'm getting... dizzy...
[PATRON C]
Iva, are you all right?
[IVANKOV]
I think I'm gonna collapse now.
Then again, maybe I won't! Ha!
[PATRON D]
You were joking?
[PATRON E]
You sure fooled me!
Unless I'm mistaken, you're Iva,
the Miracle Worker, aren't you?
Oh, goodness me!
So, you've heard about
little old moi, have you?
Hey, watch your mouth!
Show some respect
when you're talk to Iva!
He's royalty, pal!
You gotta bow down before
the queen of New Kama!
[CROWD]
Hail, King Iva! Hail, King Iva!
Hush, now, my little candies!
I appreciate the admiration,
but don't sweat the small stuff.
I'm not worried about
silly things like labels.
People can call me
whatever they like.
They can even call me "Dookie."
Never call me "Dookie"!
[PATRON F]
Then why did you say it?
[PATRON G]
You got me again!
Is this really Iva,
the Miracle Worker?
The same one that I've worshiped
from afar for oh so many years?
Never call me "Dookie"! Ha-ha!
Emporio Ivankov!
[CROWD gasping]
[BON CLAY]
Huh?
[panting]
[PRISONER]
I've been looking for you!
You were the Queen of Kama
Bakka Kingdom, weren't you?
About 15 years ago, my father,
who was the king of my homeland,
visited that country
of yours and then he--
[growls]
He came back to us as a queen!
[IVANKOV]
Ahh!
[BOTH laughing]
Do you have any idea
how ashamed I was?
His family and
his country were ruined!
I fell from my princely status
to nothing but a lowly pirate!
But all the days
I spent suffering
in this living hell
are worth it
if I get one shot at the monster
who destroyed my life!
[IVANKOV whimpering]
[IVANKOV]
No! Please!
Don't do it! Where did you
even get that thing?
Oh, no! Don't point that at me!
Have mercy! I'm fragile!
If you shoot me
with that, I'll die!
You'll kill me!
You can't kill me!
[PATRON H]
You're such a character!
[PATRON I]
You were pulling our legs!
[growling]
[IVANKOV]
Uhh?
Nuh-uh-uh!
Death Wink!
[gasps]
[PRISONER yelps]
[groaning]
Hell yeah! That's how
Iva bats an eye, girl!
How 'bout some Death Wink?
Ah! With just a wink he was
able to turn back that bullet?
[screaming]
Emporio Female Hormone!
[groaning]
[IVANKOV chuckling]
What was that?
[PRISONER yelping]
Oh no! What did you do to me?
You're throwing a fit
because your father wanted
to become a woman?
Tell me: What's wrong with that?
[PRISONER]
No, no, no! Stop it!
You wouldn't dare!
[IVANKOV]
Two mothers and one son?
Two fathers and one daughter?
What's wrong with that?
You're all family!
[PRISONER]
Anything but this!
Please, no!
[screaming]
[BON CLAY]
What?!
[CROWD cheers]
[PRISONER]
My body...
[PATRON K]
Way to go!
[laughing]
You could become a woman
or become a man. Hee-haw!
Or maybe you could be both!
You should be able
to decide for yourself!
Right?
[IVANKOV]
Hee-haw!
That which you call gender
is a label!
It's nothing but a border!
I have no need for it.
No, everyone here is beyond it!
Hee-haw! We've all crossed over
that silly border,
which means you're looking
at the new human race!
New Kama!
[IVANKOV]
This is the garden of freedom!
New Kama Land! Hee-haw!
[CROWD]
Iva rules! Iva rules! Iva rules!
Iva rules! Iva rules!
He turned that guy into a woman!
This is the real deal!
He truly is a Miracle Worker!
[IVANKOV chuckling]
I bid you welcome.
Perhaps, you'd like
to join in on the fun now?
Hee-haw!
[whimpering]
[PRISONER screaming]
[PRISONER]
This is so humiliating!
[PRISONER crying]
Hee-haw!
The poor thing's embarrassed!
She's got a long way to go
before becoming
a proper citizen of New Kama.
[BON CLAY panting]
[IVANKOV]
Huh?
What is it, Bon Boy?
It's an honor to meet you, Iva!
I never stopped believing
you were still alive!
I'm so glad I found you!
You have no idea!
If you would hear it,
I have a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
My dear friend
was poisoned by Magellan!
Can you please save his life?
No antidote can help him!
He's lying there dying and
there's nothing I can do!
Please, I'm begging you!
I'll give you my life!
I assume you're talking
about Straw Hat Boy?
[BON CLAY crying]
[IVANKOV]
Bon Boy.
[BON CLAY]
Hmm?
[IVANKOV]
Did you stop to wonder
why we treated your injuries
in the first place?
To be quite honest,
I didn't notice.
We're all just
prisoners down here.
We don't have the means
to simply take in
and care for anyone
that we happen to find injured.
We're not nearly so kind.
[IVANKOV] You see,
I took you in and treated you
because your friend
begged me to do it.
[gasps] Straw Boy did what?
[LUFFY groaning]
[IVANKOV] We've been watching
you boys on the monitor,
and I gotta say, I'm impressed.
I can't tell if you're lucky
or just plain crazy.
Either way, congratulations
on making it this far,
for all the good it does you.
[LUFFY]
Bon... Bon...
He was trying...
to help me and...
...got bitten by those wolves...
Please, take care of him!
[IVANKOV grunts]
[LUFFY] He's my friend!
I can't let him die!
That's not something
just anyone would say.
Not when they're on
the verge of death.
I didn't know the flower
of friendship could bloom
in a hellhole like this.
But I do know that
if I didn't help him,
I'd be no better than
a demon in human guise.
Straw Boy...
[IVANKOV] Anyhow,
I already started treatment
on your buddy Straw Boy
about ten hours ago.
You did?
[LUFFY screaming]
[screaming continues]
[IVANKOV]
But it's gonna be rough.
[BUGGY]
I bet the kids out there
are wondering
what these things are!
[ARMY WOLVES barking]
[MR. 3] They're what you call
old-fashioned bamboo stilts!
[ARMY WOLVES barking]
[BOTH] You gotta try them
sometime! They're fun!
[MR. 3]
Actually, I made these with wax.
So, technically, they should be
called old-fashioned wax stilts,
or maybe
new-fashioned wax stilts!
[ARMY WOLVES barking]
How much longer
can these beasts keep this up?
Go on now, shoo! Shoo!
Like that's gonna stop them!
We've gotta get off this floor
or we're never going
to lose these things!
Just keep running! Move! Move!
[MR. 3] Where's the exit?
Somebody? Anybody?
[MR. 3 yelps]
[LUFFY screaming]
[screaming continues]
That sounds awful!
What's going on in there?!
You call this healing?!
[IVANKOV] He's been screaming
like this the entire duration
of his treatment, but I assure
you that's part of the process.
We've locked him
away for safety.
This'll last another two days.
[BON CLAY]
Huh?
[LUFFY panting]
Ten years of your life.
That's what it's
going to cost you,
if I administer this treatment.
It's a high price,
but that poison is serious,
Straw Hat Boy.
Fine by me.
Just so we're clear,
this is a high-risk treatment
and there's no guarantee
that it'll save your life.
In your current condition,
you have absolutely
no chance of survival.
The best I can do for you
through this process
is increase that chance
to two or three percent.
What you face right now
is a battle the likes of which
you have never fought before.
You must temper that will
of yours to emerge victorious.
If the poison wins,
you will most assuredly die.
But, if your spirit wins,
you walk away.
It's as simple as that!
All right, then. I wish you
a pleasant journey.
To the valley of death, that is!
Emporio Healing Hormone!
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
[BON CLAY]
Are you pulling my tail?
Straw Boy has been wailing in
agony like that for ten hours?
Spirit and hormones.
These are the vital forces
of the human body.
Combined, the two bring forth
a tremendous healing potential.
[LUFFY screaming]
[IVANKOV] I have drawn out
his latent immunity
and changed his body
to enable him to battle
with the deadly poison.
Only time will tell which
of the two of them is stronger.
Within that battlefield
of a body lies destruction
and recovery raging away
at extraordinary speeds.
He will survive only if he
can withstand all that pain,
and escaping from death
does not come cheap.
[BON CLAY gasps]
[sighs]
You can take a look inside,
if you really want to.
[BON CLAY]
I-Is there a window?
Straw Boy?
[screaming]
[BON CLAY]
How awful! He's gonna die!
[BON CLAY crying]
It's gonna tear him apart!
His body will be destroyed
from the inside out!
That-That wasn't even him in
there, it was a living corpse!
I'm begging you, here!
Don't let him suffer like that.
You have to do
something, please!
Unlock those chains,
stop the bleeding,
and find a real way to cure him!
You're the miracle worker,
aren't you?
I know he's a mess, but
anything is better than this!
[IVANKOV]
Shut the hell up!
[IVANKOV] I'm helping him
the only way I can!
Don't underestimate
the human will to live!
The what?
Do you have
any idea what it takes
to strive against
one's own mortality?
To face the ultimate odds?
I'm not a god, or an angel,
or anything like that.
A "Miracle Worker"?
You can call me whatever
the hell you want,
but the truth of
the matter is this:
I could never save a fool
who doesn't have the will
to save himself.
I saved an impoverished country,
and a country that was left
in ruin after defeat in war.
But, in both cases,
all I did was draw out
their own spirit to live.
That can only happen to people
who have the courage
to keep on fighting!
Making miracles is never easy!
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY screaming]
[NARRATOR] Luffy braves
Iva's agonizing treatment,
even though it has little
chance of actually succeeding.
Unable to help in any other way,
Bon Clay cheers for his friend,
praying that his strength
of will can prevail.
Meanwhile, the guards
of Impel Down
begin to escort Ace
to his place of execution.
[LUFFY]
On the next, One Piece:
"Believe in Miracles! Bon
Clay's Cries From the Heart"!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!