Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Behold my new weapon.
The Stag Beetle!
Hell yeah!
I'm ready whenever you are!
Just a word of warning.
I haven't had a chance
to test this thing.
So I don't know what'll
happen when I let it loose.
[FRANKY]
Roger!
Now shoot me straight into that
thing's stomach and we got this!
[USOPP]
Special Attack. Iron Man Comet!
[FRANKY]
I'm gonna wipe that smug grin
right off your face, Moria!
Tch!
Franky, no!
[MORIA]
Don't stop now, Oars!
That was a nice shot,
but I'm afraid he's still alive.
Why don't you stomp on him?
[OARS]
Okay.
Kushishishi!
[NAMI]
Thunderbolt...
Look! That cloud!
[NAMI]
...Tempo!
I don't know what's
going on, but I want it to stop!
Oars, can you pound
whoever's doing it?
Nami-swan!
Could you stop yelling already?
Now they're gonna
know where I am!
Okay Master. Gum-Gum...
[NAMI]
Huh?
Wait, he's not
gonna stretch, is he?
I mean, can he?
...Pistol!
[CHOPPER]
What?
He... he stretched! Impossible!
Hey, it worked!
That was new,
but it doesn't feel new.
Kushishishi!
[LUFFY] "The Straw Hat Crew
Gets Wiped Out!
The Shadow-Shadow's
Powers in Full Swing!"
[OARS]
Gum-Gum...
Here he comes!
[OARS]
...Bell!
[screaming]
This whole stretching
thing makes fighting fun.
Gum-Gum...
He's coming back for more!
[OARS]
...Spear!
What the hell's goin' on here?
He just got
exponentially more powerful!
[ZORO] It's not like
he ate a Devil Fruit,
so how's he able
to stretch like that?
It's gotta be Moria.
What'd he do?
Kushishi!
There you have it!
Now you know
the nightmarish power
of the Shadow-Shadow fruit!
Shadow Revolution!
Revolution?
A shadow is
a helpless prisoner
to the body that casts it,
mimicking it like a reflection.
The body and shadow
are physically fused
to the same
shapes and movements.
It's a basic law of nature!
But I've freed Oars' shadow
from the dominance of Oars' body
and taken control of its
form with my own shadow!
I can now change
the shape of Oars' shadow
as I wish,
thereby forcing Oars' body
to match and follow
its every contortion!
As I said, it's a law of
nature that the body and shadow
must always hold the same shape.
But now the shadow is no longer
the subordinate, but the master!
The body is forced to obey
any shape the shadow takes!
This is the power
of Shadow Revolution!
Moria is even
stronger than we thought.
Even if Oars doesn't
have a devil fruit power,
he can still stretch.
If Moria controls his shadow,
he can rewrite the rules.
[SANJI]
It's a bit of cold comfort
to know that Oars
isn't actually a rubber man.
If he has all the same powers,
it doesn't do us much good.
Wasn't he tough enough already?
I mean, give us a break here.
Right?
It was hard before,
but now it's almost impossible!
Kushishishi!
You know, he has even
more tricks than Straw Hat.
For example, if I force
his shadow into a ball...
Oars will become a ball as well!
[NAMI]
No way.
What is happening?
Now that's nuts.
[MORIA]
Oars Ball!
Dodge this! Roll!
[SANJI]
Um. Okay.
[screaming]
C'mon, Master!
What's the big idea here, huh?
This is my fight!
I should get to drive!
[MORIA]
Kushi!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interfere.
I'll just focus on
assisting from here on.
And now, crush each one of
them however you see fit!
Hey!
This just occurred to me,
but where is Luffy?
He ran off after Moria
and got tricked somehow.
I'm sure he's
gonna be back soon, though.
Seriously?
Does he have to do
something stupid every time?
[NAMI thinking]
What should I do?
It probably won't
help if I tell them
another one
of the Seven Warlords
is somewhere on the island.
I'll get to that later.
Okay, I know I'm a
little late to the party,
but let me get this straight.
Are you saying we've gotta
defeat Luffy's zombie and Moria
if we want to get
everyone's shadows back?
Is that the gist of it?
Yeah. That's about it.
You're kidding!
The sun is almost up!
The enemy is
forcing our hand here!
It's not like we
have much of a choice!
[BROOK]
Excuse me.
[NAMI]
The skeleton.
I didn't know
you were here, too.
I beg of you.
Please allow me to help.
I have an idea
that just might work.
[CHOPPER] Get back here, Zoro!
Don't be reckless!
My friends.
I appreciate your trust in me.
I don't think it should
be too tough to pull it off.
Are you sure about this, Brook?
I'm not trying to
talk you out of it or anything,
but you saw what
happened to Franky, right?
Just don't blame me
if anything goes wrong, okay?
But if this is what
you want, I'm glad to help.
Now Dark Cloud Tempo!
[BROOK]
I'm ready. Fire at will.
I can't believe we're
using this thing again.
There is one thing
I fear more than death.
Being unable to repay my debts!
I'll fight to the last bone!
You can count on me!
Right! Try not to die!
[BROOK]
Here goes!
Slalom Vine!
Yohohoho!
[BROOK] I'm getting such a
shock that I can see my bones!
Well, I was only
bones to begin with.
Alright, here I come!
Like an arrow
forged with lightning!
Lightning Bone Sword!
Gavotte Bond En Avant!
It worked!
He shot straight through him!
There's a hole in me!
[USOPP] Now's our chance!
Follow up attack!
[BROOK] As they say,
mission accomplished.
Nice work there, Bones!
Alright. Two Sword Style:
Tower Climb!
You bastard. You're next.
But first, that skeleton's
gonna pay for hurting me.
Gum-Gum...
Oh no! He's goin' after Brook!
[OARS]
...Battle Axe!
Brook, no!
Skeleton!
[USOPP]
Take this!
Atlas Comet!
Hya!
Didn't work!
Oh, crap.
Keep fighting, Usopp!
Hey, what about you?
[OARS] You just made
yourself next, long nose.
Your friend with
the swords can wait.
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
I'm a dead man!
[OARS]
Huh?
Hey! Why can't I stretch?
Ochenta Fleurs. Cuatro Manos.
Where'd all
these hands come from?
That's cheating!
Give it up,
or I'll snap your neck.
Your shadow revolution is over.
Huh?
Tighten Hold!
Okay, this hurts.
Hell yeah! Nice work, Robin!
Kushishi!
You honestly think
your little hand tricks
are enough to
put me in the ground?
Well if you wanna play dirty,
I don't mind
slingin' a little mud.
Have some Brick Bat.
Get away from her!
Veinte Fleurs!
Calendula!
Robin, no!
You wanna sink your
teeth into something?
Then try this!
Kushishishi!
Moria's shadow?
Well, considering you've got
such an effective
choke-hold on me,
I guess I'll have to pull out
my long-range weapons, as well.
[ROBIN thinking] I can't
let his shadow distract me.
I just have to take out the body
and the shadow
will disappear, too.
Cuatro Manos!
That's tight!
Okay, c'mon now. That's enough!
And then Clutch!
[MORIA screaming]
Nice!
Awesome! You did it, Robin!
Robin, look out!
Moria's shadow
is right behind you!
Kushishishi! Kushishishi!
Shishishishi!
Kushishishi!
What?
How in the world
did Moria get over there?
Almost got me,
but not quite in time.
Y'see, I can switch
places with my Doppelman here
whenever I see fit.
Switch places? No way.
But that means...
...the one
inside Oars' stomach...
[MORIA] Yes, the one in
the cockpit is my shadow double.
And, your cute
little arm parlor tricks
don't have any effect on him.
Leave Robin alone!
Kushishishi!
I believe that puts three
of your team under my belt.
That bastard
stole Robin's shadow, too!
Kushishishi!
Too bad I don't
have a corpse on hand.
I'll just hold
onto you for safekeeping.
Diable Jambe.
You're gonna pay
for that, you monster!
Give Robin's
shadow back! Right now!
Extra Hachis!
Fly, Brick Bats!
Kushishishi!
He's switching places
with his shadow again?
If he switched out,
then that means...
Moria! He's back
inside Oars' stomach cockpit!
Kushi!
Well, look at that,
we're right back to square one.
[OARS]
Stupid Master!
I told ya once already!
This is my fight,
quit buttin' in!
[MORIA]
I do apologize, Oars.
I couldn't help myself
from getting in on the fun.
I'm takin' over now,
and I'm gonna start
by squishin that lady.
Now Gum-Gum...
He can stretch again!
There's no way
to escape him now!
Are you serious?
He's going after her
while she's unconscious?
Sanji, Robin!
Get out of the way!
...Bazooka!
[SANJI]
Diable Jambe...
...Frit Assorti!
What the...?
Whoa! He blocked it!
This is our chance.
Someone get Robin to safety!
[USOPP]
I've got her!
Hey!
Look, you guys! Check this out!
[SANJI]
Chopper?
What the hell're
ya doin' up there?
Some forensics work.
Searching for Oars'
original cause of death.
Cause of death?
[CHOPPER]
Aim for his right arm!
This one's new,
it's not his original arm!
Hogback did a
good job restoring it,
but the joints still
show signs of frostbite.
This is only an informed guess,
but I think he died
five hundred years ago
from exposure to the cold!
He might be a massive brute,
but he's still no
match for mother nature.
He got caught in the
cold and froze to death.
And if I had to
speculate any further,
he didn't just get
caught in the cold.
He was also naked!
I won't lose to
someone that dumb!
[CHOPPER]
Zombies may not feel pain,
but they can still take damage.
And all of our attacks have
weakened his original wounds.
This is our chance to
cut his attack power in half!
All we've gotta do
is get rid of this arm!
So focus all of
your attacks here!
[OARS]
Stop squeakin' in my ear!
And who the hell
said ya could stand on me?
Chopper, no!
What... Where'd he go?
[CHOPPER]
Nice punch there.
Too bad all you did
was hurt your own shoulder.
You might not be able
to feel it, but trust me!
Huh? My hand's talking.
I'm kind of a small guy.
Your fist is
like a cavern to me,
full of cracks
that I can hide in.
Rumble...
Jumping Point!
And Arm Point!
[SANJI]
Chopper! Impressive work!
Here, let me give you a hand!
Sanji! Boost me up!
Armee De L'Air...
Cloven...
Go!
--Roseo Shoot!
[OARS]
You're gettin' on my nerves!
Ya keep hittin' the same spot
but it's not even hurtin' me!
If it doesn't work once,
it's never gonna work!
Oh, it's gonna work!
Pain is a warning sign
used to protect the body.
Not feeling any pain
doesn't make you stronger!
[SANJI]
Chopper!
[OARS]
Just shut up already!
You gotta get
outta there, guys!
He's coming after you!
Now Gum-Gum...
This looks bad.
Really bad.
...Gatling!
Sanji! Chopper!
[NAMI]
He took down another two.
One by one. He's destroying us.
Damn it!
[MORIA]
Kushishishi!
Number four, and number five.
[MORIA]
Only three left to go!
[USOPP] I have no idea who you
are, but thanks for rescuing me!
Speaking of,
who are you, anyway?
[LUFFY]
Monkey D. Luffy.
[USOPP]
You're lying.
[LUFFY]
No. It's really me.
[USOPP]
What? What happened to you?
Whoa! And how in the heck did
you get so stinkin' strong?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"The Incredible Battle Starts!
Luffy vs. Luffy!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!