Believe in Wonderland!♪
[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me
my head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really, really
stuck on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop
'til I get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Stop it, you fool!
I'll take it.
Well keep searching men.
Monkey D. Luffy's crew
is somewhere in Logue Town
and we are going to find them.
[MARINE AMARINE BMARINE C]
Yes, sir.
[SMOKER]
He's not going to try to hide.
He'll find me. I'm sure of it.
I'm almost there.
I can't wait to stand in the
same place Gold Roger stood
and see what he saw
before he died.
[LUFFY]
Well that's weird.
How the heck did I end up
all the way back here?
[LUFFY]
"Usopp vs. Daddy the Father!
Showdown at High Noon!"
Captain Smoker!
If this Luffy guy is still
somewhere on the island,
then we need to blockade
the ports immediately.
[SMOKER]
There's no need to worry.
‐‐And why is that?
‐‐[MARINE A] Stop!
[MARINE B]
You can't go in there!
[MARINE C]
The captain's in a meeting.
[DADDY]
How ya doin', Smoker?
[SMOKER]
Well, if it isn't Daddy.
[DADDY]
Here's Two‐Pistol Pete and
the cop‐killing Riley Brothers.
[SMOKER]
And all three have bounties?
No, all four. I dropped
a brother off at the morgue.
If you wouldn't mind
signin' for them,
I'd sure appreciate it.
A million berries for
four guys. Times are tough.
The work may be cheap
but it's steady.
I'm fine bringing in
the little fish
that move through these waters.
I'm not really interested
in heading out to sea
to chase that one big catch.
[SMOKER] The marine's best
sniper reduced to being
a common street cleaner.
It's sad.
[DADDY] I don't want
to risk my life anymore.
Because, if you die,
that daughter of yours'll
end up on the street, right?
Tell Carol I said "hi."
[DADDY] Sure, I'll tell her
Uncle Smokey said "hello."
That was Daddy Masterson,
the bounty hunter.
Yeah. We enlisted
at the same time.
He was one of the elite‐‐
a natural with a gun.
I was sure he was
bound for great things.
[TASHIGI] Then why is he
just a bounty hunter?
[bell ringing]
A cursed sword.
Interesting.
[LUFFY]
Hey.
That's a really cool sword.
Don't sneak up on me.
So why're you
just sittin' here, Zoro?
[ZORO]
I'm bored. You?
Oh, me? Hmm.
Yeah, I'm completely lost.
[ZORO]
And that's a good thing?
[LUFFY]
Mm. It's okay.
[MAN A]
Hey! There he is!
‐‐[MAN B] It's him!
‐‐[MAN C] Daddy!
♪
What's up?
Bastard! You sold out our
friends to the highest bidder.
It's time for you to pay.
Now die!
[gun shots]
[MAN A, B, C, D groan]
[gasps]
Why don't you run on home, kid,
and see if your mom's
got supper ready?
[MAN E yells]
Whoa, Zoro!
That guy's totally awesome!
[ZORO]
I think that's... Yep.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[ZORO]
Daddy the Father, bounty hunter.
[USOPP laughing]
I got everything I need.
[laughs]
I'm completely prepared
for whatever the sea
can throw at me.
There isn't anything
Usopp, brave warrior,
can't face now.
Uhhh... Wait a minute.
I think I'm forgetting
something important.
That's it. A first class
sniper like myself
should really have a top shelf
pair of goggles to look through.
I'm going to get
the best pair I can find.
I don't care what they cost‐‐
unless it's more
than I can afford.
Super goggles, here I come!
[gasping, laughing]
[chuckles]
These are them! These are
the ones! They're perfect.
Hey, lady!
Those are brand new.
They're the top of the line
model from North Blue Company.
Oh, and the import ship
I get them from
only stops here
in port once a year.
Hey, don't you have any money?
What's wrong with you?
I can't just give these away.
No, I...
That's right. My backpack!
I'll take those.
‐‐[USOPP groans]
‐‐Oh, excellent choice!
And what a cute little girl.
I happen to know that
these are the only goggles
of their kind
on the whole island.
No. Those are my goggles!
Drop 'em!
Hm?
You snooze you lose, grandpa!
[hollers]
Huh? Grandpa?!
[laughing]
[USOPP]
Little girl! Stop right there!
There is no way you could
possibly think I'm an old man.
I'm more like
an older brother, right?
Well, you smell like an old man!
I am not old. Just give me
back those goggles.
I found them first.
They're mine!
‐‐Yeah!
‐‐They're mine! They're mine!
You better watch
your mouth... 'cause...
I'm friends with the Marines and
I'll get them to beat you up.
‐‐Th‐The Marines?
‐‐That's right.
And their captain is a close
personal friend of my family's.
He's kinda like my uncle.
[USOPP]
Why you little...
Ha! I'm a great captain, too!
Arlong Park was destroyed
by these two hands.
I was surrounded
by hundreds of Fishman
and the last thing they
ever saw was Captain Usopp,
the incredible, doing such
amazing and terrible things,
they were glad
to quickly meet their end.
Now I have a bounty of
30 million berries on my head.
So Marines don't scare me!
Oh, 30 million berries, huh?
‐‐[USOPP] That's right.
‐‐[CAROL] Hm. Papa!
Don't call me "papa"!
I'm not your daddy. Aaah!
[CAROL]
I bought a present for you.
Happy birthday, Papa!
Oh, my girl...
Carol, you are absolutely
the most angelic little girl
a father could ask for.
[CAROL]
I love you so much, Papa.
[USOPP]
What's with that girl?
[CAROL grunts]
But Papa, that silly
old man over there
was being mean and
trying to jack your present.
Now, now. Don't say "jack,"
dear. It's not right
for a proper young girl.
[USOPP]
Eek!
[DADDY] Are you
the gentleman that's been
bothering my adorable
little daughter?
Eh! No... I just...
[CAROL]
There's something else.
[DADDY]
Huh?
[CAROL whispers] There's a
bounty of 30 million berries...
[DADDY]
A bounty worth 30 million, huh?
[USOPP chuckles nervously]
[DADDY]
Let's take a look.
Oh. Are those the new bad guys?
Yeah, I just
picked them up today.
Six hundred...
One point three mil...
Seven hundred...
Ah. Thirty million...
Monkey D. Luffy.
For a first bounty,
that's impressive.
[DADDY]
Where are you going?
Okay. That's not me.
I'm not the guy in the poster.
I was just trying
to pretend to be a bad guy.
Bye bye now. I'm outta here.
Bye. See ya. Crap.
‐‐That's you.
‐‐[USOPP hollers]
Okay, you caught me again.
But just try and
lay a hand on me
and you'll see what happens.
My captain, Luffy,
won't sit idly by
and watch one
of his crew in danger.
He's a cold blooded
soulless demon
from the very pits
of hell itself.
You can't even imagine
the pain that he can inflict.
You've got your daughter
to worry about.
Why risk your life over it?
You're right. It's not worth it.
[DADDY] Anyone with
30 million berries on his head
is no ordinary man,
and that's for sure.
Papa. You can beat him;
you're the strongest man ever.
And you're not afraid of anyone.
[DADDY] Darling, I don't
have to prove anything.
I just need to get by
with enough to keep us happy.
So long as you think
I'm the greatest,
that's all that matters
to me. Understand?
Papa.
[USOPP]
I scared him off just like that.
I guess I don't know
how truly terrifying I am.
Time to flex.
I'm glad you came
to your senses, fool.
Now give me my goggles
and just maybe
I'll let you escape
with your life.
‐‐Huh?
‐‐[USOPP chuckles]
Don't worry;
I'm gonna pay for them.
I'm a killer, not a thief.
Now give 'em here.
He's letting you go, old man.
If I were you, I'd be
running for my life‐‐
‐‐Papa?
‐‐Okay, fine.
If that's how you want it,
then let's settle
this dispute like gentlemen.
‐‐Gentlemen?
‐‐[DADDY] Here.
A duel? Yeah.
I‐I think I can manage that.
If you win then
the goggles are yours.
[screams]
Two, three, four, six...
Thirty pistols!
[screams]
That's the same
number of guns as
Daddy the Father!
Yep, that's me.
[PASSERBY A]
It's Daddy the Father!
[PASSERBY B]
There's gonna be a duel!
[PASSERBY C]
Who could be that stupid?
Daddy... the Father?
Everybody knows
that Daddy the Father
is the greatest gunslinger
in bounty hunter history.
Not to mention he's
never lost a duel before.
So, what kind of idiot...
Oh, that kind.
[PASSERBY A]
Good luck, long nose!
[PASSERBY B] We got a hole dug
for ya already, so relax.
[chuckles]
[USOPP]
What the hell just happened?
Why am I dueling this guy?
[DADDY] Simple rules.
Walk ten paces and fire.
‐‐Okay.
‐‐What the hell are you doing?
‐‐[USOPP] Nami?!
‐‐It looks like you're facing
Daddy the Father
in a duel. Are you nuts?!
You're not helping!
You never have
anything nice to say!
You get one shot.
Are you ready?
One.
Two.
[CAROL]
Three.
Four.
Five.
[USOPP]
What am I doing? This sucks.
I'm so stupid.
There's no way I can beat him.
And Six.
[USOPP]
I'm gonna die now.
This can't be happening.
Seven.
[USOPP] I can't believe it.
My adventure is just beginning
and I'm already gonna die.
Who'da thought
it would come to this?
[CAROL]
Eight.
[USOPP]
Ciao!
[NAMI, CAROL gasp]
[CAROL] Papa! That was
awesome! You're the best!
That was just pathetic.
[PASSERBY B]
What a loser.
[PASSERBY C]
I don't think I've ever seen
such a cowardly move in my life.
I just shot
the coward's gun away.
What were you thinking‐‐
have you no shame?
Cheating during a duel.
You should be ashamed
of yourself‐‐it's pathetic!
[USOPP]
I'm so sorry! Forgive me!
I'm just really too scared
to die this young.
Killing me would be
too easy for you, right?
So, please don't shoot me.
You could just
let me go, couldn't you?
[USOPP hollers]
No, wait.
Nami. If you want money,
my friend here
has tons she can give you.
Please spare me.
I'm begging you, sir.
What the hell?
So, now you're
cowering behind a woman.
Listen...
No, leave her out of this.
She has nothing to do with it.
I'm the one that got
myself into this situation
and nobody can get me out it.
It's all on me.
Usopp.
Please, just leave
Nami out of it.
Usopp? Did she
just call you Usopp?
Yes.
‐‐Can't be...
‐‐[USOPP] Huh?
You wouldn't by
any chance know a man
by the name of Yassop of the
red haired pirates, would you?
Yassop...
That's my dad's name.
Uh! Wait, are you saying that
you and my father are friends?
So then you are his son.
Papa.
[birds chirping]
I met your dad.
And I've never spoken
a single word to anyone
about that fateful day,
‐‐until now, that is.
‐‐[USOPP] Huh?
We met in a hot,
dry port of call on a day
very much like today.
[YASOPP] C'mon ensign
Masterson! One shot each.
[PIRATE A]
One, two, three...
‐‐[YASOPP grunts]
‐‐[DADDY groans]
‐‐[PIRATE A] He won!
‐‐[PIRATE B] Yasopp won!
[PIRATE C] He beat the best
sniper the Marines have!
[PIRATE A]
Boy, that was a close one.
[PIRATE D]
You're the man, Yasopp!
Yeah.
All right! Finish him!
Killing the loser lets him die
with dignity and respect.
It's the right
thing to do, Yasopp.
Please. Finish me off.
There's no reason
for me to live anymore.
Yeah. You lost after all.
Huh?
[DADDY]
What are you doing?
[YASOPP]
Your daughter?
Give it.
I wouldn't expect
a cold‐blooded marine
like yourself to be treasuring
something like this.
Guess she must
be really special.
And what would a dirty
pirate know about it?
Not much.
[laughing]
[PIRATE A]
You were awesome, Yasopp!
[YASOPP] No, I wasn't. I wounded
him instead of killing him.
Still need more practice.
[PIRATE B] Maybe, but the rest
of us would have been killed.
You took on
Daddy Masterson and lived.
Thanks boss. Really.
I'm glad you let me duel him
instead of just
killing him on sight.
[YASOPP]
That hits the spot.
Hey, you want some marine?
[DADDY grunts]
[YASOPP]
Family, huh?
I could never wrap
my mind around that job.
[DADDY]
Is that so?
[YASOPP]
Y'know, I've got a son.
His name is Usopp.
Haven't seen him
in years though.
I left him for the sea
just when he started walking.
[DADDY]
Why? Didn't you love him?
[YASOPP chuckles]
It wasn't that.
I loved him plenty.
It's just that I loved
something else more.
The sea was calling for me.
[PIRATE D]
Amen, brother!
[PIRATE cheering]
[DADDY]
Mm.
[YASOPP yawns]
Now then...
It may be too late for me
to do anything for my son,
and I truly regret that,
but you... your daughter...
...she deserves to have
a parent with her by her side.
Don't ever let her go
while you have the chance.
Not that I'm the one to talk.
[laughing]
I lost our duel, Yasopp.
You can't leave me
here like this.
You owe that much to me.
[YASOPP] You Marines
may have to follow the rules
and do everything by the book,
but the best part about
being a pirate is that
I can do whatever I want,
whenever I want. Later.
So that's why you
left the Marines to become
a bounty hunter.
It all makes sense now.
Papa, no. A pirate
didn't spare your life.
Tell me it's not true.
Tell me you killed him, right?
Usopp! Wow! Your father
must have been amazing.
He beat Daddy the Father.
He hasn't forgotten you either.
Even now, as he's traveling
somewhere in the sea,
he has an image of his little
toddler boy that he left behind.
‐‐[USOPP sobbing]
‐‐[NAMI] Usopp?
[NAMI]
It's okay. We understand.
There's...
no way that you could.
That's not why I'm crying‐‐
there's more to it.
I get it. I understand
why you'd tell me
that story about my father.
You told me that
so I would try to be
more like him.
[CAROL]
Huh?
You embarrassed yourself for me.
You put yourself
beneath me so I would know
what type of man my father was.
I'll never forget that.
Most people would
just bury that story
and never tell it to anyone.
But you...
You're not afraid of anything.
Even shame.
A coward would never do
what you just did.
Carol, your dad
is the bravest man alive!
Men who are big and strong
are easy to find.
But the ones who
put their honor on the line
for others are one in a million.
I can't. If I accept
your dad's mercy,
it'll only bring him more shame.
I have one choice
and that is to face my death.
Give me another chance.
I have to prove to myself
that I am not a coward.
A life or death fight.
All right. Choose the weapon
you feel most comfortable with.
This will be our final duel.
Good. Now...
‐‐Let's see...
‐‐[bell ringing]
You must hit that weathervane.
What? That?
If you miss...
[USOPP] Right, you'll shoot me
through the heart.
[NAMI]
Usopp!
So this shot determines whether
I live or die with honor.
He can't.
There's no way he can
shoot that far with a slingshot.
[bell ringing]
[USOPP]
Relax. Concentrate.
[USOPP] It's just another shot.
Like a hundred before.
[USOPP grunts]
[NAMI]
You... missed.
Please don't kill him,
Papa. Please, no!
I can't shoot him
'cause he shot
right through the crown!
[gasps]
[NAMI]
You did it, Usopp! He's right!
Good job!
[DADDY] You're as good a shot
as your old man.
And a brave one as well.
Your father will be proud.
Go to the Grand Line.
You'll find him there.
[DADDY] He deserves to see
what his son has become.
[USOPP]
Daddy.
You're a pretty
good shot, old man.
Thanks.
[CAROL]
Later!
Wait, Papa!
[DADDY] Now Carol, don't say
"later." It's bad manners.
[CAROL giggles]
Sorry, Papa.
I'm gonna try to be a nice
little girl from now on.
[DADDY] My little angel,
you're nice enough.
[CAROL giggles]
Well, I'm gonna be even nicer.
[NAMI]
When people say Daddy the Father
is a disgraced marine, at least
we'll know the real story.
My father will see me
as a true warrior someday.
You'll see. I'll be as brave
as Daddy the Father.
And I will make my father proud.
[USOPP]
I know it.
[CARMEN]
Sanji! I finally found you
after ten years.
All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way
[USOPP] They're saying
there's a cooking contest!
[SANJI] Huh? My food isn't
meant for competition.
It's meant to be placed
delicately in the mouth of Nami.
[NAMI]
Thanks, Sanji.
[ZORO]
What? You're not gonna enter?
[LUFFY]
You get that if you win, right?
[SANJI] Wait, that's...
a blue‐finned elephant tuna.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Fiery Cooking Battle?
Sanji vs. the Beautiful Chef!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!