[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people who
seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[gasps]
It looks like we've
lost the wind again.
If this keeps up,
just getting to Little Garden
is gonna take forever.
We won't be moving for a while.
We're starting to
run out of time.
We need to go.
[NAMI]
Try not to worry so much.
We're gonna get you to
Alabasta as quickly as we can.
The wind'ill pick up soon.
Right! Now it's time to fish.
[KAROO squawks]
[SANJI]
Hey guys.
Do any of you know
where the bait went?
The bait? Oh, you mean
the stuff in there?
Yeah, I ate that.
[USOPP]
Uh!
[SANJI] You ate it?!
Those were bugs!
That right? Mm! They were good!
Oh, yuck! That's gross!
Well done! How are
we supposed to fish
now that you've scarfed
down all of our bait?!
Try using this.
[SANJI]
We can't fish with that!
Those are some picky fish.
How about him?
[SANJI]
That could work.
[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY]
Hey, come back here, bait!
[ZORO] Uh! Ow, damn it!
Knock it off, you guys.
[exhales] I guess it's
too much to ask...
...for you guys to be worried!
What should we be worried about?
Ahh! You are simply beautiful
when you're angry, Nami!
Come on!
It just seems odd.
For someone with a 30 million
berry bounty on his head,
your straw hat captain
sure doesn't seem to be
a particularly
terrifying pirate.
Yeah, I know that it's
really tough to imagine,
but he's actually beaten some of
the really big names out there.
Like Arlong, the fishman
who was determined to
rule the East Blue.
And Don Krieg,
the pirate commodore.
[NAMI]
Also Captain Kuro,
a mysterious pirate who was
notorious for his cunning.
You left one out.
Huh?
[ZORO] That freak marine captain
who had an axe for a hand.
[NAMI]
Oh, yeah! Axe‐hand Morgan!
The Axe‐hand Morgan?!
I've heard of him before.
From what I know,
he's feared by sailors
throughout the East Blue for
his strength and cruelty.
You're saying that
Luffy even beat him?
Right! The old axe‐hand man!
Speaking of the axe‐hand man,
I wonder what that kid who was
with him is up to these days.
[USOPP]
Huh?
[KAROO squawks]
[LUFFY] I wonder if he's
still at the marine base.
Who do you mean?
[LUFFY]
Oh. His name's Coby.
He's a friend of mine
from way back.
[LUFFY]
"Try Hard, Coby!
Coby and Helmeppo's
Struggles in the Marines!"
[MARINE A] Sub‐Lieutenant!
We're ready to set sail, sir.
[COBY]
All right.
All ships set sail at once!
[MARINES]
Yes, sir!
[COBY]
Dear Luffy. It's me, Coby!
How are you? Well, I've
been working really hard
since the last
time I saw you!
There have been some tough
times along the way,
but now I've finally made it!
I've become an officer
in the marines,
just like I always
dreamed I would!
[MARINES screaming]
[COBY screams]
[MORGAN yells]
It's Axe‐hand Morgan!
[MORGAN]
Coby.
I'm going to send
you to hell, Coby!
[COBY screams]
Huh?
Luffy!
Yeah! Hey, Coby!
[MORGAN grunting]
Now, Gum‐Gum...
...Tornado!
[MORGAN screams]
Wow! That's absolutely amazing!
[crash]
[HELMEPPO groaning]
A dream! I was dreaming
the whole thing!
Hey, you! Get the
hell off my bed!
[MARINE A]
Shut up!
[MARINE 1] Idiot chore boy,
go back to sleep!
I'll kill you Coby. I hate you!
[COBY]
So anyway, Luffy.
Right now I'm working at the
marine base as a chore boy!
Oh, and do you remember Axe‐hand
Morgan's son, Helmeppo?
Well, he was given chore
duty along with me!
Hey, quit slackin' off!
Ouch!
Hey, chore boys!
Wash the windows when
you're finished here.
Sir!
[MARINE B] And don't forget
to clean the mess hall, too.
But! What about our meal, huh?!
You can forget about lunch.
There's no way you're going
to be done by then.
Maybe you'll be done by dinner.
But I'm about to
starve to death!
Are you all right?
[MARINE A]
Helmeppo! Coby!
Sir?
You remember that neither
of you were qualified
to join the marines?
Yet, you were generously
given permission
to join as marine
chore boys, for now.
Like an offer to clean your
toilets is really generosity.
Yes, sir, I remember!
If there's anything at all
I can do, I'll do it!
You just give the order!
[MARINES]
Uh.
No, that will be all for now.
You boys work hard!
[COBY]
You can count on us, sir!
We would be honored to wash
and fold your laundry as well,
if you'd like!
Are you crazy?!
You don't need to go out of your
way to land us even more work!
Well, after all, we are
chore boys, Helmeppo!
And work's what chore boys do!
Yeah, is it?
Well, if you want to suck up,
you can do it yourself!
[MARINES] One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three,
four. One, two...
Uh... I can't stand this!
Coby can be the model
chore boy if he wants,
but why do I have to do it?
I remember the good old days.
[MARINE 3] Helmeppo.
Here's your cocoa, sir.
[HELMEPPO screams] Damn it!
Are you trying to kill me here?
No! Sir! I'm so sorry, sir!
You would do well to
remember who I am!
I am the only son of the great
marine captain Axe‐hand Morgan.
And don't you forget it!
[MARINES]
Yes, sir, Helmeppo, sir!
[HELMEPPO] Ah! Life sure was
good back then.
[COBY humming]
Damn it!
If it weren't for that
stupid straw hat guy,
none of this would of happened!
He showed up and
ruined everything!
Thanks to him,
my father lost his position
as a marine captain!
[MARINES] One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
It's all his fault!
It's because of that straw
hat guy that I'm here
doing stupid chores instead
of living the good life.
[COBY]
Hey, Helmeppo.
What d'ya want? Why are
you touching me like that?
Well, I'm sorry. I just...
I wanted to see if
you're all right,
you know, one friend to another.
A friend?
And why the heck would you
and I ever be friends?!
Well, we're both
chore boys, after all.
[HELMEPPO]
Hmph.
I shouldn't be in a place like
this doing stupid chores,
and I wouldn't be if it weren't
for that Straw Hat!
You shouldn't blame
everything on Luffy like that.
It isn't his fault; he was just
doing the right thing.
You can't just blame your fate
on other people all the time
and expect that to
solve everything.
That's a sign of weakness,
don't you think?
A weakness?!
[COBY] For a long time you could
use your father's power
to get through life.
Things are different now.
We've got to work long
and hard on our own
to accomplish our dreams!
Oh, please.
[COBY]
You know my dream?
Someday I'm gonna become a
great officer in the marines!
I'll chase bad guys
and defend justice!
[HELMEPPO]
How stupid can you be?!
A wimp like you becoming a
marine officer like my dad?!
No way that will ever happen!
I know that it will!
Thanks to Luffy, I know that
I can do anything that I want!
That's right! I'm gonna
be King of the Pirates!
I decided that long ago,
and if I die fighting for it,
it's all right!
[COBY] So I decided to be
like Luffy and do anything,
even risk my life, to
achieve my final goal.
Well?
Now we can work hard and
reach our goals together!
Forget it! You think I'm
going to listen to this?!
What the heck makes you
think you can tell me
what I should do?! And what
could you have possibly learned
from that pathetic
excuse for a pirate?
[COBY] Don't talk about
Luffy like that!
I haven't done anything
but try to help you out!
I don't remember
asking for your help!
[COBY yells]
[HELMEPPO yelps]
Helmeppo, will you please
just stop acting foolish?!
Oh, please! You're
calling me a fool?!
Take that!
[COBY]
Would you snap out of it?
[LIEUTENANT]
What's going on here?
[COBY]
Just stop it!
[MARINE 4] Sir, the chore boys
are fighting on the roof.
[LIEUTENANT] Why are you
standing here? Stop them!
[COBY, HELMEPPO scream]
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINES yelp]
[MARINES gasping]
[COBY, HELMEPPO whimper]
[LIEUTENANT growls]
You two!
[COBY, HELMEPPO]
We're... We're sorry, sir!
[RIKA] Really? That explosion
earlier was from you guys?
They didn't kick you
out of the marines,
did they, Coby?
[COBY]
Thank you, ma'am.
No, they actually allowed
us to stay enlisted.
Yeah, but we had to agree to
work for free for 50 years.
Getting kicked out would
have been so much better.
You two could use
some cheering up.
Yeah, look at this, Coby!
"Straw Hat Luffy Wreaks
Havoc in Loguetown!
Manages a baffling escape
from Captain Smoker."
Luffy's picture! Do you
realize what this means?!
Luffy's headed for
the Grand Line!
At last, he's making his
way closer and closer
to achieving his final goal!
[MARINE 5]
Attention!
[LIEUTENANT]
I will now inform you
about the nature of our mission.
[screams] Look!
What do you want?
[HELMEPPO]
It's my dad!
[LIEUTENANT]
Captain Morgan is being sent
to Marine Headquarters
to face a court martial for the
crimes of military exploitation
and the cruel and unusual
treatment of civilians.
Our mission is to
transfer the prisoner
to Vice‐Admiral Garp.
[MORGAN]
Rankless, low‐life bums!
You have no right to
defy my superiority!
I am Marine Captain
Axe‐hand Morgan
[HELMEPPO, COBY whimper]
[HELMEPPO] So I guess it's
really going to happen.
I mean, I know that he deserves
to get court‐martialed
and all of that.
I get it, given the stuff
that he did, but honestly...
...even after all that,
I still respected him.
He's my dad, you know,
and no matter what he did,
he was still my idol.
But I guess he did take
things a little too far, huh?
Damn it!
Why? [cries]
Coby, do you think that they're
going to execute him?
[COBY]
I don't know.
[HELMEPPO] I guess I
should probably be ready
for something like
that to happen, huh?
But he's my dad.
[COBY]
Helmeppo...
[MARINE 6]
Marines! All hands on deck!
[LIEUTENANT]
Fall in!
[MARINE 2]
It's Vice‐Admiral Garp!
[MARINES chattering]
[COBY] So that's Marine
Vice‐Admiral Garp!
The man they call the Fist!
He's a great hero of the seas
who travels all over
the Grand Line!
Vice‐Admiral Garp, thank you
for coming all this way.
We are pleased to deliver
Captain Morgan to you.
[HELMEPPO]
Dad! No!
[LIEUTENANT] Sir, did you
hear me Vice‐Admiral?
Vice‐Admiral Garp, sir!
Be quiet! I heard you.
I'm a bit tired because I've
been up for five days now.
You are indeed a
dedicated marine, sir!
No, I've been trying
to set a record
for the most doughnuts eaten
in a single sitting.
Sir?
The sugar kept
me going at first,
but I've been at it
for a while now,
and I guess the lack of sleep
is starting to get to me.
What a pathetic geezer.
[LIEUTENANT]
Morgan!
Vice‐Admiral Garp deserves
to be treated with respect
from the likes of you!
Old man. Cut the
sleeping act already.
[GARP snoring]
[HELMEPPO, COBY whimper]
[MARINES gasping]
[COBY, HELMEPPO scream]
No one move!
[HELMEPPO whimpering]
If anyone moves a muscle
I'll hack this chore boy up
and feed him to the sharks!
B‐But daddy, why
are you doing this?!
Sir, please stop this!
Helmeppo is your son!
How could you do something
like that to him?!
[MORGAN] My son?
What do I need with a son?!
What I want now is freedom!
I don't care about his life!
I'll cut him into a thousand
pieces if I have to!
[HELMEPPO]
But... Daddy!
[MORGAN laughing]
[HELMEPPO] Ah! Help me!
Somebody help me, please!
[MORGAN]
Good riddance, you fools!
[COBY]
Helmeppo!
[BOGART]
Ready the cannon!
[COBY whimpers]
Load the cannon! Take aim!
Target, 16 degrees starboard.
Distance... eight‐two‐six‐three.
Now, ready!
[COBY]
N‐N‐No, please just wait!
[MARINES chattering]
I'm begging you not to
shoot! Please, stop!
He has a hostage on that boat!
Move it.
[COBY]
I won't!
In that case, you're dead.
Chore boy, stop this!
Yeah, get down from there, kid!
No, I won't! Helmeppo's
on there, and he's...
[COBY]
He's...
Helmeppo's my friend!
That little fool.
I would just shoot him.
[COBY whimpering]
You're gonna pay for this.
Maybe so,
but at least I won't be guilty
of abandoning my friend!
Please, I can fix this! I'll
capture Morgan myself!
[COBY screams]
[LIEUTENANT]
Come back!
You idiot!
You'll never be able to
capture him by yourself!
Let's let him try.
He's either brave or
dumb, or just... dumb.
[MARINE 6]
Well, what do we do?
[GARP yawns]
[GARP grunts]
[yawns]
All right, I'm awake again.
Now, what's all
this noise about?
Vice‐Admiral Garp, you're alive!
I was certain that that
monster had killed you!
What?! One of the men
has been killed?!
I can't believe I slept through
something like that! Who was it?
[GARP]
Hm?
Oh, right.
[MARINES]
Aiye!
[MORGAN laughs]
Free at last!
Just you watch!
The world will be kneeling at
my feet again in no time!
I will rule the seas!
The world will quake in terror!
Now set our course
to the west, boy!
What are you doing?
I said set our course!
[HELMEPPO]
No!
Huh?
[HELMEPPO] I won't have
any part in your plans!
Coby put everything on the
line trying to save me.
He even risked getting kicked
out of the marines to help me
and they're his dream!
He fights for what he
believes in, no matter what,
and so could I!
Dad, I'm going to capture you!
You might as well just give up‐‐
[MORGAN grunts]
What do you think
you're doing, brat?
Are you too stupid to know
what you're up against, huh?
What can a useless
piece of scum like you
hope to do to me?
If you just shut up and
do what you're told
like the weakling that you are,
then I won't make your
life too tough.
You got it?!
You just... Shut up, Dad!
[HELMEPPO groans]
Damn it!
[MORGAN] It's time you learned
your place, you pathetic insect!
No, I'm not listening
to you anymore!
From now on,
I'm the one who's going to
decide how to live my life!
[MORGAN]
Stop being such an idiot!
What can someone like
you possibly do?
[COBY]
He can do whatever he wants!
You came!
[COBY]
Stop right there, Morgan!
It's time to give
yourself up now.
As a member of
the marine forces,
I have come here to recapture
you as a prisoner.
[COBY groans]
[HELMEPPO groans]
You two are absolutely pathetic!
How can a couple of
pitiful insects like you
expect to capture
someone like me?
If you even think about
getting in my way,
I'll kill you both!
Thank you for coming to save me.
I'm sorry it turned
out like this.
[COBY]
I'm glad I came!
Aren't we friends, after all?
Coby.
[COBY] Besides, I've made up my
mind, to fight for my beliefs!
And... And if I...
die fighting...
If I die fightin' for it,
well, that's all right.
[COBY yells]
You really want to die that bad?
[COBY]
I'm not gonna die!
I won't die until I've become
an officer in the marines.
I've already decided that.
But I swear, when I do die...
When I do die...
I'm gonna die fighting!
[screaming]
Playtime's over kid.
Coby!
[COBY yelling]
Put me down!
You big jerk, you better
put Coby down now,
do you hear me?! Coby!
[COBY whimpering]
[MORGAN grunts]
[MORGAN] You little pests
aren't worth the time
it would take to kill you.
I'd better never see
your faces again!
[HELMEPPO]
Morgan!
[MORGAN]
Huh?
I may have let you sail away
from here alive today,
but someday I'm going to catch
you! I promise you that!
Do you hear me? Someday
I'm going to capture you!
Just you wait!
[LIEUTENANT] Please forgive
my poor supervision, sir.
Allowing the prisoner to
escape was inexcusable.
[HELMEPPO, COBY]
We're very sorry, too, sir!
[LIEUTENANT]
After today,
these two will be kicked out
of the marines for good.
[HELMEPPO, COBY whimper]
[GARP] The two of you
are truly lost causes.
I don't know anyone who
would take you in now,
but turning you loose would
only burden the public.
I have no choice but to take you
with me to Marine Headquarters.
[COBY, HELMEPPO gasp]
What, Vice‐Admiral?
Sir, you're actually going to
take these two chore boys
with you to headquarters?
[GARP]
That a problem?
Of course not.
No problem here, sir.
And do you two have a problem?
If you want to run away,
this is your last chance.
Not that I'd allow you to
get very far, of course.
Well, now. It certainly has
been an interesting day.
[laughs]
[COBY]
So, Luffy.
That's how Helmeppo and I
ended up heading toward
the Grand Line!
We're on our way
there right now!
[COBY] I sure hope that
we'll meet again soon!
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I wrote you a
love song to let you
Know that I wanna be with
you 'til the end of time
Even when the sparkle fades
The doubts in vade our
once so trusting minds
Promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies
We built a castle of sand
And now we're watching
it wash away,
It doesn't have to end
We'll start again,
this time 'round,
we'll build a stronger love
Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I just wanna hold you
and not let go
You know that I'll be with
you 'til the end of time
Oh, you've got me heart and soul♪
[LUFFY] Oh, here it is!
You guys, take a look!
[NAMI] What is it? It looks
like a marine photo!
[LUFFY]
Yep! And look at the guy in it!
Know who that is?
[ZORO]
Whoa! Is that Coby?
[USOPP]
Coby? Who's that again?
[LUFFY] Coby's my friend!
He's gonna be a marine mayor!
[ZORO]
Marines don't have mayors!
[SANJI] Shows how much
you pay attention.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Coby and Helmeppo's Resolve!
Vice‐Admiral Garp's
Parental Affection"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!