[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY]
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms!
Miracle in the Drum Rockies!"
[HIRILUK] I will... make cherry
blossoms bloom in this country!
Once my invention
is perfected,
this country is
as good as saved!
I will save this country
with my doctor's skills!
[KUREHA]
Yeah, right...
Don't you mean
"destroy this country?"
This is a winter island
where it's bitter cold
year round‐‐cherry blossoms
aren't gonna bloom here.
[HIRILUK] No! I was an
angry worthless criminal on
the brink of death,
but those flowers saved my life
and transformed the very
essence of my existence.
[HIRILUK] Every human being
in this world can be saved.
[HIRILUK] There's no disease in
this world that can't be cured!
[HIRILUK]
And that's why I raised
this skull and crossbones!
As a challenge to all the
diseases of the world!
This symbolizes my belief...
that nothing is impossible!
By raising this flag,
I vow to fight just
like the pirates do!
[HIRILUK] Chopper... some day
you've got to go to sea!
If you do, you'll
realize just how small
your problems really are!
[CHOPPER]
Doctor... I...
Hmm?
[LUFFY chuckles]
Found you!
Hey, monster guy!
Don't run away!
Come be part of my crew!
You know you want to!
[DALTON groans]
[gasping]
[VIVI] Are you sure you're
going to be okay, Dalton?
[DALTON]
Yes... I'm fine...
Just feeling a little
drained, that's all.
I'll be fine after I've rested.
[KUREHA]
Hey... you over there.
[ZORO]
Hm?
[VILLAGERS gasping]
Doctor Kureha!
[KUREHA chuckles] Yeah,
it's good to see you, too...
Now, be useful and take the
injured guy to the medical ward.
[ZORO gasps]
Hey... I recognize her!
You're that damn
old hag from before.
[grunting]
[KUREHA]
Well... get moving!
[VILLAGERS]
Yes... ma'am!
[KUREHA]
I'd suggest you hurry,
unless you want to be in the
same kind of pain this man is.
[SANJI] Nami, you really
should stay and have
your illness completely treated.
Be quiet.
If I don't escape
from here now,
we won't be able to set
sail for two more days!
You know how worried Vivi is.
We need to get her to Alabasta.
[KUREHA]
Quit all this grumbling
and get back
to the medical ward.
Move it! Right now!
[SANJI, NAMI scream]
[USOPP] ♪ I'm Captain Usopp
stuck in a dungeon ♪
♪ gonna save the day...
[SANJI yelling]
[VILLAGERS whimpering]
[KUREHA chuckles]
Just as I expected...
his injuries have gotten worse.
Due to overexertion.
[KUREHA]
Ah.
Much better...
Dalton, surely you would know...
...where the key
to the arsenal is...
Isn't that right?
The arsenal? Why do
you need to get in there?
That's really none
of your business, now is it?
[DALTON] Wapol always
carried that key with him...
to keep it secure, he said...
In which case, the key
was likely blown into
the sky with him.
Oh, really, is that so?
Well, that's a shame.
[NAMI]
Doctorine.
[KUREHA]
Hm?
Think we can talk about
your fee for treating our crew?
Could you waive it? Oh, and...
Could you go ahead and
discharge me right now, as well?
[KUREHA growls]
Is that a joke?
'Cause you should know better
than that by now, girlie.
For my medical fee I will
be taking all of the cargo
and money you have
on that ship of yours,
and you will stay here and
recover for two more days...
[VIVI gasps]
Nami, she's right, you know...
You need to complete
your treatment...
I'm fine! I don't even feel
like I'm gonna die anymore.
[VIVI] That isn't exactly
a very convincing reason.
[gasps]
[NAMI chuckles]
The key to the arsenal...
This is what you needed, yeah?
[gasps] How did you
end up with that key?
If that's truly the real one,
how'd you get a hold of it?
[NAMI]
I stole it.
[KUREHA growls]
You've certainly got some guts,
trying to negotiate
with me like this...
You really are an
unbelievably frustrating
little girl, you know.
[NAMI giggles]
[KUREHA]
Okay, then...
You don't have
to pay my doctor's fee,
but that's as much
as I'll agree to.
As a doctor,
I can't allow you to leave
in good conscience...
not for two days.
Wait a second! In that case,
I'm afraid we
don't have a deal.
Give it back!
[KUREHA]
Listen here, girl.
I have to leave you alone
now and go take care
of a few things...
If you look in the back room,
you might find a dresser
with one of my coats in it.
And it's not exactly like I'm
posting any guards on you.
Also, the young man with
the spinal fissure should be
well enough to travel by now
But, girl... Don't you even
think about trying to escape.
You guys... come with me.
I have some heavy
lifting for you to do.
[VILLAGERS]
Okay... All right...
Did she really just
tell us to steal her coat,
get Sanji, and sneak out?
I think so... That's
what it sounded like to me.
[CHOPPER pants]
I sure have been
running a long time...
Night came before I realized it.
I don't hear that
rubber guy anymore...
Looks like I finally
shook him, I guess.
[CHOPPER] This is for the best.
I can't leave this place...
I just can't.
[CHOPPER]
Looks like a full moon tonight.
Hey! Deer!
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
‐‐[LUFFY] Come be a pirate...
‐‐[CHOPPER] I can't believe it!
Those guys are
still looking for me?
Come on, Luffy...
Why don't you just give it up?
We've been tracking him forever,
and he still hasn't shown up.
He's not interested
in becoming a pirate...
You're just going to
have to accept that.
No, that's not true!
I want the reindeer
to be a pirate with us!
Just because you
want something doesn't mean
it's going to happen...
[CHOPPER] It's not that
I don't want to go with them...
Reindeer!
Wherever you are, reindeer,
come out! Just for a second.
[CHOPPER] But I'm not
going to go! I can't go!
I'm nothing like
them‐‐the humans.
[LUFFY]
Reindeer guy...
[BOTH grunt]
[LUFFY chuckles]
Tony?
Hey, you're gonna
come on our ship and be
a pirate with us! 'Kay?
[CHOPPER]
I can't.
Sure you can, reindeer!
It's a whole lot of fun!
[USOPP] That's not
a very good argument...
[CHOPPER]
I can't.
I'm not a human...
I'm a reindeer! I have antlers
and hooves, don't you see?!
I even have a blue nose!
[KUREHA] Now that
you've heard his story,
do you think you can heal
the scar on his heart?
Okay... Maybe I do want to be...
...a pirate. But I can't
ever be one of you.
I'm not human! I'm a monster!
I can't be your friend,
and I can't become a pirate
on your ship! You see?
I'm just here to say thank you.
I appreciate you asking
me to join your ship...
That was really nice...
so thank you.
[CHOPPER] I'm going
to stay here for now...
But if you wanted to,
you could stop by here again.
[LUFFY]
Shut up! Let's go!
[CHOPPER gasps]
[NAMI chuckles]
Most people don't make friends
by telling someone to shut up.
[CHOPPER whimpers, sobs]
[USOPP]
Nami... How ya feeling?
Are you completely recovered
from your illness already?
[NAMI]
Sure am... I feel great!
[LUFFY] Hey! How bout we go say
goodbye to the old doctor lady
and that Dalton guy
from the village.
[NAMI]
Don't be so thoughtless!
We need to leave Chopper alone
with Doctorine for awhile.
He lived with her for six years.
We should let them
say goodbye in peace...
I'm sure it's gonna be
really sad for them both.
Doctorine acts all
tough in front of us,
but deep down, I think she
really is a kind person.
[LUFFY]
Hmm... You sure?
[USOPP] So... we're
just gonna leave without
saying anything to her?
[NAMI]
Yeah, that's right...
Once Chopper comes back,
we'll go straight down
the mountain and
set sail... to Alabasta!
Sounds good to you, right, Vivi?
Yes... Now that we have
a doctor coming with us.
[LUFFY]
Doctor?
Well... In that case...
I'll go ahead and get
the ropeway ready.
[USOPP]
Hey, Luffy! Give me a hand.
[LUFFY] I didn't even know
there was a ropeway!
So cool...
[VILLAGERS gruntin]
[KUREHA] Now, hurry up
and get them out of here...
Once they're all
outside the castle,
line them up! You got that?
[VILLAGER A]
Doctor Kureha?
[KUREHA]
Hm?
I don't understand this.
What are we taking all of these
canons out of the arsenal for?
[KUREHA chuckles]
Just hurry up and get it done.
Uh... But I...
[KUREHA]
Well, look at that...
It seems as if we have
a couple of patients missing.
Yes, they all left...
Directly disobeying your orders.
Oh, I see... What am I
going to do with them?
[CHOPPER]
Doctorine!
I need to talk to you right now!
[KUREHA] Chopper, where
have you been all day?
Hurry up and get downstairs...
You can help the men
take the cannons outside.
Please listen, Doctorine...
I'm going to become a pirate...
I'm leaving with
the others right now!
What did you say?
[CHOPPER]
I'm going out to sea!
I'm coming on board with
them as the ship's doctor.
I'm going to travel everywhere!
Stop this foolishness, Chopper!
[CHOPPER gasps]
[KUREHA]
Now, listen...
You know you're
my only assistant!
I'm the one who
taught you everything
you know about medicine!
Do you really feel
no gratitude at all
for what I've done?
No... No, that isn't true!
I'm incredibly grateful
to you, Doctorine!
And I'll always love this land!
It's where I met you
and Doctor, after all.
[KUREHA] Hmph. Then
you can just stay here!
If you think you can find
another home as nice as this one
somewhere in the outside
world, you're sadly mistaken.
[CHOPPER gasps]
Those pirates aren't
good for anything, Chopper!
You'll end up dead on some
vagabond's sword in no time!
[CHOPPER]
I can accept that!
[KUREHA]
Don't sound so sure of yourself!
A reindeer going out to sea?
That's the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard of...
Yeah, I am a
reindeer! But, still!
I'm a man!
[KUREHA growls]
[CHOPPER growls]
You can talk tough for now...
But you're still my assistant,
Chopper! If you want to leave,
you're going to have
to go through me first!
Do you understand?
[gasps]
Doctorine, I...
[yells]
[KUREHA] You're still
afraid of your own shadow,
and you're telling
me you're a man?
Oh, please,
don't make me laugh...
But, Doctorine...
These pirates, don't you see...
[LUFFY]
Shut up! Let's go!
They like me.
Quiet, you!
[CHOPPER grunts]
No, I'm not gonna
let you leave me...
[CHOPPER squeals]
[KUREHA]
You're staying!
[CHOPPER screams]
[KUREHA]
Get back here, Chopper!
[CHOPPER screams]
[KUREHA]
You can't escape!
[CHOPPER screams]
I wonder what
all that noise is about.
[VILLAGER C] Who knows?
Whatever's going on,
we'd better hurry and get
all this stuff outside...
If we aren't careful,
Dr. Kureha will start
using us for target practice.
Don't exaggerate.
[KUREHA]
Come back!
[CHOPPER screams]
[KUREHA] I won't let you
get away from me! Chopper!
[CHOPPER sobs]
[KUREHA]
Give up!
[ZORO]
What's going on?
There's a lot of noise
coming from the castle.
[NAMI]
How inconsiderate...
Making all that noise when those
two are trying to say goodbye...
That's just downright rude!
[CHOPPER] I'm sorry, Doctorine,
but I want to go out and see
the world beyond this island!
[KUREHA]
What could someone like you do
on a pirate ship, Chopper?
Are you gonna
try to live some fantasy
like that old quack?
[CHOPPER] No... You're wrong!
It wasn't a fantasy!
Doctor's research was finally
completed before he died!
Oh, finally here he comes...
[gasps
[gasping]
[NAMI]
What's going on?
He's being chased!
Hey! We got the
ropeway ready to go!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[CHOPPER]
Everyone, get on the sleigh!
We're going to head down
the mountain. Hurry!
[KUREHA bellows]
[STRAW HATS scream]
Hey... look at that.
What the hell is that thing?
That's the witch's sleigh!
[VILLAGERS murmurin]
[VILLAGER G]
What was that thing?
[VILLAGER H] It looked like
Dr. Kureha's reindeer.
[VILLAGER I] And those pirates
were riding in the sleigh...
[VILLAGER D] What's going
on up there, anyway?
[VILLAGER E]
What happened to Wapol?
I hope Dalton's all right.
[LUFFY laughs]
That was fun! Hey, reindeer,
can we do that again?
[NAMI] You idiot!
We don't have time for that!
[USOPP]
Whew! I thought I was gonna die.
[SANJI] Hey, where am I?
What's going on?
[VIVI] Oh, Sanji!
You're awake! You okay?
[DALTON] You really think that
was the best way to say goodbye?
[KUREHA] A pet I was taking
care of is being looked after
by someone else now...
That's all.
Besides, I don't like...
...long goodbyes.
[KUREHA]
Come on.
We have work to do...
We have to prepare
a fitting send off!
[DALTON]
That hurts.
[HIRILUK]
I've finally done it...
This is it... This reaction...
I've been waiting
30 years for this...
[CHOPPER] Doctor! It wasn't
a fantasy like she said, right?
You finished your work...
You accomplished your dream!
[CHOPPER]
Or was that all a lie, too?
[HIRILUK] I've done it, Chopper!
My research is a success!
[CHOPPER] Did you lie because
you knew how sad I'd be
if you died without
completing it?
"Nothing is impossible
for a man who raises
the pirate flag!"
Please, say it again, doctor!
All right, young men,
are you ready?
[VILLAGERS]
Yes!
[KUREHA]
Then fire!
[HIRILUK]
Listen to me, Kureha...
This dust is special.
Dr. Kureha...
What are you doing?
Just... shut up and watch.
[cannons booming]
[VILLAGERS gasping, murmuring]
[VILLAGER G]
It's coming from the castle!
[VILLAGER H] Is Wapol setting
off fireworks or something?
[VILLAGER G]
No, those are cannon blasts!
[VILLAGER I]
What's happening up there?
[VILLAGER D]
Watch for cannonballs!
[VILLAGER E] It's too dark to
see what they're doing up there!
Doctor Kureha, all the
cannons have been fired.
Then light them up...
[VILLAGERS gasping]
Look!
[gasps]
Oh, cool...
Yeah.
Wow!
[HIRILUK] After 30 years,
this dust finally
completes my research.
This is... This is just
absolutely amazing.
[KUREHA chuckles]
I still can't understand what
that idiot was thinking...
[HIRILUK]
I will...
...make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
Once my invention is perfected,
this country is
as good as saved!
[VILLAGER Q D] Get out of here,
you crazy quack!
[HIRILUK] I thought lizard
eyeballs would work!
[HIRILUK] This is no
ordinary red dust, Kureha.
This dust is designed
to attach itself to
the white snowflakes as they
come down from the sky...
The white snow will then become
a beautiful shade of pink
for everyone to see.
[CHOPPER whimpers]
[CHOPPER]
Doctor! Doctorine!
[wails]
[wailing continues]
[HIRILUK] I promise you I'm
not going to shoot you, see?!
My name is Hiriluk...
Doctor Hiriluk!
Tony... Tony Chopper.
Cool name, huh?
Anyway, that's what
I'm gonna call you.
You're going to
become a great doctor...
I'll make sure of it!
[HIRILUK] Even if I should
disappear right now,
my dream will come true.
I've had... a marvelous life!
[CHOPPER whimpers]
Thank you so much, Chopper...
[wails]
[KUREHA] Now... Have a
safe trip... my stupid son.
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[LUFFY]
Hey! What's the matter, Chopper?
[ZORO] How long are
you gonna be all spacey?
[USOPP]
Come here and dance with us!
[NAMI] Shh... We should leave
him alone a little bit longer.
[SANJI] He's going on his first
journey as a real man...
It's an important
rite of passage.
[USOPP]
All right, then...
Let's all drink a toast
to our new friend!
[STRAW HATS]
Yeah!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
[CHOPPER] "Goodbye Drum Island!
I'm Going Out to Sea!"
[LUFFY] I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!