Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
So, what's your plan now?
Just take me to shore already.
I wanna hurry up and knock you
out and get this over with.
That's it. I'm sick of your
talking.
Sick of it.
I'm gonna shut you up
right here and now!
Super cartwheel.
Iron Ball!
I'm gonna slam
you into the tower
and smash you to pieces!
That's your plan?
Well that would pulverize me,
gotta give you that.
Franky Centaur!
Chapa?
I've got both your legs.
As long as I've got
you bound like this,
you can't move around!
That doesn't mean anything.
At the speed we're going,
there's nothing you can
do to slow us down now!
Well let's just see about that.
70 mm Caliber Cola Cannon!
Just a little Coup de Vent!
He stopped our momentum!
We're not even rotating anymore!
Damn you!
That's far enough.
We're right above the shore.
Now, take this.
70 mm Caliber 1 point
5 Max Cola Power!
Coup de--
Stop it!
What're you trying to do?
Just give up already,
you bastard!
Coup de--
Vent!
Super!
Yoyoi!
There's no way.
He busted out of the fridge?
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you!
I am so full!
Holy crap, he got fat!
You cannot be serious!
Did you eat every piece
of food in there?
What the--?
Shing!
Alright, Sniper King.
Just hold that posture.
You are now a sword.
Someone get me a lawyer!
There is no way I am not
gonna sue your ass off for this!
Whatever you say.
In the meantime.
I'd like my sword to shut up.
Wake up! Wake up!
This is a dream!
Oh, why won't the morning come?
Hmph.
They're good for a laugh,
if nothing else.
I love it!
Oni...
Wait!
Do you think we could start off
with a different move?
One that doesn't
use swords? Please?
...giri!
Ow. Ow. I'm seeing stars.
Don't move an inch! Tiger...
Let's just calm down.
No violence. Talk this over!
Damn!
Yep. I think my nose is broken.
I said not to move, didn't I?
If it's so easy, then you do it!
Are they making fun of us?
I'm not sure.
Maybe they're just that stupid.
Looks like we're back to the
rock-paper-scissors plan.
Better to lose a hand
than lose the fight.
No!
Can't you come up
with a better idea?
One that doesn't involve blood?
No. No, I can't.
You didn't even think
about it, did you?
Actually, maybe I don't have
a hand to spare after all.
Just give up yours, all right?
If CP9 doesn't
kill me, Zoro will.
Hurry Chopper!
You gotta save me!
"Uncontrollable!
Chopper's Forbidden Rumble!"
Yoyoi!
I don't think
I've ever seen anyone
with so little self-control.
You gained all that weight
in just a few minutes?
Thank you for your
concern, but I-I-I-I--
Who said I'm
concerned about you?
Okay! I get it!
You're just fine!
Don't talk with
food in your mouth!
Mmhmm.
"I'm just fine". Yes, thank you.
That is indeed what
I was trying to-trying to--
I don't know what you're
trying to do, but stop it!
You're okay, I'm okay,
everything's great.
Now get back here!
Ah, yes, yes, of course,
where was I again?
I shall solve this shortly.
Now observe. My "Life Return"!
Digest! Absorb! Complete!
What? What the heck are you?
What did you just do?
I mean, could you
do it again, please?
Yes. As you wish.
Life. Return!
Now Digest! Absorb!
Cool! One more time!
One more time?
Uh, Life Return!
Then Digest, and Absorb!
So awesome!
How do you do that?
Well!
How kind of you to ask!
A thousand years at sea,
a thousand years
in the mountains.
Breathing in the wind and
drinking the morning dew,
I lived as a hermit
to complete my training.
And lo! At long last,
the secrets of
"Life Return" revealed
themselves to me!
From your head,
down to your toes.
Every inch of the human body
can be controlled
with strength of will.
Why you can even command
your internal organs and
each hair to its very tip.
Using the mind to control
the workings of the body.
I've read about something
similar in a medical journal.
They called it "biofeedback."
Then you're able
to move your hair
around like an octopus
because of that power?
Yoyoi! An octopus?
How rude of you!
I am, as you say, a shishi!
A valiant lion, in other words!
Octopus. Lion. Whatever.
Life Return! And Hair Bind!
Yoyoi!
Oh no.
If I get caught by
his hair, it's all over!
Shave!
Where'd he go?
Finger Pistol Q!
He did that with a blunt stick?
Q! Q! Q!
Heavy Point!
Iron Body!
Yoi!
Ow ow ow ah!
What is the matter?
Damn it. I thought so.
Unless I can hit him
with Arm Point
or Horn Point,
he's not gonna budge.
But the rumble balls
are powerful.
One in six hours is
about all I can handle.
Any more than that will put
too much strain on my body.
Even worse, if I take another,
I might not be able to control
my transformations anymore.
If I still can't win and
I have to take a third,
I might completely
lose consciousness.
Is it worth it?
I don't think I can
damage him without it.
I shall skewer you,
and roast you alive!
Shishi Kebab!
Yoi! Yoi! Yoi!
I don't have time
to think this over.
Rumble!
It's a risk, but it's
the only chance I've got!
Yoyoi!
This is do or die.
One way or another,
I have to settle this
in three minutes!
Take this! Horn Point!
Yoyoi!
Uh-oh! Hot hot hot
hot hot hot hot hot!
Shishi-Kebab!
Take this! Jumping Point!
Wrong one!
Yoyoi! Ah, yoyoi!
Damn it. Just like I thought.
My transformations
are messed up.
All I need is to
get to Arm Point.
One shot with a cloven
hoof should be enough.
If this fire keeps spreading,
I'll end up suffocating.
I can't waste time
fighting this guy
when he doesn't even have a key!
That's right.
I have to find key #2.
Zoro and Sniper King
are counting on me!
We can't save Robin
without their help.
Robin. Hold on!
I won't let you down. I--
I'm here, to save my friend!
And I'm not gonna let
anybody get in my way!
You're a stubborn
beast, aren't you?
Life Return!
His hair is pointing
at me. Who cares!
I don't have time to
think, I have to win!
I can't let my friends down!
Shishi Finger Pistol!
Yoyoi! A lion shows no mercy!
It's fury relents
for no creature!
I knew taking that second
rumble ball was a gamble,
but I was hoping it
wouldn't be this bad.
Since I have seven
different forms,
that means I only
have a 14% chance
of getting Arm Point.
But as long as I can move,
I'll try as many
times as it takes!
That's right.
I have to keep fighting!
Arm Point!
Shishi Kebab!
I can't let them down.
C'mon, Arm Point!
Yoyoi!
Arm Point!
Wrong again!
How many times is
this going to take?
My body's about
to give out on me.
I have to get Arm Point now!
Yoyoi!
I got it! When did that happen?
Prepare yourself!
My final attack.
It's all or nothing!
Cloven--
Shishi Finger Pistol!
This is my only chance.
I can't hold back! Cloven--!
Iron Body Strength!
Roseo Metel!
That has to do it!
That was my strongest attack!
Splendid!
A beautiful cherry
blossom blizzard.
Not yet. Not y--
Did I win?
You have awakened
the wrath of heaven!
Feel the thunder of the
lion's roar! Yoyoyoyoi!
Tempest Kick Lotus!
This is it.
I don't have the strength
to fight back anymore.
Chopper! Chopper!
What in the world
did you do out there?
I don't remember.
"I don't remember"
isn't gonna cut it.
This is serious, you know.
You're lucky no one died.
While you've been here sleeping,
the whole country's
been in an uproar
about what you did last night.
What am I supposed to tell them?
I did something really bad, huh?
An entire village
almost got wiped out!
I know you love your experiments
just like your old man,
but you have to plan
these things very carefully
before you jump in!
Those are the rules.
A whole village wiped out?
I know you weren't
doing this just for fun
and I'm sure you
didn't mean any harm,
but, that's exactly why
you need to be more careful.
Much, much more careful.
We doctors walk
on a narrow cliff.
People entrust us
with their lives,
but even the tiniest
error on our parts
can prove fatal for them.
It doesn't matter if our
intentions are good or not.
So imagine what kind
of damage you could do
by being careless!
If you aren't willing to weigh
the consequences
of your actions,
then you have no
business being a doctor.
You wouldn't think it at first,
but you're the spitting
image of that crazy quack.
You can't help but
cause a ruckus, can you?
I suppose that even
bad seeds bear fruit,
now don't they?
I- I'm sorry.
Please Doctorine, I promise
I won't do it again,
so don't kick me out, okay?
You fool.
Just hurry up and
get better already.
These chores aren't
gonna do themselves.
Life Return! Hair Bind!
Suffer as you must,
but do not cry!
For if you shed a tear, thy
name as a man shall suffer, too.
He's going to kill me.
Far behind you is the
peaceful mountain village
where the cicadas sing.
The sweet memories leaping
in your heart have given way
to the dancing flames of
hell, licking at your feet
with every step of
your final journey.
I give to you the
leaves of a willow tree.
Dyed in crimson to
honor your parting.
Now take it!
Take it, take it
and never look back!
See the leaves
fluttering in red!
Song of the Willow!
This is the end. Robin.
No, I can't give up yet!
He escaped from the Hair Bind?
Rumble.
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
I can't keep my word.
Maybe I am just like
the Doctor after all.
If he put his life on the
line to save his country,
then I want to put my life
on the line to save my friends.
If I'm going to die anyway.
I have to try it!
Everyone, please stay away.
I'm about to lose control.
I used three Rumble Balls.
And then, I don't know.
I lost consciousness.
What happened?
I suppose you could say
your Devil Fruit went wild.
I don't care what happens,
you can't let yourself
go down that path.
A power that destroys your foes,
but turns you
against your friends
and your own body as well.
There's only one word
for a creature like that.
A monster.
Big news, boss! Big, big news!
Oh yeah? Well calm down
and tell me about it.
We're back!
After all this time,
we're finally back!
Ah, but Buggy is back, too,
and he's making a mess
out of everything,
so we gotta hurry
and--and--and--
Okay, okay. I said
"calm down" didn't I?
Uh, right, well, the point is,
this is big news, boss!
On the next One Piece:
"Boss Luffy Returns!
Is it a dream or reality?
Lottery Ruckus."
I'm gonna be a policeman!