[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
Look there!
It's a trap!
A dirty Marine trick!
[USOPP]
Help me!
Usopp, no!
[GOATS bleat]
[ZENNY]
Drop sail!
[GOATS bleat]
[USOPP]
Huh?
No! Impossible!
A pirate ship sailing
down a mountain?
Goat man!
[LUFFY] "Whereabouts
of the Island Treasure!
Attack of the Zenny Pirates!"
[ZENNY laughing]
[GROUP yells]
[ZENNY yells]
Is that...?
[LUFFY]
Way to go, goat man!
[SANJI] Hey, don't
encourage him like that!
[ZORO] His heart
hasn't stopped, has it?
Don't make jokes
like that, Zoro!
[CHOPPER]
Old‐timer! Are you okay?
[ZENNY]
I'm actually at sea!
I've done it!
I've become a pirate!
All right!
No longer is this my coffin!
It's the pirate ship Zenny,
scourge of the seas!
Right, you guys?
[GOATS bleat]
[LUFFY]
Yay, old goat man!
[GROUP] We told you,
don't encourage him!
[CHOPPER]
He's a sick man!
Well, if it isn't
Zenny the Moneylender!
Even with that ship,
you're nothing more
than a bloodsucking
petty extortionist!
Well, not anymore, I'm not!
You're talking to
Zenny the pirate, boy!
[laughs]
And you're talking to
the Marines, you geezer!
[USOPP]
Be careful, old man!
He's after your treasure!
[ZENNY]
Oh?
Lately the Marines have started
going after treasure on the side
instead of just doing their
duty and hunting pirates
as ordered!
I'd have to say,
that's very industrious of you!
Nami, bring the ship around.
‐‐I'm on it. C'mon!
‐‐[SANJI] Dammit!
You don't get to give
my sweet Nami orders!
Sergeant Minchy!
The Straw Hats are
up to something!
Call Captain Moore for backup!
Shut up!
[gunshot]
[MINCHY] I told you you'd get
your cut of the treasure,
didn't I?
Keep your mouth shut.
We can't let the captain
know what's going on.
[ZENNY]
Let's see now.
Yes.
I figure you must be
paying your men off
so you can take on
this side project.
That must cost you a
pretty penny, eh, Sergeant?
Why, you smelly old coot!
You're gonna pay
for this if I have to‐‐
Shut your stinking mouth!
A worm like you's got a lot
of nerve, thinking you can
swipe my treasure!
Come and take it
from me, if you can!
[laughs]
[LUFFY]
You tell 'em, old goat man!
[LUFFY laughs]
Let's show 'em how
a pirate really fights!
[LUFFY grunting]
[GROUP yelling]
[LUFFY]
There!
[GROUP]
Moron!
Why did you do that?
[MINCHY]
Damn it!
If you're a pirate, you won't
mind if we do our duty
and kill you!
Does he have any weapons?
'Cause I don't think does.
[ZENNY]
So be it!
Let's see what you're
made of, sonny jim!
Have you got what
it takes to challenge
my Class Ten abacus skills?
Take 'em down, men!
[GOATS bleating]
[ZORO]
Oh, he's got his abacus and...
[LUFFY]
...the goats.
[GOATS bleating]
Oh, no!
Hold on, old man!
I'm coming!
No! Luffy!
[ZENNY laughing]
Are you guys blind
or something?
What are you shooting at?
I'm right here!
I'll make it easy for you!
Let's go!
[GOAT KID bleats]
What's the matter with
you wimps? They're goats!
You're fighting against goats!
I can't help it,
they're too cute! Sorry.
Hey, Sarge, the battle's
down here, not up there!
Why not come
get your hands dirty?
[chuckling]
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, oh!
[SANJI]
We know. Now take it easy.
Yeah, relax, Chopper!
[CHOPPER]
I can't!
The old‐timer is in no kind
of shape to be doing anything
so crazy!
[ZORO]
Damn it!
[gunshot]
[GOATS bleat]
‐‐[MINCHY] Shoot them!
‐‐[ZENNY] Don't shoot!
[GOATS bleat]
[MARINE 2 yells]
[ZENNY laughing]
You've done it now!
My boys are out of control!
[ZENNY laughing]
Go get 'em, men!
[ZORO]
No, no, no! No, no!
[USOPP gasps]
Look!
They're just waiting
for us in formation!
[NAMI] It's weird how they
show no signs of advancing.
We've got to come up
with a battle plan
while we still can.
Okay, so what should we do?
Be the ones to
attack them first?
Are you outta your mind?
[CHOPPER]
It doesn't matter!
The first thing you gotta do
is help the old man!
[USOPP] By the way, did we
hit something a minute ago?
[NAMI]
Huh? Did we?
[CHOPPER]
Never mind! Hurry!
[MARINE 3] Captain Moore,
there's no response from
Sergeant Minchy's ship!
[MARINE 4] What about
that gunfire we heard?
[MARINE 3]
Should we advance?
[CAPTAIN MOORE]
No, not yet.
Wait for Minchy to report in.
[ZENNY]
Huh?
Where did everybody go?
[gunshots]
[GOATS bleating]
[ZENNY yells]
That's enough out of you!
‐‐[goats bleating]
‐‐[gunshots]
[ZENNY]
And that's enough of that!
All right!
[ZENNY grunts]
[GOATS bleating]
Well, where's all that
energy you had a minute ago,
Pirate Zenny?
Are you out of breath?
My, my.
So you've finally dared
show yourself, eh?
You know something,
old man? You talk too much!
[ZENNY grunts]
[MINCHY] Now then,
shall we get down to business?
Where exactly is your
treasure hidden, Pirate Zenny?
What's that, Corporal?
And why didn't you
report this to me sooner?
Um...
I'm very sorry,
Captain Moore, but I...
That's what he was up to!
That miserable Minchy.
I'll kill him!
[MINCHY chuckles]
Come on, old man,
spit it out, now!
Or don't you care
about living anymore?
I care about living
more than you can know.
I treasure my life.
But when it comes to money,
I tell you, I'm broke!
I've got nothing
to spit out, not even spit!
Very well.
As dinky as this little
island of yours is,
it shouldn't take my
crew too long to dig it up
from one end to the other.
I guess I don't
need you anymore.
[ZENNY, MINCHY grunting]
Why, you‐‐!
You're finished, old‐‐Ah!
[ZENNY chuckles]
I'm afraid I broke your abacus.
I'm sorry.
[MINCHY]
What do you think you're doing?
If you think you can
defy the Marines and get‐‐
[GOATS bleating]
Old man!
[MINCHY grunting]
[ZENNY] What took you so long?
I almost died here!
[CHOPPER]
I was so worried about you!
[USOPP]
And that takes care of you!
[NAMI] Robin!
Is this where you've been?
Old man, you can relax now
that the mighty Captain Usopp
is here.
[NAMI] How did you get
that bump on your head?
[CHOPPER screams]
There's no pulse!
That's my sleeve, Chopper,
the rest of me
is over here, see?
I knew that!
Now you just take it easy
and lie down right there!
Don't you die, old‐timer!
Do you think I'd die?
[GOATS bleat]
[ZENNY chuckles]
So how are you feeling, old man?
I'm feeling fine, of course.
Now that I've
finally become a pirate...
I don't wanna die!
[laughing]
[NAMI grunts]
The only reason
we came to this island
was because our
sergeant ordered us.
Yeah?
Well, I guess if your
commanding officer says so,
you got to do it, huh?
I'll tell you, our captain can
be a little unreasonable too,
you know?
You don't say.
[SANJI] Hey, don't get
too chummy, there.
Old goat man... [gasps]
...you okay? [gasps]
I'm fine. Are you okay?
[NAMI]
Don't worry about Luffy.
He'll be fine.
Your seizure has passed, so you
should be feeling better now.
Glad to hear it, Dr. Chopper.
[LUFFY chuckles]
That's good.
Old man, how's tricks with you?
Heh. Just fine, thank you.
[LUFFY, ZENNY laughing]
Ah, so then...
Listen, old‐timer,
you can tell us now, can't you?
About your treasure?
Hey, don't you go giving
any shocks to my patient!
Hang in there, old man!
[ZENNY]
For the love of‐‐
All right.
I guess you kids
have helped me out,
so maybe it would
be okay to tell you.
That's more like it!
If the Marines know about it,
it must be some treasure!
I did have a treasure.
The pirates who were
in debt to me signed over
a mountain of valuables
to pay me off.
But then, while I was making
plans to buy a pirate ship
and organize a crew,
I exchanged it all for cash.
[MINCHY]
Cash!
[ZENNY]
When I look back on it now,
I realize that's when
my fate took a turn.
Remember when I told
you I was attacked by pirates
and I eventually drifted ashore
to this god‐forsaken island?
Well, naturally I managed
to protect the cash.
Let's face it. I'd risked
my life for that money.
I was going to use it
to buy my lifelong dream.
But when I came to, after
washing up on the beach...
[GOATS bleating]
[GROUP]
Huh?!
The goats ate your money?!
Really?!
All of it? They ate all of it?
Every last Berry.
Well, maybe they left two
or three bills, but that's it.
[GOAT KID bleats]
So it's just like I told you.
These guys are my treasure,
and not just metaphorically.
[GOAT KID bleats]
[ZENNY]
All my fortune had been lost,
but in return,
I gained my friends.
They don't betray
me or cheat me.
I finally have
friends at my side
who don't do anything
for selfish motives.
They take care of me and in
return I take care of them.
So, I think I've got the
greatest treasure in the world.
Good for you, goat man.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
I guess I can turn a
profit in any situation!
[GROUP laughs]
Oh, gag me!
Hey, Straw Hat!
You pirates aren't
in the clear yet!
There's a fresh fleet
out there just waiting
to take you on!
Don't think you're gonna
get away without a fight!
[laughing]
[LUFFY] Don't talk tough when
you're rolling on the floor.
That's sad.
You're the pathetic ones!
You think your puny boat has
a chance against nine ships?
[ZORO growls]
I'm not running away.
Tell your Marine buddies
if they want a fight
to come get me.
Gum‐Gum...
[USOPP] Yo, Luffy!
Angle it just a bit higher!
Thanks!
[MINCHY yells]
[LUFFY]
...Pistol!
[MINCHY yelling]
[USOPP]
Very nice! Good direction!
[CAPTAIN MOORE]
You miserable disgrace!
I'll see you suffer!
Take him away!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL ringing]
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[CAPTAIN MOORE] This is Marine
Captain Moore speaking.
I have no interest in
the man known as
Zenny the Moneylender.
My only goal in this matter
is to bring you Straw Hats in.
However, I feel
I owe you a debt of honor
for delivering up this
disgraced member of my fleet.
Thus, I'll let you
choose where we fight!
Come, bring your ship out!
That's fine, we were
thinking of leaving anyway.
We'll be heading
out in a minute.
[USOPP] Here you go,
old man, I fixed it for ya.
[ZENNY]
I should have known.
Thank you.
Don't mention it‐‐
it was my pleasure.
[SANJI] Everything is
set up through supper.
All you have to do is heat it.
Thanks. Much obliged.
Say, um, listen, you guys.
Are you sure about this?
I mean, you are going
to be facing a fleet
of nine ships!
[LUFFY]
Don't worry about it.
I'm not only strong,
I'm also incredibly lucky.
I can't keep up with you, sonny.
Old‐timer.
I made up a
whole supply for you,
so I want you to
take your medicine.
Promise me, okay?
All right, all right, relax.
I promise to take it just
like I'm supposed to.
We had a real
good time, old man!
Take good care of yourself.
Hey, you guys!
Take care of the old man, okay?
[GOATS bleat]
We'll see you out
on the sea sometime!
Yeah!
Once I finish making repairs
to the good ship Zenny,
my boys and I'll
be setting sail!
[LUFFY] We'll be waiting
for you, Zenny Pirates!
[GOAT G bleats]
[ZENNY] Well, let's head back
to the island for a while.
We have to fix the ship.
All right, get ready.
We're heading back.
[GOATS bleat]
So age doesn't have
anything to do with
becoming a pirate, huh, son?
That kid really knows
how to get an idea
into someone's head.
That Chopper's a pretty
determined one too.
I wonder how many years I'll
need to take this whole stack
of medicine.
Much obliged, everyone.
Very much obliged.
Thanks to you,
I think I can tough it out
a little while longer.
Besides, my life as a pirate
is only just beginning.
[laughing]
[NAMI] Gotta say, that was
pretty shrewd thinking,
luring them into
this foggy reef area.
You really use your
head sometimes, Luffy.
Huh? What's that?
Oh, right, of course not,
you weren't thinking at all!
[MARINE 7]
This is Captain Moore's fleet,
calling all ships in this
quadrant of the sea!
Requesting immediate assistance!
Repeat, this is
Captain Moore's fleet!
[NAMI] You are such a moron!
I take it back!
I wish I'd never
complimented you!
[LUFFY]
What?
It's not like he really planned
for that to happen, is it?
Ah, it was just dumb luck.
He was just pointing
in a random direction!
[SANJI, USOPP]
Eh.
Listen, ship's doctor.
How's the old man doing, really?
Will he be all right?
The medicine I gave
him will help him
to control his episodes,
but it won't keep him
from getting any worse.
His heart was fairly
weak to begin with,
and old as he is,
trying to sail a ship,
let alone lead
a pirate's life...
Will you stop worrying?
The old goat man said
he wanted to be a pirate,
so let's let him be one.
Besides, once the old‐timer
sets out to sea,
he may find an island that
has a cure for his illness
and then everything
will be fine.
I guess so.
[ZORO] I don't think we
have much to worry about.
That old guy isn't
gonna croak that easily.
Maybe he does have a weak heart,
but he's also got plenty
of guts to make up for it.
Zoro's right, Chopper.
We'll see Zenny again.
You bet!
[CHOPPER, LUFFY] We'll be
waiting for you, Zenny Pirates!
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories
go racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...♪
[CHOPPER]
An island!
And a lighthouse too!
[LUFFY] Then they've
got something to eat!
[USOPP]
Wow, that's incredibly tall!
Is it really a lighthouse?
[LUFFY] Never mind that, let's
hurry and get something to eat!
Huh? Who are you, Pops?
[USOPP] Oh, no,
not another weird old man!
I'm not taking care of this one!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Legend of the Rainbow Mist!
Old Man Henzo of Luluka Island!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!