Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Is that-- No-- It can't be.
Those aren't the real
blueprints for Pluton.
Oh, they're real.
Don't believe me?
Hey, Spanda.
The reason why Tom and
Iceberg risked their lives
to protect this is simple.
Just give me the blueprints!
If an ancient weapon
fell into the hands
of some power-hungry
dumbass like you,
who knows what might happen.
In other words, the shipwrights
passed this blueprint down
to create a possible
countermeasure
against another weapon.
Now I agree that Robin's
a dangerous woman.
As long as people
like you are around,
even if she has
the best intentions,
her knowledge could still
be used to wreak havoc
on the whole world.
But now she's got
friends who are willing
to risk their lives to make
sure that never happens.
And I think they're up to
the job. So I'm making a bet.
What the hell are you doing? No!
If you end up making
a weapon after all,
we won't be able to fight back
anymore, and that's possible
if you're able
to take Nico Robin
through the Gates of Justice.
Everything's resting on the
Straw Hats, and if they're able
to get her outta here,
then you'll be left
with nothing at all.
I've placed my bet.
I think they can do it.
Cutty Flam, how dare
you burn my blueprints!
I'm gonna make you pay!
Bro!
Big Bro's falling
down the waterfall!
Franky!
Hey! Straw Hats!
Jump into the waterfall!
Give it all
you've got! Trust me!
Is that Rocketman?
It's flying!
Brings back memories,
don't it, Tom?
Giving a hand to that Roger guy
is something I'll never forget.
In fact, it's something
I take great pride in!
My name's Luffy and I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates.
Really?
Yep.
That boy may have a screw loose,
but come to think
of it, so did Roger.
It's funny, all those years ago
you helped him out,
and now Tom's Workers
is coming together again
to help out this Straw Hat Boy.
We sure didn't learn
our lesson, did we?
But I gotta feeling you woulda
done the same thing, Tom.
We're gonna crash!
Hey! What the hell are we doing?
"Obtain the Five Keys!
The Straw Hat Pirates vs. CP9!"
No way. They're here.
Yoyoi!
No! Damn it!
You're comin' with me!
If only I could figure out a
way to get these handcuffs off.
Alright, I'm lettin'
you guys off the chain!
Now go give 'em hell!
I want you to spackle the walls
of the Tower of Law
with their guts!
You hear me?
You've got full authority
to butcher them!
Lucci! You come with us!
Protecting me is your
one and only priority!
Got it? Where's Funkfreed?
There! Good boy!
An elephant that
ate a devil fruit
with the powers of a sword?
Nope. The opposite in fact.
My sword ate the
elephant-elephant fruit.
It's a long story.
I've got CP9 on my side,
and I've got my
trusty elephant sword.
As long as I maintain my cool,
there's nothing
that can stop me.
Now! We're off to
the Gates of Justice.
If you really think
you can take this woman
from me, go ahead
and try it, Straw Hat!
Big Bro Franky is alive!
The Straw Hats
actually made it across!
They finally did it!
Big Bro is free at last!
And he's gonna join the fight!
Hell yeah! Our bro
is one helluva guy!
Go get em, Franky!
Take 'em down! Go Straw Hats!
The rest is in
your hands, Straw Hat.
Hey, talk to me! You guys okay?
C'mon you old hag! Start moving!
And just what the hell
do you think you're doing?
Pullin' a flat out stupid
stunt with Rocketman like that?
I mean, thanks
for savin' us and all.
Hey! You hear me? Get up!
Please! Don't die!
Don't die, you old hag!
Bloody noses!
You're damn lucky a
bloody nose is all you've got!
Alright! We made it!
Guess he's fine.
Thanks for the ride across,
monster granny!
C'mon you guys, get up already!
You've been through
worse than that!
Oh, sure, that's
easy for you to say.
You're made out of rubber.
We're lucky we're not
in pieces right now,
after a crash like that.
See? You're all just fine.
You know, you guys
are a bunch of weirdos.
It felt like I should
point that out.
There's a staircase over there!
We better move it if
we're gonna find Robin!
Not so fast!
What the hell is that?
Chapapapa! So you've
invaded the Tower of Law!
There's no point in going on.
You won't ever find Nico Robin!
Lucci's already taken her
to the Gates of Justice.
Oh, and the Chief's
with them, too.
Really? Thanks for telling us
where we should start looking.
Chapapa. Why'd I tell them that?
He's not too bright.
It doesn't matter.
I might have told you
where they're headed
but I'm not gonna tell
you how to get there!
And you'll never make
it past our CP9 agents!
We've been given direct orders
to eliminate you, chapapa!
Did he say eliminate us?
You want Nico Robin?
Then you're gonna have to
fight your way through each
and every one of our agents
if you want to succeed.
Duh. I liked it
better when you were
telling us things we
didn't already know.
Chapapa. You've got
some fire in you.
But, I've got one more
thing to tell you.
Well say it! We're listening.
Ah. Well, thank you.
Now. Gimme just a sec.
Take a look at this!
A key?
What's it for?
For all you know,
it might be the key needed
to unlock Nico Robin's
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
Sea Prism Stone?
It's a stone that nullifies a
person's devil fruit abilities.
It's basically the same as
when they fall into the ocean.
Well now we finally know why
Robin hasn't been fighting back.
I knew it wasn't adding up.
Yeah, she's not the
type to give up so easy.
I'm sure she'd be
mopping the floor
with their ugly mugs
if she had the choice.
She must feel so helpless.
Well, that sucks.
Even if you were
able to get past us
and save her in
some imaginary world,
that sea prism stone is
tougher than a diamond.
She'd have to live
with them on her wrists
for the rest of her life.
Chapapa. Why do I keep
telling them this stuff?
He really is dumb, isn't he?
So be my guest.
Go try to save her,
if you think you can!
Chapapapapa!
Fine! Gimme that key!
Guess all the CP9 guys
can use that move.
Don't be hasty.
You don't even know if this is
the actual key I've got here.
You have got ta be
freaking kidding me!
It might be a key to
another pair of cuffs.
For all you know! Chapapa-papa!
In this great Tower of Law.
There are five members
of CP9, including me!
And each and every member
has their very own key!
So let's begin a
game of hide and seek!
So you're saying we gotta
beat each one of you guys,
and then try every key
on her handcuffs?
And that's the only way we're
gonna find the real one?
What a stupid way
to keep us busy.
While we're wasting time
on your key-hunting game,
your chief is gonna escape
through those gates with Robin.
That's exactly the plan!
Why can't I keep my mouth shut?
Retrieving Robin is
our first priority.
If we focus on getting
Robin back first,
we can worry about
the keys afterward.
Let's just ignore that
weirdo and start searching.
Chapa! Chapapapa.
Hey, you've got some brains!
But I'm afraid if you do that,
then you'll leave me
with no choice.
I'll toss the key into
the ocean! Chapapa!
We're kind enough to give you
guys a sporting chance. See ya.
Hey! Get back here!
Hold on, Luffy!
Will you just wait a second?
Stop running and listen to me!
Let's decide what we're
gonna do before we split up!
Shut up! Just let me go!
Get ahold of
yourself, Straw Hat!
I'm guessing Lucci's
that pigeon guy?
Yeah, that's him.
From what that freak told us,
he's the only one they've
got guarding Robin.
Our best bet's to
send Luffy after them.
Luffy, since you're
raring to go,
you can hunt down
that pigeon guy.
Let me go! Let me go!
Excluding Luffy, we've
got a headcount of six.
And he said there are only
five CP9 agents with keys.
So I say we spread out,
take them down,
then catch up with Luffy.
If they drag her across those
gates, we'll never get her back!
It's a race against time!
Then let's get going!
Take 'em down, or we die trying!
Yeah!
Good luck!
Let me go! Let me go!
Excluding Luffy, we've
got a headcount of six.
And he said there are only
five CP9 agents with keys.
So I say we spread out,
take them down,
then catch up with Luffy.
If they drag her across those
gates, we'll never get her back!
It's a race against time!
Then let's get going!
Take 'em down, or we die trying!
Yeah!
Good luck!
Go, pirate guys, go!
You can do it!
Chimney? Gonbe? Where did
those two disappear to?
They must've taken
Robin this way!
They couldn't have
gotten too far ahead!
I'm not gonna let them take you
through the Gates
of Justice, Robin!
A secret passage way!
It's a secret passage way!
We found a secret passage way!
Cobwebs!
Candle-lit!
Slimy walls!
Dark and creepy!
Full of bats?
I'm starting to wonder how
far this thing really goes.
I hear something.
Nothing can stop me now!
Let's check it out!
There's no help
for you, Nico Robin!
You can keep wishing
for them to come,
but they'll never find their
way to the Gates of Justice!
Quit hiding from me,
you pigeon loving jerk!
Where are you?
It's gotta be this way!
Which way did they go?
It's gotta be that way!
Which way is it?
I bet it's this way!
Or maybe it's this way!
It's definitely
gotta be this way!
This way! Robin!
Your pirate friends can't
possibly follow us this far.
What a weird room.
This goes like this,
and that goes like that.
What d'ya think they're doing?
C'mon! Open already!
How cool!
I've gotta find the kitchen
before I do any more fighting.
I'm in serious
trouble if I don't.
Coup de Boo!
I need a bottle
and a half of cola
to properly fuel Coup de Boo,
and I've already managed
to go through a little
more than two of 'em today.
I gotta nab at least
three full bottles
if I'm gonna take on CP9.
There!
That's gotta be the kitchen!
Chapapapapapapapapapapapa!
You've come face to face
with the gossip
loving Silent Fukurou!
I suppose you want my key?
Great, just before
I could refill my cola.
Chapa.
What is this place?
It looks like some
kind of dungeon.
Yoyoi! You damn
despicable pirate!
Your hopeless quest for
your friend's freedom
has doomed you to die a
dreadful death by my hand!
Do you hear my words?
You're doomed! I said
you're doomed, doomed, doomed!
Yoyoi!
Geez, he's loud.
No one in there.
Nope. Not in there. And empty.
What's the deal? I can't
find anyone around here.
Not that I really mind.
So you're too afraid
to face the mighty--
--It's not empty.
He's asleep? Is he with CP9?
What? He just left the key out
while he's taking a nap?
My luck couldn't possibly
be this good, could it?
This is a golden opportunity!
This room better not be empty!
Dammit. I'm getting'
real tired of this.
What's wrong? Just relax.
Tell ya what.
I'll put on some tea.
Well that sounds wonderful!
Your swords are drawn.
You don't waste time.
They've been thirsty.
For the taste of blood.
Where the hell did
you fall from, Zoro?
I'm more interested to
know why you're with a wolf.
It's weirder that
you're with a giraffe.
I guess this means they
both have devil fruit powers.
Not what I expected from CP9.
Yeah, no kidding! Is this
place some kind of zoo?
On the next One Piece:
"Devil Fruit Powers!
Kaku and Jabra Transform!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!