[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[SANJI]
Island dead ahead!
Are you serious?!
Oh! An island...!
We found an island!
Hey, Nami! Did you hear that?!
This means we can
get you to a real doctor!
He'll fix you up...!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
Just go look.
Ahhhh! There it is!
Nami's saved!
I'm so happy!
Look at the... snow!
[DALTON]
That's far enough, pirates!
People! Well, that was easy.
Yeah, nice...
But, they don't
seem too friendly.
I'll only say this once.
Your kind is not welcome here.
Leave immediately.
We only came here
to find a doctor!
We have someone who's sick!
You'll have to do
better than that!
We won't fall
for that old trick!
That's great...
We barely said hello,
and they already hate us.
[VILLAGER A]
Get outta here!
Look out!
That was a big mistake!
‐‐[VIVI] Sanji, stop!
‐‐[SANJI] Jerk...
[gunshot]
[LUFFY]
"An Island without Doctors?
Adventure in a Nameless Land!"
Huh?
Vivi!
Why, you...!
[DALTON]
Ready... aim...
[LUFFY growls]
[VIVI]
No, stop it...!
Fighting is not going
to help anything!
I'm fine, Luffy.
It only grazed my arm.
It's all right. We won't land,
but can you please
call us a doctor?
Our friend is dying
from a serious illness.
I'm begging you...
please help us!
Vivi...
[VIVI] You are not fit to be the
captain of this ship, Luffy.
Not everything can be fixed
by rushing to start a fight!
We can't get into a fight here.
Think about Nami.
What would happen to her?
Yeah... right...
I'm sorry about that.
Please help us.
Call a doctor.
Our friend needs you.
[DALTON]
I'll show you to our village.
Follow me.
See... Just ask politely.
Yeah...
You're incredible, Vivi!
There is one thing I feel
I should warn you about, though.
The only doctor we have
here is actually a witch.
Huh? A witch?!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Everything about this
island is messed up.
What do you people call
this weird place, anyway?
[DALTON] Actually, this land
still doesn't have a name.
An island without a name?
I didn't know that was possible.
Aaaaah!
A bear! Hurry, everyone!
Pretend to be dead!
[DALTON]
A Hiking Bear.
He poses no threat.
Don't forget to bow.
It's proper manners.
[ZORO]
Nice...! That's much better.
Eh?
Quack.
[ZORO] Now I can finally get
back to some real training...
I was gettin' sick of that
modified training that I had
to do with my stupid injury.
Besides, just watching
the ship is boring as hell.
Maybe some ice‐water
swimming will help me clear
up my head a bit.
[DALTON] This is the
village where we live.
Its name is Big Horn.
Look at all the weird animals
walking around everywhere.
Yeah, this is snow country...
[SANJI] Look Nami, we've made it
to a village with people...
We're here.
[DALTON]
Thanks for the help, everyone.
IIf you're not a guard,
you can return to your work.
Are you completely certain
that you'll be all right
here by yourself?
They are pirates...
[DALTON] I believe these
people mean us no harm.
That's my hunch anyway...
You can trust me on that.
If Dalton says
they're all right,
then I think that
we should believe him.
They do seem to be
pretty harmless, huh?
Yeah.
[VILLAGER A]
All right, Dalton.
We'll leave them to you.
[VILLAGER 1]
Even so, be careful, Dalton.
[VILLAGER 2] Call us
again if you need anything.
You mean those men weren't
your land's security forces?
[DALTON] No they're
just ordinary citizens.
Come to my house for now.
Hey.
Look over there, Luffy!
It's one of those Hiking Bears!
Another one?
Hello, Dalton!
I heard that some pirates
landed on the island.
I hope everything's all right.
[DALTON]
Yes, everything's fine...
There's nothing to
be worried about.
Just want you to know, Dalton.
I'm looking forward to
the election in two days.
Everyone I've talked to has said
they're going to vote for you.
I'm sure you're not
serious about that.
I'm just an ordinary
citizen, that's all.
[DALTON] You can use
that bed over there.
I'm going to warm the place up.
[DALTON] I guess
I should introduce myself.
My name is Dalton.
I'm the captain of the
island's security squad.
Please forgive our
less‐than‐friendly welcome.
Excuse me, but may
I ask you a question?
Huh?
[DALTON] It's just that...
you look familiar to me
for some reason.
Uh, no... I just have one
of those faces, I guess.
Anyway, can you tell us
more about this doctor?
Or witch,
if that's what she is.
Nami's fever's gone up to 107.
[DALTON]
How long has she had it?
[VIVI]
It's been several days,
and it just keeps
getting higher.
[DALTON]
I see.
She'll likely die
if it gets any worse.
[VIVI]
Yes.
But we have no
idea what the illness is,
much less how to treat it.
We don't know how to help her.
We've got to find a
doctor as soon as possible!
Any doctor will do.
Where is this witch of yours.
The witch...?
Do you see those mountains
outside the window?
Yeah... I noticed them earlier.
[LUFFY]
Super Massive Snowman!
[USOPP] And the feared
snow beast, Snowzilla!
[LUFFY]
Yes!
Get in here before I kill you!
[DALTON]
Those mountains out there
are known as the Drum Rockies.
Look closely...
Do you see the castle
on top of the tallest one,
the one in the middle?
Castle?
[DALTON]
That castle has lost its king.
Much warmer!
[SANJI]
Yeah... I see it up there.
[VIVI] What's so important
about the castle?
[DALTON] That castle is where
our land's only doctor lives...
Dr. Kureha...
She's the one who
people here call a witch.
[SANJI]
What?!
Of all places, why does she have
to live on top of a mountain?
We need to call
her here right now.
Nami needs her help.
[DALTON]
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
there's no way to contact her.
[SANJI]
Huh?
You can't be serious...
What kind of doctor is she?!
Her skills as a doctor are
quite impressive, actually...
However, she's an
eccentric old woman...
She's nearly one hundred
and forty years old now.
Huh...?
[SANJI]
A hundred and forty...!
No wonder she doesn't
get around much.
[DALTON]
Oh, and one more thing...
She likes pickled plums.
[VIVI] What happens when
people here get sick or injured?
Doesn't she help them?
She comes down from the mountain
whenever she feels like it.
She looks around for patients.
She treats them.
Then... before she leaves,
she takes whatever she wants
from their houses as payment.
She doesn't sound
like a very nice lady.
It kinda sounds
like she's a pirate.
But how is a woman
as old as she is
capable of getting
down that mountain.
It's an odd rumor around here...
But several of the villagers
claim they've seen her at night,
riding a sleigh of some
kind through the sky...
They see her silhouette
when the moon is out.
[KUREHA cackles]
[DALTON] That's the reason
she is thought to be a witch.
There are others
who say they've seen her
with a strange creature.
A creature that none
of 'em recognize...
See...! I knew it!
A snow monster!
Where there's snow there's
gotta be snow monsters!
Oh, I knew there'd be one!
Oh no...!
Oh... no...! Oh... no...!
I don't wanna run into one...
[sobs]
Dr. Kureha is the
only doctor we have,
but she's still a woman I would
prefer to stay away from.
All we can do is wait
for the next time she decides
to come down the mountain.
Really?!
No, damn it.
We can't wait
here for that long.
Nami is getting even
worse as we speak.
Hey, Nami...
Nami... Wake up now.
Luffy, you idiot,
what are you doing to her?!
[LUFFY]
Hey...! Look, she's awake.
Here's the thing...
The only way to see the doctor
is to climb the mountain.
So we're gonna have
to climb the mountain.
[SANJI]
Are you crazy?
What about Nami?
How do you expect
to get her up there?
Easy. She'll ride on my back.
[VIVI] That's only going
to make her even more sick!
[LUFFY]
What's the problem?
I thought we needed to hurry.
We do, but you'll never
make it up there...
Look at how steep
and tall that thing is!
[LUFFY]
I can do it.
[SANJI]
Maybe you can,
but climbing that thing
would be way too hard on Nami!
[LUFFY] But look,
even if we fall or something,
we'll land in snow!
[VIVI]
That doesn't matter!
A fall like that would kill
even a healthy person!
[USOPP] Seriously, Luffy,
she has a really bad fever...
It's so high,
she's almost dying...
Don't you understand that?!
[NAMI]
I need to get over this thing...
...and quickly.
[NAMI]
We need to hurry...
...for Vivi.
Come on... Captain...
Let's go...
That's what I'm talking about...
Leave it to me.
[USOPP]
I can't believe this.
Now our navigator's as
crazy as our captain...
[SANJI]
You know you're in no shape
for a trip like this, Nami.
[VIVI]
Are you sure you'll be okay?
It'll take you
hours to get there.
[LUFFY] Hey, old guy,
gimme some meat for the road.
[DALTON]
Meat?
Right... I'm coming too.
Listen, Luffy...
Be very careful.
You can't fall even once,
or Nami is going to die!
Aw! Not even once?
[VIVI]
Hold still a second...
I need to make
sure that this is tight.
Okay, you're all set...
I'm going to
wait for you here.
If I came with you guys,
I'd only get in the way.
[USOPP]
Yep... me too.
[LUFFY]
All right.
Now you just hold on
tight to me, kay Nami?
[NAMI]
Mm.
[DALTON]
I guess you're set on going.
Huh?
I'm not going
to try to stop you,
but I will ask you to at least
climb up from the other side.
That way you can avoid the
Lapins that are on this side.
They're fierce,
carnivorous rabbits.
If you run into a pack of 'em,
you're as good as dead.
Huh?
Really...?
But we've gotta get up there...
We'll be just fine...
Right?
Yeah... fine.
[DALTON]
You can't be serious...
Do you know how easily
those things can kill you?
[LUFFY]
Nah, we'll be all right...
Now hurry it up,
Sanji, before Nami dies!
[SANJI grunts]
Don't say stuff like
that, you idiot!
Do you want to jinx us?!
[DALTON] Are you
sure they'll be all right?
[USOPP]
Well, it's not really those two
we need to worry about.
[VIVI]
Nami's the one in trouble.
I just hope her strength
can hold out long enough.
She's getting sicker
by the minute.
Why are you standing there?
Come on, inside...
It's cold out here.
Oh, no, that's really okay...
I want to stay out here.
Me, too.
[DALTON]
I see.
Huh?
Well, in that case,
I'll join you.
[DALTON] We did once have some
here on this island, you know.
Huh?
Some doctors...
However, all of them left some
time ago, for certain reasons...
They were very good at what they
did, while they were still here.
We were even well known
for the advanced medicine
that was practiced
on this island.
So what went wrong?
Few months ago...
we suffered a vicious attack,
and our country was destroyed...
destroyed by pirates...
Huh?
Oh man...
The whole country...?
[VIVI] So that's the
reason you acted that way
when we showed up?
[DALTON] Yes... After
the attack, the word "pirate"
still terrifies everyone
on this island.
I'm sorry about the
way we treated you...
Their group was small
as well‐‐only five people.
Their captain called
himself Blackbeard...
Their power was so
incredible, they destroyed
our entire country faster
than you would believe.
And there were only five
of them fighting...?
That's impossible!
Blackbeard?!
[DALTON]
What's more...
There are some here
who actually believe
that it was good
for the country.
What could possibly be
good about that happening...
That's crazy!
Who would say something
like that, anyway?!
[DALTON]
Thank you... I agree.
But they have their reasons.
The king who ruled here before
the attack was a horrible man.
His rule was despised
by all of the citizens.
Our country used to be
known as Drum Kingdom,
and our king's name was Wapol.
He was the worst
king imaginable.
[gasps]
Yes, I remember him...!
I know that man!
Not Wapol!
It feels like it's
gotten a little colder...
The wind's picking up, too.
So why don't you think about
putting on some real shoes?
Even seeing your
feet like that is painful.
[LUFFY]
No way. This is my police!
[SANJI]
Your "police"...?
I think you mean "policy."
[LUFFY]
Yeah, that's it.
So anyway, though...
Did you know this:
people in snow countries
never sleep at all.
Huh...? Why?
[LUFFY] Because if they do,
they'll freeze to death.
[SANJI]
Don't be an idiot.
Everyone has to sleep sometime.
[LUFFY]
It's the truth!
Someone told me a long time ago.
[SANJI]
Who, Usopp?
[LUFFY] No! I heard
it in a pub in my village.
[SANJI]
All right, then explain this:
What does that
Dalton guy have a bed for?
[LUFFY] Hmm.
I guess that's a good point.
[LUFFY] Hey!
Maybe it's for when he dies.
[SANJI]
That's ridiculous!
Okay, then...
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[SANJI]
Did you know this:
Women in snowy countries have
skin that's as smooth as silk!
[LUFFY]
How come?
[SANJI]
Isn't it obvious...?
Here, I'll explain...
When you get cold, you rub
your skin to warm it up, right?
It's always freezing cold in
snowy countries like this one,
so the women keep rubbing
their skin all the time...
And so it becomes all white
and silky‐smooth.
[LUFFY] Okay... but then
how come it's white?
[SANJI]
Because... the snow...
It's constantly falling
all over them,
so it dyes their skin all white.
[LUFFY] Jeez... You're
really dumb. Did you know that?
[SANJI]
Yeah... Give me a break...!
Like you're really one to talk!
[roars]
You're becoming
a pain in my ass!
[LUFFY] Really, what
was with that thing?
[SANJI] Nami... Just hang
in there a little bit longer...
We're going to get you
to a doctor, all right?
[LUFFY] The snow's getting
really deep around here.
[SANJI]
Hey, Luffy!
Try to run more
smoothly, will you?
You're just making
it harder on Nami.
[SANJI]
Huh?
What are these things?
[LUFFY] Well, they're big
and they're white,
so they must be polar bears.
[DALTON]
What's that?
You mean you know who Wapol is?
[USOPP]
Know who he is...?
We know more than that!
He's the pirate who attacked
our ship not too long ago.
But... I was able
to take care of him...
Now that I think about it, I do
remember him saying something
about heading to Drum Kingdom.
[VIVI] Yes. There's
no question about it now.
I remember it clearly.
I'm sure I met him once
at a monarch meeting
my father took me to.
I was still very young then.
But I remember it to this day...
A monarch meeting?
Uh!
[DALTON]
Who are you?
Oh! No. I, uh... Well...
The point is we do know Wapol...
We ran into him yesterday
when we were on our way here.
Yesterday...?
Are you sure about that?
But then... I don't understand
what's going on here...
He said he was a pirate.
He didn't say anything
about being a king.
He's just calling himself a
pirate as some kind of disguise.
In truth, Wapol is only
wandering the seas,
trying desperately
to return to this island...
[VIVI] So then, Wapol and the
people who were on his ship
with him were
kicked off the island
because they were no match
for the pirates?
Is that what happened?
That's not it...
No...
[gasps]
[DALTON]
When it happened...
When we were attacked,
Wapol's army
didn't even try to fight.
[VIVI gasps]
[DALTON]
In fact,
the second he learned how
strong the pirates were
Wapol grabbed his cronies
and ran like a coward.
He was the first one to abandon
the country and flee out to sea.
After that, the country
felt utter despair.
We were left behind by our king.
What sort of king would
do that to his country?!
[USOPP]
Huh?
A king abandoning his people...!
Just the thought of that
makes me absolutely sick!
Vivi...
[DALTON]
You're exactly right.
The one good thing that
came out of it, though,
was the end of
Wapol's tyrannical rule...
The people who are left on this
island have come together now...
We're trying to create
a new country.
So what we fear most right now
is the return of Wapol
and his followers...
The return of his brutal rule...
We can't afford for him
to come back now
with the country so unstable...
It would be the end of us.
We want to build ourselves
a new, peaceful nation
on this island!
Look out!
Seriously. How can
it move like that?
Is it a gorilla?
[LUFFY]
No, it's a polar bear.
It's a rabbit!
How did you go
from gorilla to rabbit?
[SANJI] These must be
the Lapins that Dalton
was telling us about!
[SANJI] Well, there
sure are a lot of 'em!
[CHESS]
Aaaaah!
Aaah...! Wapol, come quickly.
What is it now?!
Have you found
that pirate's ship yet?
No, that isn't it, Wapol...
At long last,
we've returned home!
We have?!
[CHESS] How many long
months have passed?
Wandering the sea...
That's our homeland...
It's Drum Kingdom!
[WAPOL] It truly is...
I can't believe it...
♪If there is a treasure
out there to be found,
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big place,
the oceans are wide,
Dumb luck alone
won't help you find it,
Just give up, it's astronomical.
Even so.
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on,
The laughter behind our
backs, it keeps us strong
It's too bad 'cuz we're still
sailing forward, so bon voyage!
Just leave us alone!
It may be foolish
chasing impossible things,
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream,
the more ambition
I'm gonna need!
It may be foolish
travelin' on, but I know
That I just gotta fight!
The farther the sea,
the greater paradise
We're gonna find!
Don't give up,
just keep on trying,
And you'll see that
you're closer to...
The horizon of your dreams!♪
[SANJI] Listen, Luffy, I don't
want you fighting these guys.
Do you understand?
[LUFFY]
Why not?
[SANJI] Nami will feel the
impact of anything you do.
She might die.
[LUFFY] Okay, I won't fight,
but what do I do?
[SANJI]
Just dodge.
Dodge and run,
but don't retreat.
You got it?
[LUFFY]
That's really hard to do!
[USOPP]
What?
You mean the witch is actually
in the next town over?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Are You Happy?
The Doctor Called Witch!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!