Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[PERONA]
It's him.
One of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
The Tyrant, Bartholomew Kuma!
If you could take a vacation,
Where is it you'd like to go?
[PERONA]
Stop screwing around!
I admit I was taken aback
when I realized who you were.
But I've got nothing to fear.
[PERONA]
Negative Ghost!
And Special Hollow!
[KUMA] Before you interrupted
with all that yelling,
I was simply going to
ask you where Moria is.
Where did she go?
You're the Cat Burglar,
aren't you?
One of the Straw Hat Pirates?
[NAMI thinking]
No way!
He just suddenly
appeared up there!
Did he teleport?
What does he want with Luffy?
I've got to go warn him.
Gotcha, Moria! You're mine!
What? I've been
chasing his shadow?!
Aw, dammit!
He tricked me!
"Oars + Moria!
The Most Heinous Combination
of Brains and Brawn"!
[LUFFY]
Stupid jerk!
When did he even have time to
switch places with his shadow?
Hey! Hold on!
Don't ignore me,
you dumb shadow!
No! Come back!
Or at least tell me
where the hell I am!
Hey!!
Aw, man, this sucks.
Everybody's countin'
on me to beat Moria
and get their
shadows back for them.
And I've gotta do it by sunrise.
Wait.
Why do we need
our shadows back by then?
Auuuugh!!
Oh, yeah!
The sun's gonna melt us.
We're gonna be dust if I can't
work this out before morning.
It doesn't look
like there's much time.
I gotta get moving quick.
This is bad. I've been
gone too long already.
What the hell...
How did things
turn out like this?
I guess I better
follow Moria's shadow
and just hope it's
going the right way.
Zoro!
We're just trying
to buy enough time
for Luffy to
get our shadows back!
It's not like
we need to defeat him!
I'm just finishing
the fight he started,
and I've got this new sword.
I couldn't imagine a better time
to see what it's capable of.
[USOPP]
Oh, c'mon! Don't be stupid!
[ZORO]
Oars!
You want a real fight?
Looks like you found one.
Let's see what you've got.
He's gonna fight
him on his own?
Give it a rest!
You're practically
begging to get flattened!
Can't you try out
that sword some other time?
I didn't notice it earlier,
but Shusui has a lot more
heft to it than my Yubashiri.
Never used a black blade before.
Zoro! Get out of the way!
[ZORO]
But with this weight...
Awesome.
He deflected the
punch with his sword!
[ZORO]
Three Sword Style:
One Hundred and Eight
Caliber Phoenix!
It's enormous!
Dammit! He almost had him!
I'm amazed he could dodge that.
That was stronger
than I expected.
The blade absorbed the slashes
of the other
two swords into one.
It's impressive,
but it still moves a
little too slow for my liking.
That just means
I've got some work to do
before I can fully master it.
The increase in
power sure is nice, though.
Let's just hope
I live long enough
to bring it under control.
You gave me one hell
of a sword, Samurai Ryuma.
You little guys are fast.
You coulda put
out my eye with that.
You runty bastard!
[OARS] I'm gonna
grind you down to goo!
[OARS]
I'll crush you!
Zoro!
Holy crap, is he alright?
[OARS]
Get back here!
[ZORO] I can't spend
the entire fight dodging him.
Why's he gotta be so big?
He's going down!
Three Sword Style:
One Hundred and Eight...
[OARS]
Crushin' time!
[CHOPPER]
Zoro!
That was close.
Let's see if
there's anything left.
Huh?
I didn't crush him?
How'd he get away?
Where is he?
I can't see with all the dust.
Three Sword Style:
One Hundred and Eight
Caliber Phoenix!
[OARS]
That was close.
Dammit.
Dodged me again, huh?
You're a real pain.
This pipsqueak
doesn't know when to quit.
He just keeps comin'.
Come on, Zoro! Don't push it!
You're just making things worse!
Even if you do somehow
miraculously take him down,
what's the point?
Luffy's shadow is the only
one we'll get back from him!
We don't even
have the slightest idea
where yours and Sanji's are!
If we really want to
get our shadows back,
we just need to wait here
until Luffy takes care of it!
There's no point
killing yourself
trying to take down
an undead giant!
All we gotta do
is believe in Luffy
and try to keep this
guy busy for a while!
[ZORO] I've got
plenty of faith in Luffy.
But I'm also aware of
Luffy's one major weakness.
It's trickery.
They've got an invisible man,
a girl who controls ghosts,
and a shadow master.
Trickery is the name
of the game on this island
and they're all
professionals at it.
It's safe to say
that none of them
is planning on
giving Luffy a fair fight.
I'm afraid that I must agree.
Yeah.
[ZORO] If they manage to
stall Luffy and the sun rises,
then we're screwed.
Him, me and the cook.
We'll melt until
we're nothing but ash.
Maybe we can't save ourselves,
but if we can get
Luffy his shadow back
he can lay this
damn island to waste.
Looks like we've
got maybe thirty minutes
before sunrise.
On the plus side,
that's some thick fog.
The sun's gonna have a hard
time getting through that.
So we're that close to dawn.
We should count our
blessings we've got this fog.
Can't say it's
much comfort, though.
The reality of melting's
starting to sink in for me.
How long have they
been standing there?
What the hell?
[ZORO]
What is this, an earthquake?
What's going on?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 369A] The ship's
not anchored, remember?
We're caught in another bad
current like the last one!
Hey! The sky! Look up!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 369B]
The sun's starting to come out!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 369C]
And the fog!
Why's the fog clearing up?
What's happening?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 369D]
Please tell me I'm wrong,
but do you think we could've
left the Florian Triangle?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 369D]
We have!
And it's all because
Oars was screwing around
with the helm earlier!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 369E] You're
right, it's all his fault!
Why the hell'd he
have to go and do that?
[WHITE SHIRT]] I'm tellin'
ya, somethin's wrong here!
Just look at the sky!
It's completely clearin' up!
[STRIPED SHIRT]
Oh, no, we're doomed!
It's all over!
Why's it gotta end this way?
[WHITE SHIRT]
Hey, you can't just give up!
You wanna die on
your hands and knees?
I'm not goin' out
without a fight!
Hey! Look up there!
It's Moria's shadow!
And it's headed
towards the mansion!
[STRIPED SHIRT] Is that
supposed to mean somethin'?
[WHITE SHIRT]
Idiot! Think about it!
Straw Hat's
not with him anywhere.
And his shadow's still
trapped inside that big guy!
Meaning he's gotta
be wandering around here
somewhere on his own.
[STRIPED SHIRT]
Aha! Now I get ya!
[WHITE SHIRT]
Alright!
Let's go tell the
captain and his crew!
We'll do everything we can to
help Straw Hat before dawn.
[STRIPED SHIRT]
Right! Good idea!
Master Moria!
We've got some serious trouble!
Thriller Bark
has come unmoored again!
We're on the move
and we've broken out of the fog!
And it's all Oars' fault!
[BAO, GYORO, NIN]
Master Moria!
So what,
stop screaming! Who cares!
It's not the end
of the world, you idiots.
We're pirates, aren't we?
The whole ocean is our home, no
matter where our ship ends up.
Yeah, but uh...
Time to shut your mouths.
I have the unexpected
pleasure of an important guest
and you're
rudely interrupting it.
So,
"Tyrant" Kuma.
What can I do for the only
member of the Seven Warlords
who chooses to obey
the government like a dog?
So, "Tyrant" Kuma.
What can I do for the only
member of the Seven Warlords
who obeys the
government like a dog?
The government considers
you a valued weapon
in their arsenal of goons,
but I can't say
I share their admiration.
I don't know
what you're plotting
but I'm sure
that I won't like it.
If you were to take a vacation,
where would you want to go?
Come now,
do I look like a fool?
I'm fully cognizant of the
powers you possess, alright?
Get to the point, did you
come here to fight me or what?
Speak your business.
Why have you gone to the
trouble of seeking me out?
I'm here to deliver a report.
[MORIA]
Well, let's hear it.
[KUMA]
As you know,
Crocodile has been
removed from his post
as one of the Seven Warlords.
It's been decided
who will replace him.
[MORIA]
Kushishi!
Why didn't you say so?
And who have they
chosen as his successor?
There are hoards of pirates
that would kill for the job.
You might not
have even heard of him.
His name is Marshall D. Teach.
Also commonly known
by the name of Blackbeard.
Blackbeard, huh?
You're right, I don't know him.
He was a member
of Whitebeard's fleet,
second division.
He's only recently
proven his abilities
that led to his appointment.
Black Vortex!
St. Elmo's Fire!
Darkness take you!
Great Flame Commandment!
Flame Emperor!
I suppose the news hasn't
reached these foggy waters yet,
but his powers have raised
a great deal of commotion
throughout the world.
[MORIA]
Have they?
What was the
original bounty on his head?
Zero.
[MORIA] How impressive.
A total unknown.
I'm surprised
that the government
approved him for the job.
Kushishi!
They're probably happy
they managed to find someone
to fill the spot so quickly.
I expect that
this is supposed to
restore the balance of
power or whatever, right?
Perhaps.
But if I were to place a bet,
I would say
it's the exact opposite.
Nevermind that, though.
There is an issue
we must discuss.
Something the world
government is anxious about.
After the catastrophic
events at Enies Lobby,
they're more concerned than ever
about the movements of
the Straw Hat Pirate Crew.
If they're following
the Log from Water 7,
headed toward Fishman Island,
there is a high probability that
they will find their way here.
If that's the case,
then I'm sure you can understand
what the World Government
is worried about.
It's the balance of power.
The government is
concerned the Straw Hats
will take out another
one of the Seven Warlords.
That would be most unfortunate.
You better be joking.
Do they think
I'm not up to the job?
I've never been
so insulted in my life!
They sent you here to protect me
against those pathetic nobodies?
[KUMA] If you think my
assistance could benefit you,
I'd be happy to
help if you but ask.
Just who the hell do
you think you're talking to,
you bastard?
Have you even seen their crew?
A bunch of crackpots
led by a rubber doll!
And you honestly don't
think that I can handle them?
No battle is
100 percent guaranteed.
Do you know what
transpired at Enies Lobby?
No one expected
Rob Lucci to lose.
And I'm sure he wasn't
expecting it, either.
Jet...
...Gatling!
Let me see
if I get this straight.
The government's
so scared of the Straw Hats
that they wanna pit two of the
Seven Warlords against them?
Huh?
[KUMA] They only
sent me here to warn you.
I was given no specific orders
to offer you any assistance.
[MORIA] Then I recommend you
stay out of my damn way, buddy.
And if they want some kind of
report, you can tell 'em this.
This Straw Hat
that's got the government
soiling their britches,
I've already dealt with him!
That means I stole his shadow
and made it a
part of my zombie army!
Kushishishi!
[FRANKY] The fog.
Could it get any worse?
That fog was our last hope.
There's nothing
left to block the sun now.
Perfect.
The fog cleared up
at the worst time possible.
I'm really not looking forward
to the sun melting my face off.
Dammit.
Well, this changes
the situation.
At this point, we've
got no choice
but to try and stop Oa...
[MORIA]
Kushishi!
I didn't know it was
such a beautiful night out!
It's... Moria. It's Moria!
Moria? What, where?
[SANJI]
What? You're kidding, right?
[MORIA]
Dawn is just around the corner.
Do you think
this is the best time
for you to be
standing around?
Wait, how are you here?
What happened to Luffy?
Huh?
I hear Master
but I can't see him.
Explain this, Usopp.
Just where the hell
are you seeing Moria?
Look up, you idiots,
he's right there!
The belly! Inside Oars' belly!
Inside his belly?
He... He is!
Kushishishi!
That twisted Hogback.
He's gotta be behind this.
What exactly is
he doing inside him?
But where's Luffy?
Aw, don't tell me
they tricked him after all.
Or he's done for.
Don't you ever
say Luffy's done for!
Sure.
I don't get what's goin' on.
How come I can hear Master's
voice but I can't see him?
Is that some kinda
cockpit or somethin?
Crazy. Has there always
been a cockpit in there?
Kushishi!
Hey!
It feels like
it's pretty comfy.
I wanna see da inside.
Hey! Back off, moron!
Don't jam your fingers in here,
you'll break something!
[OARS]
Sorry. Yes, Master.
But really. This is so awesome!
I'm like a robot now!
Activate power, giant robo!
[beeping noises]
Look out!
Behold, zombie robot!
I am called, um,
da Oars Bomber! Yeah, that's it!
[USOPP] What the hell
does that even mean?
Oars Bomber?
You're no robot,
you're a zombie!
And robot sounds are like...
[mimics robot]
That's what I'm talkin' about!
My robot sounds
are better dan yours.
Calm down, Oars!
If you don't quit messing
around, you're gonna fall over!
Oh, right. Sorry, Master.
Alright, you pathetic
Straw Hats, here I am!
You wanted a chance to
fight me, you've got one!
And if you prove yourselves
skilled enough to defeat me,
I'll release all of the shadows!
Go ahead and
come at me all at once.
But you'll have to
take down Oars, too.
That's the only
chance you've got
to pull me outta this cockpit!
Now that's cheap.
You're not fighting fair!
The only way to defeat
Oars is to defeat Moria first.
But how the heck can we do that
with him inside his stomach?
This narrows
our target down to one.
Quit complaining.
Can't get cold feet now.
Hey Usopp!
That little pinch
didn't work earlier.
So you're gonna have
to find a mountain of salt!
Our only chance is
to purify that monster.
We'll try to weaken him as much
as we can until you get back.
Hell yeah!
That's a plan I can get behind!
Let's do this.
Yeah. 'Kay,
I got it! I'll be right back!
If I remember correctly,
there's a kitchen somewhere
at the front of the mansion.
They should have
lots of salt there!
I should've figured as much.
The first thing
they're trying to do
is get their hands on some salt.
Oars. Ya hear that?
Better make sure long nose there
doesn't make his
way to the kitchen.
Ya might as well take out
the entrance to the mansion.
Right. I'll get him.
Usopp!
[SANJI]
Did he get him?
Usopp!
[CHOPPER]
Kushishishi!
This is bad.
With Moria inside Oars,
that idiot
actually has a brain now.
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
Answer me! Where are you?
[BROOK]
He's perfectly fine!
I thought we might
need a hefty quantity of salt,
so I rounded some up!
[FRANKY, ZORO, SANJI,
CHOPPER, ROBIN] Brook?
That was a close one!
[BROOK] Were you expecting
someone else to rescue you?
[LUFFY]
Who are you guys?
[RISKY BROS.]
We're the Risky Brothers!
We're gonna give
you incredible powers!
[LUFFY]
You what?
Whoa, wait.
Stop that!
[RISKY BROS.]
What do you think?
[LUFFY] I feel incredible!
Nothing can stop me!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"A Secret Plan
to Turn the Tables.
Nightmare Luffy
Makes his Appearance."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!