Long Nose?! Is that you?!
Now, Mr. Wet Noodle,
while we're at it,
try this one on for size!
Ramen Kenpo!
Multi-Noodle Spank!
A chef must fight without
using his hands or knives.
Those are sacred.
So it's always been my policy
not to use them in battle.
But, since we're in a kitchen
and you're using
food as a weapon.
That changes things
a bit, now doesn't it?
It's time for a demonstration.
This is how a real chef
gracefully handles
his kitchen knives.
I've had enough of you!
Likewise!
What the hell are you?!
Where'd all that
kenpo spirit go?
You gotta burn off all
those carbs, you know.
Damn it you crook cook!
Don't talk saucy to me!
My awesome noodle
fists are all gone!
What am I?
An onion?!
If you're an onion,
you're gonna make yourself
cry if you keep this up.
Just quit while you're ahead.
I won't cry and I won't quit!
Who said I was gonna lose?!
After all, I'm Wanze, CP7's ace!
I may look like I'm having fun,
but I take this
mission very seriously.
The government's been
chasing Robin for years
and I'm not gonna
be the one to blow it
now that we finally have her!
So maybe you're the one
who should quit
while you're ahead!
Now Ramen Kenpo!
Noodle Nail Knockout!
When cutting an onion,
you need to sever the stem
and the root without
harming the flesh.
If you chop through the
fiber with one clean stroke
the surface will
retain its glossy shine.
Stop it!
Go away!
Ramen Beam!
Epluchage!
You know, I wouldn't expect
it of a third-rate cook
that blows ramen out of
his nose but I have to admit,
he takes good care
of his kitchen knives.
Well?
You like my star shield?
What's up with this guy's body?
There's no way a human
could do this stuff!
Spitting fire again?!
Master Nails!
Moon Walk!
Hey, stop jumping around!
We're getting nowhere!
I was hoping my Four
Powers would be enough,
but I guess not.
I'm afraid I haven't mastered
the Finger Pistol yet.
But I've got a little stand-in
that should do the
job quite nicely.
All right!
This is my chance
to go to the next car!
Hey, I thought we were
having a fight, here!
He thinks he's smart.
I got you now.
Beans Left!
Nice try.
But I saw that coming
from a mile away!
That hurt!
I get it.
You son of a bitch,
Ouchie Finger!
Shave!
This ain't good.
He's got my number now.
Tempest Kick!
Just grazed me!
He sure moves
around a lot, though.
I know your weak point!
It's your back, isn't it?
And that's not
counting your brain,
which is an obvious
weakness, too.
At this rate, it's only a matter
of time before you're finished.
Don't get ahead
of yourself, pal.
I got a move that'll get
rid of my weak point easy!
Franky Invincible!
Eat that!
Now do you give
up, weasel face?!
That's so stupid, I don't
even have a comeback.
What's going on?
How did you get here
in the first place?
This is dangerous, you know!
Ma'am, I can hardly answer
if you bombard me
with questions like that!
Let's just calm down
and take it slowly.
Ah, shall I pour you
some coffee, perhaps?
Stop fooling around!
What are you?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Sniper King,
the King of the Snipers.
To make a long story short,
I've come to rescue you.
You're really serious.
I am not alone, of course.
Your friend Sanji and a
cyborg thug named Franky,
are currently engaged
in battle on this train.
They kept the enemy busy long
enough for me to come here.
Furthermore,
Captain Luffy and the rest
of the Straw Hats are following
closely on another Sea Train.
I hear he's bringing
a small army with him.
On my way here, I peeked
inside the other train cars.
Frankly, I believe
the four agents in
the car behind us may
prove too great a challenge.
If possible,
I would like to escape
with you before
Sanji has to face them.
Come, let's run away together!
What's the matter?
There's no need to worry.
I made all of the
necessary preparations.
Here.
These Octopu-shoes are for you.
If you use them on
your hands and feet,
you can climb through the window
and stick to the outer
panels of the sea train.
Quickly put them
on before they notice.
I won't go.
Why not?
I don't know why
you're doing this.
I told you very clearly
that I wouldn't see you again.
I said I would never
return to the Straw Hats!
The situation has changed.
They know why you
turned yourself in.
That Ice gentleman from the
shipyard clarified everything.
So he survived after all.
But still, that doesn't
change my mind.
I won't go with you,
no matter what.
Enough with that already!
Don't you get it?
They aren't so weak that
you need to worry about them!
What were you thinking,
accepting such a stupid deal
before talking to
the rest of the crew?!
You think they'd
be happy to go on,
knowing that
one of their friends
had thrown her
life away for them?
Now that they know why you left,
they'll follow you to the
depths of hell if they have to
and they'll bust every skull
they can on the way there!
You don't get it, do you?
That's the kind of guy Luffy is!
How many times do
I have to tell you this?!
Even if you think you can save
me, I don't want your help!
Don't you care how I feel?!
C'mon, gimme a break!
Hey, keep it down in there, you!
What's the matter?
Now that we're getting
closer to Enies Lobby
is that cool exterior of yours
finally starting to melt away?
Well, you can cry all you like
but there's no point
in lamenting your fate
after it's already been sealed.
Really, I'm fine.
Strange.
That's not the reaction
I was expecting.
I can't put my finger on it,
but there's something
different about her.
Maybe it's just my imagination?
I said I'm fine.
Now please, just leave me alone.
This is definitely fishy!
Why is she goofing off
at a time like this?
Rabbit Ears?
Hey!
Would you take this seriously?!
You can't just quit
'cause you were losing!
Get up and fight me!
I'll spit on you!
I'd watch my weasel mouth
if I were you, punk.
I'm not quitting,
I'm just getting started.
Anyway, this is
nothing but bad luck.
Well, bad luck for you, I mean.
I'm doing great.
Did I mention
I was super this week?
It's not a good time
to make me angry.
Let me ask you
something, brother.
Have you ever heard of the
creature they call a "Centaur"?
Hm?
You mean those
things that are human
from the waist up and like
a horse from the waist down?
Yeah, what about them?
Convert!
No way.
That's ridiculous!
Franky... Centaur Mode!
It's backwards!
Your head's supposed to be
in the front, not your crotch!
You call this backwards?
Just wait 'til I rearrange
your face, weasel boy.
Are we there yet?
Where's Bashing Tom?
It's Puffing Tom!
Anyway, get inside
before you catch a cold!
You just changed clothes and
you're soaking wet already!
I don't care.
It's more awesome up here.
Fine.
Now, Gum-Gum-
Three Hundred Caliber-Cannon!
Boom!
Splash!
Ah! You defeated me!
Would all of you
stop screwing around?!
We're bored.
Then polish your
weapons or something!
What's wrong with you?!
Uh yeah.
I tried to tell those guys
the same thing earlier,
but they wouldn't listen to me.
Hm?
Hey, check it out!
There's a train in front of us!
It's the Puffing Tom!
Seems a bit early
don't you think?
Who's in my arpmit?!!
Ahh!! I can't move!!
Dammit!
What's gonna happen to us now?
There's no engine on this car.
All we can do is wait it out.
Ah!
Another wave!
Whoa, this storm
is still pretty bad.
You think someone
will come save us?
We're in big trouble
if they don't.
Hey, guys, there's something
approaching from behind!
Really?!
It must be a rescue ship!
I don't think so.
Actually, it looks like it's
coming on the railway.
There's no way.
There's only one sea
train in the world
and we're on it right now.
Besides, it's Aqua Laguna.
No one could make it out
of Water 7 in this weather.
Well, if it's not
a train, then...
...what the heck is it?
That's the Puffing Tom all
right but it's just the caboose.
There's no engine!
And it doesn't look
like it's moving!
That can't be right.
What's going on here?!
Does this mean it
got detached somehow?
Maybe something happened
and Sanji and
Usopp are on there!
Big Bro Franky, too!
Well, I hope not, cause we're
about to crash into 'em!
Granny, hit the brake!
I already told you,
now didn't I?
We don't got one!
We're gonna crash!
Luffy!
What are you gonna do?
I'm flying over
to see what's up!
Now Gum-Gum Rocket!
There's something in the sky!
What happened?
Ow, ow, ow.
All right!
I made it!
Who the hell is this weirdo?!
Hello?
Sanji!
Are you in here?
Or Usopp?
Hey, Sanji!
You hear me?
Maybe over there.
Wait a sec.
I know that face!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
Hello?!
Are you there?
Sanji?
Shut up!
I can't hear!
B-Bring it on!
We're not scared of you!
Where's Sanji?
Wait, what?
I don't know who that is.
Sanji!
He's my friend!
Sorry, never heard of him!
Too bad.
See ya.
Shoot him!
Straw Hat's coming out!
Looks like they're shooting him,
and he's saying "no."
Well, whatever happened,
the train cars must
be full of Marines.
So what's the plan, Rope Man?
If we don't move
those cars outta the way,
we might get knocked off!
Holy crap, it is a
sea train after all!
They're gonna ram right into us!
Yeah and if they
don't slow down soon,
we're gonna get
smashed to pieces!
Let the Franky
Family handle this!
We'll dismantle 'em
before they can hit us!
Let me help!
I wanna break stuff too!
Hear that, men?
Get to work!
Yeah!
Hey!
Zoro!
Hear that, Roronoa?
He's calling for you!
Go ahead!
Cut 'em!
Okay.
That's it?!
Stop the train!
We'll die!
The ego of the entropic world.
Shall be rent in twain.
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
...Rashomon!
What?!
What?!!
Hey, if you're gonna do
something crazy like that,
you gotta warn us first!
You heard me say
"cut 'em" didn't you?
But I didn't think
he could actually do it!
Of course he could do it!
We'd be dead right
now if he couldn't!
Yeah, I guess that's true
but you're gonna
give me a heart attack!
He's got all that power and he's
not even the leader of the crew?
Good thing we made
friends with those guys.
Anyway, that was awesome!
Nice work!
I still can't believe
there was another sea train.
They might even catch the
Puffing Tom with that speed.
This is bad but if
those guys rescue
the prisoners on the train,
we're totally screwed.
There's no way
that's gonna happen!
Remember, we still have
one last line of defense.
He's waiting for them!
That's right!
As long as we have
him in the Navy,
justice will always
find a way to win!
All right, here goes!
Two-Sword Style
Sword Draw Rashomon!
Hey! You're supposed
to be the train!
No way!
I wanna be Roronoa!
Don't be a baby!
I don't wanna get cut in half!
Sure you do!
No way!
Hey guys!
We're not done yet.
What the hell is that?!
It's a Sea King!
That giant monster was--
Sashimi!
It's split in half!
Let's grill it up!
Someone killed that giant thing?
It was big enough to swallow
up Rocketman in one gulp!
There's someone
waiting on this railway.
Someone who can cut
Sea Kings in half.
Who the hell is that?!
Ahh!
That's the Ship-Slasher!
Ship-Slasher?
Ship-Slasher T-Bone!
A Captain from
Navy Headquarters!
He uses a straight sword to cut
through ships like a raw steak!
Sounds like fun.
Hey, Steak Man, draw your
sword, or get outta the way!
On the next One Piece:
"Clash! Demon-Slasher Zoro
vs. Ship-Slasher T-Bone!"
I'm gonna be
the King of Pirates!