[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[GENBO]
Laki!
[OHM]
You look so sad dangling there
while all of your
hope drains away.
That stuff important
enough to die for?
[LAKI grunts]
[KAMAKIRI]
Laki!
[LAKI gasps]
Kamakiri!
[explosion]
[USOPP] I figured since
I wasn't doing anything anyway,
I'd start hauling this wood
over to the ship for repairs.
You're gonna
swim over there, huh?
Yeah.
So you don't have a
problem with the giant sharks?
[NAMI] This is what Jaya
looked like 400 years ago.
Neat! It's a skull!
It is a skull!
Well?
[LAKI] Kamakiri. You shouldn't
even be standing right now.
[KAMAKIRI]
I can still fight.
[KAMAKIRI] You're right about
this being our best time
to strike the Upper Yard.
With Satori gone,
we proved today
that we can defeat
the remaining priests.
I say we attack again
tomorrow, at first light.
[LUFFY] "Enter God Eneru!
Farewell to the Survivors!"
[USOPP]
Aww, come on, Zoro, be a pal!
[ZORO] Forget it!
I'm not going with you!
If you're scared,
just hold it till morning
and quit whining, you big baby!
[USOPP whimpers]
I would if I could, believe me!
[ZORO]
Just go take a leak by yourself!
[USOPP groans] That's cold,
Zoro. That's really cold!
--[footsteps crunching]
--[CHOPPER snores]
--[ZORO sighs]
[footsteps continue]
[USOPP]
--[thump]
--[USOPP gasps]
--[USOPP] What was that noise?
[thumping]
[USOPP whimpers]
There shouldn't be anyone
on the ship at this hour.
Jeez, this fog is
so thick I can't see who it is.
[USOPP yelps]
[thumping]
[USOPP gasps]
[USOPP whimpers]
[screams]
[USOPP screams]
[ZORO grunts]
Huh?
[USOPP whimpering]
What's your problem, you moron?
Did you fall asleep mid-piss?
That's pathetic.
[whimpers]
I... I...
I saw... I...
Hey, Usopp,
would you snap out of it?
[USOPP]
I saw... a ghost...
A ghost. A ghost...!
[GEDATSU]
Why are we...?
--Hey.
--[GEDATSU growls]
If you're gonna say
something, spit it out.
Don't just stand there
chewing on your lip.
[gasps]
Ah!
[GEDATSU]
Ah... Sorry.
We all know why we're here,
because you let Wyper
get away instead of
killing him when
you had the chance.
Now God Eneru will
punish us all for your failure!
How 'bout you
just calm down there?
Let the Shandorians struggle.
You know as well as I do,
all their pathetic efforts
are doomed to fail.
And they will fall like mere
insects before our power!
Ha! Right.
Admit it, you still screwed up!
God Eneru should
have left it to me.
I could have taken care of
those Shandorians by now.
They'd be gone,
and I'd be reaping
the rewards for my victory!
Instead, I'm standing here
with you two fools
awaiting his punishment!
Please, Gedatsu.
There's no way you
could handle it alone.
You're stupid.
I'm what? [growls]
Both of you would do well
to remember where your place is.
If you're not more careful,
you'll lose control of
your mantora and end up
like that clod Satori.
I doubt either of
you wants that.
You're the one who needs to
remember his place around here!
[OHM growls]
[OHM] You think you're pretty
hot stuff since you got lucky
and beat that fool Gan Fall,
don't you, Shura?
[GEDATSU growls]
Amusing.
[ALL yelling]
[YAMA]
Your Majesty.
Your priests have arrived.
[ENERU]
Very well. Open the gate.
[gate creeks]
[GROUP growling]
[YAMA]
Not again.
What are you doing?
This is disgraceful!
[YAMA]
You should be ashamed!
Shut up!
These two have held
me back far too long!
Just let me unleash
my full power!
[OHM]
Hmph.
I could take care of
this whole island myself if it
weren't for these two bunglers
always getting in my way!
Hah! That's some
big talk, Shura.
Maybe it's time for me to teach
you what the true meaning
of power is if ya think
you've got the guts.
Let's see if you can handle,
heh, the Ordeal of Iron.
Your Ordeal of
Iron couldn't even
test the strength of a child!
[GEDATSU] My Ordeal of Swamp
is the ultimate challenge!
Try that if you're
not too afraid!
My Lord Gedatsu,
that looks extremely tiring.
If you want to cross your arms
you need to hold them like this
and rest them on your chest.
Ah! Hey!
Enough! Cease this chatter!
You're standing in the
presence of God himself!
Really? I see an empty chair.
I don't see
anyone sitting in it!
Yes, if he really
summoned us here,
why doesn't he show himself?
Yeah, where is God Eneru?
[GEDATSU grunts]
Surprise, boys!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[ENERU grunts]
[yelling]
You asked?
Here I am.
You boys are getting slow.
You're out of practice.
If that pathetic display
is any indication,
you're all well on your
way towards ending up
dismal failures like Satori.
[GEDATSU growls]
What is the meaning of this?
Why, God?
Why do you mock us?
Is that the reason
you summoned us here?
To entertain yourself?
[ENERU]
I was bored.
[chuckles]
Now have a seat.
You don't seem to have
given too much thought
to the Blue Sea
dwellers yet, have you?
[OHM] God Eneru, if this
is about Satori's failure.
[GEDATSU] That idiot
was too inexperienced.
[SHURA] And that ridiculous
Ordeal of Spheres! Ha!
You're hardly in
a position to talk, Shura.
Gan Fall still lives.
That's impossible!
I tell you I killed
the man myself!
[ENERU]
You injured him, certainly.
But he's far from dead.
What's more, he seems
to be hitting it off quite well
with the Blue Sea dwellers.
What a stubborn old man, eh?
[chuckles]
And just what is it
these Blue Sea dwellers
are looking for anyway?
Why, they are looking for gold.
That's obvious.
What, gold?
Impossible. How?
How did they know?
[ENERU] This island was
originally part of the Blue Sea.
It's not so odd that they
should know about it.
Of course,
they'll move tomorrow.
As will the Shandorians.
[ENERU] The rules state that
you each run an area of
the Upper Yard, and you're
not allowed to enter
each other's areas or interfere
with one another in any way.
Tomorrow, I'll allow you
to go where you will.
You may set up your
ordeals wherever you want.
There will be no restrictions.
Get as vicious as you like.
Why are you being
so generous all of a sudden?
Because, my friends.
I am pleased to announce that
the Maxim is almost complete.
So it's time
for us to put an end to
this wretched island and
set forth on our journey
to the world of dreams!
[GAN FALL] To think that these
children could defeat Satori.
[GAN FALL] They've managed to
set Eneru against them for sure.
And if I know the Shandorians,
they won't pass up this
chance for another attack.
[USOPP whimpers]
[GAN FALL] Eneru. I wish I could
figure out what it is you want.
[WYPER]
We did put up a good fight,
and today, we will break
into God's Shrine!
[WYPER]
And then... Eneru.
[screams]
It's true! I wasn't dreaming!
Someone was here last night!
[STRAW HAT CREW]
The Going Merry!
She's been repaired!
[USOPP]
I knew it!
See, guys?
I told you I wasn't insane!
[whimpers, sobs]
[NAMI]
I don't believe it.
The mast is fixed.
Hey, now that's service!
[ROBIN giggles]
You can say that again.
Can you imagine
what a chore it was
just to stand something
this heavy upright?
Well, I hate to say it,
but they did a lousy job.
Well, whoever
did it sure is nice!
[laughs]
[USOPP] There was somebody here.
I knew I saw him!
But who'd risk crossing a
river full of skysharks to come
all the way out here
and fix our ship for us?
I mean, as far as we
can tell, the only people here
on Upper Yard are
us and our enemies.
Hey, did you notice
they took all the flying gear
off the ship? That's weird.
[USOPP] Hmm... Yeah,
I been thinking about it,
and it's really
got me wondering.
Huh. It just doesn't
make any sense to me.
How could this phantom repairman
know what the Merry's supposed
to look like?
How'd he know she
didn't always have a comb,
or wings, or a tail?
[CHOPPER] Who'd you see,
Usopp? Who was it?
I still say he was
partying too hard
and was having a nightmare.
[gulps]
[CHOPPER grunts, laughs]
[NAMI]
And why are you two goofing off?
There's lots of work to do.
Or did you forget?
[ZORO growls]
But Nami, aren't you
even a little bit curious?
'Bout what?
[CHOPPER] About who fixed the
Going Merry for us, what else?
[NAMI]
Who cares?
If they wrecked it, that'd be
another thing, but it's fixed.
What, do you want to track
them down and thank them?
Well, no, but I...
[USOPP] Hmm... How could
he possibly have known?
C'mon, Merry,
just tell me who I saw.
[BOTH]
Hmm.
Right! Pay close
attention as I,
Usopp the Mighty, chief
operating officer of Operation
Get the Going Merry
Off that Stupid Altar,
swing into action!
[CHOPPER] I'm assistant chief
operating officer for Operation
Get the Going Merry
off that Stupid Altar!
Everyone's counting on me!
[NAMI]
Hey, what are you doing?
You got a plan, Usopp?
Heh. Uh...
[USOPP]
All right.
Chopper!
[CHOPPER]
Hmm!
[USOPP growls]
All right!
Go!
Ha-ha!
[STRAW HATS laugh]
Okay, Chopper!
Give 'er all you got!
Awesome! You're awesome, Usopp!
[laughing]
[ALL]
Uhh...
[CHOPPER, USOPP groanin]
[yell]
[CHOPPER]
It didn't work, Usopp. What now?
[USOPP]
Don't worry about it.
I've devised a cunning
super-secret backup plan
for just such an emergency.
Oh, boy, can you
tell me what it is?
[USOPP]
Sure!
This river is full of
huge skysharks, right?
I'll say!
There's swarms of them!
[USOPP grunts]
So what if we used their power?
The sharks' power? Yeah!
That's a great idea, Usopp!
They've got lots of power!
[USOPP] Thanks, Chopper! 'Cause
I've got a little job for you!
[USOPP chuckles]
Just name it!
You can count on me!
I'll do anything!
[chuckles]
That's the spirit!
Ah, Usopp? About this plan...
Did I miss something?
No, no, you're
doing great, keep it up!
The sharks will try to eat you.
[CHOPPER]
Y-You mean I'm bait?
No! No! I don't wanna be bait!
I don't wanna be eaten! I re--
[screams]
[SKYSHARK roars]
Let'er rip, Sanji!
[SANJI growls]
[grunts]
[CHOPPER screams]
[SKYSHARK roars]
[shrieks]
[sobbing, yellin]
[SKYSHARK roars]
[USOPP gasps]
[CHOPPER sobs]
Okay, shark,
it's time for dinner.
[CHOPPER screamin]
[shrieks]
[wails]
[screams]
Come on!
[SKYSHARK roars]
[CHOPPER shrieks]
[LUFFY laughs]
[CHOPPER wails]
[sighs]
All right!
--Okay, Usopp!
--Atta way, Usopp!
--You're the best, way to go!
--You show 'em, buddy! Yeah!
That's the way you get
a ship off a stupid altar!
[laughs]
[CHOPPER whimpers]
[shrieks]
[NAMI]
Okay, let's look at the map.
The exploration team will be
taking this route moving south.
There should be
some old ruins near
the skull's right eye.
Keep an eye out for enemies
and bring back that gold!
[ZORO]
Heh. You make it sound so easy.
[ROBIN] I'm looking forward
to investigating those ruins!
Hold on, you're the one
who keeps talking about gold
and more gold,
but you're not coming?
Well, of course not--
it's way too scary!
[CHOPPER]
She wants the gold,
but she doesn't want
to risk anything to get it?
That's just too weird!
Did you say something?
[CHOPPER whimpers]
Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh...
[NAMI] We'll be in danger,
too, you know.
We'll be taking the Merry
down river through the island.
Then, we'll head for
the beach near the ruins
as fast as possible.
[NAMI]
We can meet up here.
And then we can escape
this stupid sky island!
At long last, we'll be a rich
and powerful pirate crew!
Able to buy anything!
Oh, yeah!
All the meat I can eat!
[USOPP]
Escape. That sounds great!
[CHOPPER]
Just don't make me the bait!
[USOPP]
Look! The weather's perfect!
[SANJI] Sure, we're
on top of the clouds.
[ZORO] Okay! We'll all meet
safely on the east coast!
--[USOPP] You bet!
--[LUFFY] Let's get going, then!
[CHOPPER]
Yeah!
[GEDATSU growls]
[SHURA] Who will fall
before my Ordeal of String?
The Shandorians or
the Blue Sea dwellers?
[ENERU]
And so the festival begins.
Magnificent.
Today will be a great day.
[yawns]
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[LUFFY]
Okay! Let's go get that gold!
[NAMI]
I'm counting on you!
Once we have that gold,
we'll finally be rich pirates!
[ZORO] Looks like things
are about to start
getting interesting!
[LUFFY] Bring it on, sky island,
we can handle all you've got!
[CHOPPER]
You guys are the greatest!
You can count on me
to do my best!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Giant Snake Bears Its Fangs!
The Survival Game Begins!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!