[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
That scent is...
Wapol!
Huh?
Doctorine!
There's trouble! He's here!
Wapol is back!
Is he?
It's him!
The guy with the annoying mouth!
[laughs]
I have returned finally!
Now, at long last, we shall
restore Drum Kingdom!
[laughs]
[CHESS]
But Wapol, sir!
Look! On top of the castle!
[WAPOL]
Hm?
Why is that strange
flag flying?! It's an outrage!
Where's the flag of
the Drum Kingdom?!
[KUREHA cackles]
That old thing? I burned it.
[WAPOL] Well, Kureha, the last
survivor of our doctor hunt!
Get out of my castle!
[KUREHA] This castle is
no longer yours, Wapol!
It saw enough corruption
and misery during your reign!
Leave!
Not just here‐‐
the country, too!
Drum Kingdom has
already died out, moron!
What's that?
[LUFFY]
Wait!
‐‐[KUREHA] Hm?
‐‐[WAPOL] Hm?
This guy is mine!
[LUFFY]
"Fight Wapol's Crew!
The Power of the
Munch Munch Fruit!"
[LUFFY]
Gum Gum...
Wapol, sir! Look...
It's the Straw Hat!
[yells]
‐‐[WAPOL screams]
‐‐[LUFFY] ...Pistol!
[screaming]
[CHESS, KUROMARIMO]
Wapol!
[CHESS]
That was close...
[LUFFY] I'm really sick of
you guys, you know that?
[LUFFY]
What's your problem?
You were getting in our way even
before we got to this island!
[SANJI]
Hmm? Not these guys again!
[yelps]
[LUFFY pants]
Last time I ran into you,
I couldn't fight 'cause
I had to protect my friends,
but now... Ooooh, you guys
are so gonna get it.
[chuckles]
[KUROMARIMO]
How dare you!
Do you know who you attacked?!
This is no lowly commoner‐‐
this is Wapol,
the king and absolute
ruler of Drum Kingdom!
[CHESS]
That's right! Show some respect!
He's this country's monarch!
How dare you do such a thing
to his most excellent
of excellencies?!
For shame!
Who cares?!
He ticked me off again!
[KAREHA]
So I take it you've run afoul
of Wapol before, young man?
I sure have! He's that
annoying big mouth pirate!
[KUREHA]
What'd he do?
He ate part of our ship
and then he attacked me
and my friends!
This guy's got it comin'
and I'm gonna give it to him!
[SANJI]
'Kay, but before you do that,
aren't you cold in that get‐up?
[LUFFY]
Hmm?
[SANJI]
Y'know, cold?
Hey! Did he say
he was the king?!
But I thought he was a pirate!
Took you long enough!
Hah! So you're
disrespectful and have wax
in your ears? But yeah,
Wapol is the king
of Drum Kingdom, Straw Hat...
When he met you before,
he was temporarily a pirate for
his own reasons, but no longer.
King Wapol's pirate days
are now behind him... And so...
He's returned to reclaim both
his castle and his country.
[LUFFY]
Whoa, it's freezing out here!
[SANJI]
You really are an idiot!
[CHOPPER]
Yeah, it's 50 below zero!
[CHESS]
I think they're ignoring us!
[WAPOL grunts]
You're awake, sir!
Straw Hat...
You've got some nerve...
Just wait... I'm gonna
bite you into pieces!
[SANJI] Um, sorry,
but you'll have to hang on
for just a minute.
He had to go get a coat.
[WAPOL]
Is this a joke?!
Tell me.
Your friend...
He can stretch himself.
How?
Huh, Oh, that?
It's because he's a rubber man.
[gasps]
What the heck is that?
It's a monster!
Well, well...
Looks like we're up against
that old hag, a reindeer,
and a few of the Straw Hats!
Not that much of a challenge!
This will be over quickly,
and once we've eliminated them,
there won't be anyone else
foolhardy enough to defy me!
Of course, my king!
Today will be remembered
as the day you restored Drum
Kingdom to its former glory!
[WAPOL]
I'll start with you, Dr. Kureha!
You've committed a major offense
by moving into my castle,
and even a greater one by
flying that strange flag!
It's not yours...
Not anymore.
It's Hiriluk's grave.
I wasn't interested
in this run‐down place,
what with all the bad
things you did here...
But we could use it
to do some good,
and the reindeer insisted on
flying the Doctor's flag.
[HIRILUK] And that's
why I raised this skull
and crossbones!
As a challenge to all
the diseases of the world!
[CHOPPER]
Skull?
[HIRILUK]
This symbolizes my belief
that nothing is impossible!
I will save this
country with my doctor's skills!
By raising this flag,
I vow to fight just like
the pirates do!
[CHOPPER] Doctor... He fought
to save this country...
By raising that flag...
I demand that you
take me to the patients!
I've come to save the 20 MDs!
[WAPOL]
You idiot! Don't you get it yet?
It was a trap!
The 20 MDs are fine,
as you can see!
[HIRILUK]
So that was it...
[HIRILUK] Good... Then
none of them are sick...
[DALTON gasps]
[HIRILUK] I was afraid...
this was a national crisis...
But no... luckily,
it was just a trick.
[guns clicking]
Hey... When do you
think a person dies?
[CHOPPER]
Doctor!
[HIRILUK] When a bullet from a
pistol pierces his heart? No...
When he's attacked by an
incurable disease? No...
When he eats a soup of
deadly poisonous mushrooms? No!
A man... dies when
people forget him.
[DALTON whimpers]
Even if I should
disappear right now,
my dream will come true.
And when it does, the
citizens' sickness of the heart
will be cured as well.
You're crying... Why, Dalton?
Is that... true for a country?
Yeah, if the will
to do it, is passed on.
[HIRILUK]
Don't worry, Chopper...
your mushroom won't kill me...
I've had... a marvelous life!
[KUREHA]
Goodbye, quack...
[HIRILUK]
Thank you, Chopper!
[CHOPPER] This castle
is where Doctor died...
He gave his life trying
to save this country...
[CHOPPER]
This place is his grave,
and a symbol of
what he believed in!
[laughs]
Ah! I'd almost
forgotten that fool!
[laughs]
How dare you
desecrate my castle
by flying the flag of
that stupid doctor?!
I command that
it be burned immediately!
[CHOPPER] I'll never
let you touch that flag
or get inside this castle...
[WAPOL growls]
Never...
Look, sir! He's that‐‐
You're right! It is him!
[KUROMARIMO]
He's that Doctor's monster...
...the one Dalton stopped!
That flag there...
It's a symbol of his faith!
I won't let you
take it down, not now...
...not ever!
[laughs]
We're going to take it,
and all of you down!
And we're going into the castle!
Show them no mercy, boys!
Old lady, are you
gonna fight, too?
"Old lady"?
‐‐[bonk]
‐‐[SANJI grunts]
[KUREHA] If they're more
than you can handle "junior,"
I'll step in!
[SANJI]
'Preciate that...
Don't you worry, sir!
We'll get them out of your hair,
and speaking of hair!
[CHOPPER]
Doctorine!
Hey, big man with the afro...
Didn't your mother ever
tell you it's not right
to strike a lady? 'Specially,
not a hot, young one?
[KUREHA chuckles]
Now that's more
like it, blondie.
[CHOPPER grunts]
[KUROMARIMO]
What's that?
Huh?
[SANJI] Damn! Why won't
this stupid thing come off?!
What's making it stick to me?!
Static electricity
or something?!
Exactamundo!
[laughs]
Dammit! Get off my leg,
you disgusting hairball!
[LUFFY] Cold... C‐Cold,
cold cold cold cold...
[whimpers]
Cold...
I need a coat really quick!
Any coat'll do!
[NAMI]
What's going on outside?
I heard a lot of noise.
[LUFFY]
It's freezing out there!
You seen any coats around?
I didn't ask that...
What I want to know is
what's happening out there.
[LUFFY]
Eh, it's just a fight.
[NAMI]
Oh... Do you guys need help?
[LUFFY]
Nah, stay in bed.
If you need a coat,
you can borrow mine.
What? But it's
a girl's coat and it's ugly.
Well, you did
say any coat'll do.
[LUFFY]
Oh, yeah.
Well, as long
as it keeps me warm...
Yeah!
[NAMI] Huh. I wonder what
all the fuss was about?
[LUFFY]
All right, big mouth!
Now I can finally
kick your butt!
I swear I'm gonna
smack that hairball guy silly
whenever I finally get
this nasty thing off me!
[KUROMARIMO chuckles]
Oh, well, in that case...
Marimo's Static Cling!
[SANJI]
Oh, gross!
[CHOPPER gasps]
Reindeer! Help me!
I'm coming!
Get these things off me!
Please...
[yelps]
‐‐Here!
‐‐No!
‐‐Quit!
‐‐Here!
‐‐No!
‐‐Stop!
‐‐You‐‐!
‐‐What's wrong with you?!
You keep them!
Will you two please
stop goofing around?
Ha! There's a reason
I don't keep my
hair conditioned!
And a very good
one at that, too.
Their dryness makes them burst
into flames, much easier.
Oh, no! He's gonna
burn these things!
Here!
[SANJI]
Huh?! Hey, what are you doing!
[CHOPPER]
Decoy plan!
Decoy plan?!
Wait, I'm the decoy?!
[CHESS]
Checkmate!
[SANJI yelps]
[SANJI]
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
[CHOPPER growls]
[WAPOL]
Move! Ah!
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[CHESS] Wapol!
‐‐Oh, no!
‐‐Chopper!
[CHOPPER grunting]
[LUFFY] This might be a girl's
coat, but it's really warm!
[gasps]
Luffy!
Grab my leg from there!
Leg?! Sure!
‐‐[LUFFY] Like this?!
‐‐Yep! Just don't let go!
Oh... Gotcha!
[SANJI]
Armee de l'Air Assault...
[CHOPPER yelping]
[SANJI]
...Gum Shoot!
[WAPOL bellows]
[WAPOL yells]
[KUREHA]
Hmph.
Not too shabby.
[WAPOL groans]
Thanks, you two!
You guys were so amazing!
Hey. Wait... just a minute!
Isn't that Nami's coat
you're wearing, Luffy?!
[LUFFY] Hmm. Whoa!
Big mouth's still alive...
...but his hippo's
headed to the moon...
Take it off right now, jerk!
Wapol, sir, are you all right?
We've underestimated them!
They're stronger
than we thought!
[WAPOL] Then it's... time to
bring out my big guns and...
My... bigger appetite!
[CHESS, KUROMARIMO]
Huh?!
I'll show them...
...the true power of
the Munch Munch Fruit!
Very good, sir!
That's right...
I'll show them the
Munch Munch Factory!
Oh, he stood up!
Yeah, but how?
You hit him pretty hard.
Guess... he's tough!
[KUREHA growls]
Hey, Chess!
Tell me what I ate today
and in the exact order
that I ate it!
Well, sir, you started
by eating two cannons
on the ship; one sautéed in
butter, and the other raw...
Then it was a cannonball
and gunpowder salad,
followed by the main course
of a toasted cottage.
[LUFFY]
And you thought I ate a lot!
[SANJI] You do, but this
guy's a bigger pig than you.
[WAPOL]
You see, Straw Hats...
Whatever I eat becomes
part of my body thanks to
the Munch Munch Fruit.
[chuckles]
What's happening?!
What the‐‐?!
[WAPOL]
Munch... Munch... Shock!
The Wapol House!
A house?!
Awesome!
Now, if you'll
please excuse me...
I have to eat!
[BOTH scream]
Behold the Munch Munch Factory!
[gasps]
[CHESS, KUROMARIMO scream]
No way...
[WAPOL munches]
He... He's eating his own men?!
That's so mean!
[WAPOL sighs]
He stopped...
[WAPOL]
Feast your eyes on this!
Come forth,
you miraculous union!
What kind of union?!
[CHESS, KUROMARIMO]
Allow me to introduce myself!
I am the strongest warrior
of Drum Kingdom...
[LUFFY gasps]
Chessmarimo! Hah!
[SANJI] "Miraculous union"?
More like ridiculous union...
[LUFFY]
Swee‐eee‐eeet!
It's ridiculous!
Just don't let your guard down.
[SANJI]
Hm?
They might look silly,
but don't be fooled.
They're tough...
So tough that the citizens
couldn't stand against them...
That's how these thugs were
able to exile all the doctors.
[WAPOL growls]
[CHESSMARIMO chuckles]
[chuckling continues]
Article One of the
Drum Kingdom's Constitution...
"Those who don't do as the king
wishes will be put to death."
That's the number one
law of this country!
You refused my wishes,
and broke that law!
Now you are all going to
be punished for your crimes!
But first, I'm gonna
deal with the matter of
that quack's flag
sullying my regal castle!
It's time I took
that thing down!
[CHOPPER gasps]
A pirate flag...
Hey, reindeer... That flag...
[HIRILUK] Nothing is impossible
for a man who raises
the pirate flag! Isn't that
what I told ya, huh?
[CHOPPER]
How dare you!
You attacked Doctor's
flag, you creep!
Doctor, tried to‐‐
He tried to save even you!
[HIRILUK]
Chopper...
[HIRILUK] Try not to hold a
grudge against us humans, okay?
[HIRILUK]
This country is sick right now.
The people and the
king both suffer from
a terrible sickness
of the heart...
[CHOPPER]
But this is Wapol, Doctor!
Someone as bad as him
isn't worth saving, is he?!
[WAPOL]
Hm?
I...
[CHOPPER]
I won't hurt you if you just...
...leave this country forever!
Chopper, what are you doing?!
Even if he does promise that,
you can't trust a word
that despot says!
[CHOPPER]
But... Doctor said...
[WAPOL]
Heh.
[gasps]
Chopper!
[LUFFY]
Hey, big mouth!
[WAPOL]
Huh?!
Straw Hat!
You guys weren't real pirates;
you were just fake ones,
weren't you?
That's why you don't know what
flying a pirate flag means...
'Cause you were just a
buncha fakes who didn't
risk your lives!
That guy...
[WAPOL] "What a pirate flag
means," Straw Hat?
[laughs]
Don't make me laugh!
Flags have no meaning!
[LUFFY] If you think that,
you're dumber than you look!
[WAPOL]
What?!
Listen! Pirate flags stand
for something, big mouth!
They're not raised
as some kind of joke!
Moron! The only
joke is that I've let you
live as long as I have!
Since you dared put
that flag back
after I knocked it down, it's
time I delivered the punchline!
[gasps]
Hey, you, look out!
Do your worst!
You can't break this flag!
‐‐[CHOPPER gasps]
‐‐Luffy!
Was he hit?!
He was blown to pieces!
[laughs]
[gasps]
[LUFFY] I told you...
you can't break it...
[WAPOL growls]
[CHESSMARIMO]
What?! How did he do that?!
It's impossible!
[LUFFY] I have no idea
who this pirate flag
originally belonged to.
But it doesn't matter...
A pirate flag
is someone's pledge
to risk their life...
It's not something to laugh at!
[LUFFY] It stands for something
that you jackasses will never
understand in a million years!
[CHOPPER]
Incredible... So this...
...is a pirate!
[LUFFY]
It won't break... Ever...
'Cause the skull on it...
...is a symbol of faith!
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[LUFFY]
That reindeer's amazing!
He can transform
seven different ways!
[SANJI]
He can really jump, too.
[LUFFY] I betcha he'll
shoot a beam next!
[SANJI]
No, he won't!
Hey, where'd that
tin‐plated bastard go?!
[LUFFY] He's not here?!
When did he get away?!
[SANJI] Probably when you were
gawking at that reindeer!
[LUFFY]
Where are you, big mouth?!
On the next One Piece!
"Zoan‐type Devil Fruit!
Chopper's Seven‐form
Transformation!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!