[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
Well, take your
best shot, big mouth!
You can't break this flag!
The skull on it is
a symbol of faith!
Luffy!
That was a direct hit!
[CHOPPER gasps]
[LUFFY]
"Zoan‐type Devil Fruit!
Chopper's Seven‐form
Transformation!"
[laughs]
He and that flag
were blown to pieces!
[laughs]
[gasps]
[CHESSMARIMO gasps]
[WAPOL grunts]
Told ya... See?!
What?! How'd he do that?!
It's impossible!
[LUFFY] I have no idea
who this pirate flag
originally belonged to.
But it doesn't matter...
A pirate flag
is someone's pledge
to risk their life, it's not
something to be shot at
or made fun of, jerks!
It stands for something
that you stupid jackasses
will never understand,
not in a million years!
[CHOPPER] Incredible...
So this is... a pirate!
[HIRILUK]
This skull! symbolizes...
...that nothing is impossible!
I will save this country
with my doctor's skills!
I vow to fight just
like the pirates do!
[CHOPPER]
What are pirates?
[HIRILUK]
They're dashing swashbucklers!
It's great to be a pirate!
The most amazing
people sail the seas!
Chopper... some day,
you've got to go!
[LUFFY]
Hey, Reindeer!
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
I'm gonna kick these
guys' butts for showing
your friend's flag
disrespect. You in?
Uh, me?
[WAPOL]
You idiot!
You just don't get it
do you? All right, then!
Since you feel so
strongly about that flag,
I'll destroy you along with it!
I don't think so... Tubby!
[bones cracking]
Looks like your
backbone gave out...
[SANJI groans]
[KUREHA] Your condition
will continue to worsen
if you keep moving...
So stop! Doctor's orders!
[SANJI groans]
[laughs
If you two want to
fight amongst yourselves,
then please, by all means do so!
But I hope you'll at least
watch your friend
and that flag get blown to bits!
Straw Hat! Say your prayers!
Stop it!
[LUFFY]
That's the spirit!
Go get 'em, reindeer guy!
[CHOPPER yells]
Wapol, sir! Watch out!
[KUREHA cackles]
Would you look at that?
The little furball's got more
courage than a full‐grown man...
[laughs]
I'm sorry, freak!
But there's no way
I'm gonna let you
lay a single paw, on our king!
Wow, there really are
some strange creatures
in this world.
You must be that yeti the
villagers hated and feared.
They tried to kill you
and chased you away, right?
[CHESSMARIMO] I bet
you've spent your whole life
all alone with no friends.
You're a monster.
Nobody likes you,
people want to kill you,
but here you are,
trying to save this country.
That's the stupidest
thing I ever heard!
[CHOPPER] Shut up!
Even if I don't have friends,
I can still fight for
something I believe in!
And as long as
the flag flies... I will!
[LUFFY]
Hey, that's not true!
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[LUFFY] You do have friends!
I'm your friend, reindeer! Me!
[yells]
[WAPOL grunts]
Oh, no! Straw Hat!
[LUFFY chuckles]
You should be flat as a pancake!
Yeah, but I'm fine
'cause I'm a rubber man.
Rubber?!
[CHESSMARIMO]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Hey, reindeer.
Can you finish off that
two‐headed guy for me?
That one over there?
Piece of cake.
Good, while you're doing that...
I'll take care of...
...this one!
You dare to knock me,
this country's monarch, over?!
You'll pay for that insult!
[CHOPPER]
I'm taking you down!
Is that so?
You and what army?
Huh, you little freak?!
[SANJI] Freak? That's like the
pot calling the kettle black.
[SANJI whimpers]
If you keep moving around...
...you may lose
the ability to walk,
so just stay down
there and shut up!
And don't worry...
When push comes to shove, my
li'l reindeer can hold his own.
Listen up! My name's
Tony Tony Chopper!
Not freak! It's a name the
world's greatest doctor gave me!
He was a wonderful man!
Even if he forgave you for
disrespecting his flag...
...I won't forgive you!
[WAPOL]
Hmph.
[LUFFY chuckles]
The only one who'll show
no forgiveness is me!
I'll stomp you!
Rumble Ball!
[VIVI]
Dalton, no! Dalton!
Please wake up!
Please Dalton! You have to!
‐‐Vivi...
‐‐[VIVI] No!
You can't die!
Dalton, please!
[DOCTOR A]
Don't worry. He's not dead.
[VIVI gasps]
[VILLAGER A]
The 20 MDs!
[DOCTOR B]
He will be if we don't act soon.
He has severe frostbite.
[DOCTOR C] We can begin
treating him immediately
if you'll let us.
[VILLAGERS murmurin]
Hey, what do you know?
There are doctors here...
That's funny.
I thought I heard there weren't
any sawbones in this country.
There are a few doctors.
These guys are the 20 MDs...
But they work
exclusively for Wapol,
so that makes 'em bad doctors!
That's right! We can't trust
any of you! Traitors...
You expect us to
leave Dalton with you?
You surrendered to
Wapol without a fight
and turned your backs on us!
Wapol probably sent you
here to kill Dalton!
[DOCTOR A] Please, if you want
to save him, just do as I say!
[DOCTOR A] The 20 of us
are still doctors...
Even though we were
forced against our wills
to serve only Wapol...
We've always worked to advance
our medical research...
For the benefit of all
the patients in this country!
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
It was all because of a...
...certain quack who
taught us to never to give up.
[DOCTOR A] We can't afford to
lose any more men like him...
So please, let us help!
[CHOPPER] The effect of the
Rumble Ball lasts three minutes.
All the time I need
to take you down!
[CHESSMARIMO]
Three minutes!
Ha‐ha! You couldn't defeat me
in three years,
let alone three minutes!
Just three? Amazing!
Just three? No way.
Well, all right, this should
be an interesting battle.
C'mon, you old bat!
Let me up so I can help!
[CHOPPER]
Rumble!
[CHESSMARIMO]
You're no match!
Not against this!
Marimo's Snow Melting Arrow!
[CHOPPER]
Walk Point! Leg Boost!
[CHESSMARIMO]
Hmph! Just a transformation, eh?
I was expecting something more!
All you have to show
are devil fruit powers?
You're a Zoan type,
just like Dalton!
So you're a reindeer human, huh?
[CHOPPER]
Heavy Point! Weight Boost!
No! I'm a human reindeer!
Same thing!
And I know everything
there is to know about
the three‐form transformations
you Zoan‐types use!
Marimo's Big Super
Surprise Quattro Hammer!
Speaking of surprises,
you've got none left
to spring on me!
I've seen all your forms now!
You're nothing more than
a power fighter like Dalton!
So there's no way you can...
Jumping Point!
Jump Boost!
[CHESSMARIMO]
...get the jump on me, freak!
[SANJI]
Jeez! That guy can really jump!
[LUFFY laughs]
[CHESSMARIMO]
What the‐‐?! I don't get it!
What is that form?!
Wasn't his "human‐animal form"
the little reindeer
from earlier?! What now?!
[CHOPPER]
Guard Point! Fur Boost!
Another form?!
[LUFFY]
Whoa! Awesome!
[CHESSMARIMO]
No way! I hit you dead on!
[CHOPPER]
It won't work!
How is this possible?!
You Zoan‐types have a three form
limit! What the heck are you?!
The Rumble Ball
is a special pill that enhances
the power of the Devil Fruit's
transformations...
Over five long years of
research, I discovered
four additional
transformation points...
Do the rest of the math
yourself, you jerk!
A‐A seven‐form transformation?!
[gasps]
[CHESSMARIMO]
That's impossible!
I don't believe it!
[gasps] A talking reindeer who
can change into seven forms?!
Your friend,
what's the matter with him?
[SANJI] There's just so much
happiness of meeting
a transforming reindeer
a guy can take.
[WAPOL]
You bastard...
Did you forget
about fighting me?!
[CHESSMARIMO] A seven‐form
transformation is impossible!
I won't be deceived by what
has to be an obvious sham!
It's not one!
[laughs]
[CHOPPER]
Arm Point! Arm Boost!
[CHESSMARIMO grunts]
[CHESSMARIMO]
Huh?!
[CHOPPER]
Could a sham do that?!
If you thought that was
something, you should see
what my iron hooves
can do against rocks!
Whoa...
Not my hammers! What nerve!
[CHESSMARIMO]
These'll teach you!
Marimo's Super
Surprise Quattro Axe!
[CHOPPER]
Hm.
[CHESSMARIMO]
Snow Splitting Blade!
[CHOPPER groans]
Wow! Damn!
That reindeer can
really take a hit.
[LUFFY gasps]
[KUREHA chuckles]
Damn! You dodged it!
Let's see you dodge... this!
[CHESSMARIMO]
Omnidirectional Snow Splitter!
[LUFFY growls]
You're gonna take me down, huh?!
You're not fighting;
you're just dodging!
Brain Point! Brain Boost!
[CHOPPER] I wasn't just
dodging your swings!
[CHOPPER] I was looking
for your weak spot!
[CHESSMARIMO]
What?!
[CHOPPER]
This'll finish you! Scope!
A... A beam!
He's gonna shot a beam!
[SANJI]
No, he won't, you idiot!
[LUFFY]
Hey, you, shut your trap!
I'm telling you,
it's gotta be a beam!
[SANJI]
How do you know that?!
Huh, Mr. Smart Guy?!
[LUFFY]
I just do!
[SANJI]
Fine! What kind of beam?!
[WAPOL]
The castle's unguarded...
[CHESSMARIMO]
Looking for my weak spot, huh?
Well, I've got
some news for you!
I don't have one!
Your little transforming parlor
tricks can't save you now!
And as you're about to find out,
you're the one who's
goin' to be finished!
[CHOPPER]
Found it!
His jaw!
[CHESSMARIMO]
Yah!
Huh?
Where'd he go?!
[CHOPPER]
Hoofprint...
[whimpers]
[CHOPPER]
...Roseo!
[groans]
[CHOPPER]
Ah. Three minutes.
Yeah! All right!
Wow! You were
incredible, reindeer!
No, you were more than that!
‐‐You were amazing!
‐‐Shut up!
[LUFFY laughs]
[DALTON groans]
‐‐Dalton... He's awake!
‐‐Are you okay?! It's a miracle!
[VIVI]
I can't take this anymore!
Let's go up the mountain!
Okay, Usopp?!
‐‐Mr. Bushido?!
‐‐[ZORO] Huh?
[VIVI] This sitting around and
waiting is killing me!
Luffy and the others could've
gotten hurt in that avalanche!
They might be trapped!
And don't forget,
Nami had a high fever!
If anything's
happened to them...
[USOPP]
You're worried about Nami...
And Luffy and Sanji
and Dalton...
...and what's going
on in Alabasta.
Vivi... Can't you see it?
You're carrying too many
burdens on your shoulders!
Calm down!
We don't need
to go up there at all,
and do ya know why?
Because those three are fine!
And that's Luffy and Nami
and Sanji we're talking about!
I believe in them!
[VIVI]
That's right... He's right...
[VIVI] You have to
have faith in your friends.
Usopp does and that's
why he can be so calm...
I get it now.
Thanks a lot...
You're full of wisdom, Usopp.
[ZORO]
No, he's full of crap!
He's just afraid to
go up that mountain!
[USOPP] But I heard that
there were things like yetis
and huge, man‐eating
bunnies up there!
I don't wanna get eaten!
Then say so from
the start, coward!
[USOPP] Okay! I don't
wanna be some monster's snack!
And I'm sure they're fine!
Luffy can work out anything!
[VILLAGER D]
Dalton, no!
[VILLAGER E]
Wait!
[DALTON groans]
Hey! It's Dalton!
Thank goodness!
Would somebody please
tell me who this guy is?!
[VILLAGER D]
Dalton! Listen to reason!
Get out of my way!
We can't let Wapol retake
the castle! We just can't!
Wait! You mean that's
where you're heading?
The castle?
In your condition?!
Are you nuts?!
My country is far
more important than my health!
He can not succeed!
I will not let that happen!
Not now, not ever!
Wapol must perish!
[gasping]
But you're not strong enough
to fight them in
your condition, sir!
[VILLAGER D] And the rest of us
are no match for them, either!
[DALTON grunts]
I'm going to settle this
thing once and for all!
I'll stop Wapol
even if it kills me!
[DALTON groans]
Here. I'll take you
to the castle... Hop on.
[gasps]
Come on now,
don't be so modest...
I just want you to
save your strength for
the fight, that's all.
How considerate...
[USOPP groans] Just hold
tight... 'Kay, here goes...
[groaning]
We'll be there in no time...
Usopp meant well...
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
Um, Usopp, thanks,
but, uh... this isn't working.
Just give me a second! Okay?!
I haven't quite
hit my stride yet!
Besides...
I told ya I was gonna get
ya to the castle and I will!
Now that I caught
my breath here,
we can get back
on our merry way!
[ZORO groans] Dammit...
What the hell's he doing?!
[USOPP gasps]
You just gonna
sit there and whine,
or are you coming with us?
[USOPP whimpers]
Zoro! [whines]
You stupid jerk!
‐‐You thunder‐stealer!
‐‐[ZORO] Hey! Stop it!
‐‐Gonna knock your lights out!
‐‐Knock it off!
[wails]
[USOPP]
Why did you do that?!
And just as I was gettin'
my second wind, too!
‐‐Uh‐huh... Sure you were...
‐‐I was... No, I was...
‐‐Of ourse you were...
‐‐I'm gonna kick your...
Hey, wait! Hold up!
There's an easier
way up to the castle!
[USOPP]
Huh?
Instead of walking,
take the ropeway.
Ropeway? Impossible...
There hasn't been one connecting
to Wapol's castle for awhile.
Someone's obviously
reconnected one
because I just saw it.
There was a rope leading
from the castle to a big,
white tree on the
outskirts of Gyasta.
Gyasta, huh?!
That's the name of
the town that Dr. Kureha
was headed to! Remember?!
[SANJI]
Hey, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Yeah?
[SANJI]
Where is he?
[LUFFY]
Where's who?
[SANJI]
That guy!
That guy who?
[SANJI] That tin‐plated
bastard! He's not here!
[yells]
Well, since his hippo
got knocked away,
I doubt he could've
snuck off very far.
Yeah, but how?! When'd he go?!
Probably when you were drooling
over those transformations!
How sneaky! I'll find him!
Where do you think
he ran off to?
[SANJI] Hm. There's not much up
here, just the castle...
And Nami's all alone in there!
[LUFFY yells]
[SANJI] If he lays a finger
on her, I'll chop him up
‐‐and feed 'em to the sharks!
‐‐[KUREHA] Hold it!
[sighs]
Oh, well...
I guess the nincompoop
has a death wish.
[CHOPPER]
Doctorine?
[KUREHA]
Hm?
That guy... Did you hear him?
[KUREHA chuckles]
[CHOPPER]
He called me his friend.
[yells]
[LUFFY]
Hey, big mouth!
When I find ya,
I'm gonna kick your butt!
Seems like my fever's
gone down quite a bit.
That means I should
be able to get back to
the ship after
a little more rest.
[NAMI]
Wait! What am I saying?!
I can't just lay
around in bed like this
because Vivi's waiting...
to go home!
What?! I go away
and this is what happens?!
Drum Castle used to
be a stately palace!
Now it's nothing but a run‐down
hovel filled with snow!
What did they do to it?!
Oh, I won't let
them get away with this!
[growls]
I'll chew them up until there's
absolutely nothing left!
[growls]
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[NAMI] I should get
out of here quickly
while Doctorine isn't around!
[LUFFY] I'm gonna find
that shape‐changing creep
and finish him off!
[SANJI]
If he lays his hands on Nami,
I'll cut him into fish food!
[NAMI]
Uh‐oh! He looks like a bad guy!
[LUFFY] I've got you
cornered, loudmouth!
[USOPP]
Dalton's got dynamite!
[ZORO] I still have no idea
what's going on here.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"When the Kingdom's Rule Ends!
The Flag of Faith
Flies Forever!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!