[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
Inside the bay, the
Whitebeard Pirates
are fighting their
way toward the scaffold,
but the Navy
stands in their way.
Meanwhile at the bay head,
the Pacifistas launch
a merciless attack
on the allied pirates,
hell-bent on slaughtering
every last one of them.
[panting]
I'm serious,
this battle is a fake!
Just ask him!
I know about your
treacherous deal with the Navy!
You have their
assurance that Ace
and all of your pirates
won't even get scratched!
They'll just go
after your allies!
Forty-three captains
fight beside you
and you handed us
all to the Navy,
just to protect Roger's son!
[gasps]
I don't know if you
realize the magnitude
of what you've
just done, Squard.
You thrust a sword
into your father's body,
trying to kill him.
You've lost your way,
my poor, stupid son!
[SQUARD gasping]
But I still love you.
Even if you are a damn fool.
[WHITEBEARD] So, Squard,
please treat him kindly.
I don't love Ace more
than any other son of mine.
On that, you have my word.
Every single one of you
is part of my family!
He hasn't changed
one bit, the bastard!
But that crafty
old snake gave us a pretty
good shakeup, didn't he?
But to even suggest that I'd
sell out my sons is ridiculous!
They can leave now.
He destroyed the ice wall.
He's a sharp one.
If you're a true pirate,
then you choose which
path to take on your own!
Those of you who'll
still follow me,
put your lives on the line!
Get ready, men!
He's coming this way!
The strongest pirate
in the world!
[LUFFY]
"The Encircling Walls Activated!
The Whitebeard Pirates
Backed Into a Corner!"
Oh, man, here it comes.
[SENGOKU grunts]
Heh.
[PIRATES shouting]
We're with you
all the way, Pops!
Clear a path! Let's do this!
Don't let them get any closer!
Fire!
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[MARINES yelling]
He's too strong.
[MARINE C]
Activating the encircling wall!
Just get it done, already!
Right!
[MARINE C grunts]
What's the matter?
Uh, it seems that the wall
is jammed beneath the ice!
[MARINE D grunts]
Then fix it somehow!
[MARINE C]
Yes, sir!
[MARINE D growls]
[SQUARD gasping]
[SQUARD]
Why are you doing this?
Damn it, I-I don't
understand anything anymore!
I bought that story
hook, line, and sinker.
Even though he was from the
Navy, I trusted him over Pops.
I was jealous, I was scared,
but I knew he was right!
So, why? Why is Pops
still trying to save us?
Why didn't he just give us up
and let us die when
he had the chance?
That wasn't supposed to happen!
He swore to me Pops
would betray us!
Damn you, Squard! How the hell
could he let the Navy
trick him into stabbing Pops?
Does that fool really
think he would turn on us?
How could you do this?
Think of how Pops must feel!
[SQUARD]
If I was lied to...
...then what I've done...
What I've done to Pops...
[SQUARD sobbing]
It's unforgivable!
[crying]
I'm so sorry, Pops!
Forgive me, Ace! Please!
[SQUARD crying]
[MARCO]
Hey! Squard!
Pull it together. Tears won't
fix what you've done.
[SQUARD grunting]
Ahh! Bastards! How low
are they willing to sink?
[PIRATES yelling]
[LUFFY panting]
That old man's tough. He gets
stabbed and he's still at it.
I gotta get serious
and save Ace!
Off we go!
Hey, Jimbei!
[JIMBEI]
Hm?
Doesn't that strike you as odd?
[JIMBEI grunts]
They all abandoned their posts
and retreated to the plaza
while we weren't looking.
[JIMBEI] Hmm. Indeed,
that is a bit troubling.
But old Whitebeard
has joined the fray now.
That ought to put
our worries to rest!
True! We can handle whatever
dirty tricks they throw at us!
Why aren't the walls up?
I'm sorry, sir, we're trying,
but the ice is a lot
thicker than we thought!
[SENGOKU growling]
[ACE gasping]
[PIRATES shouting]
Fire!
[PIRATE C yelling]
Hey, are you okay?
Leave me here! Just go!
[grunts]
[yells]
I'll make you pay!
The wall is the crux
of our plan. This is bad.
[JOHN GIANT] I'm gonna buy
us some time till they fix it.
[MARINE G gasps]
[PIRATES gasping]
[PIRATES yelling]
That's as far as
you're gonna get!
You'll never reach the plaza!
Run! Vice Admiral John Giant
is attacking!
[JOHN GIANT grunting]
[JOHN GIANT yells]
[JOHN GIANT gasps]
You're blocking my view. Move.
[JOHN GIANT grunts]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[JOHN GIANT gasps]
What did he do?
[MARINE DD]
Vice Admiral!
What? Why is the ground tilting?
[MARINES yelling]
[MARINE I screaming]
Everyone, keep yer
distance from Pops!
[PIRATE AA] It's even
worse than an earthquake!
[ACE grunts]
Just as I feared.
[LUFFY panting, grunts]
[LUFFY]
Ow. Jeez.
[LUFFY gasping]
[LUFFY]
This can't be real.
This is insane.
It's not just the island.
The entire sea is tilting!
[MARINES yelling]
[LUFFY screaming]
[PIRATES screaming]
[laughs]
That old S.O.B's
sure got some style.
[DOFLAMINGO laughing]
[LUFFY screaming]
[LUFFY grunting]
[JIMBEI]
I've got you!
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Jimbei!
Hang on, I'll pull you up!
[panting]
Thanks, Jimbei.
I owe ya, again.
Thank me when this is over.
Is that crazy old man trying
to get his own crew killed?
No. His crew was ready. They're
used to this kind of thing.
[MARINES groaning, murmuring]
[MARINE J]
I need help!
Hey! Are you all right?
[HELMEPPO] I feel like
I survived the end of the world.
[gasping]
[HELMEPPO gasps]
What the...?
[COBY]
One man did this?
He really is the
strongest pirate alive.
[panting]
I've never seen such
fearsome power before,
but in the name of the absolute
justice I've sworn to uphold,
I'd rather die than let you
pass through here!
[yells]
[JOHN GIANT grunts]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[groans]
It's headed right for us!
[MARINES yelping]
The shockwave's gonna
hit the scaffold!
Yeah! Tear it apart!
[MARINE EE] What happened?
That looked like a direct hit!
But did we get it?
Doesn't look like it
even touched the scaffold.
So, did something
block the blast?
[gasps] Do you see that?
[PIRATE H]
It's the three admirals!
[MARINES gasping]
This mess wouldn't have happened
if the walls were ready.
Whose fault is that?
Your ice is blocking them!
Sure, but you could have
just melted the ice.
Couldn't you?
Holy crap.
I knew they were strong,
but to repel that shock wave?
[JOZU]
Don't give up, men. Not now.
[PIRATES]
Commander Jozu!
I say we charge
the bastards while
they're still reeling from
the blast. Are ya with me?
Pops knocked open
a window for us,
so we better not squander it!
Let's go! Give 'em hell,
Whitebeard Pirates!
[PIRATES shouting]
Take 'em down!
Sounds like they're pretty
pissed off down there.
Scary.
I want an update on the walls.
Uh, they're still down.
Then divert the energy
that's flowing into the city.
Pump every ounce of
power into the walls!
Sir! Right away!
[LUFFY yelling]
Almost there, Ace!
[LUFFY grunting]
Luffy!
I'm comin' for ya!
I'll save you!
Activating full power!
[LUFFY grunts]
What is that?
What? The walls!
[PIRATES gasping]
[PIRATE BB]
They've closed us in!
[PIRATE CC]
What the hell's going on?
Take that!
[PIRATE N grunts]
Well, did it break?
What?!
Oh, man! Not a scratch!
That's gotta be some
seriously thick steel!
[PIRATE DD] I don't know about
you guys, but I'm pretty sure
these are the walls
they were talking about.
[PIRATE EE] C'mon!
Are you too scared to fight us?
Ahh! Hey! Look up there!
They've got an arsenal
of cannons locked on us!
We gotta run!
They've got us locked in! There
isn't any place for us to--
[PIRATE P gasps]
[PIRATE P]
Except there!
[SENGOKU]
What's going on down there?
Why didn't the last wall raise?
Well, it's, uh, it's Oars' body.
The walls don't seem strong
enough to lift it, sir.
Also, it looks like his blood
is running into the system
and making it malfunction!
Damned beast!
[ACE]
Oars! You saved them.
Now, that's a noble death.
[MARCO] He may be dead,
but he's still fighting.
Impressive, huh?
[SQUARD grunts]
[WHITEBEARD]
You've given us a chance, Oars.
We must be swift.
You know what to do, Akainu!
Meteor Volcano!
[AKAINU yells]
[gasps] Holy crap.
That's lava.
Uh, I'm not feeling
good about this.
They vanished. Now what?
[rumbling]
[gasps] Do you guys hear that?
[rumbling continues]
[PIRATE Q yells]
[gasps] That's it.
We're finished.
They've got nowhere to run.
Now we'll melt that ice,
and drown them all!
[PIRATES yelling]
[IVANKOV, PIRATES yells]
[LUFFY gasping]
[NARRATOR] The Whitebeard
Pirates are trapped in the bay,
held there by Akainu's magma.
With Navy fire on all sides,
they climb over Oars Jr.'s body
in hopes of pushing forward.
In the midst of this chaos,
the order for Ace's execution
is given and Luffy
makes a drastic decision.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Execution Order Issued! Break
Through the Encircling Walls!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!