[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[HENCHMAN E] You better give
us that map back or else!
Get back here!
‐‐[explosion]
‐‐[gasps]
[LUFFY screaming]
[GIRL screams]
What... was that?!
A guy fell from the sky.
[LUFFY sighs]
But at least I'm safe now...
And...
...what just happened
to me was awesome.
[LUFFY]
"A Terrifying Mysterious Power!
Captain Buggy,
the Clown Pirate."
Geez...
I'm so hungry...
Oh, hey, boss!
Thanks for coming to save me!
Huh?
[squeals]
Who're you?
[HENCHMEN growling]
[GIRL]
They're all yours now, boss.
Have fun!
[HENCHMAN F]
Hey! That girl's getting away!
[HENCHMAN D] That's okay.
We've got her boss now.
[HENCHMAN E]
You're in trouble, kid.
You shoulda let your
crony fend for herself.
You guys know of anywhere
good to eat around here?
Food's the least of
your worries now!
[gasps]
You better keep your
hands off my hat.
[BOTH]
You bastard!
I wonder if they've
killed that poor guy yet.
[BOTH yelling]
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum Pistol!
[BOTH yell, groan]
[GIRL]
Wow.
You're really strong!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Even though both
of them had sabers,
you beat them barehanded.
[LUFFY] Hey! You're the
girl who set me up.
Who are you?
I'm a talented thief who
steals strictly from pirates.
The name's Nami.
Hey... Wanna team up with me?
Um, thanks anyway, lady,
but I think I'll pass.
[NAMI stammers]
Hold on!
[NAMI grunts]
[NAMI]
At least think about it first.
[stomach rumbling]
I just remembered...
I'm still so hungry.
Well, come with me and I'll
find you something to eat.
Yeah? Are you serious?
[NAMI]
U‐Uh...
[BUGGY] You're telling me they
still haven't caught the thief?
[HENCHMAN H]
Uh...
Not yet...
But...
But they should be in pursuit...
...right now, Captain... Sir.
Now explain to me, how in
the world did she manage
to get her hands
on that chart, huh?!
[whimpering]
If we're preparing to
enter the Grand Line,
and go on a rampage,
then why wasn't the chart
properly guarded?
I don't know, sir...
The map was just sitting out,
plain as the nose on your face.
[BUGGY snorts]
What did you say?!
I‐I mean it was easy for
her to find and take it.
[BUGGY] Did you say
something about my nose?!
[HENCHMAN H whimpers]
So, are you trying to tell
me you find my nose funny?
Is my nose amusing?
No, sir, you've misunderstood.
Oh no, you were quite clear.
[HENCHMAN H whimpering]
[HENCHMAN H]
Help me...
[HENCHMEN gasping]
This isn't good.
He's... gonna use
the Devil Fruit Power.
[BUGGY growls]
[whimpering]
[choking]
Tell me, who am I?!
[HENCHMAN H choking]
Captain... Buggy...
And what happens if
someone defies me?
Flashy... death...
awaits... them...
Please... forgive me.
[HENCHMAN H gasping]
[BUGGY]
Quit your groveling.
I'll overlook your slip‐up
and forgive you this time.
But you better get
that chart back.
Don't screw up again... or else.
[HENCHMEN]
Yes, Captain Buggy!
Yum.
So, do you live in this big
house all by yourself?
This isn't my house,
I'm just staying here
for the time being.
Everyone's left this town
because of Captain Buggy.
[LUFFY]
So you're just a petty thief.
[NAMI]
How rude!
I only steal from people
who deserve it: Pirates.
So don't compare me to
some scumbag, petty thief.
A thief's a thief,
as far as I'm concerned.
My goal is to earn a
hundred million berries,
no matter how hard it is,
or how long it takes.
[LUFFY]
Hm.
What do you need so many
berries for anyway?
[NAMI]
It's a secret.
But with this chart
of the Grand Line,
the hundred million is
now a definite possibility.
A chart.
So you must be a navigator.
I'm the most skilled navigator
you're ever likely to meet.
Oh, wow. That's perfect!
Then how about you join my crew?
I've been looking to
recruit a navigator.
Really?
Sure!
You can be our
newest crew member.
No!
I suppose this means
you're a pirate.
Yeah.
I made a solemn promise.
I promised the guy who gave me
this hat that I'd form a crew,
and become the
greatest pirate ever.
There's nothing in this world
that I despise
more than pirates.
I only like money
and tangerines.
[LUFFY]
Come on.
Be our navigator.
I said no!
Your loss.
[HENCHMAN E]
Did you find her or what?!
[HENCHMAN F]
No! I can't find her anywhere!
[HENCHMAN E]
Where could she be hiding?
[HENCHMAN F]
I don't know,
but we're gonna
be in big trouble
if we don't get that chart back.
[NAMI]
I gotta do something about them.
[chuckles]
I guess I might
consider joining you,
but only if you'll agree
to certain conditions.
[LUFFY]
Really? I'll do anything!
Well then, I want
you to come with me
to pay a little visit to
Buggy the pirate.
But first...
Why did you have to tie me up?
The rope's just for appearances.
[LUFFY chuckles]
Well, okay then...
I've been looking forward to
meeting some other pirates,
so let's get going.
Just hold your horses.
What's the big rush?
[BUGGY]
What?!
Are you telling me
the thief got away?!
[HENCHMEN whimpering]
[ALL] Please forgive us,
Captain Buggy!
I've never seen a more
pathetic group than you three!
Time to die!
[ALL scream]
Captain Buggy, I have news!
[BUGGY]
Ugh. What is it?!
The girl who stole our chart
is back and with a prisoner.
[BUGGY]
What?!
[HENCHMEN muttering]
[HENCHMAN E]
It's her!
That's the sneaky thief
who stole the chart!
[LUFFY yelps]
[NAMI] I've captured the thief,
Captain Buggy the Clown.
And here's your chart back!
Not that I don't
appreciate it.
But...
Why the sudden change
of heart, little girl?
I had another fight
with my boss,
and I just can't
take it anymore.
So I thought I'd see if
I could join your crew.
[BUGGY snorts, growls]
Ca‐Captain Buggy sure does
look angry, doesn't he?
He's gonna use the
Devil Fruit Power.
Really...?
[BUGGY snorting]
[BUGGY laughing]
You're fed up, huh?
I must admit,
you're an amusing girl.
I like you! Of course
you can join my crew!
[BUGGY laughing]
[NAMI] I've successfully
infiltrated them!
Pirates are so dumb and
easy to manipulate!
Hey, guys, why am I in a cage?
[ALL laughing]
It's a great day to be a pirate.
Girl, what do you call yourself?
I'm Nami.
Ha‐ha!
Then let's have a welcome
party for our new friend Nami.
Let's celebrate!
[HENCHMEN cheering]
[HENCHMEN chattering]
What's wrong?
We're throwing this party
in your honor, so eat up.
Thanks for the party,
Captain Buggy.
[NAMI]
I'll just keep my eyes peeled
for a chance to take
back that chart.
Maybe I'll swipe all of Buggy's
treasure, too, while I'm at it.
That's it... Almost there...
[yelps]
Dammit!
[laughing]
This is such a flashy party.
Now listen up!
Men, it's time to
prepare the Buggy Ball!
[HENCHMEN cheering]
[HENCHMAN J snickering]
[HENCHMAN J]
All set, captain.
Wh‐What are you
doing with that thing?
Just observe, the awesome
might of the Buggy Ball.
Light it.
[chuckles]
[yelps]
That was one heck
of an explosion.
It looked like it was one of the
Captain's beloved Buggy Balls.
Buggy Balls?
[HENCHMEN cheering]
[chuckles]
That was flashy.
With these Buggy Balls
and my Devil Fruit Powers,
I should have no problem
conquering the Grand Line.
Right, Nami?
Right. Yes, of course.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
‐‐[NAMI gasps]
‐‐[BUGGY] Huh?
But it's my destiny to
conquer the Grand Line.
[growls]
And then I'm gonna become
King of the Pirates.
Shut up, idiot!
[laughing]
[BUGGY] I can see why
you're sick of him, Nami.
Yeah, I know.
He never takes
anything seriously,
thinks that life's a big game.
He acts like a little kid.
‐‐[NAMI laughs]
‐‐[BUGGY] I see...
[BUGGY] Then how about
I give you a Buggy Ball
to blow away your old boss?
Huh?
It'll be a great opportunity
for you to prove your loyalty
to me, your new captain.
Men!
[gasps]
That's all right, Captain.
We don't have to finish
him off quite yet.
Let's get back to the welcoming
party and just have more fun.
[laughs]
This is my idea
of having more fun.
[HENCHMEN]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
[NAMI] If I don't shoot,
I'll be killed.
But if I do shoot, then I'm
no better than these pirates.
Now! Light the fuse, Nami!
[HENCHMEN]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
‐‐[BUGGY] Hey!
‐‐[NAMI gasps]
You're not wimping
out on me, are you?
[LUFFY]
What's the matter?
Your hands are shaking.
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
That's what happens
when you take on pirates
with half‐assed resolve.
[NAMI]
Resolve? To do what?
To kill someone
like it's nothing?
Is that a pirate's resolve?
[LUFFY]
No!
[HENCHMEN]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
You gotta be willing
to risk your own life.
[HENCHMEN]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
[NAMI gasps]
Here, new chick.
Quit bein' sucha tease.
Let me show you how
to light the cannon.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[HENCHMAN I groans]
[HENCHMEN gasp]
[LUFFY gasps]
[BUGGY gasps]
[gasping]
[gasps]
My mistake... Sorry.
[BUGGY growls]
Nami!
What's the meaning
of this outrage?!
[NAMI]
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?! Just
shoot him already!
[LUFFY]
Huh...
So... now you've
decided to save me?
Don't be so stupid!
I'm not doing this
for you, you idiot.
I just don't want
to lower myself
to the level of these
inhuman pirates!
Okay. Thanks anyway.
Pirates took the life of
a person very dear to me.
I'll never be one of them.
Oh, I see.
[LUFFY yelps]
Nami! The fuse!
[gasps]
So you think pirates
are just inhuman filth,
is that right?
Get her, men!
[HENCHMEN yelling]
[gasps]
[HENCHMEN yelling, laughing]
[NAMI grunts]
Water, water,
water, water, water!
Ohh. Not good.
[NAMI grunts]
[screaming]
Whoa!
[NAMI groaning]
Watch out!
‐‐[HENCHMEN yelling]
‐‐[NAMI gasps]
[gasps]
[thud]
[ZORO]
Hey now.
It's not very nice of you guys
to gang up on the poor girl.
[laughs]
Zoro!
[NAMI]
Huh?
[ZORO]
You hurt?
I said, are you hurt?
[NAMI]
Uh, no, I'm fine, I think.
[LUFFY]
Whew, what a relief!
I'm glad you found us.
Now hurry up and come
get me out of here.
[ZORO] How do keep getting
yourself into these situations?
First a bird flies off with you,
and now I find you
trapped in a cage.
[LUFFY] It's an
interesting story, actually.
That's...
Yeah... That little brat
just called him Zoro.
[NAMI]
The crew he mentioned earlier...
...was the Pirate Hunter Zoro?
What's going on here?
[BUGGY]
So you're Zoro?
[NAMI gasps]
[BUGGY]
If you're here for my head,
you've got quite a
struggle before you.
No. Not interested.
I gave up pirate hunting.
I'm here for my friend.
But I'm interested, though.
Killing you would
bolster my reputation.
If you try...
...you'll die.
Oh. Is that so?
[sighs]
I tried to warn you,
but oh well...
‐‐[HENCHMEN cheering]
‐‐[HENCHMAN J] Get 'em, Captain!
[HENCHMAN K]
You can do it, Buggy!
[HENCHMEN cheering]
[HENCHMEN]
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
[snickers]
[BUGGY yelling, laughing]
[BUGGY]
Die flashily!
[NAMI whimpers]
[HENCHMEN gasp]
That wasn't much of
a fight, now was it?
Oh, wow!
He's weak! Way to go, Zoro!
No way!
‐‐[HENCHMEN laugh]
‐‐[NAMI gasps]
[HENCHMEN laughing]
Hey, why are they laughing?
Their captain is lying
dead on the ground
and yet they're still laughing?
What's going on?
[ZORO]
Fellas.
What do you find so damn funny?
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO groans]
[ZORO screams]
Zoro!
[gasps]
Buggy's still alive!
[ZORO]
What the... hell?!
[ZORO gasps]
[BUGGY]
The Chop‐Chop Fruit.
That's the name of the Devil
Fruit that's given me my powers.
I'm a Chop‐Chop person,
and now I can never be
defeated by the sword!
[laughing]
His limbs... reattach?
And I always thought that the
Devil Fruits were just a story
that Pirates told.
So he's a Chop‐Chop man?
That's pretty freaky.
I didn't hit any vital organs,
but that's a serious
wound you have there.
So I'm guessing...
‐‐...that I am the winner!
‐‐[HENCHMEN] Buggy! Buggy!
‐‐[BUGGY laughs]
‐‐Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
[NAMI]
Oh, crap!
The tables have turned.
If we don't do something quick,
they're gonna kill
all three of us.
[groaning]
I let my guard down.
Stupid mistake.
[BUGGY chuckling]
[HENCHMEN]
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Stabbing him in the back was
a cowardly move, you Big Nose!
[NAMI]
You idiot! Don't call him that!
What're you doing?!
What's that...
...you...
...said?!
Who's got a big nose?!
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Buggy!
[BUGGY snorts]
I'm gonna kick your ass soon
as I get out of this cage!
[laughs]
[BUGGY laughing]
You kick my ass?
You've got a lot of nerve, kid.
No, I'm afraid all three of you
are going to die here
today, by my own hand.
So if you're going to
do any ass kicking,
you better do it soon.
[BUGGY laughing]
[NAMI gasps]
We're done for. It's all over.
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
I refuse to die!
Zoro! Get up!
What?!
You better have a really good
plan or else we're all dead.
So what are you guys gonna do?
[LUFFY chuckles]
I gotcha.
[NAMI]
Nothing makes sense anymore.
This is why I hate pirates.
[BUGGY]
Impudent fool! Time to die!
[BUGGY] Your Three‐Sword
Style has no effect on me.
I already told you I'm‐‐
Hey! Listen when
I'm talking to you.
‐‐[BUGGY screams]
‐‐[HENCHMEN gasp]
Crap, the cannon's
pointed at us! No!
[ZORO]
Hurry! Light it!
[NAMI]
Huh?
‐‐Do it now!
‐‐Right!
Wait! Just wait!
The cannon's still loaded
with a special Buggy Ball.
I don't wanna go out like this!
Done in by my own balls!
[laughing]
[BUGGY] I can't believe
you just did that,
you ungrateful little girl!
Wait!
N‐N‐No!
Stop!
Stop it now!
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[LUFFY]
You okay, Zoro?
[ZORO]
Yeah, don't worry. I'll be fine.
[LUFFY]
Great!
[NAMI]
What're you talking about?!
You can't possibly be better!
[LUFFY]
Really?
[NAMI]
Oh no! What's that?
[LUFFY]
What an unfriendly little dog.
[NAMI]
I'm not referring to that!
[LUFFY] Oh! There's a
polar bear on top of a lion!
[NAMI]
They followed you guys here!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Desperate Situation!
Beast Tamer Mohji vs. Luffy!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!