It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
Look!
We're headed straight
for a dead end!
He'll crash into it and die!
Gomorrah! Stop it!
You'll never make it! Stop!
A dead end?
I don't see one. Do you?
Nope. Can't say
I see anything of the sort.
All units!
The King Bull carrying the
pirates broke through Block D
and they are now at the
Courthouse Plaza!
All personnel on
Enies Lobby's Main Island!
Head to the Courthouse
Plaza immediately!
I repeat: The pirates have
reached the Courthouse Plaza!
Huh?
Also, the gatekeepers of the
Main Island Front Gate,
Oimo and Kashii, have
joined up with the pirates!
They're currently destroying the
central part of the Main Island!
Get outta the way!
Our guard casualties total
must be over 2,000 men!
And the man who took down
over a thousand of those men
all by himself, the
notorious Straw Hat Luffy,
has suddenly disappeared!
We're still assessing
the situation here!
In the history of this island,
this is, without a doubt, the
absolute worst thing that has
ever happened at Enies Lobby!
What's happening here?
And why now?
What the hell's going on?
Jerk!
He's fast!
Finger Pistol! Shave!
Iron Body! Strong!
Now Gum Gum--
Bullet!
Iron Body!
Tempest Kick!
It's no good.
I can't stay like this.
It won't work.
When I lost to Aokiji,
I realized something.
I said to myself.
"You keep running into guys
that are stronger and stronger.
Unless you can
get stronger too,
you can't protect your friends."
And I want to; they're
not all strong like me.
But either way, they're my
friends and I wanna keep 'em.
So I have to get
stronger than anyone else,
otherwise there's a
chance I could lose 'em.
Then what are you gonna do?
I thought of a new way
to fight with all my might,
so that I won't lose anyone.
So I won't let anyone
slip away from me.
What's happening to him?
What's going on inside his body?
That did it.
You won't be able
to stop me now.
What?
All my strength and techniques
just went up by one step.
Second Gear!
Baskerville!
Chief Justice Baskerville!
Come in! It's me!
Oh! Hello, Chief Spandam!
This is Left Baskerville
on the left!
This is Right Baskerville
on the right.
And located in the center,
it is none other than I--Central
Freeway, closed for repairs!
Shut up!
Just give me a
status report, damn it!
Is it true that the
intruders have made it
to the courthouse plaza or not?
Let's see.
A status report, huh?
That's a tricky one.
They're not so much in the plaza
as they are inside
the courthouse.
It's just awful!
What?
Chief!
Chief Justice!
I have a report!
The pirates have cut
through our defenses
and broken down the front door.
They're currently
inside the courthouse.
We can see that already, fool!
Not as much resistance
as I expected.
We should be able
to tear right through.
Wait, what's that?
Whoa, what? He's got 3 heads!
He's just like that dog
that guards the underworld!
Berberus?
You mean "Cerberus"!
Order in the court, damn it!
This is a sacred chamber
of law, you hooligans!
You had the nerve to
burst in here so shut up,
sit still and receive
your sentence!
Gero!
All right guys, you head to the
roof and join up with Straw Hat.
We'll stay here at
the door with Yokozuna
and hold off the Marines.
We'll watch your back,
so keep moving and don't
worry about the small fries!
Gero!
You got it.
Hey, it looks
like they're starting
some kind of trial over there.
Hm?
Who cares?
Just ignore them.
Which way do we go?
Straight ahead!
There are stairs on both sides.
Let's make our way to the top!
Right.
Hey!
They're ignoring the trial!
I know they're pirates,
but seriously, how
rude can these guys get!
Bastards!
How dare you mock
the judicial island!
I'll teach you some respect!
Are his swords bending,
or am I seeing things?
Charming Demon.
Sleepless Night.
Onigiri!
Is he the guy
who broke the door?
Well, that's that.
Now let's get moving!
Right!
He puts all of us to shame
and he's not even the
captain of their crew!
Hey hey hey, wait!
Outta the way, reindeer!
Outta the way, Moss Head!
I'm coming through!
Hm?
I forgot about him.
Somebody's gotta protect Nami
from all of these bad guys
and that somebody's
gonna be me, damn it!
Now move!
Watch it!
What?
Why is he picking a fight now?
If you wanna settle
this, then bring it!
Shut up!
This is your fault for trying
to hog Nami all for yourself!
Follow me, Nami.
Forget about him.
Uh, hey, we came to this place
to rescue Robin, remember?
Oh!
I bet she's waiting for me!
She's waiting for
her prince to save her!
She's probably crying right now,
'cause she misses me so much!
Whatever!
Hm? Come on!
Are you kidding me?
Come back, Zoro!
That's the wrong way!
You sure?
How can you screw this up
when the stairs are right
in front of your face?
What's wrong with you?
If you'd stop giving
such crappy directions,
this wouldn't happen!
You are not blaming this on me!
Zoro, I'll try to make you some
medicine later,
to fix your brain problem.
Brain problem?
Hey, Chopper?
Hm?
Make some for
him while you're at it.
I'll try, but he
may be beyond help.
I'm starting to have doubts
about this whole rescue thing.
They'll pull it together
when the going gets tough.
I'm sure.
I mean, probably.
I mean, hopefully.
These are serious crimes.
Yes, they're quite grave indeed.
But we should show restraint
and sentence them to death!
Agreed!
Are you still with us, Zoro?
It's this way!
Yeah, I know!
Think you can ignore
the Chief Justice, huh?
Chopper. Nami.
Go on ahead.
I'll make quick
work of this thing
and catch up with
you in a second.
Oh.
I'm a "thing" now, am I?
And easy to defeat, no less?
I'll teach you the meaning
of fear, you little--
Pull!
No! Stop it!
Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
No.
You gotta go through
us first, Cerberus!
Are you sure about this?
Curse you!
Let's go.
Uh, right!
Gear?
Your techniques have changed?
Are you supposed
to be a steam engine?
You certainly
are full of hot air.
You're starting to
test my patience.
You know, the truth is I'm
glad I met you guys when I did.
Hm?
Because thanks to you,
I won't ever lose my friends.
The truth is I'm glad
I met you guys when I did.
Because thanks to you,
I won't ever lose my friends.
I don't understand.
I think you've got it backwards.
Aren't you going to lose one
of your friends precisely
because you met us?
I knew you were foolish,
but now you're just
uttering nonsense.
You sure you didn't
hit your head?
Gum-Gum--
What, are you stopping to aim?
That only gives me
more time to dodge.
Fine.
Let's see how good
your aim is, then.
Shave!
Jet Pistol!
Rifle!
I can't see him at all!
Stamp!
And spear!
Missile!
Impossible.
No, it has to be.
The truth is I'm glad
I met you guys when I did.
He's using the Shave technique.
Only CP9 should
know the Six Powers,
but he's clearly mastered it.
Air Door!
Huh?
He disappeared.
This is unheard of.
A pirate commanding
one of our techniques?
With no training?
Besides that, he can
use it so effortlessly.
How was he able to
strengthen his body like that?
Is it because of that steam?
This is a sick joke.
Don't tell me he was
capable of this all along!
No, it doesn't matter.
No one can match the speed
of a true Six Powers master!
I won't lose to him!
If I turn his body parts
into doors like before,
that should stop him
dead in his tracks.
After that, all I have
to do is finish him off.
Door-Door!
When we fought before,
and it looked like
you were disappearing,
you were really
just moving your feet
ten or twenty times a second.
I got the hang of it, too.
But I never would've
figured something like that
out on my own.
Like I said, I really
am glad I met you guys.
When my friends are in trouble,
I'll be able to use your
tricks to protect them.
Gum-Gum--
I can take it.
I'll use my strongest defense!
Iron Body. Strength!
Jet Bazooka!
You sure are tough, aren't you?
All right then.
I was gonna save it, but
I have an even better trick.
Don't blink.
I call this--
Man, I'm beat.
Guess my body can't
keep this up for long.
Well, I don't care
about my body right now.
I need to move ahead.
Damn it! What's going on here?
Quick! Fire the cannons, men!
Before they step on us!
Yeah, nice try!
But those peashooters
aren't enough to stop me!
You can run or you
can fight, little men,
but we're comin'
through either way!
I see it and I still
can't believe it!
I don't know what
you said to those guys,
but it must've
been something else!
We warriors
understand each other!
The time has come, brothers!
The courthouse is
looming on the horizon.
Onward!
What're you doing?
Hurry up and go inside already!
The pirates are in the
courthouse, aren't they?
Yeah, but the problem
is there's a big frog
at the door and he's
not letting anyone in!
A frog?
Gero Gero Gero Gero
Gero Gero Gero Gero!
Keep fighting, Yokozuna!
Don't give 'em an inch!
Gero Gero Gero Gero Gero Gero!
We can't stop until the
drawbridge comes down!
If those guys break
our line of defense,
thousands of 'em
could pour in here!
Gero!
Only one of us
needs to get through!
Even if everyone else falls,
as long as someone
pulls that lever, we've won!
You okay, Sis?
Don't worry about me!
All that matters is
bringing down that bridge
and making sure the Straw Hats
get to the Tower of Law!
Hold it!
You're not going anywhere!
Oh yeah?
Try and stop me!
What are those pirates plotting?
Why's it so important
for them to go upstairs, huh?
You won't get
an answer outta me!
We'll see about that!
But I'll tell you one thing--
you're gonna pay
if you hurt our big bro!
After them!
Bring those pirates down!
How many of these stupid guards
are we gonna have to
beat before they catch a hint?
There they are!
Attack!
Move!
Hey, if you have to throw them,
at least don't throw them at me!
Guilty! Guilty!
Guilty! Guilty! Guilty!
Would you guys shut up?
I'm trying to think here.
Must've taken a
wrong turn somewhere.
You want us to take
Franky and Nico Robin
to the Gates of Justice now?
Yes!
Do it!
Quickly!
But we're way ahead of schedule.
The escort ship
isn't even ready yet.
I don't care!
We can just wait for it on
the other side of the gates!
If we get rid of those two,
the pirates won't have
a reason to fight anymore!
There's no point in
risking another battle
with those monsters when we have
the power to end this right now!
And while you're at it, gather
all the members of CP9, too!
Sir!
Now.
It seems as if your
one-way trip to hell
will be departing
ahead of schedule.
Then, we'll have all
the time in the world
to deal with your friends!
Giant warriors! Giant warriors!
Giant warriors are on our side!
Those pirates sure know how
to bring the party, don't they?
I don't know if they
have common sense,
but they sure as heck have guts!
Just you wait and
watch, Chimney.
In the end, whether they live
or die, that Straw Hat boy
and all of his little friends
are gonna shake things up
the whole world over.
In hundreds of years,
nobody's pulled a
stunt like this one!
Mark my words, when this battle
is over, every man, woman,
and child is gonna know
the name of Straw Hat Luffy!
Robin!
Yeah! He made it!
Luffy!
I'm here to save you!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
I'm not coming back!
I don't want to see
your faces ever again!
Robin!
Do you hear me?
I just want to die!
Sorry! We're already here
and it was a lot of trouble!
So we're going to
go ahead and save you!
On the next One Piece:
"Give Us Your Answer, Robin!
The Straw Hats' Outcry!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!