[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[NAMI]
It can't be.
[ENERU]
It's not that people fear God.
Rather it is God
who is fear itself.
Zoro!
[ENERU]
Thirty million volt Hino!
That drum.
[ENERU]
So why get back up?
[WYPER]
For my ancestors.
I... I've always wanted to
go to endless vearth.
Can I come with you?
[LUFFY] Hey! Zoro!
What's wrong with you?
Wyper, no!
[ROBIN]
Skypiea will be destroyed.
It will be cast down
to the surface.
Our village too?
Everything.
Behold the Ark Maxim!
[ENERU laughs]
[AISA]
I know where they are.
There are only two voices
left on this island.
It has to be Nami and Eneru.
I need you to take me
to them right now.
[LUFFY] "They Finally Clash!
Pirate Luffy vs. God Eneru!"
[horn blaring]
[CONIS]
There it is, Angel Island!
Everyone, heso!
The arch criminals Pagaya
and his daughter Conis,
along with their accomplice,
the former God Gan Fall,
are still on the loose!
Please be on your guard!
[MCKINLEY]
If anyone sees these fugitives,
please alert me,
McKinley, immediately!
Again, report any
news directly to me!
In the name of the great God
Eneru, we of the White Berets,
will defend the security of
Skypiea with our very lives!
[WHITE BERETS]
Heso!
Ah, it's good to know
we can count on them.
But I'm still scared!
Those horrible criminals
could be hiding out nearby
or even among us!
If they're struck down
by God's judgment,
we might be too!
[WHITE BERET D]
Captain! I have a report!
[MCKINLEY]
Hm?
What's the matter now?
[inaudible]
What? You say that
Pagaya's daughter
has just been seen
in the harbor?
[WHITE BERET E] The heretic has
entered through gate number one!
[MCKINLEY]
I don't get it.
Why'd she come back when
she knows she'll be caught?
[MCKINLEY]
Don't let her get away!
Capture her at all costs!
Ha! Come on, criminal.
Please make way!
[WHITE BERETS shouting]
[MCKINLEY]
Move it! Outta my way!
Wha--
[WHITE BERETS]
Captain!
[BOTH gasp]
Oh no.
[CROWD shouting]
[MALE A]
Captain Mckinley!
[MALE B]
It's the criminal!
[MALE C]
Stay away!
[MALE D]
Judgment will fall on her!
[ENERU laughs]
[NAMI]
Look at all that gold!
[ENERU] Remember your girl
friend from Angel Island?
I've been listening and it
sounds like she's causing
an uproar among
the citizens.
Conis? No way!
She should be waiting on
the Going Merry right now!
[ENERU] There's a great deal of
noise outside at the moment.
But no matter. It's hardly
worth mentioning.
[ENERU laughs]
[gasps]
[NAMI] Uh, about this Mantra
ability that all of you
seem to possess.
Can you use it to locate
a specific individual?
Not usually. Most of
us lack that ability.
However, I can. I am unique.
In addition to my
Mantra abilities,
my lightning powers allow me
to pick up electrical vibrations
and overhear conversations.
When I hear someone
say something, shall we say,
"out of line," I cast
my Judgment on them.
The range of my hearing extends
over this entire land.
[NAMI]
So that's it.
[ENERU] It's a suitable talent
for a god, isn't it?
[ENERU laughs]
Run as fast as you can,
people of the sky!
This is Skypiea's last dance!
A party of angels
dancing in the sky! Haha!
You! Have you ever seen the
look on a mortal's face
when he suddenly
loses his footing?
[ENERU laughs]
[gasps]
[NAMI]
He's out of his mind.
He's crazy, he's crazy,
he's crazy!
What should I do? I have to
get away from here, or else.
No. Even if I get away,
he'll destroy the sky island.
There's got to be something
I can do, but what?
[gasps] I... I-Is there
something wrong?
[ENERU]
Who is that?
No, it's nothing.
[CONIS]
Please! You must listen to me!
No! Get back, stay away!
Everyone. You have to listen
to me! Please calm down!
We don't have time to waste!
You must hear what
I have to say!
Get away from us, criminal!
Leave this island,
you pestilence!
Yes! You must leave now
or we'll all be destroyed
when the Judgment
strikes you down!
You heretic!
No please, I--
Listen, you must--
[gasps]
[WHITE BERET I grunts]
[CONIS]
Don't come any closer!
This is a Burn Bazooka.
I'll use it.
[CROWD gasps]
Everyone! You have
to go to Cloud End
at the edge of the clouds
right away before it's too late!
We have to escape
to the Blue Sea!
This land is about
to be destroyed!
There's no time to waste!
Use every ship you can find and
leave Angel Island at once!
What kind of lunacy is this?
Eneru's planning to destroy
this land and everyone on it!
If we don't evacuate now,
we're going to die!
Ha! You're crazy!
What kinda trick is this?
Is this revenge?
That's nothing to be
joking about, you know!
[CITIZEN J]
You think we're idiots?
[LITTLE BOY] Don't talk
that way about Eneru!
[gasps]
Oh, sorry.
What? What's she doing?
[inhales]
--Now! Arrest her!
--Yes, sir!
Hear me!
I refuse to accept
that Eneru is God!
[CONIS]
Father...
[CROWD shouting]
[CITIZEN K]
She must be insane!
[WHITE BERET J]
Huh?
That's strange,
the Judgment didn't come.
[CITIZEN F]
But, why not?
[CITIZEN M] And after
committing such sacrilege
against God,
I don't understand.
[CROWD chatters]
Hey, what's going on?
[CONIS] It's because
there's no longer any point
in taking one life alone.
"Skypiea is doomed." It's true.
A member of the Divine Squad
escaped from Upper Yard.
He risked his life to
deliver that message.
He died.
He died with my father when
Eneru cast judgment on them.
[gasps]
Did God do that? But why?
I thought he was supposed
to take care of us.
What does that lady mean?
[CONIS]
There's no time left.
We have to get to the edge
of the clouds at once!
To Cloud End!
No!
[CITIZEN M]
Wait just a minute!
We can't do it! We can't
just up and go like that!
We were all born and
raised here in the sky!
We can't live anywhere else!
[CITIZEN N]
Yeah, she's right!
None of us have ever even
visited the Blue Sea before!
How would we be able
to live there? Besides--
Then are you going
to stay here,
doing nothing, waiting to die?
We've all known for the past
six years what kind of a man
Eneru is! Has he ever
shown mercy? Compassion?
If he says he's going to do
this, then you know he will!
Maybe it's not that bad!
Maybe a miracle will
happen or something,
and our island will be spared!
Yeah, why not?
Maybe he'll change his mind.
Yeah, yeah. That could happen.
[CROWD gasps, screams]
[CONIS] If we know anything
about Eneru, we know this.
He's always had the power
to bring us to despair,
to make us suffer
and break us!
I tell you, what happens
now will make our past
suffering insignificant!
It's not going to do
any good sitting
and waiting for a miracle!
It's time to face the fact
that as far as this land
is concerned,
God has abandoned us!
Before we pray.
Before we close our eyes to
what's really happening here,
we have to do what we
can to save ourselves!
We can't survive by hiding
behind his victims any longer!
If we do nothing, no matter
who we try to blame,
we're all going to lose our
lives and it'll be our fault!
[CONIS] Now. If we want
to live, we must leave!
[gasps]
[CROWD yelling, shouting]
[CITIZEN DD]
Oh, miss.
Do you have any idea what
happened to the Divine Squad?
My husband is one of them
and I can't leave
the island without him!
And my son's a member!
Is he okay?
I haven't seen him in six years!
Me, too. My only son
is with them, too!
Um, I don't...
[CONIS] The Divine Squad
may already be...
I'm sorry. I don't know.
[CITIZEN E] What have they
been doing all this time
on the Upper Yard?
[CITIZEN DD]
Are they still there?
Can't you tell us anything?
Please calm yourselves.
I assure you the White Berets
will look into this matter!
We will find your
family members
and make sure they're
escorted safely to you!
Now hurry! You must escape!
[CITIZEN EE]
But Captain!
[MCKINLEY]
Move along!
Captain, why?
[MCKINLEY] I can guess what will
happen to the Divine Squad.
[gasps]
[MCKINLEY]
Eneru is that kind of man.
I've always known that.
But right now, our priority
is to make sure the citizens
are evacuated as
quickly as possible.
I won't let this
end like Birka.
Birka?
It was Eneru's homeland.
A sky island to the far
southeast of here.
I've been told it
disappeared without a trace
some six years ago.
Wait. Six years ago?
[MCKINLEY]
That's right.
Eneru destroyed his own
homeland, and then came here.
Birka was home to many
strong warriors,
but they were helpless
before Eneru.
An invincible God.
I don't know,
maybe he really is.
You might already know this,
but we White Berets were
once in the Divine Squad,
pledged to the service
of Lord Gan Fall.
We thought that if we pretended
to betray the Divine Squad
and swore our allegiance
to Lord Eneru,
we could stay on the island
and find some way to
protect the citizens.
But, now it's all too clear
that plan was a failure.
We tried to keep anyone from
provoking Eneru's anger.
We hoped that if no one
disobeyed him, they'd be safe.
What else could we do?
It was for nothing!
For nothing! For nothing!
For nothing!
[CONIS]
It wasn't for nothing.
[CONIS] After all this time,
I finally understand.
You have nothing
to be ashamed of.
You were just thinking of
everyone's welfare.
I believe that we
should be thanking you.
[gasps]
[CONIS]
Captain?
Can... Can I count on you
to handle things here?
Yes, but where are
you going? Tell me.
Well you see,
there are some people
who don't know how to escape.
Some friends of mine.
I have to go back.
Take care!
[footsteps]
[MCKINLEY] Of course!
The Blue Sea dwellers!
[ALL]
Heso!
[CONIS gasps]
[LUFFY pants]
[LUFFY shouts]
[pants, grunts]
[ROBIN grunts]
[ROBIN] I won't be able to
move them all at once.
We've at least got to
reach the upper level.
Somehow, we must escape.
[LUFFY]
Aisa!
You're sure it's this way?
Yes! We're almost there!
I'm sure this is the right way!
[LUFFY]
Good!
[AISA] That's it, Luffy!
That hole to your left!
Over there! That's it!
Then that's where we're going!
[ENERU]
As I thought,
they weren't among
the five survivors.
Now where in the world could
they have been hiding?
Could it be?
How aggravating!
There's nothing I hate more
than when my predictions
turn out wrong!
[inhales]
[LUFFY] Hey! Are you the
one they call Eneru?
[gasps]
[cheers]
[NAMI]
Luffy!
If you mess with friends
of mine, then you mess with me.
[ENERU] Hmph... Those fools
were your friends?
[LUFFY] You stay right there!
I'm coming up to kick your ass!
[ENERU]
Mind your tongue, mortal!
You're speaking to God!
[LUFFY]
What makes you God anyway?
[AISA] He's deliberately
picking a fight with Eneru!
Be careful, Luffy!
[PIERRE whines]
W-Wait, Luffy! Watch out.
[ENERU laughs]
[ENERU] I can hear it now,
the angels' party!
The citizens must have
learned of Skypiea's fate!
[ENERU laughs]
[ENERU] I wonder how far they
can run before the ground
gives out beneath them!
[LUFFY] I said, what makes
you God anyway?!
You'll find out.
[LUFFY growls]
[ENERU]
Ah, I see.
You are no ordinary human, but
you're a mere Paramecia type.
You can't beat me.
[ENERU] Nothing that lives
can stand against me!
That's why... I am God!
[yells]
[ENERU] El...
...Thor!
No!
[AISA screams]
[NAMI]
Luffy... No.
[NAMI shouts]
[BOTH gasp]
I'm impressed that you
managed to dodge it.
Sixty Million Volts!
[NAMI]
He dodged it?
[ENERU]
Julungul!
[yells]
[BOTH gasp]
One hundred million volt.
Vari!
[NAMI]
Of course!
If I'd thought about it,
I would've realized it sooner!
Lightning can't hurt Luffy,
he's made of rubber!
I've had enough of you! Get off!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[yells]
[ENERU]
Stay calm!
Physical attacks still
can't affect my body!
He's just a helpless monkey
from the Blue Sea World.
[yelling continues]
[groans]
[NAMI] His electrical powers
are completely useless!
Eneru must never have imagined
there was someone in the world
who was immune to lightning!
It's incredible, but it's true.
[ENERU grunts, groans]
[NAMI] Luffy may be the
only person in the world
who can battle Eneru.
They're natural enemies!
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice
While you wander far from home,
gazing up at the sky
You are just like the moon
You never change as
you climb into the night
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear,
fading so suddenly...
Stay as you are,
don't lose your way
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams,
through endless nights
they come to you
Again and again, until you
see them shining through!
You may not return,
I hope that you'll learn
to put your past behind,
and just keep moving on
[ENERU] Behold! This is a
ship suitable for God!
I'll destroy Skypiea
and everyone on it,
and depart for the Endless
Vearth as I was destined to do!
[LUFFY] Not if I have
anything to say about it!
[ENERU] Now, activate the
circuit of despair! Deathpiea!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Maxim Surfaces!
Deathpiea Is Activated!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!