Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NEGATIVE GHOST]
Horo horo horo horo!
[MORIA] Let's illuminate
our friend here!
[LUFFY] What are ya
gonna do, ya jerk?
I'm gonna make you pay!
What? What the hell?
My shadow?
No, don't do it!
Ishishi!
[MORIA] The shadow of a man
with a 300 million berry bounty!
And it's all mine!
Now, we'll create
the most powerful
special zombie the
world has ever seen!
Kushishishi!
[LUFFY] "The Warrior
Known as the 'Devil'!!
The Moment of Oars' Revival."
[MORIA]
Kushishishishi!
Now, Straw Hat becomes just
another one of my subjects.
And my ultimate minion
will have the power
he needs to come to life!
Kushishishishi!
Poor Luffy!
What just happened?
That's not possible, is it?
His shadow.
He cut it off and took it!
[USOPP] Wait a minute!
We've heard about
this, haven't we?
Didn't that skeleton say the
same thing happened to him?
[NAMI] Yeah! I remember!
He said his shadow was stolen!
Then this must be
the guy that did it!
I bet you're right. How awful.
[KUMACY] Uhhh...
What's the trick?
It must be a Devil Fruit power.
Kumacy! Am I imagining things,
or were you speaking again?
When I say don't talk,
you shut your mouth for good.
[PERONA] Listen, you!
Don't make me keep repeating
myself over and over again!
You're not the least bit cute
when you talk, so don't do it!
[ABSALOM] She's very
strict with poor Kumacy.
Beary strict, even.
Is there something
you'd like to say?
'Cause if you want
to talk. Don't! Ever!
Kushishishishi!
This little guy is just
what I need to bring me
one step closer to becoming
King of the Pirates.
Right, Doctor Hogback?
Fasfasfasfas!
Since the time
I met you ten years ago,
I've put all of
my time, resources,
and energy into
making number 900!
With that shadow,
it will make the greatest
zombie of all time!
With that power
at your fingertips,
nothing will be
beyond your reach!
[ABSALOM] That means it will
only be a matter of time
before I become the Cemetery
King of the entire world!
[PERONA] And I'll transform
all the cute creatures
of the world into zombies.
Then I'll have an
entire adorable kingdom
full of servants
that never talk back!
That's right!
It doesn't matter
who the person is,
how powerful they are, or how
strong-willed they may be.
Once their shadow is taken
and placed in another,
they bow to your will.
Soon, I'll fill the
world with my servants!
If I'd had an army
like that before,
I wouldn't have been beaten by
that idiot Kaido
in the New World.
I think it's about time
we open his eyes, don't you?
Gyoro! Nin! Bao!
Yes, Master!
What's your command?
Go on ahead
and open the door to
the special refrigerator!
[ZOMBIE TRIO]
Right! As you wish, Master!
[MORIA]
It's almost time, sweet 900!
In but a few moments,
your eyes will open at last!
The perfect shadow
has finally found
its way to my doorstep.
And once I've
placed it inside you,
you'll help me become
King of the Pirates!
Kushishishishi!
Hey, Spider Mouse! Come here!
[SPIDER MOUSE 349E] Yes?
[ABSALOM]
Take Straw Hat Luffy's body
and throw it back on his ship.
Make sure to remove those webs.
We'll be in trouble if he dies.
You got it!
Wait! I have an urgent
report to give you!
What is it?
Just moments
ago, the Spider Monkey,
Captain Tararan,
was defeated by intruders!
Defeated? Heh!
What does that matter?
As long as his
shadow wasn't removed.
But that's just it!
His shadow was removed!
[ABSALOM]
You're certain of this?
Yes! There's no doubt!
Grrrrr!
It's him, Absalom!
Only one man is capable of
doing this! He has returned!
Damn that
Humming Swordsman!
It seems the reports
I received this morning
weren't so crazy after all.
How could this happen?!
The Humming Swordsman
is running around
removing every zombie's
shadow he comes across!
Out of nowhere,
the number of casualties
has gone through the roof!
Everything's playing
out just like
that terrible ordeal we
went through 5 years ago.
[FRANKY] What?
Return to the ship?
You want us to go back
on board the Sunny?
[BROOK] Yes, that's right.
If your comrades have been
captured, I fear the worst.
By now, and if not, very soon,
they will have surely
had their shadows stolen.
But even if that's
the case, they won't die.
Their bodies will likely
be taken back to your boat.
You see this?
They'll end up just like me!
Wait! The shadow part,
not the dead part!
Yeah, Yeah, I get it!
Let's move on!
Anyway. Like you were saying,
even if you have your shadow
taken, you won't die. Right?
Yes, that would be correct.
But whenever it's taken,
you immediately weaken
and lose consciousness.
Usually for about
two days or so.
If the victim is strong enough,
then they'll put the
bodies on a ship and send
them to drift out in the sea,
which is why I'm urging
you to return to yours.
Any guess as to
why they do this?
[ROBIN] Well, I would assume
it's to prevent the victims
from trying to take back
their shadows. Correct?
Yes!
[FRANKY] Why don't
they just kill them
while they're unconscious
and get it over with?
That's something
they cannot do.
Hmm?
[BROOK]
Now this is important,
so be sure to
pay close attention.
Firstly, even though the body
and shadow have been separated,
they still represent one being.
Think of the shadow as a soul.
If the body dies, the shadow
will disappear as well.
Thusly, killing the
host zombie in the process.
Since they're trying to
build an army of minions,
this would certainly
not bode well for them.
Secondly, in the likely
event that your friends
have had their shadows stolen,
they would most definitely
still be alive and their bodies
would be returned to your
ship as soon as possible.
Which is why,
the two of you must not lose
your shadows, as well.
If you do, all hope will be
lost and you'll be forced
to wander these seas
aimlessly for all eternity.
[BROOK] While you have
this window of opportunity,
you should use it to attempt
to awaken your comrades.
Once you do, you must regroup
and formulate a plan
to reclaim their shadows.
Do you understand?
Does all of this make sense?
[FRANKY] Hmm...
Yeah, I think so.
Your shadow story
wasn't so crazy after all.
[BROOK] Both of you.
Take this.
Huh?
[ROBIN] What is it?
[BROOK] The weakness
of these zombies.
[BROOK] You've seen its power.
This was the weapon I used
to defeat that Spider Monkey.
What the hell is that thing?
That thing would be
the soul of the zombie.
[FRANKY] Its soul? Why's it
coming out of his mouth?!
No! Captain!
[BROOK] Go on. Get out of here!
Return to your rightful owner!
Their weakness, huh?
What is this stuff, anyway?
It's ordinary salt.
It's just salt?
Not exactly what I had in
mind as the vanquisher of evil.
Does it lift the
curse or something?
[BROOK] Well,
I suppose that would be
one way of putting it, yes.
The reanimated life
of these zombies
is brought about by
a Devil Fruit power.
And just as one who is a power
holder is weakened by seawater,
the salt that is contained
in that water can be
used as a weapon to unbind
the shadow from a zombie,
leaving them
permanently deceased.
Okay, I get it.
Then when this
Spider Monkey went down,
that black thing that
floated out of him afterward
was someone else's shadow
that he'd been given.
To think, something so simple
would be their weakness.
[BROOK] So, in summation,
in order to defeat the zombies,
simply throw salt
into their mouths.
That's the trick! Salt! Mouth!
Deader than dead!
Make no bones about it!
[ROBIN] Pardon me, Brook.
But how do you know
so much about this
island and its residents.
And how do know
the zombie's weakness?
[BROOK] It all relates
back to an incident
on this island 5 years ago.
The time when I lost my shadow.
I was sent out to sea,
just like all the others.
Luckily, I awoke and was able to
retrace my path and return here.
[BROOK] Once I did, I went
ashore and began my battle.
I fought against, the very
zombie that had my shadow.
[BROOK] Unfortunately, the
outcome was a crushing defeat.
[BROOK] Because I vowed to
survive, no matter what I faced.
I ran. Even if it was shameful,
I had to keep on living.
I have an
obligation, you see.
I was the only
survivor of my crew.
One day, I will
escape these evil seas,
and make good on the
promises made by myself
and my comrades.
Until then, I cannot
die a second time.
Sadly, living longer
hasn't helped me
to keep my promises
or reach my goal at all.
But this time, I'm back
and I won't run away!
Not until I defeat that man
and reclaim my shadow!
[BROOK] I'm in a hurry,
so please excuse me,
I'll be on my way now.
Good luck to you.
[FRANKY] Hold on a second!
While you're still
in a mood to talk,
there's one more
burning question
I still need an answer to.
[HOGBACK] That swordsman. That
damned Humming Swordsman!
Bastard. That infuriating
troublemaker is the only enemy
we have that knows the
weakness of the zombies.
How did he manage
to return here again,
and what is she doing?
How much damage has he
managed to do this time?
Cindry! Stop that!
Why do you keep blocking me?!
[PERONA]
The Humming Swordsman.
I've heard many
stories about him,
but just what kind
of a man is he?
You don't mean
that you've, Perona,
are you saying you've
never seen his face before?
I see, then that's probably how
he slipped past your
ghost network undetected.
Yeah, so it would seem.
[ABSALOM] Master!
Apparently, that humming pain
in the ass has returned.
Like I care!
Don't bother me with
such nonsense, idiot!
I'm busy! You take care of him!
[ABSALOM] Hold on!
Kushishishishi!
[ZOMBIE TRIO] Sorry to
keep you waiting, Master!
Come on! Let's make our
way to the refrigerator.
Kushishishishi!
Master, I have news concerning
the current situation.
[whispering noises]
Eh?! Why didn't you
say so before, fool?
If that's the case, slowing
him down shouldn't be an issue.
[SPIDER MOUSE 349D] True!
Keep me informed
of any more problems,
should they arise.
Now hurry up and dump
Straw Hat on the boat.
[SPIDER MICE] You got it!
One. Two. Heave ho! Heave ho!
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
Luffy!
Idiot! Keep quiet!
[USOPP] He lost his shadow!
That doesn't mean
that he's dead!
Remember? Brook said so!
[PERONA] Kumacy! Hurry up!
[USOPP] We can't just
hop out right now.
Wait for the right moment.
It sounds like they have
plans for Luffy's shadow.
We need to keep hiding
in here to find out
where they're taking it
so we can rescue it later!
[ZOMBIE GENERAL 348A] Those two
pirates aren't here anymore.
[ZOMBIE GENERAL 348B]
Where'd they run off to?
Hah! To think that
Tararan was defeated.
Impressive.
[JIGORO] Here's
where everyone went!
[CAPTAIN JOHN] Jigoro,
did you just now get here?
Were you lost?
[JIGORO] Shut up!
More importantly,
where is the enemy?
I must find them
and slice them!
Listen, Franky.
What is it? You're
wrong! I'm not crying!
I'm not crying, you punk!
Stop looking at me already!
I wanted to know.
Why did you ask him about that?
Leave me alone!
I have my reasons, okay?
Dammit! I can't help it!
I love that damn skeleton!
He's the nicest guy
in the whole world!
It's not fair!
Heh! That's true.
[humming]
[BROOK] That was scary!
He's so fearsome;
he even gives us
zombies a fright!
[BROOK] That was terrifying!
But, I won't give up!
Not this time!
Nyohohoho...
Nothing will stop me.
I'll see this battle
through no matter what.
I won't run away!
Nyohohohahaha...
[BROOK] I'm taking
back my shadow!
Kushishishi!
Kushiiii!
[HOGBACK] I'm looking
forward to this!
When I first came across this
corpse in the Land of Ice,
I couldn't stop shaking!
Honestly, I was trembling!
It's simply
fascinating to think
that such a monstrous creature
was alive and breathing,
wreaking havoc across
the seas 500 years ago!
The countries that fell at
his hands were taken whole.
Under his strength, a legendary
nation of criminals was born.
Imagine my surprise when
I found myself staring
at the demon they called
"The Continent Puller."
Man, it keeps getting
colder and colder!
Where in the world are
these guys going, anyway?
I have no idea, but they
said something earlier,
about some sort of special
refrigerator, didn't they?
[USOPP] Oh, yeah! You're right!
[CHOPPER]
The Land of Ice? A corpse?
I can't believe
I'm going to revive this
extraordinary creature!
This will go down in the books
of Zombie Creation as...
Cindry, why do
keep blocking me?
[MORIA] Another legend
will be brought back to life!
Kushishi!
It's been quite a
while, hasn't it, 900?
The time for his
revival is finally here!
Behold! The only warrior
in history who was ruthless
and powerful enough to
be given the name "Devil"!
[MORIA] This is Oars!
[USOPP] What the
hell's going on here?
Are they really going
to use Luffy's shadow
to awaken that monster?
[NAMI] I think I finally
understand the mystery
of the zombies.
Wait! Let go!
What are you doing?
[USOPP] Nami! What's wrong?
[NAMI] That invisible
bastard is here again!
[USOPP] Nami, you're,
you're disappearing!!
[NAMI] What? I am?
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Awakening After 500 Years!!
Oars Opens His Eyes!!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!