Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose
body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy was sent flying
from the Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma.
After soaring
through the sky for hours,
he found himself in a kingdom
inhabited entirely by women.
Its name was Amazon Lily.
[AMAZONS screaming]
[KIKYO] Don't let him escape!
[LUFFY] There she is! Perfect!
[NARRATOR] Luffy captured a Kuja
Warrior by the name of Margaret
and fled their village,
but could not escape the island.
If this keeps up much longer,
I'll end up growing
attached to you!
Hold on! Just stop!
I am Vice-Admiral Momonga
of Navy Headquarters!
Warlord of the Sea and
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock,
I have come for you!
Reveal yourself!
[HANCOCK] I already told you,
I like being a warlord.
However, I loathe
the World Government.
I have no interest
in following their orders.
Surely I can
find a better solution.
Love-Love Beam!
[MOMONGA]
Unless you reappear in two days,
your position will be revoked!
Do as you wish.
[LUFFY]
The Secret Hidden on the Backs.
Luffy and the
Snake Princess Meet.
[AMAZON 411A] Open the gate!
[AMAZON 411A]
The Snake Princess has returned!
[AMAZONS cheering
in excitement]
[AMAZON 411A]
We missed you!
Welcome home, Kuja Pirates!
We're glad you're back!
[AMAZON 411B]
We love you, Snake Princess!
[AMAZON 411C]
Looking good, Ran!
[AMAZON 411D]
You're the best, Daisy!
We brought back lots of loot!
They're so awesome!
I'm gonna join the
pirates when I grow up!
[cheering continues]
It's the Gorgon Sisters!
[AMAZON 411E]
I love you, Snake Princess!
[AMAZON 411F]
Welcome home, Daisy!
[AMAZON 411G]
Ran! Daisy! Hey, Rindo!
[AMAZON 411H] Bluefan!
[AMAZON 411I] Cosmos!
Welcome home, Marigold!
Hey, Sandersonia!
They're really worked up.
They simply missed
our dear sister.
It was a lengthy journey.
Can you blame them?
She smiled at me!
No, she was smiling at me!
Welcome back, Princess.
We've prepared a
Monkey Carriage for you.
Is there anything to report?
No. Everything's fine.
[AMAZON 411K] Gently, now.
It's quite fragile,
carry it slowly.
Iron ore, gunpowder,
alcohol and northern crops.
What a truly impressive haul!
[RAN] Yeah. We plundered
a couple of merchant vessels
and one pirate ship.
Not to mention the
loads of cargo we claimed
from a central government ship.
You Kuja Pirates really are
a force to be reckoned with.
Guess so.
Are you handling the
Snake Princess' gift?
Oh yeah, don't worry.
It's on the way
to the castle now.
[NYON]
Ran, did you collect any books?
[NYON] Down here.
[RAN] Granny Nyon! Books, huh?
Oh! We did appropriate
a recent newspaper
off the
Central Government ship.
Here. All yours.
Nyo my goodness!
[AMAZONS]
Welcome back, Snake Princess.
We're so glad to have
you home, Snake Princess.
Me, too.
It's nice to be back.
I thought you
might want to enjoy
your spoils of war,
so I've polished
the most exquisite jewel
from the batch for you.
[HANCOCK] Oh?
Oh, wow!
No jewel in the world
can compare to her smile!
But Snake Princess!
A gaudy rock like that
would be an unsightly
blemish upon my beauty.
[HANCOCK]
Enishida. What is this?
[ENISHIDA] Oh! I forgot.
The children of the
village lovingly crafted
a statue of your likeness
out of clay as a gift.
It's endearing
how much love and labor
they poured into its creation.
Well!
We made this to show
the Snake Princess
how much we love her!
It took them forever
to bring it up to the castle
because it would break
if they dropped it.
Don't you think it's cute?
[HANCOCK] Hmm...
It's me.
But made out of mud.
Snake Princess!
[HANCOCK] Don't bring
such filth into the castle.
It's inelegant!
Throw it away at once
and clean the floor.
[HANCOCK] I'm curious, Enishida.
Oh? About?
I couldn't help but
notice the city defenders
were absent from the
wharf upon our arrival.
Uh... Actually, you see...
A ferocious and violent monkey
came rampaging
out of the jungle.
The size and brute
strength of the beast
was simply astonishing.
So everyone has left
for the jungle to hunt it.
I see.
[LUFFY] Woo-hooooo!
There he is!
Take this.
Has the beast met his end?
Look! He's over there!
[APHELANDRA] Are all men
as stubborn as this one?
Do not think you
can escape your death.
It's no concern.
They'll be back shortly.
I am truly sorry they
weren't there to greet you.
[HANCOCK] No matter.
[ENISHIDA] Well then.
Would you care for a drink?
White sake.
[NYON] Gyo ahead and make
that two while you're at it.
[HANCOCK] Granny Nyon,
how nice of you to
defile my private chambers.
I didn't see you come in!
[AMAZON 411N]
How did you get in here?
Forget "how". I'm here.
Get rid of her.
Hold on!
Listen, Snake Princess!
[HANCOCK] You forgot "please".
Now say it.
Please listen, Snake Princess.
I have just learned that
there's a ship from Central
anchored off our shores.
They've come here
with the express purpose
of summoning you,
have they nyot?
The Central Government has
ordered you into active duty.
[HANCOCK] That's right.
They want me to go to war.
Why are you here?
You must go!
You must uphold the agreement
or they'll revoke your title!
I nyo you've just returned.
But surely you still
have the strength to fight.
I do.
But I'm afraid to go!
Aww!
She's like a widdle puppy.
Wait! I'm nyot fallin' for that!
[ENISHIDA]
That really got to her.
Nyow. Think this through.
All that is truly protecting our
nation is your title as Warlord.
[NYON] Our greatest
deterrence from outside forces
is Amazon Lily's location,
here in the Sea King-riddled
waters of the Calm Belt.
But as time marches forward,
so does technology.
And nyow these Central
dwellers have ships
that provide them with safe
passage through these parts.
We need a new weapon
to keep them at bay.
Your rank as Warlord
is the sole reason
they avoid our shores
despite the activities
of the Kuja Pirates.
[NYON] Think of your people.
Our island is home to
helpless children and elderly.
If you lost your title,
Amazon Lily would just be
another nation of pirates!
And the government
would bring ruin to us!
Now you're the one who
sounds like she's afraid.
[NYON] I am old.
I could drop dead at any moment.
Gaze into this crystal
ball and see your future!
Oh, my!
Her crystal ball is always
right about the future!
It's never wrong about anything!
I shall conjure
an image of your fate.
Nyon! Nyon! Nyon! Nyon!
Nyon! Nyon! Nyon!
Nyon nyon nyon nyon nyon!
[NYON] Your fortune!
You idiot.
[HANCOCK] Throw her out!
Right now!
Yes, of course, Snake Princess!
Wait, hear me out!
Nyot so rough!
[HANCOCK] I listen respectfully
and you treat me like a fool.
Did you think I'd fall
for your chicanery?
Your reign here ended well
over three generations ago.
How dare you act like
you're still the empress
of Amazon Lily...
...Gloriosa.
It doesn't matter what I do.
I could lay waste to every
inch of this nation of ours.
On a whim.
And still,
I would be forgiven
because I'm beautiful!
[ENISHIDA] Amazing!
She looks down on people
so much that she looks up!
[HANCOCK] Why on earth
should I listen to the words
of a disgraced ruler
who abandoned her people
to journey the outer seas?
Traitor to the Kuja!
So I live alone in penance
on the outskirts of town!
Nyon nyon nyon...
Which is where you should
be at this very moment.
Do not presume
to tell me what to do!
I'm the reigning empress!
[AMAZONS] Snake Princess?
[NYON]
Put me down already! Nyon!
That said,
I can't help but admire
your overwhelming passion.
You may be right.
[NYON] You agree to my request?
Thank you for understanding
the needs of your people!
How wonderful!
So. How soon
will you be leaving?
Never.
Know your place, fool!
Nyon!
[HANCOCK]
Now get out of my sight!
A curse on you,
Snake Princess!
Nyooooon!
[AMAZON 411K] Snake Princess...
[AMAZON 411L] You threw
an old woman out the window!
On accident.
Oh, of course!
We know it wasn't your fault!
[HANCOCK] Now clean up
all this broken glass.
[AMAZONS] Yes, ma'am!
That irritating old hag.
Nyooooon!
Granny Nyon?
I may be old, but I'm
still a Kuja warrior.
My skills
haven't withered a bit.
I touched her.
Have you prepared
my bathwater yet?
Yes. I'll issue the
advisory immediately.
[gong ringing]
[ENISHIDA]
Your attention please!
The Snake Princess
will now bathe!
Now...
Stay still, I'm almost done.
Whoa! Sorry!
[ENISHIDA] You must
evacuate the castle now!
Hey, come on, we've gotta go!
But I just sat down,
I'm still eating!
[AMAZON 411S]
Come on, hurry everyone!
[ENISHIDA] If you're on duty
today, report to your posts!
Sounds like it's bath time.
Get ready, girls.
They're clearing
out the castle now.
It's about
to get packed in here.
[ENISHIDA]
For the next several hours,
no one is allowed to enter the
castle under any circumstances!
[RAN] What are you doing here?
You know you're not allowed
past the barrier, right?
Yeah.
But why's it such a big deal
when the Empress takes a bath?
Everyone acts like we're
going to war or something.
First things first,
how old are you?
Eight years old.
Well, then I think
I can tell you.
Wait, you don't mean...
...the secret?
That's right.
[HANCOCK] You're in
charge of keeping watch.
[MARIGOLD]
As you wish, dear sister.
[SANDERSONIA] Take your time.
You see, the
Gorgon was a monster.
It stalked the tides
of the Central Oceans.
If anyone made the mistake
of gazing upon this
horrifying creature,
they would be turned to stone.
[RAN]
After facing countless perils
along a
treacherous journey,
The Snake Princess and her
sisters encountered the monster
and managed to slay it.
[HANCOCK yelling]
[RAN] But the screams
of the dying abomination
were laced with evil,
and it placed the
sisters under a curse.
The penetrating eyes
of the monster
were etched across the
flesh of the sisters' backs.
So they remain,
forever staring, even today.
And if anyone gazes
upon these wicked eyes,
their body will harden
into stone and they'll die.
[RAN]
That's why the Gorgon sisters
refuse to remove their
clothing before another human.
[RAN] As a matter of precaution,
they always post guards
when they bathe.
And they secure
and evacuate the castle.
[LUFFY yelling]
[hissing]
[LUFFY] That hurts!
Sounds like the
man's over there!
The snakes must have found him.
[LUFFY yelling]
Stop! Get off me!
Did you see where he went?
Yeah, he ran up
the side of the mountain!
You don't think he
could be headed back
to the village, do you?
I thought he was bound and
determined to find a ship.
What?
There we go.
Aw, jeez, that really sucked.
Okay, now what's next?
They'll come and shoot me
with arrows if I just sit here.
[LUFFY] But wait a sec.
Margaret did say
they've got a pirate ship.
I wonder... how hard
it'd be to borrow it.
That won't work.
Nami's not here.
I'd get lost in
no time without her.
I got it!
All I gotta do is ask someone
for a ride in their ship!
Wherever they're going,
I'm sure they won't mind
a quick trip to Sabaody!
So who am I
gonna ask for a ride?
Probably gotta be someone
important and high up.
And if they're high up,
that means they gotta live
in a tall building, right?
My head's on fire
from all this thinking!
Right! Guess I'll just try the
first tall building I can find!
Let's see...
That one'll do!
[LUFFY yelling]
[KIKYO] We need to hurry!
By this point, the Snake
Princess has probably returned.
We'll be in trouble
if she finds the man!
[LUFFY yelling]
You suck, roof!
[AMAZON 411T]
What was that?
[AMAZON 411U] The roof of
the castle tower collapsed!
Oh, no!
This is bad.
That's where the Empress
is taking a bath!
More water?
Why the heck is it hot?
Am I in a bath?
[LUFFY] I can't breathe,
I'm drowning, I'm gonna die!
It's real shallow. I'm safe!
[LUFFY]
This is... a huge bath!
A man?
Hey...
That thing on your back.
It looks...
...kinda familiar.
You saw it?
[NARRATOR] Luffy is captured
once more after seeing
the Snake Princess' secret.
Margaret and her friends
try to defend him,
but Hancock is unmoved
and turns them all to stone.
Luffy is angry
to see the empress
petrify her own comrades,
but is powerless to help
as he faces his own execution.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
Heartless Judgment!
Margaret is Turned to Stone!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!