[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever
dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[NAMI sobs]
[NAMI]
Luffy...
[LUFFY] "Luffy in Big Trouble!
Fishmen vs. the Luffy Pirates!"
Huh?
What the‐‐?!
Now which one of you is Arlong?
Arlong?
[ARLONG] Well, that just
happens to be my name.
Good. You can call me Luffy.
Luffy...? What are you
supposed to be?
A pirate!
Huh? Hey, that guy...!
Wait a sec! I remember him...!
He's the guy who
likes going on walks!
[FISHMAN R]
Hold it right there.
[FISHMAN H] Hahaha!
Where do you think you're going?
[FISHMAN R]
You wanna talk to the boss?
Well you gotta talk
to us first. Get it?
So let's talk...
That's far enough.
Move it!
So what does a
pirate want with me?
Who the hell are you?
[NAMI]
Luffy... Help me.
That's for making
our navigator cry!
[SANJI] Back off!
You're outta your league!
[SANJI]
Geez...
You just had to run
on ahead by yourself.
Don't worry. I can handle
these bozos on my own.
Oh, you fool...
I never said anything
about being worried.
I just don't want you
hoggin' all the action.
[LUFFY]
Oh.
Well I just wanna let
you guys know that,
I don't mind if you hog it all.
[ZORO] I see you're
raring to go as usual.
[HATCHAN]
Ohhh!! It's him...!
That's the unknown swordsman
I was telling you about!
Roronoa Zoro...
I thought so...
That bastard tricked me...
I can't believe it.
I fell for it look,
sine, and yanker...
Wait. Hook, line, and sinker...
Hey look! Long nose is here!
Whaaa?! But... He's dead...!
We saw Nami kill him!
Oh, he's alive... Which means...
Hmph! That Nami was
a traitor all along...
Just as I suspected...
[VILLAGER A]
Who are those guys?!
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY]
Hold it!
That guy just decked Arlong!
[VILLAGER A]
Unbelievable!
No human should
be able to do that.
Are they...
Didn't we tell you...?
Just stay back here.
[JOHNNY]
Now do you understand
why we're keeping you
away from that fight...?
You guys'll just
get in their way.
But why...
That's what I don't understand.
What reason could they
possibly have to fight?
[YOSAKU]
Reason?
[JOHNNY]
Big Sis Nami was crying.
[YOSAKU] Do they
need any more reason
than that to put
their lives on the line?
A pirate...?
Of course.
[ARLONG] This is all
starting to make sense now...
You've been after
Nami this whole time...
But... Hahahaha!
The girl is mine and
I'm not giving her up!
[HATCHAN]
Hahahaha!
A bunch of idiots like
you aren't worth Arlong's time!
We know how to deal with you.
[trumpet fanfare]
[gasps]
Not that!
Oh no... It's here!
[USOPP]
What is goin' on here guys?!
[HATCHAN]
Hahahahaha!
Every single one of you is
about to become fish food!
Momoo! Rise!
It's a monster...!
That's the beast
from the Grand Line
that destroyed the town of Gosa!
Mooo...
Huh?
Aaaauugh!
It's actually real...! Oh no!
It's Momoo.
Well look who's back.
Seems he's a friend
of the fishmen.
Hey...! Stop...!
Where are you going?!
Get back here Momoo!
You can't just leave! Momoo!
Leaving...? Now, now...?
Isn't that a shame?
[ARLONG] But... I suppose if you
really want to run away,
then who am I to stop you?
Well then...?
[growls]
[roars]
[USOPP]
It's coming right for us!
[USOPP] Aaaaahh!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Ahhhhhh!
You're all mine...!
You dumb cow!
[roars]
Looks like he's got
a plan... For once.
We'll see. I've got a
bad feeling about this.
His arms stretched!
So he must have
Devil Fruit powers.
Powers?
Aw, who cares?!
[FISHMAN U]
Attack!
Hey, let's get out of here!
Whoa, wait...!
What's he gonna do?!
I'm not sure if
I want to find out!
Time for something new!
Gum‐Gum Pinwheel!
All right that's it Arlong!
I'm done playing games with you!
I didn't come here to
beat down all your cronies!
I came here teach you a lesson!
So step up!
Oh I will, don't worry...
Actually I was just
thinking about how painfully
I'll end your life.
That was the worst plan ever!
Yeah! Were you trying
to kill all of us too?!
Uh‐oh.
That boy's incredible.
I just can't believe
there's a human
who could throw
that giant monster!
It's as if the gods
themselves are fighting.
What are you doing...?!
Are you ruining something else?!
Huh?
[HATCHAN]
How dare you hurt our brother!
Very well...
It seems that we must
now join in the fight.
Now you'll get an education
in the inferiority
of your species. Choo.
Oh... really...
I'd like to see that.
Relax, sir...
Let us handle this.
If you go on one
of your rampages
to squash these insects,
you could destroy all
of Arlong Park. Choo.
Please just let us
kill these weaklings!
All right... They're yours.
Uh, guys... There's
something I should tell you.
What the hell's
that octopus doing?
Octopus is best when
it's cut thin and salted...
Add some olive oil and paprika
and it makes the perfect
snack while drinking.
So listen to me guys
I'm kind of in trouble...
Take this! Zero Vision!
Hachi Ink Jet!
Idiot...! How come
you didn't dodge that?!
Aaaaaah!
I can't see squat!
Now to finish you off!
C'mon! Get outta
there, Luffy! Run!
[LUFFY]
Yeah, that's the problem...
I can't run! I can't even walk!
Huh?
[LUFFY]
My feet are kinda stuck!
But you're the one who stuck 'em
into the ground
in the first place!
Always thinking ahead.
One Hachi Ink Jet
served on the rocks!
You're such a pain...
Sanji that was so
totally awesomely awesome!
Looks like I ended up
picking one hell of an idiot
to be my captain.
We all did.
Luffy's great...! Hey!
But the truth...
...is that our idiot
Captain is far better
than a gang who'd
prey on a lady.
A lady, huh? Hmph!
You rushed into certain
death for one lousy girl?
I think that's the
most ridiculous thing
I've ever heard.
"Lousy girl"...?
If you insult Nami
one more time,
I can promise that you'll go
from fishman to fish sticks...
Got that?
[KUROOBI] You're skills are
quite exceptional for a human...
But I must admit that chivalry
from a pirate seems
just a little fake.
I'm damn good at what I do,
and I guarantee
you there's nothing fake
about my desire to help
a beautiful lady in need.
Looks like I'll be
acquainting you
with the true superiority
of the fishman species.
Yeah?
Nice work...
But they're still stuck.
[USOPP]
Still? They're still stuck?
We could pull all day...
And I bet my legs would
still be stuck in there.
Hey, are you trying at all?!
Or do you want
to stay stuck here?!
Maybe no one told you,
that the penalty for playing
around in Arlong Park...
...is death!
[USOPP panicked cries]
C'mon!
Get unstuck already!
Get unstuck!
Please Luffy! Come on!
Come here!
[ZORO]
Hey, Octopus!
They're a little bit
busy at the moment.
Why don't you take me on?
Ohh!! You're Zoro...!
I forgot...!
You can't get away
with tricking me!
[HATCHAN] And how dare
you mercilessly slaughter
so many of my brothers!
That stuff's old news,
octopus man...
I personally don't care
what reasons you have
for wanting to kill me.
The situation has changed...
You see the
tables have turned...
You're not the hunters
anymore understand?
Now it's you fish freaks
who're being hunted!
Yeah you tell him Zoro...
That octopus guy
is yours... Nice.
Luffy!
Huh?
Hey, I'm back.
Oh, you're dead.
Aw, crap.
I get it now...
You must actually
want me to kill you.
Hold on...
Wasn't that the guy who
saved Genzo's life earlier?
Hey, wait... You're the
people from Cocoyashi.
Judging from the fact
that you all have weapons,
I can only assume
that this is a rebellion.
Then you'll all have to‐‐
[USOPP]
Exploding Star!
[YOSAKU]
Big Bro Usopp!
Did you think it would be easy?!
You're dealing with me now!
Enough!
I'm going to get
rid of you right now!
[USOPP screams]
Who is that lad?
Brave one minute
and cowardly the next.
He's a baffling man.
[CHOO]
Get back here "long nose"!
[USOPP] Oh, you're one
to talk "big mouth."
[NOJIKO]
Why are these people pirates?
You morons are a
pathetic sight to behold.
I'm sick of watching this.
Now get out of my way.
But sir,
there's no reason
to go on a rampage.
Think of Arlong Park.
[ARLONG]
Don't worry I won't.
I just thought of
a fun game that's all.
Game, huh?
Now you're going down!
Do you honestly think your
sad little group can defeat us?
So what if we do.
Yeah, so what if we do, huh?
Now let go!
You got something to say to us?
[LUFFY]
No way! No way! No way!
Did you know that those
with Devil Fruit
powers can't swim?
But honestly,
anybody in this situation
would sink right to the bottom.
Hahahaha!
The sea...?! No!
Gum‐Gum Pistol!
Ouchie!
You fool.
How pointless.
[ZORO]
Luffy!
[SANJI]
Damn you!
[ARLONG]
Ahahahahaha!
[ZORO]
Wait! Don't be stupid!
Those fishmen
can't wait for us to jump
in the water after him...
They'd have an obvious advantage
in an underwater fight.
[ZORO] There's only
one way to save Luffy.
We gotta take these guys
out at the same time,
then go in the water.
[ZORO] There's no time,
come on, let's do it.
[SANJI]
Yeah.
So, how long can
he hold out huh...?
Time is ticking.
Oh, so that's the game.
I get it.
[ARLONG laughs]
You can take the fish.
You slice and trim the octopus.
Hahaha!
[LUFFY] This is bad...
I'm almost outta breath!
What now?!
He can't help himself!
What do we do?!
Big Bro Luffy's gonna die!
[ARLONG laughs]
They can't even
breathe underwater!
Humans are such pitiful
creatures, aren't they?
Hahahahaha!
Hey...! Calamari...! Let's go!
[HATCHAN laughs]
Game! Game!
I'll kick your ass
in five seconds flat!
We don't have more than three!
Hey... What's the rush...?
You're both running
headlong into death...
None of you will
leave this place alive.
[HATCHAN]
Hachi Ink Jet!
[ZORO]
Hang on...
...Luffy!
[USOPP]
Aw, crap! I'm gonna be killed!
All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
♪As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way♪
[LUFFY]
I can't breathe!
[ZORO]
You stupid octopus!
I don't give a damn about you!
I gotta hurry and save Luffy!
[SANJI]
Hey!
Are those the wounds
you got from Hawk‐Eye...
[ZORO] Shut up! I can't
afford to pass out here!
[USOPP]
Wait! Is running all I do?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Luffy Submerged! Zoro vs.
Hatchan the Octopus!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!