[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
My money says that
we live through this.
A cloud road that
goes straight up?
You might wanna
reconsider that bet.
[USOPP, CHOPPER scream]
I wonder if this is a natural
formation of the clouds.
There's nothing natural
about this at all!
[laughs]
[gasps]
[CHOPPER]
Look! The exit!
They put up a big
sign showing us!
[ROBIN]
Godland?
What is Godland Skypiea?
This isn't the exit.
It's the entrance!
[laughing]
[LUFFY] "Godland, Skypiea!
Angels on a Beach of Clouds!"
[ALL yell]
There it is!
Sky island!
[USOPP, CHOPPER gasp]
Wait. Didn't the sign
we passed say Skypiea?
[NAMI chuckles]
[NAMI]
Yeah, that's the same name
scribbled on the map
that Luffy found.
So I guess that galleon
that fell on us
actually did come here.
The last time they set eyes
on this was 200 years ago.
I'm amazed that this place has
stayed beautiful for so long.
Ahh.
You can smell the adventure!
Potent as the seaweed in summer!
[USOPP]
Wait for me! I like adventure!
It's kinda shallow.
Usopp. Did you hurt yourself?
Hello?
Hey, is it just me, or is this
whole place made of clouds?
Big fluffy ones!
I love this stuff!
[BOTH chuckle]
C'mon! Let's go ashore!
[USOPP]
Yeah!
[BOTH laughing]
Wait! I'm coming with you guys!
Me, too. But I gotta
change first.
Luffy, we may have a problem
with dropping anchor here.
There's no seabed at the
bottom of this cloud.
You know, I thought about
that, and who cares?!
[USOPP chuckles]
I love the way you think!
Thanks!
[BOTH laughing]
[CHOPPER]
Me, too! I wanna play!
[LUFFY, USOPP, CHOPPER laughing]
[LUFFY] Hop on down and
check this out, you guys!
The beach is actually fluffy!
[USOPP] It squishes between
my toes like marshmallow mud!
[LUFFY] What the heck
is marshmallow mud?
[USOPP] I dunno,
but that's what it's like.
Well, regardless of how
the ground may feel,
it sure is an amazing sight.
Better than I imagined it.
It's a piece of work for sure,
but I think our shipmates
are overreacting.
[SANJI chuckles]
[SANJI] Bugs me when
they get all worked up.
[laughing]
[ZORO]
When they get all worked up?
[thudding]
[NAMI] Ow! You're hurting
me! I said I was sorry!
[NAMI] Uh, we forgot
about the South Bird.
We really should've let him go.
He'll never survive here.
I wouldn't sweat it.
Birds adapt very quickly
to their environments.
And if not, there seem to be
some people living up here.
Don't worry about
it. He'll be fine.
Yeah. I guess.
Hey, the anchor!
All taken care of.
It hit the heavier cloud below,
which is what I think
this place floats on.
[ROBIN] That means that
sky island floats
on a sea of cloudcover.
I wonder if it's
stationary in the sky
or if it moves with the tide.
We could sit on deck all day
and pick this whole thing apart,
but, come on, what
fun would that be?
Fact is, most of this
makes zero sense,
so let's make the best of it.
[laughs]
This is why we came
here, you guys!
Welcome to sky island!
Come on! If I can do
this, so can you!
Just jump!
[ROBIN]
Swordsman, you joining us?
Yeah. I'll be along soon.
The captain smells
adventure. Huh.
I never stopped to think of
any of this as adventurous.
Maybe I should
reconsider my stance.
[splash]
Something about the
squishiness of this island
makes me wanna sleep all day.
[LUFFY] Ahoy! This is
your captain speaking!
I must inform you that this
place is too much fun
for me to make anymore
captain decisions.
Aye-aye, Captain.
What do you say we just
sit and do nothing? Eh?
Nothing sounds like
a plan to me. Denied!
[USOPP]
But "denied" means "no"!
[SANJI]
Such mysterious-looking flowers.
I've never seen
anything like them.
[SANJI]
I wonder if they're balloon-ish
like that sea monster,
if they'll pop when
I pick one...
This is great!
Those Marine losers
can't follow us up here,
so we can all cut loose.
[NAMI] Hey, Chopper. What do
you think that is over there?
What?
All right, Mr. Giant Fruit,
you're all mine--
Ow, well, that hurt.
Why's this thing so hard?
Hey, Usopp!
[USOPP]
Yeah?
[LUFFY]
Got some fruit for ya!
[USOPP] You practically crammed
my brain into my chest!
What's wrong with you?
[LUFFY laughing]
[SANJI]
Wait up, Robin, baby!
I've got a present for you.
An island flower.
And one, for, uh... Nami!
Nami, baby!
Where'd you run off to?!
I've got a gift for you!
[NAMI]
Whoa.
I can't believe I'm on
a chair made of cloud.
I wonder is they have a factory
that makes all this stuff.
This cloud is different from
the stuff on the beach.
It's a lot spongier.
[SANJI]
Nami!
[ZORO]
I didn't figure on gettin' wet
walkin' through clouds.
Huh? What's that?
[SUU]
Suu! Suu!
[ZORO]
Hm?
[ZORO yelps]
[ZORO]
Sorry.
Huh. And what do we have
here? Some kinda fox?
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Is that music?
Look. There's
someone over there.
On that cloud!
[growls] Oh, great.
It's another monster.
[CHOPPER] Where's the whistle?
Where's the whistle?
We can ask the Sky
Knight to save us!
No, we can't.
That's not who you think
it is. That right there...
...is an angel.
An angel?
Heso.
[BOTH]
Heso?
You think she's trying
to say hello?
What does "heso" mean?
It kinda sounds like "hello."
Suu. Come here.
[SUU]
Suu!
[CONIS] Did you come
from the Blue Sea World?
[LUFFY]
If that's what you call it.
We sailed up a river
of clouds to get here.
Speaking of "here,"
is this is your home?
[CONIS]
Yes, it sure is.
And I'd like to welcome you
to Skypiea's Angel Beach.
I bet you'd like to drink that.
[LUFFY]
Mh-hm.
The top of a conush
is as hard as steel.
It's impossible to crack,
so you have to cut through
the underside, like this.
[CONIS]
Here ya go.
[SUU]
Suu.
If it's that good,
I gotta try some.
C'mon, give it to me!
[USOPP slurping]
My name is Conis, and
this little one is Suu.
She's a cloud fox.
If you need anything at all,
please let me be of service.
Yeah, about that.
Your eyes are setting
my heart on fi--!
Lay off.
Actually, we've got
tons of questions.
I hate to bother you,
but we've never been any
place like this before.
Sure, ask me anything
you wanna know.
Guys, look. Something's coming.
Oh, that's my father.
[PAGAYA]
Heso, Conis!
[CONIS]
Heso, Father!
Can't you say hello
like normal people?
[NAMI gasps]
Conis, what's that
thing he's riding on?
Ah, that would be
my father's waver.
[LUFFY]
Whoa! That's awesome!
A sky waver.
[PAGAYA] Gang way! Stopping
this thing is a bit of a trick!
[PAGAYA yelping]
[groans]
[PAGAYA] My goodness.
I-Is everyone all right?
You're the one who crashed!
Hey, Luffy, didn't you bring
back something like that waver
from the seabed?
Uh, yeah. I did, didn't I?
Huh.
Then that must be the
boat we read about
in that "Noland, the Liar" book.
A boat that can
sail without wind.
Did you make some new
friends, Conis, my dear?
[CONIS]
Yes.
They arrived only a few minutes
ago from the Blue Sea World.
[PAGAYA]
Oh, still adjusting.
There must be a great many
things that puzzle you
about the White White Sea.
I'm sorry.
[USOPP]
There's no need to apologize.
[PAGAYA] Forgive me for not
introducing myself sooner.
My name is Pagaya.
[USOPP] Oh, it's, uh,
very nice to meet you.
So, Father, how was
the fishing today?
[PAGAYA]
Quite a successful venture.
I have an idea. You all
should come over for dinner.
We'll fill your bellies with
the taste of the island.
I'm all for that! I'm starving!
Sky island cuisine?
Do you mind if I help
you prepare it?
[PAGAYA]
No!
Before we go, I have a question.
This boat, it doesn't have
any sails to catch the wind
and you weren't
rowing it either,
so how is it propelled
through the water?
Oh, of course.
Your people aren't familiar
with dials are they?
What're dials?
[screams]
[screaming]
[LUFFY]
Why won't it stop?!
[LUFFY screams]
[CONIS]
Oh, no! I hope he's all right!
It's all my fault!
I shouldn't have let a
rookie use the waver.
Since Luffy can't swim,
I hope this sea is more
buoyant than ours.
Maybe.
If it can stay floating in the
air, then you're probably right.
He can handle it.
[LUFFY gargling]
[SANJI]
Huh? He sank.
[ZORO] Eh, it's not the first
time I've been wrong.
[CHOPPER]
Ah! I'll save you!
[SANJI]
That was close.
[ZORO] Close? You were
standing on the beach!
What do you know about "close"?
Oh, yeah, and thanks for
all the help, by the way!
[USOPP] Was it really necessary
for you to jump in too?
Sky island scary.
I apologize for letting
him take the waver out.
With its light body,
even a small wave
can shake the rudder.
Unless you know the White White
Sea like the back of your hand,
the waver is almost
impossible to ride.
Again, I am sorry.
It's only recently that I
became good enough to ride it.
Whoa! Is it really that hard?
It usually takes ten years
of training to drive it.
You gotta be joking!
Wow! Look at her go!
[NAMI]
This is wonderful!
Oh, Nami! You're a vision
riding that waver!
That's incredible!
I can't believe it!
This is her first time?
Yeah! How come she can
do it and I can't?!
[NAMI]
Wow! This really requires skill!
No wonder you had
a hard time Luffy!
[NAMI laughing]
[LUFFY]
Nami, we're invited to dinner,
so get off that thing
and stop being so rude!
[SANJI]
Talk about rude.
[LUFFY]
Stupid waver hog!
[NAMI]
You guys go on ahead.
If it's okay with Pagaya, I'd
like to stay out here and ride.
[PAGAYA]
That's fine. Just be careful.
[NAMI] Riding this freely
on the open ocean
without worrying about
the wind is like a dream!
I wonder if we can use these
on our ocean back home.
Whoa. Is that some
kinda factory?
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
[PAGAYA]
Indeed it is.
That is our cloud quarry site.
It's where our clouds
are manufactured
and cut to meet all
types of needs.
[ZORO] I didn't know
you could cut a cloud.
[PAGAYA]
You did take the Milky Road
to get to the White
White Sea, correct?
[ZORO]
Milky Road?
Is that the name of that messed
up current we took up here?
[PAGAYA]
Yes.
It's a canal constructed
by our engineers
and made using the natural
clouds we quarry.
There are actually two types of
natural clouds on our island.
Your ship traveled atop
what we call sea clouds.
And the ones that
float on their own,
that we can stand on and build
on, are called island clouds.
They're not the normal clouds
that we're used to, are they?
[PAGAYA]
No.
Their condensation
nucleus is different
from what you usually see.
It has to do with a mineral
found in the Blue Sea World
called Sea Prism Stone.
Sea Prism Stone?
What affect does that
have on the clouds?
[PAGAYA]
It's like this.
Inside the Sea Prism
are carnelian particles
called pyrobrine.
During volcanic eruptions,
these particles gain moisture
and ascend into the sky.
Our clouds are formed based on
the density of the moisture.
Oh, yeah. I heard
about those things.
Sure. I remember that
from when I was a kid.
We used to always play with
carnelian particles in the yard.
Enough sarcasm!
In all actuality,
there are three types of clouds
that we use in our day to day.
The sea and island
types are natural.
The man-made ones come
from island clouds.
Now if you'll follow me, please.
[LUFFY] Check out the
view from up here!
[CHOPPER]
Look!
If you squint, you can see
Nami riding the waver!
[SANJI]
Luffy, what are you waiting on?
How come she's so good
at that stupid thing?
Fall off!
[SANJI]
Cut it out!
[LUFFY] Thanks, Sanji!
You just made me bite my tongue!
I'm bleeding!
[SANJI]
Poor baby.
Hey, Pagaya, which
way to the kitchen?
[PAGAYA]
It's right up here.
[coughing]
What happened to you?
Well, I saw this stuff sitting
in your fridge, and I, uh...
I'd never seen anything like it,
so I tried it, and... and...
It tastes like death.
Now I'm all dizzy and
my tongue feels swollen.
How's it look?
Like you drank some
spoiled sauce.
[SANJI] Then why did you leave
this stuff sitting around?
If something's old,
you throw it...
It sounds like they're
havin' fun in the kitchen.
I bet Sanji's just excited
about sky island food
being such a new thing.
So, uh, I was wondering.
Could you explain
some more to us
about these dials you
mentioned earlier?
[CONIS]
Sure.
But it's complex. I don't
exactly know where to start.
Ah. I've never been
this relaxed.
[LUFFY]
Hm.
This doesn't look like a dial.
It's just a seashell.
Yes, at first glance,
but why don't you put it
to your mouth and talk?
[LUFFY]
Like this?
Usopp stinks.
Why do you always pick on me?
[CONIS giggles]
[CONIS] Now just press
down the apex of the shell.
Wanna tell me what an apex is?
It means vertex
or highest point.
[LUFFY]
Usopp stinks!
Ah! The seashell's makin'
fun of Usopp, too!
What'd I ever do
to you, seashell?!
[CONIS] ...press down
the apex of the shell.
Hey, that's a neat trick.
So it can store any
sound and play it back?
Then that shell is
one of the dials.
Yes. We call this
one a tone dial.
It is a shell from
the White White Sea
that records and replays
whatever it hears.
[LUFFY]
Ah.
Hey, hold on. I didn't think
there was a bottom to your sea.
Where do these
things live anyway?
They live in the shallows
in cloud reefs.
I still don't see
how that little thing
could move your
father's sky waver.
Well, that's because this is
the kind that powers the waver.
It's smaller, but it does
demonstrate the same process.
Here. Let me show you.
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Ohh.
[USOPP] So this one blows
wind out of its backside.
Lemme see.
This is called a breath dial.
It allows you the ability
to store the wind
and expel it at your desire.
[yells]
[CONIS] The wind capacity
varies depending on
the size of the shell.
If you attach the right size
to the stern of a ship,
you can move along swiftly.
I've never heard of
anything like that.
I get it now.
The waver moved by blowing
a stream of wind
through the water.
That waver is fun.
Dials don't just power wavers.
There's also the skating kind,
the board kind.
But I don't go for those.
The waver is about
as crazy as I get.
[LUFFY] I wish I was out there
on that thing instead of Nami.
And I could be if I
could just figure out
how to fix the one we have.
How did you ever find
a waver in your world?
Well, it's kinda
hard to even tell
if that's what it is, you know.
That hunk of junk is 200
years old and a total wreck.
There's no way it works.
[CONIS]
That might not be the case.
Dials are made from the
remains of dead shellfish.
They can last indefinitely
so long as the shell
itself isn't broken.
You might get lucky.
I told ya so.
[USOPP] You never said
anything like that.
[LUFFY]
I know.
[ROBIN] I'd venture a guess
there are many types of dials.
Is this one here?
Yes. That's a lamp dial.
Neat! It lit up from inside!
[CONIS] Right. There are flame
dials that store heat and fire.
Flavor dials that store
various tastes and aromas.
And wision dials that store
everything the user sees,
which you can watch
again and again.
I wanna live in the clouds
for the rest of my life.
To be honest, we couldn't really
sustain life here in the clouds
without these dials.
Huh.
Our culture has evolved
with the dials.
I suppose in the same
way they evolved
with the White White Sea.
[snoring]
[SANJI] Ladies and gentlemen,
dinner is served.
We have for you sky lobster
with special sauce
and a side of island fruits
that I can't pronounce.
[LUFFY]
That looks so good!
Let's dig in!
[LUFFY]
Oh, wow! It tastes sweet!
[USOPP] I wouldn't have
expected it from lobster.
[LUFFY]
Yum!
Hey, guys. Any of you
know where Nami is?
I think she's riding the waver.
I don't see her.
She probably went out
too far. She's like that.
Who cares? You should
have some of this!
I'm worried. Do you
think she's okay?
I have my concerns, but I can't
say one way or the other.
Uh, what're you talkin' about?
In the clouds, there's a
place called the Upper Yard
that no one is ever allowed
to set step foot on.
It's not too far away.
It would only be a short
trip by waver from here.
I'm afraid your friend Nami
might've set ashore there
out of curiousity.
They're huge. What is this?
[USOPP]
What's so bad that no one
can ever go over to this island?
Is it full of monsters?
It's sacred ground.
Sacred ground?
But it's so much more
than just that.
It's the island...
where God lives.
Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear-blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...
[NAMI] This is one
creepy looking place.
[LUFFY] That's what places
we're not supposed to go
usually look like.
[CHOPPER]
You wanna go anyway. I can tell.
[SANJI] Guys, we should
really look for Nami.
[LUFFY]
I'm game!
[USOPP]
But what about me?!
[LUFFY]
Can't say that I really care.
[ZORO] Heh. Looks like we're
headed for another disaster.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Forbidden Sacred Ground!
The Island Where God Lives
and Heaven's Judgement!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!