Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of
pirates go to battle
across the seas in
search of the One Piece,
the legendary
treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating
the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer
numerous obstacles
they capture
the unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR]
With a charted course
awash in
danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path
across the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison, Impel Down.
Luffy has now made
his way down to Level 2,
known as the Wild Beast Hell,
along with Buggy the Clown.
[BASILISK roars]
[BOTH]
Holy crap!
Now that's
a Wild Beast of Hell!
[LUFFY yells]
What are you doing?
Third gear!
[LUFFY yells]
[GUARDS yell]
What's that?
You say someone
broke into the prison?
Absurd!
This is Impel Down.
No one has ever
infiltrated its walls.
Our defenses are flawless;
how could we
possibly allow this?
[HANCOCK]
Have they found us out?
Transfer the video
footage to my chambers!
[HANCOCK]
Warden?
I was wondering,
would it be possible to
see the prisoner? Now?
Sure! Let's go! Like right now!
Warden! Wake up!
We kind of need you
to deal with this.
[MR. 3] I couldn't
help but overhear you.
If you're having trouble
on this floor, I can help.
Is that so. Who're you?
[MR. 3 cackles]
Long time no see,
Straw Hat Luffy!
You helped me out
without noticing.
How fortunate.
I am a man who always
pays back his debts.
[LUFFY]
Do I know you?
[MR. 3 sighs]
Eh...
Wait! It's the "3" hair!
Oh yeah!
You were on the island
with the giants, right?
"Three"!
Mister Three, you fool!
[MR. 3 laughs]
[LUFFY]
"A Warlord in Prison!
Jimbei, the Honorable Pirate!"
[GUARD 430A] When I was
assigned to this level,
I was a little apprehensive,
but it's a lot more
laid-back than you'd think.
[GUARD 430B] Yeah, we got
this place under control.
No big deal.
What'd you think
it was gonna be like?
Well, the lowest floor is home
to some of the most
dangerous guys here.
[SURVEILLANCE GUARD 430A]
Most of them have bounties
of at least 100 million berries.
The rest are infamous in their
own right, bounty or no.
I was pretty nervous
when they told me
I was assigned to
the bottom floor.
And even more nervous
when they told me it was
called the "Eternal Hell,"
but it's only really
bad for the prisoners.
In other words, I wouldn't
worry about it too much.
Once they're here,
they'll never see
the light of day.
Well, not until their
execution at least.
Too bad.
'Cause if you ask me,
death would be a heck
of a lot easier
than spendin' the rest of
your life in this hell hole.
[GUARD 430A]
You got a point there.
[GUARDS laugh]
[GUARD 430D]
Pardon the intrusion,
but the Warden and Vice Warden
are on their way
here with Boa Hancock.
We already got the head's up.
Kinda makes ya wonder
what she wants with
Fire Fist Ace, though.
Do you have a theory?
That's a good question.
Man, sounds scary, though.
The pirate princess
and one of the most dangerous
men in the world.
I don't like it. One bit.
[gasps]
[SURVEILLANCE GUARD 430A]
Speaking of dangerous men,
that other guy
who's a Warlord--
the one who rebelled
against Navy Headquarters--
he's got me on edge too.
[growling]
[cell door creaks]
[JIMBEI]
Strike me!
[JIMBEI growls]
I have no regrets!
--[JIMBEI growls]
--[cell door creaks]
[JIMBEI]
That violent oaf.
Yeah, Captain.
I'm sorry. Them's the breaks.
[JIMBEI sighs]
My body is fine.
My heart, however...
Craves justice.
My heart wants war.
Jimbei.
I can't die.
Not here and not like this!
To hell with my
title as a Warlord.
I don't even want it anymore!
If it means that
I could stop this fight,
I would happily lay
down my own life.
[CURLY SURVEILLANCE GUY]
No wonder we lost
communication with Level 2.
Those prisoners knocked
a Basilisk right
into the com room!
Those two were able
to beat a Basilisk?
Where the hell are they anyway?
[SHAGGY SURVEILLANCE GUY]
And what is goin' on down there?
[Mr 3., LUFFY, BUGGY yelling]
Wait! Hold on.
There they are! I've got 'em!
[MOUSTACHE GUARD]
You do? Really?
Yes, sir.
But now it seems
there are three of them.
There's what?
[MANTICORES panting]
[HIPPO 425A panting]
[MANTIS 425A panting ]
[CENTIPEDE 430A growling]
[ALL panting]
Nice job, I think
every Wild Beast
on this floor is
chasing us now!
[LUFFY panting]
Okay, guys.
We can't keep running
like this forever!
Yeah, and the longer
we run the more people
they're gonna send after us
'cause this ain't
exactly subtle, you know!
Still, somehow
that sounds better
than gettin' eaten
by these things!
[MR. 3 sighs]
I'm too exhausted!
I can't keep this up!
[BEASTS growling]
[LUFFY] I don't have
time for this crap!
Gum-Gum!
--[BUGGY] Chop-Chop!
--[MR. 3] Candle Lock!
--[BUGGY] Cannon!
--[MR. 3] Pistol!
[BEASTS yell]
[LUFFY]
The big centipede just exploded
into a bunch
of little ones!
[MR. 3]
What centipede?
It was a bunch of
poisonous Puzzle Scorpions
stacked on top of one another!
[BUGGY] Now there are
more things chasing us!
[MR. 3, LUFFY, BUGGY screaming]
[MANTICORE panting]
Huh?
[BEASTS groan]
[footsteps]
[MANTICORES grunt]
[MANTICORES growl]
[LUFFY exhales]
Heh.
That's why I'm the best!
[BUGGY]
While those dumb animals
are following my footsteps,
we're free to make our break!
[BUGGY laughs]
Huh?
[LUFFY] But it didn't trick
them for very long!
[MANTICORES growl]
[BUGGY]
Damn these things!
By the way, I heard
the boss of beasts on Level 2
looks like some sort of lion.
Are all of these things bosses?
Of course they're not bosses!
These are clearly manticores.
Can't you see their human faces?
[MR. 3]
And if they catch us,
they'll chew until
only bones remain!
That's harsh!
[MANTICORE 430 A]
The key. Give me the key!
Ignore them!
Since they have
human faces,
they can imitate
different people
they've heard
around the prison!
[MANTICORE 430 D] Help me!
Please? It's too painful!
They're just repeating things
they've heard some
of the prisoners say!
They have no idea
what it means!
It sure is creepy!
[MANTICORE 430F]
Loincloth! Loincloth!
[MANTICORE 430 G]
Strawberry panties!
Who the hell have they
been listening to around here?
Beef steak! Beef steak!
Beef steak!
--[LUFFY] Steak?
--[BUGGY] Don't listen to them!
[LUFFY]
Hey! Hey, you!
You said you
were gonna help
us get through
this place, right?
[MR. 3 giggles]
Of course I did,
and I meant it!
We should join forces
and break out of
this prison together!
What do you say?
I told you, I don't
wanna break out,
I wanna know how to
get down to Level 3.
Huh?
I'm afraid you don't
understand the situation.
I assure you, it only gets
worse the deeper you go!
[BUGGY] Here's the scoop,
Straw Hat broke into the prison
to rescue his brother Ace!
Are you seriously telling me
"Fire Fist" Ace is
Straw Hat's brother?
I never knew!
[MR. 3] And you... you broke in
to Impel Down to rescue him?
I'm running out of time.
[MR. 3] If someone like "Fire
Fist" Ace is being held here,
then he would be all
the way down in Level 5.
He wants to go there?
[MR. 3]
No way! Count me out!
That's madness! I wouldn't dare!
[LUFFY]
Wait! Look.
I get that you don't
wanna join us. Fine!
But how do we get there?
[MR. 3 whimpering]
Use the stairs, you imbecile!
Oh, wait a second.
The stairs are all connected
from Level 1 to Level 3.
I could use Straw Hat as bait
for the beast guarding the
stairs and make my escape!
[MR. 3 giggles]
Yes, that's good!
Why, it's ingenious, even!
No. I'll stay.
Let's go together!
[BUGGY yells]
[ALL panting]
[MR. 3] You can count
on me, Straw Hat!
It's this way!
Oof!
[BUGGY gasps]
[growling]
Oh, crap.
You ran into something big!
[MR. 3 whimpers]
[MR. 3]
It's the guardian of the stairs!
The hell beast
known as the Sphinx!
Is that a lion
or a grandpa?
[BEASTS growl]
[BEASTS gasp]
[MANTICORE 430I]
Omelet rice!
--[MANTICORE 430J] Steak!
--[MANTICORE 430K] Loincloth!
[MANTICORE 430L]
Strawberry panties!
[BUGGY whimpers]
[MR. 3 whimpers]
[LUFFY whimpers]
[SPHINX]
Noodle.
What? Noodle?
Pork noodle!
[ALL panting]
[SPHINX]
Chinese noodles!
[MR. 3, BUGGY]
Were the prisoners really
talking about noodles that much?
Vegetable noodle!
[BUGGY and Mr. 3 yell]
[SPHINX]
Ramen!
[LUFFY]
Oof!
[SPHINX]
Hot men!
[BUGGY yells]
[BOTH]
You mean me?
[ALL yell]
[LUFFY]
This thing's tough!
[explosions]
That's gotta be...!
The Sphinx! And he's goin'
crazy about somethin'!
I knew it, I just knew it!
We're gonna be stuck
in this place forever!
Rice noodle!
Hot Pot noodle!
Canton noodle!
[LUFFY'S stomach growls]
Aw, Sanji used to make that.
Man, I sure miss my friends!
[SPHINX growls]
Wonton noodle!
Dammit!
He's strong and
makin' me hungry!
[BUGGY sighs]
You know, to be honest,
I have no interest
in going down
to the lower levels
of this place.
[MR. 3] I'm right there
with you on that one!
[MR. 3 and BUGGY]
Good.
Now, what do you say
we form an alliance
and break out of this dump?
I'm so pleased to hear
that you're a real escapee!
Now that that's settled,
let's begin the
"Straw Hat for dinner" plan.
[MR. 3]
My favorite plan!
Miso noodle!
Salty noodle!
Soy sauce noodle!
[tapping]
Hey! What are you two doing?
Let's move!
[SPHINX growls]
[BOTH]
Here he comes! Look out!
Now! Gum-Gum! Bazooka!
[SPHINX roars]
What are you doing?
How is it a good idea
to piss him off?
--[BUGGY] So long!
--[MR. 3 whimpers]
[MR. 3]
That's not fair!
Why can't I go to
a higher, safer place, too!
[SPHINX growls]
Cold noodle!
[BUGGY gasps]
[LUFFY gasps]
[MR. 3 laughs]
I tricked you, you
ghastly abomination!
What you smashed
was just a wax figure
I created
with my Wax-Wax power!
Hot thin noodle?
[MR. 3] Though I admit they
look much more convincing
with Miss Goldenweek's coloring.
But it was still enough
to trick a foolish beast,
such as yourself.
Are you ready? Here we go!
[MR 3.] Think you can tell
which one is the real me?
[SPHINX]
Noodle!
[MR. 3]
Missed me!
[SPHINX]
Noodle!
[MR. 3]
Missed again!
[SPHINX]
Noodle!
[MR. 3]
Wrong! Try again!
Ha! That looks fun!
Get him! Get him!
[SPHINX]
Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
There he is, look!
[SPHINX]
Noodle!
[MR. 3]
You're bad at this.
Aw, man! Try there!
Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
[LUFFY laughs]
Yeah! Get him!
He's playing with him!
What the hell?
I know you're
a risk-taker kid,
but you're gonna laugh
yourself into an early grave!
Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
[LUFFY]
Seems like you're startin'
to get the hang of this!
Let the simpletons
have their fun!
Now's my chance to
make a break for it!
[rumbling]
Hey. What's that rumbling
and shaking all about?
Holy crap, those three guys
must really be pissing
off the Sphinx!
Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
[LUFFY laughing]
[SPHINX]
Noodle!
[PRISONER 430F]
What's happening?
I don't know.
But I don't like it.
[SURVEILLANCE GUARD 430B]
Level 3 to Monitoring Room!
We're hearing a lot of
noise from upstairs!
[GUARDS gasp]
Mister 3!
It's time to fly!
[BUGGY laughs]
The perfect escape plan, huh?
This wasn't our plan,
we're just running!
Works either way, I guess.
Hey, look!
That must be the door that
leads to the stairs!
[MR. 3] I'll make
a key out of wax!
Yes, this is
the Monitoring Room!
Look, we still can't
get in touch with Level 2.
So we have no idea what's
goin' on down there!
[BUGGY and MR. 3 yell]
Noodle!
[LUFFY yelps]
[BUGGY] No, no, no!
You stupid beast!
You've cracked the floor!
Now we're all gonna--!
[GUARD] This is Level 3!
The ceiling is giving way!
The Sphinx is--!
[MR. 3 and BUGGY yelling]
[SPHINX yelling]
[LUFFY yelling]
Oh, no!
Damn it all!
We're falling! To Level 3!
Noodle!
[JIMBEI]
The government knows me
as the pirate who
hates other pirates.
Heh. An accurate assessment.
Excluding your people.
[ACE]
Really? You? Hate pirates?
That must be a shock,
coming from me.
I used to visit Whitebeard's
ship on a regular basis.
But because of my status
with the government,
I'd travel underwater
to get there.
Even so, he and his crew
were good friends to me.
[ACE chuckles]
Hmm. That so?
Well, I recall you almost
killed me one time.
I suppose I can say
the same thing about you.
But all that aside.
I owe Whitebeard a great debt.
[JIMBEI] Fishman Island is now
a peaceful haven once again.
And it's all thanks to
that "old man" of yours.
As you know, pirates
sailing along the Grand Line
must pass through Fishman Island
to reach the New World.
So, not long after the dawn
of the Great Pirate Era,
the island was in trouble.
[JIMBEI] Numerous human
pirates and Navy ships
that were chasing
after Whitebeard
arrived there, wreaking havoc.
Countless Fishmen and mermaids
were kidnapped
and sold as slaves.
And just when despair threatened
to conquer our hearts...
Whitebeard showed himself.
[WHITEBEARD]
From this point forward,
I claim this island
as my territory!
[JIMBEI]
A simple proclamation.
A precious few words
ensured that no one
would lay a finger
on Fishman Island again.
The power that Whitebeard
commands is that great.
As long as I live,
I will never forget that day.
[JIMBEI]
Not just my homeland,
he protects other islands
in much the same manner.
The government targets
him because he is a pirate,
but they refuse
to see the truth!
That is why I object.
If he happened to die,
what would become of the sea?
Who would dare to
welcome the chaos
that would reign
in his absence?
Who but a fool would dare
to usher in such madness?
[JIMBEI growls]
I want to stop this war even
if I must give up my life.
[JIMBEI]
I wanted to rescue you, Ace.
But I failed.
[ACE]
Jimbei. Please.
That's enough.
This is painful.
Even so, I haven't
given up hope yet.
I believe that a miracle
and our chance may come.
[CROCODILE laughs]
My, my...
Sounds like
there's a lot of fun
going on in the world.
[CROCODILE chuckles]
[CROCODILE] This is a
now-or-never opportunity
to defeat Whitebeard.
Even locked down here, I can't
help but feel a bit excited.
How dare you!
Oh, yeah?
You think you can
take the old man?
[CROCODILE]
Not just me.
[PRISONERS laugh]
Kill him! Kill him!
They're gonna kill Whitebeard?
[laughing]
About time!
Take him out!
You gotta let me out of here!
I wanna be the one
to kill him! Lemme out!
[PRISONER 430L] I wanna
take a crack at him, too!
I'm gonna put
an end to his era!
[PRISONERS chanting]
Fools! Silence!
Jimbei. Ace.
Look. Do you get it?
This world is full of
dozens of second placers.
Silver medalists
who could never defeat
Roger and Whitebeard,
all holding back their tears.
[CROCODILE laughs]
[ALL yelling]
[BUGGY]
I swear, Straw Hat!
You're the biggest pain in the
ass the world has ever seen!
[NARRATOR]
Luffy and company
descend to the Starvation Hell,
where prisoners are forced
to go without food or water.
All the while
enduring torturous heat.
However, before they can escape
this desert-like
den of suffering
they fall into the
Chief Guard's trap.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece
"Chief Guard Saldeath's Trap!
Level 3 - Starvation Hell."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!