[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever
dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
[ARLONG]
What's wrong little girl?
I bet it's the village...
You want it left alone?
Then how about this...?
Let's make an agreement okay?
[NAMI]
An agreement?
[ARLONG]
That's right...
Gather up 100 million berries,
then bring it to me...
Do so and I will
let your village go
in addition to giving
you your freedom.
Promise?
I promise...
...and I'm the kind of fishman
who would rather die
than break an agreement
concerning money.
And I don't even care
how long it takes you,
I will honor our agreement.
[NAMI] I'm gonna
save 100 million berries!
Bellemere... I will do it!
I don't care what it takes!
[LUFFY] "Luffy Rises!
Result of the Broken Promise!"
[NAMI thinking]
Genzo...? And the Marines?
Are you the pirate
thief known as Nami?
The Marine's
sources have revealed...
That you have quite
a large sum of treasure
that you've stolen
from pirates...
The government hereby
confiscates all said property...
It is required that
you comply immediately.
Chichichi... Sorry...
But perhaps you didn't
hear me the first time...
The government herby confiscates
everything you've stolen...
It is required that
you comply immediately.
Do you understand?
Hmph. Isn't that something...
I can see you're very
passionate about your duties.
You won't bring a brutal
gang of pirates to justice,
but you will shake down
a lowly sneak thief.
That's so very noble.
I'm only going
to warn you once...
I'm one of the leaders
of the Arlong Pirates...
If you mess with me,
Arlong won't sit by quietly.
Chichichi... Silly girl...
Who do you think I am?
Do you honestly think
you can intimidate me...?
Find the stolen goods!
Don't move.
I said stop!
Do you really think this is
what the Marines
should be doing now?
The Arlong Pirates
are murderers;
they've destroyed entire cities
and you're doing nothing!
He's ruling over this island and
trampling over people's lives!
You'd ignore Arlong's atrocities
to steal from a thief...?
Is that what you stand for?!
Chichichi... Big talk
from a filthy criminal...
Ha... Continue the search men.
Every person on this
island has been waiting
for the Marines to come
and help them for years!
How dare you pass them by
and come here
searching for money!
[MARINE C]
Colonel...!
This tangerine orchard
seems a little suspicious!
[NEZUMI]
Dig it up!
The whole thing if need be!
Keep your filthy hands
off Bellemere's
tangerine orchard!
I won't let you
take my money...!
That money's for... It's for...!
That poor girl's money is meant
to save Cocoyashi Village...!
What gives you the right to take
our salvation away from her?!
Damn you!
My my...
A mere village
representative talking down
to a Marine colonel.
How bold.
Genzo...
How'd you know about that?
I've always known... Nami.
[NAMI]
I'm...
[NOJIKO]
Huh?
[NAMI]
I'm joining Arlong's crew.
[gasping]
[GENZO]
Nami!
[NOJIKO]
But why?
[GENZO] I couldn't believe
what you had done...
So I confronted
Nojiko about it later.
Since then, everyone
has known that you stayed
with the Arlong Pirates so
that you could save the village.
But we all agreed we'd
never tell you that we knew...
If you ever thought
the villagers
were placing
their hopes on you,
you might never leave his gang
for fear of letting us down.
That can't be...
Now hold on a minute,
just what are you
trying to say here?
Are you telling me that the
villagers are thieves,
and we should arrest
every one of them...?
Is that what you're saying?
[NOJIKO] What he's
saying is that every last
one of us is fighting to survive
[NOJIKO]
We have to fend for ourselves
because we can't rely on support
from you government people!
So if you're not gonna
protect our village,
then get the hell outta here!
And be quick about it,
or Arlong'll sink your ship too!
Arlong will...?
I wouldn't be so sure.
You still haven't found it...?!
We're looking for
100 million berries here,
not a grain of rice!
[GENZO]
Hey you!
How do you know
how much there is?!
Oh... I don't know...
I just have a hunch that that's
the amount we're looking for.
It's him...
[ARLONG laughs]
Tell me...!
It was Arlong that
sent you wasn't it?!
Chichichi... 'Course not...
I wouldn't do a pirate's
dirty work, that'd be wrong...
I'm just a public
servant dealing
with theft the way any
government worker would.
You corrupt marine scumbag!
The Marines have stooped
to being nothing
but pirate cronies!
[NAMI thinking]
Arlong!
[MARINE G]
Sir, I found it!
Hahaha!
[NEZUMI]
Incredible!
I must say I'm impressed you
gathered this much treasure!
The money's
all ragged and bloody.
No matter... Money's money!
Chichichichi...
[thinking] Thirty percent
of this is all mine!
[NAMI]
Don't touch that...
Nami...
Stop it... Don't touch that!
Stop it!!
[NOJIKO]
Nami!
Nojiko! Nojiko!
[LUFFY]
A pinwheel huh?
It's so cool!
I thought of a new move!
[GENZO]
Doctor! Doctor!
[DOCTOR]
Genzo! What is it?!
[GENZO]
Nojiko's been shot!
[DOCTOR]
By who?!
[GENZO]
The Marines.
[DOCTOR]
The Marines?!
Nojiko?
[NOJIKO]
Uh... I'm alright...
Arlong has been working
with those damn Marines.
[DOCTOR]
What?
He's been lying to Nami
for the last eight years...
He never intended to
honor their agreement at all.
That bastard!
Oh no...! That means...
[VILLAGER C]
That scoundrel!
He lied to our Nami!
[VILLAGER D]
Poor Nami!
Nami.
Hey Nami...! What's up?!
Need help with anything?!
Why are you still here?
Stay outta my business...!
Just get away from our island!
[NAMI thinking]
Arlong...
Arlong.
Arlong!
And I'm the kind of
fish‐man who would rather die
than break an agreement
concerning money.
And I don't even care
how long it takes you,
I will honor our agreement.
[NAMI]
Arlong!
What's her problem?
[NAMI]
Arlong!
[GROUP]
Hmm?
[ARLONG]
Ah...
What seems to be the problem,
O skilled surveyor of ours?
Why the sour face?
Those Marine maggots you keep
on the payroll stole
every last berry I had!
What happened to all
that crap about dying
before you'd ever
break a promise
when it comes to money...?!
Bastard!
Refresh my memory.
Did I break a promise?
Don't play dumb with me!
I know that you teamed up
with the Marines to‐‐!
Just when did
I break that promise...?
Speak up girl.
Hahahaha!
[laughter]
[NAMI thinking]
Damn you... Damn you! Damn you!
Too bad... All your
stolen money got stolen...
That certainly is unfortunate...
But a deal is a deal Nami...
If you can't come up
with 100 million berries,
then both you
and your village stay
in my possession indefinitely.
Well, you know the terms. Hmm?
You pig!
Hahahaha!!
It's only 100 million berries!
Start saving again and
you'll have it in no time!
Hahahaha!!
Or, are you gonna run out on me?
Listen...
If you do that, I'll kill
everyone in that village.
Do you understand me?
[GENZO]
Nami...
We agreed we would never
tell you that we knew...
If you thought all of us
were counting on you,
you would be bound by guilt
never to leave his gang
for fear of letting us down.
Aww... Running away so soon?
Hahahaha!
Shouldn't we chase after her?
[ARLONG]
No need for that.
Trust me Hachi she's
not going anywhere...
There's no way Nami
could just abandon
the lives of all
those villagers.
[CHOO] Choo. Now that's
what I call playing dirty.
There's no way I'd let go of
an asset like Nami that easily.
I may be cruel but
I'm not totally heartless.
Once she's done charting
all the world's oceans,
she'll have her freedom.
[laughter]
That's pretty harsh man,
it'll take decades for sure.
Yeah, I bet a hundred
years wouldn't be enough!
All right!
Let's go meet up with
Luffy as soon as possible!
[USOPP]
Hey, Sanji... What're you doing?
I'm appreciating happiness.
Wait, what are
you talking about?
Nami has had to live
with way more suffering
than any normal person...
Right now I'm making
a lot of good vibes
so I can send them her way...
Isn't everything great?
I bet that's not
all you're thinking about,
Love cook.
I'm trying to fight
for a beautiful person...
Is something wrong with that?
That's not right at all...!
This is supposed to be for
Nami and all the villagers!
Yeah, yeah.
[ZORO sighs]
Quit bickering!
Let's go.
We've had enough...!
Take up arms!
It's time to fight!
[NAMI thinking]
Genzo! Please!
Don't do anything stupid!
We have to live or our
struggles will mean nothing!
You can't throw your lives away!
[GENZO]
Eight long years ago...
We promised we wouldn't
live our lives in vain!
No matter the
pain or humiliation
we endured under Arlong, we
swore to fight the long fight
so Nami could
meet their demands!
But, they lied!
They never intended to
keep their end of the deal.
Instead they stole our
only chance at freedom!
So now...
We should make
those filthy fishmen pay
for the years they manipulated
that kind young girl...!
Am I right?!
[VILLAGER E]
Yeah! Let's do this!
[VILLAGER H]
We were always ready
to fight those monsters!
Let's get 'em!
Time to show those
lousy stinkin' fishmen
what we're made of!
Yeah!!
[NAMI]
Everybody! Wait!
Huh?
[NOJIKO]
Nami!
Hahaha.
Calm down...!
It's not that much money...!
I can make it
back in no time...!
I'll take care of it,
don't worry!
It'll be easy... this time!
I'm used to it!
I'll be fine! Just relax!
Everything is okay!
Hey... It's nothing
compared to back then.
It's okay...!
You don't need to save me!
C'mon everyone!
I'm perfectly fine!
You've done enough ...
You have to know
that there is no point now.
You struggled so hard,
carrying our lives
on your back this whole time.
I can only imagine
that joining them
must have been more painful,
than being stabbed
through the heart.
[GENZO]
You fought very well.
[NAMI]
Genzo...
Set yourself free
from this village.
[NAMI]
Genzo!
[NOJIKO]
Nami. Do it.
[NAMI]
What?! Nojiko!
Nami...
Go on.
You are an exceptional
young woman...
And you have a dream.
Everyone! Listen!
I won't let you go...!
Just stay right there...!
I'm not going to let any one
else get hurt by these monsters!
You'll all die...
We know that.
Nami... It's no use,
we've made up our minds!
Get outta the way!
[GENZO]
Move out!
[DOCTOR] We may not win
but we will give 'em hell!
[cheers]
[ARLONG laughs]
Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong!
Arl‐‐!
Luffy.
[NAMI]
What do you want?
You don't know
anything about this.
what's been happening
on this island for
the past eight years.
[LUFFY]
Nope. I don't.
This has nothing to do with you!
I told you to leave this place.
Yep... You sure did.
[NAMI] So leave...!
I told you to leave...!
Get out of here...!
Get out of here now...!
Go...! Go away...!
Go...! Go...! Go!
[sobs]
[NAMI]
Luffy... Help me.
[LUFFY] Of course...
That's what friends do.
He's gonna pay!
You better keep
your hands off my hat.
[NAMI]
Luffy.
Let's go!
Right!
[VILLAGER A]
Hey! Are you guys all right?
[DOCTOR]
Did Arlong do this to you?
[GENZO]
Move aside!
We have business to take
care of with the fishmen.
When we finally found out
the truth about big sis Nami...
We realized the
only thing we could do
was defeat Arlong in battle...
So we decided to come back
here and challenge him.
Yeah... Then we lost,
but only by a hair.
I'm sorry but I can't
let you through this door...
You have no chance of victory.
What's that?
Be patient...
It won't be long now.
You see we're waiting for
the arrival of certain men.
What "certain men"?
[YOSAKU]
Don't worry.
They'll be here soon...
I'd bet my life on it!
There!
It's them...
But why would they come
to defend our village?
If those men can't
handle Arlong and his gang,
then there really is no hope...
Not only for this island
but for the whole East Blue.
[JOHNNY] Those are
the faces of the four men
who are here to
change your destiny...
Burn their images
into your memory!
[LUFFY]
Step aside.
[ARLONG laughs]
Hey.
Do you think those two idiots
that showed up earlier
are members of
Zoro's little crew?
Zoro? They seemed
too weak for that...
They weren't even worth killing.
That's for sure!
Hahahahahaha!!
Huh?
What the‐‐?!
Now which one of you is Arlong?
♪All that's in my heart
confuses me
I cannot understand
As I face what I must do
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand
I'll set sail alone
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near
As I drift away
I pray you watch me
as I disappear
As I watch the sunrise
I began to wonder
What could be the reason
It's so hot inside
No answer has come
But I can't get away
from what's true
It's because of you
Show me how to
catch those feelings
Get 'em to come back to me
I'll do what I must
Because they're
everything I wanna be
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back from yesterday
If I'm holding hands with you
I'm sure that we can
make the way♪
[SANJI] You just had
to run ahead by yourself!
I said don't hog all the prey!
[LUFFY]
Really? Huh?
[ZORO]
What's wrong?!
[LUFFY]
Yeah, that's the thing!
I'm kind of in trouble!
Hear me out!
[USOPP] Oh, crap!
That guy plans to do something!
[LUFFY] What do I do?
What do I do?! What do I do?!
Ahhh!
[USOPP, ZORO, and SANJI]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Luffy in Big Trouble!
Fishmen vs. the Luffy Pirates!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!