Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[ROBIN] It's hard to look at.
[SANJI] He... He's going...
to marry her?
No way in hell! Lemme at him!
Wow, this guy
must be pretty brave
if he wants to marry Nami!
And what's this about
me being a monster?
Why does my shadow get
to do all the cool stuff?
So if we find this guy with the
clogs, the dog penguin thing,
the one that has Sanji's shadow,
and Luffy's
giant monster zombie,
all we gotta do is throw
some salt in their mouths
and then we'll get
our shadows back?
Is that it?
Nice job on figuring
out their weakness--
how'd you pull that one?
[FRANKY] Save your thanks
for the afro skeleton.
Not only did he know
how to beat the zombies,
he also told us you'd be
waiting back here at the Sunny.
I was wrong.
That skeleton's a real man.
After all, you said before
that you were so lonely,
you wanted to die, right?
If I were you,
I would've given up
on life a long time ago.
What is it that's
keeping you alive?
You said you made
a promise to a friend?
What is it? How could
it be so important?
[BROOK]
The story is quite simple.
At a certain point in the past,
before we came to these waters,
my crew left behind
a good friend of ours.
It was a troubling situation,
but we did it out of necessity.
The only consolation we
could offer this friend was
a promise that we would return
one day, no matter the cost.
But then the crew
was annihilated.
And the promise that we
made was left unfulfilled.
How long has it been
since the day we died?
I've lost count, but it's
been more than 50 years now.
50 years?
You're talking ages ago, here!
Hell, I wasn't even born yet!
I hate to break
it to you buddy,
but there's no way your
friend's still waiting for you.
[BROOK] But, it's true that
he would have every right
to leave by now.
I realize I may be foolish to
believe that he's still there.
[BROOK] The name of that
friend that we left at the cape,
swearing to meet again, is...
...Laboon.
Even if I am able to return,
I don't think he'll
forgive us for running away
and dying like that.
But no matter how
much he resents me
for forcing him to suffer
all of these years.
[BROOK]
Death is never an apology.
Because when a
man makes a promise,
he doesn't stop fighting
until he fulfills it!
[FRANKY] So there you have it,
that's it, the whole story.
Laboon.
This is crazy,
what're the chances?
I'll be damned.
Hm? Hm?
Oh, right. Chopper and
Robin weren't with us then.
We've met that whale before.
And we know, that promise.
[whale roar]
[LUFFY]
"I Swear to Go See Him!
Brook and the Cape of Promise."
Hold on, you know him?
That's crazy.
How is that possible?
[SANJI] It was when
we passed through
to the Grand Line
at the two capes.
That damn giant whale
was blocking the entrance.
[SANJI] Nami! I see
a mountain up ahead!
What? That's impossible!
[SANJI] But, it's right there!
I can see it!
Who cares? Go!
[roaring sound]
[CREW screams]
[SANJI] Oh crap!
It's not a mountain!
[LUFFY] It's a black wall!
[NAMI] No, it's not!
[ZORO] Then, what is it?
[USOPP] It's a whale!
[roars]
[USOPP] What're we gonna do?
[LUFFY] Should we fight?
[NAMI] Idiot!
How are we supposed to
fight a hundred-ton whale?
[USOPP] B-But, we
h-have to do something!
Our path is blocked!
How do we escape?
Wait! I know!
This'll work! It has to!
[NAMI] Hey!
Luffy! What're you doing?
[USOPP] This is pointless!
The ship's not gonna turn!
[ZORO] Dammit!
[SANJI] Don't give up!
[NAMI] Is this the end?
[CREW] The cannon?
[LUFFY chuckles] Done!
We're screwed.
This is it.
Aaaaaaah!!
Hey, that was
my special seat!
[ZORO] Let's get out of
here before it's too late!
[USOPP] Someone mind telling
me what the heck is going on?
[SANJI] It's so big
that the cannon ball
didn't even make it flinch!
That or his reaction
time is really slow!
[ZORO] Who cares?
At least we're alive!
[roars]
Aaaaaugh!! My ears!
[USOPP] Paddle! Just paddle!
[ZORO] We have to
get away from here!
[NAMI] Luffy?
[LUFFY] You think you
can break my special seat
and get away with it?
Take this!
[CREW] You moron!
[CREW screams]
Please! No!
[NAMI] Luffy!
[SANJI] Luffy!
[LUFFY] I'm not gonna die!
[SANJI] Thanks to
Luffy's idiotic temper.
Laboon swallowed the
ship with us aboard.
What? The whale
ate you guys?
And this is the
same Laboon as Brook's?
[SANJI] Has to be.
There was an old lighthouse
keeper that lived inside his gut
and told us all about the whale.
What?
That flower head guy.
[SANJI] Not only did
he go inside him.
He took care of him
and treated his wounds.
What's a lighthouse guy
know about wounds?
[USOPP] Plenty if they've
got medical experience.
He was apparently the doctor
for a pirate crew at one time.
Wow. But how'd
the whale get so hurt
that he needed a
doctor to treat him?
What happened?
It was at the Red Line.
Grief drove him to keep
bashing his head against
the dividing wall.
The grief of abandonment.
He'd spent fifty years
waiting for his friends there,
believing they'd return
for him after their voyage.
[USOPP] Don't you think
fifty years is a bit extreme?
Those pirates sure know how
to test someone's patience!
[SANJI] Idiot! Don't ya get it?
This is the Grand Line.
His friends are dead.
[SANJI] That whale can wait
forever, they won't be back.
[NAMI] Sad to say,
but that's probably true.
Back in the day when those
guys traveled the Grand Line
it was an uncharted sea,
a thousand times more
treacherous than it is now.
[USOPP] Why are you
all being so pessimistic?
You don't know if they're dead!
They could still
come back for him!
C'mon, have some
sympathy will ya?
I thought it was
very touching.
I mean, a whale still
believing in a promise
his friends made
despite all these years?
That's a true bond!
Right, pops?
[CROCUS] Indeed.
But the lesson here is
that reality is cruel.
Laboon's cohorts aren't dead.
The truth is, they
abandoned their quest.
I learned from that they turned
tail and left the Grand Line.
[USOPP] I don't believe it.
I mean, why abandon
him like that?
[CROCUS] I can't claim to know
exactly what became of them.
But I doubt they'll
ever come back here again.
Seasons, weather,
currents, wind direction.
On the Grand Line,
these elements seem
to defy the very laws of nature.
Common sense is useless.
And the terror of that fact
can be quite overwhelming.
Why would anybody
abandon such a loyal creature?
Just look at him!
It's cruelty on a grand scale!
But if you've known all this,
why haven't you told him?
Laboon can obviously
communicate with you.
He seems to understand
humans quite well for a whale.
[CROCUS] I did tell him.
Down to the last,
miserable detail.
[roars]
Laboon! Please! I say
this for your own good!
They're not coming back!
I understand that you
don't wanna accept it,
but you need to realize
this is how things are.
Listen!
Laboon!
[CROCUS] That was
the day that Laboon
began to howl at
Reverse Mountain.
Soon after, he started slamming
his body against the Red Line.
It's as if he believes that wall
is what keeps his friends away,
and by breaking it, he can
clear the path for their return.
[SANJI] I admire his dedication.
[USOPP] He never gave up on 'em.
[CROCUS] He refuses
to believe me
because then he'd have
to admit that it's over.
And that terrifies
him more than anything.
There's no way for him to
go back to the West Blue.
So, what we have here is a
paradox of tragic proportions.
Laboon is a lost soul dying
to live with his friends,
but won't stop killing
himself to reach them.
[CROCUS] The scars
on his hide are deep.
Those in his heart
are even deeper.
He needs someone to tend his
wounds and I'm all he's got.
For years,
he's battered himself
while I've patched him up.
A strange friendship,
but it works.
What the hell is
that idiot up to?
Ya gotta watch
him every second.
[SANJI] We've been watching
him, look what happens.
Gum-Gum...
...Flower Arrangement!
Ya think he's aware
that that's our mast?
And now it's on top of a whale.
Why'd he do that?
Hey, Luffy, stop
tearing up the ship!
[wails]
You ass! Luffy, stop!
The boy! He's dead!
Oh, don't worry!
It'll take way more
than that to kill Luffy!
Ha! Gotcha!
What's does he
think he's doing?
[ZORO] You wanna let us in
on your plan before
you kill yourself?
[LUFFY] It's a draw!
I'm stronger than I look!
But, I have a
feeling you knew that.
I can always tell when
someone's itching to fight.
Well, if you want a battle,
I'll gladly give ya one.
Your shipmates used to
spar with you didn't they?
You miss it. Well, I can rival
anything they threw at ya!
Tell ya what.
After me and my friends
travel the Grand Line,
we'll come back and find you.
And then you better
be ready for a rematch!
[LUFFY] Hey, not bad!
Consider this a
symbol of my promise
to come do battle with you!
Of course, it's
a rush paint job,
so you'll have to be careful
and avoid hitting your head
or you'll rub it
right off. Understand?
[LUFFY] Good whale!
[LUFFY] See ya, pops!
Thanks again for the
Log Pose! Take care!
[CROCUS] Have a
safe trip, my boy!
[LUFFY] I'm off, Laboon!
Be ready to fight
when I get back!
[LUFFY] Next stop, Whisky Peak!
Ready gang? Let's set sail!
I couldn't believe it,
but somehow,
Luffy convinced
him to stop trying
to break through the
wall like a damned idiot.
Even now, he's alive out there.
Waiting at that cape for
his friends to finally return.
[USOPP] It's an
incredible story.
Talk about true friends.
He kept his promise to them
for more than half a century.
And to think,
we met one of Laboon's friends
by complete coincidence.
[ZORO] Wonder what that
skeleton's doing right now.
[RYUMA]
Nyohohoho!
I won't deny that
you've gotten stronger
over these past
five years, but so have I!
And remember,
I already know every
move you're gonna make!
[RYUMA]
Nyohohoho.
You care more about
that damn afro
than the skull beneath it.
Too bad for that it's
the biggest target
on your whole body.
[BROOK] Shut up!
[BROOK thinking]
Laboon, I wonder, old friend,
after all these years,
do you still remember me?
[BROOK thinking] When I think of
how alone you must have felt.
It breaks my heart in two.
[BROOK thinking]
Although, I don't suppose
I have a heart anymore.
[BROOK thinking]
The Grand Line is so fearsome.
Believe me. I tried
as hard as I could.
I tried to bring
them back to you,
but all of our friends
have passed away.
[BROOK thinking] Not only
have I lost our friends,
I've lost my face,
my body, my shadow.
Everything I once was.
If we were to meet again.
You probably wouldn't
even recognize me.
How could you, with
me looking like this?
Nyohoho!
Keep away from the afro!
Nyohohoho!
[BROOK thinking]
I don't have anything left.
Not a single reminder
of my old self.
[BROOK thinking] Except
for this hair on my head.
Black, round,
and funny, just like you.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 354A]
I didn't notice it before,
but they kinda look alike.
Brook's head is almost
the same shape as Laboon's.
[RUMBAR PIRATE 354B] The two
of you could be brothers!
[BROOK thinking]
I must protect it,
so you'll still recognize me!
[BROOK thinking] I'm coming,
Laboon! Just as I promised!
[BROOK thinking] I hope
you're still waiting.
[BROOK thinking] Waiting for me.
[BROOK thinking]
At our promised cape.
[FRANKY bawls]
I love that bonehead
and his stupid whale!
Shut up!
I'm so pumped, guys!
He's a musician,
a talking skeleton, has an afro,
does that "yoho" thing,
and he was one of
Laboon's best friends!
[LUFFY] Even if I've
gotta force him to,
he's gonna join our crew.
We got us a musician.
Any objections? Speak up.
Haha. Would it really change
your mind even if we did?
I want him to
join the crew too!
No question! Him and Laboon!
Complete and total approval!
Same here,
you big dumb bastard!
And I'm not scared
of skeletons, dammit!
Before I can answer
such an easy question.
I've gotta put a stop to this
shotgun wedding of Nami's!
[LUFFY] Hey, Zoro!
Where ya goin'?
I'm going off to get started.
Ya keep adding shadows.
We got a lot we
need to get back.
[chuckles]
[LUFFY] Alright, crew!
Time to get serious!
Prepare for the counterattack!
We're gonna put Thriller Bark
in a watery grave!
[CREW] Yeah!
Have fun!
You're with us, moron!
[SANJI] Unforgivable!
This creep thinks
he can marry Nami?
[USOPP] He fell head
over heels in love.
It all happened when
she was taking a bath.
[SANJI] A bath?
You mean he peeped on her?
[USOPP] He touched her, too.
[SANJI] Arrrrrrrgh!!!
He's a dead man!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Food, Nami and Shadows!
Luffy's Enraged Counterattack!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!