[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
You pathetic, little maggots.
You would knowingly
attack the invincible fleet
of pirates commanded by Captain
Usopp of the Going Merry?!
Ah! Attack them!
Show no mercy!
Uh?!
[yawns]
[sighs] Geez. I really
expected you guys
to be a little bit
more lively than this.
‐‐[LUFFY] I'm finished!
‐‐[USOPP yelps]
[LUFFY]
Heh, heh. Look! Our pirate mark!
Now that Ussop's joined
we got four people,
that's almost a whole crew!
I think it's about time
we got our own flag!
[ZORO]
Uh... Luffy?
Is that really
gonna be our mark?
[LUFFY]
Heh. Whadya think? Nice, huh?
Our mark should be scary.
It should strike fear
into our enemy's hearts.
If our enemies were
terrified infants,
then this would be perfect.
You guys really should've
told me about this.
Maybe you didn't know
this about me,
but I am an artist.
Does that mean you can draw?
[USOPP]
Heh. When it comes to painting,
I'm in a league of my own!
I've been drawing graffiti
for 50 years straight.
[LUFFY]
Whoa! Fifty years!
[ZORO] That would mean
he's an old man by now.
[NAMI] Which would give him
five or six grandchildren,
and I don't see 'em!
‐‐[LUFFY] That is so cool!
‐‐Hey.
Behold! A priceless
work of pirate art!
Ta‐dah!
Looks a lot like you
on that flag. Jerk!
So, how do you
like this one?
Wow. That's actually
pretty good, Usopp.
Yeah! Keep it! That's the one!
So, we've finally settled on it.
This is gonna be our mark?
[LUFFY]
Sure is!
Hey, Usopp! Draw one
on the sail, too!
[USOPP]
Right!
[LUFFY]
Okay! It's all done.
Now the Going Merry
has everything
she could possibly need!
[LUFFY laughs]
"You're the Weird Creature!
Gaimon and His Strange Friends!"
Ah... I'm pooped.
[thunder rumbles]
[ZORO]
Huh?
[LUFFY] Are we going the right
way? Seems kinda dangerous.
What's that?!
Hold on.
[USOPP]
Hm?
[NAMI]
That's the place.
Yep. There's no
doubt about it.
Hey, what do ya' see out
there? Is it something cool?
The legendary Treasure Island.
You mean the Treasure Island?
Even I've heard of that place.
Yeah. I'm not surprised,
this place is famous
the world over. And so are
the crazy stories about it.
What crazy stories?
Legend has it that
whoever's dumb enough
to sail close to the island
incurs a god's wrath.
[USOPP screams]
Now we know that all those
stories were true, guys!
This is a god's wrath!
I think that sounds pretty cool.
Hey, wait! We're not gonna‐‐
You bet we are!
[LUFFY]
Let's go to Treasure Island!
[USOPP]
This is gonna be bad!
[ZORO grunts]
[NAMI laughs]
[USOPP whimpers, yelps]
Hey. This place is creepy.
Yeah, so?
It's said that somewhere
on this island rests
an unimaginable fortune
just waiting to be found.
Supposedly, many pirates have
landed here in the past,
but they all fled
in absolute terror
before they ever got
a chance to look for it.
[gasps] Absolute terror?
[NAMI] I'd be afraid, too.
They say one pirates' face
suddenly turned
into a boar's face.
And another pirates'
mustache stretched out
like a couple of snakes
and strangled him.
[USOPP] But, that's
not true... right?
Well. I'm sure that
some of those stories
are a bit of an exaggeration.
[USOPP] Don't talk anymore,
you're scaring me.
[yawns] I'm tired.
Nap time.
[snores]
[USOPP] How can he possibly
sleep in such a creepy place?
[NAMI] He's either dumb,
or he's got nerves of steel.
[LUFFY grunts]
[SNAKE BUNNY screeches]
[USOPP screams]
What's happening?!
Are we in danger?!
Uh... What?!
No, I was just making up a
little dance to liven things up!
[USOPP sings]
Hey. Come on,
stop that Luffy.
[NAMI, USOPP scream]
[ROOSTER DOG crows]
[PANDA BAT wails]
What's going on?!
[STRANGE VOICE]
Leave now!
‐‐Who's there?!
‐‐[STRANGE VOICE] Leave now!
Guys? Where's that
voice coming from?
[STRANGE VOICE]
I am the vengeful island god!
Leave at once if
you value your lives!
Island god?
[STRANGE VOICE] Wait.
You guys are pirates, right?
Well, yeah.
[STRANGE VOICE]
Ah... I knew it.
Why would a god need to
ask something like that?
[STRANGE VOICE ]
I dunno. I‐I mean,
take one more step
into the forest!
The instant you do, you
will instantly receive
my divine punishment
and meet your doom,
which is my punishment.
Wait, uh.
Okay. That made
no sense at all.
This guy is weird.
Yeah. What's his
deal, anyway?
[STRANGE VOICE] What did
you say, straw hat boy?!
[ANIMALS roar]
[USOPP]
What are these things?
[STRANGE VOICE]
They used to be humans!
They came looking for treasure,
but all they found was my wrath!
Uh. You transformed them?!
Then you are a god!
[LUFFY]
Look at all these weird things!
Huh. So, is this a pig?
Could be a lion.
‐‐[PIG LION roars]
‐‐[LUFFY grunts]
[STRANGE VOICE] You stretchy
freak of nature! What are you?!
One time I ate a Devil Fruit.
So now I'm a rubber person.
[STRANGE VOICE]
Yeah right. A Devil Fruit?
I heard those same
stupid stories
back when I was a pirate, but‐‐
Back when you were a pirate?
[STRANGE VOICE] I mean, uh...
No! I wasn't reminiscing
about the old days!
Enough of that kinda talk!
I don't wanna hear about
the old days! Got it?!
Are you nuts? You're the
one who brought it up.
You faker! You sound too
dumb to be a god!
[STRANGE VOICE] Shut up!
If you won't leave,
then prepare for my
divine judgment!
[ZORO snores]
You're really pushing
your luck... "god".
[STRANGE VOICE]
How are you not dead?!
‐‐[LUFFY] There you are.
‐‐[STRANGE VOICE] Don't move!
[STRANGE VOICE]
I said don't move!
[NAMI, USOPP scream]
[STRANGE VOICE]
No! That can't be!
Hey "island god".
Even mortals know bullets
can't hurt a rubber man!
Maybe not, but I
still hate them.
[STRANGE VOICE]
You're some kind of monster!
Over there!
[LUFFY grunts]
Hey, look. Found his gun.
Where did he go?
[NAMI, USOPP]
Huh?!
[LUFFY]
What is this?
[USOPP]
Could it be the island god?
[LUFFY, NAMI gasp]
It's moving!
[STRANGE VOICE grunts]
Stand me up!
Stand me up already!
[NAMI]
It's a person!
[LUFFY] Awesome! He's like
a talking scrub brush!
That's it? You're not
even a minor deity.
You're more like a box.
Come on! Stand me up now!
[USOPP]
Relax. Here.
Uh... I'll let you off
with a warning this time!
[LUFFY]
No. Wait!
[STRANGE VOICE grunting]
[LUFFY groans]
[BOTH yell]
‐‐[screaming]
‐‐[LUFFY laughing]
[NAMI, USOPP]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Huh!
[screams]
[NAMI, USOPP gasp]
There. You're all set now.
[NAMI] You're a pretty
popular guy, Mr. Island God.
So lemme get this straight,
these crazy animals
helped you scare
off the pirates
who came to this place
looking for treasure?
[LUFFY]
I've never seen a person
stuffed inside a
treasure chest before.
You're a real life
"jack in the box".
Yes. Ironically I am in fact
in a box, and my name is‐‐
You idiot!
I'm a person! Not a toy!
I've been stranded,
alone, on this island,
and stuck in this contemptible
box for 20 years.
That long?
So you've been all alone on this
island for 20 years? Amazing.
Yeah, just take a look at me.
I got a beard like a wild man.
And in all that time,
you're the first people
that I've had a real
conversation with.
Can you understand
how painful that is?
[LUFFY]
That's ridiculous.
What did you say?!
Oh, oh... here you are.
I've been looking all
over for you guys.
[NAMI] How could you
have slept through
everything that's
just happened?
[ZORO gasps]
What the heck is that?!
He finally sees him.
Check it out!
He's in a treasure chest.
Like a "jack in the
box". But real!
Yes. Ironically I am in
fact in a box and my name is‐‐
You idiot!
We've already been
through all that!
[LUFFY]
Zoro! Gimme a hand!
Oww! What are you doing?!
Stop it would you?!
You're pulling my
head off! Stop it!
Sorry, I'm afraid you're stuck.
[GAIMON]
Don't be stupid!
I've been stuck inside
this blasted treasure chest
for so many years now
that it's slowly become
a part of my body!
If you try to break it,
you'll break my body, too!
You're a strange little man.
[sighs] All right guys enough
about me, who are you?
You're not like any of
those other pirates
who've come around here,
that's for sure.
I'm Luffy!
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates.
[gasps] You're what?!
I'm gonna get the One Piece.
And then I'm gonna
be King of the Pirates.
The One Piece?!
Don't tell me you idiots
are actually planning to
sail on the Grand Line!
[LUFFY] Yup! We got
a chart right here.
Don't be such a fool!
The Grand Line's a graveyard!
I once saw a group of pirates
who had managed to escape
from that horrible place,
and I'll never forget it.
It was an awful sight. They
were just the hollow shells
of the men that they used
to be. There's no telling
what horrors they witnessed
in that ghastly place.
Not one among them
even tried to speak.
[LUFFY]
Mm...
Now listen to me well
young pirates.
The rumors of the One Piece
spawn more rumors.
Who knows what's true?
It's been only 20 odd
years since the start
of the Great Pirate Era, and
the One Piece is already
a dream within a dream
beyond a legend!
So, which one of these
is the Grand Line?
I dunno. Figured you could
tell me, Mr. scrub brush guy.
Sorry, I never learned
how to read a sea chart.
I never did, either.
[BOTH laugh]
[NAMI]
Ignorance is bliss, isn't it?
Anyway, even if we do some how
make it to the Grand Line,
the best idea would be
to get as much treasure
as we can and then escape.
You go ahead and do that,
I'm gonna find the One Piece.
Where do you get all that
confidence of yours?
[LUFFY]
I'll get it! You'll see.
[NAMI]
Whatever you say.
You're me.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
You're exactly like me.
You even look like me.
We could be twins.
How can you say
he looks like you?
Young man. I understand about
the pursuit of your dreams!
When I was a younger man,
we used to feel the same way!
What do you mean we?
We were willing to put
our lives on the line
to search for treasure.
It was that single‐minded zeal
that changed the course
of my life forever.
Wait. Slow down.
What are you talking about?
It happened 20 years ago...
I was a much younger man then.
My fellow pirates and
I landed on this island
with a single purpose.
To find the treasure
that was said to rest here.
[CAPTAIN] Two‐hundred men have
searched for an entire month,
and nothing has been found!
The only treasure chest
we've uncovered is empty!
Pack up men! We're leaving.
[PIRATES grumble]
[PIRATE A] What are you looking
at Gaimon? It's time to go!
Right.
[GAIMON]
Did anyone look way up there?
I know that the captain stayed
down here the whole month.
[GAIMON grunting]
[GAIMON] I'd better go
ahead and double check.
[GAIMON]
I couldn't believe my own eyes!
Ha! I found it.
Guys, it's up here!
Hey! You guy‐‐
[GAIMON screaming]
[GAIMON] That's when I
got stuck in this chest!
[GAIMON gasps]
[GAIMON] When I came to, my crew
was already far out to sea.
Hold on. Yes.
I believe this means
that the entire fortune
belongs to me now!
I can't climb up like this! I
can't get out! I can't get out!
Hey! Come back!
Come back, please!
And after all this time, the
fortune I found but only saw
for an instant has never strayed
far from my lonely old mind.
Pirates have come here countless
times to search for my treasure.
But fortunately my friends
here, help me scare them away.
That's how I've kept my
treasure safe and sound
for the past twenty years.
It's my treasure!
No question.
It's yours all right!
You know, I think we
can help you out.
Gaimon, why don't we get the
treasure down for you?
[gasps] Wait, Do you mean it?
Yeah.
Nami.
Hey, aren't you a thief that
only steals from pirates?
[NAMI]
How rude!
I am a thief, but I
have a conscience!
[gasping]
It's here?
Yes, this is the place.
It's all up there.
The time has finally come!
It's a great day!
Get to it Straw Hat!
Sure thing! Gum‐Gum...
[laughing]
[LUFFY]
...Rocket!
[LUFFY laughs]
Awesome!
[LUFFY grunts]
Hey! The chests! You see?!
What the hell is he up to?
Hey!
[USOPP]
Hey, Luffy!
[NAMI]
What's going on?!
[LUFFY grunts]
I found 'em! Six
treasure chests!
Yes! Good work! [laughs]
Now it's mine! I got my
treasure! C'mon toss it down,
I wanna see it! Go ahead
and toss it down boy!
Let's have a look at it!
No way!
No way?!
I don't wanna.
Sucks for you!
What kind of crap is that,
Luffy? Give the man his gold!
You ass! That treasure
belongs to Gaimon
and you know it!
Toss it all down now!
Hey, I'm not joking
around, mister!
[GAIMON]
It doesn't matter.
It's all right.
[NAMI]
It's not all right.
Gaimon. You've been
guarding that treasure
with your heart and soul
for the past 20 years!
[GAIMON]
Straw Hat.
You're a great guy!
Uh. What do you
mean he's great?
I always had an inkling that...
this might be the case.
I tried not to think
about it. But still...
[cries] They're empty!
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Yep. Every last one of 'em.
How sad. The treasure he
guarded for 20 long years
was just a bunch of empty boxes.
[GAIMON]
It happens all the time
with treasures that have
maps leading to them.
You set out on a
quest to find it,
but some one else
got to it first.
That's the kind of
risk you have to take
when you're a treasure
hunting pirate.
You can waste a whole
lifetime searching
and never once touch treasure.
Plenty of pirates lived
like that. Believe me!
[laughs] Try not to
be too upset, old man!
It's a good thing we came
along after twenty years!
Thirty years later, and
you might've been dead!
Oh, Straw Hat...
‐‐Luffy...
‐‐Is he...?
Since this treasure hunt's
a bust, you're gonna need
something else to
fill your time.
Why don't you join up with us
and search for the One Piece?
What? Really?
You're asking me?
Oh... I know how
I must look to you.
Other people wouldn't even
speak to me, but you were kind!
It's been so many years since
I've had a friend! [cries]
Thank you!
[LUFFY] Are you sure you wanna
stay on the island, Gaimon?
Yes, I'm sure. There's something
here far more valuable
than treasure that
I feel I must protect.
[NAMI]
Huh?
Worth more than gold?
For the past 20 years,
these guys have stood by my
side through thick and thin.
I can't leave 'em.
[laughing]
[GAIMON] Now that I know
there's no treasure here,
I somehow finally feel free.
Without that heavy burden
I can concentrate on the things
that really matter to me.
And besides,
after all these years
I've grown fond of
this little box.
Too bad! You're a neat guy.
Pretty cool for a scrub brush.
The weird creatures here
are your true friends.
[LUFFY] Yep! And he's
the weirdest of them all.
Excuse me!
[NAMI, USOPP, ZORO laugh]
[ALL laughing]
See ya! Take care okay?!
Bye, Gaimon!
Straw Hat guy.
Don't ever give up on making
all your dreams come true.
If the legendary One
Piece exists out there...
then it's yours.
I hope it finds you well.
And when you have
it, buy the world!
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[USOPP]
Hey Zoro.
When did you start
using the Three‐Sword Style?
[ZORO]
Oh, well‐‐
[NAMI]
Stop being stupid, Usopp!
Zoro would never tell
anyone about himself!
[ZORO]
Actually...
[LUFFY] One sword is different
from the others, right?
[NAMI]
He just couldn't get a full set!
[USOPP] It's just an
ordinary old sword?!
[USOPP, LUFFY laughing]
[ZORO]
Shut up, you guys!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Three‐Sword Style's past!
Zoro and Kuina's vow!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!