[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[ENERU]
What?
[WYPER] Are you familiar with
the "Sea Prism Stone", Eneru?
[WYPER]
Die!
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
You're aware of the
consequences, are you not?
Your body will pay a
heavy price as well.
Why sacrifice yourself for a
homeland you will never regain?
If I must... I'll die. Gladly.
[WYPER] If it means I
can take you with me!
[gasps]
[ENERU]
Don't do it.
[WYPER]
Reject!
[CHIEFTAIN] Hold our true
ambitions in your heart
and speak not of them.
We are the weavers of history.
Those are the words
that were written on
a Poneglyph 800 years ago.
[WYPER]
Poneglyph?
[CHIEFTAIN] Yes. And when those
who sought to steal the stone
revealed themselves,
the Shandorian Warriors
of the City of Gold fought
bravely to protect it.
[WYPER]
Did they succeed?
Yes. They did. However...
...the battle took its toll.
A great many warriors
died that day.
Those few who survived vowed to
become guardians of the stone.
They kept watch over the city
and the sacred Poneglyph
they swore to
defend to the death.
[WYPER] And you say that's the
true story of our ancestors?
But then the island and City
of Gold were taken away
to Skypiea 400 years ago.
Since then, it's been
under Skypiean control.
[WYPER] Our ancestors
fought to their last breath
to defend that island.
And then it was taken away!
The Upper Yard.
That is our homeland,
but at the same time,
it alone holds a history
that has disappeared
into the darkness of time.
Even though it's is under the
control of the Skypieans now,
we must never allow the fire
of the proud city of Shandora
to die out.
[WYPER breathes heavily]
[LUFFY] "Ambition Toward the
Endless Vearth! The Ark Maxim!"
[grunting]
[NAMI gasps]
Robin.
[NAMI]
Gan Fall!
Oh no...
[gasps]
[grunts]
[NAMI]
It can't be.
He's restarting his own heart!
[gasps]
[groans]
[ENERU]
It's not that people fear God.
Rather, it is God
who is fear itself.
[ZORO]
What the hell is with this guy?
[chuckles]
[ENERU]
Wyper. I warned you, did I not?
I warned you of
the consequences.
[WYPER grunts]
[WYPER groans]
[ENERU]
And now look where you are.
How pitiful.
[ENERU]
You call yourself a warrior?
[WYPER]
Don't address me...
[ENERU]
...as if you know
anything about me!
[WYPER]
Eight hundred years ago,
proud Shandorian warriors fought
for the fate of this city.
They fought to their
death to protect it.
I am a descendant
of those warriors.
One day, our homeland
was taken away from us.
For 400 years we've carried
The Great Warrior Kalgara's
injured pride.
We've sought to return
our homeland to its
rightful place for generations.
And now that...
...I've finally made it...
...you're standing...
...in... my... way.
[ENERU] I must admit
you landed a good blow.
But what a cheap trick,
using that Sea Prism Stone.
And on top of that,
using a Reject dial should
easily kill the ordinary user.
But you shot it twice and
you're still breathing.
[ENERU scoffs]
Quite impressive.
[grunts]
[ENERU] However, you're still
no match for me.
[gasps]
Is that... a bird?
[ENERU]
Thirty million volt Hino.
[ENERU grunts]
[WYPER gasps, shouts]
[yells]
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO] So this has a Sea
Prism Stone in it, huh?
And now it's your turn,
Swordsman of the Blue Sea.
The only choice now is
to kill or be killed!
[ENERU]
Kiten!
[ZORO grunts, shouts]
[ZORO yells]
Zoro!
[NAMI]
I don't believe it!
Even Zoro!
[NAMI]
Everyone... has fallen to him.
[gasps]
How could he?
[NAMI]
Unreal.
Even as hurt as he is...
[NAMI]
...he still intends to fight.
[ENERU]
What do you hope to prove?
You're going to die anyway.
Why not make it
easy on yourself?
Did you say it's been 400 years?
For all that time you and the
Shandorians have been fighting
to take back your homeland?
And yet, you are the only
warrior who was managed
to make it here. No wonder
this nation will soon fall
to the Blue Sea and be
lost for all eternity.
[NAMI]
How could he do that?
[ENERU] You're fighting
for a lost cause.
Can't you see that you'll never
regain your homeland?
[NAMI]
He's unstoppable!
[ENERU]
So why get back up?
For my ancestors.
I must confess I was hoping for
a better answer than that.
But then again, I doubt you're
even completely conscious.
[gasps]
[NAMI]
Look out!
El Thor!
[NAMI shouts]
[gasps]
[ENERU] Of all who stood before
me, you are the only one left.
[gasps]
[NAMI]
I.... Just hear me out.
[NAMI whimpers]
[NAMI] I want to....
I want to go with you.
I've always wanted to
go to Endless Vearth.
To your dream world.
Can I come with you?
[CHIEFTAIN]
Wyper...
Wyper, come here.
[WYPER]
What is it?
[CHIEFTAIN] Since you
are a descendent of the
Great Warrior Kalgara, I feel
I must impart this to you.
Not many know the real reason
Kalgara wanted to regain
the homeland, and why he would
stop at nothing to do so.
[WYPER] So tell me.
What's the real reason?
[CHIEFTAIN] You see. Kalgara
felt that the loss of his
homeland was his
greatest failure.
The problem was, he lost
something else important to him.
[footsteps]
What's the matter? Are you
having second thoughts?
[NAMI] I haven't changed
my mind. I'm coming. Hold on!
[NAMI grunts]
That thing? Are you sure you
want to bring it along?
[NAMI] Uh, so... you don't
think I'll need it?
Honestly, I'm not certain
you'll be able to use it
where we're going.
It's up to you.
Do as you please.
[NAMI] Huh. Thanks for
letting me bring it.
I just really like this thing.
[NAMI whimpers]
[ENERU] Do you mourn them?
[NAMI gasps]
Uh, no, sir.
Heh. You don't have to put on
such a formal act, you know.
Express yourself, but don't make
the same mistakes as those fools
who couldn't comprehend
the true power of God.
They took me too lightly and
so forfeited their lives
in the process. Their failure
was that their minds were not
controlled by fear,
and so they were not
prepared for battle with me.
Do you understand?
[NAMI]
Yes. I-I suppose so.
I can't let him onto my plan.
I have no choice but to
obey everything he says.
An opportunity for escape will
present itself at some point.
But until then...
[gasps]
[NAMI]
Where is he taking me?
[NAMI gasps]
Excuse me.
Keep your mouth shut
and follow me.
[gasps]
[gasps] What's this?
[ENERU] What do you think?
Amazing, isn't it?
It's the only ship of
its kind in the world.
And it can only be
controlled by me.
In other words, it's powered
purely by lightning.
[gasps]
Is that even possible?
[ENERU] It's only natural
for you to be skeptical.
But I assure you it is possible.
I channel my abundant energy
through a material that
can handle the power
and automatically transmit
it throughout the ship.
What material could possibly
withstand that much power?
[gasps]
That's right.
The gold I have harvested from
this island works perfectly.
And I'm sure it will make many
inhabitants of this island
happy to see a flying ship
before their demise.
The sight of this
magnificent ship in flight
will be the last thing they see.
[ENERU laughs]
[NAMI] A flying ship?
I don't believe it!
If it really flies,
I might not have a chance
for escape after all.
Behold the Ark Maxim.
With this ship we will reach the
land that knows no boundary.
We will travel to the
Endless Vearth.
[ENERU laughs]
[AISA, LUFFY, PIERRE scream]
[AISA] We're outside.
We finally escaped.
The ground is made
of stone. Where are we?
[LUFFY yells]
[AISA grunts]
What going on, Luffy?
Hey, wait up!
[AISA]
Luffy!
[PIERRE groans]
We're free!
We made it out!
Woo-hoo! Where are we?
What are these old buildings?
It looks like this could be the
place that huge golden bell
is supposed to be.
What is this place? Wait.
Could this be our homeland?
[LUFFY]
Your homeland? Hey, not bad!
But where'd that
big hole come from?
[LUFFY gasps]
[AISA] Luffy! Wait!
Where are you going this time?
[AISA]
Wait for me!
[LUFFY gasps] Hey, Zoro!
What's wrong with you?
Come on, say something!
How could this have
happened to you?
How could any of this have
happened with you here?
[PIERRE yells]
[LUFFY] Nami! Where's Nami?
She's not here!
Wyper...! Wyper, no!
Bazooka guy was really strong.
But even he fell in this fight.
Who could possibly
have done all this?
It was Eneru!
[AISA] He's the only one who
could do something like this.
[LUFFY grunts]
Eneru, huh? That God guy?
[AISA]
Mm-hm.
My Mantra didn't work
at all the whole time
we were in the snake.
So I don't know
what happened here.
But I do know that it was
Eneru who did this.
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY]
Robin!
Our Navigator.
She went with him.
[gasps]
Just hang in there.
It'll be okay.
So you're saying Nami
was taken away from here
by that God guy? Where?
[ROBIN]
I don't know.
Listen carefully. If we
don't do something, Skypeia...
...will disappear.
What? It'll disappear?
[gasps] My homeland will
be completely gone?
Everything will fall.
He said this nation in
the sky was unnatural.
He said he'd send it
crashing to the ground.
[LUFFY] Eneru is definitely
going after the golden bell.
[gasps]
He won't destroy this
place until he's found it.
Right, and you have to stop him.
But you must hurry because
there isn't much time left.
You can't let Eneru
find that bell.
[AISA]
Don't worry.
I know where they are.
There are only two voices
left on this island.
It has to be Nami and Eneru.
[LUFFY]
Aisa.
I need you to take me
to them right now.
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[ENERU] I'm truly annoyed at the
non-fulfillment of my prophecy.
[NAMI]
Luffy!
[LUFFY] I guess
you're this Eneru jerk.
Wanna tell me what you think
you're doing to my friends?
[ENERU] Watch your mouth
when you speak to God!
[LUFFY] You're nothing
at all like a god!
On the next One Piece!
"They Finally Clash!
Pirate Luffy vs. God Eneru!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!