So what you're saying is
that you left the Straw Hats,
but you haven't given
up your life of crime.
What a shame.
If you're a pirate,
you're coming with us.
Merry!
I think I know
the answer, actually.
You have no idea how
much the World Government
has warped my life,
do you hear me?
If you hate the
government so much
then why would you help them?!
Because I have a wish that I
would sacrifice anything for.
They picked up
the life I gave up on,
returned the heart I lost
and continued the dreams
that I no longer believed in.
Even after all I've done,
I've found friends who
will still believe in me.
I see but then
what is your wish?
That excluding me, all of
the other Straw Hat pirates
will be allowed to
leave this island safely!
And as long as you have that,
you don't care what happens to
you of the rest of the world?!
I don't.
She was willing to
sacrifice the lives
of everyone in this
world, even her own.
As long as she could
save the six of you.
She was protecting us.
C'mon Chopper, wake up!
We have to find everyone!
You can sleep when you're dead.
We gotta get moving before
they take Robin away for good!
All right, CP9 should
be here any second now.
Let's go, Robin.
You'll have to get on
that train sooner or later.
You heard me.
Take the lady and
get moving, you dimwits.
Yes, sir!
A government rep,
a bunch of marines and Robin.
Let's see, how
should I play this?
Because inside of me,
I carry a darkness that
none of you know about.
No matter how you look at it,
they're obviously
escorting her away.
But those guys are chumps,
if she wanted to run,
she could take
them out, no problem.
She must be planning
something we don't know about.
There's gotta be a reason
why she's not running.
I'm here for you my darling!
Oh, my prince has
come to rescue me!
I've been waiting!
Aw, you want me
to save you, Robin?
Corgy, sir. CP9 is here.
Stop man handling me, damn it!
This body is expensive!
Oh man that's Rob Lucci, huh?
He's got the eyes of a killer!
Never thought I'd
see CP9 in person.
I'm gonna give you
to the count of ten,
and then it's gonna
get ugly! Do you hear me?!
Let go!
You don't know who
you're messing with!
I've got eight thousand men
hiding in the shadows
just waiting to teach
you losers a lesson!
Yep! They're gonna pop
out any minute now!
Any minute, you hear me?!
Better put me down quick!
Usopp, too?
The Sea Train Starts to Run."
All right, I'll give
you one last chance!
I'll call my men off for now,
but once we get on that train,
they're gonna tear
you limb from limb!
Listen jerks, if I were
you I'd quit while I was--
Why is he here?
Excellent work as
always, sirs and madam!
Here, Mr. Lucci, your coat.
What is this, a parade?
Stop it.
It's foolish.
Ah, right.
Sorry, sir!
This isn't over until we reach
Enies Lobby, so look sharp!
Everyone, board the
sea train immediately!
You heard the man!
Get on the train
and make it quick!
Hey, you bastards
gonna put me down or--?!
Who are those
guys in the suits?
He says he's sorry for
causing us so much trouble
then he goes and gets
in trouble all over again.
A little further to the right!
Spray over there!
Bring the hose this way!
We've almost got it!
I think we're good
over here for now.
Go see if you can help
out with the injured!
Right! I'm on it!
Is there anyone left inside?!
Hey!
Watch your step over there!
So you mean Robin
doesn't hate us after all?!
Uh-huh!
I'm so happy!
Huh? He's a raccoon dog?
I thought he was a reindeer!
Did he just transform, or what?
Anyway Chopper.
We have to find the rest
of the crew right away
so we can all go rescue Robin!
Okay! Let's go!
Uh, but where are they?
I don't know!
That's why we have to find them!
Yeah! Let's do this!
Now he's a gorilla!
Wait, you two.
I don't care if you
go after Nico Robin
but before you run off, you
should know that the sea train
for government personnel is
departing at 11 o'clock tonight.
This is just my guess
but there's a good chance
you'll find CP9 there.
And that means Nico Robin
will be there as well.
Thanks to Aqua Laguna,
they're stopping all service
after this final departure.
In other words,
you won't be able to chase
them on another train.
Wait, you mean we have to--
Since you obviously
can't sail in this weather,
you won't be able to
leave the island
unless you go after
that train right now.
Huh?!
No way!
What time is it?
Almost 10:30.
What?!
That means we've only
got half an hour left!
Hey, but you're
the mayor, right?
Can't you do something
to stop the train?
Mwell unfortunately,
it's bound for Enies Lobby,
which is only accessible
to government personnel.
Even the engine driver
works for the government.
So I have no say in this matter.
Oh no!
I guess our only choice
is to head to the station
and try to talk
some sense into Robin.
Chopper!
I'll tell you which direction
Luffy and Zoro flew off in,
so you go search there, okay?
If you find them,
tell them to come to the
station as quickly as they can!
Okay.
Got it!
Hey, listen up.
Look you guys!
Paulie's okay!
See that girl over there?
I want you to help
her find her buddies.
What?
You sure that smoke didn't
get to your brain, Paulie?
These are the guys that
tried to kill Mister Iceberg.
We should wring their
no-good-sorry necks!
Besides, why should we waste
our time helping some criminals
when Lucci and Kaku
are still missing?!
The Straw Hats aren't
the ones who did it, okay?
The real criminals set them up!
If we hadn't been so damn blind,
we wouldn't be in this
situation right now!
I don't know the real identity
of those guys in the masks
but I do know
that the Straw Hats
tried to protect us from them.
As a matter of fact, Iceberg
and I wouldn't even be alive
right now if it
wasn't for their help.
Don't bother looking for
Lucci and Kaku there's no point.
In fact, I don't know if we'll
ever be seeing them again.
What?
If you know what
happened to the foremen,
then you gotta tell us, Paulie!
They went back home.
Huh?!
Why would they do
that at a time like this?!
Just shut up and
go find Straw Hat!
Hey, immoral girl!
What? You're still
calling me that?
If you're going to the station,
I'll show you the way.
Uh thanks, I guess.
Hey, hold a sec, Paulie!
Is that stuff you told us true?!
Quit yer yapping and
help them out already!
You're making
Galley-La look bad!
Yes!
Sorry, sir!
We'll do our best!
You're the boss!
Yeah!
We'll help any way we can!
Open the cage!
Bring out the yagaras!
Yeah!
"Went back home," did they?
I spared 'em the details.
It's better that way.
It was bad enough
when we found out.
They deserve the truth but
I don't wanna hurt those guys.
'Kay, Chopper!
It's all up to you, now!
Right!
I'll find Luffy and Zoro,
you can count on me!
Hey!
Guys!
Hello?
Hey! Guys! Can you hear me?!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, you can come
with us too, okay?
Now shout it with me!
All right buddy, you
got it. Let's do it, guys!
Yeah!
Hey!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, you can come with us too.
Take that canal over
on the left-hand side.
It's a shortcut to the station!
We still have 20 minutes
before the train leaves.
Don't go, Robin.
You don't have to
sacrifice yourself!
We can save you!
Mr. Yagara, you think you can
go a little bit faster, please?
The 11 o' clock train
is about to depart.
All passengers going from
Blue Station to Enies Lobby,
please board immediately.
That hurt!
I don't wanna hear another
word out of you two!
Well maybe I wouldn't
complain so much
if you weren't
such big jerkwads!
Yeah you big jerkwads!
Why don't you come
over here and fight?!
Hey, that's too much.
Due to the approaching storm
surge, the departure time
has been moved up and the
train will be departing shortly.
Damn it, this was
bad enough already.
After all these years,
our mission has
finally come to an end.
We're not there yet.
Stop spouting nonsense
and take your mission
seriously, you fool.
My apologies.
You can't sail in this weather.
Unless you can catch that train
you won't be able to leave.
Come on.
We're so close!
Franky, wherever you
are I hope you're safe.
Hey, Luffy!
Roronoa!
Luffy!
Hey!
Come back!
Where are you?!
Come on!
There's not much time!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, you can come too.
Luffy, please!
Those guys're gonna
take Robin away!
We need your help!
Where are you?!
I wonder how the rest of the
crew is dealing with this mess.
Anyway, time's up. They'll
have to catch me later.
I repeat: the final train will
be departing ahead of schedule.
Please board immediately.
Damn it!
You bastards!
I'm coming for you!
Just wait, you'll see!
Once I get out of here.
One little slip-up,
then this crap happens.
I'm coming for you bastards.
Once I get out of here.
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Where are you?
We gotta save Robin!
Straw Hat!
Roronoa!
I don't get it.
Where in the heck are they?
Have we checked over there yet?
Hey!
Straw Hat!
Zoro!
I guess they're not here.
Has anybody checked
over in the backstreets yet?
I don't know if we can.
They're probably
completely flooded by now.
It'd be too dangerous
to look for them there.
Come on, guys!
Where are you?!
There's no time!
Excuse me.
The waves are getting
dangerously high,
so we've decided to depart
early as a safety measure.
If it's any trouble, we could...
It's fine.
Just go.
Coo coo!
Yes, sir.
We lived here for five years
but even as we leave I don't
feel nostalgic in the least.
Hey, was that a
steam whistle just now?
If it was, that means
the train is running
nearly fifteen minutes
ahead of schedule.
They're probably
taking off early,
'cause the weather's
getting bad.
The government runs that line,
so they can leave
whenever they want!
Hurry it up, guys!
The station's right there!
Hold on, train!
Don't leave yet!
Attention, tonight's final
departure, heading from
Water Seven to Enies Lobby
is now leaving the station.
You heard her.
Sit down already.
Have a safe trip.
I no longer have
any reason to live!
Just leave me here to die!
I don't have to listen to you.
You're coming with me
whether you like it or not.
I wanted nothing more than
to die at that very moment.
But, you forced me to live.
That's your crime!
I'm afraid there's no place
left for me to go or return to.
So I've decided to
stay here with you.
I see your problem,
guess there's no
other choice, is there?
Welcome.
Luffy!
Hey, there's nothing
to worry about.
She isn't a bad person.
Trust me, okay?!
Could he... Could he
mean the Rio Poneglyph?!
Like Gold Roger before me,
I have an important
duty to fulfill.
To guide the passages,
I've read to the end of
the Grand Line to Raftel.
Hey, Robin!
Robin!
Are you feeling okay now?
Hey, I think we're moving.
Stupid government jerkwads.
Good job, Mr. Yagara!
Go down the stairs
through the middle entrance!
Got it!
We're coming for you
Robin, please don't go!
Hey, stop!
Who are you?
That's dangerous!
Stay back!
Robin, get off that train!
I don't care who you're
up against. We'll help you!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Where are you guys?!
Can't move.
Wait!!
No!
Come back!
Robin!!
Robin!
What's this letter?
You mean Sanji
got on the sea train?!
Good!
Then he can protect
Robin 'til we get there!
Right!
We'll meet up with
everyone at Enies Lobby!
But I still can't
find Luffy and Zoro.
There's no way we can
do this without them!
They have to be here somewhere!
On the next One Piece:
"Sanji Barges in!
Sea Train Battle in the Storm!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!