[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!
[roaring]
I see its fangs!
What are you waiting for?!
[LUFFY]
Grandpa Ryu!
Hang in there. I'll help you!
Grandpa!
[LUFFY]
"Through the Sky They Soar!
The 1000 Year Legend
Lives Again!"
Hang in there!
Look, I've never been
to the Dragons' Nest,
but I don't think
it's down there!
Please don't die.
Grandpa Ryu!
Damn those Marines!
Not good!
Yeah. It looks like
the dragon can't swim.
[sighs]
What a relief. That beast
was headed right for me.
[MARINE A] Commodore! The
Millennial Dragon is sinking!
It's fine.
There's still time to reach him.
Drag in the carcass
with a harpoon.
That's it. Aim high!
Now take your best shot!
Fire!
[BOTH gasp]
Wha‐‐?!
That wasn't nice.
[NELSON laughing]
[NELSON] You've no idea the
value of that stupid animal
you're standing on!
You can keep the dragon.
I just want its bones!
With the Dragonite
in my possession,
nothing can prevent me from
attaining the ultimate power:
Everlasting life!
[NELSON laughing]
[screams]
This dragon has a name!
It's Grandpa Ryu, jerk!
Ya got that?
And he has every intention of
keeping his bones to himself!
You try my patience!
For your insolence, you can
sink to the bottom of the sea
with your dragon!
Now prepare for your punishment!
Destroy that obnoxious brat!
Uh... Um, but, Sir,
we can't destroy the boy
without obliterating the dragon!
So what?! Bone fragments
will serve my purpose fine!
[OFFICER]
Yes, sir!
Ready the cannons!
[MARINES]
Yes, sir!
You're fine with staying here?!
Well, I'm not.
You gotta fight back!
You haven't accomplished
your goal, remember?
What happened to going
home to your nest?
Don't give up on your dream
when you've gotten this close!
Sure I will.
Don't worry about Apis.
I'll protect her.
You need to stop worrying
about everyone else
and think about yours‐‐
[APIS] Please, you've gotta
untie these ropes!
Grandpa Ryu needs my help!
[USOPP]
What's that?!
[APIS] It's up to me!
I can't let him down!
He'll be safe with Luffy!
I promise!
No! You're not listening!
I have to go!
If anyone can save
the dragon, it's him!
[NAMI]
The entire sea is shaking.
Oh, come on! As if we don't
have enough problems!
[LUFFY] What the‐‐?!
What's going on?! Hey.
Really?
Oh, so that's it.
[NELSON]
What's going on?
[OFFICER]
Uh. I don't know, Sir!
There aren't any underwater
volcanoes in this area.
No matter! Fire! Fire! Fire!
[yelps]
[roars]
I get it!
That's it!
You're calling some of your
friends, aren't you?!
He's calling them.
[USOPP] Calling them?
Exactly who's he calling?
The others.
[BOTH]
Huh?
What do you mean?
He's calling out to all
the other Millennial Dragons,
telling them it's time.
Finally.
Time for what precisely?
I'm confused.
[USOPP stammers]
Wh‐What's that?!
[NAMI, APIS]
Huh?
Who knew that Grandpa Ryu
had so many friends!
A whole army of dragons!
What the...?
Where did these
things come from?!
[laughing]
Huh? Oh my!
Look at this!
A whole fleet of Dragonite!
[screams]
Idiots! What are you doing?
Shoot them all down!
We can't!
Our cannons just can't reach
high enough for that, Commodore!
[roars]
Ryu!
Yeah. Don't worry.
I'll tell her for you. Promise.
[NELSON laughing]
Gum‐Gum...
[LUFFY]
...Rocket!
Gonna borrow your neck!
[LUFFY]
Battle‐Axe!
[NELSON]
What's he doing?
[MARINE C]
Ship down!
[MARINE D]
Ah! What just happened?!
[MARINE E] The commodore's
ship's been destroyed.
Yep. Never fails.
Take out the leader and
the troops all run for cover.
I was hopin' these guys
would stay and fight.
We better get goin' ourselves.
They're circling. Wonder why.
[ZORO]
Hey! Let's go!
Right!
[MARINE F]
The chains! Unhook the chains!
[MARINE G]
You idiots! What are you doing?!
[MARINE H]
We're gonna crash!
Whoa! That was awesome!
[SANJI]
Nami, I've defended your honor!
[ZORO]
Get on board already!
[NAMI]
Where's Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum!
Rocket!
'Scuse me!
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY]
Yo!
Yo, yourself!
Do you have to slam
into the deck?!
You're gonna destroy the ship
if you're not more careful!
Grandpa!
An earthquake?
Again?!
[APIS] It's not fair.
Why did you have to die?
Now I can't keep
my promise to you.
I couldn't help you
realize your dream
of returning to
the Dragons' Nest.
[LUFFY] That's not true.
He got his wish.
[LUFFY] Can't you hear the
voices of the other dragons?
[APIS screams]
What's that?
A‐An earthquake!
The island's falling apart!
They're getting bigger!
What's going on?
Huh? Hey! Look!
[VILLAGER D]
The ocean! It's receding!
That's it. So that's
what it means!
What? What's "what" mean?
[NAMI] The Dragons' Nest!
It really is here!
The name, Millennial Dragon.
Why didn't I see it before?
The reason they're called
"Millennial Dragons"
has nothing to do
with their lifespan!
[NAMI] It's because they
migrate to this island
only once every 1000 years!
By no means is that
an arbitrary schedule
they've decided
to stick to either!
They only visit every 1000 years
because that's the only time
the island surfaces!
That's why they
call it Lost Island.
Anyone who was around to
see it last time is long gone!
And here we are!
The next generation
to bear witness
to the rising of Lost Island
and the Dragons' Nest!
Is... that what I think it is?
Yeah.
Now I can see why Grandpa
Ryu was so anxious
to get back to this place!
It's here.
[SANJI]
Hey! Apis!
[USOPP]
Come back!
And she's off, but where to?
Grandpa Ryu.
He's finally home.
[APIS]
Grandpa Ryu!
Grandpa!
Please get up!
Grandpa Ryu!
How strange.
I mean, what are the
chances he would fall
directly on top of
the Dragons' Nest.
I hope that brought
him some peace.
I think so.
I heard him say his wish had
come true as he was sinking.
Strange place to put a nest.
I mean, what's with all these
weird looking rocks?
[SANJI] It's likely that
they're all made of Dragonite.
Notice the structure.
They look just like
dragons if you ask me.
Oh, yeah, right.
So what, the dragons carved
statues of themselves?
They're not statues.
Those are actual skeletons.
Fossilized Dragonite that's been
preserved on the ocean floor.
Ah, yeah.
[ZORO]
You still don't get it, do you?
Nope! Not a bit.
I've heard that when
elephants are about to die,
they instinctively travel
to a pre‐determined area,
like an elephant graveyard.
Maybe the same is true here.
It's a dragon graveyard.
[ZORO]
A graveyard?
[APIS]
It can't be.
Because Grandpa Ryu
promised me
that going back to his nest
would make him better!
It's not a graveyard! It's not!
Apis.
Listen to me. Grandpa
Ryu was lost and lonely.
Luffy?
He didn't have a friend.
Until you came along.
Then... everything changed
for the better.
And he wanted you to know
that for all the centuries
he's been alive,
this last year with you was the
happiest time he's ever known.
Wait.
Are you saying you can
understand the dragon?
It just came to me.
Are you making this up?
Nope. That's what he said!
[APIS]
You're a liar.
If this is the place you
always talked about,
then it should heal you
and make you strong again
like you promised me!
Talk to me!
You have to get better!
[APIS crying]
Ryu was telling you
the truth, Apis.
I'm serious.
He said that Millennial Dragons
return to the nest
every thousand years
and are reborn again.
[APIS]
Grandpa Ryu said all that?
[LUFFY]
Over there!
[gasps]
[APIS]
A baby Millennial Dragon?!
[NAMI]
I was wrong, Apis.
I don't think this is
a graveyard at all.
I think it's a place of renewal.
A special location
designed to bring
both old and new life together.
[APIS]
Thank you so much.
You all risked a lot
to bring Grandpa Ryu
back to the Dragons' Nest.
I always knew this place
was important to him,
but I never knew why until now.
Apis.
[APIS]
This is a place of miracles.
Now I understand
why my ancestors
went to so much trouble
to build the temple.
[APIS]
Thank you most of all, Luffy.
So let's go home!
Everyone's probably worried.
Won't they be surprised!
[chuckles]
Yeah!
All right! Let's get Apis back
home! It's time to celebrate!
‐‐[USOPP] Sounds good to me!
‐‐[LUFFY] I'm starving.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Sanji. Food. I need food.
[SANJI]
All right.
[LUFFY]
I want meat right off the bone!
[USOPP] We gotta have sprouts!
I want sautéed bean sprouts!
[SANJI] Hmm. Why does
that sound familiar?
[USOPP chuckles]
[USOPP] Man, these fossils are
unlike anything I ever imagined.
It's unbelievable that
they all used to be
living, breathing Dragons.
[NAMI]
But they were.
[SANJI] Even if the whole
Dragonite thing is true,
it can't be extracted
in their current state.
[USOPP] Then the Marine's whole
Elixir of Immortality plot?
[NAMI] Was nothing
but a silly dream.
These fossils are covered
with centuries of coral.
Even if we took 'em
back with us,
we'd never get a drop
of elixir from them.
[ZORO] Mean those Marines did
all that work for nothing.
[NELSON] Inept fools!
They think they've won!
As if I could be
dispatched so easily!
I must pay them back
for their effort!
But first things first. Ha!
Look at them all.
[NELSON laughing]
[NELSON]
A limitless supply of Dragonite
just waiting to be plucked!
[NELSON laughing]
[NELSON]
Hm?
[ERIC]
Move.
Eric, Look! A flock
of Millennial Dragons!
How fortuitous for
us both, my friend.
What say we seal
another deal?
How much money will it take‐‐?
[ERIC]
Get out of my way!
♪All that's in my
heart confuses me,
I cannot understand,
As I face what I must do,
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand.
I'll set sail alone,
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near,
As I drift away,
I pray you watch me
as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise,
I began to wonder,
What could be the reason,
It's so hot inside.
No answer has come,
But I can't get away
from what's true,
It's because of you...
Show me how to
catch those feelings,
Get 'em to come back to me,
I'll do what I must,
Because they're
everything I wanna be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back
from yesterday,
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we
can make the way.♪
[USOPP]
It's Eric!
[LUFFY]
He's persistent!
[ZORO]
I'll handle him.
[LUFFY]
No, I will! Get lost!
[NAMI] Lost Island. It's kinda
sad leaving it behind.
[LUFFY]
All right, set sail!
We're off to the
Grand Line at last!
[ZORO]
It's about time.
[USOPP]
There it is!
[LUFFY]
So that's the Red Line!
On the next One Piece!
"An Angry Showdown!
Cross the Red Line!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!