[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
Just go straight...!
What does it matter...?!
We've already been eaten here!
Straight, okay?!
Just keep going!
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY] "Nami's Sick? Beyond
the Snow Falling on the Sea!"
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
We're flying!
[ZORO]
Hmph.
[LUFFY]
Don't bother lookin back!
'Cause we're goin'
straight ahead!
Look at us!
This is so incredible!
They cut... the sea... itself!
The strength of...
the Elbaf Warriors...
...is amazing!
Friends!
Go... Good luck!
Gya gya gya gya!
Gya ba ba ba ba!
[LOUIS] Long ago, the sea
was ruled by colossal,
swashbuckling ruffians known
as the Giant Warrior Pirates...
Living only for the thrill
of battle and conquest,
these pirates laid waste
to all who opposed them.
They were presided
over by two bosses,
Red Ogre Broggy
and Blue Ogre Dorry,
both exceptionally strong...
The power and influence they
held went largely unchecked,
for no other giant
was their equal
and ordinary men cowered
in their massive shadows.
This made the fact that a lone
little girl single‐handedly
put an end to their attacks
all the more surprising.
Our two bosses are truly great!
Did you hear about their catch?!
Yeah!
I can hardly think
about anything else!
It's so exciting!
It's not every day someone
bags a huge Sea King!
And they each got one...
Now, that's impressive...
Yeah. Take us for example,
we're Elbaf giants.
No greater warrior exists,
but even we don't come close
to taking down one of
those massive beasts...
Wouldn't you say
that's fair, men?!
Yeah!
You got that right!
Our bosses are the best!
[BROGGY]
Gya, ba, ba, ba, ba!
I bet... that no one's ever
slain a bigger Sea King than us!
A conquest destined
to become legend!
Gya, gya, gya, gya!
Awesome!
So which one was bigger?!
[BROGGY]
Hm?
What?
Which one?
[LITTLE GIRL]
Mm‐hm!
Who won the contest,
you or Broggy?
[DORRY, BROGGY]
Hmm...
[DORRY] Look at them
side‐by‐side, Broggy!
Mine is slightly bigger, see?!
[BROGGY]
Keep dreaming!
Mine beats yours by
three whole centimeters!
[DORRY]
What?! You're joking!
[BROGGY]
No!
[GIANT A]
Bosses, please! Stop bickering!
I suppose I should
mention Broggy...
I recall something
about a hunting contest,
but I can't exactly remember...
Don't worry, Dorry.
The same thing goes for me.
[DORRY, BROGGY]
Hmm?
It's Middle Mountain!
So...
What do ya say... you and
I go ahead and finish this?!
Sure...!
We can always think
things through after that!
[fighting sounds]
[USOPP]
Guys, listen up!
I will go to Elbaf someday!
To the village of warriors!
Yeah! Great!
[LUFFY, USOPP]
♪ Gi‐Gi‐Giants! Gi‐Gi‐Giants!
♪ El... baf! El... baf!
♪ Everyone is huge!
♪ They're so huge...
because they're giants... ♪
♪ Gi‐Gi‐Giants!
♪ Everybody's huge! Yeah!
Where do they
get so much energy?
[LUFFY, USOPP scream]
[KAROO]
Quaaack!
[sighs]
Wow...
After everything that's
happened here, I'm exhausted...
Um... Vivi, could
you watch this for me?
Sure.
You're on your way...
Soon you'll return to Alabasta.
Well, my rosy
outlook is assuming
we can make it there safely
and without any more surprises.
Yes. I must return!
It's my obligation...!
I am the person everyone
in the kingdom is counting on.
[IGARAM] Believe me
when I say it is the only way
to save the kingdom!
It is true that your father no
longer has sway with the people.
Our only hope of
stopping this uprising
is for you to tell
them the truth!
This is the only action
that can save us.
You have to understand that
your survival is paramount.
You must live, even if
it means sacrificing others.
Whether by grace
or betrayal, live on...
No matter what!
Sometimes...
it's harder to live...
...than to die
I will return home... alive.
[SANJI]
You'll get home,
but there's no need
to push yourself so hard.
You've got me!
Here ya go... Try these sweets.
They'll help you relax.
I've made some delicious tarts,
and your choice
of coffee or tea.
Thank you...
[SANJI]
Yours are in the kitchen!
Now go!
[LUFFY, USOPP shouting]
[LUFFY] Mine, mine,
mine, mine, mine...
Uh...
[ZORO]
603...! 604...! 605!
60... 6!
Dammit all...!
If I only could've cut that wax!
I wouldn't have...
left anyone hanging there!
I'm so weak!
[ZORO]
If I'm gonna get stronger,
I need to be able to
slice through stuff like that
from any stance!
[HENCHMAN A]
Mr. 2...! Bon Clay...!
The Swanda is ready to set sail!
[BON CLAY]
Okay, okay! I heard ya, sheesh!
Do you have to scream?!
Honestly, somebody
give me one good reason
why I should be
the one to do this?!
Mr. 3 is a piece of garbage!
Go toss him out yourselves!
That's impossible!
We wouldn't even stand
a chance against him!
But you have to help!
Those were the boss's orders...
[BON CLAY]
Un... deux... trois...
Uh, what's "four" again...?
Anybody?
[sighs]
That 0... So much trouble.
[NAMI]
Vivi... I'm sorry, but, I...
I need to rest.
I understand, Nami...!
Don't worry,
everything's under control.
I'll keep an eye on our course.
[VIVI gasps]
[pants]
You're burning up!
Hey, everyone...! Come quick!
[ZORO]
Huh?
What's wrong, Vivi?
Are you okay?!
[VIVI]
Nami has an awful fever!
What...?! Nami's sick?!
[NAMI pants]
[USOPP]
Huh...?
It's most likely the climate...
It's quite normal...
See... Sailors in the
Grand Line aren't used
to the strange weather
and can become quite ill...
There are countless stories
of tough, notorious pirates
who suddenly died.
Their immune systems
were attacked and ravaged
by colds and fevers.
Ignoring the symptoms can make
even the slightest cold deadly.
[whimpers]
[SANJI]
Nami!
Is there anyone aboard this ship
with even the slightest
amount of medical experience?
Well... when you're sick eating
lots of meat always helps
Right, Sanji?
Huh? Meat is protein
and that does give the body
energy to operate properly...
I can cook some foods
that'll boost her energy,
but there's no guarantees.
I'm not a doctor.
Besides, if my cooking
made that big a difference,
she'd never get sick.
I put a hundred times more
care into preparing her meals
than I do for you losers.
I serve Nami fresh meats
and vegetables
to ensure a balanced diet...
Anything that's
rotten or moldy...
...goes to you.
Jerk!
Oh well,
still tastes good to me!
[laughs]
[sighs] My point is that as
long as I'm this ship's cook,
nobody's gonna feed Nami
better in terms of nutrition.
I can do anything
in the kitchen...
Still... I do know that
there are specific foods
for different
kinds of illnesses,
but I can't make that call.
She needs to be
diagnosed by a doctor
who will tell us
how to help her.
Just... feed her
everything that we've got.
Oh, shut up...
She doesn't have
the energy to eat.
She's sick...
Ah! One hundred four!
No, this isn't good...
There's bound to be doctors
and nurses in Alabasta
that can help, right?!
How much longer
till we get there, Vivi?
[VIVI]
I don't know.
At least a week,
and that's too long!
'Kay, so she's sick.
Maybe we're overreacting.
I don't know.
I've never been this sick.
Morons! Have you
all lost your minds?!
This is serious!
She shouldn't have
such a high fever
unless her body's
fighting an infection!
This is bad...
Whatever's wrong,
it's possibly life‐threatening.
Ahhh!
You mean Nami's gonna die?!
Your screams aren't helping!
We have to find a doctor
to help Nami before she dies!
Okay! Everyone just calm down!
You're only going to
make her feel worse...
Listen.
[gasps]
Huh?
I'm fine.
Nami?
Yay! She's cured!
Shut up!
[pants]
Go to my desk,
open the second drawer...
There's a newspaper
in the bottom.
No change... in our course.
[VIVI]
No!
That's not possible!
Huh...? What's up?
Something wrong?
Is it about Alabasta?
Tell us!
According to this article, three
hundred thousand royal soldiers
have defected to the Resistance.
Until now, we've been
embroiled in a cold war,
with six hundred thousand
royal soldiers against
four hundred thousand rebels...
With this...
the balance has shifted!
[pants]
The uprising in Alabasta
will seriously escalate now.
Things'll get ugly.
That paper you're looking
at is three days old.
I'm sorry I didn't
say something earlier.
We can't change our speed,
so I didn't want to worry you...
There's nothing anyone
can do right now.
You understand... Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Hmm...
Things are bad, and
they're beyond our control!
[NAMI] That sunk in
better than I'd hoped.
Nami, look...
You need to see
a doctor right away!
I'm fine...
That thermometer's broken...
I mean, come on,
nobody gets a
temperature of 104...
It's probably just a
mild case of sunstroke.
There's nothing a doctor
can do for me that time won't.
Besides we don't have
time to hunt for one.
We need to head straight
for Alabasta, right?
I appreciate the concern...
Thank you.
Huh, she sure recovered fast...
No... She's faking.
[pants]
[VIVI] Now that this conflict
has escalated,
more blood will be shed
throughout the kingdom...
We're at war.
If I don't put a stop
to this insanity,
the entire Kingdom of
Alabasta will be doomed...!
Crocodile will move in
and seize control!
You're trying to get me home
safely, but there's no time...!
I need to get home
as quickly as possible!
If I don't make it back in time,
a million innocent citizens will
give their lives needlessly!
There's a million people there?!
Wow!
What a horrible burden
you have to carry...
I'm sorry.
[whimpers]
[gasps]
Zoro, what the hell have you
been watching all this time?!
What are you talking about?
We've been goin' straight
ahead as you ordered.
Oh yeah, straight
at a right angle...!
Look at the Eternal Pose...
It doesn't lie!
I don't need to look at it...
I've been using that big cloud
over there as my guide.
You moron, clouds move
and change shape constantly!
Ow! Jeez, my head's killing me.
So leave the navigating
to me and go to bed!
I wish that I could,
but I'm here because
I can't trust you with this!
[grunts]
The air... It's changed...
[ZORO]
What do ya mean...?
The weather's been
nice like this all day.
[NAMI]
Never mind!
Just get the others!
Hey! Get your butts out here!
Right now!
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Huh?
What do ya want?
[SANJI] Ya know,
I find it hard to get motivated
when you're giving the orders.
[ZORO]
Shut up and get moving...!
Take the seat and
catch the portside wind!
[SANJI]
Nami, what's up...?
It's a perfect day.
The sun is shining,
the waves are quiet...
[NAMI]
The wind...
Wind?
There's a powerful wind...
It's heading right this way.
I think.
Luffy...?
You're head's on fire!
You gotta stay in bed!
And we need to get you a doctor!
Maybe you should mind
your own business.
This is my normal temperature!
Now quit being so stupid
and pull the damn ropes!
Nami... I know you're
acting brave for Vivi,
but if you keep pushing,
your body won't have
a chance to heal!
Quack.
I told you guys I'm fine!
Let it go!
Whoa... Hey...
Take it easy.
Not another word, dammit!
Hurry and move the ship!
[SANJI]
Right, we're on it.
[USOPP]
You got it.
Sheesh...
Something... I don't know...
But something's headed
this way... and soon.
[ZORO grunts]
Huh?
[VIVI] I need to get home...
before time runs out.
[VIVI]
I have to ask you all a favor!
As a passenger on your ship,
it's not my place to ask this,
but I have no choice...
My homeland is in
jeopardy of being destroyed.
So I would
really appreciate it,
if we could move even faster...
Every minute I'm out here,
puts more of my people in
danger of losing their lives.
We need to head for
Alabasta at full speed!
Of course, we will...
Just like we promised.
Then it's settled.
Let's find an island with
a doctor on it right away!
Huh?
First thing's first...
We need to hurry and
get Nami healthy again.
Then we head for Alabasta!
After all, we need her at the
helm to move at top speed...
Right...!
No one makes this
ship move like Nami!
Princess... Hold on.
Won't finding a doctor
for Nami take time
the citizens of Alabasta
just don't have?
That's right!
So the sooner we
get Nami a doctor,
the sooner we can
get to Alabasta!
Those are wise words, Vivi...!
You're beautiful and brilliant!
The girl's got guts.
Thank you, Vivi.
Don't overexert yourself, Nami!
I'm... uh...
I'm sorry...
I may need to lie down...
[VIVI]
Nami!
What the hell is that?!
[VIVI]
It's a cyclone!
[LUFFY]
It's huge!
Wait! That's the same
path we were headed on!
[SANJI] Vivi's right...!
That's the exact same direction!
It would've been a direct hit
if we'd kept goin' straight!
We'd be dead right now!
See that...?!
Way too close...!
We barely missed it!
[VIVI]
Incredible!
Cyclones in the
Grand Line are said
to be impossible to predict...!
Yet, somehow Nami did!
However she does it,
it's obvious her technique
isn't based on any
conventional method...
It's as if she's detecting
the weather with her body!
It's beyond reason...!
A miracle!
All right!
What are we waiting here for?!
Let's find Nami a doctor!
[CREW]
Yeah!
[pants]
[SANJI] Ah!
What're we gonna do, Vivi?!
Nami's fever won't go down!
[KAROO]
Quack!
Hey, guys... Stop.
That behavior isn't helping!
[LUFFY]
See any doctors yet?!
Luffy, you can't be serious.
Uh, hey, guys...
What do you think about
people standing on water...
What‐‐do I think it's possible?
What kind of question is that?
It's impossible, of course!
Yeah...?
Well, then... what's that?
What's what?
Say what?
[LUFFY]
Hmm...
You think he's a doctor?
♪If there is a treasure
out there to be found,
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big place,
the oceans are wide,
Dumb luck alone
won't help you find it,
Just give up, it's astronomical.
Even so.
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on,
The laughter behind our
backs, it keeps us strong
It's too bad 'cuz we're still
sailing forward, so bon voyage!
Just leave us alone!
It may be foolish
chasing impossible things,
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream,
the more ambition
I'm gonna need!
It may be foolish
travelin' on, but I know
That I just gotta fight!
The farther the sea,
the greater paradise
We're gonna find!
Don't give up,
just keep on trying,
And you'll see that
you're closer to...
The horizon of your dreams!♪
[SANJI]
Oh, Nami!
Please forgive me for not being
able to bring your fever down!
[ZORO]
You need to cool your head off!
Look around!
[LUFFY] The Going Merry 's
being attacked!
[USOPP]
What'll we do?!
[SANJI]
That's it!
This is intolerable!
Nothing's worse
than Nami being sick!
[USOPP]
Would ya look at that?!
He's eating our ship!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"A Raid! The Tin Tyrant
and Tin Plate Wapol!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!