There's just one more
thing I want to tell you.
Slow-Slow Beam!
You should've learned your
lesson by now, Straw Hat!
Everyone knows, the
Silver Fox never forgets
a grudge and he
always gets what he wants.
Your fate was sealed the moment
you set foot on this ship!
[STRAW HATS scream]
This time, I'll settle
things once and for all.
And you'll have no
choice but to admit
that the Foxy Pirates are
the strongest in the world!
Feh-feh-feh!
[FOXY CREW cheers]
[FOXY CREW]
Boss!
Porche!
Hamburg!
[FOXY]
Feh-feh-feh!
[HAMBURG]
Puh-puh-puh!
The Straw Hats bit the dust.
[PORCHE] That was lovely
Boss, but what's next?
What do you think?
We're gonna humiliate
them the same way
they humiliated us in
that last Davy Back Fight!
All right you two,
let's begin Operation D!
[CREW cheers]
Do you hear that?
Sounds like a party.
I wonder what everyone's
doing over there.
Why don't you go pay
them a visit and find out?
I should be fine watching
the ship on my own.
If something bad happened,
I wouldn't want you to
get left here by yourself!
Besides, I'd rather
stick around and study.
[LUFFY] Why you gotta
be so tricky all the time,
Split Head?!
If you want a fight,
then come and get it!
Auugh!!
Calm down Luffy,
it'll be okay.
That afro might make you strong,
but right now I think
it's making you crazy!
Yep, Figures. All that afro
power has gotta go somewhere.
Please tell me that's
supposed to be a joke.
Getting revenge is one thing,
but using us to take out
his enemies is pretty low.
So what if you had to
beat up a couple of losers,
I'm more worried about our gold!
Any way you look at it,
he bit off more
than he can chew.
He should know better
than to get on our bad side.
We'll tear this sorry ship
to pieces in no time flat!
You can't beat the five of us!
Or the four of you at least.
[collective sighs]
Well anyway, before
we can wreak any havoc
we have to find
a way out of here.
And since this is Foxy's ship,
I'm sure there's some
dirty trick involved.
I think we can just
break through the wall.
Huh?
[SANJI]
What the hell is this place?
[FOXY] Choppy! Choppy,
wherever could you be?
Are you hiding from me again?
Jeez! If you don't come out,
I'll have to punish you!
[ROBIN]
Is something the matter, Doctor?
Uh... No, it's nothing.
Why you!
This is the lamest trick
you could possibly pull!
Let me handle this.
Luffy?
Listen! I'm on to you!
Oh?
Tell me where you're
hiding Split-Head now!
[collective shocked sounds]
I don't know what
you're talking about!
[LUFFY]
Wonder where he could be...
[ZORO] Even for Luffy,
this is pretty bad.
[NAMI]
Should we say something?
This is kinda awkward.
[SANJI] Let's just
see how this plays out.
Well, looks like
Split-Head's not here, guys.
Behind you!
Hmm? Huh?
Luffy, take a closer
look at that face.
Okay, but it looks
pretty normal to me.
You're not Porche!
You're Split-Head's
sister, aren't you?!
Ah!! This is getting me nowhere!
Feh-feh-feh!
Aaah! It was
Split-Head all along!
I'm gonna make you
pay for tricking me!
I don't know if I should
laugh or cry about this.
Say your prayers,
Straw Hat. Slow-Slow Beam!
Feh-feh-feh!
Haven't you fools
learned your lesson?
Sure, you can run
but my Slow-Slow Beam
will always find you!
Ugh! I've had about
enough of that thing.
Yeah, no kidding.
Slow-Slow Beam!
Look out!
Keep your hands off her!
Watch where you're going!
Sanji! Zoro!
No! They got hit!
I should've known
you'd dodge, Straw Hat!
You coward!
[LUFFY]
Hey, stop running away!
Ugh, C'mon, just
fight us already.
Hey, Nami, let's go!
Mm!
I'll see you guys when your
30 seconds are up, okay?
[ZORO thinking]
No! Don't leave us like this!
[SANJI thinking]
Nami, come back!
[USOPP]
Wait, what's that?
[NAMI] There's some
kinda note on the door.
[USOPP] Let's see. From
here on, it's a man's path.
No women allowed.
So, any clue what
that's all about?
Nope. Beats me but we'd
better stay on our toes.
Eh?
Is something the
matter, Doctor?
No, it's nothing.
That was about to get ugly.
For once, I agree with you.
[USOPP]
Huh...
It looks like a regular
old hallway to me.
Yeah.
[USOPP]
I take it back! This is weird!
What kind of place is this?!
Oh, I see. It's like a
holding cell under there.
These guys probably
did something bad
and got locked
away as punishment.
They can leer all they
want. I'm going ahead!
[USOPP]
Wait.
[PRISONER A]
It's a woman!
[PRISONER B]
All right!
[PRISONER C]
It's been so long!
I can't do it. I can't give
those creeps the satisfaction!
Leave it to me, Nami.
Huh? What are you?
Seems like they've been
locked up in the dark
for a while now and
if that's the case
they must be weak to light.
All I gotta do is bust
out one of my flash balls
and they'll be blind
as bats in no time.
And then we'll make
a break for it, huh?
Right, now close your eyes.
'Cause here it comes!
Okay, let's go!
You got it!
Help me!
[PRISONER D]
I got her!
Usopp, no!
My manhood!
[PRISONER E]
Let me touch her, too!
Don't worry! I'll never
forget your noble sacrifice!
[USOPP]
Don't leave me!
No!
[PRISONER B]
It's been too long!
[PRISONER F]
She's so soft!
Ah...!
Is something the
matter, Doctor?
No, it's nothing.
[NAMI panting]
Oh, that was a close one!
Huh? Another weird room.
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Hey, Nami!
[NAMI]
Luffy?
Took you long enough!
What're you doing sitting down
in the middle of Foxy's ship?!
What am I doing?
I'm eating these rice
crackers and having some tea.
Well duh, I can
tell that much!
[FOXY] You've done
well to make it this far!
Congratulations!
But now that you're both here,
perhaps I should be
congratulating myself instead.
You see, it was my
plan to separate you two
from the rest of
the crew all along.
Luffy I get, but why me?
[FOXY] Because you're obviously
the brains of the operation!
With you and the captain
out of the picture,
the Straw Hats are
as good as done for!
I bet those other goons
will wipe themselves out
long before I get to them!
[LUFFY]
Mmm... That's a good plan...
This could be bad.
But hey for now
might as well fight!
[FOXY]
Feh-feh-feh!
Right on, brother!
That's what I like to hear!
[PORCHE] Oh yay! Does
this mean we'll finally get
our revenge on Straw Hat?
[NAMI]
What are those things?
[LUFFY] I've never
seen that one before,
but this one is
called Gorilla Pants.
[FOXY] Puncher! Not pants!
It's Gorilla Puncher 13!
Now get ready!
Here comes the Gorilla Punch!
Leave this one to me, Nami.
Right!
Now, Gum-Gum...
I wouldn't do that if
I were you, Rubber Boy.
Remember what happens
when you touch the gloves?
[LUFFY]
...Pistol!
[FOXY]
It burns.
Hot hot hot hot...
[FOXY]
You forgot, didn't you?!
Luffy!
[PORCHE]
You better not ignore me!
Cause if you do,
Mr. Donkey Kicker 18
is gonna stomp you silly!
[LUFFY]
Hey! Nami!
Water, water, water,
water, water, water!
Oh, I see! That's a good idea!
Wow, I knew you were pathetic,
but if you think you can
beat us with magic tricks,
you're just plain crazy!
All right here goes!
Today's forecast is rain!
Thunderstorm Tempo!
Nice try, but it's
gonna take more
than a little crappy weather to
bring down my Gorilla Puncher!
[FOXY] You really
are stupid, aren't you?
If this thing can take
punches and lightning,
you think a little rain
can make any difference?!
We won't know
until we try, right?
All right, have it your way.
Since you clearly don't
have any common sense,
I'll have to beat some into you!
Gorilla Punch Golden Hit!
Can't burn me now!
Somebody stop him, quick!
Now Gum-Gum...
...Spinning Top!
Hey, Boss? You're
not gonna hit us, right?
Holy smoke!
No!
What was that?!
Look, it's Boss!
Did he beat the Straw Hats?!
Men, I've returned!
[cheers]
Yeah!
I got beat.
[snickers]
See? Just like I said,
you took too long
and they finished
the fight without us.
The only reason we're
late is 'cause you got lost!
Hey, Rubber Boy!
I lost fair and square
to a fellow pirate,
so you won't hear me complain.
Skin me, turn me in,
or do whatever you want.
All right, then. In that case.
Why don't you let them
join your crew again?
Huh?
What?! But they
stole the Sexy Foxy
and stabbed me in the back!
Yeah, so?
I said I wouldn't complain,
so have it your way.
All right, men. Straw Hat
says you get a free pass,
so that's how it's gonna be!
Boss? You mean it?
[LUFFY]
Go ahead. Talk to them.
Thank you.
Straw Hat.
Listen up, frogs. If you
all wanna be foxes again,
then that's fine with me.
Awww, Boss!
Yeah!!
Well, he's got charisma,
if nothing else.
[FOXY WOMEN]
We love you, Boss!
Kinda makes me mad.
Boss!
You better not be
switching sides on me.
I was just kidding, my darling!
[FOXY] Bon voyage,
Straw Hat, take care!
You too, Split-Head!
So, funky!
Yeah!
[NAMI]
Oh no you don't.
Good! I thought
you'd never wake up!
Where am I? Last
I remember I was...
Hey! You left me
stranded with those creeps!
That's not what happened
at all! Did you forget?
Ohh... When you put it that
way, then it all makes sense.
I don't remember
beating up all those guys,
but I guess I am
pretty strong, huh?
Eh-heh heh...
Hey, Boss, now that we
have our old crew back
we're finally done dealing
with those horrible
Straw Hat Pirates, right?
Not a chance.
Didn't take long for Boss
to cook up another scheme!
No matter what it takes we
have to crush the Straw Hats!
Otherwise, we're gonna be stuck
with this stupid looking flag
for the rest of our lives!
That being said, I think
you know our destination.
Yeah!
[thinking]
I'm coming for you, Rubber Boy.
Feh-feh-feh!
Hey guys! I think
I see an island!
[NAMI]
Hmmmm...
Looks uninhabited to me.
Ready the anchor!
Let's go check it out!
[SANJI] Find me some ingredients
and I'll start cooking lunch!
[CREW]
All right!
[NAMI] Listen, nothing
slimy or gross, okay?
[ZORO]
What does it matter?
Once it's in your stomach,
it's all the same.
Get over yourself.
[punch]
[ZORO]
Ow!
[LUFFY]
Hey! Sanji!
We got fish and fruit
and everything. It was easy!
Nice work!
[ALL]
Cheers!
Yummy!
It'd taste a lot better if
you didn't scarf it down!
I figured you wouldn't have
any room left for dinner,
since you finished off
all the snacks on the ship.
But I'm just getting warmed up!
[SANJI]
That's not good,
since we've decimated
half our supplies already.
[CHOPPER] Robin,
you better eat fast
before all the food is gone!
Just let me get to a
stopping point, first.
[CHOPPER] Okay, but I heard that
if you read too much you turn
into a yucky bug.
They call them book worms.
[FOXY]
Feh-feh-feh!
I found you Straw Hat!
You kids ready to
teach him a lesson?
You bet we are! Let's go!
Any time, Boss!
One, two, one two...
Hey, Boss, they're all
looking right this way.
What's the big deal?
Even if they do notice us,
they'll think we're
just an ordinary crab!
I hope they
don't try to eat us!
Is that who I think it is?
Who else would be that stupid?
Don't these guys have
anything better to do?
Okay while they're busy
eating, let's wreck their ship!
What's going on back there?!
I caught a crab! Let's eat it!
He's kidding, right?
Nope and I think he's about
to get a nasty surprise.
Stop! We're not food, you fool!
One, two, one, two!
Hey, come back! You look yummy!
Oh yeah? Then
take a bite of this!
[FOXY] Now's our chance!
Crab-Crab Punch!
The only thing you'll
be tasting is defeat!
Hey, now!
You better learn your place
if you know what's
good for you, crab!
Now open up!
'Cause I'm gonna eat you!
Wow, I can't believe you guys
got eaten by that big crab.
That's pretty lame!
Get that out of your mouth!
[SANJI]
Now that that's taken care of,
let's get back to our barbecue!
[LUFFY] All that crab-bashing
worked up my appetite.
[SANJI] Hey!
That isn't done cooking yet!
[LUFFY] Whatever.
Still tastes good to me!
C'mon, Boss,
I want barbecue too!
[FOXY]
Well, too bad!
We didn't come here to eat,
we came here to fight!
But don't worry.
Because soon we'll
taste victory--
Thank you for
waiting, Mademoiselle!
I hope that my barbecue
special is to your liking!
Oh! You bet!
Here you go. Help yourself!
This is positively scrumptious!
Why don't you come to
Boss' ship and be our cook?
[SANJI]
Oh no! Don't tempt me!
If you ask, I might
have to say yes!
Please, by all means.
Don't let me stop you.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL rings]
Puru-puru-puru...
[FOXY CREW C] Hello, this
is the communications room.
Hi, it's me. Boss is knocked
out, so we're done here.
Come and get us, okay?
Mhmm, mhmm...
Don't worry.
Yeah, he'll be fine.
All right then,
see you in a sec.
Bye-bye Mr. Cook.
I'll never forget
your yummy barbecue!
It touched my heart!
Take care Porche,
I'll miss you!
Are you sure you don't
wanna go back with her?
No way! You may not
appreciate good food,
but Nami and Robin deserve
nothing less than the best!
Right, Nami?
C'mon guys! Let's go!
We still need to stock up
on some emergency supplies!
[SANJI]
Wait for me, Nami-swan!
Hey, Chopper, did you
find any new herbs to use?
Mhmm... This place has
all sorts of neat stuff.
I got a good stock,
but I'm still looking in
case I missed something.
Which reminds me,
I noticed something
weird a second ago.
There's a little groove
along the trail here.
I wonder what it is.
Oh, you're right. That is weird.
Looks like a bicycle or
something came through here.
[SANJI] C'mon, that
doesn't make any sense.
There's nobody
else on the island.
Why would there
be a bicycle?
[USOPP chuckles]
Yeah, that's a good point.
[LUFFY] Hey, check it out.
We're almost through the jungle!
[LUFFY]
Well, that's a letdown...
Just looks like a whole
lotta nothing out here...
Ah!
He's excited.
Did I miss something?
[ZORO] I don't get it either.
Maybe he found some new herbs.
[LUFFY] Huh?!
Chopper, you cheater!
You were gonna hog
that big mushroom
all to yourself, weren't you?!
Get back here!
Hahaha!
Hey! What happened?
Are you okay?!
There must be
something behind that rock.
C'mon! Hurry!
[CHOPPER] Whoa!
You're not a mushroom!
[snoress]
[AOKIJI] Hmm?
A raccoon dog?
Can't you see the antlers?!
I'm a reindeer!
[LUFFY]
I saw you fall. Are you hurt?
Who the heck is that?!
[ZORO]
What's going on?
I dunno someone's here.
[AOKIJI]
Do you mind? I was sleeping.
Did you hit my friend?!
Oh man that guy is huge!
I thought we were
alone on this island!
[gasps]
[CREW] Huh?
You know him?
Hey, is this guy an enemy?
Who is he?
If Robin's freaking
out, then so am I!
Something's wrong.
Whoa, whoa, hold on.
Look, I know you're
surprised to see me,
but don't get so worked up.
It's not like I came here on
official orders or anything.
It's a nice day, so
I decided to go for a ride.
Orders, huh?
And who is it you work for?
He's a marine.
Not only that,
he's known as one
of the World Government's
Ultimate Powerhouses.
Whoa, for real?!
[ROBIN]
I'm afraid so.
This is Admiral Aokiji
from Navy Headquarters.
My, my, you've grown into quiet
the lovely lady, haven't you?
Nico Robin.
♪ ending song ♪
[LUFFY]
So this guy's a big deal?
[ROBIN]
That's right.
There are only three
officers in all of the Navy
that hold the
position of Admiral.
They call them
the World Government's
Ultimate Powerhouses.
[AOKIJI] That pretty
much sums it up.
Anyway, I've been looking for
you for a long time, Nico Robin.
[LUFFY] Stop!
You leave her alone!
On the next One Piece:
"Navy Headquarters
Admiral Aokiji!
The Ferocity of an
Ultimate Powerhouse."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!