[thinking]
Wait, that's it!
[crash]
I never thought of that!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
[NARRATOR] The final round of
the Davy Back Fight rages on.
Atop the deck of Foxy's ship,
the epic battle between the
two captains reaches a climax!
Luffy!
[LUFFY] I won't let you take
a single member of my crew...
...even if it kills me!
Straw Hat is back
on his feet yet again!
What a guy!
He may fall...
Luffy.
[ITOMIMIZU] ...but he gets
right back up every time!
[panting heavily]
Why can't you just stay down?
You'll kill yourself!
Luffy!!
[TOMIMIZU]
He's battered and bruised.
Luffy!
[ITOMIMIZU] He's tired
and out of breath.
[RANDOM FOXY A]
Don't give up!
[ITOMIMIZU] And yet
he still stands tall
with a glimmer in his eye!
All for the sake
of his friends!
Now this is a
Davy Back Fight!
I don't know what to say...
I... I'm so teary-eyed
I can't see straight!
Ya-ha-ha-ha!
Luffy!
We love you!
I'm gonna cry!
You rock!
[FOXY CREW C]
You can do it!
[CROWD]
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
[ITOMIMIZU]
The crowd has spoken!
Straw Hat has
touched our hearts!
No one has ever lasted
this long against our boss!
No one has ever
shown so much courage!
Grrrr...
You idiots! Jeez!
Don't you realize you're
cheering for the enemy?!
C'mon, Boss!
Boss!
[CROWD cheers] C'mon Boss!
C'mon Boss! C'mon Boss!
Just you wait!
I'll end this soon!
Slow-Slow Beam Sword!
You'll have to do
better than that!
Oh no! He can't dodge!
His poor legs are
too worn out to run!
It's too cruel!
I can't stand to watch!
Here let me
put you to rest!
Slow-Slow Beam!
[ITOMIMIZU] Boss
goes on the offensive!
He slowed down a
cannonball, but to what end?
Flying Foxy Fighter!
Watch out for my flying fists!
They're gonna knock you out
at the speed of a cannonball!
[ITOMIMIZU] He's using
the Flying Foxy Fighter
to finish his foe!
It may be slow now,
but once the beam wears
off, there's no escape!
Listen!
He used his beam on you a
few seconds before the ball!
Dodge as soon as
you're back to normal!
Feh-feh-feh-feh!
[LUFFY]
I can move!
[ITOMIMIZU] Oh! Straw Hat
recovers but is it too late?
Nice try but I'm too fast!
Watch out, that
thing's about to blow!
[FOXY]
Feh-feh-feh!
Here you go a parting gift.
[ITOMIMIZU]
A direct hit! Ow!
I don't think Straw Hat will
be getting up from that one!
Oh no! Luffy!
[CROWD]
Boss! Boss! Boss!
That jerk is he
trying to kill him?!
Huuuh?
[ITOMIMIZU]
He, he, he, he's back up!
But how?!
[LUFFY]
You're going down.
Is that so?!
And how do you
plan beat me
if you can't even
stand up straight?
But never mind, if
that's how you want it.
Then I'll just have
to pound your face in,
until you stay down for good!
Megaton Nine Tails...
Now, Gum-Gum...
...Rush!
...Gatling!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Such intensity!
Both fighters are unleashing
a flurry of fists at
lightning speed!
Go! Slaughter that fox!
You can do it!
So fast!
So Strong! So brutal!
Slow-Slow Beam!
[CROWD gasps in surprise]
Wait, what?
He stopped moving.
I... I think Straw Hat
is beat! No, wait!
He's on his knees,
but he's still moving!
Unlike our boss, who's standing
but strangely frozen in place!
Noooooo...
How did he?
Gah! Oh no! Boss!
[ITOMIMIZU]
It's a mirror!
A piece of a mirror has
fallen from Straw Hat's hand!
It was stuck in my afro.
I got it when
I broke the mirror.
Nooooooo...
Gum-Gum...
...Flail!
Boss, no!
Ha! Eight seconds.
Ha? Huh?
Could this be the end?!
Seven seconds.
'Til what?
Six.
Say it ain't so!
Wa-ha-ha-ha! Five!!
Hey! C'mon you guys,
don't just sit there-count
along with me! Four!
All right, we're almost at the
end--everyone together now!
Three!
Two!
One!
[CROWD]
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Aaaaaah!!!
All right!
Aaaah! He's flying!
Up goes our boss!
High into the sky!
Oh, no, Boss, come back!
[splash]
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
[ITOMIMIZU] And now,
he finally comes down
Chirp, chirp! Chirp, chirp!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Outside the battlefield!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the final round
of the Davy Back Fight
has come to an end!
After an epic battle
between captains,
our boss' legendary record
of 920 wins and 0 losses
has been broken!
[LUFFY] I won't let you take a
single member of my crew...
...even if it kills me!
[ITOMIMIZU] Let's hear
it for Straw Hat Luffy!
[CHOPPER]
He won! He did it!
Hahahaha!
[NAMI]
Stop, that tickles!
[bell ding]
Our boss really lost.
[ITOMIMIZU] We've
seen it all today, folks.
Hey! Don't just
sit there, guys!
The boss needs our
help let's do something!
[FOXY CREW G] You can
count me in--let's go!
[ITOMIMIZU] It's
the end of an era!
[RANDOM FOXY E]
Move it! Boss needs me!
[RANDOM FOXY F]
He needs me, too!
[ITOMIMIZU] The Davy Back
Giant has been toppled
and the boy with the tiny
crew and the massive afro
has seized the day
in a grand fashion!
[PORCHE screams]
[FOXY CREW]
Boss! Boss!
[construction noises]
[USOPP] You little showoff!
Who do you think you are?
Take this! And this!
Hey stop that!
He's really hurt!
You'll poke him to death!
Yeah, afro power, my butt.
That was a close call
if I've ever seen one.
Whoa, hey! Let's not
disrespect the afro, here.
[CHOPPER]
Look! He's waking up!
Where am I? What happened?
Is it over? Did I win?
That wasn't just a
dream was it? Was it?
You don't need to
freak out. You beat him.
[sighs]
What a relief.
Everyone else said
you'd lose but not me.
You're a bad liar.
Guess it would of been
a real pain if you'd lost.
Imagine being stuck on a
boat with Foxy. Screw that.
[ROBIN chuckles]
[RANDOM FOXY G]
Boss, wait!
[RANDOM FOXY H]
You gotta take it easy!
Hey Rubber Boy,
I was pretty attached to
that win streak of mine.
I'm not pleased
about you ruining it.
[FOXY CREW]
Boss, no!
I'm kidding, brother.
Let's shake.
[RANDOM FOXY I]
What a man!
[RANDOM FOXY J]
He's the best!
[RANDOM FOXY K]
You're too kind, Boss!
[chuckles]
[LUFFY]
Hmm?
Hi ya! Taste my
Shoulder Throw of Spite!
[FOXY CREW]
Oh no!
[ZORO] This guy's a
real piece of work.
[FOXY] You forget
the rules already?
C'mon You've got 500
new crewmates to choose!
He's right!
We haven't made the
final exchange yet!
Chopper! Robin!
[sobbing hysterically]
[LUFFY chuckles]
I'm so happy!
Thank you. Thank you!
Here your mask.
You can have it back now.
Straw Hat starts out
with two obvious choices.
The question is, who's next?
Don't leave us hanging!
Guess I'll take your flag!
[FOXY CREW]
What?!
You monster!
You'd strip my poor
crew of their livelihood
without a second thought?!
I don't need your sail!
You gotta use that thing
to go places, after all.
[RANDOM FOXY L]
You hear that? We're saved!
[FOXY CREW H]
That's nice and all,
but I'm afraid
it's not that easy.
We have a flag
on our sail too.
[FOXY CREW I]
We don't need your pity!
You won fair and
square, so take it!
I got a plan.
I don't actually have to
take the sail off the boat
as long as I can take
the mark off the sail
and I can do that with paint.
Once you have a new flag,
you should be fine, right?
Thank you Straw Hat.
Your kindness is...
[LUFFY]
There.
[FOXY]
Ahh...!
[FOXY CREW]
It sucks!
Aw, you guys don't
have to bow to me!
We're not!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Whoa, hold on a second!
You still have another
497 crew members to pick!
We don't need any more.
The rules are the rules!
I don't care if
you need them or not.
You're gonna pick those
crew mates right now!
Aw... Do I have to?
[FOXY] Of course you do!
Stop complaining!
Aw...
Hey Luffy, a crew follows
their captain's orders
no matter what, remember?
Yes, good point.
That makes it easy!
Easy? What is?
I got it. No problem.
Now. Let's see.
You!
Me? Really?
Yep. Everyone from you...
...to you.
Me?
[LUFFY]
How many people is that?
We have 500 total.
So excluding our Boss,
Hamburg and Porche,
that should leave us with--
Oh, that's four ninety
seven exactly.
Well, there you
go, it's settled.
Captain Luffy!
Nice! Thanks!
[fireworks blasts]
[ITOMIMIZU] Well folks, this is
Itomimizu signing off for today,
and signing on as the
Straw Hat's brand new MC!
[FOXY CREW] Three cheers
for the New Straw Hat Pirates!
[FORMER NAVIGATOR]
I hate to say this,
but no matter
how you look at it,
the Merry can't
hold this many people.
[FORMER DOCTOR]
Ah, it's no big deal.
We'll just follow
along in the Sexy Foxy
'til we work something out.
[FORMER CAPTAIN]
Good point!
[FORMER CREW chuckles]
You'll do no such thing!
The Sexy Foxy is my ship,
you miserable ingrates!
Your ship, eh?
I'd like to see the
three of them run
that huge ship by themselves.
They wouldn't last a week.
Yeah! Fat chance!
Aaahhhh...
Puh! Fat chance.
Puh-puh-puh!
Awwww!
Then go, you jerks!
Who needs you?!
[RANDOM FOXY M]
So long ex-boss!
[RANDOM FOXY N]
Don't catch a cold!
[RANDOM FOXY O] Brush
your teeth twice a day!
[RANDOM FOXY P]
Take a bath!
Hey! Rubber boy!
I'll make you pay
for this! Just wait!
[ZORO] That's supposed
to be a joke, right?
Okay! Listen, men!
It's time for your
first job as members
of the new Straw
Hat Pirate crew!
Are you guys ready?
[FOXY CREW]
Yeah!!
[RANDOM FOXY Q]
You can count on us!
[RANDOM FOXY R]
Yeah, Rubber Boss!
[LUFFY]
You're all dismissed!
Uhhh...
You mean you're
kicking us off?
[LUFFY]
Yep. You got it
[ZORO]
A captain's orders are absolute
so I don't wanna hear
anyone complaining.
[LUFFY] I don't care if you
join your old crews again
or if you go back
to Split Head,
but whatever you do,
you can't stay with me!
So long!
[RANDOM FOXY T] Come
back ex-boss! We miss you!
[RANDOM FOXY U] We belong
with the Foxy Pirates after all!
[NAMI]
Well, that worked out nicely.
[neighing]
[TONJIT]
That's right, Shelly.
It's finally over.
[neighing]
Don't be afraid, girl.
The bad guys are gone.
I know what you're thinking
but I won't ride on
stilts ever again.
We'll catch up
to the village, too.
I don't care how
many years it takes us.
Huh?
[TONJIT]
You made it back!
[LUFFY]
We brought you a souvenir.
You're hurt. Are you all right?
Oh, this? It's nothing.
Thank you for your help.
[neighing]
[NAMI] Is that why
you accepted the fight?
Because you wanted to help him?
And here I thought you were
just being stupid again.
[LUFFY]
Man, you're rude!
[rumbling]
Wha... What's happening?!
[frightened neighing]
[CHOPPER]
Guys, I don't like this!
It's huge! What is that?!
[LITTONTO] I might ask
you the same question!
Whoa, you mean
that thing can talk?!
[LITTONTO] I'm not a
thing! I'm a moooole!
"Moooole," you say?
I don't get it.
I'm the champion! You dig?
[NAMI]
Great. Another weirdo.
[SANJI]
Champion of what?!
[LITTONTO]
You really need to ask?
Obviously, I'm the world
champion of hole-digging!
As crazy as it sounds,
I'm challenging my
own record as we speak!
That's no excuse for wrecking
the old stilts guy's house!
Where's he
supposed to live?!
Huh?
[LITTONTO]
What old stilts guy?
[TONJIT] They call this
a mooole, you like him?
Listen, Littonto,
I'm about to go for the
world record in stilt-standing.
[LITTONTO]
Huh?
It won't be easy,
so I may be up
there for a few days
but at least you'll have the
moooole to keep you company.
You can manage
while I'm gone, right?
[LITTONTO] Uh-huh! I'll
wait as long as I have to
but you better come back
a champion, okay, Grandpa?
[TONJIT] You bet
I will! Don't you worry!
I promise I'll
make you proud!
It can't be.
It's really you?
Well, of course!
Grandpa!
Littonto!
[LITTONTO]
I missed you so much!
I was so lonely without you!
You turned into
a fine young man!
I'm so sorry I didn't
get to watch you grow up!
I didn't mean to worry you.
I hope you can forgive me!
[USOPP]
I didn't see that one coming.
[LITTONTO] When I thought
about how hard my grandpa
was working on
his world-record,
it inspired me to start
on a record of my own!
And suddenly,
before I knew it,
all my loneliness turned into
a passion for hole-digging!
And now you're the champ.
[LITTONTO] Yep! I'm gonna
dig through the whole world!
[LUFFY]
Hahaha!
You aim big, huh?
Just like the old stilts guy!
[TONJIT]
Yeah?
[USOPP]
That's not a compliment.
[ALL laughs]
[ROBIN] Say, couldn't you
follow one of your holes
to reach the
other villagers?
[ALL]
Huh?
[LUFFY] Looks like it
all worked out, huh?
[TONJIT] Yes,
I don't know how
to thank you for
all you've done.
[LUFFY chuckles]
Don't worry about it!
Thanks a lot, ma'am!
If you hadn't
said something,
I probably would've
been waiting
for years to see
the other villagers!
Farewell, my friends!
I won't forget you!
[TONJIT]
Again, thank you so much!
[USOPP] Take care on
your way home, old man!
[TONJIT]
You too!
Wherever you may go,
I pray for your safe journey!
That's that.
Time to head off.
Nami, is the
Log ready yet?
Sure is! We're all good to go!
All right, it's about time.
Yeah.
So... What now?
Are we gonna snag
us a shipwright?
Yeah! Just hold on, Merry!
We'll find a shipwright
to fix you up in no time!
[CREW]
Yeah!
♪ ending song ♪
[LUFFY] Ummmm, what
was I doing again?
[SANJI] Who are
these weirdoes?
[NAMI] Why am I on a ship
with a bunch of pirates?!
[CHOPPER] Who?
What? Where am I?
[ROBIN] Don't tell me
you've lost your memories!
[USOPP] Ahhh!
My head! My head!
[ROBIN]
What's wrong, Long-nose?!
[USOPP]
It itches!
[ZORO] Shut up!
Nobody cares!
[LUFFY] On the
next One Piece :
"Was it Lost?
Stolen? Who are You?"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!