[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR]
In the land of oases,
a dry cloud of sand blankets
the people with anguish.
Some cling to hope,
and others seek to destroy it.
As their paths cross,
they mark an era
in the country's history
that will forever
be overshadowed by sadness.
Despite his severe injuries,
Karoo picks up Vivi
and the two run
from the attacks of Mr. 2.
They dash through the
battlefield where the rebel
and royal armies are fighting,
on their way to Alubarna Palace.
However, Karoo is hit
by a stray bullet,
and he can go no further.
Mr. 2 closes in.
Fortunately, Sanji and the
Supersonic Duck Squadron
arrive just in time.
Meanwhile, a battle has
begun at the southeast gate,
with Chopper and Usopp
fighting on one side
and Mr. 4 and
Miss Merry Christmas
on the other.
[LUFFY]
"Sworn on a Friend's Dream!
The Battle of Molehill,
Block 4."
[USOPP yelling]
Four.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
They're over there!
How did you two
have the time to move?
You changed form.
All right, so you're
a Zoan type.
And I was thinking you
were just a normal person
all this time.
[CHOPPER]
Usopp, are you all right?
Thanks, Chopper.
You really saved me there.
Maybe he did save you this time,
but that still
doesn't change the fact
that you're gonna die today.
Mr. 4, let's get going.
Move! Here we go! Off we go!
Would you go? Come on, you slug!
She's underground again!
Usopp, we have no
choice but to keep moving.
If we stop for a second,
we're dead.
I get it.
If we stand still, then
we're just sitting ducks
for them to keep firing at.
[LASSOO sneezes]
Here they come!
[MR. 4]
Four!
[CHOPPER yells]
If I can get to that guy
and knock him down...
Just hold on!
The game isn't
going to be any fun
if we don't have a batter,
now is it?
[CHOPPER yells]
Chopper!
Whew! Well, at least
I can still do that.
Dirty mole!
[CHOPPER]
Bastard!
Damn, if they keep running away
through these mole tunnels,
even if I use a rumble ball,
I won't have enough time
to do any real damage.
Hey, where is he?
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Huh?
We're missing one of 'em!
Where'd the ugly guy
with the long nose
run off to?
Where is he? Where?
Yeah. I don't see Usopp
around anywhere.
[USOPP] What's the matter?
You guys lose something?
[USOPP]
I gotta say, mole woman,
I'm impressed that you
could dig all these
underground tunnels
in such a short time.
Good work, really!
Then again, there can
be some pretty literal
pitfalls when you
fight like this, I bet.
You should be careful.
Where are you?
Where did you go?
Wait, is he...?
[USOPP] Yep! So kind of you to
dig all these tunnels, really.
You do realize, though,
that you're not the
only one who can crawl
around inside them.
[USOPP]
Usopp...!
You sneaky little rat!
You were hiding
in one of the holes.
[USOPP]
...Pound!
[MR. 4 groans]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Mr. 4!
[USOPP growls]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
What?!
It looks like he's using
a five‐ton hammer!
How does a string bean like him
have the strength to do that?
That's a big hammer.
Who exactly is this
long‐nosed freak?
[USOPP] I am a traveler
of the world's oceans.
A crusher of notorious monsters,
beasts, and foes.
A sinker of countless ships.
A flattener of numberless towns.
Trembling with fear,
people everywhere
call me the master
of destruction! Heh heh.
I suggest that you take
the time to remember
my name carefully.
I am... Captain Usopp!
Wow! Wow! Wow! Awesome! Awesome!
Yes, yes, thank you very much.
Ah, it's nothing, really.
I'll be signing
autographs later.
[CHOPPER] I thought you
were useless up until now!
[USOPP]
Hey!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Mr. 4...
[USOPP]
He isn't moving.
Could I have really
hit him that hard?
No, it doesn't matter.
This is my chance
to beat them both.
I have to take it.
[USOPP]
Your turn, penguin!
Now you'll feel the wrath
of my five‐ton hammer!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS yells]
[USOPP]
Taste my Usopp Pound!
She escaped.
Where are you, penguin?
I told you! I'm a mole,
not a penguin, moron!
Now I see you!
Pound! Pound! Pound! Pound!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Here! Here! Here! Here!
‐‐Pound! Pound! Pound! Pound!
‐‐Here! Here! Here! Here!
[USOPP]
Rubber band of doom.
‐‐Pound! Pound! Pound! Pound!
‐‐Here! Here! Here! Here!
[USOPP] Damn, you're
everywhere, mole woman!
Ha! Hey, ya missed me,
so what's the point
of that big hammer
[inhales]
if you can't
manage to hit me?
[USOPP chuckles] Let me tell
you something, penguin.
I'm sure you've heard
by now that a good number
of your fellow
Baroque Works agents
have been eliminated by us.
But the truth is it was all me!
You did all that?
[USOPP]
And in addition to that...
I command eight thousand men!
That's awesome!
‐‐Five tons!
‐‐Awesome!
[MR. 4]
Ow...
Ah! He has to wake up now?
[CHOPPER] He survived being
hit by a five‐ton hammer?
What kind of monster is he?
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] Yeah.
He doesn't even have a bump
on his head.
He took a direct blow to the
head from a five‐ton hammer
and he's okay? Why is that?
[LASSOO sneezes]
Four?
[CHOPPER yells]
[CHOPPER]
You mean that thing was a fake?
This whole time?
Of course it was!
You think I can
really lift five tons?
I stop trying after
just 10 pounds!
This is a model I made.
It's only a couple of
frying pans tied to a stick
and covered with paper.
[USOPP gasps]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Why, you...
You tricked me with
a piece of paper?
No more mercy for you!
Mole Swimming!
Mole fish escape!
She's gone underground
into the mole tunnels again.
Watch out for
the holes, Chopper!
[USOPP]
What's she planning this time?
Where are you, mole‐thing?
Where did you go?
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS laughs]
Watch out for the holes,
did you say?
[laughs]
That won't do you any good!
Moving around underground
is just like
swimming in a pool to me.
You can't escape this time!
[laughing]
Pool?
Now this is bad.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Mole‐mole!
Usopp!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Banana!
[USOPP yells]
Mr. 4. Lassoo.
Go ahead and take care
of that reindeer man
‐‐over there, would ya?
‐‐[MR. 4] Four!
Let's show them your
Four Hundred Base Knocks!
[CHOPPER]
It's no use.
There's no way I can
handle an attack like this.
It's all or nothing now.
I have to think up
a way to beat this guy,
and quickly,
before he kills us both!
[CHOPPER]
Rumble!
Brain Point!
Scope!
[VIVI panting]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[VIVI]
Koza. Where are you?
What have you done
to our country?
[KOZA yelling]
[VIVI grunts]
[COBRA] Remember,
a country is its people.
[VIVI]
Oh, father!
Don't you have a rebellion
to stop, Princess?
[LUFFY] You want it to work
out so that nobody dies
in this fight,
isn't that right, Vivi?
You can't win like that.
[LUFFY]
People die.
[VIVI] Stop talking like that!
I won't listen to it!
[ZORO] If you truly are
the one and only hope
for preventing that tragedy,
then you must survive,
no matter what.
What happens to us isn't
the least bit important!
[KAROO squawks]
You guys, go on ahead!
We'll wait for you in Alubarna!
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
[CROCODILE]
It will be.
The demise of
this pathetic kingdom,
Miss Wednesday.
[VIVI]
I'm going to stop this,
no matter what I have to do!
Where's Chopper?
Chopper.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] You don't
have time to be worried about
someone else!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] I told
you I was done being merciful.
Now, then.
I think I'll torment you
for just a little while
longer before I finish
you off for good.
Here comes my mole banana!
[USOPP yells]
Hey, now. What are you doing?
It's poor form to go
after that spot on a guy!
Stop your whining!
You're alive, aren't you?
Mole Banana!
Banana! Banana! Banana!
[USOPP]
Perfect!
There's part of a wall there!
If I keep running at this
speed and she follows me,
she'll run into the part of
the wall that's under the sand!
And she'll crash
really hard, too!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Banana! Banana!
[USOPP] Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Now it's time to split
your head in two,
stupid penguin!
[USOPP yells]
Usopp.
[CHOPPER yells]
[MR. 4]
Four.
Usopp.
[CHOPPER] No, I can't
be worried about that.
The Rumble Ball will only
last for two more minutes.
Usopp will be fine.
It'll take more than
that to finish him.
Right now, finding the enemy's
weakness comes first.
Otherwise, we are
going to die here.
I just have to remember
what Usopp told me
back on the ship.
Right now...
I just have to do
whatever I can!
[USOPP]
Hi‐ya!
[USOPP chuckles]
[laughing]
Got crushed, huh?
Well it serves you right, you
stupid old penguin woman!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] A mole!
I'm a mole, you moron!
[USOPP screams]
Molehill Highway!
[USOPP yells]
[USOPP] What are you doing?
Let me go!
Stop it, already! This is
too dangerous to do out here!
If you're not careful,
we'll run into something!
Ahh! Like that wall
in front of you!
Look ahead! A wall, a wall!
Help! I'm too young to die!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Mole‐mole Impact!
[USOPP grunts]
[USOPP yelling]
[CHOPPER] I got it!
I see your weakness now!
[CHOPPER yelling]
[CHOPPER]
Now!
[LASSOO]
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
Usopp, can you get up?
Come on, Usopp!
Stay away from the mole
and all the holes, too!
You don't have to tell me twice!
I'm going!
[CHOPPER]
Hurry up!
What exactly are those
morons doing now?
[USOPP whines]
[USOPP, CHOPPER yell]
What's that?
And that's the
molehill's weakness.
All of the tunnels are
connected to each other
in one big network.
Oh?
Yeah?
[CHOPPER]
They're alive?
This isn't good!
My Rumble Ball's
effectiveness is already
half‐gone by now!
[USOPP whimpers]
No more.
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
No more of this!
I don't wanna die in this place!
Usopp, wait!
No way, I'm outta here!
I've had it!
There's no way
to beat these two!
Not when they're still
alive after that explosion!
Running away from
them isn't going to do
any good, don't you see?
[USOPP panting]
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] The Blue
nose is right, you know.
[USOPP yells]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS] That was
quite a little stunt you pulled!
After doing something like that,
we're not gonna just
let you run away
like nothing happened.
Oh, no! Usopp!
[USOPP yelling]
Well, I guess with a
captain who's so pathetic,
it's no surprise that the
rest of the crew's useless.
[USOPP]
Captain? Wait.
Are you‐‐
Are you talking about Luffy?
If you're talking
about the Straw Hat kid,
that idiot was killed a little
while ago by the boss.
What a shocker.
And now the rebellion has
started and is well under way.
Well. I guess you
picked the wrong people
to mess with.
She said Luffy is dead?
Don't you dare lie to us!
♪I couldn't say just how long
I've wanted to
Tell you everything
yet I could not begin to
Now, I'm here beside you
and I know
That the glimmer that I see,
is my dream revived
Kindly, your smile
is all I can see
Happiness is what
you've given me
And my heart feels so free
Glory, glory, now I shine
Because you're here with me
Wipe away these tears of mine
for they turn to bravery
What I want is to be strong
And to share this fight with you
And someday,
I know we'll get there... ♪
[CHOPPER]
Luffy's been killed?
[USOPP] Quit lying to us,
you freaky mole‐woman.
Luffy... Luffy can't be dead!
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
[SANJI] Ha! You're really
getting annoying, ballerina boy.
And your Clone‐Clone
powers aren't going to
do you any good, either.
So what if your face
changes a bit?
Come on, let's see
what you've got!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Big Opening Day Today!
The Copy‐Copy Montage!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!