He was shot two
times in the front
and another three from behind.
I have no idea what happened
in that room last night.
But whatever it was,
it was brutal.
Extra! Extra! Read all about it!
Who in the hell did this?
They're not gonna
get away with it!
[FRANKY]
Damn you, Straw Hat Luffy!
So this is your payback
for us stealing your
200 million berries?
Unforgivable!
Come on, everybody,
no need-to-be-shy!
Say my name!
Come out and show
yourself, Straw Hat!
[LUFFY]
Come on, Straw Hat,
you can't hide from me!
Stop being such a pansy!
Get out here and
fight me already!
I dunno how that weirdo
figured out my name--
I've never seen him
before in my life!
Didn't you hear what
those people said?
I think that guy
might be Franky!
Then we've found him.
[thinking] He's the one
who beat up Usopp!
[FRANKY] This money belongs
to us now. Understand?
No! Give it back!
Give it back!
[LUFFY]
If it wasn't for him...
Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Hey! Bikini Guy!
[NAMI]
Hold on a sec!
Huh?
That's me. I'm Straw Hat.
[CITIZEN A] There's
still no information?
[CITIZEN B]
What's going on?!
[KALIFA]
Everyone.
So, what's the word?
[KALIFA]
You may enter,
but try to keep your
voices down, please.
Then he... He's okay?
His injuries are still
serious but Mr. Iceberg
has finally
regained consciousness.
That's great news!
C'mon, let's see
how he's doing!
[PAULIE]
You're okay!
Mmwell, I've been
better, I suppose.
All things considered,
you're pretty lucky!
Anyway, you just
focus on getting better.
In the meantime,
you can count on us
to take care of
the shipyard, okay?
Yes, of course.
Now, I need to talk
to you about the people
who broke into my
room last night.
Uh, yeah.
Well, that's still under
investigation, I'm afraid.
[ICEBERG]
No. I remember them.
Huh?
[gasps]
There were two.
One of them was a large man
who was wearing a mask.
And the other was a woman.
Tall, with long black hair.
[ICEBERG]
I could never forget those eyes.
It has to be her.
I can't believe
what I just heard.
Mr. Iceberg's awake, everyone.
It looks like our
mayor's gonna be okay!
[CITIZEN C]
Is that true?!
[CITIZEN D]
All right!
[CITIZEN E]
I was so worried!
[CITIZEN F] I knew
he'd make it!
So you're Luffy, huh?
Didn't expect you
to look so shrimpy.
I got a bone to
pick with you, kid.
It seems you and your
gang had a little party
at my place
while I was gone.
When I came home,
now, what did I see?
My house was ripped to shreds
and my gang
was on its knees,
and it's all thanks to Luffy.
I'll make this
as plain as can be--
when you mess with my boys,
you mess with Franky.
I'd hate to
be you right now
cause I'm on one hell
of a roll this week,
and ain't nobody
gonna stop me!
Now you can cry if you like,
but either way I'm gonna
pound you so hard
even your own mother won't
recognize you when I'm done.
[NAMI]
Shut up!
Huh?
You jerk! Give us our 200
million berries back already!
You hear me?!
Huh?
You want your
money back, you say?
Well that's a damn shame,
cause I'm afraid I spent it all!
You pirates are all a
bunch of sore losers!
Don't act all high and
mighty when you probably
just stole the money
from someone else!
[LUFFY]
The money doesn't matter.
Maybe not to you,
but it does to me!
All I care about now
is getting revenge.
So money or no money,
I'm gonna make you pay!
[FRANKY] You're stealing
my lines, you bastard!
Are you trying
to make me mad?!
[LUFFY] Whatever!
Just come down here and fight!
Ah! Uh-oh!
Everybody get out of the way!
[CITIZEN H] Franky's
going on a rampage!
[CITIZEN I] Run away!
Is he holding his breath
or something? Weird.
[CROWD screams]
He just spit fire!
Yeah, I can see
that much but how?!
Oh? You scared?
Having second thoughts?
[NAMI]
Careful. If he can do that,
he might have
Devil Fruit powers!
Okay, but that
doesn't really help!
If that guy did
eat a Devil Fruit,
he wouldn't just jump in the
water for no reason, would he?
Maybe nobody told him that
if you try to swim, you die.
That'd be pretty pathetic,
but at least it would
save us the trouble
of fighting that weirdo.
Aaaaahhh!
I guess he can swim!
Lucky he didn't drown, huh?
I didn't eat no Devil Fruit!
You think I'm crazy?!
Doesn't matter to me!
Can't surprise me.
I heard about that
little power of yours.
[FRANKY]
Strong Right!
What?
Luffy!
[NAMI]
Hey! Are you okay?!
If you don't have Devil Fruit
powers, then what are you?!
Huuuh?
You poor saps don't
know anything, now do you?
All right then, I'll humor you.
I'm just a normal guy
with some extra parts.
A cyborg, you might say.
[chuckles]
One of the Straw Hats did this?
Sure about that? Of all people.
Yes. And my personal
investigation
led to the same result.
To make sure, I had Lucci
contact the government
to confirm her
identity and bounty.
Coo coo! Yes.
They said she's a
notorious criminal,
so it's no surprise that
she'd do something dastardly
to our boss, coo coo!
Then our next course
of action is crystal clear.
We gotta find those rapscallions
and show them what's what.
What in the hell
were they thinking?
Don't tell me
they're pissed off
'cause we wouldn't
fix their ship!
[KAKU]
I wonder that myself.
But regardless of what
their motivations might be,
the bottom line is that
they're the culprits
and they need to be dealt with.
[PAULIE]
In other words,
we should just capture
the Straw Hats
and interrogate them ourselves
instead of wasting time
trying to figure
this crap out.
None of this
makes sense to me
but anyone who
messes with Galley-La
is gonna have
hell to pay.
[SANJI] Stay on the lookout
for Robin, okay? Chopper?
[CHOPPER]
Uh, yeah, right.
Hey, Sanji?
[SANJI]
Hm?
[CHOPPER] Uh, this
Aqua Laguna thing,
it's gonna be
pretty crazy, huh?
Yeah. By midnight tonight,
everything here is
gonna be under water.
So do you think that
there might be somebody--
like a tourist maybe--who
doesn't know it's coming yet?
Yeah, I guess.
And that guy, if he had a
boat he wanted to take care of,
the storm would
be really bad, huh?
[CHOPPER]
Well, I mean...
You think we should--
[SANJI]
Hey, that reminds me.
You told me you
forgot something
back on the Merry, didn't you?
A medical bag or something.
[CHOPPER]
Hm?
That's what
you said, right?
[SANJI]
Better go back then, huh?
I forgot something, hurray!
We're going back to the Merry!
[manly grunting]
[TILESTONE]
Hey!!
There's trouble!!
Shut up Tilestone, you're
way the hell too loud!
You fools! You're
just as loud as he is!
Oh!! I didn't know you were up
already Mr.
Iceberg--that's great!! Hahaha!
[pow]
[TILESTONE]
Ohh!!
He may be awake,
but that doesn't mean you
should scream his ears off!
Take it down a
notch or two, okay?
I'm sorry!! I can't
help it!! I swear!!
Oh!! I almost forgot!!
I gotta tell you something!!
[PAULIE]
Fine, but stay outside.
You can tell me
from over there.
We got trouble with
that Straw Hat guy!!
I dunno what happened,
but he got in a
big fight with Franky
and they're both
wrecking up the shipyard!!
If we don't stop 'em,
who knows what they'll do!!
Straw Hat again?
Well, at least we
know where to find him.
He's got some nerve.
I'll teach that punk to
show his face on our turf!
Now you can finally have
a bit of peace and quiet.
Let them take
care of Straw Hat.
I'll be watching over
you in the meantime,
so there's no need to worry.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
[CITIZEN J] Watch out!
It's coming down!
[CITIZEN K]
They're trashing the ship!
[CITIZEN L] Stop it!
Go fight somewhere else!
Luffy! Tear him to pieces,
and then make him
put some pants on!
Hey, Bro!
You gotta put on a good show!
You're a lot tougher
than I thought you'd be.
But I'm still gonna
beat you, Bikini Guy!
If you say so!
Though it's gonna
take a long ass time
with those weenie
attacks of yours!
[FRANKY]
Weapons Left!
Gum-Gum Whip!
I can't see-- It seems
like they both got hit!
No! Look who it is!
Who just punched me?!
This is too easy.
If you knew what
was good for you,
you woulda skipped
town a long time ago.
You're in for it now!
Galley-La? Great,
that's just what I need.
All right, the guys from
Dock 1 finally made it!
Lock those losers up
and throw away the key!
Woooo!
[CROWD cheers]
[CITIZEN Q]
All right!
The foremen'll take
care of these guys!
[CITIZEN R]
That was close!
If they didn't show up,
the whole shipyard
was gonna get totaled!
Wow, lucky break!
Finally, someone can put
a stop to this nonsense!
I bet they hate Franky too!
[FRANKY] I'd butt out
of this if I were you.
Once these fists start
rockin' and rollin',
they don't discriminate
between pirates and shipwrights.
[KAKU] And that goes for
other people's property, too!
Surely you don't expect
us to stand here gobsmacked
while you wreck
our entire shipyard.
[TILESTONE] Hhhhhgh!!
I'm warning you, Franky,
if you don't pay for
these repairs in berries,
you'll pay in blood!!
[PAULIE]
All right Tilestone, calm down.
We can take care of
Franky some other time.
We've got more important
business to deal with right now.
Yeah. I'm lookin'
at you, Straw Hat.
You know exactly
what I'm talking about.
I don't know if
you're brave or stupid,
but either way, you're dead.
Wait, what?
We just came here 'cause we
heard the news about Ice Pops.
Wasn't enough
to wreck my house
and beat up my boys, huh?
What's wrong?
Don't feel like a
man unless you're
pounding the crap out
of shipwrights, too?
I know that
puberty can make you
do some really
crazy stuff, but wow.
I don't even know
what's going on,
so stop making fun of me!
Play innocent all you like.
I won't go easy on you!
Rope Action Half Knot!
I can't breathe. Can't breathe.
Air Drive!
Damn it, just, go away!
I told you shipwrights to
stay out of this, didn't I?
I'm the one who owes
this guy a beating, not you!
Coo!
Go Galley-La! Show 'em
what you're made of!
There's no way
they can beat
the top 5 shipwrights
in the city!
What? Why are the shipwrights
fighting against us too?!
Makes me itchy.
[LUFFY]
What're you doing?!
I don't have any
reason to fight you guys!
Just hold on!
Would you look at that?
He's got Devil Fruit powers.
Hey stupid, are
you even listening?
How many times do
I have to tell you bozos?!
For the last time...
[FRANKY]
Straw Hat is mine, damn it!
Hm?
Sorry Franky,
but we don't have time
for your shenanigans today!
Get the hell outta my way,
you flying monkey!
[TILESTONE] You're the one
who's in the way, Franky!!
Oh yeeeah!
[CITIZEN V]
That's our Tilestone!
He's even stronger
than usual today!
Coo coo! Coo coolookoo!
Coo coo! Coo coo!
Hey, stop it!
Damn, you guys are strong.
But I still don't
know why we're fighting!
[PAULIE] Straw Hat,
I think we're the ones
who deserve an
explanation here, not you.
Someone broke into
Iceberg's house last night.
Shot him twice in the front
and three times in the
back before they left.
They were from your crew!
That can't be! None
of us would do that!
[thinking] I'm never
gonna settle this, am I?
[thinking]
That was Nico Robin.
There's not a single
doubt in my mind.
But was that masked man one
of the Straw Hats as well?
And why did they attack
me in the first place?
Surely it wasn't
about their ship.
No. They must've been
aiming to steal something.
But seeing as they
left empty handed,
I have a good idea what
they were looking for.
The question is if they're
working with the government
or if they want
it for themselves.
Straw Hat Luffy.
[REPORTER A] This just in!
Breaking news!
Iceberg has already
identified the culprits
from the break-in last night!
[REPORTER B] What?!
Is that true?!
Spread the word
through the city
and we'll capture
them ourselves!
We can't let those
criminals leave Water 7!
[CITIZEN W]
Who did it?!
[REPORTER A]
Show no mercy
to the monsters who
attacked our mayor!
[REPORTER A]
Capture the Straw Hat Pirates
no matter what it takes!
♪ ending song ♪
[PAULIE] I'll never forgive
what you did to Iceberg!
[LUFFY] How many times
do I have to tell you,
that wasn't us!
[FRANKY] Hey! Stop
ignoring me, damn it!
[LUFFY] We'll just have to
talk to Ice Pops in person.
[PAULIE]
Yeah right!
[FRANKY]
Nobody's going anywhere
'til I settle
things with Straw Hat!
[PAULIE]
Nobody cares, Franky!
Don't make me
beat up both of you!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece :
"The Straw Hat Pirates
are the Culprits?
The Protectors of
the City of Water."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!