[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Unable to save Ace's
life during the War of the Best,
the injured Luffy was
taken to Amazon Lily,
where he fell into despair.
But this is a story from ten
years ago, in the East Blue,
when Ace, Luffy,
and their friend Sabo
made a promise to each other
that they would become pirates.
Sabo, whose parents are
members of the nobility,
was kidnapped by his father
and forced back to High Town,
while his friends in
Gray Terminal could only watch.
I'll do whatever
you want me to, okay?
I'll live whatever
life you've mapped out.
Just please, I'm begging you,
don't hurt my friends!
They've done nothing wrong.
I can't stand this.
Those two are my brothers.
[gasps]
[NOBLE F] It's important that
we all keep our mouths shut.
Think, what would happen if
someone outside of High Town
found out about the plan?
[SABO gasping]
[NOBLE F]
You and I are special!
We come from
great noble families.
[SABO screams]
Luffy! Ace! Get away!
[LUFFY] "The Fire Has Been Set!
The Gray Terminal in Crisis!"
Hold on!
Wait a minute, kid!
[NOBLE E]
Of course I know about the fire.
Why? What's wrong?
Did they cancel it?
[NOBLE SOLDIER A] Bluejam
and his men have been placing
explosives all over Gray
Terminal, just like we asked.
[SABO grunts]
[NOBLE A yelps]
[SABO groans]
Oh, my, are you all right?
[SABO]
Outta my way!
[CITIZENS gasp]
[SABO grunting]
I have to tell them!
[SABO groans]
Boy, where are your parents?
Learn some manners!
There's no time! [gasps]
[COP A]
Settle down, kid!
[COP B]
Yeah, just relax!
Ace! Luffy!
[ACE]
Huh?
We're burning down
Gray Terminal?
But why the hell would
you wanna do that?
[BLUEJAM]
Not so loud!
We gotta keep quiet about this.
If anyone finds out,
it won't work.
You really are a meanie,
I knew we shouldn't
have trusted you!
We gotta hurry and tell
everyone we can, Ace!
I told you to keep quiet.
Hey. Shut 'em up.
[LUFFY, ACE grunting]
[BLUEJAM] I'm just following
orders, same as you.
[ACE gasps]
[BLUEJAM]
In case you didn't guess,
all those boxes you've
been lugging around
are filled with explosives.
You get it?
Nothing will survive
that fire and no one.
[LUFFY gasps]
But...
Bluejam, don't do it!
[laughs] Since when
did you brats
start giving a damn
about other people?
Well, now that you know
about the grand plan,
you're stuck here.
We can't risk letting you go.
Sorry.
Actually, there's something I've
been meaning to ask you boys.
Heh. So, tell me.
Is it true that you brats
are hiding treasure
somewhere around here?
[LUFFY, ACE grunting]
[SABO'S DAD] You've crossed
me for the last time!
[SABO grunting]
Sabo! You've caused us
nothing but disgrace!
From now on, I'm through
with your antics!
I was right to adopt
another child!
[gasps]
[SABO]
Open up, Dad!
Please, I gotta go warn them!
Everyone in Gray Terminal
is going to die!
Please, Dad, let me out!
This is serious!
[SABO crying]
It's no use.
[DOG barking]
Stupid dog! Huh?
Hey, wait. What's that?
[MAN B, MAN C]
Huh?
Something weird is
happening in Gray Terminal.
That looks like fire.
[MAN R laughs] Who knew the plan
would turn out to be this fun?
[DOGRA]
Hey, boss!
Come quick! Ya gotta see this!
All right, what's the big deal?
It's the sky! Look!
Is that the town?
[BANDIT C]
No, it's closer than that!
I think it's Gray Terminal!
It's on fire!
[DADAN gasps]
[MAN S]
What's going on?
Where's that smoke coming from?
[WOMAN A] Gray Terminal
has never caught fire before.
What happened?
[NOBLE SOLDIER A]
Edge Town is too dangerous,
evacuate immediately!
[NOBLE SOLDIER B] All residents,
please head downtown!
[NOBLE SOLDIER C]
Stay here, where it's safe.
We'll take care of the fire
and other citizens!
[MEN panting]
[MAN E]
The Great Gate!
[MAN D]
We finally made it!
[MAN E groans]
Hey! Wh-What are you doing?
[NOBLE SOLDIER D] We only
protect the residents inside!
You're kidding!
Why are you doing this?
[MEN gasp]
This is insane!
Let us in, dammit!
Help us, we're begging you!
[grunts, gasps]
Everybody, get up!
We gotta escape!
[MAN J gasps]
The fire almost
has us surrounded!
Where did this mess
even come from?
Look, it's no use, man!
Leave it behind
and make a run for it!
[BOTH panting]
[MAN N] Crap! The fire's
already gotten to the shore!
[MAN O] The entrance
to the forest is burning, too!
[screams] We're all gonna
die! Where do we go?
[BLUEJAM PIRATES laughing]
[BLUEJAM] Say so long
to this dump, fellas!
Good riddance! [laughs]
It'll be easy living
from here on out!
Yeah, just like the nobles. Heh.
'Course not.
We couldn't care less
about the living garbage
stinking up Gray Terminal,
but it makes a good hideout.
The place is huge, plus no
law around to bug us, get it?
[KING]
I'm aware of that,
but think, if you
do this for me,
well, you won't need a hideout.
I have the authority to make you
and your crew bona fide nobles.
[ALL gasp]
Really? You'd do that for us?
[BLUEJAM]
Once this is through,
the king of Goa
will give us titles!
We'll live in
High Town as nobles!
No more of this trash heap!
[laughing]
Now, let's move.
We're almost done
and don't worry.
On to the Great Gate!
The military is waiting for us!
[BLUEJAM PIRATE E]
Captain, we left those
two brats in the hideout.
[BLUEJAM]
Forget 'em.
They had their chance to join up
when I asked them where their
treasure was, but they blew it.
[BLUEJAM] Fools like them
aren't gonna live long, anyway.
[ACE grunting]
[BLUEJAM PIRATE F]
Captain!
The gate is already closed!
[BLUEJAM]
It's nothing.
They just don't want
other people to break in
and cause a riot.
I'm supposed to give them
a sign once we're here,
then they'll open it up.
It's me, Bluejam. We're here.
Huh?
Hey! Open the damn gate!
Captain?
You don't... think...
Hey! Come on!
What the hell are you doing?
This isn't funny! Open the gate!
We made a deal!
You're supposed to let us
evacuate from this pit!
Quit screwing around
and let us in!
You bunch of bastards!
The king made me a promise!
If we burned down the terminal,
he'd make us nobles!
Don't tell me he--
[gasps] The king set us up!
That liar! Dammit!
[CITIZEN A]
Did you hear?
They found out
who started the fire.
It was some pirate named
Bluejam from Gray Terminal.
[CITIZEN B]
How despicable!
A criminal turning
on his own men!
I bet he was trying to keep
the World Government's
observers away
so he could keep on
terrorizing people.
Gosh, what an evil pirate!
[ACE panting]
[LUFFY crying]
It's way too hot, Ace!
I think I'm gonna melt!
The hell you are!
Damn! Why did Bluejam
rope us into this mess?
[LUFFY yelling] We can't get
away! I don't wanna die!
If you don't stop complaining,
I'll kill you!
[LUFFY]
It's not that hot.
[ACE, LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY] Whoa, I'm burning!
I mean this isn't so bad!
[ACE]
It's all over the place!
[coughs] I can barely breathe.
I mean, I'm cool!
The fire will kill us all!
We're gonna be fine.
Don't worry!
We'll live, somehow.
[SABO'S DAD]
Someone call the police!
Sabo did it again!
[SABO'S MOM]
Hello, police?
Anyone? Hello?
[SABO panting]
[NOBLE SOLDIER E]
Hey, are you nuts?
You're going the wrong way!
--[NOBLE SOLDIERS gasp]
--[SABO grunts]
[SABO]
Open the gate, now!
[NOBLE SOLDIER H]
What are you talking about?
[NOBLE SOLDIER H grunting]
Dumb brat!
Go home!
[NOBLE SOLDIER I yelps]
Luffy! Ace! Run!
[SABO groaning]
[NOBLE SOLDIER J]
Let go, brat!
Stay away from the lock!
Open the gate! [groans]
Stop!
No!
[SABO yells]
[NOBLE SOLDIER L]
Why don'tcha be a good kid
and get outta here!
[NOBLE SOLDIER M]
Don't give us any more trouble!
[SABO groaning]
[SABO]
I'm sorry, guys.
[DRAGON]
What happened to you, boy?
[SABO groaning]
[SABO]
Who's there?
Whoever you are, listen,
the nobles are the
ones behind this fire.
[SABO]
You gotta believe me!
[SABO] High Town reeks worse
than Gray Terminal ever did.
The people act civilized, but on
the inside, they're all rotten!
They only care about making
themselves look good,
no matter what it takes!
I can't stay here.
If I do, then
I'll never be free!
I'm ashamed of being born noble!
I hate myself!
[DRAGON]
Goa Kingdom,
look what you've
done to this child,
how you've turned
him against you.
[DRAGON]
I know how you feel.
I was born in this country, too.
[DRAGON] But I alone do not have
the power to change this world,
and maybe I never will.
But at least...
At least you're actually
listening to me, aren't you?
[DRAGON] Of course I am,
and I'll never forget.
[ACE, LUFFY panting]
Keep running, Luffy! Don't stop!
[LUFFY panting]
It... can't be!
Do something!
[BLUEJAM PIRATE G]
It's all over, isn't it?
[BLUEJAM PIRATE H] It's too late
to put out the fire, Captain!
We gotta abandon the ship!
The sea is blocked off anyway!
Damn the king!
That filthy cheat thinks
he can get away with this?
Just you wait. You're dead!
[KING] Must Gray Terminal
be an assault to my senses,
even in its final moments?
That light is far too bright!
[SERVANT A]
We are sorry, your majesty.
Please allow us
to close the curtains.
[NOBLE D chuckles]
[GIRL NOBLE A]
Say, Papa,
how come we wanna burn
everybody in Gray Terminal?
Aren't they people
too, just like us?
Not exactly.
They chose to live
meaningless lives.
Just think about it.
If they had chosen the
path of high-class nobility
like you and me,
they wouldn't be in this mess.
They wouldn't?
[gasps]
I get it!
You mean it's their fault for
being born all poor and dumb!
[chuckles] How silly!
[NOBLE D]
Yes.
Now enough about those people.
You need to get some
studying done before bedtime.
[NOBLE GIRL A]
M'kay!
[NOBLE D]
See you tomorrow.
Hmm.
It's blocked off here, too!
[MAN T] Damn it,
we just keep losing ground!
[MAN U]
I don't wanna die like this!
[ACE, LUFFY panting]
[ACE yells]
[LUFFY] Do you think all
those old guys got away safe?
Who cares about them?
We're in trouble!
[ACE coughs]
Crap! I can't tell.
Where are we?
[BLUEJAM] Who said you two
brats were allowed to escape?
[ACE, LUFFY gasping]
[LUFFY]
Bluejam!
[gasps]
[ACE]
How come you're still here?
I thought you were escaping
after the fire got lit!
Did something happen?
Shut up, ya punk!
It's hopeless.
You do know that, right?
There's a sort
of irony to this.
[BLUEJAM chuckles]
It's a new perspective.
Humans are strange
creatures. [chuckles]
I hit rock bottom and all
I can do is laugh about it.
[BLUEJAM chuckles]
[BLUEJAM PIRATES laughing]
They're acting really weird.
It's creepy.
Luffy! Run for it!
Grab 'em!
[ACE, LUFFY panting, gasp]
[BLUEJAM PIRATES chuckling]
[BLUEJAM]
Where do you think you're going?
We did this job together.
That means we get
to die together!
We're not gonna die
with you losers!
We don't give up that easy!
Is that so?
Actually, you still
haven't told me
where you're hiding
that treasure.
Friends don't keep
secrets from each other.
I'll save it for you before
the fire reaches it.
All you have to do
is tell me where it is.
Your life is in danger and
all you care about is treasure?
[BLUEJAM]
Well, if you don't want it,
then you might
as well tell me, right?
Dammit, you've gone nuts.
[BLUEJAM] I'm just trying
to stop another tragedy.
I already saw my ship
reduced to charcoal.
It'd be a shame if that
happened to your treasure, too.
All your hard work,
and for nothing.
You suck! Get your own treasure!
All right. You win.
[LUFFY gasps]
No!
You spent forever
collecting that!
What would Sabo think?
[ACE]
Shut up!
Sabo would understand!
[LUFFY gasps]
[ACE] The treasure
isn't important anymore.
The only thing that matters
is getting out of here alive.
[ACE grunts]
[BLUEJAM grunts]
Ace.
[ACE]
Six years.
We've collected
treasure for six years
and hid it in this tree.
[BLUEJAM]
Why, thank you.
[ACE]
Don't cry!
It's okay, Luffy.
This won't be the end.
[ACE, LUFFY grunt]
[ACE]
What are you doing?
I told you where
it is, now let us go!
I'm sorry. I don't
think I trust you.
Now then, about that treasure.
Let's go. You can lead.
You moron!
That won't leave us
time to escape,
and I'm not dying here! Just go!
You've got the damn map!
[ACE grunts]
[BLUEJAM]
Listen, kid.
Don't you dare piss me off.
I'm not above stealing
from children,
or murdering them.
I'll have my revenge.
And believe me,
those nobles will regret
the day they crossed Bluejam.
And to think, you call
one of them your brother.
They act like a little
money and influence
makes them a gift to
the rest of the world,
like it gives them the
right to look down on us
like we're trash!
Shut up! Sabo isn't
like that! Take it back!
Yes, he is! Face it!
Sure, you stayed together,
but he was looking down
on you the whole time!
Liar!
[BLUEJAM]
His parents are loaded.
He doesn't have
any of the problems
that you or I deal with!
He used you idiots
to get some kicks.
He was just bored.
Then got a taste of real life
and he ran back home
to his rich daddy!
That's enough!
Sabo is our brother!
He's right! Sabo just
wants to be free!
[BLUEJAM PIRATE D groans]
[BLUEJAM PIRATE D growls]
[ACE]
Luffy!
[LUFFY yelps]
[ACE gasps]
Say goodbye, kid!
[BLUEJAM chuckles]
[LUFFY groaning]
Just let me go!
[LUFFY yelling]
[BLUEJAM PIRATE D yells]
Get the hell away from Luffy!
[BLUEJAM gasping]
Hey! Talk to me!
[ACE grunts]
What the hell did you do?
[ACE groans]
Ow.
You screwed up big time, brat!
Go on.
Try that crap again
before I kill you.
Get off of me, you scumbag!
[BLUEJAM]
Time's up!
Ace! No!
Don't do it!
[gunshot]
[NARRATOR] Even as the
fires in Gray Terminal
threaten to consume them,
Ace and Luffy fight Bluejam
with all their might.
In the wake of the tragedy,
Sabo decides to seize freedom in
his hands and takes to the sea,
as a Celestial Dragon
arrives in High Town.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Where Can Freedom be Found?
A Sad Depature of a Boy!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!