[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[LUFFY]
"The First Patient!
The Untold Story Of
the Rumble Ball!"
[ALL snoring]
[NAMI sneezes]
[yawns]
[gasps]
[ALL snoring]
Can't breathe!
Eyelash!
Stop!
[ALL snoring]
[NAMI]
C'mon, you guys! Wake up!
Wake up!
Nami.
Morning.
How about a passionate
good‐morning kiss?
You bastard!
Your disgusting face
nearly scared me half to death!
I scared you?
What the hell do ya
think you're do‐‐
[NAMI]
There's an island up ahead!
Guys! Did you hear me?
Island?
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY laughs]
An island? Where?
Over there!
[LUFFY gasps]
Whoa!
This island looks like
it should be full of
big, strong, crazy monsters!
Ow, my nose still
isn't working right!
Look what you did!
It could be permanently broken!
Nothing here feels
out of the ordinary.
Appears to be a small island.
[SANJI]
Look, Nami!
Fruits like this are perfect for
replenishing our food supply!
And judging from this crop,
there's no shortage of goodies!
Wow.
We should find as many as we
can and load 'em on the ship.
I bet there are plenty
of plants and vegetables
we can use for food, too!
With all it has to offer,
this little island seems
like a cook's paradise!
Okay, then. It'll be
your job to look for anything
we can use as a source of food!
As for the rest of you, here!
Huh?
What's that?
Draw lots?
It's simple! The three
who draw the shortest lots
will spend all day
collecting this fruit.
And whoever draws
the longest lot
will have the duty of staying
here to protect the ship.
And just who made you captain?
Why do you get to
give all the orders?
Back off.
I may not be the captain,
but who else is gonna do it?
Look! All of 'em
are kinda short.
Why'd ya draw three?
You're only
supposed to take one!
I thought the person who
grabs the most is the winner.
I don't think
further explanation
on this subject
is necessary, do you?
[ZORO, CHOPPER, USOPP]
Not at all.
[laughs]
I know. Am I great or what?
[ZORO, USOPP]
You idiot!
[LUFFY yells]
I drew the long one, so...
I stay and watch the ship?
That's right! Just make sure to
keep her in one piece, okay?
Hurry up! Hurry up! Let's go!
There's lots of fruit
waiting to be picked!
You're coming
with us, Nami. Right?
No, thanks.
While you guys are
gathering supplies,
I'm gonna spend the day
measuring the island
so I'll be able to
add it to our sea charts.
Now let's get to work!
Be careful!
See ya guys later!
Have a good one!
You, too!
Look after the ship!
The one who collects
the most fruit is the winner!
Ugh. Can't wait.
Gonna be a long day.
All right! It's time!
♪ Measuring, measuring!
Oh! How lively Nami is
when she's taking measurements!
The tools on her back
glistening in the sunlight!
Nami, wait for me!
[ZORO] Stop acting stupid
and catch up already!
[giggles]
I'm all alone today.
The ship looks really big,
especially when no one's around.
[CHOPPER grunts]
Ha! Listen up, guys!
Today I am in charge
of the Going Merry!
That's Captain Chopper to you!
And remember! I'm the law!
Luffy! Don't eat food
that doesn't belong to you!
Usopp! You need to
work harder! And no excuses!
Sanji! Prepare special dishes
to satisfy my every craving!
Hail me!
Hurray! Hurray!
[yells]
[screams, groans]
[CHOPPER gasps]
How long have you been
sitting there, huh?
Being so quiet‐‐very sneaky!
You‐‐You spy!
I still don't trust you!
I see what you're doing
and I'm not fooled for a second!
You were a Baroque Works
Officer Agent.
You've been nothing but a
selfish rogue all your life.
Mean and stupid!
I won't accept you as a crewman,
not even if Luffy himself
vouched for you!
Monster!
I'm not afraid of you
so stay away from me!
[CHOPPER pants]
[CHOPPER] Her special skill
is assassination, right?
I hear she's also very smart.
Need to be careful.
[gasps] That's right!
I almost forgot!
Before I went to bed last night,
I made ten Rumble Balls!
I'll spend the rest
of the day making more‐‐
quietly, safe and sound!
Good 'ol Rumble Balls.
I have to make them
whenever I can
since there's no telling when
we might run into enemies!
[CHOPPER sighs]
But still. Ha, ha, ha.
This takes me back... to when
I made my first Rumble Ball.
[CHOPPER] I don't think
Doctorine will notice
if these get reduced
little by little.
She always mixes a little bit
of this and this, right?
Or was it this one?
She didn't put
this one in, did she?
[KUREHA]
Chopper!
Do you know where my
medicine bottles are?
[gasps]
[KUREHA] They have
important ingredients in them.
They're very rare
and valuable medicines.
I'd better not find that you've
been playing with them.
Do you hear me?
[CHOPPER gasps]
[KUREHA]
Chopper!
[CHOPPER yelling]
Back then I received
a good scolding from Doctorine
that I'll never forget.
I wonder how Doctorine is
getting along these days.
I think I'll write her a letter.
[CHOPPER sniffs]
Huh?
So, they're called
Rumble Balls, right?
[screams]
[CHOPPER]
You're trying to uncover
the secret of the
Rumble Ball, aren't you?
And once you get it,
you're going to assassinate me!
But that's not gonna happen!
I won't be taken down
by a snake like you!
[CHOPPER screams]
Rumble!
[CHOPPER]
Guard Point!
And now Heavy Point!
[CHOPPER yells]
[CHOPPER]
Jumping Point!
[CHOPPER gasps, groans]
Horn Point!
See the power of
the Rumble Ball!
You are no match
for the Rumble Ball!
It can give me the ability
to find your weak point!
Brain Point.
Wide Scope!
[CHOPPER]
Weak point, weak point!
Where's her weak point?
[ROBIN laughs]
Hey, what do you find so funny?
Look, there's no need
to be afraid.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Hey! Stop it!
Stop it! Stop tickling me!
[laughing]
Aren't you just
the cutest furball.
I do like you.
Cu‐Cutest?
[yelps] Give me a break!
I'm not falling
for your flattery!
Think by making me happy it'll
throw me off guard or something?
C'mon, do I look happy to you?
Can't fool me!
I gotcha! I'm in!
I'm wise to your game...
[ROBIN]
Well then, shall we go?
Don't we need to refill
the water you just wasted?
[CHOPPER]
Uh...
[ROBIN]
I like to drink a cup of coffee
on deck while reading.
‐‐[door opens]
‐‐[CHOPPER grunts]
[ROBIN]
What's the matter?
It's only fair that
you go draw the water
since you're the one who
spilt it in the first place.
[CHOPPER]
Yes.
[USOPP]
Jeez.
How could I even
contemplate working
on such a beautiful
day like this?
[yawns]
Whoa! Lots of monkeys!
[gibbering]
[whooping]
[laughs]
[yells, groans]
[gasps, groans]
He got me!
My life flashed before my eyes.
I thought that was it...
...the end of Captain Usopp!
No more adventures!
I didn't get a good look
at what attacked me,
but it must've been
a huge condor!
Why me?
Because I had to
fight for my life,
I couldn't gather
a single piece of fruit!
Oh, well.
That's okay.
No need for anyone
to worry about me.
I'm dead.
[ZORO] I wish somebody would
give me a good explanation
why I have to take orders
from that woman!
Seriously, she's gonna
drive me insane!
Three‐Sword Style...
...Dragon Twister!
[groaning]
Where's the contour line?
That's it!
[NAMI] The right ridgeline
is right around 42 degrees.
What a coincidence!
If you measured my love for you
it would be exactly
42 degrees Celsius!
Move it!
‐‐[SANJI] Ow!
‐‐Moron!
[footsteps]
[CHOPPER] I'm the one who's
gotta fetch the water.
Why is she tagging along?
[ROBIN]
What a nice day!
What?! [screams]
You scared me to death!
What's wrong?!
Nothing.
Just commenting...
on the beautiful day.
I've been longing to
take a walk like this.
I haven't felt such peace
for quite some time.
[ROBIN hums]
In the past, it seemed like
I was always wound too tight
from repressing my emotions.
I never got the chance to smile.
Huh?
Fresh water!
So, um, if I remember
the story correctly,
didn't you say you've been alone
since you were eight or so?
That's right.
I spent most of my youth
following pirates
and I barely survived.
It's your turn.
Tell me about this
Doctorine person.
[CHOPPER gasps]
You were talking
about her earlier.
She's a doctor, right?
She's your teacher.
A mentor perhaps?
Uh, yeah, kinda.
Doctorine is someone
I owe a great debt to.
Most people refer
to her as Dr. Kureha.
[ROBIN]
Dr. Kureha.
What is she like?
[CHOPPER]
She really loves alcohol,
but the best way to
describe her is a woman
who's like a pirate,
who's also a doctor.
Did I mention she
really loves alcohol?
[CHOPPER] I studied under
Doctorine for about six years.
I wanted to be a doctor
myself, you know.
That was my passion.
"After mixing these three
types of herbs together
in a large bowl,
grind them well."
[KUREHA]
Chopper. Chopper!
[CHOPPER yelps]
[KUREHA] Are you finished
with your reading?
I expect all
500 pages memorized.
[CHOPPER panting]
Ha! You were playing around
with my medicines again.
[CHOPPER]
No! I was experimenting!
[KUREHA]
That's the same as playing.
B‐But I...
No excuses!
But‐‐I've been studying for
three years now, Dr. Kureha!
I've read and re‐read over 200
medical books and journals.
Please let me help
prepare the medicine!
You're about a hundred
years from that!
[CHOPPER screams]
I‐I've memorized every single
word that I've ever read!
It's true! I swear it!
I even managed to memorize
The Seventh Principle
by Dr. Alexandra,
cover‐to‐cover!
That's the one you said
was the most difficult book
you ever read!
"The TaboTabo bacteria
start dividing
on the seventh day of culturing,
after showing signs
of overreaction
mentioned on page 1,254,
chapter seven, section two."
[KUREHA grunts]
So, what... does...
[CHOPPER gasps]
[KUREHA groans]
Doctorine!
You okay?
It seems I've been infected
with the febrile disease
from the patient
I saw the other day.
You're burning up!
Chopper.
Anyone can memorize words,
but now you must put what
you've learned to the test.
I guess this will make me
your very first patient.
[gasps]
I won't give you
a single word of advice.
You're on your own.
If you fail, I'll die.
No pressure.
Learn the ultimate lesson.
Once you decide to
practice medicine,
you take the responsibility
of your patients' lives
in your hooves.
Can a blue‐nose reindeer
master such a burden?
[KUREHA chuckles]
[CHOPPER gasps]
There's no mistake!
This is the pathogen
of the Mondolin Virus.
What would work best
to counteract it?
Found it!
Doctorine...
[CHOPPER]
...don't die.
Please!
Let's see.
Dr. Kureha,
aren't ya gonna ask what sort
of ingredients I combined?
Most patients will have
little knowledge of medicine,
or what is used to compound it.
They simply trust
their doctor's judgment
and abide by whatever
prescription he gives them.
All right.
Do you feel a little better?
Dummy. No medicine
works instantaneously.
Go. I need to sleep for awhile.
[KUREHA]
Chopper!
[gasps]
[KUREHA]
Not a bad job,
considering your
lack of experience.
[CHOPPER] That was the
first time that Doctorine
truly praised my
aptitude in medicine.
And it was the only time
throughout the six years
I worked under her.
Instead of giving me
verbal acknowledgments,
she proved her faith in me by
placing her life in my hands.
That's Doctorine for ya.
She believes in
actions, not words.
And I agree with her.
Someday I'll become
a great doctor,
one that'll surprise even her.
Oh, no! I think I said too much!
[gasps] Hey!
[ROBIN]
The sun will be setting soon.
We should go.
I wish I had someone in my life
who I had a strong
connection with...
...just like you do.
[CHOPPER]
This is really... heavy!
[CHOPPER grunts]
Go on.
Explain to me why you
weren't able to gather
so much as a single
piece of fruit!
That's a good question.
What's your answer?
Look, I thought
I was being attacked...
...by a huge condor who was
trying to claw my face off!
[yells]
Sorry I failed you!
I tried my best! I really did!
But I guess, in the end,
it wasn't good enough!
And now I'm dead!
[groans]
I have to hand it to you, Zoro.
You did an impressive job today!
[ZORO grunts]
So impressive
that you should just
keep working the
rest of the night!
Ahh!
How lovable Nami is, even when
she's yelling at everyone!
Oh, shut up!
You're a moron!
You want some of me, Moss Head?
[NAMI]
You two calm down.
[BOTH laughing]
[laughing]
Oh, I can't remember
the last time
we had a nice, peaceful
day like this!
Hey, Chopper!
Was it tough being alone
all day on the ship?
Kinda.
It was a chore.
But, way more fun than
I've had in a long time!
Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!
[NAMI]
Sanji, do me a favor!
There's something I want
you to buy for me, okay?
[SANJI]
Anything for you.
But, these papers cost
4.8 million Berries!
We don't have
enough money. Sorry.
[LUFFY]
We can afford it.
[NAMI] That's right!
We have plenty of money.
[SANJI] True. The bounty
for this guy's worth a fortune!
[LUFFY]
What?!
On the next One Piece!
"Uprising of the Navigator!
For the Unyielding Dream!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!