Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[PERONA] Hey, Kumacy? Kumacy!
The Risky Brothers
should be delivering
the coffin as we speak.
Pick it up from them
and take it straight to our
Master over at the Dance Hall.
Got it?
Did you hear me?
Don't just stare.
[KUMACY] Yes.
Ugh, that's gross!
I told you not to talk!
I'm heading to the
Straw Hat's ship to clean out
their treasure collection
while they're busy
with all the zombies.
Let me know if
anything strange happens.
Okeydoke?
[chuckles] There you go!
You're much cuter when you
keep that ugly mouth shut.
[KUMACY] Take care out there.
[PERONA] Hey! Did you
just mumble something at me?
[FRANKY] I bet that
old guy was right
and Moria's been watching
us this whole time.
We gotta keep our
eyes peeled for traps,
or we'll end up like our cook.
We're already
missing half our crew.
Wouldn't surprise me if Moria
was trying to split us up.
[OINKCHUCK chuckles]
Probably just
Sanji's fault.
He is pretty dumb.
Still, can't believe we found
one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea out here.
My question is:
What're we gonna do if one
of our shadows gets stolen.
Now that would be interesting.
Well, don't look at me.
I'm not squealing.
I know I promised that
old guy I'd beat up Moria,
but maybe that should
be second on the list.
Gotta look out
for my crew first.
Hahaha! I can't tell you
where your friends are,
but wherever it is, they're
in for a world of pain.
But I wouldn't
worry about them--
you're not much
better off yourself.
You'll see.
Okay, Wall Pig,
you're gonna stop oinking
and start guiding us.
Got it?
[CHOPPER] Are you okay?
Behind you!
Chopper! Look out!
No! Chopper!
Perhaps you should worry less
about your friends and
a bit more about yourself.
[DOGGUIN] Don't you dare!
[ZOMBIE BULLDOG] Hey stupid!
Who's side are you on, anyway?
[ZOMBIE RAM] I know you're new
here, but that girl's a pirate!
Kick her ass!
[DOGGUIN] I don't
care who this lady is
or where she came from.
I don't even care if I have
to disobey our Master's orders.
'Cause even if it kills me,
I'll never kick a woman!
Stupid pig!
Just tell us where you hid
our friends already! C'mon!
Like I said before.
Ask all you like--
I don't know a thing!
When we get our cook back,
we're making bacon out of you.
Perhaps, they were strangled
and so they can't
call out for help.
No more predictions out of you!
They're way too depressing!
[LUFFY] Hey, wait a second.
When did we last see Zoro?
[LUFFY]
"The Vanishing Straw Hat Crew!
A Mysterious Swordsman Appears!"
I don't like this.
I wonder what could
have happened to them.
It's certainly strange.
[FRANKY] There's nowhere
for them to go!
They were walking
right next to us!
[ROBIN] Perhaps ghosts
had something to do with it.
[ROBIN] I hope they
didn't lose any limbs.
[FRANKY] Dammit!
Stop with all that creepy-talk
and start thinking
about how we can find
those guys and save 'em!
[clanking noises]
[crash]
[LUFFY] Zoro! Sanji!
Man! Where did they go?
This is no time
to screw around!
What's wrong with you?
[LUFFY] Hey!
Everybody knows if
there's armor laying around,
you gotta put it on and wear it!
It's like fulfilling
a man's dream!
Wha--? Oh, wow.
That's a good point!
[LUFFY] Don't tell me when
you made a body out of iron,
you gave yourself a cold,
iron heart, too!
I'm sorry! You're right!
Even if I have fists of iron,
that's no replacement for a
heart that's full of dreams!
[LUFFY] Yeah! Song time!
Realizing I've lost
something so precious
has blown a cold wind through
the rusty cracks of my heart.
I call this one Steel
Cyborg Traveler Blues.
I think you've forgot
the situation here.
[ROBIN] Hey.
[ROBIN] There's a
large hall up ahead.
[LUFFY] Really?
[gasps]
Hahahahaha!
I see. That's what this is.
[LUFFY] Robin! Are Usopp
and the others here?
No. But take
a look at this room.
We should be outside
once we pass through here.
[LUFFY] Whoa!
What is this place?
[FRANKY] Looks like
some kind of arena.
It's actually a lot more
complicated than that.
Oh, but don't worry
about the details.
You'll find out soon enough,
since you've conveniently
walked right into our trap!
[LUFFY] Franky!
Who is that?
Oh! A haunted suit of armor!
It must be a zombie.
It has spears piercing its body,
but it's still moving around.
[FRANKY] So now the zombies
are arming themselves?
Great. 'Cause this
wasn't bad enough!
Strong Right!
Right through the wall!
[FRANKY] So what if
you can use a sword!
[FRANKY] Weapons Left!
[FRANKY]
Stop wasting my time, punk. Huh?
[LUFFY] Eh?! Man, he's tough!
[FRANKY] What the hell?
[LUFFY] Did he just--?
Impossible.
A little cut from a dead
guy ain't gonna kill me!
[LUFFY] Stay down already!
That guy is different.
He's a lot tougher
than those knuckleheads
we beat the crap out of earlier.
Hahahaha!
Now you will
know real terror!
You'll see what makes a
zombie truly frightening!
Hey! Why're you
way over there?
They don't feel
even a hint of pain--
they never get tired.
And these Zombie Generals
offer even more.
They all made quite a name
for themselves in battle
before they died and
were brought back to life.
Among them are a knight,
a wicked criminal,
a samurai, a pirate,
and also a gunslinger!
Just imagine the possibilities!
These ruthless fighters combined
with the relentless power
of the undead.
Not a single member
of your crew
is going to escape this place.
Give up! You're done!
Shut up, pig!
[OINKCHUCK] Wall Zombie!
He locked us in here!
Then we can only
move forward, but--
[LUFFY]
Whooooa!!
Speaking from experience
of fighting one Zombie General.
I'd say we're in
pretty deep crap here.
[LUFFY] There's armored
guys everywhere!
Trying to take down
these corpses one at a time
doesn't seem like the way to go.
But trying to take
them all on at once
seems like an even dumber idea.
This ain't good.
[LUFFY] Yeah. You got a point.
And this isn't even the
fight we came in here for.
If we somehow manage
to escape this hall,
we'll most likely end up
outside in the courtyard.
[LUFFY] Right.
Then let's split up
and meet there.
And be careful.
I don't want anyone
else to disappear.
Got it?
[ROBIN] Got it.
Attack!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Lola! Lola!
Dammit! Where'd that warthog go?
Lola!
[LOLA] Absa-lover!
Cut it out,
you crazy beast!
Don't you listen
to a word I say?
[panting heavily]
I told you. This is the
woman I'm going to marry!
[LOLA] Master Ab is mine. Mine!
[LOLA] That hussy cat-burglar
will never have you!
[ABSALOM] Lola! Stop it!
I'm coming for you!
[ABSALOM] Stop it,
dammit! Don't do this!
[DOGGUIN] If any of you so
much as touch this lady,
you'll regret it!
What the heck
is going on here?
Isn't that penguin
one of the zombies?
Did you notice
his fighting style?
It can't be.
Hey! Dumbass!
You're really starting
to piss me off, chum!
You're fighting the
wrong enemy, idiot!
The girl is one of our targets!
[DOGGUIN] Anyone who
mistreats a lady is gonna get
a crash course in table
manners from yours truly.
You got that?
You crappy zombies!
That dog-penguin is...
It's him. I'm sure of it!
[PERONA] The ship of the
famous Straw Hat pirates.
The crew that defeated
Crocodile and many others.
Awesome!
I can't wait to see what
goodies they've got hidden here!
[PERONA]
Horo horo horo horo!
[ZORO] Hey! Can anybody hear me?
Let me outta here, dammit!
Come on!
Cut me loose, you bastards!
I can't see anything in here.
Just where the
hell am I, anyway?
What's the big idea?
Hey! What are you doing?
Let go of me!
You're dead, whoever you are.
What is this?
What's with that light?
Answer me, damn it!
What the--?
[FRANKY] Strong Right!
You don't know who
you're messin' with!
Trienta Fleur!
Move it!
[LUFFY] Now! Come on!
Stay down, already!
I don't have time for
this, you damn zombies!
[ROBIN] Clutch!
There. Now stay outta the way!
[ROBIN] It doesn't seem
like we're making any headway.
Dammit!
Kicking their asses over
and over is gonna wear me out.
They're stubborn, huh?
What a pain.
Now Gum-Gum Gatling!
[MALE VOICE] One-Sword Style!
36 Caliber Phoenix!
That move! Zoro!
Zoro! What's your problem?
That's dangerous!
Hmm?
Scars on the back are the
shame of a swordsman, but...
...I've got scars
on my entire body!
[LUFFY] You look different,
but you are Zoro, right?
[JIGORO] Nu-uh, I'm Jigoro!
[LUFFY] Jigoro?
You mean you're not Zoro?
Then why are you using
Zoro's sword moves?
I'm tired of hearing
your loud mouth,
you damn pirate.
You are my sworn enemy.
I am?
I'm gonna cut you
into little pieces!
[LUFFY] Man,
you're a lot like Zoro!
Only dumber!
[FRANKY] Bastard!
[FRANKY] Holy crap!
There's no end to these guys!
Franky! Quick! Grab hold!
It's no use!
They're still coming!
I know what'll stop 'em.
Fresh Fire!
[CAPTAIN JOHN]
Prepare the buckets!
[FRANKY] No way!
Hey! Look out!
How about
some Once Fleur!
And Slam!
[ROBIN] Where's Luffy?
[FRANKY] It looks like he
wasn't able to make it out.
I don't see him anywhere!
Probably 'cause he's
wearing that stupid armor!
He blends in with
the rest of 'em!
[FRANKY] Unless-- Wait.
You don't think he
disappeared, too, do ya?
It's not a good idea
to wait and find out.
Those zombies will
catch up to us any second.
[FRANKY] Hey! Straw Hat!
[LUFFY]
Arrrrghh!!!
This sucks! Stop it!
Lemme outta here!
[FRANKY] What the--?
[LUFFY] Lemme go, you bastards!
Open up this box and let me out!
Is that a coffin?
[LUFFY]
Oh, you're gonna regret this!
[ROBIN] That voice--It's Luffy!
[FRANKY] Wait, you mean Straw
Hat's inside of that thing?
C'mon, Robin! After it!
[ROBIN] Right!
What are you doing
in that box, dumbass?
Why'd you go and get
yourself caught like that?
Hey! Straw Hat!
[TARARAN] That's far enough.
[TARARAN] Hey, Hey!
Monkey! Monkey! Monkey!
All those stories you've
heard about Spider Monkeys?
You're looking at one!
That's me!
A giant spider!
Even for a monkey,
that's damn big.
It's a monster!
[LUFFY] I'm warning you!
Lemme outta this box or else!
Ah! Got another one!
It sounds like it hit the floor!
Damn it!
What are you punks
gonna do to him?
Heee. Oh, don't worry.
You'll find out soon enough,
since you're gonna be next.
But I'd be more worried
about myself, if I were you!
You've got me in front of you,
and armored warrior zombies
closing in from behind.
There's no escape!
Prepare for annihilation!
[ABSALOM] You stupid zombie!
Don't you know I'm your leader?
Get out of my way!
[DOGGUIN] Even the
mightiest island must relent
to the whipping
winds of my heart!
That's right!
This is a love hurricane!
[ABSALOM] Would you shut up and
move so I can capture my bride?
[DOGGUIN] I won't let you
lay a hand on that lady.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"Chivalry Remains!
The Traitorous
Zombie Protects Nami!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!