Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[RYUMA] It'll be
just like before.
You talk big, but you'll end
up begging for your life
while screaming,
"Anything but the afro!
Anything but the afro!"
[BROOK] Wrong!
This time is different!
Arrgh!
Nyohohoho...
[BROlOK] During
these past 5 years,
I've been thinking of nothing
but this second chance.
And I've trained
to become stronger!
[LUFFY] "A Man's
Promise Never Dies!
To the Friend Waiting
Under the Distant Sky."
You said this thing's
bigger than a giant?
What is it, some
kind of monster?
Yeah, that huge
crash you heard
and all that crazy yelling
came from the same creature.
In other words, Luffy's
zombie is going on a rampage.
C'mon.
[USOPP] Hey, look!
I can see the Sunny!
Good.
Then it looks like what that
Skeleton guy told us is right.
Indeed.
I see.
So that's the way
this works, huh?
You land right
here on the island,
take a little stroll through
this gate and up the stairs.
And before you know it,
you've walked straight
into the boss' room.
Serving him your shadow
on a silver platter.
[panting heavily]
Somebody lowered
the stairs on the Sunny.
I wonder why they'd do that.
[USOPP]
Whooooooa!!
I don't know what happened
while we were gone,
but they totally
wrecked the place!
[ROBIN] This is
the zombies' work.
Their footprints are everywhere.
[CHOPPER] Huh? Then, you
think they're still here?
[USOPP] I wonder what
they were trying to do.
They tore through all our stuff.
Jokes on them.
We don't have
anything worth taking.
[sniff, sniff]
I don't smell
any zombies.
[sniff, sniff]
So, you think the
others are really here?
Won't know 'til we look.
Hey! Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Are you here, or not, huh?
Answer us?
They probably placed
them inside a cabin, right?
Why would they do
something like that?
They have to protect
Luffy and the others.
If they die, then their
zombies will die as well.
I see. Okay. Hey, Franky!
You and Chopper
check the first floor.
Robin and I will
check things upstairs.
There may still be some
zombies hanging around here,
so everyone be careful, okay?
Okay.
Hey! Look! They're right
up here in the dining room!
All three of them!
Luffy!
What the hell, is this?
Those zombies really
had a field day with them
while they were
knocked out, huh?
[ROBIN] It's hard to look at.
Wake up already!
This isn't the time to be
taking a nap, okay? C'mon!
[FRANKY] Leave this one to me.
[punching sounds]
[FRANKY] Get off
your asses, damn it!
We're in a lotta trouble here!
Take that crap off your face
and get with the program!
[USOPP] Still didn't do it, huh?
[FRANKY] So you punks
wanna be lazy, do ya?
All right, then. Step aside.
I'm using my bazooka.
[USOPP] I have a more
delicate solution.
In times like these.
There's a beautiful
lady swordmaster
with a whole bunch of meat!
A lady?
With meat?
And swords?
You guys are hopeless!
Did you hear the news?
Indeed! It looks like
she's a 95, 55, 85!
Those three sizes...
...are nothing
short of a miracle!
Ah, this's the one!
He he he! Perfect match!
Dearie, I'm gonna
make you shine!
Oh, almost forgot.
What the hell are you trying
to pull here, you old coot?
[chuckles] I'm saving
your necks, boys.
If Master Absalom found out
you were peeking at his bride,
you'd be even deader
than you are now.
Isn't that right,
Master Absalom?
[footsteps]
Wait, don't tell me.
He was still here?
Ahhh!!
No! Save me!
Damn it! I didn't
think he would find me.
Ahh! What're you waiting for?
Go invite the Zombie
Generals to the wedding!
Move! Get out of here!
[ZOMBIE PRIEST] Yes, sir!
That bastard!
Where's my shadow?
It ain't here, you idiot.
Take a look at where you are!
Uhhhn....
[LUFFY]
Huh? This is...
[FRANKY]
Yeah, the Sunny.
[ZORO] Wait, but what are we
doing back here all of a sudden?
Ah crap, it wasn't a
dream after all, was it?
I really lost my shadow.
This feels weird.
You guys, this is an emergency.
Someone came in here and stole
all our food while we were out!
[LUFFY] Now I'm mad.
The guy with a
mouth full of grub
is complaining that
there's nothing to eat?
I'm mad too,
but at least they left
the dried food behind.
Who cares about that stuff?
I need meat! Bastards!
I screwed up.
How could I let that happen?
I really let my guard down.
They took our lunchboxes--
there's nothing but cheese!
No fair! Why cheese?
So where's Nami?
Is she waiting
outside or something?
About that, uh...
Uh...
You let some
bastard kidnap my angel?
Why didn't you chase them
to ends of the world?
It-it's not really
our fault, okay?
This particular guy is kind
of hard to catch, you see.
[SANJI] You tell me who he is
and where I can find him.
I'll hunt him down right now
and bring her back!
Wait, let me explain
the situation here,
it's sort of complicated.
[USOPP] Okay, so this
is the deal, you guys.
Even if it kills us,
we have two big things
we have to get back,
no matter what!
[LUFFY] Food and Nami.
Oh, and our shadows,
too, that's three.
[USOPP] Okay, uh...
I'm not sure if one of
those really makes the list.
Food is great and all,
but let's just focus on
Nami and shadows for now.
[SANJI] He, he's going.
To marry her?
No way in hell! Lemme at him!
Wow, this guy
must be pretty brave
if he wants to marry Nami!
And what's all this
about me being a monster?
Why does my shadow get
to do all the cool stuff?
So Usopp, you guys
already saw who,
or what, has Sanji and
Luffy's shadows, right?
No one told me
we were fighting
one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea.
[CHOPPER] Can I just hide in
a hole and cry myself to sleep?
[FRANKY] You guys were all
business just a second ago.
[USOPP and CHOPPER]
We didn't know any better!
[USOPP]
Oh wait, I almost forgot.
Hey, wait a sec.
if you put someone's
shadow in a zombie,
then they act like
that person, right?
Then, I think I've seen
your Zombie, Zoro.
Oh yeah?
What kinda guy was he?
Well, he looked
just like you.
Scars on the back are the
shame of a swordsman, but...
...I've got scars
on my entire body!
But since he was
wearing wooden clogs,
I could tell it wasn't you.
All right, whatever
you say then.
So if we find this guy with the
clogs, the dog penguin thing,
the one that has Sanji's shadow,
and Luffy's giant
monster zombie,
all we gotta do is throw
some salt in their mouths
and then we'll get
our shadows back?
Is that it?
[FRANKY] Uh-huh, that's
what it looks like.
[ZORO] Nice job on figuring
out their weakness,
how'd you pull that one off?
[FRANKY] Save your thanks
for the afro skeleton,
not only did he know
how to beat the zombies,
he also told us you'd be
waiting back here at the Sunny.
What? You ran into Brook again?
[FRANKY] Yeah, though
I feel a little bad,
since I asked him a
pretty cruel question.
[FRANKY] Even though you
wanted him to join the crew,
when I met the guy,
I didn't give him a fair shake.
Truth be told, I barely
even thought of him as human.
But once I actually
took the time
to talk to him for a second.
I found out he has
a real backbone.
Other than the obvious, I mean.
[FRANKY] What I'm saying is...
I was wrong.
That skeleton's a real man.
I,.. I shouldn't
have said it, but...
I'm in a hurry,
so please excuse me.
I'll be on my way now.
Hold on a second!
While you're still
in a mood to talk,
there's one more
burning question
I still need an answer to.
If you go out in
public looking like that.
You know how people are
gonna react, don't you?
I mean, you're
a talking skeleton.
There's no way someone
as creepy as you
is ever gonna make
friends with anyone.
People're gonna
run away in terror.
Franky, why are you
telling him that?
[FRANKY] Even if you
could see the sun
and make it out of
these cursed waters,
your life would still
be full of suffering.
[FRANKY] You've had it rough
for a long time already.
Are you sure you
could handle that?
After all, you said
before that you were
so lonely that you
wanted to die, right?
If I were you,
I would've given up on
life a long time ago.
And yet you still
act like a gentleman.
You laugh. You sing.
You pretend like you don't
have a care in the world.
What is it that's
keeping you alive?
You said you made a
promise to a friend?
What is it? How could
it be so important?
Yohoho...
Interested in me, are you?
[BROOK] The story
is quite simple.
At a certain point in the past,
before we came to these waters,
my crew left behind
a good friend of ours.
It was a troubling situation,
but we did it out of necessity.
The only consolation
we could offer
this friend was a promise
that we would return one day,
no matter the cost.
But then the crew
was annihilated.
And the promise that we
made was left unfulfilled.
[BROOK] Since
I am the only survivor,
it is my duty to
return to our friend,
even if I must bear sad news.
How long has it been
since the day we died?
I've lost count, but it's
been more than 50 years now.
50 years?
You're talking ages ago, here!
Hell, I wasn't even born yet!
I hate to break
it to you buddy,
but there's no way your
friend's still waiting for you.
You don't know that!
[BROOK] But it's
true that he would
have every right
to leave by now.
I realize I may be foolish
to believe he's still there.
However, if by some chance,
he did believe in our
promise and is waiting
for us even after
all of these years.
Then the loneliness
he's suffering,
would be far worse than my own.
How sad must he be,
wondering if we betrayed him,
wondering if our
promise was a lie.
Yet still waiting for
us in the same place.
You're right, but...
[BROOK] The name of that friend
that we left at the cape,
swearing to meet again, is...
...Laboon.
He was just a child.
We simply couldn't
take such a young whale
on a dangerous
journey like that.
A whale?
Yes.
[RUMBAR PIRATES]
Goodbye Laboon!
I'm sorry we have to leave you!
Don't worry, we'll be
back soon! Be a good boy!
[whale cry]
[BROOK] I can only imagine
how big he's grown since then.
[FRANKY] You think that whale,
understood your promise?
In his own way.
I can't help but think
that he's still waiting
for us at that cape, staring
longingly at the Grand Line.
[BROOK] He probably
wants to hear us
play our cheerful music again.
Dancing and singing.
Although I suppose it's
a bit late for that now.
[BROOK] Even if
I am able to return,
I don't think he'll
forgive us for running away
and dying like that.
But no matter how
much he resents me
for forcing him to
suffer all of these years.
[BROOK]
Death is never an apology.
Because when a
man makes a promise,
he doesn't stop fighting
until he fulfills it!
[FRANKY] So there you have it,
that's it the whole story.
Laboon.
[chuckles]
[whale roar]
This is crazy,
what're the chances?
I'll be damned.
Hm? Hm?
Oh, right. Chopper and
Robin weren't with us then.
[whale roar]
[LUFFY] You! You think
you can break my special seat
and get away with it?
[roars]
I'm stronger than I look!
[LUFFY] I can always tell when
someone's itching to fight.
Well, if you want a battle,
I'll gladly give ya one.
Your shipmates used to
spar with you didn't they?
You miss it.
Well, I can rival
anything they threw at ya!
[LUFFY] Tell ya what, after
me and my friends travel
the Grand Line, we'll
come back and find you.
And then you better
be ready for a rematch!
Hey, not bad!
Consider this a
symbol of my promise
to come do battle with you!
Of course, it's
a rush paint job,
so you'll have to be careful
and avoid hitting your head
or you'll rub it
right off. Understand?
[roars]
We've met that
whale before.
And we know that promise.
[roars]
[ZORO] So Laboon's been waiting
at that cape all this time.
[USOPP] Even after 50 years,
he's still thinking
of his friends.
I thought that whale's story
was crazy enough already,
but this is almost
too much to swallow!
[ZORO] And that skeleton
is a swordsman, huh?
Now I'm getting interested.
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"I Swear to Go See Him!
Brook and the Cape of Promise!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!