[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated
from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
However, the two could
not escape Admiral Akainu,
and Ace died protecting Luffy.
Then, suddenly, Blackbeard
appeared, killing Whitebeard
and accomplishing
something truly unthinkable.
[BLACKBEARD]
Just watch!
[MARCO gasps]
No, it can't be.
[cackling]
[MARINES panting]
[MARINE AA]
HQ's comin' down! Run for it!
[cackling]
[MARINE BB]
Abandon your posts!
[MARINE CC]
We're all gonna die!
It's over...
There's nothing left.
[MARINES gasp, yell]
The pirates, they took
everything we had.
Our citadel, where we've watched
over these waters
for centuries...
It's all crumbling down.
The symbol of the
Navy's strength.
This is a nightmare!
[BLACKBEARD cackling]
[MAN A]
Damn!
He planned this from
the very start, didn't he?
He betrayed Whitebeard,
captured Ace and
became a Warlord,
all to force them
into this battle!
All right, then!
Take a good look,
'cause you ain't seen
nothin' like this before!
[gasps]
[CROWD gasping]
They can't stop
him now. No one can.
[BLACKBEARD chuckles]
Hmm?
[MARINE D whimpering]
[BLACKBEARD chuckles]
I can hardly blame 'em.
I'd be crying, too, if my
enemies had this kind of power!
Now what?
[BLACKBEARD] Took some time,
but this is a hell of a payoff.
I got the whole world
wrapped around my finger!
You bastard!
[BLACKBEARD]
Huh?
[BLACKBEARD grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[BLACKBEARD]
Hey, what's wrong?
Ya don't wanna fight?
I'm right here.
If you let me get away,
who knows what I might do!
Okay, I warned ya!
[BLACKBEARD]
Huh! Now, where to start?
Ohh, I know!
How about I give
Marineford a burial at sea!
[MARINES gasp]
He wouldn't dare!
[BLACKBEARD]
Huh?
[BLACKBEARD groans]
[BLACKBEARD]
Shock Wave!
[BLACKBEARD groaning]
You can tear down our buildings,
but in time,
we will rebuild them.
[BLACKBEARD grunts]
[SENGOKU]
But this island is different.
It's more than a symbol
of our strength,
it stands in the
center of the world.
Admiral...
And that means
if we want to protect
innocent people from
criminals such as yourself,
it must be our stronghold
so it's light can
reach every corner.
Compassion is justice--
It defies chaos.
It doesn't perish,
and it will certainly
not sink by your hand.
Time to learn your place.
[cackling]
[BLACKBEARD] Well, that's
a downright noble sentiment.
"Compassion" or what have you.
Well? C'mon!
Let's see what you're made of!
[PIRATE A yelps]
That isn't good!
[PIRATE A] We gotta get this
ship to the island, quick!
Our men are gonna sink if we
can't get them outta there!
Don't give up.
We are leaving here together!
[PIRATE B panting]
[PIRATE B]
The ships are coming for us!
We can still make it!
[PIRATES panting]
Even if we have to strike
our foes in the back,
our victory must be absolute!
Pops wanted all of us
to escape this place,
and that's what we're
gonna do, damn it!
We'll strike the fear of
justice into their hearts.
Crimes will be punished
and order will reign!
That's our duty...
...as Marines. He's right.
C'mon, men, one last push!
Now's our chance.
We'll show every criminal what
happens when you defy the law.
We'll let the
whole world know...
[MARINES]
...that justice will prevail!
We made it!
In the name of justice!
[MARINES]
[PIRATE B]
Kizaru!
[PIRATES gasp]
We bought you some time!
Get him out of here!
Good luck!
[INAZUMA groans]
Oh, no!
Bad move, Jimbei!
Now get over here!
You're a pesky one, aren't you?
Either way, I'll finish
this in time for dinner!
I'll strike you down,
here and now!
New Kama Kenpo,
Aesthetic Technique.
Laser Surgery Fist!
[yells]
[shouting]
[IVANKOV chuckles]
[IVANKOV]
Hm?
No, you melted
my fabulous nails!
[AKAINU] Emporio Ivankov
of the Revolutionary Army.
I'd heard your
techniques were eccentric
and that certainly
seems to be the case.
[IVANKOV] New Kama Kenpo,
Aesthetic Technique.
This one's my
Fat Suctioning Fist!
[IVANKOV]
I like it hot, baby!
[IVANKOV groans]
[AKAINU]
This isn't a game, damn it!
Get the hell out of
my way or pay the price!
[IVANKOV groans]
[IVANKOV grunting]
[IVANKOV]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
My lips, they're melting,
my whole face is melting!
Oh, that's not my face!
That's just my garish makeup!
Uh-oh...
[PRISONERS]
Ah! Iva, no!
[AKAINU]
Who's next?
[MARINE DD]
Don't let them escape!
Fire!
[PIRATES shouting]
[PIRATE F groans]
[PIRATE G yelps]
[PIRATE H groans]
[HELMEPPO]
Aw, jeez.
I understand going
after Blackbeard,
but this seems kind
of like overkill.
I know they're pirates,
but haven't enough
people been killed?
[PIRATE I whimpering]
[PIRATE I yelps]
[COBY grunts]
[MARINE M] Hunt them down!
Leave no man standing!
[gasps]
[MARINE N]
This is our chance.
Let's show the world what
happens when they defy us!
What the...
[MARINE O]
This is justice!
[MARINE P]
The power of the Navy!
[PIRATE J screams]
[MARINE Q]
Destroy them!
[MARINE Q, MARINE R]
[MARINE Q, MARINE R, MARINE S]
Destroy them!
[MARINES]
[COBY gasps]
What are these
voices in my head?
Don't you dare, Akainu!
You'd be wise
to run while you can.
I have no business with you!
[PRISONERS gasping]
[JIMBEI grunts, growls]
I dare not face him on dry land,
but the sea will aid me!
[AKAINU growls]
[JIMBEI grunts]
The water--it's frozen solid!
Damn! Aokiji!
Here he comes.
Nowhere left to run,
you bloated fish!
[JIMBEI grunts]
[AKAINU groans]
[JIMBEI groans]
I'm helpless, then.
[AKAINU]
Hand him over!
I'm putting an end to this!
[JIMBEI groans]
[groaning]
[PIRATE K, PIRATE L]
Jimbei!
[yells]
It looks like it went
straight through him.
It might've hit Straw Hat!
And they're falling fast, too!
[JIMBEI groaning]
[JIMBEI]
I have to protect him.
[JIMBEI groaning]
Still have some
fight left in you?
That's a pity.
[JIMBEI groaning]
Forgive me,
Luffy.
It seems that
I couldn't uphold my vow.
You might have saved yourself
instead of condemning
the both of you.
[growls]
[AKAINU]
If you keep making me miss,
it won't be good for anyone.
A blow to the heart would
be quick and painless...
Better than this.
[JIMBEI groaning]
The boy's got
a hole in his chest.
You sure you still
wanna protect him?
[JIMBEI groaning]
You know he's gonna
die, either way.
[yelling]
[ACE]
Jimbei.
I know I might not make
it out of this alive.
I'm sorry, but if I die,
would you look after
my brother for me?
[JIMBEI] Although your
death was a tragedy,
it did not sway my feelings,
yet I've found the
answer to your request.
You aren't the only
tenacious one here.
I've decided to protect this
boy, no matter the cost.
[JIMBEI]
I refuse to let him perish!
[JIMBEI groaning]
Strike at me as many
times as you like.
I will shield him
as long as I live!
What a load of crap.
[AKAINU gasps]
[groans]
He protected us.
Sables!
[JIMBEI groans]
They won't be up there long,
so catch them when they
fall and put them on a ship.
[PIRATES]
Uh-huh.
Why the sudden change of heart?
I say if you're gonna protect
someone, then do it right!
I don't like either of you,
but if you screw this up,
then you let the Navy win.
Sorry I blew it, guys.
You had so much faith in me,
but I was nothing more
than a coward all along.
I'll just float away somewhere
and find a hole to crawl in,
'cause the only thing I'm
the king of is disappointment.
[PIRATES]
Oh, crap, they're getting away!
[BUGGY yelps]
They're stuck in the air?
[BUGGY]
Wait, what's happening here?
[ALL]
Nice catch, Captain Buggy!
You saved Straw Hat and Jimbei!
[PRISONER A]
I never should've doubted you!
He wasn't running!
He was just looking
out for Straw Hat,
because all the
glory in the world
means nothing compared
to the life of an old friend!
[PRISONERS gasp]
[PRISONER B]
How beautiful!
[PRISONER C] His heart's
as pure as a baby lamb!
I can't hear what they're
saying, but I bet it's stupid.
[JIMBEI groans]
Huh? Jimbei and Straw Hat?
What the hell?
What are you idiots
doing all the way up here
and why are you
both covered in blood?
This is weird,
even for you guys!
Also, is it just me,
or is it hot?
[BUGGY yelps]
Th-That's magma!
[BUGGY yelping]
Thank you, my red-nosed friend.
You saved our lives!
We're not friends!
I don't even know
what's going on right now!
I'm afraid I allowed
Luffy to be harmed.
We must find a doctor.
He was burned quite badly.
I don't care!
And good luck finding a doctor
in the middle of this mess!
I oughta drop the
both of you right now!
Wait, were you making
fun of my nose?!
How many people do I have to go
through to finish that brat?
[VISTA]
Rose Rondo!
You're fools, each
and every one of you.
Is one boy so damned important
that you're willing to
throw your lives away?
You may mock us if you please,
but there is a strength
in Straw Hat's tenacity
that may prove
invaluable to this world.
Pops bet his life on him.
He has to carry on Ace's legacy.
This is the dawn of a new era
and we have a duty
to see him through it.
Noble sentiment from
a bunch of criminals,
but in the end,
it's just empty talk.
[AKAINU] I won't hesitate
to strike you down.
[MARCO]
Same here.
Your insistence
on killing Straw Hat
just proves to us how
much you fear him,
and if a tough guy like you
is scared of a boy like him,
that means he's
worth protecting,
to the death, if need be!
Ugh. Can't you jackasses
do anything without my help?
Hey, are you even
listening to me?
You didn't just
pass out, did you?
[gasps] Hey, I didn't mean
it buddy, don't die on me!
C'mon, you gotta
tell me where to go.
I'm lost here! Help!
[CROCODILE] Frankly,
I should be applauding him
for making Straw Hat suffer,
but I suppose the pirate in me
would rather punch
him in the face.
[AKAINU] I see that trying to
reason with you is a lost cause.
Have it your way!
This is too much.
[PIRATE Q] It's Sengoku
vs. Blackbeard over there.
[PIRATES gasp]
[PIRATES yell]
And it's Akainu vs.
the commanders on that side.
[PRISONERS yell]
[PRISONERS] I thought this
war was supposed to be over!
Captain Buggy,
do something! Anything!
I've got my hands full, okay?
Come on, guys, you're
stressing me out over here.
Huh?
[BUGGY yelping]
[PRISONERS yell]
[BUGGY yelps]
[BEPO] Captain, we found a spot
where the ice doesn't reach.
[LAW]
Then, surface.
[BUGGY yelling]
What is that?
It was underwater... A ship?
[PIRATE BB]
It's a submarine!
[PIRATE T]
Not another enemy, is it?
[PIRATE CC]
That's a jolly roger.
Huh? I don't take
orders from you, pal!
And besides, what do you want
with him anyway, ya weirdo?
Actually, who the hell are you?
[LAW] Straw Hat
may be my enemy someday,
but I'll let the fates
decide that one.
Either way, it'd be
a waste to let him die here.
Hand him over and we can escape.
He'll die without my help.
What?
Trust me. I'm a doctor.
[NARRATOR]
As senseless violence
dyes the battlefield
red with blood,
Luffy's allies
struggle to save him.
As the admirals
maintain their assault,
with the world
burning around him,
a boy who lacks
the will to fight
makes a stand that may change
the future of the entire world!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Desperate Scream!
Courageous Moments That
Will Change the Future"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!