[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
With Jimbei's help,
he cleared the encircling walls
and inched closer
to the scaffold.
He continues his
progress towards Ace
as the battle between the
Whitebeard Pirates and Navy
rages on in the plaza!
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
Son of a--[groans]
The ravages of time
humble us all.
Yes, even you.
Screw the fight,
this is what I was afraid of!
[KIZARU] Huh. Wouldn't turn
your back on me, if I were you.
[MARCO groans]
Marco!
You gonna make the same mistake?
[JOZU groaning]
[AKAINU]
Someone has to see you off.
And that duty seems
to have fallen on me.
[AKAINU grunts]
[WHITEBEARD groans]
Pops, no!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY] As long as I
do everything I can,
I don't care if I die.
I'm begging you,
you have to let me fight!
If I don't keep fighting...
...and they kill Ace 'cause
I wasn't there for him...
...then I'd rather
be dead anyway!
[IVANKOV gasps]
Right now is the only fight
that matters--live or die!
Oh, fine!
It's your life!
Give us a good show!
[groans]
[yelling]
Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[groans] This is ridiculous!
What could possibly
take so long?
[MARINE A] I'm back, sir,
sorry for the wait!
These two replacements
should be able to
carry out the execution, sir.
All right, fine!
Hurry and get up here then!
Right!
[IVANKOV]
Remember, Straw Boy.
Energy Hormone may
get you pumped for now,
but if you fall
again, that's it!
You're a dead boy! Got it?
Energy Hormone only
tricks your body
into thinking you're okay!
It's not actually healing
your injuries at all!
[LUFFY panting]
That's all right.
In that case...
[LUFFY]
...I just won't fall again!
Huh? Well don't kill
yourself too badly.
Crap! It's happening!
Hold on a sec!
They're not executing
Ace while I'm around!
The kid's crazy.
But it isn't like he's
going to change his mind
under these circumstances!
Guess I might as well
give him some backup, then.
Hold on, Straw Boy,
Iva's coming for you!
He's over there!
[MARINE AA]
Straw Hat's still alive!
Not for long he's not!
[LUFFY grunts]
[gasps, groans]
Move it. I've got him!
[MARINE E grunts]
[LUFFY groaning]
[MARINE G grunts]
I'll finish him off!
[gasps, grunts]
[MARINE G groans]
[LUFFY grunting]
[MARINE E, MARINE G groan]
[MARINE H]
Enough crap!
You're not taking another step!
We've got you surrounded, now!
Yeah, he's right! There's no
way you can defeat all of us!
The Navy always wins.
Ya might as well give up!
[MARINES growling, chuckling]
[LUFFY groans]
[IVANKOV]
Incoming!
Death Wink!
[MARINES scream]
[IVANKOV]
My, what a fanciful strike!
Thanks, Iva, I owe ya!
[MARINES groaning, coughing]
[COBY]
Luffy.
[gasps]
[COBY panting]
You gonna fight?
[BOTH panting]
[MARINE L screams]
Coby!
I see it now.
I decided long ago that I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates.
If I have to die fighting
for that, then I die.
[COBY] If I put my mind to it,
if I'm prepared to die for it,
could I do something like that?
Like what?
Do you think...
Do you think I could
ever join the Marines?
Marines?
Yes!
Catching bad guys is the only
thing I've ever wanted to do!
It's been my dream
since I was a child!
If Luffy and I had
never met back then,
I couldn't have
made it this far.
[LUFFY panting]
All right, focus.
If I want any hope of
growing stronger as a Marine...
[COBY] ...I have to fight all
enemies, no matter who they are!
This is war!
I'm sorry, Luffy, but I'm
gonna have to kill you!
Gum-Gum...
Now Shave!
[LUFFY grunts]
Because I promised myself
that I'll keep trying...
...till...
...till I become
a Marine admiral!
[COBY gasps]
[COBY]
No.
I-I'm sorry, I got carried away!
This is so embarrassing.
I just wanna dig a hole
and bury my head in it!
That was really arrogant of me.
I got all worked up after
seeing you again and I just--
[LUFFY]
Coby.
You said you're gonna
fight me, right?
Then you will
become that strong.
You'll have to.
[COBY gasps]
Yeah, but a Marine admiral?
Next time I see you,
we're gonna be stronger, too.
A whole lot stronger.
[COBY]
I don't get it.
[COBY] I just blurted out
some ridiculous dream,
something I don't even
have a right to follow...
[COBY]
...but he didn't laugh.
He believed in me.
[LUFFY]
...Bullet!
[COBY] Looks like I got
carried away again.
I'm useless after all. Guess
it's back to the drawing board.
[HELMEPPO gasps]
Hey! Coby!
[LUFFY panting]
Ace!
[BOTH scream]
Not you again!
Those dirty frauds.
Impersonating my friend!
[KUMA]
Monkey D. Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Why can't they just move?
[gasps]
Hey, what d'you
think you're doing?
[KUMA]
Boa Hancock.
One of the Seven Warlords.
Navy ally detected.
Ceasing attack.
[LUFFY] Oh, yeah! You guys
are on the same side!
Thanks a bunch, Hancock!
[IVANKOV panting]
Isn't that the pirate empress?
Have you two got a thing
going on I should know about?
He said it.
He said my name and
he didn't get it wrong.
But of course! How could I?
[HANCOCK gasps]
Shower me in sweet
gratitude, my love!
You have my thanks.
Yes.
Oh, and Hancock.
I owe you my life.
[HANCOCK]
Yes!
Boa Hancock.
Please move. You are
standing in the way.
I never gave you permission
to address me in such a manner!
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
[WHITEBEARD]
Is that it, magma brat?
[MARCO]
Hold on... Pops.
I'm... coming to save you.
[MARCO groans]
Wow, it went straight through.
Take a few more of these
and have yourself a
nice, long rest, okay?
[MARCO grunts]
Yeah, just try and stop me!
Ah! Well that certainly
throws a wrinkle into my plan.
Regeneration, huh?
So that must be why they
call you the Phoenix.
Hey, give me a hand, will you?
[MARCO gasps]
[MARCO grunting]
Sea Prism Stone?
[PIRATES]
Commander Marco, no!
Ohh. It hurt that time, huh?
[PIRATE A]
They got Jozu, too!
He's frozen solid!
[PIRATE C]
That's two commanders down.
What should we do now?
Take out the head...
....and the body will follow!
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
[MARINE BB groans]
He's in danger! [groans]
Hold still, you monster!
You fools! I will
not be chained!
Good, now close in fast!
Forget the others and attack
Whitebeard with all you've got!
[MARINES yelling]
[PIRATES]
Pops!
[WHITEBEARD gasps]
[gasps]
[JIMBEI gasps]
[PIRATES]
We'll save him!
[PIRATES shout]
No, stay back!
[PIRATES gasp]
[JIMBEI gasps]
[WHITEBEARD]
You punks really think...
...that's all it
takes to defeat me?
[gasps]
[WHITEBEARD]
Just a few toy swords and guns?
[MARINES gasping]
[WHITEBEARD] I could tear
you all apart single-handedly.
But you know that, don't you?
Because you quake...
...when you hear
the name Whitebeard!
[WHITEBEARD yells]
[MARINES screaming]
[MARINES gasping]
[MARINE R grunting]
[MARINE CC gasps]
[MARINES screaming]
[MARINES gasping]
Th-That's insane!
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINES groaning]
[sighs]
[WHITEBEARD groans]
This is our chance!
Quickly, before he recovers!
[MARINES groaning]
Everybody, follow me!
[MARINE DD]
Sir!
[panting]
What did he say?
Hmph. That's a good one.
I don't need to recover
from a scratch like this!
[ACE gasping]
[WHITEBEARD]
You think this will stop me?
That I'll lie down and give up?
[WHITEBEARD]
I'm not... such a fool.
[WHITEBEARD] I know what
will happen if I falter,
even for a moment.
What will happen if I die.
[PIRATES scream]
[WHITEBEARD]
And knowing that cold truth...
...I can't allow
myself to submit,
not until the bitter end.
So I'll wait until I've taken
care of the future for my sons.
[ACE gasping]
Got it, Ace?
Oh, Pops.
Bah! Old fool's lost it!
[MARINES gasp]
[JIMBEI grunts]
What the hell?
[MARINES scream]
[MARINES groan]
Damn. And we were so close, too!
Bastards have formed a barrier
around Whitebeard's back!
You want us to bury
you with the old man?
[pants] Your mockery
does not sway my honor!
[JIMBEI grunts]
It is our pride and our
joy to stand beside him!
You bunch of fools!
Get away!
[SQUARD]
Pops...
What are your orders, Captain?
Shouldn't we go help
defend Pops, too?
[PIRATE B] Captain Squard?
Where are you going?
[SQUARD]
Don't follow me.
You've done well,
but a cowardly traitor
such as myself
must face his punishment.
[SENGOKU]
Concerned about the future?
I'll be more than happy
to show it to you now.
Let's end this.
Execute it!
[PIRATES]
Ace! No!
[LUFFY panting]
I'm too slow!
Don't make me laugh!
You think I can't stop
those runts from doing it?
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
[WHITEBEARD coughs]
From the start,
this was the only way!
[WHITEBEARD groans]
[LUFFY]
Ace!
[ALL grunting]
[LUFFY growls]
[LUFFY grunting]
Don't do it!
[WHITEBEARD gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Don't you dare!
[grunts]
[LUFFY]
It's not over yet!
[IVANKOV] Did you just
do what I think you did?
It's the Conqueror's... Spirit!
[LUFFY panting]
Well damn, this is a mess.
There's a surprise for you.
Why, that little brat.
[LUFFY yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Unaware of his own power,
Luffy unleashes the
Conqueror's Spirit,
temporarily halting
Ace's execution.
The Navy, now recognizing
the threat he poses,
sends all of their
forces after him.
Thankfully, Ivankov has a plan
that may forge a path to Ace.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Scaffold at Last!
The Way to Ace Has Opened!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!