[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated
from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally
arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
[NARRATOR] Fighting alongside
Whitebeard and his associates,
he continues to push
toward the scaffold.
As the all-out battle continues
between the Navy's elite and the
strongest pirates in the world,
Luffy puts his life on the line,
vowing death before defeat!
[SENGOKU]
Concerned about the future?
I'll be more than happy
to show it to you now.
Let's end this.
Execute him!
[LUFFY pants]
I'm too slow!
Don't make me laugh!
You think I can't stop
those runts from doing it?
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
[WHITEBEARD coughs]
[WHITEBEARD groans]
[WHITEBEARD gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Don't you dare!
[LUFFY grunts]
Did you just do
what I think you did?
It's the Conqueror's... Spirit!
Well damn. This is a mess.
There's a surprise for you.
Why, that little brat.
[LUFFY]
"The Scaffold at Last!
The Way to Ace Has Opened!"
We're good!
Ace is still alive, guys!
Hey! Pull it together, pal!
That power--it came
from Ace's brother, huh?
What the...
I almost passed out back there.
[LUFFY yelling]
That was the Conqueror's Spirit.
Like Pops and Shanks use.
Damn. That kid is
full of surprises, huh?
I don't think he realizes
what he just did.
I tell you, boys, we got
some scary stuff right here.
[PIRATE C groans]
He didn't learn that power,
he was born with it.
Just like Pops.
If your will is
weak, stand back!
He's not just another rookie!
Conqueror's Spirit, huh?
We can't forget he's
the son of Dragon.
That's what we get for
underestimating him.
What next, Vice Admiral?
My energy hormones
didn't do that!
What hat did you pull
those powers out of?
Power? What d'you mean?
We'll discuss it later!
[IVANKOV]
He's not aware of it.
That means we can't count
on him using it again.
Either way, it's no wonder that
people are so drawn to him!
The apple doesn't fall far from
the tree, does it, Dragon?
[DOBERMAN] Do not let that
boy escape this battlefield.
If he does, he'll turn
into a dire threat to us!
Dead or alive,
you take him down!
[MARINES shouting]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[MARINES gasp]
[BOTH gasping]
[MARINES groaning]
[WHITEBEARD chuckles]
Scared to death of a mere
boy and an old man?
You were so cocky before,
but where's your fire now?
I thought you wanted to kill me!
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[MARINES gasping, groaning]
Focus on Whitebeard first!
He may be a monster,
but he's injured!
Take him down,
then go for the kid!
Heh. Just try it.
Don't let a single Marine
lay a hand on him!
[PIRATES cheer]
Don't be intimidated. Go!
[MARINES shout]
They're aiming for Whitebeard!
Move those buns
while you still can!
[DOBERMAN growls]
After Straw Hat, hurry!
[MARINES]
Sir!
[BOTH grunting]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[MARINES yell]
We finally make headway
and the bastards start
pulling it together.
Thinks he can push through.
He'll be pushing up
daisies first.
Damn it all.
[MARINE K groans]
Crap. Come on...
I can't help them, not as long
as I've got these things on.
Hey, Pops!
We got your back,
so don't overdo it!
Stop and listen to me!
What's wrong?
[MARCO gasps]
There's a new plan!
I'm either gonna live
or I'm gonna die.
So back up Straw Hat with
everything you've got!
[PIRATES murmuring]
[FOSSA gasps]
Ace's brother? Why?
What the hell?
Stop your gawking and
take out Straw Hat already!
[LUFFY grunts]
They're coming straight atcha!
Watch out!
[MOMONGA gasps]
I know you.
You're Doma.
"The Bohemian Knight," correct?
Vice Admiral Momonga.
Pleasure to meet you.
[DOMA'S MONKEY screeches]
[LUFFY pants]
[DALMATIAN growls]
The DeCalvan brothers.
It sucks to be you.
You gotta fight us.
[DOBERMAN grunts]
"Thunder Lord" McGuy.
Pardon me, Vice Admiral,
but I require a moment of
your time, if you would.
We've got some friends!
If Whitebeard says
to lend you a hand,
then we're on it in a flash!
Ace is right there, Straw Hat!
No way they're gonna
stop all of us!
[PIRATES shouting]
Whitebeard's allies are
backing up Straw Hat.
This does not look good.
[PIRATES yelling]
Who are you guys?
[RAMBA]
Never mind that, keep running!
The Navy forces are
focused on Pops right now.
So this might be
your only chance
to slip past the
admirals and move in!
[DELACUAJI]
We're slamming them all at once,
so wait for your opening!
[LUFFY gasps]
Hey, not bad!
I think they like you!
The greatest pirate in the world
gave his seal of approval!
Huh?
[IVANKOV]
Heehaw!
Ace may be your brother, but
he's Whitebeard's son, you know.
And he trusts you with his life!
So why don't you stop
trying to be coy
and rise to the occasion,
you cocky little snot!
I don't care what
that old man wants,
and I don't care
what he thinks, either.
I only came here
to do one thing!
[LUFFY] I don't need
anyone's "approval" for that!
The pirates are
gaining headway on us!
They're about to break through!
We need backup in a hurry!
With all due respect,
maybe we should change plans.
Not yet!
If we have a chance
to defeat Whitebeard,
then we must take it!
Everyone move in, now!
If he falls,
then it's only a matter of
time for the rest of them!
One or 100 doesn't matter.
You can stand in line,
or you can all die at once!
[WHITEBEARD grunting]
[MARINES screaming]
He's still up!
What's it going to take?
[WHITEBEARD coughs]
[WHITEBEARD]
We think alike, brat.
As long as Ace goes home,
nothing else matters.
Show me the will of D.
Show me the future.
Even if my days are numbered,
I can see tomorrow blazing
through this battlefield!
[gasps] Hawk-Eye!
This could get nasty!
[IVANKOV]
Did you hear me? Move!
Whoa, thanks.
It's the president's order.
For now, we're still allies.
Go.
"Mr. 1," I believe?
[MR. 1 grunts]
[IVANKOV grunts]
Look out!
[LUFFY gasps]
Crocodile, too?
[MR. 1 groans]
Stop sleeping on the job, Mr. 1.
I thought it was like old times,
but maybe prison made me soft.
You aren't needed here,
Straw Hat. Get moving.
Before I change my mind.
This won't end well.
Are you certain?
I'm not in the mood to
put up with your crap,
or anyone else's.
If you wanna fight,
then shut up and do it.
[LUFFY panting]
[giggles] Luffy! I'm here!
I'll do everything in
my power to aid you!
Target is Monkey D.
Luffy. Open fire.
Boa Hancock. In sight.
Aborting the attack.
[SENTOMARU]
That's enough!
Are you out of your damn mind?
This isn't the first time
you've gotten in the way,
but it will be the last.
What are you trying to
accomplish here, anyway?
You're going to lose
your Warlord status!
[HANCOCK]
You foolish, misshapen manchild.
Your ignorance is an
affront to my beauty.
My what now?
I shall set a pearl
of wisdom before you.
Love is always a hurricane,
you little pig!
You're insane, aren't you?
[LUFFY panting]
[BUGGY]
You better run, Straw Hat.
So what's going on, Captain?
You don't seem
too happy right now.
I'm not.
It doesn't look good out there.
All of you saw it, right?
How incredible I was
on my broadcast.
The whole world
should be watching me!
But nobody cares!
They're too busy gawking at that
chump running to the scaffold
to feast their eyes on
whatever awesome thing
I happen to be doing!
Now answer me this.
Who should be the star
of this pirate show?
[PRISONERS]
That would be you, of course!
Damn straight it should be me.
Now I've got to do
something flashy in a flash,
so people stop watching
Straw Hat's shenanigans
and pay attention to mine!
Hey, fork over that snail, pal.
Uh, yeah, about that.
The snail--it's kind of
frozen solid right now.
What a pain!
Just defrost the damn thing.
Give it a quick dip in that
magma water or whatever
and the ice should
melt right off.
It melted, all right!
[BUGGY]
Nice. Lemme see.
[PRISONER B]
Good as new.
--[BUGGY] Hm?
--Here.
It's all gross! What did you do?
Oh, yeah, saltwater and snails
don't get along, do they?
[BUGGY growls] After we
went to all that trouble
to steal it from the Navy, too.
Well, it's not gonna
win any beauty contests,
but the thing might still work.
I'll just try to
sweet talk it a bit.
Hey, little buddy, think you
could open those peepers for me?
We're gonna be
best buddies, okay?
[PRISONERS chuckling]
What?! I was nice!
It's because of your scary
faces, you bunch of goons!
Sorry, I was born this way.
I guess good looks
don't run in my family.
[BUGGY]
Damn it!
Once Straw Hat makes
it to that scaffold,
nobody's gonna care
about anything else.
I gotta do something
distracting!
[BOTH grunt]
[MARINE Q]
Fire!
[PIRATES yell]
Make a path to the scaffold!
We only need one moment
to break through!
[PIRATES shout]
[MARINES gasp]
Getting desperate, are they?
[DOMA yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[DOMA'S MONKEY grunts]
[DALMATIAN growls]
[BOTH grunt]
[ALL grunting]
[BOTH growl]
[DALMATIAN growls]
[DOBERMAN grunts]
[MCGUY yells]
That's enough!
[MARINES yelling]
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
[MARINES scream]
[WHITEBEARD groaning]
[MARINES yell]
[JIMBEI]
Fishman Karate!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
[MARINES scream]
Jimbei.
I can handle this, damn it.
I said to leave me
and help Straw Hat
get to the scaffold, didn't I?
Sorry, friend, but I'm
not one of your pirates.
That means I don't have to
listen to a word you say.
Heh. Have it your way, then.
[LUFFY panting]
[MARINE S grunts]
[LUFFY yells]
[gasps]
[MARINES, PIRATES grunting]
[LUFFY panting]
They did it!
They cleared a path!
Everyone else has
already done their part.
Now you do yours!
Keep on running and
don't look back!
[LUFFY]
Uh-huh!
[IVANKOV] For better or
worse, it's our turn now.
Look, I'm sorry to
make you do this
when I know you're
still recovering,
but we need your
skills in particular.
[INAZUMA] No apologies
necessary, I assure you.
I shall give it my best.
[LUFFY gasps]
Crab Guy!
[MARINES gasp]
[ALL gasping]
[LUFFY panting]
[ACE gasping]
[MARINE CC]
They made a bridge!
[MARINE DD] It's Inazuma
of the Revolutionary Army!
Is that handy or what? Thanks!
[MARINE EE] Straw Hat's headed
straight for the scaffold!
Stop him!
Sorry! Too busy
to do it myself!
What are you doing?
Block his path!
We can't, sir! See?
These pirates are blocking us!
We can't get past!
Fools! Use your guns!
Cannoneers, open fire!
[LUFFY gasps]
Ugh. Damn, it's them.
[MARINE U] The Whitebeard
Pirates team of Commanders!
[LUFFY panting]
Pops said to watch your back.
So keep running. We got this.
Everyone push.
We're breaking through!
[MARINES yelling]
[FOSSA grunts]
[BLENHEIM grunts]
[MARINES screaming]
Here he comes, men!
Gum-Gum...
...Battle Axe!
[MARINES groan]
Take it straight to the top.
[LUFFY]
You got it! Thanks!
[MARINE FF]
He's getting away!
[IVANKOV]
Death Wink!
[MARINES groan]
If you really wanna rumble,
then step right up!
Heehaw!
Now you just keep on
shining, Straw Boy!
[PIRATE AA]
It worked! He's gonna make it!
[PIRATE BB]
We got this! We really got this!
[MARINE GG]
It's not over! Pull him down!
Straw Hat! Save Ace!
Yeah, it's all you
from here on out!
I've got to admit,
I didn't think Whitebeard
would gamble it all on you.
It's been a fun ride,
but don't kid yourself, boy.
[WHITEBEARD grunts]
Well, don't that beat all.
It's gonna be a good show,
why don't you just
sit back and watch?
[LUFFY panting]
[ACE gasping]
Luffy!
We did it!
I'm here!
[LUFFY gasps]
[PIRATES gasp]
[MARINE HH]
Is Garp gonna fight, too?
Grandpa!
Get outta the way!
I'm not moving a damned inch!
I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting pirates since
long before you were born,
and I ain't stopping today!
Old man!
You're not my grandson here.
You are the pirate,
Straw Hat Luffy.
And I'll fight you to the death.
[LUFFY gasps]
This is the path that
you chose to take!
You and your brother alike!
[NARRATOR] Thanks to
Inazuma's makeshift bridge,
Luffy is able to ascend
to the scaffold.
Garp, unable to watch any
longer, leaps into Luffy's path.
Maintaining his
pride as a Marine,
he faces his own
grandson in battle,
cursing the life of piracy
that Luffy and Ace chose.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Each on Different Paths!
Luffy vs. Garp!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!