[NARRATOR] Sanji
and Zoro square off
against the Foxy Pirates
in a Groggy Ring Match
to win Chopper back.
[ITOMIMIZU] Once again,
Hamburg nabs Sanji
with a perfect catch!
The ring is in sight!
Is this it?!
[ZORO] It ain't over!
I won't let you score!
I can't let Zoro
bail me out of this!
I'd never hear the end of it!
Time for revenge
my friend. You ready?
Hamburger Hammer!
Punk Attack!
[crash]
[pained grunting]
Sling Tackle!
[HAMBURG]
Size Attack: S!
[PICKLES]
M!
[BIG PAN]
L!
[loud crash]
[ITOMIMIZU] In fact you
might say they're "groggy!"
Now all that's left is to stuff
the ball man in his coffin,
I mean, goal and
it'll be two wins
in a row for
the Foxy Pirates!
Hey, let's work
together for ten seconds.
Okay, fine, but no longer.
[ITOMIMIZU] The second
match of our Davy Back Fight
has come to a
dramatic conclusion.
It's another win for
our Groggy Monsters!
And while the Straw Hat
pirates put up a good fight,
they were simply no match
for our reigning champs.
So, with two wins in a
row for the Foxy Pirates
and one adorable new
doctor on the crew,
we must wonder who
Captain Foxy will choose next!
Hey, wait! Look!
Huh??
[ITOMIMIZU]
They're up! Against all odds,
the Straw Hats are
back on their feet!
Even after a demoralizing
beat down the swordsman
without his swords
and the savage chef
stand tall in the face
of adversity once again!
Yeah!!!
You guys! Why you gotta
scare me like that?!
[ITOMIMIZU] The question
is even if they can stand,
do they have enough
strength left to fight?!
[FOXY]
I have a little request.
[GROGGY TEAM]
Huh?
One monster burger, please!
Feh-feh-feh!
[NAMI]
Huh?
Now what could that mean?
Huh? Did someone say burgers,
'cause I could go for one.
Is that all you
ever think about?
[ITOMIMIZU] Uh-oh!
Did you hear that?
Our boss has just ordered
the famous monster burger!
[CROWD cheers]
Feh-feh-feh-feh!
I get that you guys
are cheaters and all
but you can at least
try to hide it!
Grind em' all up
like some burger meat.
Slice 'em like pickles,
sour or sweet.
What're the toppings?!
[HAMBURG and PICKLES]
A head of green lettuce.
And some fine yellow cheese.
Hee-shee-shee-shee...
Smashed between some
big pans, what do I see?
A monster burger
for me to eat!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Here it comes!
The most terrifying
triple attack!
The most horrifying
hamburger!
Feh! Feh-feh-feh!
[ITOMIMIZU] It seems hopeless
for the Straw Hats,
but I can't help but think
that the Groggy Monsters
might get handed a red card
for such a flagrant
violation of the rules!
[ITOMIMIZU] But look at that!
What a coincidence!
The referee
just happens to be
doing some
stretches right now!
Oh well! He can't
catch everything!
I'm gonna make
you turn around!
Luffy, no!
Why not?!
'Cause they want
you to get mad,
so you'll butt in and
do something stupid!
We just gotta grin
and bear it, Luffy!
[ITOMIMIZU]
The preparations are complete!
All that's left now is to
sit back and enjoy the carnage!
Whatever happens from
here on out, don't blame me!
Anyway, looks like they're
going straight for the ball man.
Unless he acts fast,
he'll be ground and pounded,
sliced and diced, trashed and
smashed into a burger patty.
[SANJI] All right, then.
If you want a cooking
battle, you got one.
Though I gotta warn you,
I've never cooked
scumbags before,
so I can't say
how it'll turn out.
You are mincemeat!
Troisième...
Huh?
...Haché!
Bouquetiere... Shoot!
[PICKLES]
Stop crushing!
No! Hamburg!
Huh?
You're gonna pay for that!
Hold up fatty.
Forget about me?
Outta my way,
small-fry! I'll cut you!
No Sword Style...
Tatsu... Maki!
Huh?
Aahh!
[ITOMIMIZU] Oh no!
Say it isn't so!
Big Pan has fallen victim to
Pickles' spinning blade attack!
Somebody help me,
I can't stop spinning!
Bad Manner...
...Kick Course!
Wha-Wha-What?!
Not only did they
knock Big Pan down,
they knocked him
right back up, too!
Although Big Pan is
indeed on his feet,
I'm not sure if he has any
idea where he's at right now.
To make matters worse,
Pickles is looking
pretty dazed, himself.
Team Foxy is in a real pinch!
Uh-oh! Now Zoro from the
Straw Hats is charging in!
Will he be able to overtake Big
Pan in his state of confusion?!
[PICKLES]
You're not getting past me!
[CROWD cries out in fear]
I've had enough of your crap
and that goes for the ref, too.
[ITOMIMIZU]
The crowd or rather the ref
takes a direct hit
from the flying Pickles!
Did Sanji have an
ulterior motive, perhaps?
You did that...
...on... purpose, didn't you?
Red card... Huh?
Wait a sec my whistle
and my cards they're gone.
Heh heh...
You're such a naughty girl.
What can I say?
Old habits die hard.
Oh! This is bad!
Here they go again!
With victory in their grasp,
the Straw Hats turn on
each other! What a shame!
Armée de l'Air... Power Shoot!
In-cred-ible! Big Pan.
What?!
No way!
[ITOMIMIZU]
The massive Wotan warrior.
[STRAW HAT PIRATES]
All right!
[ITOMIMZU] They're
headed for the goal ring!
It can't be!
AAAAAAhHHH!
[CROWD gasps]
[ITOMIMIZU]
Goal!
Incredible! Big Pan...
...is airborne!
[STRAW HAT PIRATES]
All right!
It can't be!
AAAAAAhHHH!
[CROWD gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
[ITOMIMIZU] It goes in!
Goal! Goal! Goal!
Wooo! Yeah! Way to go!!
Yeah! All right!
We won! Ha! We won!
I'm so happy!
Waaaah!!! You won!!
Aww...! No fair...!
He's mine! You can't have him!
Zoro! Sanji, Thank you!
Whoa! Awesome!
Those guys are amazing!
Bravo! Bravo!
Aw man.
I'm moved to tears!
Give it your best in
the third round too.
Shut up! Whose side are
you on anyway you traitors!
Grrrr...
I can't believe this.
Nobody's ever beaten
the Groggy Monsters!
[NAMI]
Oh, hi, Ref. Wakey-wakey.
Hey! You better make
your call! Go ahead! Here!
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, that last move
was a flagrant foul
if I've ever seen one!
He's outta the game!
[whistle]
[ITOMIMIZU] And that's
the final whistle!
There you have it, folks,
the Groggy Ring Match
is officially over!
[cheers]
[fireworks booms]
Waaah!!
Yeah! They did it!
Yeeeeeaaaahhh!!
Nice work! You're a real pro!
[ITOMIMIZU]
It's the end of an era!
The Groggy Monsters
have finally been dethroned
as the kings of the Ring!
Our new champions, and
winners of the second round
are Zoro and Sanji of
the Straw Hat Pirates!
[CROWD cheers]
Hahahahaha!
What did ya think would happen?
Like our guys would
ever lose to you!
Hey, Nami! Hey, Robin!
Was I great? Huh? Was I?
You were just wonderful.
You're nothing but a jerk!
Don't scare me like that!
Hey! Hey! Stop!
I'm so glad you followed
my plan after all!
You really think you had
something to do with this?
Chirp, chirp, chirp!
Now, as I'm
sure you all know
at the end of the fight our
winners the Straw Hat Pirates
can claim their
hard-earned prize!
Will they take a
member of Foxy's Crew
or will they take
his Jolly Roger?
Either way,
it's up to their captain
and their captain alone!
Now, drumroll please!
Well the choice
is obvious, isn't it?
Huh? You mean
he's gonna pick me?!
I get it. They want
me, don't they?
They've wanted me
this whole time!
My heart...
My heart isn't ready
to say farewell yet!
Oh no, he's
looking this way!
He's gonna take
me I know it!
I bet it'll be me.
So long, guys.
I don't wanna go!
I'll put a smile on
my face for my friends,
even if I'm crying
on the inside.
Curses! Why do I have
to be so lovable?!
Come on Luffy, please.
Okay! I choose...
[NAMI]
Hold on a sec!
What's up, Nami?
[NAMI] Think about it
their boss is probably
gonna take part in
the next round, right?
Yeah?
[NAMI] We've already seen
what his Slow-Slow Beam can do.
If he fights, we won't
stand a chance in any game,
no matter what the rules are!
So, the answer is obvious.
If Foxy is gonna be our
biggest threat in round 3,
then we should recruit him,
so we have the advantage.
Sure, we'd all like
to get Chopper back
but if we end up
losing the next round,
then they'll probably
take him right back
and our win
would go to waste.
And since his crew
will be dumbstruck
when they lose
their precious boss,
we'll stomp 'em no problem
and claim Chopper
in round three.
Then we're guaranteed to
keep him for good. Get it?
[gasps]
No...! Say it isn't so...!
They're really gonna
take our Captain away?!
But... that's the
Peanut Strategy!
You guys're the
lowest of the low!
Go home, lousy Peanutters!
Are you afraid
to fight us fair?!
[ITOMIMIZU] Although there's
no rule against this strategy,
it certainly seems
a bit underhanded...!
A little cheating is
expected of pirates,
but suddenly taking
a crew's captain away
in the middle of a
game is no different
than running from a fight!
Shame! Shame on
you Straw Hats
and shame on the
heartless devil of a woman
who came up
with this plan!
You're truly a
nefarious navigator, Nami!
How dare you talk
trash about Nami!
I oughta filet you punks!
[ITOMIMIZU] In the long
history of Davy Back Fights,
no one has ever
had the audacity
to pull such a
lousy, no good stunt!
So, What do you say, men?
You can't call a
win against a crew
with no captain a
true victory, can you?
[CROWD]
No!
After swearing on
Davy Jones' name,
is it right to
throw away your honor
as a pirate just
to win a match?!
[CROWD]
No!
[NAMI sobs]
Why are they so mean?!
Well, even if it doesn't
go against the rules,
it does seem to go against some
of their pirate sensibilities.
[CROWD]
Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts!
Shut up! You guys
are making me mad.
I'm with
Nami on this one!
I dunno.
I think they're right.
Nami, why don't you
grow a backbone?
You're just making a
big fuss because you lost.
How 'bout you shut up
and deal with it?
Yes, ma'am, we're sorry!
[ITOMIMIZU] Underhanded
witch though she is,
the girl is right!
Monkey D. Luffy is the
captain of the winning team,
so it's up to him to decide
how this battle will unfold!
That is to say, he's
free to choose anyone
he likes including Foxy himself.
This is it! He's
picking me for sure!
It's not so bad.
I'm sure I'll have
fun sailing with them.
No matter how you slice it,
I'm the only choice
that makes sense.
Don't look at me! Please!
I know I'm handsome
but I don't want to go!
So they're gonna
pick me, huh?
I knew these
guys were cool!
Can I leave my friends behind?
How will they go on without me?
Oh no, how is Foxy
ever gonna replace me?
Straw Hat you little punk.
[thinking] You're really
gonna choose me, aren't you?
Yes, it's obvious. That was
probably your plan all along.
Farewell, Foxy Pirates.
Farewell, my wonderful crew!
I'll say goodbye with
a smile on my face.
I owe you that much, at least.
If having such a
charming personality
and stunning looks is a sin,
then I accept my punishment!
Those poor Straw Hats
really need a poster boy
for their crew.
I can't blame them
for wanting me.
I can't blame
anyone for wanting me!
Say, just a quick thought.
That plan of yours
although it would
give us a big advantage
you realize it would also
make Foxy a part of our crew.
Uh...
Yeah, I think I'll pass.
Oh! Our sweet captain's
heart has been crushed
under the weight of
those cruel words!
It's one thing
to turn him down,
but did they have
to do it like that?
Aww! It's okay.
Even if they don't
want you, we still do!
You're always welcome here!
[FOXY]
Do you mean it?
Nobody makes fun of our
boss and gets away with it!
Yeah, you'll see!
We'll get 'em next round!
We won't let you
down, boss. I promise!
We love you!
[thinking]
You guys. Thank you.
I promise I'll never leave!
You're the only crew for me!
Cut the crap, will ya?
[ITOMIMIZU] Now that
the Straw Hats are done
emotionally abusing our
boss, it's time for them
to make their decision!
Come on! Don't leave us
in suspense any longer!
Fine. In that case, there's
someone I wanna take back.
Shelly!
Huh?
[ITOMIMIZU]
What a turn of events!
The captain of the
Straw Hats has chosen Shelly,
a horse that
Captain Foxy picked up
on a whim after
coming to this island!
Is this pure genius
or just plain idiocy?!
Do you have any
idea what you did,
you sorry excuse
for a captain?!
Yeah, of course.
Listen, I know you
didn't like my Foxy plan,
but this is seriously
a bajillion times worse!
Okay, but could you stop pulling
my face like that, please?
Did you hear that,
little Choppy?
Looks like you get to
stay with us after all!
Feh-feh-feh!
[NAMI] I know I told
you not to pick Chopper,
but I wouldn't
have said
that if I thought
you'd pick some horse!
[LUFFY] Seriously,
stop pulling my face.
[LUFFY]
There you go, Stilts Guy.
Now you have your horse
back once and for all.
[TONJIT]
How can I thank you?
[LUFFY] Seeing you
together is thanks enough.
Hey, your friends
don't look so good.
That last match was a real
doozy you sure they're okay?
I blame it all on that
loser with the crazy eyebrows.
Huh?
[TONJIT] They certainly
are lively, aren't they?
Hahahaha!
This means so much.
Really, thank you.
I told you, it's fine!
Don't sweat it.
[laughs]
Good girl!
[sighs]
Well, guess
I can't blame him.
Yeah. That is totally
what I would've done.
Let me repay your
kindness by treating you
to some cheese
back at my house.
Not in a million years!
[chuckles]
It's your loss. Suit yourself.
[neighs]
Shelly says "thanks," too.
Heh heh heh...
Just keep off
the stilts, okay?
Are you sure
about this, though?
What about your
little reindeer friend?
Yeah, you jerk!
How do you think he feels
being left with those weirdoes?
[sniffles]
Luffy.
Poor little guy.
Chopper, I'm sorry.
I know this is hard on you
but no matter what, I promise
we'll win the next game
and get you back! So hang
on a little longer, okay?
I know you can take it.
[sniiiiff]
After all, you're a man, right?
You bet I am!
[chuckle]
That's our Chopper.
Leave it to me little pal,
you'll be just fine.
If you're Chopper's
last hope. He's screwed.
Eh-heh!
I wonder what the
next game is going to be.
Hmph! Whatever it is,
I'm ready for it.
Hahahaha...!
We're gonna have Chopper
back on the crew in no time!
♪ ending song ♪
[ITOMIMIZU] Game number
three is the Roller Skate Race
a five-round match
on our special track!
[NAMI]
I'm so cute,
they're gonna pick me
for sure if they win!
[USOPP]
I say let 'em.
[FOXY]
You're no match for us!
Why, you ask? Because.
[LUFFY]
Okay, guys, let's do this!
We're gonna
get Chopper back!
[CREW]
Yeah!
[FOXY]
Ignored again, huh?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece :
"Round 3! The
Round-and-Round Roller Race!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!