[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[USOPP] "I've decided
to set out on my own
and visit Elbaf!"
"No! Please don't go!
We need you to stay!"
"I was just kidding!
I totally understand
not wanting
to live your lives without me."
"So, does that mean
you're staying, Usopp?"
[USOPP laughing]
Of course I will, dummies!
Man! I didn't know
anybody could love someone
as much as you guys love me!
What the hell's he
doing? What an idiot.
Whoa!
[FRANKY] Hurry it up,
Yokozuna! I need you over here!
[YOKOZUNA]
Gero, gero!
[ICEBERG]
Over here, too!
[YOKOZUNA]
Gero, gero!
[FRANKY grunting]
[metal scraping]
[hammar banging]
[PAULIE grunts] Damn it,
I'm having a hard time
keeping up with those two.
But I guess that's
Tom's Workers for ya.
[LULU]
No kidding.
It's an honor to see
Iceberg at work like this,
but Franky's pretty
impressive, too.
To think he had
all that talent...
[TILESTONE] I feel like
I gotta start my training
all over again!
[PAULIE] There's no use
in thinkin' like that.
We gotta step up our game
and show 'em what
Dock 1 is made of!
[TILESTONE, LULU]
Right!
[PAULIE grunts]
Lookin' nice, you guys!
Keep up the good work!
[GONBE] Meow, meow!
[KOKORO sighs]
[ICEBERG chuckles]
[FRANKY]
What're you laughin' about?
[ICEBERG]
Mwell...
Working with you
really brings me back.
When I think about all
those little battleships
you used to make
here on Scrap Island,
I can't help but chuckle.
Yeah, well you weren't
chucklin' back then.
If I recall, you were
pretty pissed off.
[ICEBERG]
That's true.
And after what
happened with Tom,
I felt justified in
those feelings as well.
But when I see this,
I understand.
All that experience wasn't
a waste of time after all.
It was preparing you
to build this ship.
[FRANKY grunts]
If you say so.
[ICEBERG]
When it's all said and done,
I suppose he's still
Tom's apprentice.
[FRANKY]
Hm?
With a ship like this,
sailing to the New World
will be more than a dream.
Just like Tom would say.
You did it with real gusto.
[FRANKY]
Iceberg...
[KOKORO]
Oh, it warms my heart
to see those two working
together for once.
[ICEBERG grunts]
[FRANKY] Ow!
Idiot! Don't you know
you're not supposed
to be goofin' around right now?
We got real ships to work
on, not your crappy toys!
Don't yell at me when
you don't have a clue
what you're talkin'
about, Ice-for-brains!
[ICEBERG]
That Franky's got a lotta nerve.
If I were you, I'd kick him
out for what he just did!
Mwell, I know the boy
can be a handful,
but he's a fellow shipbuilder.
At his young age,
he's almost on par with the
best craftsmen on the island.
He does build battleships, yeah.
His problem is he's too honest.
I'm positive that
both of you boys
are gonna grow up to be
world-class
shipwrights someday.
There's no need
for you to be rivals.
If we can keep this up,
we should be able to finish
way ahead of schedule.
[FRANKY]
Iceberg,
I told you before, this isn't
an ordinary pirate ship.
Yes, I know that.
For you, this is
an opportunity to--
[FRANKY]
Will you let me finish?
This is a ship for
the Straw Hat Pirates.
They're not a bunch
of random upstarts;
they're a group that declared
war on the World Government,
and burned down their flag.
And you're not just any
old shipwright, either.
You're also the mayor
of Water 7, remember?
If people knew you
helped build this ship.
It would put you in a
pretty sticky situation.
You understand the
consequences, don't ya?
[ICEBERG] I do. But I can
worry about that later.
Besides, Tom said it himself.
The ship you build
is just a ship.
[TOM]
Franky, there's no such thing
as blueprints for a pirate ship.
It's the flag, boy.
Skull and bones
means pirate ship,
and a seagull flag
means that it's Navy.
[TOM] Whatever you build,
just remember this:
Build it with pride, and a
whole lot of manly gusto!
[ICEBERG]
That's what I believe.
And when we build
a ship at Galley-La,
that's the mantra that
our company follows.
I'm not making
a pirate ship.
[FRANKY]
Hm?
[ICEBERG] I'm helping a
friend achieve his dream.
No matter how you look at it,
that's the only reason I'm here.
[FRANKY] Maybe you
should ask your friend
how he feels before you
butt in, Ice-for-brains!
[KOKORO laughing]
[ICEBERG] You may have
changed your life,
you may have changed your
face and rebuilt your body,
but you're the same
person I've always known.
The same old friend.
[FRANKY]
My dream, huh?
Give me Tom back!
[train whistling]
You hear me?
Stop now, sea train!
[FRANKY]
Tom...
[FRANKY] I don't want
to build ships anymore.
I can't love ships
that hurt the people
I care so much about!
I won't do it!
But even so...
My goal in life is
to be just like you!
[FRANKY grunting]
[FRANKY]
Come back!
Come back and
teach me once again!
[train whistling]
[FRANKY]
Because someday,
I want to build
my own dream ship!
A ship that will proudly sail,
bravely over uncharted waters,
all the way to the
ends of the world!
[train whistling]
[FRANKY]
I'm beat.
My body's burning up.
I'm still alive,
but at this rate,
I won't be for long.
[FRANKY gasps]
[ship creaking]
[FRANKY]
Nobody's here.
An abandoned ship, full of
broken wood and scrap iron.
Funny, huh? I fit right in.
I gotta do something about
this useless body of mine,
or I'm not gonna make it.
[ICEBERG]
Mwell, maybe.
But anyway, what's up with that
strange looking body of yours?
[FRANKY]
Screw you!
The sea train mangled my body,
so in order to stay alive,
I rebuilt it using
some iron scraps.
[ICEBERG]
We never change, do we?
Every time we meet face to face,
we yell and argue
with each other.
I won't forgive you,
and you may feel the
same way about me, too.
Franky...
[ICEBERG sobbing]
I'm-- I'm really--
I'm so glad that
you're still alive.
[ICEBERG sobbing]
[FRANKY]
Glad I'm alive, huh?
Well, don't go
wishin' I was dead
when the government
comes after you.
It's outta my hands now!
Jeez, my skull's made of iron
and you're more
hard-headed than me!
[USOPP]
Oh, hey there, Luffy!
I never expected to
run into you here!
What, me? Oh, I'm just
takin' a walk, that's all!
I guess that
settles it, huh?
Since we're already here,
I might as well
join the crew again!
All right, and that one
makes scenario number 53.
I like it, but I have
to make it look like
I run into him by coincidence.
That's a little risky.
Maybe I should take
a more direct approach.
All right, let's go for it!
[USOPP grunts]
[USOPP]
Whoa, what's going on in there?
Everyone looks so serious!
Well, I can't blame them;
I'd be upset without me, too.
For their sake,
I'd better join this crew
again before it gets ugly!
Scenario 34!
Ah-choo! Ah-choo!
[USOPP] I'll warm their hearts
from the chilling evening wind.
I just gotta make sure
they heard me sneeze.
This is it!
I can't blow it now!
Just play it cool and pretend
like it's all a coincidence!
"Oh, is that Usopp
I see over there?"
"Hey, I just happened
to be passing by!"
"That's no good at all!
It's chilly out there!
You better come inside
before you catch a cold!"
"Well, if you insist.
And what's that?
You want me to
join the crew again?
I guess I might as well,
since I'm already here and all!
Lemme tell ya,
it's great to be ba--!"
They went to sleep.
[USOPP sighs]
I better come up
with something fast,
or they just might
finish that ship
and take off without me.
It's so much easier to talk to
them when I'm Sniper King.
All right. I'll try harder.
I'll come up with an
even better scenario!
One that will melt
their hearts for sure!
[ZAMBAI]
Hey, Big Bro,
we brought some grub
for you to chow down on!
The guys from Galley-La
can have some, too!
And don't worry,
we've got plenty of cola
to wash it down with!
Yeah! Better hurry and drink
it while it's still cold!
[CHIMNEY] Yay!
[GONBE] Meow, meow!
[CHIMNEY] Bring it over
here first, I'm starving!
Any booze? I'm starting
to run a little dry!
Let Franky and
Iceberg eat first.
They've been at this
longer than us.
You two are going to pass out
if you don't take a break.
You don't have to worry about
us falling behind schedule.
Yeah, we'll cover for
you in the meantime.
[ICEBERG] All right, but we
might eat it all, you know.
If you think I'm a
good shipwright now,
once I get some cola in me,
I'll blow your pants off!
[ALL munching]
[FRANKY]
Recharge Complete!
Franky Pose Time!
[KIWI]
Max Power!
[MOZU]
Super!
Oh, by the way...
What'll you do when
the ship is done?
[FRANKY]
What'll I do?
If you give your ship
away to the Straw Hats,
are you sure that
you'll be satisfied?
Is that what your
dream is about?
Will it be fulfilled so easily?
Perhaps you should
go with them.
Surely you've considered that.
[FRANKY FAMILY gasps]
All my bros
are in Water 7.
No matter how awesome it is,
it's gonna take more than
a ship to get me to leave!
[ICEBERG]
I see.
[FRANKY FAMILY]
You mean it?
[FRANKY]
C'mon, back to work!
Yokozuna, you can
take a breather for now.
[YOKOZUNA]
Gero.
[ICEBERG]
Paulie, take 15.
[PAULIE groans]
[LULU grunts]
[TILESTONE groans]
[PAULIE groaning] This food is
starin' me right in the face,
but I'm so tired, I don't think
I have the strength to eat it.
[TILESTONE]
Look at us,
we can't even eat hotdogs
as well as those two.
[LULU]
It's depressing.
[FRANKY FAMILY]
We're cheerin' for you, Bro!
[FRANKY FAMILY] As soon as
you're done building the ship,
we're gonna throw a big party,
just like the Straw Hats did!
[MOZU]
An even bigger party!
[KIWI]
The biggest!
[FRANKY]
Even if it wasn't for long,
I had a lotta fun
with you guys.
[LUFFY] We'll save
you, no matter what!
[FRANKY] That's why I'm gonna
pass on my dream to you.
Nothing'd make me happier.
You wait, Straw Hat,
I swear I'll make you the best
damn ship you've ever seen,
just like I promised!
Big Bro...
[hammars banging]
[FRANKY FAMILY snoring]
[KOKORO giggles]
[PAULIE grunting]
[FRANKY]
Hey, Ice-for-brains!
I know you're gettin' tired--
Why don't you
take a beauty nap?
[ICEBERG]
Why don't you take a nap?
I don't need sleep!
'Cause I'm doin' super
good this evening.
Well, what do you
know? So am I!
[FRANKY]
Heh!
[ICEBERG]
Hm!
[KOKORO]
I hope you're watching, Tom.
It's been a rocky
road without you,
but your boys are
doing you proud.
You might've left us, but
watching these two right now
is like seeing the ships
you built come alive again.
[KOKORO chuckling]
[hammars banging]
[NAMI]
It's finally set!
Look, the Log Pose is
pointing to the next island!
[LUFFY] All that's left
is to get our ship!
This is gonna be fun!
[NAMI] I can't wait
to see the ship, myself.
But Franky said no peeking
until he's finished.
By the way, guys.
You know where that
log is pointing?
Might come as a big surprise
if you're not ready!
[NAMI]
Actually, I don't have a clue.
Come to think of it,
it kind of looks like
it's pointing down a bit.
[KOKORO laughing]
You bet it is!
'Cause where it's pointing is
on the bottom of the ocean!
It's called Fish-Man Island.
Uh--
Huh?
What?
We're finally going
to Fish-Man island?
Really?
Whoa! Sanji's acting weird!
[NAMI sighs]
Fish-Man Island, huh?
That's tricky.
[LUFFY]
Yeah, I guess so.
Is that gonna be tough after
what happened in your village?
They were pirates.
Not all Fish-Men are gonna
give us trouble like that.
[SANJI] See? Everybody knows
Fish-Man Island is awesome,
even Zoro! And he's stupid!
Fish-Man Island is one
of the most famous spots
on the whole Grand Line!
Beautiful mermaids
leap and dive,
painting the water with
their elegant tailfins.
There you can
frolic with the fish
and make all your
dreams come true!
Wow, for real? Neato!
[KOKORO]
Ahem.
[KOKORO chuckles]
[SANJI]
Let me dream, damn it!
I'm not hurting anyone!
Relax! There's young
mermaids, too!
Thing is, even if the
place is nice to visit,
that don't mean it's easy
for people to get there!
[ROBIN] I assumed
that was the case,
since it's at the
bottom of the sea.
[LUFFY] Eh, we'll figure
it out on the way.
Well, "on the way"
is a problem, too.
[KOKORO] Take a look at today's
paper and you'll understand.
Huh? What is this?
14 ships have disappeared
this month alone.
All in the same place?
I don't understand.
They call that patch of
water the Florian Triangle.
[KOKORO] Anyways, you won't be
making it to Fish-Man Island
until after you
sail through there.
[LUFFY gasps]
[NAMI gasps]
[KOKORO] Every year, over 100
ships go missing in that area,
and nobody has a clue as to why.
What's spooky is that later
they show up totally empty,
without a single
crew member in sight.
Other people say they've
found ghost ships,
with crews of dead men wandering
the ocean, lost in a haze.
You mean they're
like zombies? Scary!
Hanging out with a buncha
skeletons sounds cool!
"Hanging out?" That's some
imagination you've got.
No way! No ghost ships
for us! Not on my watch!
We're passing straight
through that place!
I mean, what really
happens in there?
[KOKORO laughing]
Who knows!
After all, nobody ever
comes out of there alive
and dead men tell no tales!
I'd be careful!
The water is dark,
the fog is thick.
It swallows you up!
[NAMI, CHOPPER shrieking]
Many a soul has
been a sacrificed
to that treacherous sea.
So you'd better be darned
ready before you even
think of setting sail.
Although some people do
call them ghost ships,
abandoned vessels are often
called "treasure ships", too.
We're more likely to
find a ship filled with
riches than the undead.
Yeah! Let's hunt down
those ghost ships!
All right, leave it to me!
No, but I don't wanna!
I'll stock up on plenty of
food and water before we go,
so even if we do get
lost, we'll be fine.
A treasure ship, huh?
I wonder if they have swords.
[CHIMNEY]
Hey, Pirate people!
[GONBE]
Meow!
[KIWI, MOZU]
Straw Hat!
[KIWI, MOZU grunt, panting]
[LUFFY]
You need something?
Franky wants to
talk to you guys.
He's got something
big to show you!
It's been a long night,
but they finished
his ship of dreams!
And boy is it super cool!
Meow!
You mean it's done already?
That was really fast!
[MOZU]
Of course!
That's what happens
when the best shipwrights
in the world work
around the clock!
[KIWI]
You better believe it!
What're we waiting
for? Let's go!
Yeah!
[ZAMBAI]
Straw Hat!
We've got bad news!
[KIWI]
Oh, hey you guys!
[MOZU]
What's going on?
They look upset.
[KIWI]
I wonder what's wrong.
[ZAMBAI grunting, panting]
To be honest,
we just found out
about this ourselves.
Have you seen
the wanted posters?
Wanted posters?
[ZAMBAI] You've got a huge
bounty on your head, Straw Hat!
They're gonna hunt
you down for sure!
Actually, you've
all got bounties.
The whole crew is wanted!
Took long enough! How much?
Not me, too!
I'm wanted?
No point in talking, just look.
Wanted posters for
all seven of you.
[ZAMBAI] Straw Hat Luffy with
a bounty of 300 million Berries.
[LUFFY laughing]
All right! It went up!
[ZAMBAI]
Pirate Hunter Zoro with a bounty
of 120 million Berries.
[ZORO grunts]
[ZAMBAI] Cat Burglar Nami with
a bounty of 16 million Berries.
No!
[ZAMBAI] Cotton-Candy
Loving Chopper. Pet.
With a bounty of 50 Berries.
50?
[ZAMBAI] Demon Child Robin with
a bounty of 80 million Berries.
Who is that?
[ZAMBAI] Black Leg Sanji.
Attempt to take a photo failed.
Bounty: 77 million Berries.
[NAMI groans]
Hey look, Sniper King
has one, too!
Only 50?
Well I know that this
is probably big news
for you and all, and I'm
sure there's a lot of
pirate stuff you want
to talk about, but uh,
hold on a sec okay?
I came here 'cause I gotta
favor to ask of you guys.
Take a look at this.
It's Franky!
[ZAMBAI] Cyborg Franky, with
a bounty of 44 million Berries.
[KIWI] This is awful, Big Bro's
wanted by the World Government!
[MOZU]
What're we gonna do now?
[ZAMBAI]
Yeah, that's the question.
I was happy when I found
out we didn't have bounties.
But then this had to happen!
Everyone in the whole
city knows about our bro.
He can't stay
in Water 7 anymore!
And if he gets arrested again.
I don't think we'll
have the power
to save him like
we did last time!
But I'm sure he's
worried about us, too.
Knowing him, he probably
wouldn't leave the island
no matter how much
we begged him.
That's why we came to you.
We have no other choice!
We're begging ya
here, Straw Hat.
Even if he tries to fight,
you gotta take our bro
out to sea with you!
Come on! His parents were
pirates it's in his blood!
[LUFFY] Okay, take us
to the new ship already!
I can't wait anymore,
I'm too excited!
[CHOPPER]
Oh! That's it, Luffy!
Look! It's huge!
[LUFFY laughing] Whoa, you're
right! Hey, but where's Franky?
Franky!
On the next One Piece:
The King of Animals
that Overlooks the Sea!
The Dream Ship
Magnificently Completed!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!