Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary
treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue.
The crew will cut a path
across the Grand Line
to the New World!
[NARRATOR] After being
separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue
his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the
government prison, Impel Down.
Along the way, he ran
into Buggy the Clown,
as well as Mr. 3,
a former Baroque Works agent.
Together, they descended into
the depths of the prison.
[MR. 3] This is Level 3,
The Starvation Hell.
In other words, let's move while
we have the sweat to spare.
Okay. Then let's go
to Level 4 already.
[MR. 3, BUGGY]
Seriously?
[SPHINX]
Spaghetti.
[LEVEL 3 GUARD 431C]
The Sphinx is awake!
[SPHINX]
Deep fried noodles!
Gum-Gum. Gatling!
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Boa Hancock,
who helped Luffy
break into Impel Down,
drew ever closer to the floor
where Ace is
being held prisoner.
[BON CLAY]
♪ Un. Deux. Ora!
Hey. Who's that singing?
[BON CLAY]
♪ Un. Deux. Ora!
♪ Un. Deux. Krah!
[MR. 3 yells]
[LUFFY]
"The Unleashed Swan!
A Reunion with Bon Clay!"
[BON CLAY]
♪ Oh, come my way!
♪ Oh-Oh-Oh, come my way!
♪ Yeah, Yeah!
♪ Oh, come my way!
[BUGGY panting] I can
barely stand in this heat,
but that guy's singing
like he's at somebody's
birthday party.
If he's a prisoner here,
he must be tough as hell.
[MR. 3 panting]
[MR. 3] I know this voice.
I know this song.
Hey, partner. I think
this guy can help us out.
[MR. 3] Wait! What?
Let's discuss this first!
[BON CLAY]
♪ Oh, come my way!
♪ Spin! Spin!
Keep it up, boys!
♪ Spin and spin
♪ like you're caught up
in the tide of the times! ♪
Hurry! This way!
Wait! Listen.
I don't think... we should.
[PRISONERS yawn]
C'mon lazybones, the party's
just getting started!
If you think it's
steamy in here now,
you'll really hate
it when I'm angry!
Huh?
Oh! Mr. 3! How are you?
[BON CLAY giggles]
[MR. 3]
Well, this is awkward.
[BUGGY sputters]
[BON CLAY humming]
Uh...!
What the--? Mr. 3?
Wait just a minute here!
What are you
doing in Impel Down?
You're behind bars, so you
must've been caught, right?
No, no.
I'm the one who's
behind bars, aren't I?
How did you like my
one-of-a-kind double take?
It's a kenpo
special technique called
"Looking Back on
that Autumn Night's Dream."
Hey, what the hell
is this strange creature?
Hard to say.
Let's be sure to not let it out.
[BON CLAY]
Aw, don't be mean!
I've got way too much energy
to stay cooped up in here!
[footsteps]
[LUFFY panting]
How hot's it gonna get?
Whatever.
As long as I keep going down,
I'm sure I'll find where
they've got Ace sooner or later.
[LUFFY yells]
[handcuffs clanking]
[BON CLAY]
He headed downstairs?
You're sure of that?
You saw him go?
[BON CLAY] You're not
pulling my tail, are you?
Heh, no!
Of course not.
[BON CLAY] Very well and
thank you ever so much
for letting me out
of that cell, Mr. 3!
I'll pay you back sometime.
--[MR. 3] Huh?
--[BON CLAY] Now then.
I'm on my way, my friend!
Oh, come my way!
All the way to hell and back!
That worked out
well for everyone.
Mmhmm.
[alarm beeping]
[DAIGIN]
Our security here is legendary.
How was he able
to slip through?
And though he's
just one invader,
if we let him rescue Ace,
not only will it be the ultimate
humiliation for Impel Down,
but for the entire
World Government!
We can't let that happen!
In the name of
Navy Headquarters,
we're gonna head
into that prison
and stop Straw Hat Luffy,
no matter what it takes!
[MARINES]
Sir!
Hold on a moment.
[MARINES]
Huh?
[DAIGIN]
Wh-Who goes there?
I'm Mistress Sadie,
our torture expert.
We've already been compromised,
so accepting the help
of the Navy
would just further disgrace
the good name of Impel Down.
[MARINES]
Uh...
"Mistress"? Really?
What, does she think
she's being cute or somethin'?
[SADIE]
I'm adorable!
You will refer to
me as "Mistress"!
[MARINE screams]
[SADIE moans]
Those screams are irresistible!
Why, you--!
[DAIGIN]
Hold it!
Are you telling me you
don't need the Navy's aid?
Yes.
This whole prison is
a labyrinthine hell.
If you don't know
your way around in here,
you'll be of no help to us.
[SADIE]
That being said,
if you wish to serve us,
you can guard the outside.
[SADIE] This drawbridge
is the only entrance.
We'll secure ourselves
inside, raise it and...
[SADIE moans] ...seal off
Impel Down completely!
We'll do our job.
And as long as you
do yours, nobody...
{SADIE moans] ...will escape
from this prison alive.
Fair enough.
We'll remain here and
guard the gate, then.
There. That's a good boy.
Is that a...?
No way...
Koala?
A koala?
Sure is.
[DAIGIN] Impel Down is
now completely sealed off.
Huh?
[DAIGIN]
A koala?
[footsteps]
[PRISONER 432A]
Hannyabal?
Yeah, and Magellan's here, too.
What's goin' on?
Hmm...
[HANNYABAL] You've got
a special visitor, Ace.
Behave yourself.
You'll never guess who it is.
Jimbei.
[HANNYABAL]
You know her well,
but even you've never met her.
Maybe I should give
Ace here a hint?
Her name is notorious,
but she never shows herself.
She leads a tribe of
warriors called the Kuja.
And she's one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
The Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
Hmm?
Yay! It's Hancock!
Check her out!
Hey, quick question:
When I become Warden
will you do me the honor
of being my beautiful bride?
Marry me!
Ouch!
When I'm warden,
I'll hit on her all I want.
I mean, sorry Warden,
you can hit me all you want.
That's enough of
your tomfoolery!
Wooo! Holy crap!
Guys, am I seeing things?
She's gorgeous!
[PRISONER 432D] So she's
the Snake Princess of the Kuja?
Hey! Move a little closer!
[PRISONER 432E]
Turn around, Hancock!
[PRISONER 432F]
Yeah, That is some choice meat!
[PRISONER 432G]
Hey, hot stuff!
Come to our cell!
We'll give you
some tender lovin'
like you've never had before!
[PRISONER 432H]
Damn! She smells amazing!
If I ever get out of here,
I'm goin' straight
to Amazon Lily!
[PRISONER 432I] I heard
it's full of hot naked chicks!
Count me in!
[PRISONERS chanting]
What is it?
What do you want from me?
Nothing, really.
I simply wanted to take
a good look at you.
To see the cause of the war
I will take part in first-hand.
That's all.
[ACE] Am I everything
you'd hoped for?
[JIMBEI growls]
[PRISONER 432K]
Come on, Hancock!
Don't ignore us like that!
[PRISONER 432L]
Get over here and gimme some!
[PRISONER 432L laughs]
In the past, you've
always been the empress
who stood her ground
and disobeyed every summons.
Yet you're going to
take part in this war?
[JIMBEI chuckles] I hope your
title is worth your dignity!
A pleasure to meet you, too.
Now mind your foolish tongue.
Oh, man, I wanna
lick her everywhere!
They're trying to talk!
Keep it down, you damned louts!
Can it, Magellan!
Or should I say "Diarrhea Man"?
[PRISONER 432M laughs]
Nice one!
Say, Snake Princess!
I bet the women on your island
are hungry for guys like us!
Hey, you!
Why don't you make
Hannyabal the Warden!
[DOMINO]
Really now?
Come on, Hancock!
Move that sexy ass
over to our cell already!
I'll only say this once.
[PRISONER 432N]
Hancock look at me!
If you keep accosting me
with those coarse voices.
I'll get... scared!
[PRISONERS]
Wooo!
[PRISONER 432O]
I can't take it!
[PRISONER 432P]
She's so cute!
She's perfect!
Let us have her,
Diarrhea Man!
If there's a more vile
place in this world,
I don't want to see it.
This makes me sick.
Everyone's calling
you "Diarrhea Man."
And you just put up
with it? It's disgraceful.
If that's your attitude,
I know a guy who'd
love to have your job.
So cute!
Diarrhea Man! For shame!
[MAGELLAN growls]
Enough.
She's hot!
Let me have her for
myself, Diarrhea Man!
Diarrhea Man!
Let me show her my snake!
[MAGELLAN]
I won't tolerate
your impertinence any longer.
This ends now.
No! Warden Magellan!
Wait a second, please!
You're gonna kill us, too!
[PRISONERS whimpering]
[HANNYABAL whimpering]
You are going to suffer.
No... No!
We're dead!
You degenerates seem to
have forgotten your place.
[MAGELLAN] Let me remind you
who the boss is around here!
Man, he is pissed!
[PRISONERS whimper]
[PRISONER 432U]
He's brought out the Hydra!
[HANNYABAl whimpers]
[PRISONER 432V]
Wait! What are you doing?
[PRISONER 432W]
Warden Magellan! Stop! Please!
[PRISONER 432X] Come on!
We were just jokin' around!
Honest!
[PRISONER 432X screams]
[MAGELLAN growls]
[PRISONERS scream]
[PRISONERS gasp]
No. You bastard!
You can't do this to me!
[PRISONER 432X]
Wow, sorry buddy.
You're a dead man now.
Dammit!
I need the antidote!
Help me!
[PRISONER 432Y screams]
Never forget that I have
not only the authority,
but also the ability,
to execute any one
of you at my whim!
[PRISONER whimpering]
[ACE whimpering]
There. So sorry about that.
You're free to speak
with him now. Proceed.
[HANCOCK]
I'm finished here.
[MAGELLAN]
Huh?
Wait! Is what you just
told me the truth?
What reason would
I have to lie?
[HANCOCK]
By the way...
He was afraid you
might be angry,
but he still had to do it.
Is... that really
all you needed?
What do you think
they were talking about?
I have no idea.
Honestly, I was busy
trying to get away from you.
So... Ace.
[JIMBEI] Will you tell me
what she said to you?
She said that my
brother is here.
Huh? You mean Luffy?!
The one with the straw hat that
you're always talking about?
That fool.
[LUFFY panting]
Aw, man!
When the heck did
I start going upstairs?
I wanna go downstairs!
Well, if it started going up,
it'll probably go back down
again sooner or later.
I'm getting hungry!
[GUARD 432A]
I've got an image of him!
And it appears he's about
to enter District C!
[LUFFY panting]
Right. We see him.
[LUFFY yells]
They're using
Sea Prism Stone nets again!
Oof!
[LUFFY grunts]
Ahh!
Close one!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY grunts]
[SPHINX grunts]
[LUFFY] Aw crap!
It's that lion-thing!
[LUFFY grunts]
--[SPHINX roars]
--[LUFFY yells]
Hey! Let him go!
[SPHINX]
Huh?
Need a hand, pal?
Hey! Zoro!
Ha-ha! Fooled ya!
[BON CLAY]
Swan. Arabesque!
[SPHINX grunts]
[BON CLAY giggles]
Swan! Swan!
Huh?
That is not Zoro.
But he does sound familiar.
Been a while, Straw Boy!
Did you miss me, old pal?
[LUFFY yells]
[BON CLAY]
And twirl open plie!
Well, did everyone enjoy
my very special secret talent?
[ALL]
Oh, yeah!
[ALL singing]
[BON CLAY]
Running now would go against
everything Bon Clay stands for.
If we abandon allies
who are risking their lives
to pick up a friend, could we
live with ourselves tomorrow?
[MARINE A] Miss Hina! The
enemy ships are splitting up!
[BON CLAY] You must be feeling
pretty stupid right now,
falling for such
a simple trick!
See, we're masters
of disguise!
As well as friends
to the Straw Hats!
Bring it on, sister!
[LUFFY crying]
I promise you, Bon Clay!
We will never forget you!
It's Bon!
I'd still rather have Zoro,
but I'm glad you're alive
after all that happened!
Take aim!
Open fire on Straw Hat!
[BON CLAY]
Piss off!
[GUARDS]
Huh?
[GUARDS yell]
Bastards!
You stay away from my friend,
or things are about
to get very ugly!
Good boy, Sphinx!
Now, take them out!
[SALDEATH yells]
[LUFFY] There.
After a beating like that,
he shouldn't be
bothering us anymore.
[BON CLAY] Sometimes when
you're dealing with an animal,
you have to teach it
the law of the jungle!
[BON CLAY giggles]
Fried noodles.
[LUFFY cries]
You really bailed
us out last time,
and I thought for
sure you were dead!
Am I ever happy to see you!
[BON CLAY cries]
Oh, stop pulling my tail!
You know swans never die!
Unless that isn't true.
[BON CLAY crying]
[NARRATOR] And now a reminder
of how Bon Clay's power works.
He ate the Clone-Clone Fruit,
allowing him to
transform into anyone
whose face he's touched
with his right hand.
He was able to turn into Zoro
because he had
touched him before,
but he is not able
to mimic his strength.
[BON CLAY crying]
Now there's another
escapee to deal with.
The deeper the
Straw Hat descends,
the more friends he seems
to pick up along the way.
Blugori!
I don't care what it takes,
don't let them escape!
[BLUGORI grunt]
Hmm?
Oh, and by the way.
I heard that you wanted to go
all the way down to Level 5!
That's the plan, but I could use
a guide if you're not too busy.
[BON CLAY] Wouldn't have it
any other way, my friend.
As fate would have it,
there's someone down on Level 5
I'd like to see, too!
Really?
Now, then. Shall we go?
[LUFFY]
Let's do it!
[BON CLAY]
Uh-huh!
[NARRATOR]
Teaming up with Bon Clay,
Luffy races from
Level 3 to Level 4
pummeling every Blugori that
dares to stand in their path.
But all good things
must come to an end,
and a powerful
demon guard, Minotarus,
is ready to do some
pummeling of his own.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Warden Magellan's Strategy
Straw Hat Entrapment Completed!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!