[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[LUFFY]
"The Pirates' Banquet
and Operation Escape
From Alabasta!"
My, your medicine‐making
skills are so innovative
and practical.
It's amazing.
You're a genius, my boy.
[CHOPPER]
Uh...!
Where in the world did
you learn such techniques?
Tony was a practicing
doctor back in Drum Kingdom.
He was?
You mean the same Drum
that was once renowned
for its advanced medicine?
No wonder this little
fellow is so talented.
Wow. I've been a doctor
for forty years,
but even I don't know
the techniques and remedies
that you do.
You're far younger
than I but it's obvious
I'm no match for you.
You're clearly
the superior doctor.
Bravo, my boy!
Shut up, jerk! Stop saying that!
I can't stand it!
Get outta here if you're
gonna talk like that!
He's offering me tea and a
chair despite what he's saying.
Does he want me to stay?
He certainly does!
[DR. HOU] Well, in that case,
show me more of your
incredible talents!
[CHOPPER]
I said shut up!
If only I could have
splendid skills such as yours!
I can't tell you
how impressed I am!
[CHOPPER]
Get outta here!
I can't take it anymore!
[hammering]
Hey! Does anybody have
any more lumber?
[TOWNSPERSON B]
No, I'm out, too!
I have some left;
take whatever you need.
[TOWNSPERSON A]
Thanks!
Look, everyone's
coming together.
It's 'cause their
princess is cute.
Oh, please.
‐‐It is!
‐‐[TOWNSPERSON D] Dammit!
House after house is like this!
How could this have happened?
It's like someone kicked
a hole through them!
[SANJI] Ah, there's no way
I have time to go around!
There! A shortcut!
[USOPP]
How awful.
Say, Usopp.
What's that over there?
Let's take a look.
[ZORO]
I'll improve my concentration.
Until I can bring out
that power anytime,
I can't consider
myself stronger.
[NAMI] Wow, they're all
such interesting books!
Is it really okay
to take some with me?
Absolutely, take any you'd like.
I've read all of them.
Thanks so much!
And I'll definitely take
you up on that offer!
I've told you a hundred times
there are no pirates.
Lying to us will only
harm your country!
Harboring pirates
is a major felony!
‐‐[SANJI] Hey, what's up?
‐‐[USOPP] Yo!
[CHAKA]
Oh, welcome back.
[SANJI]
I was surprised we...
There's no evidence,
and I don't see
any pirates here, do you?
Well I...
I wonder if Luffy's
woken up yet.
I doubt it. Things would
be noisier if he had.
Ah, man! I slept good!
[laughing]
Hey! My hat!
Where the heck is my hat?
I'm starving, too!
Where's my breakfast?
My hat! My breakfast!
You just woke up and you're
already making a racket!
And it won't be breakfast,
it'll be dinner. It's evening.
Your hat's right
over there, Luffy.
Lucky for you,
a soldier found it
near the front of the palace.
I missed ya!
I'm so relieved you
finally got well, Luffy!
"Got well?" Whaddya mean?
I was never not well.
[NAMI]
You dummy!
You were in really bad shape
and had a high fever.
Vivi and Chopper have
been taking care of you
all this time!
Really? Thanks, you guys!
[ZORO]
Ah, Luffy! You woke up!
[LUFFY]
Zoro! Long time no see!
Wait a minute.
[CHOPPER] How dare you! You were
out training, weren't you?
So what?
I didn't need your permission.
[CHOPPER]
Of course you did!
I'm your doctor!
Where are your bandages?
[ZORO] It was too hard
to move with 'em on.
[CHOPPER]
You shouldn't be moving!
"Long time no see."
Why'd I say that?
Probably because
it has been long.
You've been asleep
for three entire days.
[LUFFY]
Three days? Three whole days?
Uh‐huh.
[LUFFY]
I missed fifteen meals.
You sure calculate quickly
when it comes to food!
By his count, that's like
five meals a day!
[VIVI giggles]
I heard the captain's awake.
Dinner will be served shortly.
I hope you're all hungry.
Hey! Old tube hair
guy! You're still alive?
So that cross‐dressing
thing wasn't just an act!
[VIVI]
No, everyone, you're mistaken.
This is Terracotta.
She's Igaram's wife and the
head of the palace's servers.
Thank you for helping
Vivi and my husband.
[ZORO] I've heard of wives
resembling their husbands,
but this is too weird!
I heard the captain eats a lot,
so I had my staff put
together a little snack
to tide you and
your friends over.
Thank you.
Greedy pig!
[LUFFY] I'm gonna eat three
whole days' worth of food, lady!
Oh, a challenge!
Good! I'm looking forward to it!
I've never lost to
anyone's stomach,
so eat to your heart's content!
Jeez. I've seen
hungry pigs eat less.
And with more manners,
too, I'm sure.
This is the Royal Dining
Hall, not a trough!
Come on, Captain,
keep it up. I can handle it.
This smells good!
Luffy, you just snatched
my food, didn't ya!
You liar!
Hey, you keep eating
like that, you're gonna choke.
There's plenty more.
Snatch my food, will ya?
Some hot sauce will fix you.
[ZORO]
Serves you right, Luffy!
Eyelash! When did you get here?
[EYELASH laughing]
What do you call
that dish there?
It's called konafa‐‐
noodles baked in a brick oven.
Yummy!
[TERRACOTTA]
Here's more! Eat up!
Old man, I never
knew you were the king!
I guess that means you're
also Vivi's dad, huh?
That's pretty cool.
Uh, maybe we should
talk after dinner.
[LUFFY]
Yeah, okay.
I need another round
down here, guys!
And water down here!
They're loud,
uncouth, and disgusting.
I'll say! I can't watch!
[chattering, munching]
[laughing]
The princess‐‐
How can she keep
laughing like that?
[USOPP] Bean sprouts!
I want sauteed bean sprouts!
[GROUP chattering, munching]
[ALL laughing]
[COBRA]
This is the palace's royal bath.
Normally we only use it
during the rainy season.
[USOPP]
I'm royally impressed!
It's gorgeous!
I'm goin' in first!
[LUFFY]
No way! I am!
[SANJI]
Real mature, guys.
Well. That was some dinner
tonight, wasn't it?
I thought an after‐dinner
bath would be a more
sedate affair.
But it seems anything
you lads get involved with
becomes a party very quickly.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Zoro, look over here!
Look at what we're doing!
[USOPP]
We're training!
[ZORO]
Real funny.
Um... Hey.
Where's the women's bath?
You're nuts!
And why would I tell you that?
That's where the princess is!
I know!
[COBRA]
It's right behind that wall!
Your Majesty!
[USOPP] Hey, thanks,
old guy! You're the best!
[NAMI]
This feels so good!
I wonder if a ship with a
big bath like this exists.
[VIVI]
I'm sure one does.
The sea's full of surprises.
Think of what we've seen.
Giants and dinosaurs.
Blossoms blooming
in a winter land.
If those things exist,
there must be plenty of
more amazing things
out there in the sea.
[VIVI]
I... I guess.
My turn!
[VIVI chuckles]
Thank you.
What are you all
doing over there?
Peeping.
All right.
It'll cost 100,000
Berries each.
[USOPP]
Huh?
[NAMI]
Happiness... Punch!
[GROUP gasps]
Nami!
[NAMI chuckles]
[SANJI]
Nami swan...!
Can't make up your mind?
What?
Better think quick.
I was thinking we might
actually leave here tonight.
Really?
Yeah, we need to go
while the goings good.
We know that the Marines
are looking all over for us,
and that means the ship
is in danger.
Thank you.
[GROUP]
Pervert.
[COBRA]
Not for that!
For the country.
It's not that we
don't appreciate it,
but is a king supposed
to do that?
The swordsman is right,
Your Majesty.
You're this land's
sovereign ruler‐‐
you should bow to no one.
Listen, Igaram.
Authority is something that
you wear over your clothes.
But we're in the bath now,
and there is no such
thing as a naked king,
is there?
I want to thank all of you
from the bottom of my heart,
as both a father and
a native of this land,
Alabasta will forever be
in your debt, Straw Hats.
[LUFFY laughing]
Thank you all very much.
I cannot tell you how
much we appreciate you!
[USOPP]
Tonight?
[NAMI]
Yep.
[CHOPPER]
We have to leave?
The Marines know we're here.
More'll be coming.
I agree with Nami.
We need to get out now
Me, too.
And not just 'cause
she's got a pretty face.
[USOPP] Do you think
we should leave, Luffy?
[LUFFY] Yeah, but only
after we've had some more
yummy food!
[ZORO]
No, now, you idiot!
[GROUP]
Jeez, Luffy!
[CHAKA]
What should we do, Igaram?
We have to let them
know right away!
You're right. I agree. Well...
Word of what's happened
here has traveled fast.
They've already released
new wanted posters,
and the bounties
are quite large.
Roronoa Zoro.
Sixty million Berries!
Monkey D. Luffy.
One hundred million Berries!
[CHAKA]
Incredible.
[IGARAM] With bounties like
that, Marine Headquarters
must have a keen interest
in capturing the Straw Hats.
You're no longer a
mere pirate, Luffy.
Not since you took down
one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea!
[IGARAM panting]
[IGARAM]
We've got trouble!
[gasps]
[IGARAM]
Vivi! Where are they?
[VIVI]
Oh, Igaram, what is it?
Luffy and all the others.
Where are they?
The sea. They are pirates.
[IGARAM]
Oh, no.
Listen up, you guys.
Pirates are nothing but scum.
Every one of them.
Hey, wait.
Don't you remember?
What are you saying?
Come on. You used to be one.
You're right!
How could I forget?
Uh‐huh, oh, baby!
Let's dance!
[JANGO]
Aw, yeah! Dance! Dance!
That's right, in a funky style!
[music playing]
[SGT SHINE] It looks like those
two subdued the enemy ship.
[HINA]
It took them long enough.
Don't tell me.
They're dancing, right?
I trusted those two to
finish off that pirate ship
that tried to escape us
and this is what they do.
Disappointed.
Hina's disappointed.
Have you finished
deploying all the ships?
Yes, that's affirmative, Ma'am!
Every harbor in this
dust ball of a country
is now blockaded!
But Ma'am.
[HINA]
Hm?
There's one thing
I'm concerned about.
What's that?
Well, it's just the
Straw Hats' ship, ma'am.
It was confirmed to be
near Erumalu, and now...
...it's gone.
Don't tell me they've
left the country already!
No! I doubt that, Ma'am!
Then go search for it!
Scour the entire coast!
Yes! Right away!
Oh, no.
[FULLBODY] Miss Hina!
We're sorry it took us so long.
[JANGO] Aren't you gonna
ask us why it took so long?
[HINA]
Why'd it take so long?
Because we were picking these
flowers for you, Miss Hina!
[HINA] No thanks. Now man
your positions right away!
We're going after
the Straw Hat pirates.
The Straw Hats?!
[DUCKS squawking]
Not bad.
So a final farewell,
o' kingdom of the sand.
Luffy, aren't you full yet?
[LUFFY] These Alabasta dishes
are great aren't they, Sanji?
You should make 'em sometime.
Yeah, I liked 'em too,
so I got some recipes
from Terracotta.
I also got some of
their local spices.
Um... What's wrong, Nami?
Are you sick?
[LUFFY] I'll give you a
piece of this if you want,
but just a small one.
Nami, if you're thinking
about Vivi again,
I understand.
Listen. Moping around
about it won't help.
I know it must be really hard
for you. You two got close.
Just keep your chin up, 'kay?
[NAMI]
It's not that.
I'm just sad
we didn't take the reward.
The one billion Berries.
[GROUP]
Gah!
You're moping about the money?!
[CHOPPER]
Agh! Usopp fell off!
[ZORO] You shouldn't mislead
people like that, Nami!
[NAMI] What did you
think I was upset about?
We just walked away
from a huge payday
that we actually earned!
[CHOPPER]
Guys, Usopp fell down!
[NAMI]
That's his problem!
[LUFFY, ZORO, CHOPPER]
But you caused it!
[IGARAM]
Karoo! Wake up!
You're needed!
[KAROO squawks]
[VIVI]
It's no use, Igaram.
[IGARAM] But the world
government has released
new bounties on their heads.
We should at least warn them.
[VIVI] I had the Duck
Squadron take them.
Even if Karoo could
catch up to them,
it wouldn't change anything.
[IGARAM]
Why's that?
Those new bounties...
They'll actually
make them happy.
They'll all be tickled pink.
[IGARAM]
But Princess, they‐‐!
[VIVI]
Trust me, they'll be fine!
Now out you go!
I've got to get some rest.
I've got a big day
tomorrow, remember?
Oh, that's right!
Your coming‐of‐age ceremony
is tomorrow morning
at ten!
Uh‐huh.
Now come on, Karoo.
Let's get some sleep.
[KAROO squawks]
[door closes]
[CHAKA]
Igaram...
[IGARAM]
Something's bothering me.
[CHAKA]
Hey!
[IGARAM]
She's awfully calm.
Strange. Very strange.
[KAROO snoring]
[VIVI] It's really quiet,
isn't it, Karoo?
We haven't had a night
this quiet in a long time.
The cook who guards
the refrigerator
from a late‐night
raider is gone.
So too is the swordsman
who trains every night.
The navigator who throws
pillows when she's asleep.
Her, too. They're gone.
[NAMI]
Snail communication? From who?
Don't know.
He called himself Bon.
Just Bon? That's it?
Uh, never heard of the guy.
That's strange. He insists
that you're all good friends.
[SANJI]
Friends with us?
[MR. 2] Hello? Hey,
old friends, it's me!
[laughing]
I betcha never thought you'd
hear from me again, did‐‐?
[MR. 2 screeching]
You freak! Shut up!
So you escaped, Mr. 2,
and what do you want?
[MR. 2]
Straw Hat!
I'd recognize that
voice anywhere!
You're right, I escaped,
and I wanna keep it that way,
so don't call me Mr. 2!
If the Marines intercept
this call, they'll be able
to ascertain the locations
of both me and you!
Thanks a lot, you jerk!
Tell us what you want!
[MR. 2]
Oh, it's not what I want.
It's what I have. Your ship!
[GROUP]
Stop joking!
I'm gonna kick your
butt for saying that!
Where are you?
On your ship, the Going Merry!
I shoulda kicked him harder!
[MR. 2]
Hey! Calm down! Please!
I mean, we are friends, right?
Right.
[laughing]
[LUFFY] He's at the upper
part of the Sandora River.
[SANJI]
Can we trust him?
We did become friends
that one time, but...
That was before we knew
he was part of Baroque Works!
I guess we have no choice.
[SANJI]
You're right. He has our ship.
If he tries to trick us,
I'll be more than happy
to kick the crap
out of him again.
[ZORO]
All right. We gotta move, guys.
[USOPP] Yeah, before he changes
the ship's figurehead to a swan!
Hey, you guys...
I, uh... I don't...
I don't know what to do.
If you were me,
what would you do?
[NAMI] Vivi, we can give you
twelve hours to make a decision.
We'll travel down the Sandora
after teaching Ballerina Boy
why he shouldn't steal from us
and by noon tomorrow,
we'll draw near
the eastern harbor.
I doubt we'll be able
to drop anchor, though.
If you do decide to join us,
that's gonna be the only
chance for you to come aboard.
Twelve o'clock, on the dot.
It's your choice.
You could stay a princess.]
or become a pirate.
[SANJI] I'm sure being
a pirate doesn't compare
to being a princess,
but we'd sure love to have you.
[LUFFY] Yeah, so why wait?
Come with us now, Vivi!
[USOPP]
Knock it off, Luffy.
‐‐[ZORO] Yeah, come on!
‐‐[LUFFY] Why?
Don't you guys
want her to join us?
[USOPP] We do, but that's
something she has to decide
for herself!
[VIVI]
Twelve o'clock on the dot.
If it's the eastern harbor,
it'll take four hours
to get there on Karoo.
If I left here by eight,
I'd make it on time.
Life as a pirate, huh?
Adventures on the
high seas surrounded
by loyal friends.
If I miss this chance,
I know I'll never get
another one like it
for the rest of my life.
On the other hand, I have
duties here as a princess.
And at a critical
time since this land's
in the midst of a rebirth.
Whatever I do choose,
you'll stay with me, won't you?
Say... Karoo?
What would you like to do?
[KAROO snoring]
[MR. 2]
Finally!
Long time no see, my friends!
Did you guys miss little ole me?
[ZORO]
Not a bit.
[SANJI]
Let's unload!
Later, ducks,
thanks for the lift!
[USOPP] Yeah! You ducks
take care of yourselves.
[ZORO]
Have a safe trip!
[LUFFY] Say bye to the
King, the old tube hair guy,
and all the others for us!
[USOPP]
So long, fellas!
Farewell!
May you ugly ducklings...
...turn into beautiful swans!
[crying]
Wait, hold on!
[SANJI]
Yeah, what?
Don't "yeah, what" me!
That's just rude!
You should learn
some manners, pretty boy!
Friends aren't supposed
to talk to their friends
that way!
Quit saying that, you weirdo!
We're not friends,
we're enemies!
You lied to us!
[MR. 2]
No, I didn't!
I just didn't mention
that I was a member
of Baroque Works!
Besides, none of that
really matters now does it?
Baroque works is done for now,
and that means that
we're no longer enemies.
Hey, move it!
Oh, my bad.
Well if we're not enemies,
Ballerina Guy,
then why the heck
did you steal our ship?
[MR. 2]
Oh, how dumb are you?
Watch it!
Listen, if I hadn't
taken your little ship
from where it was moored,
what do you think
would've happened to it?
The Marines probably
would have seized it.
[MR. 2] Change that
"probably" to a "definitely,"
honey!
The Marines have
been looking all over
for you guys and your ship!
Every port in the country's
been blockaded. Lockdown.
Hey, hold on.
Are you telling us you
took the Going Merry
so the Marines wouldn't?
‐‐Really?
‐‐How come?
'Cause you guys are my friends!
[MR. 2]
Oh, gimme a break, guys!
We may have had to fight
on opposite sides of a war,
but our friendship
will last all of eternity!
Need help loading?
[SANJI]
Nope, this is the last one.
Friends? Yeah, right.
Tell the truth, Twinkle Toes.
You and your crew
don't have a chance
of getting through
that blockade,
but you might if you
had us as allies, right?
[STRAW HATS]
Bon Clay!
[MR. 2]
That's right, you got me,
but in trying times
such as these
we have to band together
under the flag of friendship!
if you believe in true
friendship, say "aye"!
[LUFFY, CHOPPER, USOPP]
Aye!
[groans]
[SUBORDINATES]
Aye!
[SUBORDINATE A]
Thanks, Straw Hats!
[ZORO]
Where were you guys?
[SERGEANT SHINE]
Miss Hina!
We've spotted the
Straw Hats' ship!
It's near the upper reaches
of the Sandora River!
What do you think
we should do, Captain?
Attack, of course.
♪Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!♪
[CHOPPER]
Vivi will come, right?
[LUFFY]
Adventures are fun!
There's no way she wouldn't!
[SANJI]
I don't know about that, Luffy.
She's a princess, not a pirate.
[USOPP]
Bad news, guys!
The Marines are on our tail!
[LUFFY] I betcha anything
she'll come and be a pirate!
[VIVI]
Father... Igaram.
I have something
important to tell you.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"It All Started On That Day!
Vivi Tells the Story
of Her Adventure!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!