Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[USOPP whimpers]
[KUMA]
Stand down, PX-1.
[BROOK gasps]
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO]
It's him. The real Kuma.
[KUMA]
I see you survived, Roronoa.
Hey, Zoro. C'mon!
Let's get out of
here while we can!
Huh?
Is he gone?
No.
What happened? Where is he?
Zoro... He just disappeared.
[LUFFY]
Eliminated Friends.
The Final Day of
the Straw Hat Crew.
[USOPP]
Z-Zoro...
[USOPP whimpering]
He's gone! What the
hell did you do to him?
You! Where is he?
You bring him back
here, you monster!
[LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY]
Zoro...
What did you do?
[LUFFY]
Zoro...
No!
Zoro!
[CHOPPER growling]
[ROBIN gasps]
[SENTOMARU grunts]
[ROBIN grunting]
Chopper, stop this!
You've lost control!
Zoro! Where the hell are you?
[CHOPPER growling]
[CHOPPER roaring]
This beast has gone mad but
that's not what worries me.
I wanna know what
he's doing here.
Well, Bartholomew Kuma.
Can't trust pirates.
The Seven Warlords are
supposed to be at Navy HQ.
I wish I could help, but
there's nothing I can do.
[FRANKY]
It's like Zoro was erased.
I'm gonna guess that means
this guy is the real Kuma.
There's no question.
That power he used,
I've seen it before.
Back on Thriller Bark.
He erased a girl like that.
Just made her disappear and
that was the last I saw of her.
[FRANKY grunts]
Let's just hope
he's still alive.
Hey! What the hell'd
that guy do to Zoro?
Where is he?
You think I'm gonna answer you?
Did you forget I'm the
world's most guarded man?
But someone might tell
you he can send you
flying for three days and
nights with those paw pads.
Can't say if it's true or
not but that's the rumor.
[LUFFY gasps]
[SENTOMARU]
Only Kuma knows where they go.
But there's no way you're
going to find your friend
on these islands.
Or anywhere else around
here, for that matter.
He'll probably land on
the other side of the world.
What?
[SANJI groaning]
[USOPP] Say something,
dammit, tell us what you did!
[USOPP]
Tell us where you sent Zoro!
So that's the real deal, huh?
The first three were bad
enough and now he shows up
to finish the job.
There's no way to win.
What kind of power is that?
[USOPP whimpers]
Stop it! Get back!
[beeping]
[USOPP]
No! You stay away from me!
I've-I've got 8,000 men
under my command!
Don't make me
unleash them on you!
Usopp, he's behind
you! Get down!
Oh, cra--!
Usopp, no!
[KUMA]
Don't interfere.
[BROOK gasps]
He erased him. But why?
[SENTOMARU]
That was PX-1 he just hit.
What's your problem,
you fool? That was your ally!
[USOPP whimpering]
Just run! Move you guys!
Luffy, hey!
[LUFFY]
Just go! Get out of there!
We can figure out a plan
once we're safe! Run!
Alright, you heard him!
But, Zoro...
The captain just said
we can figure it out
after we're safe! C'mon!
[USOPP]
C'mon buddy!
That last beam just grazed
me. I can help you walk.
[BROOK] Go, you two!
I'll cover you!
[USOPP]
Stop it, Brook! That's crazy!
I'll protect you, even
if it costs me my life!
Oh, but I'm already
dead, I suppo--
Brook! No!
That bastard did it again!
[SANJI]
Dammit!
How the hell can
I let this happen?
The bastard's erasing all of
my friends right in front of me!
[SANJI grunts]
Get back!
Sanji?
Start running, Usopp.
Not a chance!
I'm not going
without you, Sanji!
Son of a bitch!
Sanji! Just run!
C'mon! Nobody does
that to my crewmates!
[LUFFY]
Sanji!
[USOPP whimpering]
No! Get back!
[USOPP]
Stay away!
[USOPP whimpering]
Stop where you are! Get back!
Flame Star!
One more! Flame Star!
C'mon! Go! Go away, please.
Just, just leave me alone!
[USOPP whimpers]
Usopp, run!
[USOPP screams]
No! Stop it!
Usopp!
[SANJI panting]
[SANJI yelling]
[LUFFY]
Sanji!
[SANJI yelling]
Damn you!
You can't win! Don't fight!
[LUFFY]
He got Sanji. What now?
What do we do?
It can't be. They're all gone.
It's startin' to sound
like they could really use
my help over there,
but there's only so much
an old man can do.
I guess I'm not quite
the fighter I used to be.
So fending off a navy
admiral isn't enough
to make you satisfied, huh?
Why don't you keep those
thoughts to yourself?
You're already making
me look bad, y'know!
[KIZARU sighs]
[RAYLEIGH panting]
[KUMA]
Dark King Rayleigh, correct?
Huh?
Huh? Kuma?
[RAYLEIGH]
Hm?
[LUFFY grunting, panting]
[ROBIN]
Wait, Luffy.
[RAYLEIGH]
You can't be serious.
You're asking me to trust you?
[KUMA]
That's entirely your decision.
But I'm putting my own
neck on the line too.
Alright.
I feel like I deserve an
explanation here, Kuma.
[KUMA] This matter is of no
consequence to the government.
So, I have no obligation
to cooperate with the Navy.
And you deserve
nothing of the sort.
[LUFFY]
You bastard!
Now. Second Gear!
Luffy!
[FRANKY]
Let's move it!
[NAMI, FRANKY gasp]
Get the hell out of our way!
Strong Right!
[FRANKY]
What the--?
[LUFFY yells]
Luffy! No!
Now Gum-Gum...
Jet Pistol!
[LUFFY yells]
Luffy!
[FRANKY yelps]
[NAMI screams]
[NAMI whimpering]
Someone help me!
[LUFFY]
Nami!
[LUFFY panting]
Someone help me--
[LUFFY growls]
[LUFFY yelling]
Luffy!
[CHOPPER roars]
Chopper, no!
[CHOPPER roaring, growling]
Chopper, no! Don't do it!
[CHOPPER roars]
[LUFFY sputtering]
[LUFFY]
Damn it.
[ROBIN grunting]
No more. Please, stop.
Please, stop. Just stop.
Please, stop.
Stop it, leave her alone!
[LUFFY yelling]
[ROBIN]
Luffy!
Robin!
[LUFFY gasping]
[LUFFY grunting, sobbing]
[LUFFY]
How could I?
I'm useless. How could I?
[LUFFY]
I got a question. You ready?
Will you join our crew?
[BROOK sobbing]
've never been this
happy in my life!
Come on, Straw Hat,
you can't hide from me!
[LUFFY]
Well? Come on!
Get on my ship!
Captain's orders.
What can I say?
You don't leave me much choice.
I gotta take care of my
masterpiece, after all!
So set sail--
I'm joining the crew!
Why did you come to save
me in the first place?
[ROBIN]
Do you hear me?
I just want to die!
[LUFFY] There's still
something I wanna hear you say!
Tell me you wanna live!
I want to live!
[CHOPPER] Shut up!
Even if I don't have friends,
I can still fight for
something I believe in!
[LUFFY] You're wrong!
You do have friends!
I'm your friend, reindeer! Me!
[CHOPPER] I am going
to stay here for now...
...but if you wanted to,
you could stop by here again.
[LUFFY]
Shut up! Let's go!
[NAMI]
What do you want?
You don't know
anything about this.
This has nothing
to do with you!
I told you to leave this place.
Luffy, help me.
[LUFFY]
Hey! Nami,
You'll always be my friend!
[SANJI]
Wait.
Your dream is foolish.
Then again, so is mine.
[LUFFY gasps]
[SANJI]
You hear me?
I wanna be the
cook on your ship.
Thanks, you geezer!
I owe my life
to you, old man!
What are you talking
about? Get on already!
Huh?
We're friends, right? So get on.
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
Bullet!
[LUFFY]
You idiot.
You knew it would end like this!
You knew you
could never beat me!
[USOPP]
I'll do anything!
Please, let me join the crew.
Just one more time!
[USOPP whimpers]
Hurry up! Grab on already!
Scars on the back are
a swordsman's shame.
[ZORO]
I will never, ever be defeated!
Is that okay?
[ZORO]
King of the pirates?
[LUFFY]
Zoro...
Usopp...
Sanji...
Nami...
Chopper...
Robin...
Franky...
Brook...
They're... They're all gone.
[LUFFY sobbing]
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
[LUFFY sobbing]
[KIZARU] So, you're just gonna
blast him off like the rest?
You can't pull this mess without
an explanation, you know.
And boy, it had
better be a good one.
[LUFFY sobbing]
[KUMA]
You and I...
We'll never meet again.
[LUFFY growls]
Farewell, Straw Hat.
[NARRATOR] Grove 12.
The Sabaody Archipelago.
Deep in the Grand Line.
On this day,
the Straw Hat Pirates, led
by Captain Monkey D. Luffy
came face to face
with true despair.
And one by one,
they were eliminated.
[LUFFY]
That was harsh.
I think I could use a
break from serious stuff.
[NAMI]
Lucky for you, we've got
a Boss Luffy episode up next.
Everyone's taking to the streets
for a portable shrine race!
I hear first prize is
a sacred treasure!
[LUFFY] Mm. Sacred
treasure. Sounds yummy.
[NAMI]
It's not food!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece.
"Feudal Era Side Story--
Boss Luffy Appears Again!".
I'm gonna be a police man!