Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Time to feel
my full heat power!
Maximum Temperature!
10,000 degrees!
So he can get even hotter!
[LUFFY]
Waiting in the New World!
Farewell to the Brave Pirates!
[ACCINO]
Hot! Hotter! Hotter!
[NAMI] Oh boy, this looks bad.
What's happening?
[NAMI shrieks]
[shrieks]
[ACCINO] Straw Hat!
Too bad, kid!
This is the end of the road!
I'm gonna melt
you down to nothing!
Heat Tire!
What the--
[yelling]
Now Gum-Gum Pistol!
And Rocket!
[LUFFY] Uh-oh!
And now Second Gear!
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Nose Jet!
[ACCINO] Heat-Heat Head!
[ACCINO] Straw Hat!
Die!
Not gonna happen!
[ACCINO]
Here comes my Steam Iron!
10,000 Degree Press!
Yeah?
Well, Gum-Gum Jet Gatling!
[yelling]
Gum-Gum Jet Whip!
[LUFFY screaming]
[LUFFY]
Hot! Hot!
What's that stuff?
It's lava.
Underneath this island.
That means that--
What?
No way! That's crazy!
I let my guard down.
Tricky little brat!
Doctor...
Come on, Robin.
Can't you link a bunch
of your arms together
to reach those flags?
Yes.
But I can't tell
which one of them is ours.
There're too many.
Aw crap! What do we do now?
[SANJI]
Looks like we're screwed.
Hey, wait.
Look, guys!
What's wrong?
Do you see something?
A bird?
[FLYING FISH calling, cooing]
[FLYING FISH cooing]
[CHOPPER]
Hey! I can't breathe!
Look! This is it!
It's our flag!
We finally got it back!
The flag!
I can't believe it!
I thought it was gone for good!
Good for you, Doctor!
[CHOPPER] Jiro!
--[JIRO] You really did it!
--[CHOPPER] We did it!
[JIRO]
Get off me, you big goof!
[CHOPPER, JIRO, USOPP cheering]
Thank you, Lil.
Hey, Robin! Time to go!
Now that we've got the flag,
there's no reason to
hang around here any longer!
[ROBIN] Right!
Let's move out!
Next stop: The Sunny!
[CHOPPER] Yeah!
[STANSEN] Keep it up, men!
This is it.
Give it all you've got!
Hard to believe
you're the same guy
that bowed down
to those bounty hunters!
Which one is the real Stansen?
The suck-up traitor or this guy?
Who the hell knows?
But the man we used to put
our trust in is this one.
Enough!
Stop wasting your energy
on flapping your mouth
and use it for pulling!
Captain Puzzle and Jiro are
putting their lives on the line
by fighting
to get our flag back!
We need to do the same
by protecting our ship!
Don't let go! No matter what!
Protect our pride!
We're gonna show them what
the Phoenix Pirates are made of!
Yeah!
[straining]
[PENGUINS squawking]
[cheering]
Nice! Good work!
Now, back on the ship!
[ALL] Yes, sir!
What the hell?
It's not over yet--
Those penguins are heading
over to the Straw Hats' ship!
[GUYLE] Little bastards!
[PENGUIN squawking]
[BASIL] What's going on?
They're retreating!
[PENGUINS squawking]
[PENGUINS panicking]
Yo! What's up, penguins?
It's been awhile.
I think it's time
for a little payback.
So hot...
Now.
There's nowhere left to run.
It's only a matter of time
before that ice you're
standing on melts away.
[LUFFY]
Guess I'll just have to beat you
before that happens, then.
Should be easy enough, right?
Y'know kid,
you really do piss me off.
Now Heat-Heat...
[distant rumbling]
Luffy...
...Lava Surfing!
[LUFFY] Oh crap!
No!
Not so fast!
Red Hot Fried Egg!
[LUFFY screaming]
I'm melting!
Wait a minute.
No, I'm not.
What's going on here?
[NAMI] Luffy!
[LUFFY] Nami!
Looks like the Cool Ball
I shot down there
made it just in time.
But it won't
last long in that lava!
Move!
Hurry up and finish him off!
[LUFFY] Right.
Thanks for saving me, Nami.
Just give up already.
You'll never win.
No, you're wrong.
And as soon as I finish you off,
we're gonna set sail
for the New World.
[ACCINO] I guess idiocy
is common among you pirates.
You really are all the same,
aren't you?
"I'm headed to the New World."
"I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates."
Head in the clouds,
not a doubt in your mind.
Don't get me wrong.
It's quite convenient for me.
Get it?
Thanks to idiots like you,
my family has a fortune in
the bounty hunting business.
[laughing]
[ACCINO] A bunch of damn morons,
ready to throw your lives away
over some useless flag,
over some useless
sense of pride!
Makes my job easy,
I'll tell you that!
[laughing]
[LUFFY] Shut your mouth.
[ACCINO] Why? Did I say
something to offend you?
That's enough.
Got it? It's over.
Prepare yourself,
Naked Balloon Man!
Prepare myself?
What?
[laughing]
So the only option
you've got left
is to bluff
your way out, huh?
[ACCINO]
Come on. Take a look around!
You've got the
flames of oblivion
creeping in
from every direction!
Of course, it's no problem for
me to stick around here, but--
For people like you,
it's gotta be unbearable.
Like standing inside
a giant boiling pot!
Huh! This is nothing.
Huh?
[LUFFY] You're not as
hot as you think you are.
In fact, from
the way I look at it,
you're as cold as ice
compared to my heat.
Huh?
[laughing]
You're out of your mind!
You actually think
you're hotter than me?
Ha!
My temperature is even higher
than all this lava
surrounding us!
If you don't think that's hot,
why don't you
take a little swim?
[laughing]
[LUFFY] You're all talk!
If you think you can take me,
then come at me already!
I'm gonna beat
the hell outta you!
Huh? What was that?
Aw, how dare you!
I'll burn you at
ten thousand degrees!
Is that really
all you've got?
How about this?
I'm burning at
1 million degrees!
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum...
Have it your way!
You really wanna end this?
You got it!
[laughing]
...One Million Degree Bazooka!
Whoa! Careful!
You're gonna melt your hands!
It's not that hot.
This is nothing.
It's not hot. This is nothing!
[ACCINO] No! That's impossible!
[yelling]
Now fly!
[groaning]
And now, to find our flag.
What's that?
What the hell?
What's going on here?
[CHOPPER] Look! Over there!
[ZORO] Luffy!
[USOPP]
What's he doing out there?
Hey!
Look, Luffy!
We got the flag--
What do you know--It's my crew!
Hey!
What do you guys think
you're doing over there, huh?
No! He saw us!
Great, so now what?
[NAMI] Everyone!
Hurry!
Let's head back to the ship!
Right.
Yeah.
--[SANJI] Let's go!
--[ZORO] Move it!
[LUFFY] What the--?
Come back!
Hey! Guys!
I wanna ask you
about our flag! Hey!
Listen! Stick to the plan!
We can't let him know the truth!
[LUFFY] Come back!
He's right behind us!
Stop! Wait!
Why are you running?
What about our flag?
[ALL] Sorry, can't hear you!
Sorry, can't hear you!
Sorry!
Hey! You're back!
Hurry it up!
--[LUFFY] Hey, you guys!
--He's almost here!
[USOPP]
What's the plan?
Sanji! Zoro!
Aye-aye. Let's do it.
[SANJI] Fly!
[screaming]
Here we go, Usopp.
Make sure to hang it
nice and straight.
What? Wait a minute!
Usopp Cannon!
[USOPP] I'm flying!
Franky!
Leave it to me!
Coup de Boo!
Why'd it have
to be cola farts?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
You let our flag get stolen!
We need to hurry
and get it back!
Stolen? The flag?
What on earth
are you talking about?
You probably just had
a bad dream or something.
Right?
Uh... Sure!
Yeah, that's it!
[laughing awkwardly]
Here, see for yourself.
What the--
It's right there,
safe and sound!
That stupid clone guy.
He must've been lying to me.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have doubted you.
It's okay. No worries.
Oh man.
That sure was a close one.
Yay... I made it...
[GUYLE] Excellent work!
[GUYLE laughing]
[GUYLE]
I knew you could do it!
You did a great job, Jiro!
Now you're a true man.
Way to go!
[STANSEN] Jiro...
I knew we could count on you
to get the flag back.
Well done.
I can't tell you how
proud I am. Thank you.
Captain...
But why?
[PUZZLE] Jiro...
I think you should
hang the flag,
because the Phoenix Pirates
are setting sail!
Yes, Captain!
Yeah!
Come on! Let's do it!
[ALL cheering]
[STANSEN sobbing quietly]
Stansen.
Like I said before, your
decision was the correct one.
I'm sorry all my failures
caused you so much trouble.
[sobbing loudly]
[PUZZLE]
Are you watching, Vigaro?
Your death won't be in vain.
I promise.
[PUZZLE] All right, men!
We're off!
[ALL cheering]
Hey, look!
I don't know what's happening,
but I know I don't like it!
Accino went nuts
with his heat powers,
causing the volcano under the
ocean floor to become active.
We need to hurry!
It's only a matter of time
before this thing erupts!
Right! Then let's set sail!
Move it!
[ALL] Aye-aye!
[USOPP] The whole island...
It's gone!
Phew!
Man, that was a close one.
There you are.
You're in big trouble!
How could you let the Straw Hats
get their hands on
Papa's flag collection?
Have you lost your m--
Shut up for one second!
Listen. I'm sorry.
Big sister?
I got caught up in my marriage
and didn't pay
you enough attention.
Come on, let's go apologize
to Papa together, okay?
I'm sure he'll
understand about the flags.
After all, we're family, right?
Arbell...
My Lil.
[ARBELL, LIL]
La-lala-lala!
--La-lala-lala!
--[SALCHOW] Aw! So sweet!
Reconciling with your little
sister is just so adorable!
No... No!
Straw Hat! How could--
Papa! I'm sorry, but better
late than never, right?
Here you go!
Happy Birthday to Papa!
Eh?
[ACCINO] It's--It's a--
It looks like a--
Damn Straw Hat!
[ACCINO FAMILY screaming]
[BRINDO] Hey! Where's Campacino?
How could he be missing
at a time like this?
[CAMPACINO] Straw Hat!
I swear upon the honor
of the Accino family,
you and your crew
will never escape!
Get lost, you annoying
clone-twin guy!
I'll make you pay
for what you did to Papa!
Campacino!
What? It's Puzzle!
I'll be your opponent!
You and I have
a score to settle!
Hey, Straw Hat!
This guy is mine!
Stay out of this! Got it?
He is?
[PUZZLE] You go on ahead!
And be prepared to face me when
we meet again in the New World!
Right! I'll be ready for you!
Damn you! Die!
Let's go!
[ALL] Aye-aye!
Jiro!
Luffy, turn around!
We have to go back
and help them!
They're gonna get
themselves killed!
You're wrong.
Take a look, Chopper.
They won't lose.
They're doing better than ever.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey! You!
Why are you still
hanging around?
Hurry up and leave!
Bye! We'll see you in
the New World, Doctor!
Bye! Until then, Jiro!
Sunny, full speed ahead!
Set course for the New World!
[ALL] Yeah!
[CHOPPER]
Greetings to one and all!
It's me, Chopperman!
It's been a while, huh?
Well, guess what?
Your dreams have come true,
you big jerks!
'Cause I'm back!
Get ready for my
Killer Cute Spark!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Chopperman to the Rescue!
Protect the TV Station
By The Shore!
I'm gonna be a giant robot?