Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
No! Please, no!
[USOPP] What the
hell is going on?
We beat Moria and got the
shadows out of him, so why?
[CHOPPER]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
"Not Out of Danger Yet!
Orders to Annihilate
the Straw Hat Crew."
[panicked screams]
No! Zoro!
Robin!
Sanji!
[ALL THREE] Their bodies
are burning to ashes!
What's going on?
We beat Moria, didn't we?
That should've done it!
Were we too late?
Ahhh!
They're all disappearing!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 375A]
Captain Lola!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 375B]
Everyone!
[ROLLING PIRATES]
We should've won! Dammit!
[PIRATE 375A] Whoa! Captain!
Captain, you need to come
on to the deck, quickly!
[PIRATE CAPTAIN 375A]
You idiot.
We haven't seen
the sun in two years
since Moria stole our shadows.
Go back to sleep.
[PIRATE 375A]
I know, Captain, but look!
Take a look at my feet!
[PIRATE CAPTAIN 375A]
Your shadow!
It's...
[PIRATE 375A] I bet it's
the same for you, Captain!
[PIRATE CAPTAIN 375A]
We... We... We...
We got our shadows back!
[cheering]
[RANDOM PIRATE 375A]
All of us, Captain!
Every member of the crew
had their shadows returned!
Hey Captain,
do you think this means
someone out there
was able to beat Gecko Moria?
Oh, come on!
Like that's bloody likely!
Even before Moria became
a Warlord, he went toe-to-toe
with Kaido-one of the
four pirate emperors.
You think someone came along
and was able to bring him down?
That's just crazy talk.
I got it back!
My shadow has returned!
[PIRATE 375B] It feels so
good to see the sun again!
[PIRATE 375C]
I don't know how,
but our zombies at
Thriller Bark must have died!
Moria's curse has
finally been lifted!
I can't believe it!
We can stand out
in the sunlight!
We have our shadows back again!
Look, they're following us!
It's back!
My reflection! I can see it!
[RICH MAN 375A] What's all
the fuss about, Margarita?
My shadow!
My shadow has returned
after all this time!
What?
It just returned? Huh.
You said a pirate stole it ten
years ago, but now it's back?
It's true!
[MARGARITA]
Master! I'm so sorry!
I was so surprised
when I saw it I dropped
your cherished plates!
I've hated plates
for a long time now.
But all of a sudden, I seem
to have gotten over all that.
I'm... I'm sorry to
be so much trouble.
I'll pack my things and
leave the mansion right away.
Goodbye.
[RICH MAN 375A]
Hold on.
Now what are you talking about?
Who cares about those
silly old plates?
All that matters is
you weren't hurt, okay?
And now you have
your shadow back.
I am so happy for you!
Sir!
[loud sobbing]
[RICH MAN 375A]
Thank goodness that's over.
[ZORO]
Well, look at that!
Guess it wasn't my
day to die after all.
I thought I was on my way
to Heaven for a moment there.
That sounds good to me!
It'd be like Heaven two
times over if I was with you!
Stop laughing,
you jackasses!
Half of your bodies were gone!
We thought you were
all dead! Get a grip!
That was scary!
You people almost
gave me a heart attack!
Except that I don't have a
heart, so ya know, lucky me.
Yeah, it's sunlight!
We don't have to be
afraid of it anymore!
We have our shadows back!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 375C]
Our days of hiding
in the dark are finally over!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 375D]
Yeah! All right!
[CHOPPER] It looks like
everybody survived.
The sunlight had definitely
begun to erase our existence.
But our shadows returned,
changing our bodies to
their fully recovered state
just in time.
That would follow
the same logic as
when we saw Moria
change the shape of Oars
by manipulating his shadow.
[MORIA] For example, if I
force his shadow into a ball,
Oars will become
a ball as well!
[MORIA]
Oars Ball!
My theory is that
the shadow must know
what shape its owner is
supposed to be or something.
Hell if I know. But relax.
Now that we beat Moria,
I don't think we'll
ever have to worry
about our shadows being
stolen away from us again.
I'm glad that's over.
And that no one or their shadow
ended up disappearing for good.
[sighs] I don't
know about you guys,
but all that
fightin' wore me out.
Does anybody got any cola?
[SANJI]
All the creepy crap
and weird creatures in
this place were an illusion.
A false reality made
by Moria and his crew.
[SANJI] Now that
he's been beaten,
there's nothing
left in this place.
It's like we all woke up from
the same horrible nightmare.
And I, for one, am sure
as hell glad it's over.
[HOGBACK]
Hey! Hey! Absalom!
Wake up! Wake up, dammit!
Hey! Come on! Wake up!
Oh my God! Lola!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
I'm not gonna marry you!
Would you calm down!
Her shadow's
already left her body.
[ABSALOM]
Doctor Hogback?
What are you doing here?
And what happened to me?
How the hell should I know
what happened to you?
You probably got your ass kicked
in some embarrassing manner.
I wasn't here!
But anyway, something awful
has happened to Master Moria.
[ABSALOM]
What?
Master Moria has been
defeated by Straw Hat Luffy?
Shut up!
You're too damn loud!
Use your inside voice!
Your inside voice!
What the hell are you flying
into a rage for, huh?
Doctor Rage-back.
I'm pissed because Thriller Bark
is useless to me now.
But I have no
intention of living out
the rest of my life
as a washed up loser.
How about you?
Wait. What do you mean?
[ZORO] Luffy got small
again a second ago, huh?
[CHOPPER] He told me that
when he uses Third Gear,
his body shrinks for a
while as a side effect.
[USOPP] These new
fighting techniques
seem like too much
for his body to handle.
He could actually hurt himself.
It's really starting
to worry me.
Every enemy we
run into is stronger
than the last one we faced.
He's gonna have
to keep doing this
to himself every single time.
We need to pull ourselves
together, and soon.
Yeah, you're right.
Holy crap,
it's a zombie!
One of them kept their shadows
even after we beat Moria!
No, I'm just an old man
with serious injuries.
That's too damn confusing!
Can't you just
be a zombie? Jeez!
Aren't you that old
geezer we met in the cemetery?
[SPOIL]
It's unbelievable.
To think that we'd see the day
when we'd be able to
walk under the sun again.
Thank you so much!
I don't know how
we can ever repay you.
[LOLA]
Hey!
Old man Spoil!
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
Gramps!
[RISKY BRO. BROWN HAIR]
It's the honorary chairman
of the Victim's Club!
Oh! Well, look who it is!
You're all okay, then?
[LOLA]
Yes! And you?
[SPOIL]
Sure am!
[USOPP] I guess they all
know each other or something.
[LOLA]
Good. You're all here.
I'm sorry we didn't
thank you sooner.
We're really grateful
to every last one of you folks!
Sorry we got you all
wrapped up in our mess here!
We knew it when
we first saw you!
You were our only
hope against Moria
and that damned
curse he put on us!
So thank you all, very much.
From me and all the members
of the Thriller
Bark Victim's Club.
We will never forget
that we owe you our lives.
Thank you, from the
bottom of our hearts!
If you ever need anything,
please let us know.
We may not have much,
but what we have is
yours for the taking.
And lastly,
and most importantly,
I will allow one of
you to marry me!
Hell no!
Shot down by five people,
all at the same time!
[RISKY BRO. BROWN HAIR]
That's four thousand,
four hundred and
forty-nine rejections!
There's really no need for
all this "thank you" stuff.
[LOLA]
Who's it gonna be?
It's like Luffy told the
old man when we got here.
[LOLA]
You? Or you?
We were fighting for our own
crew and on our own terms.
[LOLA]
Who's the lucky guy?
The fact that you guys were
rescued too is just a bonus.
Hey! What's wrong with you?
Someone was finally
showing us a little gratitude!
Yeah, she's right!
Let us thank you
all proper-like! Okay?
You guys might not've
set out to save us,
but we're still glad
you sent Moria packing!
You are? Really?
[USOPP] I shoulda known.
Yeah! And how about
we start off by showing you
where Moria's
treasure is hidden?
You guys can take
every piece we find!
You sure did earn it!
That's so sweet!
Okay, if you insist!
[NAMI]
Oh, no.
I forgot something
really important!
Yeah? What?
[NAMI] There's still another
Warlord on the island.
Is something wrong?
Everyone, this is serious!
[MARINE COMMANDER 375A]
I see.
My greatest fears
have become an
unfortunate reality.
[KUMA]
So it would seem.
[USOPP]
Whoa. Who is that guy?
[NAMI]
He's here!
Everyone.
Stay calm and listen.
Please.
[NAMI] During the fight
with Moria and the others,
I forgot to tell you, but...
...there's another one
of them on the island.
One of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea!
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
Wait. So he's...
...one of...
[CREW] ...the Seven
Warlords of the Sea?
[USOPP] There's...
There's no way!
[CHOPPER]
What's going on?
They weren't working together,
so why would there need
to be two of them here?
[MARINE COMMANDER 375A] Of
course all of this happens just
when we finally chose
a successor for Crocodile.
Losing another Warlord
in such a short time
sets a bad example.
Can you tell if
he's still breathing?
Even in the slightest?
No.
[MARINE COMMANDER 375A]
If he is in fact still alive,
we will wait for his recovery
and hope he can
maintain his position
as one of the Seven Warlords.
We will follow up
after such time comes.
[MARINE COMMANDER 375A]
The dignity of the Warlords
would be tarnished if we were
to keep losing them so easily.
[MARINE COMMANDER 375A]
It is critical
that this news not
reach anyone else.
These damned Straw Hats
are such a nuisance.
It's him!
The man who stands
just as tall as Moria.
The pirate known throughout
the world as "The Tyrant."
Bartholomew Kuma!
Aw, no way!
That's "Tyrant" Kuma?
Hold on, you mean like the one
who's famous for his brutality?
[MARINE COMMANDER 375A]
I feel I've made my orders
quite clear on this matter.
[MARINE COMMANDER 375A] We
cannot afford to let anyone else
know of Moria's defeat.
This is a direct order
from the World Government.
Obliterate the Straw Hat Crew
and everyone else
on Thriller Bark.
Leave no one alive.
Simple enough.
Wait.
Did he just say
what I think he said?
He... He's gonna obliterate us?
They wanna kill all of us?
I don't understand! What for?
Man, this cannot
be happening!
We just managed to
get all our shadows
back from Moria
and now this, too?
Oh, come on!
How many of these Warlords
do we have to fight?
It took everything
we had to defeat Moria.
We're worn out and done for!
[ZORO]
Everyone stand back.
I'll handle this.
Be careful!
He has some strange abilities!
I saw him make someone disappear
with only a touch of his hand!
[PERONA] Negative Ghost
and Special Hollow!
Wait, do you mean like,
"poof" and they're
suddenly gone?
So scary!
And he can move
from one location
to another in a split second.
You're the
Cat Burglar, aren't you?
One of the Straw Hat Pirates?
[KUMA] I've heard
that Monkey D. Luffy
has an older brother.
Is that true?
[NAMI]
No way!
He just suddenly
appeared up there!
Did he teleport?
These bad-asses just keep
popping up out of nowhere.
Don't let him touch you.
It's dangerous.
What the--?
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 375C]
He's right here!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 375D]
And he's huge!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 375E]
How'd he do that?
I'll be damned.
The bastard really can
change places instantly!
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
Damn it all!
And just when we got
our freedom back, too!
There's no way I'm goin'
down now without a fight!
If you think we're
just gonna roll over
and die after all the
crap we've been through,
you got another
thing coming, pal!
Let's take him down!
[RISKY BRO. MASK]
You heard him!
It's do or die!
Stop it, all of you!
This guy's way
too strong! Back off!
Even the ones he didn't touch!
It's almost like something
shot right through them!
[RANDOM ROLLING PIRATE 375F]
Aww, dammit!
[KUMA]
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Shall I begin the
annihilation with you?
[ZORO] What's with this padding
on the palms of his hands?
It's deflecting all my attacks!
[KUMA]
It is my ability
and your time is up.
[ZORO]
So be it.
I'll give the fight you want.
If I die here and now,
then this is as far
as I was meant to go.
On the next One Piece:
"It Repels Everything.
Kuma's Paw-Paw Power."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!