[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR] In God Eneru's land,
the Upper Yard, a battle rages.
On one side, Ohm and
his guard dog, Holy.
And on the other, Wyper,
a Shandorian warrior.
Gan Fall, the Sky Knight.
And Zoro!
Each warrior loyal to his own
cause yet bound to the others
in a struggle to survive
Ohm's Ordeal of Iron.
[gasping]
You idiot!
Aisa...
[OHM]
You were so distracted
that you neglected
to protect yourselves.
Quit worryin' about
other people!
Accept it.
There's nothing you
can do to save them.
[LUFFY] "The Ordeal of Iron!
White Barbed Death Match!"
[bleating]
We're behind with you, Ohm!
[OHM]
Quite the gathering.
How many players remain
in our little game?
We have four
Divine Squad members.
And since I doubt the wounds
I dealt those two were fatal,
that leaves us with
four Shandorians
and one Blue Sea dweller.
Counting the Lord
of the Sky and Holy,
that's ten people
and two animals.
Soon we'll pare that
number down to five,
just as God Eneru predicted.
So, there we stand.
Let the game commence.
You will pay...
...for harming Wyper!
Is that so?
You'd willingly forfeit
your life for this sad speck?
Mind who you throw
your loyalty to, savage!
How dare you?!
Wyper is our leader!
You have now broken the most
sacred of Shandorian laws!
We're here to reclaim our
homeland and our honor!
You and all servants of
the abominable Eneru
will settle your debt...
...with flesh and bone!
[OHM]
You are savages.
No more worthy of reparations
than the weeds crushed
beneath my feet!
[grunts]
Who wants to die first?
Ahh! Back to Hell, demon!
[grunts] Huh?!
You cannot run!
Enough of this... Holy,
it's time for your Mad Dash.
[HOLY grunting]
Huh?!
[yelling]
[groaning]
[gasps, screams]
Don't stop! Finish it!
[gasps]
He's building some
kind of fence.
Damn.
He's using more of his tricks.
This could be trouble.
[grunts] No tricks here!
Behold, the Ordeal of Iron!
[DIVINE SQUAD A] The White
Barbed Death Match has begun!
So, you can put up a fence.
Big deal. I wasn't
planning to run.
[bleats]
The purpose of this barrier
isn't just to hold you.
Yes, there's a reason
it's called White Barbs.
What's that?
[WYPER]
Huh?
Show us!
[groaning]
I guess the thorns are painful.
Thanks for the warning.
So how do I get outta here
once I'm done with all'a you?
You can worry about that later,
assuming you survive.
[OHM] Only eight people
and two animals left.
I've gotta help Nami and that
old guy who saved Chopper.
Somehow...
It's Gan Fall the Sky Knight!
I have to get 'em out
of that stupid snake.
[WYPER growls]
[SNAKE roars]
[yelps]
[WYPER growling]
[LAKI]
Wyper...
I still remember the story you
told me when we were children.
[WYPER] Our ancestors
weren't born in the sky.
They originally lived
in the Blue Sea world,
in the sacred city
known as Shandora.
It was protected by
the Great Warrior Kalgara.
Until 400 years ago.
The entire city was
torn from the ground
and lifted up into Skypiea
by the Knockup Stream.
Our people were left stranded.
It must have been
very hard on them.
But at least they still had
a place they could call home.
But then, on one fateful day,
the Skypieans bared
their vicious fangs and
revealed their true intentions.
Without mercy they
seized Shandora,
claiming it as sacred ground.
Our ancestors were driven off
the land they had nourished
and cared for since
the first setting sun.
For 400 years now, we have
suffered the humiliation
of being driven away
from our birthright.
[WYPER]
Never forget, Laki.
The Upper Yard belongs to us!
We will take back what is ours!
Our homeland!
Our pride!
[KAMAKIRI] Once we kill Eneru,
there will be no need for you
to sneak around obsessing
over a single bag of Vearth.
We will return after
400 years of exile
to the true home
of the Shandorians!
If you don't think you're
up to it, stay behind!
I won't hold it against you.
[BRAHAM]
Come on, Wyper, don't say that.
You know we're up to it.
[WYPER]
Are you up to abandoning
anyone who falls
during the battle?
[WYPER] If you can step over the
bodies of your dying comrades
and keep fighting,
then follow me.
Now, I swear.
Eneru's head will be mine.
[LAKI]
Wyper...
[DIVINE SQUAD groaning]
[roars]
[LAKI grunts]
[LAKI gasps]
[LAKI]
Wyper!
[WYPER]
Huh?
[panting]
Wyper! Listen!
Laki!
Quickly! There isn't much time!
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
I had to come to give you
Kamakiri's warning!
Nobody can beat... Eneru...
You must run away!
Abandon this fight!
[WYPER grunts]
[LAKI panting]
Eneru. He's in the forest.
Enough!
Eneru is lightning itself. He
truly has the powers of a God!
Stop!
Leave! At once!
He cannot be defeated!
[WYPER]
Do as I say!
[LAKI]
Wyper...
Did I hear my name?
Eneru.
[DIVINE SQUAD A bleating]
Eneru!
Leave her be!
Laki's not here to fight!
I'm the one you want!
She has no part in this!
Laki!
Run!
[WYPER]
Laki, no!
Put the gun down!
Laki! Run!
[gunshot]
You're a fool!
I'd forget about her and
worry more about myself!
[grunts]
[growling]
[panting]
[KAMAKIRI]
Laki... Hear me.
He comes as lightening.
An element that man has
feared from the beginning,
and rightly so.
He can't be conquered.
[growling]
[DIVINE SQUAD A grunts]
You've sealed your fate, Wyper!
Huh?
You damn fool.
Please survive.
[LAKI groaning]
[LAKI sighs]
[ENERU laughing]
[WYPER growling]
Eneru!
Huh? You should be
writhing in pure agony.
Let's try that again!
[grunts, groans]
You didn't actually
think I'd spare her?
Wyper, the "ruthless
Shandorian warrior."
Surely you understand
the concept of "no mercy"?
She opposed me,
and now she's dead.
You'll join her soon enough.
[ENERU laughing]
[DIVINE SQUAD C grunts]
[SHANDORIAN B yelling]
That's him?
That's God?
[WYPER gasping]
[OHM]
Wyper.
Weep not for her.
Laki received the
divine judgment
that all God's children
pray for. She is free.
Since we're all
gettin' personal,
there's a score I
have to settle as well.
[WYPER, ZORO]
The snake!
Time to cough up
what's in your belly!
[WYPER growls]
Get out of my way!
[ZORO, WYPER grunt]
Holy! They need a hug!
[HOLY roars]
[OHM]
Eisen Whip!
[ZORO gasps]
Axe Dial!
[groaning]
The numbers dwindle.
Six people and
two animals remain.
[roars]
[NAMI groans]
[gasps]
[PIERRE]
Pie-rre...!
Good sign.
By the looks of it, I'd say
she wasn't seriously injured.
[GAN FALL grunting]
Where in the world
is this place?
We're in the belly
of a giant snake.
We got swallowed up, remember?
Ah, yes. Of course.
The beast seems even
larger from the inside.
[AISA grunting]
[NAMI]
Aisa, are you okay?
[gasps]
Wyper, please forgive me!
[gasping]
Pierre!
[AISA]
What happened?
[NAMI]
Right, for the umpteenth time...
We've been eaten by a snake.
A snake?!
[NAMI]
Calm down. We'll survive.
If we can escape
before it digests us.
What were you two
doing out there?
You should be on the ship.
Tell that to the creeps
who were chasing us.
We had to run for lives.
Isn't that little
girl a Shandorian?
[whimpering]
Gan Fall, it's you!
[yelling] I'll mash
you into pieces!
Stop. Just calm down.
[GAN FALL laughs]
[AISA grumbles]
[NAMI]
Heh!
Anyway, why don't we
simply carve our way out?
Are you insane, old man?!
Suppose the snake
starts going wild!
You're gonna get us all killed!
Ya know, for a knight,
you're pretty dense!
I, uh, was kidding.
[NAMI]
Do you think this is a joke?
Take a look around you!
We are in a stomach!
A snake's stomach!
I don't know how much
you know about anatomy,
but it won't be long
before we're bathing
in its metabolic acid!
[grunting]
[footsteps]
[GAN FALL]
Those sounds are...
[gasping]
[whimpers]
[footsteps continue]
They're footsteps.
What else is down here?
Who goes there?
[ALL grunt]
[GAN FALL]
Hm?
[BOTH gasp]
[cries]
Nami! Weird knight guy!
It's you.
Luffy...
[LUFFY] I was starting to think
I was the only one here.
Isn't this the strangest cave?
[PIERRE chirps]
Huh. That's an understatement.
How'd you end up here?
I don't know.
I just got stuck here
and I can't get out.
Incredible.
What are the chances that each
of us would get swallowed?
This snake's turning out
to be a serious problem.
Huh, what do you
mean swallowed?
Uh! A snake?
Who'd you think this
stomach belonged to?
But... How could you
be here talking to me
if you were swallowed
by a giant snake?
Like I said!
Big, blue reptile
with mile-long fangs!
It ate us and now we're
stuck in its belly!
Ow, come on, Nami. That hurts!
Heh! Hi, I'm Usopp!
[LUFFY laughs]
Is he a... jester?
That job would suit him best
but he's actually Captain.
[gasping]
He's your captain?
My word.
What's this world coming to?
Yeah, that's pretty much
the reaction everyone has.
You sure are calm for someone
who's been eaten by a monster.
[screams]
Wait a minute! I thought that
Nami was only joking!
You mean we're being
eaten by a snake?!
I've been trying to tell you...
Its stomach acid is
melting your clothes.
[gasping]
Whoa, you're right!
Well, what're we waitin' for?
We need to find its
butthole right away!
Ridiculous.
You're despicable!
Why? Maybe we can get out
next time the snake
goes to the bathroom.
No! I'd rather get digested!
Nami's scary.
I know what you mean, child.
She's meaner than the snake.
[sighs]
Hardly. When the snake
gets in a bad mood
it starts eating people.
And speaking of which,
we'd better think fast.
Its temper was wild enough
on the outside, and be--
[LUFFY] Wait, the snake was
in a "bad mood"?
Yeah, right.
All hisses and fangs.
In fact, before it attacked us,
it was writhing in pain.
[LUFFY]
Hm. That's weird.
I wonder what was bothering it?
[ALL gasp]
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[NAMI] Luffy. What have
you been doing in here?
Oh. I was tryin' to
bust through a wall.
Didn't work, though.
[laughing]
Ah, so this is all your doing.
Throwing all those punches
burned up a lot of energy.
Say, um... Did any of you
think to bring some food?
What's wrong?
How about you eat my fist!
[growling]
[ALL gasping]
[ALL screaming]
[roars]
Heh.
What's the matter,
gotta belly ache?
It serves ya right!
[SNAKE growls]
[WYPER]
It won't be long, Aisa! Hold on!
Open up, serpent!
[SNAKE grunts]
[WYPER grunts]
I've got to get to Nami
before it's too late.
Well, unless it's
too late already.
[gasps]
You're not gonna
stand in my way.
It's time for final judgment.
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[LUFFY] Okay! Let's hurry up
and get out its butt hole!
[NAMI]
I told you, forget it!
[LUFFY]
Let's get pooped!
[ZORO]
Stand aside!
[OHM]
You misunderstand, swordsman.
Survival is not
an option for you.
Pray to God for mercy,
for I show none.
[ZORO] Don't be an idiot!
I never pray for anything!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Bursting Slash! Zoro vs. Ohm!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!