[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[SANJI]
Where is he?
[LUFFY]
Where's who?
[SANJI]
That guy!
[LUFFY]
That guy who?
[SANJI] That tin‐plated bastard!
He's not here!
[yells] Wapol! Where do
you think he ran off to?
He's going down!
What did they do to it?!
Drum Castle used
to be a stately palace;
now it's a snow‐covered hovel!
[CHOPPER]
Doctorine?
[KUREHA]
Hm?
That guy... Did you hear him?
[KUREHA chuckles]
[CHOPPER]
He called me his friend.
[LUFFY]
"When the Kingdom's Rule Ends!
The Flag of Faith
Flies Forever!"
[NAMI]
We've gotta get Vivi home!
I've spent enough
time resting...
Doctorine doesn't
seem to be around,
so maybe I can slip away
without her noticing.
Huh?
[WAPOL]
Heh.
Great! Looks like
the coast is clear.
[WAPOL laughs]
Wh‐What the‐‐?! Who's he?!
[WAPOL chuckles]
Well, well, another
Straw Hat, I presume!
[NAMI]
Uh‐oh! He doesn't look friendly!
[WAPOL chuckles]
[NAMI] Huh?! Straw Hat?
What's that mean?
I'm sorry, sir, but I don't know
what you're talking about.
What?! Oh... I was wrong?
[NAMI] Yes. I'm just a traveler
who was passing through
and I'm actually
on my way out.
[WAPOL]
Oh, I see...
[NAMI]
Nice talking to you. See ya.
[WAPOL]
Right...
‐‐Huh?
‐‐Liar! Ah!
[NAMI screams]
[WAPOL] The king of this country
commands you to stop!
[screaming continues]
[NAMI] No! I won't!
Get away from me, you big creep!
[WAPOL laughs]
[WAPOL yells]
[NAMI gasps]
I must have
gained weight recently!
Well, I can fix that!
Munch Munch Factory!
What is he‐‐?!
[WAPOL grunts]
He... turned into a bucket?!
[WAPOL] Ah! My miraculous bone
structure shaping technique
is now complete!
[gasps]
I'm lean and mean!
[NAMI gasps]
And I'm hungry!
[NAMI]
No!
[WAPOL laughs]
[NAMI yelps]
Time to gobble
you up, Straw Hat!
‐‐[laughs]
‐‐[LUFFY] Found you!
[WAPOL]
Huh?
[NAMI sighs]
Hey? That's funny...
Wasn't that guy
a big fatso before?
Gah!
[LUFFY grunts]
So... Do you mind
telling me why the coat
I kindly loaned you is all
torn up before I murder you?
[LUFFY gasps]
Do you have any idea how
much I paid for that thing?!
Twenty‐eight thousand,
eight hundred Berries!
That was after haggling!
Hey, wait! I didn't do it;
that loud mouth over there did!
It's not my fault he
shot a cannon at me!
[NAMI sighs]
Okay...
Then, in that case, Luffy,
I guess I can forgive you...
To be honest, I should have
known that you would've never
brought it back in
good condition when
I let you borrow it.
You can just pay me back at
my usual 300% interest,
which comes to...
one hundred thousand...
Agh! You should have said!
I would never have
taken it, then!
[chuckles]
Hello! I'm still here!
Oh! That's right!
I still gotta kick your butt!
Hah! I'll be the one
doing the butt‐kicking!
Behind me lies this
castle's arsenal,
and I'm the only one
who has the key to it!
Inside its walls are some of
the most fearsome weapons
known to man...
All I need to do is devour
them, Straw Hats...
Then my Munch Munch
Shock will make them
part of my body...
And you'll be forced to face
a fearsome living weapon
the likes of which
you've never seen!
The two of you don't
stand a chance!
[WAPOL laughs]
I hope you're ready
to die, Straw Hats,
because I'm going... Hey...
[screams
[LUFFY]
Huh?
This isn't over!
[LUFFY] Hey! He's getting
away! Come back!
[WAPOL] At least I've got
another trump card!
[NAMI] This must be
the key to the arsenal
he was yapping about.
Jeez, why couldn't
it have been the key
to this castle's treasure
vault? Oh, man...
[SANJI] Nami, my love! Thank
heavens! I'm glad you're safe!
Sanji! What happened?
Why are you crawling?
Are you okay?
I'm great now that
I've seen you, Nami dear,
but there are two things that'll
make me feel even better!
If I could just rest my head
on your warm, billowy‐‐
[NAMI]
No way!
[SANJI]
Pretty... please?
[LUFFY]
Run all you want!
You can't get away from me,
you stupid loud mouth!
[WAPOL grunts]
The upper levels
are full of snow, too?!
Trash my castle and
defy my orders, will they?
They won't get away with this!
It's time I taught those
insubordinates a lesson!
[WAPOL]
A painful lesson...
[WAPOL] To do so,
I'll use the ultimate weapon
of the entire Drum Kingdom...
My devastatingly lethal
Tin Titan Royal Crown
Seven Barrel Cannon!
[laughs]
Oh, yeah?!
Well, I've got you cornered!
On the contrary,
rubber man! Time to die!
[WAPOL growls]
[WAPOL grunts]
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
[tweeting]
[tweets
[gasps]
Snow birds! Cool!
[LUFFY]
Aww...! [laughs]
Stop it! How
dare you laugh at me?!
Shut up!
[VILLAGER C]
I have to admit I was skeptical
when I heard about this
ropeway to the castle.
[VILLAGER D]
But here it is, just like
the young man told us...
[VILLAGER E]
This place looks familiar.
Didn't it used to
be Dr. Kureha's house?
[ZORO]
Great view from this thing, huh?
[USOPP] Yeah, but isn't it just
the teensiest bit overcrowded?
[VILLAGER F] We can't let Dalton
go alone when he's injured!
[VILLAGER G]
We'll fight alongside him!
[USOPP]
Okay, I get it!
But we're so overloaded;
it'll take forever to get there!
[DALTON pants]
You! You gotta peddle faster!
Dalton! Please! Just relax.
[DALTON]
Wapol...
[WAPOL] Who do you
think you are, Dalton?
"There's no medicine that
can cure fools," you say...
Did you call me,
the king, a fool?
What, do you think you're
some hero who speaks
for the lowly subjects of my
kingdom?! Don't make me laugh!
You're just a servant!
[WAPOL] A week in this cell
will give you plenty of time
to reflect on your mistake.
There's nothing like prison
to change a man's attitude.
And just in case
that doesn't work,
I'm gonna have that rebellious
streak beaten out of you!
[laughs]
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[DALTON groans]
[KUROMARIMO] You're an excellent
guard the citizen's trust.
Don't be a fool.
Apologize to the king and
show him respect, Dalton.
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[DALTON groans]
[CHESS] That dead doctor
Hiriluk was an idiot!
I can't believe you
fell for his nonsense!
Risking your status
and insulting the king?!
Have you lost
your mind, Dalton?!
[WAPOL] I'll grant you
a full pardon, Dalton.
All you have to do
is get on your knees
and say the following:
"I'm so sorry,
oh, great King Wapol.
You always know what's
right for this country!"
[laughs]
To hell with status!
To hell with the king!
[WAPOL]
Hm?
[tweets]
You dare mock me, too?!
Stupid bird!
I'm the king of Drum!
Yeah, so what?
[LUFFY]
It doesn't matter...
if you're a king or
even if you're a god...
It doesn't matter if
you're someone who's great
or someone who's not‐so‐great!
I'm still gonna
kick your lousy butt!
[WAPOL chuckles]
It does matter, Straw Hat!
Drum Kingdom is a member
of the World Government!
Don't you know
what that means?!
It means this
is a capital offense
because I'm the king!
Like I said,
big mouth, it doesn't matter!
King or no king,
I'm taking you down!
Oh, really? Well, not if I...
...take you down
first, Straw Hat!
[LUFFY chuckles]
That won't work!
[WAPOL]
But this will!
Munch Munch Shock!
Tongue Cannon!
Agh! His tongue
turned into a cannon!
[WAPOL]
Goodbye!
[screams]
[DALTON coughs]
[VIVI] Dalton! Someone
help me lift him!
Dalton, can you
hear me?! Dalton?!
Say something, please!
You can't die! You just can't!
Dalton! Please!
[DALTON groans]
I'm okay.
Please don't die...
[pants]
[DALTON]
I won't... I can't!
Not until I've put an end
to Wapol and what
he's done to this country!
[CHESS] "A government should
care about its country
and its people"?
You mean you weren't joking?
That's what you
really think, Dalton?
Please! A government
doesn't need to have a heart!
That's right!
It just needs to
control the people!
[gasps]
[WAPOL chuckles]
[DOCTOR A] What‐What are
you doing?! Unhand me!
Stop it! Let me go!
You can't do this!
I have patients who will
die if I don't treat them!
Throw him in the ocean!
If he resists, you have my
permission to shoot him!
[DOCTOR A] No! Think of
my patients at least!
They're the ones
who are going to suffer!
Don't do this!
[DALTON] To hell with
controlling the country!
[DALTON growls]
[HIRILUK] Good...
Then none of them are sick...
I'll show them what
happens to a country
that doesn't have a heart!
[gasps]
[ZORO]
Hm?
[VILLAGERS murmur]
[USOPP]
Dynamite?!
Everyone, listen...
Once we arrive, take cover,
because once I'm inside,
there'll be explosions.
Chopper, are you worried
about your friend?
[CHOPPER]
No, Doctorine, not at all!
Know why? 'Cause he's a pirate!
[WAPOL laughs] That idiot!
He let his guard down!
[laughs]
[LUFFY chuckles]
Whoa, look who's talking!
‐‐Huh?!
‐‐One... two...
Hey, what are you doing?!
Now stop!
Gum Gum...
[LUFFY]
...Blowgun!
[WAPOL screams]
[WAPOL groans]
[WAPOL growls]
[CHOPPER]
Doctorine...
[KUREHA] It certainly seems
like it's finally over...
The long nightmare
has reached its end.
Its end...
[HIRILUK]
This country is sick right now.
[HIRILUK] The people and
the king both suffer from
a terrible sickness
of the heart.
And one day, I'll end up
saving this country
with medical science!
[VILLAGER D] Get out
of here, you crazy quack!
[VILLAGER E]
Don't ever come back!
[HIRILUK]
It's Wapol's guards! Run!
[CHOPPER laughs]
[laughs]
[yells]
I told ya not to
mess with that flag!
Now I'm finally
gonna kick your butt!
[screams
[LUFFY]
Gum...
[CHOPPER]
Doctor...
[WAPOL]
Wait a minute!
I'll give you a medal and
a position in my cabinet!
[LUFFY]
Gum... Gum...
Look! There's
something going on,
on top of the castle!
[CHOPPER]
Doctor...
This...
This Kingdom...
Drum Kingdom, it's...
[yells]
[screams]
Fine! I'll make you vice‐king!
[CHOPPER]
It's... about to fall!
...Bazooka!
[WAPOL screams]
[gasps]
[KUREHA chuckles]
[LUFFY chuckles]
[KUREHA] So the Drum Kingdom
was ultimately defeated by
the Skull and Crossbones...
[cackles]
[USOPP]
Everybody, wait here!
I'll brave whatever dangers
lie ahead and let you know
when it's safe!
[gasps]
Agh! I'm going first!
Hey?! What the
hell are you doing?!
Just watching your back!
Hiding behind it's more like it!
Why'd you even come
if you're so scared?!
[LUFFY grunts]
[USOPP]
Me? Scared? Don't be ridiculous!
I always laugh at
the face of danger!
[LUFFY yells]
Mommy!
Luffy?!
Zoro?! Usopp?!
[ALL yell]
[gasps]
[LUFFY grunting]
[laughs]
Why'd you do that, ya moron?!
I didn't recognize you at first!
[laughs]
I thought you were
more of big mouth's guards
coming to fight!
Whoa, I'm really surprised you
guys came all the way up here!
Well, not you,
Zoro. But you, Usopp.
Aren't you normally
scared of doing stuff
like climbing mountains?
[laughs]
Yeah, right!
Whenever there's a
towering peak in front of me,
I get to climbing!
But let me tell you,
scaling that mountain
hand over hand was no picnic!
Actually, we took a
ropeway car up here, Luffy.
[USOPP groans]
[VIVI] Nami and Sanji‐‐
are they all right?
Yeah! Both of them
are just fine!
Oh! Thank goodness!
[chuckles]
Here's why! We're on the way...
Then! A giant condor flew out
of nowhere and attacked us!
So... What was that
you were doing on top
of the castle a few minutes ago?
[LUFFY] Beating the crap
out of the king.
[ZORO]
Oh... Okay...
[DALTON] You mean that person
I saw flying through the air,
it was actually Wapol?!
You‐You beat him?!
Yep! I sure did!
[USOPP] ...I threw a rope around
his neck and showed that bird...
And his two henchmen?
What happened to them?
Oh, well, the
reindeer beat them up.
What? Those two? A reindeer?
Once again, Captain Usopp
saved the day!
Oh, hey, Usopp...
I made a new friend
and you gotta meet 'em!
Get this‐‐he's a reindeer!
Reindeer?
A reindeer...
[DALTON]
Could it be...?
[DALTON gasps]
It is you...
[DALTON]
Stop!
I apologize for
those who had the nerve
to laugh at Hiriluk's death!
[CHOPPER gasps]
[DALTON] Without enough
strength you'd only die in vain.
Don't waste your life...
Don't sacrifice it
for this country...
Blue Nose...
You never gave up...
...did you?
You still kept fighting...
believing in what this
country could become.
[DALTON]
And now, thanks to you...
...Drum Kingdom...
It can... finally be reborn!
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
Wha‐What is that
strange creature
behind that tree?!
It... almost looks like a...
...reindeer...
No... You're wrong! It's a...
...monster!
No! Don't shoot him!
[screams] It's a yeti!
No! Somebody shoot it!
[CHOPPER sobs]
[LUFFY growls] You jerk face!
He's not a yeti you idiot!
He's my new friend!
That thing's your friend?!
[LUFFY] You guys scared
him so bad he ran away!
[CHOPPER screaming]
[LUFFY] I'll bring him back so
you can meet him, you jerks!
[VILLAGERS]
Hey!
[LUFFY]
Come back, reindeer!
I want to introduce
you to my friends!
Would you stop
running for a second?!
[CHOPPER]
No!
[LUFFY]
But my friends wanna meet you!
[CHOPPER]
No, they wanna shoot me!
[LUFFY] That's just 'cause
they don't know you yet!
[CHOPPER screams]
[LUFFY] Hey, slow down!
Where are you going?!
My friends are back that way!
Don'tcha wanna meet 'em?!
[CHOPPER] Doctor...
This is for the best...
...isn't it?
[LUFFY]
They're not so bad! You'll see!
Come back and meet 'em!
They're my friends!
[CHOPPER] With friends like
yours, I don't need enemies!
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[CHOPP] Doctorine, thanks
for teaching me medical science
over the last few years.
[CHOPPER] Even though life
here wasn't always easy for me,
I love this country!
However, I've decided to leave.
When the Straw Hats
set sail, I'll be with them!
[CHOPPER]
I'm gonna go see the world!
[KUREHA]
Don't sound so cocky.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms!
Miracle in the Drum Rockies!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!