[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention of
the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from
the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived
at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace.
In their attempt to save Ace,
the Whitebeard Pirates
have launched
an all-out assault on any Marine
standing in their way.
And now the battle is really
starting to heat up!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Giant Rifle!
[LUFFY yells]
Hey, Ace!
[PIRATES cheer]
[PIRATE AA] He toppled
a giant all on his own!
Hell yeah, Straw Hat!
You took him down
with one punch!
[LUFFY yells]
I'm back!
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, Straw Hat?
If you were aiming to
get their attention,
I think you succeeded.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Do not let the foremost
group advance any further!
Hold them off and put that
rookie in the ground!
Damn it!
Make 'em pay!
[MARINES yell]
[PIRATES yell]
[MARINE AA groans]
[MARINE B yells]
[MARINE B grunts]
[PIRATE CC groans]
[ACE whimpers]
Enough beatin'
around the bush!
Let's launch a frontal attack
and join Pops inside the bay!
Whatever it takes to save Ace!
Drive them back with
everything you've got!
[RAMBA PIRATES yell]
[PIRATES groan]
We gotta fight the
vice admirals too?
Those guys're too strong!
I don't think we have
any other options.
Well, this is gonna be
rough, but do it for Ace!
[PIRATES yell]
[ACE] They're all going
to get themselves killed!
Bazooka unit ready!
Now fire at Whitebeard!
Look out!
[MARINES yelp]
[ACE]
Dammit! Please don't do this!
[MARINE E yells]
Now, slash him to pieces!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Twin Pistol!
[MARINE EE growls]
[LUFFY]
Back off!
You're not gonna stop me
from saving my brother,
so you might as well
get outta my way!
[ACE]
Luffy! Why do you care so much?
Why do any of them care?
I deserve to die like this!
Why can't they see I'm not worth
risking their lives for?
We, the 2nd division of
the Whitebeard Pirates,
will save our commander, Ace,
no matter what the cost!
--[PIRATES] Yeah!
--[PIRATES] Right!
[ACE]
Please don't do this.
Just stop.
Just let me die like
I'm supposed to!
[LUFFY]
Ace!
You're my brother!
You can't be this stupid!
Stop, Luffy! Turn around, Pops!
[GARP]
What is it, Ace?
[ACE]
I'm ready.
[ACE] Ready to accept
whatever I deserve.
[ACE] I'll accept any help
that's offered to me.
[ACE] But I'll also
accept any punishment.
Either one.
Whichever comes first.
I'm just ready for
all this to end.
On my signal, men! Fire!
[PIRATES gasp]
[PIRATES scream]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Balloon!
[MARINES yelp]
[PRISONERS gasping]
Look at that punk,
it's like he's tryin'
to steal the show.
Like this's his war!
It should be
Captain Buggy's!
I think it's time, boss.
You gotta stand up and show
the world who you are!
This is the perfect moment
for you to defeat Whitebeard!
Maybe I will! Maybe I will!
[laughs]
[BUGGY]
I gotta keep stalling!
This war is completely bonkers!
It's nothing but monsters
on both sides!
I'll just keep my head
down and stay quiet.
[WHITEBEARD]
Hey, you. Clown nose.
[BUGGY gasps] What the hell
did you just say to me?!
Are you cruisin' for
a bruisin', punk?!
Uh...! Huh?
[BUGGY groans]
I take it back!
I thought I recognized you.
You worked for Roger back
when you were a just a brat.
It's been a while,
but it doesn't look like
things've changed too much.
[BUGGY] I can't believe
I just threatened him!
He's gonna kill me!
[MR.3]
Yep, he's a dead man!
His only chance is to run!
Holy crap, it's Whitebeard!
And he's speaking to him!
That is like the coolest
thing I've ever seen!
It's just further proof that you
are a genuine living legend!
[BUGGY] Don't they realize
I'm about to die?!
Must be nice if it's not
your ass on the line!
You've got an entire
battalion of prisoners.
Now, you're not planning
on challenging me, are you?
[ALL]
Damn right, he is!
Oh. Sorry 'bout that.
You probably wanted
to tell him yourself.
You give him hell,
Captain Buggy!
[BUGGY] I don't have much
choice, thanks to you morons!
[BUGGY]
Yeah! We meet at last!
Now prepare yourself!
[PRISONERS cheer]
[MR.3]
Jeez, he is pushing his luck
right off the edge of a cliff!
[WHITEBEARD]
Oh, yeah?
It doesn't bother me if
you're hungry for a fight.
But if you beat me,
then what's next?
Might be more Navy soldiers than
you can handle on your own.
Aw, hell.
If I'm being honest, they're
more than I can handle.
Now, I'm not one to back down
from a challenge,
but it would make more sense
to form an alliance.
Once we're done,
then you can kick my ass.
--[BUGGY] Huh...?
--[PRISONERS cheer]
Oh, holy crap!
Whitebeard actually recognizes
you as his brother in arms!
He considers you an equal!
[MR.3] No, he called him a brat
like one minute ago!
Don't tell me you're gonna
try to take on the Navy!
You don't really think
you can win, do you?
[BUGGY] Well, yeah.
I've just gotta go all out.
[MR.3] Oh! He's completely
lost his grip on reality!
Seriously?!
Oh, I've got goosebumps!
[BUGGY] You know what?
Maybe I can do this!
Maybe I really was
destined to be king,
standing on top of the world!
[BUGGY] Hm... I think you
might be on to something.
Let's join forces and
take down the Navy.
[PRISONERS cheer]
This is amazing!
Man! It's too much!
All right, you win, Whitebeard.
I'll partner with you.
But only 'cause
you're beggin' me to.
[ALL]
Huh?! So arrogant!
Oh, well! That's Captain Buggy!
[MR.3]
What's wrong with them?!
Did he pull some kind of
brainwashing technique
on these idiots?!
[MARCO] Hm. Well, that guy is
unbelievably easy to manipulate.
He's a fool, to say the least,
but the prisoners
he's got behind him
are something else entirely.
The last thing we need
now is more enemies.
--[PRISONERS cheer]
--[BUGGY laughs]
Now. Back to the war.
All ships in the back, come
forward and deploy backup!
It's time to show 'em
what we're made of!
[DECALVAN PIRATES yell]
[MARINE HH panting]
I have a report, sir!
All of the pirates
stationed in the rear
are currently heading this way!
It took them long enough.
Calling the forward
unit at the bay head.
Change the formation as
the Fleet Admiral ordered.
Prepare to deploy strategy.
All units!
Start backing up,
but keep fighting!
And make sure
you retreat slowly!
Did they stop firing on us?
Yeah, and it looks like
they're starting to pull back!
Those Navy bastards
are starting to buckle!
One more push and we got 'em!
[PIRATE FF]
Enemy ships on both sides!
It's too late now!
They can't stop us
from charging the bay!
Right.
Now's our chance to finally join
Pops at the center of the fight.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL A]
Pudda pudda pudda pudda.
Pudda pudda pudda pudda. Click.
[WHITEBEARD]
Come in, this is Whitebeard.
Put Squard on the line, now.
Oh, Pops! You need
Captain Squard?
Well, he, um, he was right
here just a few moments ago,
but now, uh, the thing is, I'm
not seeing him anywhere, sir.
[MARCO]
Yeah, go figure.
All that tough talk and
then he's not even around
when you ask for his help.
[WHITEBEARD]
Mm... Well, so it goes.
Get me the DeCalvan
Brothers, then.
Hey, Pops. What's up?
Yeah, Pops. What's up?
I want you to follow my lead.
Take command of all pirate
divisions around you.
[LEFT EYE]
You got it!
[RIGHT EYE] Yes, sir!
And what's the command?
[WHITEBEARD]
Just focus on sinking
the approaching Navy ships.
What?! But, Pops, this is
the best shot we've had
at making a frontal assault
since the battle got started!
Yeah, you're not
givin' up, are you?
Just trust me on this one.
I've got a bad feeling
about those ships.
Well, you can count on us, Pops!
That's right! We got it!
We'll spread the order
to the other captains!
Really? That's
straight from Pops?
Well, all right then.
I can take the right side.
I got it, we'll take
the left side.
Right. Understood.
We'll join in on the
right side, too.
Okay, if that's what Pops wants.
My ship can take any direction.
Whatever works best.
Squard's missing?
No, I haven't seen him lately.
How unusual.
Sure thing.
We'll take the left flank.
Excuse me, Fleet Admiral, sir,
but the pirates of the New World
have altered their
battle tactics!
Yes. It seems they've
turned to the sides.
[MARINE I] They've suddenly
started attacking
the approaching Navy ships!
[PIRATES yelling]
Your bluff's been called.
Whitebeard must've sensed
something's wrong.
[SENGOKU] So I tried a cheap
trick and he didn't fall for it.
I'll admit it was
a bit too obvious.
But still,
he can't prevent the inevitable
just because he sees it coming.
Uh! Dammit! There's
too many of them!
I don't see how we'll
ever break through!
[IVANKOV]
Death Wink!
[MARINES yelp]
[LUFFY gasps]
[IVANKOV]
Hee-haw!
Whoa, Iva, you're all right!
[IVANKOV grunts]
Iva, we've gotta clear these
jerks out to get to Ace!
--Jimbei!
--[JIMBEI] Hm?
[MARINES yelling]
Fishman Karate!
[IVANKOV]
Death...
[LUFFY]
And Gum-Gum...
Five Thousand Brick-Fist!
[IVANKOV]
...Wink!
[LUFFY]
...Bazooka!
[MARINES scream]
[screams]
On we go!
[MARINES scream]
[LUFFY yells]
I'm coming!
Do not let them
get any farther!
[laughing] Ah, Straw Hat!
You don't really think
you can get past me?
Him again?!
[JIMBEI] I shall be your
opponent this time!
What are you talking about?
[JIMBEI] My karate skills
will be more than adequate
to thwart you. Alone.
That's a mighty fine speech.
I'm impressed! [laughs]
But that's good!
'Cause once I take care of you,
my zombies can run wild again!
You keep moving, Luffy!
Don't waste a moment
on this villain!
[LUFFY]
I won't! Thanks a lot, Jimbei!
Ah. I can't believe I'm
letting Straw Hat slip past me.
So, Jimbei.
Are you really so delusional
that you think you can
beat me on dry land? Huh?
[MARINES murmur]
[MARINE I]
Oh, man.
I liked it better when
Jimbei was on our side!
The Seven Warlords are a
crucial part of our forces!
It just doesn't seem right
to fight each other!
--Huh?
--What's up? Is something wrong?
[MARINE J]
It's my shadow.
[MORIA cackles] Now, suffer
damnation, Navy soldiers!
For your shadows
shall fight for me!
[MARINES gasping]
[MARINES groan]
[MORIA cackles]
[cackles]
Since you know all of
my secrets, Jimbei,
did you know that my power
grows exponentially
with every shadow I consume?
I'm guessing not,
or you wouldn't have so
foolishly challenged me.
So you got bigger. Pointless.
The power you flaunt is
stolen from others.
Your selfishness is not your
strength, but weakness.
[MORIA]
Shut up!
We'll see how smug you are
when I turn you into sushi!
[MORIA cackles]
[MORIA] And I'm gonna add your
shadow to my collection!
[MORIA cackles]
You'll spend the rest of your
life toiling within my darkness.
How does that sound?
[JIMBEI growls]
I'll take that shadow now!
[MORIA cackles]
[JIMBEI grunts]
You're rather fast for such
a hulking fellow, aren't you?
You're the only hulking
fellow here, you imbecile.
[MORIA growls]
Fishman Karate!
[JIMBEI]
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
[MORIA growls]
[MORIA groaning]
And Shark Brick Fist!
[MORIA groans]
In the end, you gave up
those coveted shadows
of yours rather easily.
Perhaps you should
train yourself more.
It's time you gave up
and let me pass.
I'm done with you.
My only concern is Ace.
[MORIA]
You don't get to lecture me!
This fight's not over!
[IVANKOV grunts]
[MARINE LL grunting]
[MARINE MM grunting]
--[LUFFY grunts]
--[MARINE LL groans]
That's Straw Hat!
[SMOKER]
Huh?
Move, Tashigi!
[LUFFY groans]
Jeez!
It's you!
Smokey!
I finally found you.
About time.
[IVANKOV]
Huh? No, Straw boy!
Kuma! Would you just
stop already?
[IVANKOV]
Oh, no, no, no, no!
[IVANKOV screams]
[LUFFY]
Oh, yeah.
I forgot that his weapon is
tipped with Sea Prism Stone.
That cheater!
Fine. Second gear!
I'm not gonna let you
get away this time.
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Jet Gatling!
White Launcher!
You're a lot stronger
than you used to be.
[TASHIGI]
Straw Hat!
[grunts] He vanished! Uh!
[SMOKER]
He's fast! Where is he? Huh?
[LUFFY yells]
Seems I can return
the compliment.
You're a real force
to be reckoned with.
[LUFFY grunts]
[SMOKER grunts]
--[LUFFY groans]
--[SMOKER grunts]
[MARINES gasp]
[LUFFY groaning]
Hate to tell you, though,
you're still not strong
enough to beat me.
Whoa, Commodore Smoker
just pinned Straw Hat!
He's amazing!
Dammit! Ya cheap jerk!
Move that thing!
After all this time, I finally
understand the truth.
I know why Dragon
really helped you.
If it weren't for him that day,
you'd be dead.
You may've had Dragon
to save you in Loguetown,
but no one's gonna
save you today!
[groans] This sucks!
[HANCOCK]
Get your filthy hands off him!
[SMOKER groans]
My body's smoke...
how'd she hit me?
You can't just kick him!
He ate a Logia fruit!
[MARINE OO]
Wait a sec!
Why did the pirate empress
just save Straw Hat?
Hey, Hancock!
What the hell's wrong with you?
Don't tell me you're resigning
from the Warlords?
Shut your mouth!
The screaming fury in my heart
has rendered me deaf
to your words!
How dare you pin
my beloved down
with your boorish club
and threaten him?
You will die for your actions.
I've never felt this angry
in my entire life!
I'll feed you piece by
piece to wild animals!
The Kuja's Haki
is overwhelming.
[LUFFY coughs]
Thanks, Hancock!
[HANCOCK giggles]
Of course!
Also, I'm happy you got
my name right again!
[ALL scream]
[IVANKOV]
Please! Listen, that's enough!
Kuma! Look. It's me!
Have you forgotten my face?
If you don't stop, friendship
be damned, I will fight back!
[DOFLAMINGO laughs] I don't
know what kind of a history
you two have, but
it doesn't matter.
Trust me, Emporio Ivankov.
There's really no use in
talking to him as he is now.
Doflamingo. What're you saying?
Is something wrong with him?
[DOFLAMINGO] You're clearly a
friend of Bartholomew Kuma's,
so I doubt you'll
take this well.
The man you knew as
"The Tyrant Kuma"
is not the man you see
before you now.
Because that man is dead.
Huh? But that can't be true!
[DOFLAMINGO laughs]
How can Kuma...
be dead?
[NARRATOR]
Facing Kuma on the battlefield,
Ivankov reveals they
were once friends.
However, Iva's pleas to his
companion fall on deaf ears
as Kuma continues his attacks.
In a sea on confusion
only Doflamingo
seems to know the truth.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Kuma's Transformation!
Iva's Blow of Anger!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!