[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention of
the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind
of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Separated from the
rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy is headed to
the Navy Headquarters
rescue his brother, Ace.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, with
Ace's looming execution
only a few hours away,
the Whitebeard Pirates
suddenly appear at Navy HQ.
[WHITEBEARD]
We've got plenty to talk about.
Like you not killing my son.
[ACE]
Father!
[NARRATOR]
In an instant,
the silence is broken
and all-out war erupts.
[MORIA]
What the...? That's not right.
And here comes the final payoff.
That harmless seaquake he
threatened us with earlier
was just the prelude
to a massive tsunami!
[MARINE CC]
It's a tsunami!
[AOKIJI]
Ice Age!
[DOFLAMINGO]
Huh?
You gonna grace them with
your sword for once?
[MIHAWK]
I'm just gauging the distance.
How far do you think he is?
Strange, but somehow
it feels like...
he's standing right
in front of us.
[LUFFY]
"An All-Consuming Inferno!
Admiral Akainu's Power!"
Ah!
Run away!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES scream]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE C]
Pops, no!
[JOZU yells]
[WHITEBEARD]
Hmm.
That's insane!
He blocked the world's
greatest swordsman.
[JOZU grunts]
No! It...
It's him.
[MARINE A] Third division
commander, Diamond Jozu!
[MARINE B gasps, groans]
[MARINES groan]
Wouldn't let my guard
down, if I were you!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE D]
C'mon, guys!
Keep advancin' on
the front line!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yell]
Push them back!
[MARINES yell]
Damn fools.
They're trying to break
through from the front.
[SENGOKU]
Attenion artillery unit!
Open fire on all enemy ships as
well as the approaching pirates!
[MARINES]
Sir!
[MARINE AA]
Forward units!
Block off all access
to this plaza!
[MARINES]
Sir!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES groaning]
[MARINE F groans]
My, my.
[KIZARU]
Whitebeard's commanders
are a frightening bunch of
monsters, aren't they?
Though I do admit,
they put on a good show.
[KIZARU] Still, if we want
to stop this party
before they wreck the place,
we simply need to remove the
head of this unruly, behemoth.
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES grunt]
It's so bright!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE F]
What the hell?!
Ah! It's Kizaru!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
It's too bright.
Could ya tone it
down a little, pal?
[KIZARU]
Hm?
[WHITEBEARD chuckles]
He stopped the Admiral's
attack, but how?
I dunno!
It's almost like he's got wings!
Huh? Well, fancy that!
[MARCO]
The king's off limits.
If you wanna reach him...
...you gotta go
through me first.
Scary.
These Whitebeards play rough.
What the...?
He's on fire!
[MARINE J]
He took Kizaru's attack head on
and he's just... floating there!
[MARINE K] I dunno what
kind of Devil Fruit that is,
but I don't like it!
Even more rare
than Logia powers.
Zoan type. Mythical creature.
[MARINE BB]
Look! His wounds are healing!
[MARINE CC]
This can't be real.
That didn't hurt him at all?
Oh, it did.
Don't lie to protect my pride.
[MARCO yells]
So that must be the 1st
division commander. Whoa.
"If his flames can't
turn away an attack,
then they can heal
him when it's done!"
Marco the Phoenix!
Look at that lovely bird.
It must be quite rare!
[KIZARU]
Uh?
[MARCO grunts]
Well, that's quite
the painful kick!
Now you're lying! Ha!
[MARINES gasping]
Just standing here
is dangerous enough!
He okay? Kizaru!
[MARINES gasp]
[KIZARU]
Hm... My fault.
I really should've known better.
If your boss was
that easy to kill,
you wouldn't be here
right now, would you?
Heh.
Hey, giant unit, keep an eye
on the sky from now on!
[GIANT MARINES grunt]
[MARINES gasp]
Aw, crap, here come the giants.
Everyone, knock 'em down!
Attack their feet!
Outta the way! Clear a path!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES]
Uh?
Jozu!
[JOZU grunts]
[MARINES gasping]
Is he breaking the ice?
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE H]
Okay, retreat!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES whimper]
What the hell is he doing?!
[JOZU yells]
Try blocking this one!
[MARINE R]
It's gonna crush us!
[MARINE DD]
We can't outrun it!
Damn those two, cocky hotheads.
What were they thinking,
abandoning their
posts like that?
[AKAINU] What if I had
done the same, huh?
There'd be no one here
to do their job!
It's Akainu!
Great Eruption!
He... didn't just crush
that block of ice.
He evaporated it!
Right into thin air!
Oh, no.
Run away!
Volcanic rocks!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yelp]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE AA]
There's too many of 'em!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE BB]
Aw, damnit!
The ship has been hit!
Everyone, back away!
I feel like we're watching
the apocalypse unfold here.
[WHITEBEARD growls]
Sure like to be
flashy, don't they?
[WHITEBEARD]
Hm.
Think I'll have ya light the
candles for my next birthday.
Ya magma punk.
Ha, ha. I'd rather provide the
lighting for your funeral.
How 'bout it, old man?
[MARINE 463S]
Still three ships left!
Don't fall back! Now, fire!
Push on!
[grunts]
Get to the plaza!
[MARINES groan]
[MARINE T gasps]
[HARUTO grunts]
[BLAMENCO chuckles]
[MARINES groan]
Take out the commanders
at all costs!
[MARINE EE] Don't let them get
ashore! Sink the Moby Dick!
Push forward and
aim for Whitebeard!
[COBY whimpers]
[COBY]
These are pirates, my enemy.
This isn't a training
exercise, this is war!
I can't!
[COBY] My knees are
frozen! I can't move!
[HELMEPPO]
It's pointless.
These guys would slaughter us
without a second glance!
[COBY whimpers]
I mean, you realize
that, right?
[COBY whimpers]
[HELMEPPO]
Just look around you.
They're monsters, butchers!
There's not a single
thing amateurs like us
can do against
guys like that!
We've gotta run if
we wanna live, okay?
Okay?
[COBY]
But...
Look, don't be an idiot!
There is no but!
Do you understand me?
The only thing we can
contribute to this battle
is more blood for those
killers to spill over the ice!
[COBY exhales]
Just listen!
You wanna become an
admiral, don't you?!
[COBY gasps]
Because I promised myself
that I'll keep trying.
Till, till I become
a Marine Admiral!
You said you're gonna
fight me, right?
Then you will become that
strong. You'll have to.
[COBY]
Uh...!
Hey, look!
Don't take this the wrong
way! I'm just sayin'.
That's why we should run!
We both have a future!
It's not right for either
of us to die here!
There's too much
left for us to do!
We're the chosen ones!
But, Luffy! I made a
promise to him, didn't I?
[BOTH gasp]
[HELMEPPO]
What now? Where is it?
[gasps]
Here he comes!
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES groaning]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES yell]
[MARINE W]
Attack! Kill it!
All right, bring down
their artillery defense!
[OARS JR. growls]
[MARINE X whimpers]
[ALL gasp]
[OARS JR.]
Brother Ace!
[ACE gasps]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATES cheer]
[WHITEBEARD PIRATE M] Nicely
done! Get 'em, little Oars Jr!
[OARS JR. roars]
He must be related to
the Continent Puller.
He's enormous!
At least twice as big as
one of the regular giants.
We can't let him invade
the island, no matter what!
He'll give them too much
leverage in the fight!
[MORIA cackles] Just look
at that beautiful beast!
And I didn't even know that
Oars had a living descendant!
I want it! I call his
corpse after the battle!
[DOFLAMINGO chuckles]
Now that's more like it!
[ACE whimpers]
Little Oars!
Ace is a nice guy!
He's my friend!
I'm not gunna let you hurt him.
He won't die!
[NARRATOR]
Although the Straw Hat Crew's
battle with Oars is
long in the past,
Little Oars Jr. is
still wreaking havoc
as a member of
White Beard's crew.
Bursting through the bay,
he goes head-to-head with
the Navy's team of giants in
an Earth-shaking confrontation.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Descendant of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.
Full Speed Ahead!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!