Have a nice flight!
Damn you!
Now that hurt.
If that leopard freak
wanted to piss me off,
he sure as hell did.
All right, now time
for some payback.
Damn it! Not again!
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
Interesting.
Many ships were born
in this cobwebbed room
and now look at it. Filthy.
They built ships here?
Tom, Iceberg, and Cutty Flam.
This place must hold
countless memories of days
when you still shared
a life with those two.
And now you call it
"your top secret base."
That's heartbreakingly adorable.
Damn you. Just get
the hell out already!
We won't leave till
we get what we're after.
Make this easy on yourself.
There ain't no
blueprints in here!
Oh? No? You don't say?
Hey!
Kalifa!
Dammit!
Just keep it together Usopp.
You bastard.
Take your time,
but be aware that we know
many things about your past.
Things that you
don't want getting out.
For example, we know what
happened eight years ago.
And that you are guilty
of committing a very
serious crime back then.
Just like your dear old Tom.
You shut up! Tom was
never a damn criminal!!
You don't know what the hell
you're talking about! You freak!
Tom!
Stay back!
I disagree.
You're both criminals.
And as such,
you should be made to feel the
consequences of your actions.
Franky. Whatever happens,
don't interfere with
what I'm about to do.
No matter what.
You talk like you
know everything.
You don't know Tom.
And you don't know
anything about Water Seven!
I heard the Judicial Ship
will be here in three days.
Finally putting Tom
on trial, are they?
I hope it ends well for him.
I'm sure it will.
Right. He fulfilled
his promise after all.
That he did.
Alright, let's get
that lumber in the dock!
So, how'd the deal
work out with St. Poplar?
Not that great.
They're taking advantage of us
since we don't have
much to trade with 'em.
Like iron from San Faldo.
We'll all be in the red if
this kinda crap keeps up!
We're not gonna let this keep
happenin', now are we guys?!
Yeah! No way!
The people do seem to be happy
about being able
to cross the ocean.
But they say the trade situation
isn't as good as they'd hoped.
I wonder if this town
needs more than a sea train.
Ah, but their
spirits are up, boy!
That's a major step,
so give the rest some time.
We've done our best,
so be proud, keep your head
held high and walk with gusto!
Yeah.
You there!
Am I correct in assuming
I'm speaking with Mr. Tom,
the shipbuilding engineer?!
You're a difficult
man to pin down.
I have some matter of
great importance I wish to--
Uhm Sir?
This man and I are talking!!
Yes, sir!
Again before I was so rudely--
I was going to say.
My name is agent Spandam.
From Cipher Pol Number Five!
Spandam, sir!
OW! Sorry about that! My bad!
Looks like you got in the way
of my victory cannon salute!
Tough luck! It's! Super!
Battle Franky thirty-five
comes back home with booty!
That's right. Check it out!
Is this not the biggest Sea King
you ever laid your eyes on?!
I can't believe him.
Still acting like a child.
Hey! What hell do ya think
you're doing, Ice-for-brains?!
Will you ever grow up?
Ever since you were a kid
all you wanna do is build
these stupid battleships!
It's time to stop!
This better be the last one!
Or I'm gonna start
tearin' em all apart myself!
Wanna bet?!
You lay a finger on my ship
and you'll draw back a stump!
You hear me?!
Yeah? Mwell! Listen, Franky!
If you were able
to kill a Sea King
with this floating
piece of junk
that means it's a
dangerous weapon.
And you've got all
those other "battleships"
of yours just
strewn around here?
What're you thinking?!
Hey, it's not like I'm attacking
people with them, am I?
I'm not saying you'd do that!
But you're making it easier
for anyone else who'd
want to, you idiot!
Sir--
Am I right? Back me up here Tom!
Flunky's weapons are gonna
be the end of our business!
Ah! "Flunky" That's rich!
Hold on! This is
no laughing matter!
I demand a sincere apology!
And that you listen to
what I've come here to say!
Government guy are ya?
So, is this about the trial?
Trial? What the devil
are you talking about?
No, this concerns an
altogether different matter.
Now what?
Did Tom come back with you boys?
No, I think he's with a visitor.
Some man from the government.
It wasn't about the trial.
Span-Span something.
Span-Something, dumb? Maybe?
How strange. And he's not
from the judicial ship?
The government
is so disorganized.
Fraid not.
I've got no blueprints
for something like that.
That's nonsense!
Do you take me for some kind
of weak minded simpleton?!
I researched the history of
Water Seven for countless hours!
And I am absolutely
certain this document
can only be in your possession!
You're saying that
you actually have
the authority to
investigate me?
That's right, I do!
And what's more.
I learned all about your
dealings with Gold Roger
in the course of
my investigation.
So unless you want me
to share that information
with my colleagues,
you're going to cooperate.
Why would I care? The government
already knows about it!
We do? That's utter poppycock!
If that's true,
why are you here and not rotting
away somewhere in a jail cell?
Use your investigative powers
and find out for yourself.
Good day.
Hey! You can't treat a
government agent like this!
Open the door this immediately!
That's right.
It's all true. Yes sir.
He did exactly what he
told the judge he'd do.
And they should be dropping
the charges at the
trial that's coming up.
That man saved
this island, for sure.
It makes my blood boil.
To think, that damned criminal
is being treated like a hero.
I see. You're certain that
such a thing truly exists?
Yes sir!
And the pirates are scouring
the globe for it as we speak.
That's why it's imperative
we locate it immediately.
If it were to fall
into the wrong hands,
the resulting destruction
would be inconceivable.
We've been suffering through
this "great pirate era"
for more than a decade now.
It's a vile sickness that grows
worse with every passing day.
The time for idle
discussion is over.
We must do more than to prevent
this weapon's construction.
We must build it ourselves
and use it as a mighty
instrument of justice!
With it, we can eliminate
this pirate scourge
and bring law and order
back to our land!
Hmm.
This is indeed a troubling era.
There's no doubt about that.
Your primary objective
will be to locate
and then obtain
these blueprints.
That will be all at this time.
We trust that you can complete
this mission, Spandam.
Yes sir! Without fail!
I've been working on
this case for far too long
to see it all go up in smoke.
It's right within my grasp now.
Let's go!
Damn! If the judge
decides to acquit him
that'll mean a
real headache for me.
Spandam, sir!
The charge will stick
and that bastard will hang.
Men! I'll need five
more agents, stat!
Spandam, sir!
Iceberg, Franky.
Yeah?
Hey, boys, come here.
What's up?
It's about time I let you
in on somethin' important!
Why would anyone even
dream of something like this?
Is this for real? Can this
thing actually be built?
Those are the blueprints for
a nightmare, a real monster.
The government has
learned of their existence
and has started
sniffing around for them.
It's too dangerous for
me to keep them anymore.
This is terrifying,
but I agree. I'll keep them.
Wow, Iceberg. Hey let's see
if we can build this thing!
You idiot!
Do you ever think
before you speak?!
This thing can never be built.
Do you realize how much
destruction it could cause?
Yeah, the world
would be done for.
Besides tryin' to
build the damn thing,
you can do whatever the
hell you want with it for now.
Even toss it if you need to.
Yes, of course.
While I got your attention.
Here's another storm a brewin'.
Franky! Hold on!
For what?
For your pants, you silly boy!
I swear, you'd think after
all that attention you got
last time you went out
dressed like that, you'd be
wise enough to not do it again.
Geez. I'm just goin'
out to get a few things.
Now, that you're dressed,
you can skedaddle!
Thanks. I can't believe
she's makin' a big dinner
just cause the stupid judge is
finally sayin' Tom's not guilty.
He never was in the first place.
Alright.
Rise and shine!
Tom! Iceberg! Get up!
Today's judgment day!
Don't wanna sleep
through your big trial!
Let's get down to the harbor!
They're gonna hand
down Tom's sentence!
The spectators are
boarding the ship in droves.
The people are
really interested.
Seems like it'll be a big trial.
Seems that way.
Have you had a chance to see
the sea train yet, your honor?
I have indeed. Quite impressive.
A true feat of ingenuity.
He fulfilled his
end of the bargain.
I'm certain the
people will rejoice
to see their hero go free.
Is Tom here yet?
I wish it would start already.
Come on! We gotta hurry
before all the seats are taken!
I know, I can't wait to
see the look on his face
when the judge lets him off!
What a trip! Wow, can't believe
it's been fourteen years.
The ship's under attack!
Get away from it!
Run! Hurry!
What the?!
Is this a pirate raid?!
But how? Where is this
attack even coming from?
Hey, look over there!
What? Some kind of fleet!
Those look like battleships!
Those pirates are attacking us!
There's so many of them!
Are they all working together?
Everybody! Run!
Get outta the harbor!
Hurry!
It's not safe near the water!
My baby! Where's my baby?!
What's happening?
Who the hell? Who's doing this?!
Who took my ships?
Tom! We're in trouble!
Franky's ships are
attacking the harbor!
It's not him. I saw him earlier.
He wouldn't do such a thing!
I know that! Look, I'm positive
it's not Franky doing it.
This is a whole other
kind of trouble we're in!
Let's put a stop to it!
Right!
Pirates? Or worse,
the Government.
Evacuate!
Hurry! Into the city!
Get away from the harbor!
My father's still inside!
Bastards! They're gonna pay!!
Who the hell is it, huh?!
Who the hell is screwing
around with my ships?!
Please, come with us your honor!
The ship can't take much more!
Who does that fleet belong to?
The raid on the Judicial Ship
was a success sir.
Excellent. Now, I want you to
proceed to step two immediately.
We must ensure that
justice is served.
Yes, sir!
Now, let's begin your impending
trial in earnest. Shall we, Tom?
It looks like it's
about to go down.
Alright! Let's get back
to Scrap Heap Island.
Right!
Hey. The fleet is
starting to turn around!
Hold on.
I'm pretty sure I've seen
those ships somewhere before!
Tom, look!
They're heading this way!
They're getting closer!
I think that we can catch 'em!
I can't imagine what the
hell they were thinkin'
pullin' a stunt like that!
I see two men
approaching from the island!
That's Tom. Right!
Let's abandon this ship!
What the?!
Not a soul on this thing!
Same here! I don't see anybody!
What the hell is going on here?
More of Franky's ships?
Iceberg! Watch out!
Dammit! My Battle Frankies!
They're destroyed!
Tom! Iceberg! Hey!
Can you hear me?!
Are you okay?! What in
the hell happened here?!
Tell me what's
going on. Hey! Ice--
You stupid ass!
It's your fault this happened.
It was that intelligence agent.
He used your damn battleships
to attack people at the harbor.
No I-I didn't hurt anybody.
I told you this would happen.
But you don't listen.
Listen, Franky!
If you killed a Sea
King with this ship,
then it's a dangerous weapon.
You're making it
easier for somebody
who wants to use it
like one, you idiot!
My ships did this.
They hurt Tom!
Look. We have the ability to
create powerful things, weapons.
Even if you weren't trying to.
Weapons are made to hurt people.
Whether you want them to or not,
they can hurt your friends.
That's what the
government did to us.
They used your creations
to hurt a lot of people.
People we care about!
And now they're gonna
put the blame on us.
They want to back
Tom into a corner
so they can get
those blueprints.
After all this.
You still think your hands
don't have blood on them?!
If Tom gets taken away.
If he hangs for this.
I swear on my life.
I will never forgive you!
Tom! Forgive me,
this is all my fault!
Silence! Criminals are
not allowed to speak!
That's a load of crap!
We didn't do it!
Be quiet, you hooligan!
My business is solely
with the Fish-man!
What're you gonna do to him?!
When I'm done, Tom's workers
will be a thing of the past!
On the next episode One Piece:
"The End of the Legendary Man!
The Day the Sea Train Cried."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!