[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
‐‐[PIRATE EE screams]
‐‐[PIRATES gasping]
What the...?!
[PIRATE Q yelps]
[PIRATE NN groans]
[LUFFY growls]
[PIRATES scream]
[LUFFY]
Don't you have any honor?!
Those men are your friends!
[USOPP]
There! Over there!
[LUFFY] "Anger Explosion!
Kuro vs. Luffy, How it Ends!"
[KURO]
Heh.
Aren't you tired?
I bet you are after all
that dancing around
you've been doin'.
[KURO]
Don't get cocky.
That was simply a warm up.
Huh?
[KURO]
The real fight begins now.
Soon I will be feasting
on your fear.
Complimented by the sweet
wine of your agony.
Uh!
Now!
[KURO]
Out of the Back Attack!
[LUFFY grunts]
[PIRATES murmur]
[KURO groaning]
Nice try. You jerk!
[KURO] Damn you!
Get away from me!
Wow, butler‐man! Right now
your life really sucks.
Your plan of three years is a
complete and total failure.
[KURO]
Let go!
Hey look! That weird kid
caught Captain Kuro!
I don't believe it! If that
goofy kid manages to beat him,
then that means Captain Kuro
won't be able to
slaughter us, right?!
[KAYA whimpers]
It's time to die!
‐‐[PEPPER] Oh no, you don't!
‐‐[KAYA] Uh?!
[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT yell]
[JANGO]
Ow!
Stupid, snot‐nosed brats!
[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT]
Ah!
It looks like you're one
step too late, Swordsman!
[ZORO]
Wouldn't say that!
Excellent!
That branch was getting
in the way of my shot!
What?!
Usopp, you're here.
[ZORO]
Heh.
Yeah! Get 'em you
crazy, rubber guy!
You're goin' down,
you mean bastard!
[LUFFY gasps]
[KURO]
Get off me!
[LUFFY grunts]
Just shut up!
You have no right
to cheer me on!
[USOPP]
Eat this, hypnotist!
Help me, Usopp!
[ALL]
Do it, Captain!
[KURO groaning]
Let go of me!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...!
[KURO groaning]
Now! Time for the
exploding star!
‐‐[JANGO groaning]
‐‐[KAYA screams]
‐‐[KURO] You insect!
‐‐[LUFFY] Bell!
‐‐My plan will absolutely
‐‐Bell!
‐‐not be disrupted!
[KURO]
Uh!
[LUFFY grunts]
[KURO groaning]
[PIRATES murmuring]
That crazy rubber guy
beat Captain Kuro!
[PIRATE I] Not even the marines
were a match for Kuro,
Man of a Thousand Plans!
And this guy still beat him!
[PIRATE A]
Just... just who are you?!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
The only time a pirate
should abandon his name
is when he dies!
I would never lose to a coward
who ditches his name,
betrays his friends, and
runs from life on the sea.
Uh... Luffy... I never
heard that name before.
You should remember my name
for the rest of your lives.
'Cause one of these days I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates!
[PIRATES murmur]
You are?
Now get outta here!
[PIRATES gasping]
And never come back!
[PIRATES chatter]
[NAMI panting]
[gasps]
Ya did good, Luffy.
[NAMI]
I'd expect even you to collapse
after what you just
went through. Say...
Tell me, why were
you so mad earlier?
'Cause I truly hate people
like them. They're so wrong.
That is not how
friends should act.
[NAMI]
What are you talking about?
Of course it isn't. Most
pirates aren't the brave,
honorable people you
always make out them to be.
I'd say Captain Kuro
is pretty standard.
I want some meat.
‐‐[NAMI] You're unbelievable!
‐‐[LUFFY groaning]
[USOPP]
Hey guys,
think you can keep everything
that just happened here secret?
What? A secret!
Why would we want to
keep all this a secret?!
Yeah! Why, huh?
We put our lives on the
line to save the village!
Now everyone'll change
their opinion of you so
instead of being Usopp the liar,
you'll be Usopp the hero!
[CHILDREN cheering]
Really, Usopp...
You need to clear up this
misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding...?
I was known as the village liar
because I lied all
the time, Miss Kaya.
They were right
to not believe me.
Besides, there's no
point in scaring people
with something
that's already over.
And I seriously doubt that
any more pirates like Kuro
and his gang will show up.
There's no reason for pirates
to attack our out‐of‐the‐way,
little village.
So listen up! Pretend this
never happened! 'Kay?
This was all just another
one of my great, big lies.
Now I won't force you to, but...
No, I can do it!
I'll do whatever it takes
for the good of the
village, Captain!
Yeah me too!
Me, too. My lips are
totally sealed, I promise!
[CHILDREN chattering]
Kaya... Will you...
Will you tell?
[KAYA]
No.
Something just isn't
right this morning.
Where is Usopp?
It kinda throws everything
off if he's not around.
I feel so bored.
[LITTLE GIRL]
Mama!
Is that screaming liar guy
not coming to town today?
[MAN]
That lying little twerp!
Where the heck is he?
You don't think I hurt his
feelings yesterday, do you?
Oh, don't worry.
He'll be up to his old
tricks in no time.
[MAN]
I hope so.
[USOPP laughs]
Thanks guys!
I wouldn't have been able to
protect the village without you.
Give credit where
credit's due.
If you'd just stood
by and done nothing,
I wouldn't have done
anything, either.
Yeah! Same here!
Who cares about any of that?
I've got my hands on this
sweet, sweet treasure now.
And I couldn't be happier.
[USOPP laughs]
Everything that happened
here today helped me.
I've just come to a very
difficult decision...
[LUFFY]
Uh?!
[CARROT] Captain Usopp! What did
you want to talk to us about?
[USOPP] The three of
you fought well against
those terrible
Black Cat Pirates.
As Captain, I'm proud of you
for being so brave
and courageous.
You're too kind.
We're nothing
compared to you!
You're embarrassing us!
I'm serious. You were
very courageous.
You were scared to death,
but you kept your cool,
worked together as a team
and kept Kaya safe.
Thanks to you, we overcame our
biggest and most important
battle since we formed the
Usopp Pirates five years ago.
That was when you
three brave soldiers
were only four years
old. Remember?
[CHILDREN]
Yep!
Now I know this
is sudden, but...
I've decided that I'm gonna
set out to sea by myself.
[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT]
Uh...?
I'm finally gonna leave this
place and become a real pirate!
At first, I wasn't sure
what I would do.
I couldn't decide if I wanted
to stay here forever or not.
But once I saw them, I knew deep
in my heart what I must do.
I feel that, as a man, I must
set out to the vast ocean. So...
‐‐I'm leaving this place behind!
‐‐[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT] Uh?
I leave for one reason! When
the great pirate flag beckons,
you must heed its call!
[CARROT]
Captain! Say it isn't so!
[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT panting]
You're lying again, right?!
Isn't that a bit hasty?!
There's no reason to leave!
I thought you loved
this village!
And what's gonna happen to the
Usopp Pirates without you?
[USOPP] You've been
so good to me, guys.
I plan to leave without
telling the villagers.
Give them my regards.
Captain...
No, I don't want to!
Don't go, Captain!
Just stay here! Please.
Usopp Pirates. Do you
remember this place?
This is where we first met,
and formed the Usopp Pirates.
[laughing] Finished!
[CARROT]
Hey, it's that liar guy!
[USOPP]
Huh? Who are you guys?
And why are you so
buddy‐buddy with me?
Well, duh! You're famous!
Yeah. You're a really
famous guy!
Right! I know, you've
come face to face
with the man that is known the
world over as Captain Usopp!
Actually everyone in the village
calls you Liar Usopp.
[PEPPER, ONION laugh]
[USOPP]
Ah!
'Kay! From this day forth,
you're officially members
of the Usopp Pirates!
[ALL]
Huh?
C'mon! Man up!
[whimpers] A lot's
happened since then, huh?
[DOG barks]
[USOPP]
A Cerberus! Scare it away!
A dragon! Capture it!
Flour Star!
[PEPPER]
You're amazing, Captain!
‐‐[USOPP laughs]
‐‐[CHILDREN sigh]
[USOPP] But of course! I'm
a brave warrior of the sea!
Please don't talk about the
old days! I can't stand it!
Pepper's right! It's
much too painful.
This kind of lie isn't like
you, Captain! It's not fun.
Why would you say that
you're going to leave us?
[CARROT]
You're not serious, are you?
[ONION] You're being stupid,
Captain! Stupid!
[CHILDREN cry]
All right, men! Tell me
what all your ambitions are!
When I grow up my dream
is... to run a pub!
My whole life I've wanted
to be a master carpenter!
My goal is to
become a writer!
Then, swear to me
now that each of you
will continue on your paths!
Promise me that you will never
let the fires of your
ambitions die out!
[USOPP]
As of today...
our group...
the Usopp Pirates... [cries]
[USOPP]
... are disbanded!
Now that we've eaten, we
should probably get going.
Yeah, you're right.
[KAYA]
Here you are!
Hello there, Miss!
Are you all right
being out of bed?
[KAYA]
Yes.
I think now I can truly
start recovering.
You see, my sickness this
last year was caused
by the mental shock of
losing both my parents.
And Usopp's friendship
helped me start getting better.
I can't stay in bed
forever, you know.
You've all done
so much for me.
I can't thank you enough.
I've prepared a present for you
from the bottom of my heart
to show you how grateful I am
for everything you've done here.
I'd be honored if
you'd accept it.
[sighs] All packed!
[USOPP] Guess it's farewell
to this house, too.
[USOPP]
All right.
[door opens]
[USOPP]
Hey!
[USOPP grunting]
I can't get out!
This stupid backpack!
[USOPP grunting]
[USOPP yelping]
‐‐[LUFFY] Oh!
‐‐A real caravel!
[LUFFY] Are you actually
giving this to us?!
[KAYA] Mm‐hm. As a token
of my appreciation.
[MERRY]
It's a slightly older model,
but I personally designed
it and she sails like a dream.
She has a carvel‐make
caravel with lateen sails
and a central stern rudder.
She's a fine ship, and her
name is the Going Merry.
[MERRY] Allow me to
explain the rigging.
First, about the Kruger
net yard adjustment,
it may seem a little‐‐‐
Hold on! You'd be better off
just explaining the
technical stuff to me!
[LUFFY] What a cool ship!
Have you guys seen the front?
It's totally awesome!
We've loaded it with
all the provisions
you might need on a long voyage.
[LUFFY] Thanks! It leaves
nothing to beat tired!
That's "leaves nothing
to be desired", idiot.
[USOPP yelping]
[ALL]
Uh?!
[USOPP]
Somebody stop this thing!
Oh, no, Usopp!
Hey, what's he doing?
Looks fun.
Well, we'd better stop him.
That weirdo, is on a collision
course with our boat.
Uh. Hey, thanks guys.
Anytime.
[KAYA]
You're really doing it.
You're gonna take
to the ocean.
[USOPP]
Yeah.
I've decided to get going before
I have time to change my mind.
[USOPP]
Please, don't stop me.
[KAYA] I won't. I know
it's time for you to go.
Kaya, don't be
sad about it.
Just think, the next
time I come back here,
I'll tell you about adventures
that'll sound more like lies
than my old lies.
Good. I'll look forward to it.
[USOPP] You guys take care!
I hope we meet again sometime!
How come?!
Uh. Well... Because I...
Are you antisocial
or something...?
I'm taking off for life
on the high seas,
and I hope that we'll eventually
meet again, that's all.
What are you talkin' about?
Get on already!
Huh?!
We're friends. Right? So get on.
[USOPP]
This is it...
I'm really a Pirate
Captain now!
[LUFFY] Don't be stupid,
Usopp! I'm the Captain!
[ZORO, NAMI, LUFFY laugh]
[USOPP laughs]
[ALL laughing]
[CARROT]
There goes the Captain...
[PEPPER] He fell in with
some pretty awesome people,
so I'm not too worried.
[ONION]
Yeah, he'll be safe with them.
I've never seen anybody
as strong as they are.
He's always talked about
becoming a pirate,
and now he's headed off
to live his dreams!
You know the villagers
are gonna be sad
when we break the news to 'em.
Our Captain was the only person
who could liven things
up around here.
And now he's gone.
Hey! I just had a great idea!
[ONION, CARROT]
What is it?
[MERRY] They certainly
were a pleasant bunch.
[KAYA]
Merry...
[MERRY]
Yes?
[KAYA]
Lying hurts... A lot.
[MERRY]
Are you referring to Klahadore?
[KAYA]
No.
You must be talking
about Usopp.
You really wanted him
to stay, didn't you?
Miss Kaya. Years ago, one of
the villagers told me a story
about your good friend
Usopp's childhood.
Only a short time after his
father left the village
to become a pirate.
His mother, whom he was very
close to, passed away.
[KAYA]
Uh?
[USOPP]
Pirates! Pirates are here!
[USOPP panting]
Pirates are here!
Dad's pirates are here
Mom! They're here!
Hold on, Usopp, you mustn't
shout! Calm down!
Mom, we're saved! Dad
finally came back for us!
Uh. There you go with
your wild imagination again.
You silly boy.
It's true. He always said
he'd come back for us
and take us with him when you
got better, didn't he Mom?
Usopp, my dear.
Your father won't
be coming back.
But... I'm proud to have
married such a brave man
who dared to chase
his dreams.
I heard about a
special medicine...
This stuff can cure
any sickness!
So silly. You dream too much.
I am a dreamer! And I'm silly!
It's true. I'm proud of it!
After all, I'm the
son of a pirate!
Promise me one thing.
Promise me you'll grow up
to be brave, like him.
[USOPP]
Pirates are coming!
[MERRY]
Perhaps out of loneliness.
He continued to shout it after
his mother passed away.
In the hopes that one day
his father's pirate ship
would be at the shore, ready
to spirit him away to the sea,
and give him a family
that he never had.
[MERRY] The villagers say
that his outlandish lies
contain his most heartfelt wish.
[USOPP]
Pirates! Pirates are coming!
[MERRY] As someone else
who lost both parents,
he saw you as a kindred spirit,
and he couldn't sit by
and ignore your suffering.
Now it's time for you too to
rise from the ashes of tragedy.
And live up to the example that
Usopp worked so hard to set.
Yes!
[LUFFY] Cheers to a new
ship and a new crewmate!
[ALL laughing, cheering]
[KAYA] They said that they
were fighting to live.
Not to die.
Usopp's wild stories
and outlandish lies
always spoke of the
joy of being alive.
They helped me through
my grief by cheering me up
and telling me to live!
[MERRY]
Indeed!
Okay!
We're really doing this?
[ONION]
Mm‐hm.
You bet!
We're gonna follow in our
great Captain's footsteps!
[ALL]
One, two, three, go!
[ALL inahle]
[ALL]
Pirates! Pirates are coming!
Pirates! Run for you lives!
[KAYA] My life starts now,
Merry. I'm going to be a doctor.
[MERRY] That's wonderful,
Miss Kaya. Just wonderful.
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[USOPP] Hey! This island gives
me the creeps! Let's go back!
[LUFFY] Treasure hunting, huh?
That sounds exciting!
[ZORO] Watch out!
There's something here!
[USOPP]
Ah!
[NAMI] What's with this guy?!
Looks shady to me.
[ZORO] He says he's the
protective god of the island.
[LUFFY]
Neat! A scrub brush!
On the next One Piece!
"You're the weird creature!
Gaimon and his strange friends!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!