[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
Anything from the sky, Pell?
[PELL] I searched every
rooftop in the Square,
but I couldn't see any
sign of a cannon.
Well then, it might be
in a building somewhere.
Right. I'll search them all.
[VIVI]
Good!
[CROCODILE] But even so, I don't
feel any anger toward you.
And do you know why
that is, Nico Robin?
Hah. All right. I've worked
with you for four years.
I knew you'd try something
like this someday,
so I'm more than ready.
[gasps]
Water.
If you get wet,
then a knife should
go right into you!
Dammit! Where'd he go?
[thud]
Now all is forgiven, Nico Robin.
[CROCODILE]
Because I never trusted you.
From the very beginning
of our partnership,
I knew better than to do
something as foolish as that.
Yes! That place would work!
Special Attack:
Red Serpent Star!
[LUFFY]
"The Nightmare Draws Near!
This is the Sand‐Sand
Clan's Secret Base!"
Where are you?!
Crocodile!
What's with this freaky
place, anyway?
The whole thing is
crumbling into pieces!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
I'm certain of it!
The cannon has to be in there.
I can't think of any other
options besides that place.
What makes you so sure that
it's in there, anyway, Vivi?
[VIVI] We have to assume
that this dust devil
is part of the plan.
The cannon must be in a place
where they can still see well
enough to hit the target.
Also, it has to be an open space
where a cannon can fit,
but where it can't be
seen from the sky.
[KOZA] This place is
big enough, isn't it?
So then, let's make it
the clan's secret base!
What do ya say?
[CHILDREN]
Yeah!
So that has to be it!
It makes perfect sense to me.
Okay, hold on.
We'll leave the others a message
since they're headed this way.
Thanks, Usopp. I'm going
ahead to the tower.
Hey! Wait, Vivi! Wait!
[VIVI]
Hurry!
[USOPP]
Right.
[BILLIONS A]
Well, look at that!
It's the princess.
We found her, boys!
[BILLIONS B laughs]
Yeah, that was just too easy.
The signal led us right to her.
There are more members of
the Baroque Works Billions.
Oh, no! We signaled
the enemy, too!
That smoke. It's Usopp's signal.
He must've found it.
Okay. But why's the
palace so far away?
Good. It's not far from here.
I wonder if that signal means
that they found the cannoneer.
[NAMI]
They must have. Let's go!
[USOPP]
Now! Noisy Attack!
[BILLIONS grunting]
[USOPP]
Ha‐ha!
Tremble at the
power of my nails!
Come on, Vivi! Let's go.
[VIVI]
Yeah.
Hey, over there! Get 'em!
[BILLIONS yelling]
It's taken a long time
to get this far.
But now, finally,
I will have my way.
This country is entirely mine!
[laughing]
[CROCODILE]
Huh?
[growls]
So, it's you.
You can't get away. You're mine!
[CROCODILE]
How are you still alive?
No matter how many
times I kill you,
you just keep coming
back for more.
Well? Answer me, brat!
How'd he do it?
How did he live and come
here? Who is this boy?
It's Straw Hat.
Tell me, just how many
times do you have to die?
There's something you still
need to return, Crocodile.
And I came here to get it back.
What is this thing I took?
Is it money? Is it fame?
Or people's trust? Their lives?
Is it rain?
[CROCODILE laughs]
I have taken all
of those things.
So which is it that you want
me to give back, Straw Hat?
This land.
The land?
Really, you should know
better than that by now.
I have no intention of
relinquishing this country.
Why would I, when
I'm going to become
its next king before long?
We came to this island
to save Vivi's country.
But then, when we
got here, it was gone.
You stole her country!
[VIVI]
I have to get to the rebel army.
I must persuade their leader
to stop all of this
pointless bloodshed.
Up until a few short years ago,
it was a thriving city
full of gardens,
and palm trees,
and lush greenery.
[gasps]
[TOTO]
Please, Vivi!
You have to stop these fools
from tearing our country apart!
This is her country,
and I'm here to take
it back from you.
And what's wrong with that?
What's so very wrong about
not wanting to see people die?
Just being in this
country one day
and taking one a look
around, even I can tell...
...what this country
needs more than anything!
You think that putting
just your life on the line
is enough to stop
this from happening?
What, Luffy?
I don't have anything else
I can put on the line.
Just... Just me.
Well, you can at least try
putting all of our lives
on the line together!
Aren't we friends?! Huh?!
I will defeat you and take this
country out of your evil hands.
And then, Vivi will smile again!
[LUFFY yells]
Threaten me as
much as you like,
but without any water,
you're nothing.
[CROCODILE]
This is impossible.
He doesn't have any water,
so how can he kick me?
[VIVI]
This is your fault, you monster!
This country would be peaceful
if it weren't for you!
[CROCODILE chuckles]
It's heartbreaking, isn't it?
Their love for the kingdom...
...will be what destroys it.
[yells]
No!
I see. You're using...
your blood.
Clever.
Blood can harden
sand, too, can't it?
[chuckles]
[CROCODILE] First Rainbase,
and then the royal palace,
and now this underground temple.
You should be rewarded for your
insistence on challenging me.
Even after I've put you
through hell twice now,
you keep on coming back.
[LUFFY]
Why, you!
[CROCODILE]
You're a pirate, Straw Hat.
You've certainly proven
that in your determination
to defeat me no matter the cost.
And I'll admit that
you've become
an annoyingly
persistent opponent
during our three encounters.
All right. What's that?
[CROCODILE]
A poisonous hook.
I see.
You seem to be a competent
pirate, I suppose.
So surely, you must understand
that a duel between
pirates is always about
two people fighting
for survival.
And when that's the case,
there's no such thing
as playing dirty.
[CROCODILE chuckles]
When the explosion
happens in the Square,
this place will most
likely crumble to dust.
This will be our final battle,
so let's settle this
once and for all!
[ZORO] The smoke was coming
from this direction, wasn't it?
[ZORO]
Or was it? Argh.
[MARINE A gasp]
Wha‐‐? The Marines?
Hey, look. It's Roronoa Zoro.
Just great.
I didn't realize the Marines
were in this town now.
I don't have time for this.
Oh, damn it.
I guess I have no choice but
to deal with them quickly.
Why are you here in the
middle of the battlefield?
Yeah, what do you think
you're doing here?
Well, I could say the
same thing to you!
[MARINE B]
Hold it, Zoro!
We know that you have absolutely
no sense of direction,
but this is just ridiculous,
even for you.
Go that way.
If you head north
at the next corner,
then you can reach
the Palace Square.
[MARINE D] Go back and
turn right! It's not this way!
[MARINE C]
Are you that stupid?
[ZORO]
Stupid?
[MARINE B]
Get outta here!
[MARINE C]
Go!
Uh. What the‐‐? How di...?
[BILLIONS shouting]
Faster! We have to
run faster, Vivi!
I don't think I can, Usopp!
Don't let the princess get away!
Our promotions are on the line.
[BILLIONS screaming]
[USOPP]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
Uh... Thank you?
We're here to help
you, not fight!
Go stop the explosion
in the Square, okay?
Now go, quickly!
Let's get going Usopp.
Come on, hurry.
‐‐[USOPP] Right!
‐‐[VIVI] Thank you!
Your orders are to assist
them in any way you can.
Move out!
[MARINES]
Right!
Are we chasing after
the Straw Hat Pirates?
Or, uh, reinforcing
the royal army?
[SMOKER]
That's up to you.
You'll have to decide
which is more important
when you get there.
Rely on your sense of justice.
Whatever happens,
I'll accept responsibility.
[USOPP]
Hurry! We have to hurry!
We've wasted a lot of time!
I don't know why they
helped us back there,
but if it weren't
for the Marines,
we'd be a lot worse off now!
[USOPP]
No, don't look at that!
We don't have time to help them!
If we don't stop the explosion,
the casualties will be
a lot worse than that!
Right.
Crying about it isn't gonna
stop the attack from happening!
[USOPP] In two minutes,
we're either gonna beat them,
or we're gonna die.
We still have time left!
[VIVI]
Yes!
[USOPP]
And we're all helping you!
[VIVI]
Yes!
Right there! Vivi! Usopp!
It's Nami! And Tony!
What's going on?
The Marines just helped
us out back there!
Were you able to find
where the cannon is?
We haven't confirmed it yet,
but that's this is the
only place it can be!
We must've passed it a bunch
of times before I realized it.
The cannon is up there.
I'm absolutely sure of it now.
[gasps]
The clock tower?
I see.
From up there, he can get a
really good shot at the Square.
We still need Pell
to get here, though.
It's the only way to stop it.
Pell.
[PELL]
We don't have much time.
I could've sworn I saw
the smoke coming up
from somewhere around this area.
[gunshot]
[MISS FATHER'S DAY]
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
Did you see that?
I just shot down that big bird
with my Ribbit‐Ribbit Gun.
Quite impressive, huh?
[MR. 7 laughing]
I'm sorry.
[LUFFY yells]
Gum‐Gum Pistol!
[BOTH yelling]
[COBRA] He's so strong.
Who in the world is he?
Crocodile made even our best
warriors look like children.
But now, he's
actually struggling.
[chuckles]
[CROCODILE] You were skewered,
buried alive, and dried up.
You may have made it
through all that,
but you won't escape
this time, Straw Hat.
There's no hope for survival.
The game is over.
This poison will spread
through you soon.
You know, Crocodile?
You just don't understand.
[VIVI]
I wonder what happened.
Pell? I don't see him
up there anywhere.
But I don't think there's
any way that we can get
to the top of the tower in less
than a minute without any help.
Pell, where are you?
Hurry. We need you.
For now, we're going to have
to get moving without him.
We're gonna have to climb
all these use the stairs.
You guys ready?
[SANJI]
Hey!
[ALL]
Huh?
Nami! Hey, Vivi!
[USOPP] Sanji, what are you
doing all the way up there?
[SANJI]
What do you think?
You left a message where
the smoke was, didn't you?
The message said
"Go to the clock tower,"
so I figured I'd better
head up here to meet you.
So what should I do?
Where's the cannoneer, anyway?
[USOPP]
The top! He's at the top!
Go up from there
and take him down!
[ZORO]
Sanji?
Hey! Where were you?
I was looking!
[SANJI]
Zoro! You're here, too?
[ZORO]
What are you doin' down there?
[SANJI] Funny, I was gonna
ask you the same thing!
[ZORO]
It was the Marines.
They kept saying
"go north, go north,"
so I just kept going north till
I got all the way up here.
[SANJI] "North" and "up"
aren't the same thing!
Anyway, good job, you two!
Now just keep on
going up from there
and destroy the
clock tower, okay?
No way!
They can't get inside
the clock tower
from where they are now.
You see, there are
only two ways in:
The back stairs on the first
floor and from the sky.
That's why we need Pell!
But can't Zoro just go ahead
and destroy the wall
or something?
We can't risk that.
It could make the
cannonball explode
even earlier for all we know.
We have no choice but
to take the stairs.
No, wait. Vivi!
I think I have a better plan.
[MISS FATHER'S DAY]
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
[MR. 7 laughing]
[USOPP, CHOPPER scream]
[MISS FATHER'S DAY]
So, Mr. 7,
according to what
the boss told us,
this is going to be our final
mission for Baroque Works.
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
[MR. 7 laughs]
That's right, Miss Father's Day.
According to the plan, we have
just 30 seconds left to go.
[MR. 7 laughs]
Who are they?
Mr. 7 and Miss Father's Day!
♪Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!♪
[SANJI] Just what we need,
more of those creeps.
[ZORO]
So if we take care of them,
the attack'll stop, right?
[USOPP]
Hey, Nami.
What're you trying to do by
stacking us up like this?
[NAMI] Just shut up
and do as you're told.
[CHOPPER]
We've only got 20 seconds!
[VIVI] It's a risk,
but we have no choice.
With this little time left,
we have to try anything we can!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Magnificent Wings!
My Name is Pell, Guardian
Deity of the Country."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!