[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other instead.
In an attempt to halt
the pending rebellion
that threatens her
country, Princess Vivi
has decided to speak
with the rebel leader.
The ruined Erumalu behind them,
Vivi and the Straw Hat Crew
now head for Yuba,
where they hope to meet
the rebel camp in time.
[LUFFY]
"Spiders Café at 8 o'Clock!
The Enemy Leaders Gather."
[USOPP]
Hey, Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[USOPP] What was that thing
your brother gave you?
[LUFFY]
I don't really know.
Just looks like
a scrap of paper.
It's just paper?
[SANJI]
Lemme see it.
Well, it looks like it really
is just a piece of paper.
There's nothing written
on it or anything.
Is that all? Really?
[LUFFY] I'm not really sure
why Ace gave it to me,
but it's important. Ah...!
[LUFFY]
Wahh...!
Don't eat that!
Dumb camel.
Hey, Luffy. Give me your hat.
Huh? Why?
[NAMI] If it's really
that important to you,
I can sew it to the
underside of your hat ribbon.
[LUFFY] Good idea!
Sew it on real good!
[NAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
There, it's all done.
Here you go.
Now I don't have to
worry about losing it.
Thanks!
If there isn't even
anything written on it,
what's the point of
hanging onto the thing?
Ace said it's important
and I should hang onto it.
So I'm hanging on to it.
That's all.
So, you're pretty much
just basing your decision
on nothing.
No, my instincts.
They're right a lot.
[GROUP chattering]
[USOPP]
Will someone please carry me?
You guys. We're close now.
Yuba's just past
those rocks there.
One last push,
and I'm sure we'll make it.
[GROUP cheers]
[LUFFY]
Yuba or bust!
‐‐[NAMI] Almost there!
‐‐[CHOPPER] Yuba!
[USOPP]
Come on Zoro, I'm light.
[ZORO]
Suck it up.
[LUFFY]
Hey! Carry me, too, Zoro!
[ZORO]
Morons!
[CROCODILE] The operation will
begin at the stroke of noon
two days from now.
Have you completed
the arrangements?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Yes. Everything's in place.
We have a hundred
and fifty Billions
who are standing by in Nanohana.
I've also called
Mister Two back here.
It appears that he failed
utterly in his assignment
to capture and
kill Mister Three.
The officer agents
have been instructed
to gather tonight,
at eight o'clock.
They're meeting
at the Spiders Café.
[CROCODILE]
Yes. Very good.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
It's already past five o'clock.
I would imagine that
the officer agents
will begin gathering at
the café any minute now.
[music playing]
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Well, well! Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
That was an exhausting trip!
My back is really
killing me here!
This is your fault, Mister Four!
You're so slow!
If we had gotten here quicker,
my back wouldn't hurt right now!
[MISTER FOUR]
Oh... I'm... sorry...
Yes, yes, yes, yes! How's
business these days, Paula?
The place sure is empty today!
It's an empty place.
Place. Empty.
Place empty. Plempty!
Well, it is certainly
good to see you again.
Miss Merry Christmas
and you, Mister Four.
You will have the shop all
to yourselves for a while.
I can go ahead and
brew some tea for you
if you don't mind
waiting a few minutes
for it to steep. Is it chamomile
as usual, Mister Four?
No! I don't wanna
wait for tea!
I want something
I can drink right now!
Something fast! Right away!
Right away! No waiting!
Right now, okay, got it?
You seem to be in good spirits.
Is work going well
for you right now?
In my line of work,
if you don't do well, you die.
So obviously, it's going well.
You stupid woman.
Stupid woman. Stuman! Stuman!
[PAULA]
Of course, how forgetful of me.
I'm sorry.
[MISTER TWO]
Un, deux.
[GROUP]
Ora!
[MISTER TWO]
Un, deux.
What is that noise?
What kind of crazy
singers are you using
in this place these
days, anyhow?
Singers?
No, I have a classical
sonata playing right now.
There are no words.
There shouldn't be any singing.
[MISTER TWO]
Un, deux.
[GROUP]
Ora!
[PAULA]
Strange.
[MISTER TWO]
Un, deux.
[GROUP]
Krah!
[MISTER TWO] Head in the clouds,
and feet on the ground
and un, deux!
[GROUP]
Krah!
[MISTER TWO]
Fly like a fish in a stream.
Un, deux.
[GROUP]
Ora!
Spin! Just remember!
Spin!
Pretty shoes!
And mascara!
Pretty shoes and mascara!
[GROUP]
I'm such a lovely dancing boy!
Now! We say!
Switch foot!
[GROUP]
[MISTER TWO]
And up!
[GROUP]
[MISTER TWO]
And now! Leap away!
Let's hear you boys sing it!
Mascara!
[MAN B]
And shoes!
[MAN C]
And a...
[SUBORDINATE 1]
...tu‐tu!
[GROUP]
Oh! Dance away!
[MISTER TWO]
Hello to all!
And how are deux today?
Huh?
[PAULA]
You're a freak.
[MISTER TWO]
I am not a freak, Paula!
I am merely a talented
dancer practicing my craft.
I will take one
sparkling water, please.
[PAULA]
Don't have any.
Don't have any?
Gimme a break!
That's what all the high‐class
ballerinas drink!
[whines]
[MISTER TWO]
Oh, you're still here?
You guys can leave now.
[GROUP]
Right!
[MISTER TWO] And don't
forget to practice those new
dance moves like
we talked about.
[GROUP]
Right! Un, deux, un, deux.
How nice.
The fatty and the
old hag are here with us.
Why don't you just
shut your fat mouth,
you weirdo ballet‐dancing,
swan‐wearing
freak of nature!
Well! Nice to see you!
Did you hear?
It seems like even
Mister One's team
is being mobilized
for this assignment.
I've never actually
had the pleasure
of meeting him and his partner.
I'm really very excited!
[laughing]
[MISTER TWO sighs]
Moment by moment,
the night grows later.
We are nearing eight o'clock,
the appointed time.
[MISTER TWO]
Oh! I'm so bored!
Time to practice my spinning!
Yes, I'm bored,
so I'm going for a spin.
Around and around I go.
Quit it!
Just looking at you hurts!
Ooh!
What's your problem,
you old hag?
Do you wanna fight?
Do you really think
you can handle me?
Come, now, why don't
you two cut it out?
Stop fighting.
[GROUP yells]
Hey, what happened to you?
Why are you lying
there on the ground
instead of practicing like
you're supposed to be doing?
[SUBORDINATE 1]
We were! Until him!
[MISTER ONE]
Oh.
So these men are
acquaintances of yours?
[MISTER TWO growls]
[MISTER ONE] You see, I found
them acting suspicious
out in the desert.
Don't worry.
I doubt they'll die.
You seem unnecessarily
concerned about them.
Fostering friendships
will only make you weaker.
Those men are mine!
They don't belong to you!
You'd better stop, Mister Two!
[MISTER TWO]
Un. Deux. Krah!
[laughing]
Ball Change! Un. Deux!
What the hell?
He flew straight
through the wall!
He barely seemed to
notice it was happening!
[MISTER ONE]
Do you want to die that badly?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Hold it.
That's enough playing
around, Mister One.
I'm not done.
Move, Miss Doublefinger.
I still haven't killed him yet.
[MR. 2] Stop it! Come on!
Just get off of me, fatty!
Oh! You're killing me...
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
Mr. 2.
It's time for you to
calm down as well.
It's eight o'clock.
All the agents that
should be here are here.
What's more, a letter
containing the orders
has arrived at the
Spiders Café. So...
We're instructed
to head to Rainbase,
the city of dreams.
In that city,
we'll meet someone.
A man we know, but whose
face we have never seen.
[GROUP gasps]
We're heading to meet the boss.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
The officer agents should all be
on their way here
to Rainbase as we speak.
I sent Bunchi to get them.
I expect them to arrive
sometime later tonight.
[MISTER TWO] To think that
you've actually been
Miss Doublefinger
this entire time.
That's very interesting.
Who knows, perhaps
I would have told you.
But none of you ever
asked me about it.
[CROCODILE] The Billions
that we lost in Nanohana‐‐
have you been able
to find replacements?
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
I've made the assignments
for the replacements.
As far as contacting
the new Billions,
I've dispatched the Lizard
Runners to see to that.
Good to hear.
Things are almost ready.
[VIVI]
Look up ahead! I see a light.
[LUFFY] Does that mean
we made it to Yuba?
I can't see with all this
sand blowing everywhere.
[VIVI] Something here
doesn't feel right.
There's something wrong
down there. I can tell.
Oh, no!
The entire city is being
struck by a sandstorm!
Can't be.
[ZORO]
It doesn't look good.
This place doesn't
look much different
from that Eramalu
town from before.
Water!
Vivi, I thought this city
was supposed to be
some sort of oasis.
It looks like the
oasis has disappeared!
It's been swallowed up
by all the sand!
[shovel strikes]
[TOTO] I'm assuming
that you're travelers.
You must be exhausted from
all the time spent in that heat.
Sorry, but this town
is a bit dried up, too.
It doesn't have
much relief to offer.
But still, you're free
to rest here for a while.
[TOTO]
We may not have much water,
but there are plenty
of inns here in the town.
It's what we've prided
ourselves so much on,
after all.
[VIVI] Thank you, but we came
here because we thought
the rebel army was in this town.
[TOTO] What business do you
have with the rebel army?
Curse all of you!
If you're here to
join the rebel army,
you can just go back
where you came from!
[TOTO] If you're looking for
those fools, look elsewhere.
They're no longer in this town.
Wait, they're gone?!
They left?
[TOTO]
I'm sure you noticed
the town was just
hit by a sandstorm.
But that one certainly
wasn't the first.
After three years of no rain,
the land has become
increasingly dry.
Sandstorms became a
regular occurrence here.
Little by little,
the oasis that we knew
was swallowed up.
Until the town became
what you see now.
A dying wasteland.
With the flow of supplies
to the town ended,
the rebel army couldn't maintain
their drawn‐out struggle.
So they packed up.
They've moved on.
The rebel base is
now located in Katorea.
[VIVI]
Katorea?
Um, where's that?
Is Katorea close to here, Vivi?
It's near Nanohana.
Back the way we came from.
Katorea? That's where I
ended up when I got separated
from Sanji and met Eyelash!
That's right.
When you helped me get away...
Wait a second! Eyelash is
saying that he was carrying
rebel army goods to Katorea!
[GROUP arguing]
[CHOPPER]
Whatever.
[GROUP arguing]
[ZORO]
Well, great.
Coming all this way
was just a waste of time.
[TOTO]
Vivi. Wait, your name's‐‐
Hold on!
She's definitely not a princess!
Nice one, Luffy!
[TOTO] Princess Vivi?
Is that really you?
You're alive!
I can't believe it!
Thank goodness!
It's me, Vivi.
Don't you recognize me?
I look different.
I lost some weight, I suppose.
Toto! Is it really you?
That's right.
[VIVI]
It can't be.
[TOTO]
So long, my princess.
We won't see you for a while.
As soon as Yuba's
up and running,
stop by, Princess.
Yes, of course I will, Toto.
[TOTO] Yuba is going to do
a great deal for this dry,
desert country of ours.
[TOTO]
I know it.
Toto? That's this guy?
Whatever it's worth, Vivi dear,
I have faith in you
and the king.
He's a good man.
A true king who would
never betray his country.
I know it.
[TOTO crying]
This rebellion is ridiculous!
A bunch of faithless fools.
[TOTO] True, our country
hasn't seen so much as
a drop of rain in three years.
But I still put my
trust in the king,
as I always have.
Most of the country still
has faith in him, actually.
[TOTO]
So many times.
I tried to stop them
so many times.
But they won't listen
to anything I say.
The rebellion isn't stopping.
Their strength,
supplies, and men
have reached the limit, however.
Their intention is
to settle everything
once and for all
with the next attack.
Their backs are
against the wall.
They're stuck in a corner.
Prepared for death.
[TOTO]
Please, Vivi!
You have to stop these
fools from tearing
our country apart!
[REBEL A]
Where's Leader?
[SOLDIER]
He's inside.
[TOTO crying]
Toto, old friend.
Please don't be worried.
Vivi, dear.
We'll succeed.
We're going to stop this.
[TOTO]
Thank you, Vivi!
So long, my princess.
We won't see you for a while.
As soon as Yuba's
up and running,
stop by, Princess.
[VIVI]
Yes. Of course I will, Toto!
It's gonna be
the best town ever!
When it's up and running,
I'll personally give ya
the grand tour!
See ya, Vivi!
I hope ya grow up to become
a great princess someday!
'Kay!
[laughing]
[REBEL A]
Koza.
I've notified all of our
contacts in the other towns.
[KOZA]
This is it.
The time to strike
has finally arrived.
[REBEL A]
It has.
We aren't nearly as well armed
as I would like us
to be, though.
[KOZA]
I know.
But there's no other choice now.
We have a duty to
protect our country.
No one else can do it.
Only we can.
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[LUFFY] I wanna kill
Crocodile right now!
[SANJI] He has a way of going
straight to the point sometimes,
doesn't he?
[USOPP]
So he does have a good quality.
[LUFFY] Vivi, you're saying
that you don't want
anyone to die in this fight?
You'll never win that way!
[NAMI]
Calm down, Luffy.
[LUFFY] Sometimes you have to
put lives on the line to win!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Luffy vs. Vivi!
The Tearful Vow to Put
Friends on the Line!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!