[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
♪Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!♪
Might as well throw
that gas mask away!
You are no longer worthy
to be a Krieg Pirate.
[KRIEG]
Die!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY] I'm not going to let
that happen, you bastard!
You're wasting your
time, Chore Boy!
[LUFFY yelping]
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Aw, crap.
Ghin!
You don't have to
listen to that blowhard,
because I'm gonna
kick his ass!
[GHIN growls]
No! My captain
cannot be defeated.
Don Krieg is the
strongest man alive
and I respect his punishment.
Will you please snap out of it?
He's going to kill you!
I deserve it.
Obeying my emotions meant
betraying my captain.
If I were in his position, then
I would've done the same thing.
And now, death is the
only honor I have left.
Don't!
[SANJI grunts]
Why? No...
Heh! So you've
remembered your place.
But, it's much
too late for that.
Now, you will both die together.
It's the MH 5...
Poison...
Gas Bomb...
Fire!
[LUFFY]
"I Won't Die!
Fierce Battle, Luffy vs. Krieg."
[PIRATES yelling]
[COOKS screaming]
[PATTY]
Get inside the restaurant!
‐‐[LUFFY] Thank you!
‐‐[PIRATES gasp]
Sanji, Ghin, catch!
Now, for mine.
[LUFFY gasps]
Where'd they go?
[LUFFY gasping]
[gasps]
[yelling]
Don't die!
Don't die, don't die,
don't die, don't die!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[KRIEG]
This, is power.
[LUFFY huffs]
I'm alive!
That mask appeared just in time.
[COOK J]
What a crazy bastard!
[COOK K]
He tried to kill us all.
That guy's gotta be insane.
[COOK L] I can't believe
he used poison gas.
[COOK JJ]
He must be a demon.
No human would do that.
[BOTH growling]
Do ya' think Sanji and
the Chore Boy made it?
I don't know.
Look, the poison
gas is clearing up.
[SANJI]
Ghin!
Let go.
You can let go now.
Hey, Ghin, are you okay?
[GHIN gasping]
It's your mask...
you gave it to me.
[GHIN groans]
[LUFFY]
No!
[KRIEG laughing]
[KRIEG]
What a fool!
You are paying for a plate
of food with your life.
Oh, well.
Maybe you'll learn...
when you're dead. Heh!
[KRIEG laughing]
That bastard.
First he orders
Ghin to kill himself
and then he mocks the poor guy.
He should respect the fact
that he followed his order
in the end.
[labored breathng]
Don...
Ah! Don Krieg!
Ghin...
[GHIN panting]
So, it seems...
Don Krieg was not the right
man for you to follow, was he?
[KRIEG laughing]
[KRIEG]
It figures
that you still feel for
that pathetic scum.
[SANJI]
Scum?!
[KRIEG]
That's right.
Anyone who loses focus
and betrays my ship,
is worthless to me.
They'll almost
certainly do it again.
Putting him out of his
misery is an act of mercy
to keep him from dishonoring
himself in the future
and endangering my crew.
But... he just...
I never thought the Captain
would kill his chief commander!
I know!
Ghin has been his right hand man
for even longer than I've
been part of the crew.
That's right, see, no one's
ever showed more loyalty
to Don Krieg than Ghin
has over the years.
How could he forget what
Ghin did for us after
we escaped from the Grand Line
and Fullbody's
Marines were after us?
It was a miracle we escaped!
[PIRATE J] Yeah, he was willing
to sacrifice his life for us
by acting as a decoy.
Without him, we wouldn't
have made it out of there.
Ghin's laid down his
life for Don Krieg
a hundred times, easy.
I can't believe the
captain would kill him
with such little care.
[panting, coughing]
That's so cruel.
Patty, get the kit, hurry!
It's for food poisoning.
I don't think it will
work on gas, Sanji.
I don't care! We have to try!
Put the mask on em'.
It will detoxify the
gas in his lungs.
Then, bring him upstairs
and let him breathe.
It's the only chance
we have to save him.
[GHIN coughing]
Patty, Carne, hurry!
Help me!
[PATTY]
All right already!
[CARNE]
Me too? All right, I'm comin'.
Ha! It's no use.
He's going to die
within the hour.
[LUFFY]
Don't you dare die, Ghin.
[gasps]
[GHIN gasps]
[LUFFY] You can't let
someone like him win.
Stick around. Now, I'm mad!
You'll wanna see what I'm
going to do to him next!
[GHIN grunting]
You can't defeat him.
Wait a second.
Attacking him head on
is exactly what he wants!
He's strongest that way.
I'm not worried.
[gasps]
[LUFFY] Go ahead and
give it your best shot!
[SANJI]
Don't!
Dumb kid. When you lose your
patience, you become easy prey!
You are only running toward
one thing, Chore Boy.
And that is...
He's dead.
Really dead.
... your funeral.
[LUFFY]
My funeral?
Oh, no, get out of there!
He got hit!
He's done!
Poor guy.
[KRIEG]
Huh...
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
Heh... C'mon!
The spikes!
Here we go!
[KRIEG]
Just try it!
He's got no place to hit!
[LUFFY]
... Pistol!
Ah! No!
[KRIEG groans]
[LUFFY grunts]
[PIRATES chattering]
[PIRATE Z]
Don Krieg is down!
That punk got him!
[PIRATE J]
What is that kid, anyway?
He punched him right
through the spikes!
[PIRATE Z]
That's messed up!
[PIRATE J]
I've never seen him get hit
in any kind of fight, ever!
[PIRATE A] He busted right
through that porcupine cape
and smashed him
right in the face!
[PIRATE Z]
I... I can't believe it!
[LUFFY grunts]
So, is this my funeral?
Or yours?
You can't kill me...
[LUFFY grunts]
...with little spikes!
My funeral...
[LUFFY grunts]
...will take more than this!
[LUFFY pants]
[LUFFY] You'll have to
do better than that...
...if you wanna beat me.
Because I don't think its
time for me to die, just yet.
I know one thing, he's nuts.
I've seen one or
two like him before.
Stubborn kids who'd rather die,
than have to turn away from
a fight, once it's started.
He'll stay.
That's for sure.
I'm glad he's with us,
'cause guys like that
are hell to fight.
[ZEFF] I don't care
if he wins or loses,
I consider it an honor,
just to be able to watch him.
[SANJI gasps]
[PATTY]
Hey, man!
[CARNE]
You all right?
Try to breathe.
You need a little fresh air.
You want a pillow
or maybe some water?
Speak!
[labored breathing]
This is bad.
You know what?
I make a great banana pudding.
Want some?
You idiot, we don't want
him to choke to death
on any of your
culinary disasters!
Better that, than
the trots he'd get
from choking down one of
your raunchy meat pies!
The reason I won't feed
him one of my meat pies,
is because after one bite,
he'd think he'd died
and gone to heaven!
[BOTH yelling]
Don't die yet!
Come on, breathe more!
You're not really dead,
you're not really dead,
you're not really dead!
Shut up!
[coughs, pants]
[BOTH]
He's still alive.
[GHIN]
Don... Don... Don Krieg.
Well, this isn't good.
We're in trouble.
No, that was just luck!
Don Krieg is gonna get up and
kick his ass any minute now.
Just watch!
I hope he's dead.
[KRIEG grunts]
[LUFFY]
Hm?
So, boy.
It's not your funeral,
yet, is it? Too bad.
[KRIEG]
Because one of us has gotta go.
And since I'm here...
I'd really like to
pay my respects!
Go to hell!
[KRIEG grunts]
[LUFFY]
You first!
[KRIEG groans]
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE Z]
This can't be happening!
He's taken another fall!
But... But how?
I've never seen anyone hit him,
because their usually dead
before they get close enough.
The fact is... He might
not actually be invincible.
[gulps]
[PIRATE B]
What the hell are you?!
Look at that!
The kid's pretty good.
Yeah, no kidding!
He's amazing!
Finish him off, chore boy!
Yeah! End it once and for all!
That punk is fighting
with Don Krieg
as if he were the same strength!
This can't be real. It's like
I'm watching my own nightmare.
He's supposed to
be truly invincible.
If he get's beaten by this
little kid, his reputation
will be completely‐‐
Shut up, maggots!
Never doubt me!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[SANJI grunts]
[PIRATES]
Ha, ha!
[KRIEG yells]
What... was that?
[PIRATE B] Finally, he's
gonna stop messing around
and step up his game.
[PIRATE C]
The Mighty Battle Spear!
What was that?
An exploding spear?
Now what?
You gonna try
to hide from me?
All right then, boy.
This should be fun.
My Mighty Battle Spear.
It's different from the one
I was fighting with earlier.
When this thing hits you,
you won't just be
wounded and flailing,
you will be blown
straight into Hell!
[KRIEG yells]
[LUFFY screams]
That's not a normal spear.
[LUFFY] Woah, woah,
woah, not in the water!
Not in the water! [grunts]
That spear really sucks!
It explodes every time
he hits anything.
[LUFFY gasps]
What's going on?
My knees...
He's lost way too much blood.
He can't fight for much longer.
This better end quickly.
You look tired, too bad.
Guess you should've saved
a little more energy.
[LUFFY]
Damn.
With everything rocking,
I can't hit him with full force.
I've never in my life seen
a more stunning weapon
than The Mighty Battle Spear.
Don Krieg is the only one strong
enough to handle the spear,
since the harder
he strikes with it,
the bigger the
explosion it causes.
Anyone else would just
be completely destroyed
by their own pathetic attempt.
‐‐[KRIEG yells]
‐‐[LUFFY grunts]
[KRIEG, LUFFY grunting]
It's strength...
His strength is the key.
He causes the kind of
damage no one else can
'cause there's just no one
else who can swing a spear
that easily weighs
more than a ton.
[PIRATE J]
That's exactly why Don Kreig
is the most dangerous
man in the East Blue!
[KRIEG, LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY yelping]
[KRIEG yells]
[LUFFY yells]
[KRIEG growls]
Now, die!
[LUFFY, KRIEG grunt]
Chore boy, look out!
[PATTY, CARNE gasps]
Phew... that was really close.
[KRIEG growls]
[KRIEG]
You're just like a little bug!
[KRIEG yells]
[LUFFY yelping]
Chore Boy!
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY grunts]
[KRIEG]
Heh...
[LUFFY grunting]
That's rough.
You all right, Chore Boy?
[KRIEG] Heh. I'm not
finished with you.
If you hadn't made me so angry,
I would have killed
you more quickly.
[laughing]
Damn it.
There's no way that Chore Boy
can take much more of this.
That spear is way too powerful.
No, you're wrong.
Even with a hundred
thousand more weapons,
our Chore boy can still
bring him to his knees,
because he does not know fear.
[KRIEG yelling]
[LUFFY gasps, grunts]
[PIRATES chuckle]
[LUFFY gasps]
[KRIEG]
Heh. That was too easy.
[LUFFY grunts]
[KRIEG]
Huh?
[LUFFY grunting]
[KRIEG]
Heh...
Now, that's impressive.
Stand or fall...
Life or death...
In a struggle for
your very existence,
you cannot have even the
slightest bit of fear,
or you will be lost.
What are you talking about?
That kid out there...
[KRIEG, LUFFY yelling]
When he's fighting...
[ZEFF]
He's not afraid of anything!
Not even death!
[KRIEG growls]
[KRIEG yells]
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY groaning]
Is it just instinct,
or all a plan?
We'll know soon, if he lives.
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI]
What plan? Killing himself?
You... son of a bitch.
[LUFFY]
Heh!
[COOKS cheering]
[COOK J]
Way to go Chore Boy!
‐‐[COOK K] Do it again!
‐‐[COOK L] Kick his ass!
I told you, today
is your funeral!
I am invincible!
There is no doubt that Krieg
and his pirates are strong,
But Chore Boy has something
they'll never have.
[ZEFF] Krieg may have more
pirates at his command
than anyone else before him,
he may have terrible weapons
that cause mass destruction
to everything in his path,
but he will never
have that kid's heart.
[SANJI gasps]
[LUFFY grunts]
[KRIEG]
Huh? What?!
My Battle Spear!
What the hell did you do?!
I just punched it in
the head five times.
It looks tired,
maybe it needs a rest.
[KRIEG growling]
[LUFFY]
Now, it's my turn.
♪As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...♪
[SANJI]
Why does he keep fighting?
Is he trying to
get himself killed?
No, he's not even scared.
It's been a long
time since I fought
like I had something
worth dying for.
[LUFFY]
This is it!
[SANJI]
Chore Boy, Don't die like this!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"The Conclusion of
the Deadly Battle.
A Spear of Blind Determination!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!