[SANJI]
Should we go after Franky?
[ZORO]
And start looking where?
[SANJI] Aw, man, looks
like these idiots really
didn't know where
he took the money.
Even if we do manage
to find Franky.
If he spent it, there's
no getting it back.
[ZORO]
What now?
Even if we wait
around for him,
he may not be back
for quite a while.
Hanging around here
won't do any good.
Let's head back
to the ship for now.
We left Nami there
all by herself.
And Robin's still missing.
The ship's a problem, too.
[ZORO]
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
I've made a decision.
About the ship.
Huh?
It's time to part
ways with the Merry.
We'll say goodbye
to her here.
[LUFFY]
Hey! Usopp's finally
awake, you guys!
All right! Good to hear!
[NAMI sighs]
That's one less thing
to worry about.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Usopp!
[SANJI] Huh... Robin
still isn't back yet.
[NAMI]
You know,
I oughta punch you for
scaring us like that!
Yeah, no kidding.
Though it looks like you've
taken enough punches already,
if you ask me.
What were you thinking
taking those guys on alone?
You can't just run off
and fight whoever you want.
[ZORO] Oh that's a good
one, coming from you!
[LUFFY]
Hahahaha!
This wouldn't have happened
if I was strong like you guys.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I'm so ashamed of myself.
Hey, hey, stop! I get it!
I know you're sorry,
but you don't have to get
all touchy, feely on me okay?!
[USOPP]
But all our savings!
All that trouble
we went through!
What about the Merry?
Take it easy! You shouldn't
be out of bed yet!
C'mon, calm down.
Stop your whining and
listen to the doctor!
[USOPP] So is there a chance
we might get our
money back after all?
Well, maybe.
We won't know for sure
'til that Franky guy shows up.
I see. I'm sorry.
Hey, even if we can't
get the rest back,
we still have a hundred million
Berries left over! Don't worry!
Hahahahaha!
[NAMI] Yeah, but he
lost twice that much!
[CHOPPER]
Nami.
[NAMI]
Eh. Sorry, Usopp.
No, it's fine.
More importantly, is
Merry gonna be okay?
I mean, can we get her repaired
with the money we have left?
We're lucky we have all
these awesome shipwrights
to work on her.
But I know things are
gonna get rough out there,
so I want her to be
stronger than ever before.
We gotta do a lot more
than just a little touch up.
So do you think those
guys'll still do a good job
if we only have 100
million to pay with?
You talked to
them about it, right?
[LUFFY]
Uh... yeah.
But we aren't
having them repair it.
We decided to get
a new ship instead.
Eh?
I know that we probably
should've asked you first
but we didn't have much choice.
Either way, I've
made up my mind.
The Going Merry has
taken good care of us.
But it looks like our journey
with her has to end here.
[LUFFY]
Anyway.
Ice Pops gave us this awesome
ship catalogue to flip through.
There's all kinds of different
ships we could pick from here.
And if we decided to
shop for a used model.
We could go bigger
than the Merry.
And still keep our budget
under a hundred million.
[USOPP]
Wait.
Just stop.
I get it, Luffy but the joke's
gone on long enough, okay? See?
Chopper doesn't
know you're kidding!
Look how upset
this is making him!
Jeez, Captain, you
should know better
than to treat
your crew like that!
Come on, Nami,
back me up here.
Hold up does
that mean we,
we don't have
enough for the repairs?
It's 'cause I lost the
200 million, isn't it?
And now we can't afford
the work on the Merry.
Is that what this is about?
After all,
a first-class shipyard is
gonna cost a lot, right?
Would you stop
and listen to me?!
What is it?! Tell me!
Don't try to sugarcoat it!
I'm not, okay?!
I don't even care that you lost
all the money, that's over now!
If that's how you feel,
then what's with all this
crap about buying a new ship?!
Both of you, stop it!
Fighting isn't gonna help.
Just calm down for a sec!
I don't see what
I'm doing wrong!
He's the one saying
all this dumb stuff!
[NAMI]
I know how you feel,
but you shouldn't get
so worked up right now.
Listen to Nami, Usopp,
if you don't get any rest,
you're not gonna get better!
Who cares about me?!
How can you just sit here
when he's making jokes
about getting a new ship?
I'm not joking about anything,
this was a hard
decision for me, too!
Oh yeah, I feel
really sorry for you!
Already window-shopping
for a new toy!
You trying to pick
a fight with me?!
I don't want your
damn pity, got it?
If you tell me it doesn't
matter that I lost the money,
then why are you talking
about buying a new ship?
Just spit it out already.
If we can't afford the
repairs 'cause I screwed up,
then tell me!
Don't show me some
stupid catalogue
and change the subject!
I wanna know the truth!
The Merry can't be...
[loud wave crash
covers dialogue]
[USOPP]
Wha... What did you just say?
[LUFFY]
Don't make me repeat myself.
I told you, the Merry
can't be repaired any more.
No matter what we do,
we... we can't fix her.
Otherwise I wouldn't
say something like that.
You mean this ship?
This ship that we're riding
on right now is broken?
[LUFFY] That's right.
It's only a matter of
time before she sinks.
What're you talking
about Luffy? That's nuts.
[LUFFY]
No, I'm serious.
The shipwrights took a look
at the Merry themselves.
They said she wouldn't even
hold out until the next island.
[LUFFY]
And it's settled? So that's it?
A bunch of strangers tell
you to scrap your ship
and you don't even
ask any questions?
[LUFFY]
That's enough.
[USOPP] I understand
that these guys know
what they're talking about,
but this is just wrong.
Don't give up on the Merry!
What about all the adventures
we've gone on together?
What about all the
battles we've fought?!
She's our friend!
She's one of us!
Are you gonna abandon
her for another ship
without a second thought?!
After all we've been
through is that how little
the Merry means to you, Luffy?
I know you're upset Usopp,
but you need to calm down.
[USOPP]
Sorry, but no.
I'm not backing
down 'til we settle this.
Usopp, please.
What? So you know
better than the shipwrights?
If we had someone on the
crew who knew about this stuff,
we wouldn't have asked
them in the first place!
Then forget them!
We don't need those
guys telling us what to do.
I'll repair the Merry
myself, just like before!
We've made it this far,
so there's no reason why
we can't go on that way.
Here, I'll get
started right now.
C'mon guys, help me out.
That's not gonna work.
That's right, we don't
have enough lumber do we?
I'd better go buy
some at the shipyard.
We've got a lotta work to do.
You're not a shipwright,
Usopp, you hear me?!
Stop it, Luffy!
[USOPP]
Yeah, you're right! I know.
But so what?!
I don't see why
you're so hung up
on everything those
stupid shipwrights say!
If they knew what
she'd gone through
they wouldn't give up
on the Merry so easy!
They just want your money!
[NAMI]
Usopp.
[USOPP]
The Merry's our ship,
so it's our job to take care
of her without
someone else butting in!
I'm not giving up.
I won't let them take
the Merry away from me!
This is stupid.
You got fooled by
a bunch of salesmen
trying to pawn off a used boat.
The Luffy I know
wouldn't cave in
to some sales pitch
from a total stranger!
He'd believe in the
strength of the Merry
and the strength of his crew!
But here you are, acting like
you know everything and
ignoring your friends!
I can't believe that's the kind
of captain you turned out to be!
I thought you were
better than that!
You're not being fair,
Usopp. Luffy felt the--
You stay out of this!
It was my call. I stand by it.
There's nothing you can do.
We're getting a new ship
whether you like it or not.
This is the end of
the road for the Merry!
I'm not leaving her here.
I don't care what you say!
I know you're always trying
to think about the future,
but not everyone on
this crew is like that!
I see the Merry as one
of our friends, got it?!
And I won't abandon
her when she's hurt!
[LUFFY]
Don't be stupid!
Even if she is a friend, that
doesn't mean she's a person!
[USOPP]
She is to me!
And she still has
the strength to live!
But you wouldn't
appreciate that,
'cause all you care about is
getting a new ship to play with!
[SANJI] All right, that's
enough, both of you!
Just calm down and we
can settle this later!
[LUFFY]
Would you listen to yourself?!
Luffy!
Don't act like you're the only
one who's torn up about this,
we all feel the same way!
If that was true,
then you wouldn't be
looking for a new ship!
All right, fine!
If you don't like the way
your captain does things,
why don't you go
ahead and get off--
[CHOPPER]
Sanji!
This is going way too far!
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
If you don't watch it,
you're gonna say something
you can't take back!
So calm down!
Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't
know what I was thinking.
[USOPP]
You don't have to apologize.
'Cause that's how you
really feel, isn't it?
That's not true!
Just get rid of your dead weight
and move on before
they can slow you down.
[USOPP] If you're gonna
throw away the Merry,
might as well
throw me away, too.
Just get rid of
your dead weight
and move on before
they can slow you down.
If you're gonna
throw away the Merry
might as well
throw me away, too.
I know you're pissed off but
don't say stupid crap like that.
No, I'm serious.
I've been thinking about
this for a while now.
[USOPP]
It isn't like it was before.
You guys are just too strong
for me. I can't keep up anymore.
I mean, look at
what happened today.
You can't even trust
me with your money.
There's no point
in keeping me around
if all I do is
cause you trouble.
You don't want weak
people on your crew, do you?
Luffy,
I still believe that you'll be
the King of Pirates one day.
But as for me,
I'm just lucky I was
able to make it this far.
Even back when we first met and
I was going to set off alone,
you probably just invited
me on your ship out of pity.
[ZORO]
What are you talking about?
Get on already!
[LUFFY] We're friends.
Right? So get on.
That's the only
reason I'm here.
[USOPP] There's no sense
in travelling together
if we don't even
have the same goal!
[SANJI] Hey! Usopp,
where're you going?
[USOPP] Wherever I go,
it's my business.
It has nothing to
do with you anymore.
Sorry guys.
I'm leaving the crew.
This is goodbye.
♪ dramatic music ♪
Usopp, why?
Oh no.
Hey! Don't just
sit there, Luffy!
Who knows what he's
gonna do out there!
Go say something to him!
Stop him before it's too late!
[NAMI]
We've come too far together.
We can't part ways like this!
Usopp's not just a crew member.
He's one of our
friends too, isn't he?
[NAMI]
Get up and stop him!
Luffy, what's wrong? Please.
You're the captain, aren't you?
[NAMI]
Fine. Have it your way, then.
Usopp!
Get back here!
It shouldn't be like this!
C'mon! We can talk!
Yeah! Come back!
I want you to stay!
Don't leave us!
[CHOPPER]
Usopp! Please!
Say something.
[USOPP] Luffy. I'm sorry
I can't follow you anymore.
And I'm sorry I was a
pain 'til the bitter end.
[USOPP] I know you're
the captain of this ship,
so the Merry belongs to you.
That's why I want you to
fight me, Monkey D. Luffy.
[USOPP]
I challenge you to a duel!
Huh? Whoa, wait!
What are you saying?!
At ten o'clock tonight.
I'll be back. So you better
be ready for a fight, Captain.
I can't stop you from destroying
your own ship but if I win,
I'm taking the
Merry and leaving.
Either way.
When we're done, the last bond
between us will be broken.
What's with you?!
Would you stop this
nonsense already?!
Usopp just got worked up
because things were
moving too fast, right?
That's no reason to
fight with your own friend,
especially when he's hurt!
If you give it some time,
I'm sure both of you will
see how silly this is.
We've gone too far
to turn back now.
That's not true!
There's nothing stopping
you from apologizing
and talking it
over one more time!
Like I said, no turning back.
And why not?
Usopp is willing to
risk his life to fight me.
He's more than just angry.
Besides, if just talking it over
was enough to make things right,
we wouldn'ta come to
this in the first place.
That's all I have
to say, so goodnight.
Luffy...
[SANJI]
Think about it!
You said the Franky Family
came here this afternoon, right?
Yeah? So, what are
you trying to say?
If you hadn't let
them off so easy,
they would've have
stolen the money
from us in the first place!
It's your fault those
guys attacked Usopp!
He's just freaking out
'cause he feels guilty!
Hey! Don't go blaming me for not
kicking their asses hard enough,
you were the one who
ran off to go shopping!
What am I 'sposed to cook
if I don't have any food?!
[NAMI]
Both of you shut up!
Huh?
[NAMI] There's been
enough fighting already.
[NAMI] Whatever
happened, it's over now.
I know but this wouldn't be
happening if it wasn't for him!
Oh, hey. You're back.
You were going after
Usopp, weren't you?
Even if he was mad, I still
wanted to treat his wounds.
But he turned me away.
He found a place to stay.
So at least he
can get some rest.
But do you know
what he said to me?
He said we
aren't friends now.
So I should leave him alone
and go back to the ship.
Just this morning we were
all so happy and now what?
[NAMI]
We lost Usopp.
Robin's still missing.
I feel like if we
don't do something...
...the whole crew
is gonna fall apart.
[thinking]
Mmwell, the Straw Hats, huh?
I have a bad feeling about
tonight. I wonder what it is?
[LUFFY]
It's 10 o'clock.
Usopp'll be here
any second now.
Listen up! I don't want
any of you leaving the ship!
You got that?
Look!
Please don't fight!
♪ dramatic music ♪
So you didn't lose
your nerve after all.
No matter how this battle
ends, you can't regret it.
This is exactly
what you asked for.
That's perfect.
Don't go easy on me.
I won't be the
underdog this time.
In fact. I've already figured
out a way to defeat you.
♪ ending song ♪
[NAMI] Stop it!
You two are friends!
You shouldn't be fighting!
[USOPP] As soon as we stop
working for the same dream,
we're no longer
friends! It's over!
[NAMI] Don't say that!
Luffy, talk some sense into him!
[LUFFY] Just sit
back and watch, Nami.
As a friend, you owe him
that much. Let's go, Usopp!
On the next One Piece :
"Luffy Vs. Usopp!
Collision of Two Men's Pride."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!