[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
After losing his brother, Ace,
Luffy fell into despair.
Me? King of the Pirates?
Dammit!
I'm too weak!
[NARRATOR] However,
after speaking with Luffy,
Rayleigh convinced him
to return to Marineford
and deliver
a message to his crew.
[NARRATOR]
When the rest of the Straw Hats
learned of his puzzling behavior
through an article
in the newspaper...
[NARRATOR] ...they each found
a new purpose in their journey.
Because Luffy wants to become
the King of the Pirates.
And to help him,
I need to be the best navigator
the world has ever seen!
[FRANKY]
Listen up, Luffy.
The Thousand Sunny
isn't givin' up, not ever.
And as her captain, I know
you aren't givin' up either.
So, let's sail.
[SANJI]
Luffy, when we meet again...
...I'll be the best damned chef
in all of the New World.
I'll make food fit for
the King of the Pirates!
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
[NARRATOR]
In Tehna Gehna Kingdom
on Sword Mountain Island.
Ladies and gents,
feast your eyes!
[CROWD shouts]
What is everyone looking at?
Must really be something!
[MAN I] I heard they found
some kinda crazy monster!
[LONGARM BOSS]
Come one, come all!
This is a spectacle you'll
have to see to believe!
No organs!
No skin!
No eyeballs either!
Step right up and meet
the walking, talking skeleton!
The strangest thing is,
it's only got one set of elbows!
Who knew such an anomaly
could exist in this world?
Hey! Do you think we're
a buncha suckers? Gimme a break!
Huh? Did we offend you?
[MAN B]
It's not walking or talking!
I'm not paying for this!
[MAN J]
Yeah, it's just a stupid statue!
[LONGARM BOSS]
U-Uh--
[CROWD shouting]
[BROOK] It seems
Luffy's made up his mind.
There's no more time
to waste, for me or anyone.
Hey, bonehead!
What's the big idea?
I'd better do
something and quickly!
That's right.
Sing, tap dance--
anything's fine!
We can't disappoint
this whole damn crowd!
But how can I possibly
be of any use?
[LONGARM TWINTAILS] He already
told you that, lazy bones!
Just get up and move around!
This is a rip-off!
[BROOK] When he saw me
for the first time,
he wasn't afraid of my
appearance in the slightest.
He reached out to me
without hesitation.
Here's a question, you ready?
Will you join our crew?
Yes, certainly.
[SANJI, NAMI gasp]
[BROOK]
I was overjoyed.
For 50 years,
I'd been drifting aimlessly
on those dark, lonely waters.
[BROOK]
My shadow was stolen.
I don't want to hear you
make excuses like that!
If you need your
shadow back so bad,
then we'll get it back for you!
Bone Balloon!
[MORIA groaning]
[BROOK gasps]
[LUFFY yelling]
[MORIA groans]
I'm so glad to still be alive!
Heh. Well of course, right?
Ah, so does the offer to
join your crew still stand?
Yeah, welcome aboard.
[SANJI, USOPP]
What?! Just like that?!
[CHOPPER, FRANKY]
For real?!
[NAMI yells]
[laughs]
[BROOK] You'll never know
how much that meant to me.
[BROOK]
In that moment,
I realized that my 50 years
of waiting had finally paid off.
Where's our money?
Yeah, give it back!
Crap. The stupid skeleton's
hanging us out to dry!
Fine then, we'll just have
to force him to get up!
[LONGARMS gasping]
[CROWD gasps]
So, it does move!
[LONGARMS gasp]
Forty degrees!
[CROWD gasps]
[BROOK]
That didn't go as planned.
They were right, that thing
is alive and it talks!
This is creepy!
What if it tries to eat me?
Seems I can't go lower
than 45 degrees.
I thought as much.
But if I can overcome that...
[BROOK] ...perhaps I can
be of more help to Luffy.
Hmm...
Well, maybe there's
an easier way.
[guitar plays]
He's playing a guitar?
Hey, that's cool!
Where did you even
get that thing from?
You were enough of a damn
freak show to begin with!
Let's tone it
down a little, okay?
Sticks and stones
may break my bones,
but spiteful words like those?
They're harmless. Why?
Because I have friends now.
[guitar plays]
Come on, everybody,
life's a lot more fun
when you're dancing
to the music!
Hey, that's pretty catchy!
[MAN G]
Yeah, he rocks!
[CROWD cheering]
I hope you all enjoy my
rockin', rollin' new single!
"Bone to be Wild"!
[CROWD cheers]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, near the
giant bridge in the East Blue.
[BUNNY JOE] So, you want to come
to Baltigo with us after all?
What made you change your mind?
[BUNNY JOE] Well, whatever the
reason, we're glad you did.
Dragon's been eager to
meet you for a long time.
If I'd known the
revolutionaries were so nice,
I might have come knocking
on your door years ago!
We're sorry about that!
We gave it our best,
but you were hard to track down,
what with changing
crews and all.
I'm teasing. Don't you worry.
In the end,
everything worked out
and I don't have any regrets.
[BUNNY JOE gasps]
[REVOLUTIONARY B]
Let's go!
Time to head out to Baltigo!
[ROBIN, SAUL laughing]
[ROBIN crying]
[SAUL]
The sea's a vast place.
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
[ROBIN panting]
[MAN K]
Seventy-nine million Berries?
Why does an eight-year-old
child have such a high bounty?
[MAN L] They said she's
one of the devils of Ohara.
You know, those scholars who
were plotting to end the world.
[MAN K]
Really?
[MAN L] I heard she sank
six Marine battleships, too.
She must have some
kind of weird power.
[MAN K]
Well, that explains the bounty.
[ROBIN grunting]
[MAN M] We can't let a child
of the devil run wild!
[LUFFY]
'Kay! I'll be right over!
Why did you come to save
me in the first place?
For the last time,
I don't want you here!
[panting]
[ROBIN]
Do you hear me?
I just want to die!
[LUFFY] If that's Robin's
enemy, then I know what to do.
[LUFFY]
Shoot down that flag.
[gasps] No way.
You're all going to die!
You morons can't challenge the
entire world and expect to win!
Yeah? Bring it on!
[ROBIN crying]
Robin!
There's still something
I want to hear you say!
Tell me you want to live!
[ROBIN]
If I'm allowed to say my wish,
just this once...
[ROBIN]
...then I...
I want to live!
Take me with you!
Take me away from here!
Please, Robin, come back inside.
You're going to
catch cold out here.
[ROBIN]
I'll stay here, thank you.
After all, I'm a pirate
and you're Revolutionaries.
It's not wise to trust you yet.
I can't go into a cabin
without any exits.
Robin! There's no reason any of
us would ever want to hurt you!
It's all right. This is
the way I did things
back when I was alone.
Just let me stay.
Well, okay, if that's
what you want.
All right!
Go get as many blankets
as you can find!
And get her some food
and something hot to drink,
make it snappy!
But, we already
set things up inside!
Hurry up! And bring a sofa
out here while you're at it!
Sir!
[ROBIN] Luffy, do you
think I can get stronger
seeing the world through
your father's eyes?
By walking in his footsteps,
till we meet again?
[ROBIN] This is the
first time I've wanted
to grow stronger
for someone else.
It's not such a bad feeling.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, on the
Bowin Islands on the Grand Line.
[USOPP panting]
[HERACLES]
What's gotten into you, Usopp'n?
[USOPP] Gotta turn
all this fat into muscle!
[HERACLES]
Oh, that's a good idea!
[USOPP]
Gotta get strong!
[HERACLES]
Because that's the only way
to get off this island'n?
[USOPP]
Gotta get really strong!
[HERACLES]
Yes, you mentioned that!
[USOPP]
Gotta get really, really strong!
[HERACLES]
Er, how strong, exactly?
[USOPP]
Really, really, really, really,
really, really, really strong!
[HERACLES] You're quite
serious, aren't you?
[USOPP panting]
[HERACLES]
But why the sudden change?
[HERACLES] What did you
see in that newspaper'n?
[USOPP panting]
[USOPP]
Our captain sent us a message.
[HERACLES]
Message'n?
[ZORO]
What are you talkin' about?
Get on already!
[USOPP]
Huh?
Come on, we're
friends now, right?
[panting]
Luffy!
Usopp.
I didn't know you
were here, too.
Finish him!
Then we can all leave
this place together!
I'll win no matter what!
[USOPP]
You know,
I never doubted him.
I just thought,
he could become King of the
Pirates with or without me.
Of course he could!
We're finally here! We made it!
If we keep this up
and sail around
the rest of the world, we'll
come to this wall one more time.
And when we do... then I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates!
[USOPP] But I was wrong--
not because he's weak,
but because others are strong.
Even Luffy's not invincible.
And he can't do
everything on his own!
So I have to get stronger,
to protect him and
the rest of the crew!
[panting]
Dammit, Heracles!
I need your help, okay?
Whatever it takes
to improve myself, I'll do it!
[USOPP]
Please, Master Heracles.
[HERACLES]
Huh? M-Master'n?
That's right.
You have weapons, so teach me!
You're obviously a good fighter
if you can survive
on an island like this.
Tell me your secrets!
[HERACLES] You-- You really
think I'm a good fighter'n?
Sure! I mean, you're amazing!
[HERACLES] It is I!
Your Master'n! Heracles'n!
I know that, but awesome!
[HERACLES]
Er, please have a seat, Usopp'n.
[USOPP]
Yes, Master!
[HERACLES]
Pay close attention, pupil'n!
This forest is full of plants
called Pop Greens'n.
They're known for turning
hostile as soon as they sprout,
which you've no doubt noticed.
Now these are their seeds'n.
What do you use them for?
[HERACLES]
Many things.
They each have
unique applications.
Whoa.
[USOPP]
Hang in there, Luffy!
[HERACLES]
Run, Usopp'n!
This forest is your
training ground'n!
[USOPP] If it'll help you
be King of the Pirates,
I'll become the
Sniper King for real!
[USOPP yells]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, on Gloom
Island on the Grand Line--
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
[ZORO]
Please!
Will you train
me as a swordsman?
You disappoint me. Stand up.
I can't believe you would ask
your enemy for instruction.
Have you no shame?
[MIHAWK] Get out of here.
This is pathetic.
A pity, perhaps, but
I overestimated your worth.
[ZORO grunts]
[MIHAWK]
I said stand up.
You're making
a fool of yourself.
Please help me!
First of all,
the baboons beat you,
and after that, you couldn't
even make it out to sea.
I can't help you. It's hopeless.
[ZORO]
They didn't beat me.
[MIHAWK gasps]
[MIHAWK]
What?
[ZORO] You're the only
one left to take down.
But I'm just not good enough
to win against you
the way I am now.
Anybody can see that!
I don't follow.
Clearly you still
consider me your enemy,
yet here you are bowing down,
begging for my help.
What do you mean to do?
Kill you, of course.
[grunts]
[laughs]
You admit you want to kill me,
and you expect me
to assist you in that?
You're strange.
What a ridiculous request!
Aren't you the least bit
embarrassed? [chuckles]
Perhaps your priorities
are different now, Roronoa?
[gasps]
You, the ghost woman.
Go take care of his injuries.
[gasps] What?
Why on earth would
I take orders from you?
[MIHAWK]
We'll begin after you recover.
[gasps]
[PERONA groans]
Mr. Fancy Pants,
treatin' me like
some kind of maid!
Well, what're you waiting for?
Let's go, stupid!
[door opens]
[MIHAWK] He's a fool,
but a man like that would not
throw away his pride
for his own sake.
He must be thinking
of someone else.
"3D" is crossed out,
and "2Y" is under it?
You're right, I see!
It's like a tattoo on his arm!
A while back, the whole crew
promised we would meet up in
a certain place in three days.
But we just couldn't.
So, let me guess--
"3D" means three days, right?
Then the "2Y" is probably, um...
[ZORO]
Two years!
I knew that!
So, the meeting is going to
be two years later. All right.
Means he pulled that
stunt in Marineford
knowing it would get
him in the newspaper.
That way he could make sure
each of us got the message.
That was smart,
especially for Luffy.
But none of us
have what it takes
to survive in the New World.
That's why we have to train.
So, we'll all be stronger
the next time we meet!
[PERONA] Hey, didn't I
tell you to rest up?
[ZORO grunts]
No way!
[LUFFY]
Heh. See ya!
You saved me.
Who the hell are you anyway?
My name's Monkey D. Luffy.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!
[ZORO] Until the day comes when
I defeat him and take his title,
I swear that I will never lose!
Is that okay,
King of the Pirates?
[chuckles] Uh-huh!
As long as I can still
stand, I can train.
Let's get started.
Heh. There's one baboon
you haven't beat yet.
They've mastered swordsmanship
by observing humans.
They even organized by rank,
all the way up to their master.
He's the leader of every
baboon on this island.
[MASTER HUMANDRILL growls]
[ZORO]
That sword...
He learned to fight
by copying what I do.
He's not like the others.
You should be cautious.
[ZORO]
Sounds like fun.
[ZORO] You're nothing but
a stepping stone, baboon!
[MASTER HUMANDRILL yelling]
[ZORO yells]
[STRAW HAT PIRATES]
See you at Sabaody in two years!
[NARRATOR] Plotting
a course for his future,
Luffy leaves Amazon Lily behind
and travels with Rayleigh to
the deserted island of Ruskaina.
There he struggles to unlock
an arsenal of new abilities
as he goes head-to-head
against the giant creatures
that inhabit the island.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Luffy's Training Begins! To the
Place We Promised in 2 Years!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!