Right.
So even though we got in
a few fights back in town
with both the Franky Family and
with the Galley-La shipwrights,
the enemy we're all going
after here is one and the same.
From this point forward,
we fight as one!
Now Gum-Gum--
Three Hundred Caliber--
We're gonna crash!
Cannon!
We... We made it!
That you, Luffy?
Yep, it's me!
What's up?
You save Robin?
No, sorry.
Afraid I'm still
working on that one.
Nami told me why Robin
surrendered and all that stuff.
I see.
That's good.
Well anyway,
you know what's next.
Go ahead give 'em hell, Sanji.
He'll die if he fights them now!
If wants to stand a chance,
he's gotta wait on us!
Hey, Cook, can you hear me?
Some of the guys on that
train are really tough--
Zoro!
It's fine.
If it was you, would you wait?
If you were on that train
right now instead of him and
I told you that Robin sacrificed
herself to protect us.
Would you just sit
there and do nothing?
No use trying to stop him.
But thanks, Moss Head.
I never knew you cared
about me so much.
I hope they kill you!
Anyway, that settles it.
I was willing to fight for Robin
even before I knew the truth.
But now that you told me
how she really feels.
I wouldn't stop,
even if you begged me.
No, I'm... I'm not coming.
Eh?
This doesn't have anything
to do with me anymore.
You're about to make
yourselves personal enemies
of the World Government.
I don't wanna be
any part of that.
Besides, Luffy and the
rest of the crew are coming.
I still feel bad for
Robin but I'm sorry.
It's not my job
to save her anymore.
I am not a part of Luffy's crew!
See ya.
Ahhh! They're right here!
Dammit, they found us!
Metallic Star!
Who the hell are you?!
Your friend told me everything.
I understand that you're here
to rescue a certain
mademoiselle.
That alone is reason enough
for me to join your cause.
My weapons are at your disposal.
My name is Sniper King.
♪ Oh, the wind
carries my name. ♪
♪ From Sniper Island,
far away. ♪
♪ When I aim,
it's straight and true. ♪
♪ Lulu lala lu ♪
♪ Whether you're a man
or a mouse, Lock on! ♪
♪ I will put your
heart in my sights! ♪
♪ And lock on! ♪
♪ No one knows
the secrets hide ♪
♪ beneath this
mask and my cape. ♪
♪ Lululu, lulu lala. ♪
♪ There is no escape! ♪
♪ Sni-papa snipapa. ♪
♪ Sni-per-king aims true! ♪
"A Mysterious Man Appears?!
His Name Is Sniper King!"
♪ Oh, the wind
carries my name. ♪
♪ From Sniper Island,
far away. ♪
♪ When I take aim,
it's straight and true. ♪
♪ Lulu lala lu. ♪
♪ Whether you're a... ♪
What the hell is
he doing over there?
C'mon just humor the poor guy.
He has too much pride to
show his face to the crew,
but he still wants
to rescue his friend.
♪ No one knows
what secrets hide ♪
♪ behind this... ♪
Well long as he
stops singing, I guess.
Hey!
Get over here!
Oh, sure.
'Kay.
Let's start the meeting for
"Operation Rescue Robin."
We've never met before.
Don't you two have
any questions about me?
So the car you were
in was car number 6.
That means that
we've got five more left.
Y'know, like
"where's Sniper Island?"
But we don't know which
one of those Robin is in.
The answer is:
It's in your heart.
And by the way are you strong?
Are you kidding,
I'm super strong!
Even stronger
than usual this week!
Remember, the point is to rescue
Robin, not beat the enemy.
'Least in theory.
We're up against
a lot of Marines,
in a narrow space
so we gotta make sure
we don't get surrounded.
We should avoid as
many fights as we can,
and whittle down the
main force in turns.
Makes sense to me.
Even though
we're total strangers,
my intuition tells me that
I can trust your judgment.
With that in mind.
I have a plan.
Oh?
Hm?
Here we go, listen up.
Am... Am I dreaming?!
It's a miracle.
Okay!
Now I'm ready for battle!
Hm? What's going on?
Don't you play innocent
with me, immoral girl!
Have you no shame,
changing your clothes
out here in front of everyone?!
Shame is overrated.
What was I supposed to do?
The train only has one car!
Cover up your legs!
Cover up your stomach!
That goes for you too,
Square-Head-Sisters!
People like you are
corrupting society!
Whatever, you're just too shy.
Shy boy!
Why, you!
If you fellas like,
I could change too.
Please, anything but that.
We promise we'll behave.
If you don't like mature women,
it's your loss.
Stupid black shorts with
their stupid tiny pockets!
Come on get in there!
Don't put meat in
your pants, you idiot!
I'm starting to think you
might actually pull this off!
You certainly seem
riled up, if nothing else!
You bet we are!
Those jerks got away
with Robin last time,
but now that
I know what's going on,
they don't stand a chance!
I hope you're right!
'Cause if you get stuck
in something again,
you're gonna have hell to pay!
Nah, don't worry,
I got a reason to beat
them this time around!
Uh, right.
Hey.
Did you change
your weapon, Nami?
Hm?
Oh, no.
It's pretty much the
same one as before.
Usopp just improved
it with some dials
after we got back from Skypeia.
This is the Perfect Clima Takt.
I see.
So that's his--
Right.
It's Usopp's...
Uh...
Last work...
Don't get all sad now!
You ready?
Let's do this.
An intruder?
Uh, yes, sir.
That's what I heard.
It's not feasible to board the
Puffing Tom while it's running.
If there really is
an intruder that means
we let him sneak on
board before we departed.
What an embarrassment.
I agree, sir.
It's inexcusable.
But if you can't get on
while the train is moving,
you can't get off, either.
That means the intruder as well
as the missing prisoners
are still here somewhere.
You just have to find them.
Yes, sir!
Captain T-Bone.
I don't think there's any room
for someone to hide in here.
Good evening!
It's them!
They were right outside!
We found 3 suspicious men,
including the
criminals in car 7!
Corner and capture them!
Ever use a hammer before?
'Cause you sure do suck.
Sh-Shut up!
There's no point in resisting!
Open the door already!
They're gonna break through!
I know!
This way!
They found the
intruder in car #7!
The criminals, too?
Yeah.
Let the guys in car 3 know.
That Franky guy's
a lot of trouble.
Move in and capture them alive!
Move it! Stand back!
Whoa!
They're shooting at us!
Then hurry it up!
A little help would be nice!
Don't shoot blindly!
We don't want these guys dead!
You're right.
What do we do, Captain T-Bone?
Allow me to handle this.
I hate crooked men
and crooked swordplay.
Here comes my Right-Angle Flash!
Bone Soir!
I hate crooked men
and crooked swordplay.
Here comes my Right-Angle Flash!
Bone Soir!
They're gone!
The roof?
Go!
They're at the end of the train!
Now! Hurry!
Oh no.
Everyone get back to
the front cars right now!
This is a trap!
What are you talking about?
What the?!
Quick! Retreat-they tricked us!
Huh?!
We can't go back anymore.
The door is blocked.
No way.
The cars are detached!
What?!
Damn it!
That's cheating!
You'll pay for this!
I was too late.
Have a safe trip, gentlemen!
Say hello to the
Sea Kings for me!
Fair thee well!
That's two cars down!
Should cut the small fries
down by about 50 or so.
But aren't Luffy and the others
coming on the same railway?
What happens when the
cars run into each other?
Eh, they'll come
up with something.
You arrogant thugs.
I'm gonna tear this door
down and you with it!
Oh?
Going for a swim?
All right five to go!
You bastard.
You're gonna
suffer for that one!
What will poor
Captain T-Bone do?!
Hey!
Report this to CP9!
Great, more of these guys.
And Frit Assorti!
Sniper King Gunpowder Star!
Strong Right!
Huh?
Heavy weight shot fire!
Whoa! They hit him!
That hurt.
Keep shooting!
Why isn't the gun
working on him?!
Whoa, that was crazy.
What the hell are you?!
Huh?
Oh guess I forgot to
tell you, I'm a cyborg.
Those are real?!
Yep.
I got steel and weapons
built right into my body.
It still kinda
hurts if I get shot
and I might bleed a little, too.
But no big deal.
Just when you think
you've seen it all!
The world's a crazy place.
Awesome!
Poke.
Auuughhh!!
What in the hell was that for?!
Huh?
You can deflect bullets,
but needles hurt?
For one, I'm not
your science experiment,
so stop poking me!
And for two, just so you know,
my back isn't the
same as my front!
Get it?
I had to do the
operation on myself,
so I couldn't reach
around behind me.
In other words, only
the front side is cyborg!
I see.
While I'm at it, lemme tell
you another little secret.
My belly is always cold.
Can you guess why?
How would I know?
It's 'cause I got
my own personal fridge
in there to keep my cola cool!
Wow, that's handy!
Man, that's gotta
be great in the summer!
Okay, the cola
thing is really neat,
but we don't have time for this!
We gotta get moving
to the next car!
This one is number 4.
Hm?
I'm Wanze!
It's a mad, mad, mad, mad, world
and I'm a mad, mad,
mad, mad, Wanze!
Here I come!
What's up you guys?
Are you hungry?
You look hungry.
How 'bout some ramen?
I'm the head
steward of this train
so I can cook anything you
fellas would like to eat.
Okay, ramen it is,
but before I start,
a little trivia for you.
My nose hairs're
shaped like this!
They crisscross inside
so they look just like
fishnet stockings.
This is very important!
First I grab the flour.
And knead it in
my mouth like this.
Done! Here!
Hell, no!
Okay, that was a waste of time.
Listen we've got someone
waiting on us, Wanze.
You'll have to enjoy that
nose ramen on your own.
Not so fast!
If you wanna pass
through this car,
you'll have to defeat me first!
You think you can stop us?
I know I can!
Go, go, go!
This is an important
escort mission
so they got an important guy
like me to keep the train safe!
If you wanna rescue
that friend of yours
then first you'll have
to defeat my Ramen Kenpo!
Ra-Ramen Kenpo?
Ra-Ramen Kenpooooo?
That little turd
is making fun of me!
I know he's annoying,
but you gotta keep your cool!
How'd you like my
idiot imitation,
was it dumb enough for you?
Don't let him get to you!
Go, go, go, go!
This dude got ants
in his pants or what?
I swear that I grazed him
with one of those shots.
But he doesn't even care!
He even looks happy!
I thought my heart was
gonna leap outta my chest!
How was I supposed
to know you make
that same stupid face
for everything!
I'll take this guy
down, just watch.
Hold on.
You can't let this
clown get under your skin.
We got more important things to
do than sit here and play games.
You stay back and
I'll make quick work of him.
I don't know what your deal is,
but if you were a real chef,
you'd conduct yourself
with a little more dignity.
I'm talking to you, stupid!
Why don't you take your own
advice for once?!
Look!
He dodged that kick
without even blinking!
In fact, he even looks happy!
I thought I was gonna die!
Stop making that damn face!
Don't do the same joke twice!
I've had enough.
Like I said, this guy is mine.
You go ahead.
I'll catch up
with you two later.
How do you like my
mad mad Ramen Kenpo?
Pretty crazy, huh?
I hate people who
play with their food.
If you're gonna talk saucy,
you better bring
your cooking skills!
It's not like me
to use my hands,
but since this is
a kitchen battle,
I'll make an exception
and show you how a
real chef handles his knives.
On the next One Piece:
"Showdown between Cooks!
Sanji vs. Ramen Kenpo."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!