[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began--
I left behind those
shores of sand--
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere-ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand-new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves--
From all despair,
I can be saved--
For the horizon
on the other side is--
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began--
Over seas of green
and shores of sand--
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me--
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally--
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!
[USOPP]
What was the noise?
Shh!
[NARRATOR] After the campfire
celebration, Usopp witnessed
an eerie sight late that
night on the Going Merry,
[USOPP whimpers]
[screams
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, the
priests, Ohm, Gedatsu and Shura
were summoned to God's Shrine.
Surprise, boys!
[yelling]
[NARRATOR] Where Eneru
himself appeared before them.
[yelling]
[ENERU]
The rules state that each of you
run an area of the Upperyard.
Tomorrow, I'll allow you
to go where you will.
There will be no restrictions.
Get as vicious as you like.
C'mon, Merry,
just tell me who I saw.
[ZORO] Okay, we'll all meet
safely on the east coast.
[USOPP]
You bet!
[LUFFY]
Let's get going, then!
[CHOPPER]
Yeah!
[LUFFY]
"A Giant Snake Bears Its Fangs!
The Survival Game Begins!"
Hey! That's the wrong way, Zoro!
We're supposed to be going west!
You know, west? This way!
Jeez, I can't believe
your sense of direction!
But he's going east!
Aw, come on, Luffy,
use your head for something
besides a hat rack,
for a change.
We're supposed to go
to the skull's right eye,
so we gotta go right,
you rubber brain!
They've both lost their minds.
Why don't you go tell
those two heroes that
we're supposed to be heading
south before they end up lost.
Sure thing, Robin.
[LUFFY]
Hmm...
[CHOPPER]
Luffy! Zoro! Wait up, guys!
[LUFFY] South, huh?
You should've said so sooner!
[LUFFY humming]
[CHOPPER] Luffy, that's a pretty
neat stick you got there!
[LUFFY laughs]
Isn't it? It's mine, though.
You gotta get your own!
[CHOPPER]
Aw... I want one.
Stick! Stick!
What's up with sticks?
[CHOPPER] You know, I thought
this forest would be scarier,
but so far, it's been
nice and peaceful!
[laughs]
Hey, Chopper, you're in
a pretty good mood today!
Are you feeling
courageous for a change?
Yep, you betcha!
[laughs]
[CHOPPER]
I feel so safe with these guys!
Yeah, you're right.
This forest really has been
a big disappointment.
Nothing but birds and trees
for two whole days!
Makes me wanna scream;
I'm so bored.
We haven't even seen
one of Eneru's priests,
so I know exactly
how you feel, Chopper.
Do you?
[laughs
Just listen to the two of you!
Are you that eager for
something dangerous to happen?
[laughs]
[gasps]
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
Where did that weird stripey
looking root come from?
[gasps]
It's moving!
[LUFFY] What do you see
back there, Chopper?
[CHOPPER] Oh! Uh, it's nothing
really, nothing at all.
[CHOPPER] If I tell them
I saw a moving root,
they'll laugh at me for
getting scared over nothing.
I'm supposed to be brave today.
It was probably
my imagination anyway.
[birds chirping]
[ROBIN] There's something
eerie about this place.
[CHOPPER whimpers]
[ZORO] Chopper! Why do you
keep looking behind us?
[CHOPPER gasps]
No reason! No reason at all!
Whoa, get a load of that weird
stripey-looking root back there.
Oh, that? So,
you guys can see it?
I've never heard
of roots moving before.
Oh, no! You see that, too?
I thought I was
just imagining things!
Huh?
--Ah! What's that?
--What in the hell?
[PYTHON growls]
[screams]
[roars]
[USOPP]
Wind, good! Helm, good!
Hmm. This is so nice. It's
just like a pleasure cruise!
But we're making bad time!
Navigator! Pick up the pace!
[NAMI] I'm afraid we can't,
Captain Usopp!
[USOPP]
Say that again.
[NAMI]
I'm afraid we can't!
[USOPP]
No, the Captain part.
[NAMI] The Milky Road gets
pretty steep in places,
so we have to rely on
dial power to get by!
[USOPP]
Pour it on, little Crow!
Sanji! You are
my official bodyguard!
The captain is afraid
of this creepy forest.
Come on, for crying out loud,
knock it off with the
"bold Captain" business!
The only person I'm planning on
protecting is my little Nami!
Hey! It's about time
for that weird knight's
medicine, isn't it?
Do you remember where Chopper
said he was going to put it?
[GAN FALL] Excuse me dear,
my name is Gan Fall.
That's Gan Fall.
[SANJI] Oh, yeah, that's right,
I think he left it sitting
on a barrel down in the galley.
Can you grab it, Nami-sweet?
[NAMI]
Sure thing!
Heh. Well, well old man,
looks like you're better.
[GAN FALL] Mm. I'm very
grateful to you all.
Hey, if anyone deserves
thanks, it's our ship's doctor!
When it comes to medicine,
that Chopper is
a real miracle worker,
there's no doubt about it!
But now that I think about it,
you saved Chopper from
that priest guy, didn't you?
So I guess you're even, then!
[laughs]
Old man?
[GAN FALL] Shall I tell you
a little of this land's history?
[USOPP]
Hm?
[GAN FALL]
Until six years ago, I was God.
[USOPP] Uh, did you hit
your head, old man?
[yells]
[GAN FALL]
As you have no doubt learned,
it is believed that the
Upper Yard first appeared
in Skypiea abruptly,
a good 400 years ago.
Until then, Skypiea
had always been
a peaceful sky island.
[GAN FALL] Items from the
Blue Sea that were occasionally
brought here by the Knock-Up
Stream were rare
and valuable treasures
to the sky people.
Likewise, all of the
Vearth on the sky islands
was brought here by
the Knock-Up Stream.
[GAN FALL] But a quantity of
Vearth as vast as the Upper Yard
appearing in the sky seemed
like an unimaginable miracle.
[GAN FALL] The sky people
were understandably overjoyed
and worshipped it
as holy ground.
A gift from Heaven itself.
[USOPP]
Hmm...
[GAN FALL] But the original
inhabitants were still on
that Vearth and a war
erupted over its possession.
Those inhabitants
were the Shandorians.
--Then they're the guerillas?
--[GAN FALL] Mm-hmm.
So you're saying the
Shandorians used to live on Jaya
when it was still
in the Blue Sea?
[GAN FALL]
That's right.
The current blasted them into
the sky against their will.
Hold on, does that mean
that you just stole the land
that was rightfully theirs?
[GAN FALL]
It does.
The sky people's greed
drove them to steal
the Shandorians' homeland.
[GAN FALL]
And for the last 400 years,
the war between the
Shandorians and the sky people
has gone on without a break.
The Shandorians are
simply trying to regain
their lost home.
How sad. All those lives lost.
[BOTH] Wait a second, doesn't
that make you the bad guys?!
--[PIERRE growls]
--[BOTH scream]
[GAN FALL] I'm sorry,
but I'm afraid that's correct.
[GAN FALL]
Oh, my medicine.
Excuse me, I almost
forgot to take it.
[USOPP whimpers]
What about... Eneru.
[GAN FALL grunts]
Who's he? What's his story?
[GAN FALL]
While I was still God,
he appeared from
another sky island,
leading a group of warriors.
They dealt a heavy blow
to my Divine Squad
and to the Shandorians.
Then they seized control
of the Upper Yard.
That was six years ago.
Since then, nearly all
the Divine Squad have been
enslaved and forced to perform
some mysterious labor.
I don't know what it is.
But the Shandorians
don't care who God is.
They want what they've
always wanted:
the return of their homeland.
Yeah, right, if all these
Shandorians are interested in
is getting their
homeland back,
then why did they attack us
the minute we showed up?
[GAN FALL] The Members of the
Divine Squad sometimes steal
a ship in hopes that they
might escape from Eneru.
However, the Shandorians
still consider
the Divine Squad enemies.
And they will eliminate
them on sight.
They must have
mistaken you for them.
[SANJI] Oh, of course.
That makes it all better.
[GAN FALL] One reason I became
the Sky Knight was to help
these escapees make it safely
away to other sky islands.
There is no place on the
Upper Yard that such outlaws
would be able to
avoid Eneru's eye.
To hear the way you tell it,
this Eneru guy sounds like
he must be the devil himself.
Shut up! Shut up!
For all we know, he's out
there right now listening
to every word we're say
and taking notes!
Notes! Notes! Notes!
Oh, you've got to be kidding,
don't tell me you've suddenly
become a convert.
Hey! You heard
what the old man said.
Scary!
[GAN FALL] The devil himself?
No, but he comes very close.
[GAN FALL] Eneru has
decreed that all outsiders,
like yourselves, are criminals.
What's more, he has made
the inhabitants of Skypiea
responsible for leading
them to judgment.
[GAN FALL] This gives rise to
the islanders' sense of guilt.
[GAN FALL] When the people
believe they are committing
a criminal act, they
become overwhelmed by it.
It weakens their will.
Eneru knows this
and exploits it.
He has created a flock of
helpless lambs to rule over.
The lives of the people are like
playthings to him.
A devil indeed.
[NAMI]
Hmm...
When we landed
on Angel Beach,
we thought we'd found
something like a paradise.
Boy, were we wrong.
Of all the places
that ancient City of Gold
could've ended up being.
This is just our luck.
[GAN FALL]
Oh, that's right. This city...
You sure were excited about it.
But please tell me something.
What is "gold"?
[STRAW HATS gasp]
[WYPER]
You back again, old man?
Get out. Now!
[CHIEF] Enough, Wyper!
Gan Fall is here to negotiate!
[WYPER]
Negotiate what?
No, Chief, we're through!
We're not going to stand by
while two old men negotiate away
everything we've fought
for our whole lives!
Listen, Gan Fall,
you can forget about
any kind of treaty.
If you want compromise
so badly then give it all back!
For generations,
we've watched you sky people
slaughter us like little pigs.
Enough!
And now you're saying that
you want to make peace?!
Ha!
I cannot give
it all back to you.
The power of the
Upper Yard's Vearth is of
the utmost importance
to every man and woman
now living in Skypiea.
All are grateful
for its many blessings.
I have no right
to take that away.
These people are,
after all, innocent.
Oh, so the sky people
are innocent, are they?
I guess you can call them that,
since they let you do
their fighting for them and
never bloody their own hands!
Maybe it's time we involved
a few "innocent" people!
I won't allow that!
[WYPER] You want peace
so badly, make a sacrifice!
Execute a hundred
of your own innocent people
on the ancient altar and
bring us their heads!
You're mad. I won't!
[WYPER growls] Then we're
done talking! Get lost!
Or I'll take your head
as a down payment!
[GAN FALL]
Wait!
Wyper.
Be careful when
you use my name, old man.
[GAN FALL] I am quite
fond of the juice made
from your pumpkins.
[WYPER growls]
I'll kill you!
[CHIEF]
Wyper, stop!
Warriors! Restrain him!
What is this?
Kamakiri! Braham! Not you, too!
[yelling]
[AISA wails]
[LAKI] Aisa cries a lot,
doesn't she, nurse?
[NURSE] Yes, she always cries
when there's a disturbance
in the village.
It's Wyper, right?
[WARRIOR A yells]
[WARRIOR B grunts]
[yells]
There, there.
There, there, baby. Shh.
I really don't know
but you have to admit,
when there are
problems in the village,
he's right in the
middle of them.
Why? What do you
think of him, Laki?
I think that he
frightens me as well.
[LAKI]
He's like a demon!
--[yelling]
--[AISA wailing]
[gasps]
[LAKI]
The Vearth!
[gasps]
Wyper.
I told you before,
that's Aisa's treasure,
--you have no right to--!
--[BRAHAM] Enough!
But, Braham...
[WYPER] We can't assume we'll
get another chance like this!
I won't let this
opportunity pass!
If you don't think you're
up to it, stay behind!
I won't hold it against you.
[BRAHAM] Don't say that.
You know we're up to it.
[WYPER]
Are you?
Are you up to abandoning anyone
who falls during the battle?
[WYPER] If you can step over the
bodies of your dying comrades
and keep fighting,
then follow me.
Now. I swear.
Eneru's head is mine!
[LUFFY]
Run for it! It's a giant snake!
[laughs]
[screams]
[PYTHON growls]
It's enormous!
I wonder if it's another result
of the environment here.
[CHOPPER screams]
[LUFFY grunts]
[ZORO grunts]
[PYTHON growls]
Okay, catfish face, it's time
for you to get filleted!
[PYTHON roars]
[LUFFY gasps]
[CHOPPER shrieks]
How in the hell
can something so big
move so freaking fast?
[PYTHON growls]
[gasps]
[ZORO grunts]
[CHOPPER]
Ah! Acid!
Uh, change of plan--
we're running away.
Sounds good.
Yeah!
[laughs]
[PYTHON roars]
Don't let that venom touch you!
It's death!
[LUFFY bellows]
Hey, Mister Snake!
Over here! Follow me!
Better hurry up!
Your dinner's getting away!
[laughs]
[CHOPPER]
Robin! Look out!
[ROBIN]
Cinco Fleurs!
Ha! Nice try!
[CHOPPER]
That was awesome, Robin!
--[roars]
--[CHOPPER screams]
Good!
I finally managed to make
my way around the back of it.
[PYTHON slurps]
[ZORO gulps]
Crap.
[PYTHON roars]
[ZORO yells]
[CHOPPER shrieks]
[LUFFY]
This way, whiskers! Over here!
[laughs]
[ROBIN]
This is bad.
I know I'm on the right path,
but where is everyone?
Are they lost?
Should I wait for them?
[CHOPPER sobs]
I'm lost, guys! Wait for me!
[ZORO] Well, it figures,
I turn my back for one second
and they go and get lost on me.
Well, whatever, they know how
to take care of themselves.
I got most of the map
memorized anyway.
I go to the right.
[LUFFY sighs]
Now what?
Where did everybody go?
Did they get lost?
I better keep moving.
I'll catch up with them
later at the ruins.
Robin said we had to go south,
and it always gets warmer
when you go south.
So I go this way!
It looks like our
Shandorian friends
are making their move.
How nice.
And the Blue Sea dwellers
have split into two groups.
And then split up again.
That's interesting.
Today is certainly
shaping up to be
a very lively day.
I wonder how many of our
players will live till its end?
Well then, let the
survival game begin!
[laughs]
[WYPER]
Our objective is God's shrine!
Don't let anything
get in your way!
[WYPER] Our only goal
is to bring back his head!
[SHANDORIANS yell]
Even if, there are times
when we are far apart
Through it all, remember
I'll be there in your heart
And on days when
you start to cry
You know you'll always have
Someone who's there at your side
To wipe all the tears away
We will never yield
We won't back down
We'll keep our dreams alive
They'll never change
the way we feel inside
And the light that
shines eternally
So many tried to grasp
Will someday be held
within our hands at last
[ENERU laughs]
How many will survive?
[CHOPPER]
Where is everyone? Help!
[WYPER] If you want a shoulder,
you can have it!
[ZORO]
They always get lost without me!
[WYPER]
Eneru's head will be ours!
[ENERU] In three hours only
five will be left standing!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Deadly Reject!
War Demon Wyper's Resolve!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!