[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[LUFFY]
"The Fabled Pirate Hunter!
Zoro, the Wandering Swordsman!"
[BILLY, VILLAIN A, VILLAIN B
laughing]
Boys, we ain't leaving
until we've drank
every drop of liquor
in this joint!
[BILLY laughs]
Jeez, this has
gotta be the fifth bar
you've said that
in today, Billy.
[BILLY]
What can I say? I'm thirsty!
[BILLY, VILLAIN A, VILLAIN B
laugh]
That big ape behind us‐‐
There's a five‐million‐
Berry bounty on him.
Yeah, but... but look at 'em.
Let's just back off.
But, Johnny,
if all we ever do is
go after small‐timers,
we'll never get anywhere.
If we're gonna make it
as bounty hunters,
we have to start
going after the big fish.
Yeah, I agree.
But that guy's more
than big, he's humongous.
Even we could lose by a hair.
[ALL]
Huh?
[grunts]
Gimme something
to eat, will ya.
Got money?
[ZORO]
Well, not at the moment.
But I will.
Right after I collect the bounty
who's sitting at that
table back there.
You got it all
wrong, stranger...
...'cause I'm gonna cut you
into bite‐sized pieces!
[BOTH yell]
[BILLY grunting]
[ZORO]
I hope you'll forgive me.
I normally put up
more of a fight,
but I haven't eaten today.
Answer me this, gruesome.
You do have a bounty
on your head, right?
Yeah! It's a big one, too!
Last I checked it was
five million Berries!
[ZORO] Really?
Then I'll be eating well.
What?!
[BILLY gasps]
[BILLY yells]
[VILLAIN A, VILLAIN B gasping]
[ZORO] All right,
you heard what he was worth.
Now get me some grub.
[MASTER]
Yessir! Comin' right up!
[VILLAIN A, VILLAIN B gasping]
That was... amazing!
That guy's not on
the wanted list.
He's not an outlaw,
but if he's a bounty hunter,
I don't know who he is.
[JOHNNY]
Could he be the pirate hunter
we've heard so much
about lately?
You know, the one who's
supposed to be so brutal?
[YOSAKU] Nah. That guy
there only has one sword.
Word has it the pirate hunter
always carries three of 'em.
One sword's supposed to be
famous, with a white sheath.
And also, people always
describe the pirate hunter
as a demon beast who's
taken the form of a man.
Oh, yeah, he doesn't
look like that at all.
And in that case,
we can't just let some newbie
come in and steal our bounty
right out from under our noses!
Hey, wait!
[ZORO]
Mm?
Listen here, pal.
There are certain guidelines
for bounty hunting.
You know, like not stealing
another hunter's prey.
[ZORO]
What?
Unlike you, we didn't want to
make any extra
trouble for the pub.
We were waiting until he
got up and went outside.
We had first dibs on
the guy you just laid out.
He was our bounty.
You lousy‐‐!
Hey, I'm talking to you, buddy!
You can't just waltz
in here and take our prey!
[ZORO sighs]
[gasps]
[ZORO]
Hawk‐eye.
‐‐[YOSAKU] Hm?
‐‐[JOHNNY] Huh?
Have the two of you ever
heard of a Hawk‐eye Mihawk?
The Mihawk?
One of the Seven Warlords?
I'm on a journey with
the goal of defeating him.
When I do, I'll become the
greatest swordsman in the world.
I do collect bounties, but just
to earn enough money to eat.
I don't consider or
call myself a bounty hunter.
The greatest swordsman
in the world?
Ya hear that, partner?
I really doubt that'll happen!
You've gotta be dreaming, pal!
[ZORO] As a kid, that's
what I made up my mind to do.
And I will,
despite what you say.
[YOSAKU] No offense,
but you look more like
the world's greatest
drifter to me!
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU gasp]
[ZORO] I didn't know
you had a claim on him.
Sorry about that.
Tell you what.
I'll let you take him
in to the Marines.
You can even keep
the reward money, too.
[BOTH]
Really?
[ZORO] Yep, just as long
as you pay for my lunch.
[BOTH gasping]
We finally did it, Johnny!
Five million Berries!
We can live off this for a while
and not have to
chase after any bounties!
Hey? What's wrong?
Aren't you happy?
Yosaku.
[YOSAKU]
Huh?
So why did you
become a bounty hunter?
Why? Well, I... I haven't
ever thought about it.
To make a living I guess.
The small village where
I was born and grew up in
was extremely poor.
It didn't matter.
That didn't stop the bandits
from raiding and
stealing what we had.
But when they came,
so too did the bounty hunters,
trying to collect the prices
on the bandits' heads.
Those guys were my heroes.
[BANDITS laughing]
[JOHNNY]
Deep in my heart,
I wanted to be just
like those daring men.
They were brave, and strong,
and feared no one,
not even the most
infamous bandits.
I always used to say to myself,
"Someday I hope I can do
what those guys do."
And years later, I realized
I could as a bounty hunter.
Takin' down bad guys is the
reason why I do what I do.
Come to think of it,
that's one of my reasons, too.
[JOHNNY] When I heard what
that "world's greatest" dude
said in the pub,
it really reminded me
of myself back then.
Ha! Hey, what are you
getting all sentimental for?
That's not like you!
Just shut up.
[TOWNSPERSON A whimpers]
[TOWNSPERSON B grunts]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[TOWNSPEOPLE yelling]
[YOSAKU]
What the‐‐?
What's wrong?
What's going on here?
It's Dick the Bandit
and his gang!
They're attacking a ranch
on the outskirts of town!
Now let go!
[YOSAKU]
Dick the Bandit?
[YOSAKU] Here he is.
And he's a big leaguer, too!
Ten million Berries big!
Get in there! Move it!
[DICK'S BANDITS yell]
[DICK'S BANDITS chattering]
[DICK laughs]
[DICK] They sure had
a lot squirreled away!
And now it belongs to us!
[DICK laughs]
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasping]
That him?
What should we do?
We can't just do nothing!
Well, we can't
fight him, either!
That's Dick the Bandit up there!
Better he takes our crops
instead of our lives!
Damn, you're right!
[DICK]
All right! Next one!
You know the drill!
Clean it out!
[DICK'S BANDITS
yelling, laughing]
[DICK]
Hm?
Ha! Look at 'em!
All a buncha cowards!
They won't fight
for what's theirs!
Don't any of 'em have
the guts to do anything?
Guess not.
But maybe they're smart.
Maybe they know how
the world's divided.
There are those who take
and those who get taken from.
They know which group
that they belong to...
...and that they're fools
if they try to fight back!
[laughs]
[groans]
[BOTH growl]
So there is a fool here?
You! Give back our food!
We worked really
hard to grow it!
What gives you creeps
the right to‐‐
[HARRY groans]
[TOWNSPERSON F]
Harry!
[laughs]
That's what gives us
the right, you pipsqueak!
[HARRY groans]
Darn you!
Harry, no, stop!
This is suicide! Harry!
[grunts]
Come on!
[YOSAKU] He's as big
as the other guy.
Even we could lose by a hair.
[HARRY yells, groans]
[JOHNNY]
I don't care.
That kid...
[JOHNNY]
He's who I used to be.
‐‐[DICK grunting]
‐‐[HARRY groaning]
[JOHNNY] He wants to stand up
and fight for what's right...
[JOHNNY]
...just like I did at that age.
[yells]
[YOSAKU]
Hey! Johnny!
[DICK grunts]
What the hell?
Who are you two guys?
Ranchers?
[JOHNNY]
Heh.
Yeah, you wish, pal.
We're bounty hunters!
Bounty hunters?
[DICK growls]
[JOHNNY grunts]
[HARRY pants]
Wait, you two are
bounty hunters?
And you came here to catch me?
Don't make me laugh.
You guys couldn't catch a cold.
[YOSAKU]
What'd you say?
Since you won't be
collecting my bounty,
I'll give you some charity.
Hope you don't mind
small change.
[JOHNNY]
We don't take stolen money!
Why?
[JOHNNY]
Because we're not like you!
We're not low‐class thieves!
We're champions of justice!
Uh, we‐‐we are?
Champions of justice, huh?
[laughs]
[DICK'S BANDITS laughing]
‐‐Hey.
‐‐Partner.
This is something I have to do.
Uh‐‐
Johnny... you sure?
All right then.
[DICK laughs]
Fools! Justice doesn't
exist in this day and age!
All that matters is strength
and you losers look like
you don't have any!
[DICK laughs]
Oh, yeah?
You'll see!
Yeah! Just this morning
we turned in a wanted
man to the Marines!
The five‐million‐Berry bounty
we got is nothing to laugh at!
Ha‐‐huh? Five million Berries?
[BOTH]
Huh?
In these parts, only one man has
a bounty that big‐‐my brother!
[BOTH]
What?!
[clinking]
[explosion]
[SMITH]
Mm?
Have you finished honing
the sword that I left with you?
[SMITH]
Yup.
[ZORO]
Hm. Exceptional work, pal.
I spent a lotta time on it.
You shouldn't be so reckless
with such a precious sword.
If it were an ordinary one,
it would have met the same fate
as those two broken ones
you brought in.
You have to be more careful.
[ZORO]
You're right. I do.
And I will.
[ZORO]
I'll get stronger!
Stronger than she
ever was, you hear me!
Strong enough that my name
reaches up to the heavens!
[ZORO grunts]
I am going to be the
world's greatest swordsman!
[ZORO]
You did a great job.
I'd like to pay you
a little extra,
but unfortunately,
I'm a little broke right now.
Don't worry about it.
It's not often I get to work
with such a quality
piece of steel.
That thing's a work of art,
unlike this long
sword I loaned you.
Thanks for bring'n it
back in one piece.
[gasps]
Better make that two.
C'mon, what's your deal?
Do you have to be so rough?
You keep breaking every sword
you get your hands on!
Dammit! Did it again, huh?
I'm sorry.
I'll find some way
to pay you back.
That sounds like Dick
the Mountain Whale again.
Up to no good, as usual.
No wonder that jackass'
bounty is so high.
A bandit? With a bounty?
[chuckles]
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU groan]
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU yell]
[JOHNNY]
Damn you!
[JOHNNY yells, groans]
[BOTH groan]
Uh‐oh! Those two guys are
absolutely no match against him!
[JOHNNY groaning]
[YOSAKU groaning]
[DICK]
I don't get it.
My brother Billy was taken out
by you two weaklings?
There's got to be a mistake.
[YOSAKU] Hey, get the wax
outta your ears!
We said we turned him in,
not took him down!
Someone else did that!
Well that makes more sense.
After all, you wannabes
are pretty damn weak!
‐‐[YOSAKU yells]
‐‐[JOHNNY] Shut up!
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU groaning]
[BOTH groan]
Wrong, pal.
I'll shut you up.
[ALL gasp]
[HARRY grunts]
Stop!
[DICK]
Hm?
[gasps]
‐‐No!
‐‐[YOSAKU gasps]
Well then.
You must wanna die, too, huh?!
[gasping]
[DICK]
Heh.
Yo, boss! We've got all the
loot loaded up in the cart.
We're ready to go when you are.
You're done?
I was about to
kill these losers,
but, now that I think about it,
they're not worth the ammo.
Let's go.
[JOHNNY grunts]
[JOHNNY]
Hold it right there!
[DICK]
Hmm?
[JOHNNY] I said "hold it
right there," dirtbag!
We've turned in dozens‐‐no,
hundreds of bounties by a hair!
You might be bigger
and stronger than us,
but we're not
lettin' you get away!
If we did, it'd shame us
for the rest of our lives!
But you'd have lives.
You won't if you
try to take me down.
Is it worth it?
In my opinion it is,
and you know why?
Because...
...there are times
when a man has to
stand up for what he believes
in, no matter what the odds!
[HARRY gasps]
Even when the odds
are 20 against two?
[YOSAKU]
We'll take that bet, scumbag!
Then you'll lose.
Hey, fellas!
Soften these bums up!
[DICK'S BANDITS yell]
[JOHNNY groans]
[HENCHMAN A]
Let 'em have it!
[HARRY yells, groans]
‐‐[BANDIT A grunts]
‐‐[JOHNNY groans]
‐‐[BANDIT B chuckles]
‐‐[YOSAKU groans]
‐‐[DICK'S BANDITS grunting]
‐‐[JOHNNY, YOSAKU groaning]
[JOHNNY yells]
[BANDIT C]
Get 'em!
[HARRY groaning]
What are you doing? Let me go!
I have to help them!
Then think first before you act.
[gasps]
You're just a kid.
You're too small to fight, but
there are other ways to help.
[YOSAKU groans]
[JOHNNY groans]
[DICK]
Well, lookie there.
I don't think there's
a single spot on your faces
that hasn't been messed up.
That looks real painful.
But don't worry,
we'll put you
out of your misery.
You two could've been smart
and walked away from this
with your lives,
but you just had to be stupid.
You came after my head,
but now I'm gonna take yours.
Well, "champions of justice,"
I guess you should
look on the bright side.
You two'll be partners in death
just like you were
partners in bounty hunting.
[DICK laughs]
Here goes!
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasp]
[HENCHMAN B laughs]
Bye, guys!
[chuckles]
[HENCHMAN B grunts]
‐‐[DICK] Huh?
‐‐[HENCHMAN B gasps]
[ZORO]
That's enough, don't you think?
This fight was over
a long time ago.
[JOHNNY groans]
What the‐‐
You're that guy.
Uh‐huh.
I hope you'll forgive me, but I
have to swipe your prey again.
[JOHNNY,YOSAKU]
Uh...
[ZORO] I just had some
urgent money issues pop up.
[YOSAKU]
Sure.
Okay.
[HENCHMAN B grunts, groans]
Who is that?
Look.
That sheath, it‐‐it's white.
[ZORO] Mind if I borrow
your swords for a minute?
No, not at all.
But why do you need three‐‐
[BOTH gasp]
[JOHNNY]
Three swords?
That means you're‐‐
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
the pirate hunter, Roronoa Zoro!
[DICK'S BANDITS gasp]
Oh.
So you're the fabled pirate
hunter we've heard about.
[ZORO] Do what you told
the kid to do. Think.
You've gotten stronger,
while the strength of
the swords hasn't changed.
As a result, the swords
have been breaking.
Like the swordsmith said,
you've got to be more careful.
The trick is getting the
most out of each sword
without overdoing it.
Focus, know the steel's
strength, and then strike.
[DICK'S BANDITS chuckling]
[DICK]
It doesn't matter
what kind of reputation
you have, Zoro,
or the fact that you
fight with three swords!
Even with them,
you won't be able to defeat
that many men at once!
[DICK laughs]
Using three swords
isn't the same...
...as using Three‐Sword
Style, genius.
Oh, it's not, huh?
Like it even matters,
pirate hunter!
Run 'em through, fellas!
[DICK'S BANDITS grunt]
[gasps]
Oh, man! He did it!
[YOSAKU]
Incredible!
[ZORO sighs]
‐‐[TOWNSPEOPLE gasp]
‐‐Watch out!
[ZORO gasps]
Heh.
[LUFFY]
Woo‐hoo!
This is awesome!
[ZORO sneezes]
[footsteps]
[ROBIN gasps]
Didn't I tell you
not to stand beside me?
You're going to catch
a cold dressed like that.
The only people who catch colds
are those who let their
mind's guard down.
Okay...
I guess all those
stories I've heard
about how tough Zoro the Pirate
Hunter is are really true.
For the record, I never once
called myself a pirate hunter.
Well, obviously
other people did.
So then who came up
with that name?
Who knows?
Doesn't matter to me, lady.
[canon fires]
[ROBIN chuckles]
[HARRY yells]
[DICK]
Huh? My flame!
[ZORO]
Oni... giri!
[DICK yells]
So that's...
the Three‐Sword Style...
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, good. They didn't break.
Nice move, kid.
[chuckles]
[JOHNNY]
Roronoa Zoro!
Huh?
We're deeply impressed
by your skills.
Would you let us join you?
We're the famed bounty hunting
duo that's fearsome enough
to silence a crying child
by a hair: Yosaku and Johnny.
Suit yourselves.
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU gasp, cheer]
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
Big Bro!
Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories
go racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...
[ZORO]
Hey, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Yeah?
[ZORO] Let's hurry and
get off this island.
I can't shake the feeling
there's going to be
nothing but trouble for us here.
I get the same sense from that
old‐timer that I get from you.
[LUFFY] You've got nothing
to worry about if he's like me!
[LUFFY laughs]
[ZORO]
That's exactly why I'm worried!
[LUFFY]
Oh, yeah?
On the next One Piece!
"Zenny of the Island of Goats
and the Pirate Ship
in the Mountains!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!