[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[IAN snores]
[crash]
[PUKAU]
What are you doing?
Hurry and pick that up!
[RONGO]
All right, all right.
Shut up, would you?
What's with all the noise?
[RONGO]
They're coming for us!
We're going back to Luluka now.
Wait, what?
They? Who's coming here?
Tell me!
Let me out of this thing!
[PUKAU]
Hurry up, Rongo!
[IAN]
Hey, hold on!
Please! Let me out!
Can't I go with you?
Are you planning to
leave me here all alone?
So you're just going to
let me starve to death here?
All you have to do
is give me the key.
Don't abandon me in this place!
[RONGO]
Well. Yeah, okay!
[IAN]
Oh!
Thank you! I owe you!
[LUFFY]
"An Inevitable Melee!
Wetton's Schemes
and the Rainbow Tower!"
Now, Gum‐Gum Rocket!
Let go of me right now, damn it!
Please stop this, Rapa Nui!
There has to be some
mistake here, Rapa Nui!
Henzo wouldn't ever
become one of Wetton's men!
He can't pass this off
as a mistake, Akibi!
Or don't you remember?
It was Wetton who
burned down Luluka!
[WETTON]
Let it burn!
Burn it all to the ground!
If he's never forgotten
the misery of that day...
If he had remained
true to Luluka,
then he'd die before doing
anything Wetton told him to!
Things change in 50 years, huh?
Have you already
forgotten all the pain
that man put us through?
Fifty years may have
passed for you, old man,
but for us what happened
wasn't nearly that long ago.
Hold it. You're only saying
that because you don't know
what's been going
on all these years.
Do you have any idea at all
what the professor's been
going through out there‐‐
what he's had
to deal with, do ya?
No, I don't think you do.
I, uh‐‐
All the people in Luluka
call him Wetton's dog,
and all this time they
treated him horribly!
But he put up with
all of the abuse anyway,
so he could keep
researching the Rainbow Mist.
But why?
[USOPP]
Isn't it obvious?
He was trying
to save all of you!
[HENZO]
No, it's all right.
I have no good excuse
for what I've done.
None at all.
Hit me, go on!
It's what I deserve, Rapa Nui.
I swallowed my pride in order to
live under Wetton's protection,
so hit me!
I deserve it!
Go on and hit me!
Okay?
Damn it, no!
Why did 50 years have
to pass with us stuck here?
and no matter how
much I might want to,
I just can't bring
myself to hit you.
Okay, anyone else
feeling awkward here?
There. You see?
You are still friends.
A lot of time may have passed,
but you still understand
each other in the end,
and that's what really matters.
Henzo!
Rapa Nui!
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Sorry!
[USOPP]
Hey! Luffy!
Luffy. Dumb ass.
It shouldn't be a problem.
The inside of the
mist loops, remember?
They'll be back here
any moment now,
or maybe not.
Yeah. What now.
Now we look.
There's no telling what
could happen in this mist.
[ZORO] He's more
trouble than he's worth.
Please be all right.
Where are we?
[WETTON]
Pick me up! Hurry!
[FLIP, LAKE]
Right.
Damn it.
You've gotta be kidding me.
[CHOPPER]
Hurry, Nami!
Would you do something already?!
At this rate, Nami's going
to be devoured by that.
Oof!
[CHOPPER]
Sanji!
Well, that's too bad.
It's what you deserve
for refusing to obey me.
But Grandpa,
shouldn't we do something?
With that thing
blocking our path,
there's no way for us to
get into Ape's Concert, either!
You think I don't know that?
But at this point,
there isn't anything we can
do to stop the sea king.
[NAMI] I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
[shrieks]
Miss, I have an idea!
Try using the safety gear!
Yeah, so what's it do?
[FLIP] It's something that
Professor Henzo invented!
I'll bet he specially designed
it for this kind of situation!
Professor Henzo, I have
absolutely no idea who you are.
But please help me!
It's a lifeline?
[screams]
Nami!
[CHOPPER]
[NAMI] Ah!
No, you stay away from me!
Aah!
Huh?
What was that?
Damn it. What now?
Chopper! Catch.
What? I can't catch that thing!
Wow, I caught it! All right!
Okay, I'm headed into the mist.
When I give you the signal,
I want to you pull
the rope back in!
You got it, Nami! Good luck!
She certainly is
a brave girl, huh?
Not a single person who has
ever gone into the Rainbow Mist
has come back out of it.
She'll be back, that's for sure.
After all, Nami is definitely
the best navigator
this world's ever seen.
Chopper we're not
going to let a single person
lay a finger on that
rope until Nami's back.
You got that?
Got it, Sanji.
All right then, let's just
let the girl go for now.
It should be interesting to see
if she comes back out
of the Rainbow Mist safely.
What's this?
The mayor is changing.
Oh, what now?
Flame Suit!
[SOLDIER A]
Commence fueling now!
[SOLDIER B]
Roger that!
Commencing fueling!
[SOLDIER C]
Internal tank pressure rising!
[SOLDIER D]
Safety valve released!
I'll burn the flesh
right off your bodies!
[RAPA NUI]
Hey, wait a minute!
Where are we going?
Isn't it obvious?
Back to our friends.
Are you serious?
You mean you really know a way
to get back to where they are?
Nope. Sure don't.
[RAPA NUI groans]
What's wrong?
So then, we're just
blindly running around?
Well no, not exactly.
I have a hunch, see?
That's the same
thing as blindly running!
I hope you realize that this
whole mess is your fault.
Why did you have to go and
knock me out here with you?
I'm sorry.
Saying sorry's
not going to help!
Henzo and I were finally
reunited as friends again,
and I didn't even get
a chance to shake his hand.
What's more, I'll never
get back to Luluka now.
Ever.
Damn it!
Now I'm going
to die in this mist.
Just like my dad did years ago.
[LUFFY]
Your dad?
Yeah, my dad was in the Marines.
He was an officer.
When I was a little kid, he
went off on a long journey
to explore some unknown
region of the sea.
Years afterward.
I was still waiting.
Waiting for him to come back.
My dad was off having these
grand adventures at sea.
That's what
I believed for years.
But then...
That's the ship!
Dad, no!
I searched the ship frantically.
But no matter how hard I looked,
I couldn't find him anywhere.
So I can tell you,
we're not going to
get out of here alive.
We'll be stuck
inside this mist forever.
Hey! Where are you going?
[LUFFY] I told you.
Back where our friends are.
[RAPA NUI]
But how do we do that?
You don't even know
where we are!
You're just going to keep
wandering through
the mist anyway?
What else should I do?
Standing still isn't gonna get
us back to where we need to be.
Usopp, did you find anything?
No. I didn't see a sign
of them anywhere.
It is possible that the two
of them were flung very far.
Enough to be beyond the mist.
But what's that mean?
Rapa Nui?
Is he not here anymore?
Quite possibly.
Oh no!
[ROBIN] That galleon there
is two hundred years old.
I've never seen
a ship like that before.
I wonder.
Is it possible that
inside Ape's Concert,
the course of time itself is‐‐
[NAMI]
Hey! You guys!
[USOPP]
Huh?
Oh, Nami. Hi.
[NAMI]
What do you mean, "Oh, Nami"?
Could you sound less excited?
And after I came all
the way here to rescue you!
How rude!
Oh yeah, you do seem
terribly broken up about it.
[NAMI]
Don't mind me.
Hey, uh, who are all
these children, anyway?
And where did
Luffy run off to this time?
You all look kinda upset?
What happened?
Well he, went beyond the mist.
Huh?
Like I said,
they're not here anymore,
and we can't find them, either.
What's this jibber‐jabber?
Exactly what he said.
You weren't here, so there's no
real way to explain it to you,
but they've gone
beyond the mist.
Okay. We'll withdraw!
Huh?!
Are you crazy?
Have you forgotten about Luffy?
I don't know
what happened,
but what are the
chances that he's dead?
He can handle it.
Just leave him be.
Come on, we're heading back!
So you've found a way
for us to escape from here?
Kind of, yeah.
It's a rope.
Ah come on.
[IAN] So you're the one
who came from Luluka, huh?
[ALL]
Huh?
Ian!
And he's, who?
He's a Wetton crony.
One of Wetton's men, huh?
So what's he doing here?
[IAN] Why don't you hand
that rope over to me, girlie?
But why?
If you're looking for
a way to get yourself
out of the Rainbow Mist then
you can just come with us.
Don't you care what
happens to this little boy?
Why should I?
Really?
I don't know who he his anyway,
and I'm not really nice enough
to help out some little kid
who I've never even seen before.
Well, yeah. I can't argue.
Wait a second!
What are you saying?
I'll shoot the boy.
I'm not kidding!
Ahh! Murderer!
Come on!
Please help him!
Don't be silly.
Why me?
Hey, easy!
[ISOKA] I don't want to lose
any more of my friends,
so please just do what
he's asking you lady!
Good decision, Isoka.
Now why don't you go ahead
and attach that lifeline
to the boat there.
Now, why don't you come
along with me, Isoka?
With all this treasure,
we'll never have to work
again as long as we live.
You don't get it, do you?
Rapa Nui is the only
leader that we'll ever have.
And I have no intention of
following some jackass like you.
What?
Ow!
Run away, Isoka!
[IAN]
Brat!
[ISOKA]
Rongo!
[IAN]
You're not going anywhere.
[USOPP]
Leave her alone!
Ugh! Damn it! Stop that!
Let me go!
[gasps]
[ZORO]
Hey! What happened?
[ROBIN]
Sea Prism Stone.
[ZORO]
Really?
[IAN]
Damn!
You jerk. Come back.
You better not miss him, okay?
Hurry up and shoot!
[USOPP] Calm down,
let me shoot, would you?
[NAMI]
Shoot him! Shoot him!
[USOPP]
He's too far away.
Now it's time.
To burn.
[CHOPPER]
It's no use.
I can't get away
from him like this.
Rumble!
[WETTON]
Lake! Get him!
[LAKE] Electroshock Suit
Maximum Output!
You're finished!
Dragon Spark!
[SANJI]
Chopper!
Always watch your opponent, boy!
What is this thing?
Silver Barbeque.
[SANJI]
Barbeque?
[WETTON] You think you can come
here and do whatever you please?
Think again.
We'll show you your place!
Grandpa!
The rope! It's pulling!
[FLIP]
You can't be serious!
You mean that girl
is really coming back
from inside the mist?
Impossible!
Well, pull her back to shore.
Right.
No way.
[LAKE]
What?
I promised, that until Nami
returned from the Rainbow Mist,
no one would lay a
finger on that rope, so.
[WETTON]
Ridiculous!
Promises are only words!
You just want to get
a hold of the treasure!
But do you really want it
badly enough to die?
[SANJI]
We're not after any treasure,
but Nami is going to come back.
So we're going to
do whatever it takes
to make sure she returns
safely, no matter what.
Joue Shoot!
This pretense of
friendship is disgusting.
Mayor! There's a boat
heading towards the shore!
[WETTON]
All right.
Pull the rope, and lead
the boat straight to us.
Those kids are morons.
They can just live inside this
mist forever for all I care.
Ooh!
Feels so nice,
being back under an open sky!
Oh, finally!
There it is!
I can see it!
The town of Luluka!
Huh?! Is that?
[CHOPPER]
Nami isn't in the boat.
Who are you?
Sorry to be away so long.
I'm raider captain Ian.
I'm very pleased to see
you, Captain Wetton.
And you're looking
even better than ever!
Huh? Me?
Yes, I'm doing well.
Thanks.
[FLIP]
Ian?
[WETTON]
Ian's your name?
Really?
The same Ian who
served under me?
Huh?!
Hey, Captain, who's the old guy?
Uh, uh‐‐
I'm the captain here.
I'm Wetton, you fool.
[IAN]
Really? Then who is this?
[WETTON]
My grandson, Lake.
[FLIP]
And I'm his son, Phillip.
Huh?
You mean you're really that
bedwetting pipsqueak Phillip?
And you have a son
of your own now?
You've gotta be kidding me.
[FLIP]
Stop laughing, all of you!
Stop now!
So old friend, tell me
what it's like in there.
Uh, sure.
[USOPP] Here. Captain Usopp's
super special hot chocolate.
Thank you!
[AKIBI]
Well?
[HENZO]
It's no use.
When we were able
to get a signal
from outside and make contact,
it must have been
a temporary thing.
Of all the bad luck‐‐to
have a piece of jewelry
with a sea prism stone in it
among all the
treasure on that boat.
What is that thing?
It's a type of sea crystal.
It has the unique power
to cancel out anyone's
Devil Fruit abilities.
[NAMI] Hmm...
What's the point of having
so much beautiful treasure
if we can't even take it outside
of this stupid mist with us?
You're a navigator, aren't you?
Can't you do something about it?
[NAMI]
Nope.
This absurd area of
the sea is a first for me.
We're out of options then.
Not really. I guarantee
they'll be coming here.
What for?
Wetton's ultimate
goal has always been
to get all the treasure out of
Ape's Concert for himself.
And now that his man
Ian has returned alive,
he'll be putting
together a large force
and charging into
the mist very soon.
[NAMI]
You've gotta be kidding me!
Then we'll fight.
I'm not handing over
this treasure to anyone!
I wish Rapa Nui
was back here with us.
Hey. Come on.
You have to get up now.
Okay?
[ISOKA]
No matter how much we paddle,
we just wind up back
where we started.
[AKIBI]
It's impossible.
We're never going to make it
out of this stupid mist, are we?
Is that really so bad?
We're the only ones
in here, right?
We can sleep whenever we want,
play whenever we want.
It's our own paradise.
We're free here,
and we'll never die!
Rapa Nui!
We never have
to go home, you see?
So let's stay here and
make a land all our own!
Only now,
I really want to go home.
Back to Luluka.
That's home!
Is that?
Dad! Dad!
What's that light there?
What?
It looks like...
[RAPA NUI]
...an exit!
[WETTON]
Finally.
After 50 years of
waiting and working,
my plan will be
completed at last.
The Rainbow Mist and this world
will be joined together forever.
Hey! What's happening?
[USOPP]
Everyone!
Hurry up and
grab on to something!
[ZORO]
What the hell is that?
[HENZO]
It's the Rainbow Tower.
That was a close one!
Here's your hat.
Thank you.
By the way, what is
that thing over there?
[RAPA NUI] I guess it's what
they're planning to use
to invade Ape's Concert.
What do you mean by "they"?
Never mind that now.
We have to get going.
Everyone's in danger.
So Wetton, you've finally come.
Get going. Faster now.
Take every last bit of it.
All of Apes Concert's treasure.
[laughing]
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...♪
[HENZO]
Wetton is here.
[USOPP] This is a mayor
we're facing, right?
Won't he have a
lot of guys with him?
[HENZO] I've fought him
for all these years by myself,
and I'm not about
to give in now!
[ROBIN] Aren't you forgetting
about us, Professor?
You're not alone now.
[HENZO] No one will harm
the land of the Pumpkin Pirates,
not as long as I'm alive!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"And so, the Legend Begins!
To the Other Side
of the Rainbow!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!