[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Unable to save Ace's
life during the War of the Best,
the injured Luffy was
taken to Amazon Lily,
where he fell into despair.
But this is a story
from ten years ago.
Ace, Sabo, and Luffy prepare
for battle with a giant tiger
to decide which of the
three is best suited
to be a pirate captain.
While out hunting, they meet
a former captain named Naguri,
who once challenged Gold Roger.
At Luffy's request, he agrees
to share some of his wisdom.
[LUFFY] "The Battle
Against the Big Tiger!
Who Is Going to Be Captain?!"
[ACE, SABO yelling]
How did you think
that was a good plan?
We could've snuck around behind
it, or, I don't know, anything!
[yells]
[ACE gasps]
Yeah, 'cause your idea
worked out great!
[SABO grunts]
[screams]
[ACE, SABO screaming]
[SABO sighs]
Okay, not our finest hour.
Let's put some poison mushrooms
in the bait tomorrow.
That should slow him down.
Hold on a sec,
that tiger may be big,
but at the end of the day,
he's still a cat, right?
So, what d'you say we
give catnip a try?
Hello?
[SABO]
I wonder how Luffy's doing
with his "secret training."
I dunno if you noticed, but it's
been a whole week since he left.
We should probably pay him
a visit, don't you think?
Uh, you know how he can be.
Maybe the training
is too hard on him
and he's like,
"No, I just wanna go home!"
Wait! What if we haven't
heard anything from him
'cause he's dead already!
What, Sabo?
Oh, come on!
Don't you care about
your little brother at all?
Stop playing cool!
Shut up!
He's the one who left--
it's not my problem if he dies!
Listen, I don't know who you're
trying to impress with this,
--[creaking]
--but Luffy--huh?
[gasps]
[screams]
[BOTH screaming]
[BOTH groaning]
What the hell?
[LUFFY]
Oh, oops!
Sorry! You okay?
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Luffy!
[gasps] Ace! Sabo!
Hey! What's up, guys?
How have you been?
[SABO chuckles]
Uh, pretty good!
[SABO]
What's that? A target?
[LUFFY]
Oh, you noticed, huh?
[LUFFY giggles]
Now, lemme show you the
moves I've been working on!
Here we go! Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
[gasps]
÷[{SABO]
Uh--
Huh? [groans]
[gasping]
Uh-oh!
[laughs] Not bad at all!
Your aim still sucks, but your
reach has gotten pretty far!
[LUFFY laughs]
I meant to do that!
Not this again.
What kind of "special training"
have you been giving him?
None, really. To be honest,
I've just been having him
chop some wood every day.
All the work might've helped
him build a bit of muscle,
but I can hardly
take credit for that.
My men, at the height
of our strength,
challenged Roger to a fight.
Really?
A fight that we lost.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Put in our place,
we all split up.
[ACE]
You hate him, too, don't you?
I don't follow.
Because he defeated
your old crew.
Oh, you mean Roger. I see.
I was rather devastated,
that much is true.
But the only reason
I lost to Roger
was because I wasn't
strong enough.
In that respect, he taught
me a valuable lesson.
What, by kicking your ass?
In a way, yes.
[NAGURI] We surrender.
We never stood a chance.
Cut off my head, I don't care!
But please, please,
spare my crew in return!
I take responsibility
for our foolishness.
[NAGURI PIRATES]
Captain, no!
I beg of you!
[NAGURI]
Huh?
Gold Roger was a man of
extraordinary character indeed.
And that's why I say he--
Stop lying!
If he's so great, then why
does everybody hate him, huh?
[PIRATES laughing]
[laughing]
[NAGURI]
Did those men fight with Roger?
Did they even meet
him face-to-face?
In the world of pirates,
if you lose a fight,
you lose your life, and yet,
Roger chose to spare mine.
So, if those pirates did face
him, they should be grateful.
Complaining like that
is a luxury, you know.
One they only have because
their lives were spared.
You watch--I'll get
even stronger!
[ACE]
If Roger had a son,
you think he should
be grateful, too?
Actually, I'd feel
sorry for him.
Regardless of his path,
his father's name would
haunt him wherever he went.
With a legacy like that,
I wouldn't blame him
for resenting the man,
and it's not like he could
talk it out with him, either.
At any rate, if I were his son,
I wouldn't want to be a pirate.
His name could scarcely
do me any favors
and more likely than not,
it would put a
target on my back.
What the hell do you know, huh?
I'm sick of hearing
your crappy lectures.
You really think you're
some great pirate?
Prove it! Fight me!
[ACE grunts]
Whoa! What?
I'd be careful, boy.
Like I said, you lose a fight,
you lose your life.
I'm never gonna lose to you!
[ACE grunting]
[NAGURI grunts]
[LUFFY, SABO gasp]
You've still got
some growing to do.
Dammit!
Spare me another lecture
and just finish me off!
I'll spare you the lecture
and a violent death
if you'll come with me.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Heh! You're gonna love this!
Oh, wow!
I didn't know there was
a cove down here--
this place is pretty cool.
[LUFFY] C'mon!
Stop gawkin' and hurry up!
[LUFFY laughs]
Go! Go! Let's see some hustle!
Okay, jeez, what's the big deal?
[LUFFY giggles]
Why don'tcha look and see?
[SABO]
Huh?
[SABO gasps]
Holy crap.
[ACE]
It's huge!
Not bad, huh?
A real-life secret pirate ship!
Wait, that's crazy.
This is why you collected
all those parts?
Since I've been working all
alone, it's gone a bit slow.
Anyhow, you boys
are pretty tough.
Do ya think you could
lend me a hand?
[ACE, SABO]
Huh?
Why would I do that?
[NAGURI]
Because I spared your life,
you ungrateful little snot.
That's fine for Ace, but how
did I get looped into this mess?
Well, you did follow us.
What is this,
a child labor scheme?
I'm too busy hunting that tiger
to waste time on some ship!
[NAGURI] I can give you
some tiger-hunting pointers
if you stick around.
[SABO]
Yeah? Hmm.
Okay, maybe.
[ACE]
I got one question.
What are you gonna do
when the ship is done?
Ha. I'm taking it
to sea, of course.
To find my crewmates that
split up all those years ago.
You sure you're up to that?
And why not?
I was a captain once.
I'm hardly some rookie.
I know. That's kinda
what I'm saying.
[NAGURI]
No matter how old you are,
you can always chase your dream.
I'm sailing again and
nobody can stop me!
Once a pirate, always a pirate.
You kids got a
problem with that?
[LUFFY giggles]
Nuh-uh!
Heh, heh. Well,
I'm not gonna stop you.
Hm? Ace?
You spared my life--
what can I say?
I'll help you build
your ship. For now.
[NAGURI]
Hm?
'Cause I'm beating you tomorrow.
That's Ace for you.
[NAGURI]
Heh.
[ALL grunting]
[NARRATOR] And thus, begin
their training with Naguri--
building his ship
day in and day out.
With every heavy log they
lifted, they grew stronger.
And with every sparring match,
they honed their skills.
Although the work was intense,
bit by bit, they learned what
it truly meant to be a pirate.
[NARRATOR] Spring always seems
to arrive late in Gray Terminal,
but even the most
stubborn of snow
eventually gives way
to warm weather.
[BOTH grunting]
[ACE]
I'm not losing!
[SABO]
Yeah? Neither am I!
[yawns]
[LUFFY]
I'm beating both of you!
Get ready!
Now, Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
[NAGURI gasps, groans]
Aw, jeez.
[LUFFY gasps]
Every damn time!
What is wrong with you?
[LUFFY giggles]
Sorry!
Listen, boys.
You've done this enough already.
There's more to being a pirate
than just whacking
everyone with a pipe.
Surely you want
more than strength.
Yeah, all that stuff can wait.
Right now, we wanna be strong,
'cause the strongest one of
us gets to be the captain.
Why d'you think
we're training, huh?
Remember? Whoever
beats the tiger wins!
The tiger again.
I agree that a captain
needs to be tough,
but there's something more
important than that, you see.
A different kind of strength
that can triumph over any foe.
[ALL gasp]
Can you teach us that?
Oh? Curious, are you?
It slips my mind. [chuckles]
[SABO] There's no secret!
You're making stuff up!
[NAGURI]
No, I really forgot!
[NAGURI chuckles]
[LUFFY snoring]
[thudding]
Hm? Can't sleep?
I'm sorry if my
hammering's too loud.
What, is something the matter?
[ACE] What does it take
to be a captain?
If there really is a way
for me to be stronger,
I have to know what it is!
So just tell me!
All right then.
[NAGURI]
I'll be honest.
Even after all these
years, I'm not sure.
Frankly, I don't think
I was a very good captain.
But my crew, they still
followed me. Heh.
Right to the end, they called me
"captain" without any doubt.
And so, in a way,
I'm still Captain of
the Naguri Pirates.
Not because of my strength,
but because of the
approval of my crew.
That's the true test
of a captain.
Or so I always say.
Ha. Bunch of crap.
Huh?
[gasps] All right! We did it!
Okay. Not bad! I'm jealous.
Awesome! Too cool!
I couldn't have done it
without all your help.
Thank you, boys.
I really mean that.
[LUFFY giggles]
So is this it?
Like, are you leaving now?
Not yet. I have one
last loose end.
I think it's about
time we finish
that training of yours, eh?
So, are you boys ready to
go tiger hunting or what?
--[LUFFY, SABO gasp]
--[ACE] Hmph.
Wait, for real?
[ACE]
I'm gonna kill him
and put this crappy training
behind me for good!
[SABO]
Yeah, except I'm gonna kill him!
[LUFFY]
I'm gonna double kill him!
Here it comes.
[NAGURI] He certainly
hasn't gotten any smaller.
[roars]
I got this!
[BOTH gasp]
[ACE grunts]
[growls]
I'm a lot faster now!
[ACE yells]
And stronger!
[SABO]
Over here!
You gotta pay
attention, big guy!
[grunts] Just give up already!
[gasps, groans]
Are you okay? Hey, Ace?
--[TIGER A growls]
--[gasps]
[roars]
[gasping] C'mon.
Now, Gum-Gum... and Pistol!
[gasps]
[gasps, screams]
Aw, crap! Luffy!
Run away!
[LUFFY screaming]
[roars]
[screaming]
[gasping]
You saved me!
So heavy! I thought
we were strong!
No, there's still one
thing none of us have.
Huh?
[NAGURI]
Not because of my strength,
because of the
approval of my crew.
[groans] We've come
too far to give up now!
All right, you guys, teamwork!
[SABO, LUFFY]
Huh?
[NAGURI] Ah. Seems things are
finally getting interesting!
We're not fast enough on our
own, but with Luffy's powers,
maybe we can make
something happen.
Sabo, keep him busy!
[SABO]
I'm on it!
Hey, stupid, over here!
Eat me, not them, okay?
Now kiss my ass!
[TIGER A roars]
[SABO yelps]
[SABO screams]
Okay, you ready?
Yeah!
[ACE] Pull back as far
as you can and wait!
Sabo, this way!
I hope this works, 'cause
I think I'm about to die!
You're gonna be okay!
Just a little bit more
and he's history!
[SABO panting]
[SABO screaming]
You know what we're
doing next, right?
Uh-huh!
[SABO grunts]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
[yelling]
[ACE, SABO, LUFFY]
All right!
Wait.
We just helped Ace
be the captain. [sighs]
But we worked for like a
million years on this! Aww!
That's the deal. We all agreed.
Dammit. Stop your complaining.
I'm not gonna be the
stupid captain, okay?
[BOTH]
Huh?
But why not?
[ACE]
I dunno, it doesn't feel right.
You two kicked as
much ass as I did.
Fair enough.
Well, for now,
but one of these days,
I'm gonna kick so much ass,
it'll blow your mind
and you're both gonna be
begging to join my crew.
Are you gonna beg?
Over my dead body!
What? Just you wait!
[LUFFY, SABO laughing]
I couldn't have asked
for a better ending.
My work here is done.
So long, boys.
[ACE]
Naguri!
[NAGURI]
Hm?
I know you're old,
but you can't die yet!
I still want a rematch!
I never did get to beat you!
[LUFFY giggles]
See ya!
Bon voyage and good luck!
Heh. I have a feeling
we'll meet again. Soon.
[NARRATOR]
Thus, they bid farewell
to their teacher, Naguri.
A little stronger
and a little wiser,
they continued on their
path to be pirates.
[BLUEJAM] I trust you know
where we can find the boy?
[BLUEJAM PIRATE A] Yes, sir.
I've kept a close eye on him.
[BLUEJAM] I think we've
waited long enough.
Why don't you call him
and share the good news?
Let him know that...
..Sabo's coming home.
[NARRATOR] Sabo's days of
adventure come to an end
as he is forced to
remain in High Town,
apart from his friends.
However, fate soon brings
the three boys together again
as Luffy and Ace take on
work for the pirate Bluejam
and Sabo uncovers a
terrifying conspiracy.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Freedom Taken Away!
The Nobles' Plot Closing
In on the Brothers!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!