There's still lots of things
we don't know about Robin.
Now it's time to decide
if she's a friend or a foe.
Pardon me sir, but why on Earth
did you put Nico Robin's
wanted poster up on your wall?
It bother you?
A bit.
It's better if you don't know.
That girl is a demon.
Tonight, we'll infiltrate
Iceberg's residence
one more time.
Among Tom's apprentices
who could've had it
from the very beginning,
Iceberg is the only
one who remains alive.
No matter how much
he denies having it,
in the name of CP9,
we will take it tonight.
Never forget this is
a mission of justice.
Our best chance to settle
this is tonight. Are we going?
Of course.
I mean, what is our goal here?
We find Robin and capture her.
That's the only way
we'll ever know the truth.
Yeah, you're right.
We're wasting time
sitting around here
trying to figure it out.
Like he said, it's the only
way we'll really know for sure.
Yeah. Let's settle
this right now!
[LUFFY]
Right.
Come on. Galley-la's waiting.
This is our turf!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
[CRAFTSMAN B] Any of those
pirates tries to set foot
on these grounds tonight,
it'll be the last thing they do!
The honor of Galley-La
depends on it!
[CRAFTSMAN C]
Mr. Iceberg depends on it!
[CRAFTSMAN D]
They'll pay for what they did!
Is the back door covered?
Yeah, we got guys coverin'
the entire perimeter
of this place and then some.
Nobody's gettin' in here!
[CRAFTSMAN G] Come on pirates!
I dare ya! Bring it on!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
[ZORO] Sounds like
something's going on down there.
Whadaya see?
[CHOPPER] They're all kinda
standing around now.
But...
...they're all huge, and
armed, and angry.
We need to be careful.
Those guys have a
reputation for being able
to handle themselves
when push comes to shove.
We don't wanna rush in
and do anything
we're gonna regret later.
[LUFFY] Yeah, if we
try to barge in swingin'.
We'll just be
askin' for trouble.
Eh...?
[NAMI] Right, and we
wouldn't want any trouble.
Says the guy who charged-in
in broad daylight!!
Anyway, don't take your
eyes off of 'em, Chopper.
We don't want any kind
of surprise down there.
Right.
[ZORO] Anything happens,
you let us know.
Okay. You got it.
I think we're gonna have a
really long night ahead of us.
But if we blow our
opportunity, it's over.
We can't let our guard down,
no matter what happens.
If we wanna know
the truth about Robin.
Then it has to be
tonight, or never.
Yeah. I gotta feeling we'll
be talkin' to her real soon.
♪ opening song ♪
[LUFFY]
Kalifa.
Yes, Mr. Iceberg?
[ICEBERG] Not to be rude,
but do you mind stepping out
of the room for a moment?
No, of course not.
[ICEBERG]
One more thing.
Fetch Paulie. I need
to have a word with him.
Yes, sir.
[KALIFA]
Excuse me, Paulie.
[PAULIE]
Huh?
[KALIFA]
Mr. Iceberg needs to see you.
I assume it's very important.
He asked for me?
[KALIFA]
Yes. Specifically.
I have some things
to take care of
in my office if
anyone needs me.
Right.
[KAKU] Seems like
awfully strange timing
for a one-on-one conversation.
What in blazes
could it be about?
Don't have a clue.
[TILESTONE]
It's his will!!!
Well, what're
you doin' out here?
Go on in there and talk to him.
[PAULIE]
Uh... sure.
Don't worry... We can
step away from the door
if you're concerned
about privacy.
[KAKU]
Good idea.
[TILESTONE]
What the heck
could he wanna talk
about with Paulie?!!
Whatever it is,
it's between them.
We got enough to deal with.
I think we need to stay
focused on our pirate problem.
Right.
Okay, according to Kalifa,
it's a small group with only
seven people on their crew!
The ones to watch out
for are Straw Hat Luffy.
Pirate hunter Zoro
and Nico Robin.
I wouldn't
underestimate the girl
traveling along with
them or that other guy
with the long, round nose.
Yeah. There are those
two you just mentioned
along with two others.
Coo-coo!
It doesn't matter what
those pirates are after.
They set foot on this property
tonight, they're done for.
Every single last one of
them, got it? Coo-coo!
[TILESTONE, LULU, and KAKU]
Right!
Yeah. I understand, sir.
I apologize for putting you
in harm's way like this, Paulie.
But this is a very grave matter
and I trust you
can get it done.
Can I put my faith in you?
I give you my word, sir.
I swear. I won't let you down.
You're a good man.
[PAULIE]
Well s'pose I should get on it.
Thank you.
[door opening]
[HATTORI] Coo coo.
He done talking with you?
Yeah. Hey listen guys.
Uh. I gotta head out and
take care of somethin' cool?
No problem, that'll be fine.
The four of us will keep
watch over things here.
Thanks.
Just keep Iceberg safe you guys.
[ICEBERG'S VOICE]
When you leave here.
Go straight to my office
and move my desk.
I want you to lift up the
rug and look underneath it.
There's a safe hidden there.
Jackpot.
[ICEBERG'S VOICE]
Once you find that,
enter this combination.
First, right to number six.
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Puru-puru. Puru-puru.
Chuk chuk.
[MASKED WOMAN]
Are you ready?
[MASKED MAN]
Yes, awaiting your signal.
[MASKED WOMAN]
It will be very soon now.
At that time, the four
of you are to carry out
your respective missions
with ruthless efficiency.
[MASKED MAN] As a loyal
member of CP9, you have my word.
Nico Robin, are you ready?
Yes, I am.
Whoa! Something blew up!
Uh?
Oh no! What
the hell was that?
[CRAFTSMAN H]
Grab water, now!
[CRAFTSMAN I] We got
a man down over here!
[CRAFTSMAN J] Make sure
that fire doesn't spread
to the building!
Guys. They're shooting at us!
No man!
I'm pretty sure it
was some kind of bomb!
Someone must have set it then!
[CRAFTSMAN N] Hurry men!
We gotta put out this fire!
[CRAFTSMAN O] Someone!
Give me a hand!
[MASKED MAN] Not too subtle,
but it'll do. Let's move!
[CRAFTSMAN P] The fire's in the
north corner of the first floor!
Is anyone hurt?
[CRAFTSMAN Q] There've
been no pirates spotted yet!
Everyone keep your
eyes peeled for intruders!
[CRAFTSMAN R]
Stay at your posts men!
Don't let them get inside!
Sir! Iceberg, are you okay?!!
Yeah. Just a bit shocked.
[CRAFTSMAN S]
There they are!
Huh?
[CRAFTSMAN T] It's that guy
in the costume! Get him!
Those bastards!!
RAHH!! I'll pound
in their faces!!
[LULU]
I got your back!
[KAKU]
Wait! Hold on!
For Pete's sake.
[HATTORI]
Coo coo.
There he goes! Hurry!
We got this clown!
He's alone. Box him in!
Stop! It's the end of the line!
[CRAFTSMAN W]
He's headed for the roof!
[CRAFTSMAN AA] So, ya
thought ya could get away.
Didn't ya, punk?
[CRAFTSMAN AA] It's gonna take a
lot more than that to get by us.
You made a big mistake when you
decided to mess with Galley-La.
Prepare for the
beating of your life!
Cause we're not gonna
show any mercy, scumbag.
[MASKED WOMA] You can come
at me with all you've got.
But it still won't be enough.
[CRAFTSMAN II]
Got two over here!
[CRAFTSMAN UU] They're
headed for the back door!
[CRAFTSMAN KI]
Let's try and corner them!
Move, move! After them!
[CRAFTSMAN KU] Don't let
those bastards get inside!
[MASKED MAN] You have the
floor plan memorized.
Is that correct?
Yes.
So, they all seem pretty
worked up down there.
Yeah. There is definitely
something going on right now.
Alright, then. When are
we gonna make our move?
Hey, where's Luffy?
Ahhh!!!
[ZORO and NAMI] That idiot!
What about the plan??!
I thought we weren't
gonna rush into anything!!
[CHOPPER]
Too late.
[CRAFTSMAN KA]
They're going for the back door!
Let's head em off!
[CRAFTSMAN KI] No matter
what, they can't get inside!
You got alotta
nerve coming here.
After the crap you
tried to pull last night?
You're gonna pay
for what you did!
Oh yeah, you guys are in
for a world of hurt for
messin' with Mr. Iceberg!
Surrender!
[CRAFTSMAN KO]
Give it up now,
and we might just go easy on ya!
[CRAFTSMAN KO.5]
You're surrounded!
There's nowhere to run!
[CRAFTSMAN SA] We already
know that it's not just the two
of you guys in your
little pirate gang.
Now where are the others?!
He's pullin' out a weapon!
[CRAFTSMAN SHO]
Shoot 'em!
[CRAFTSMAN SE]
No way! They're gone?!
[CRAFTSMAN SO]
What the hell?
[CRAFTSMAN TA]
Where'd they go?
Hey, are you okay?
Man, that guy's a monster.
He flew. He was
flying through the air.
[CRAFTSMAN TSU]
What the hell?
He can fly?
[MASKED WOMAN] Idiots.
Do you not know when to give up?
Aaaaaah!
[CRAFTSMAN TO]
He's jumping!
[MASKED WOMAN]
Moon Walk!
What the?! He's really flying!
[MASKED WOMAN]
Thorny Road!
[MASKED WOMAN] I told you
you were bested, didn't I?
[CRAFTSMAN NA]
Get ready! Here he comes!
[CRAFTSMAN NI] He's gonna
land in the courtyard!
Don't let him escape!
[CRAFTSMAN NU]
There he goes! Get around him!
We can trap him in there!
[CRAFTSMAN NE]
Yeah!
[PAULIE]
This is it.
[SKULL MASK]
Interesting.
Huh?
[BULL MASK] All this time it was
literally right under our noses.
Hand it over.
[BULL MASK] You can't possibly
understand its importance.
Who are you bastards?
Where in the hell
did you come from?
[SKULL MASK]
From the shadows.
[BULL MASK] Yes. From the
darkest corners of existence
we bring with us
the light of justice.
We are Cipher Pol No. 9, an
undercover intelligence agency.
[PAULIE] Well, no matter
where you freaks came from.
You sure as hell didn't
get in without running
into the Galley-La craftsmen.
[BULL MASK]
Perhaps we did.
Huh?
[BULL MASK] The details
are all very hazy,
a sea of fists and bodies.
What's important
is we're here now.
[PAULIE] I get it.
This ain't just some
assassination plot, is it?
[BULL MASK]
Very astute.
But then, we never claimed
that it was, now did we.
In any case we need what Iceberg
was trying to keep hidden.
The item you hold in
your trembling hand now.
And since you have been
made aware of its existence.
We need to take
your life, as well.
[BULL MASK]
In trusting you to this task,
Iceberg has signed
your death warrant.
[CRAFTSMAN NI] What's
the word? Did you find 'em?
Nu-uh!
There's no sign of
those guys anywhere!
They get inside?
There's men standin' guard
at every single point of entry.
No, there's
no way they got in.
[CRAFTSMAN NE]
Dammit!
Then where the
hell did they go?
[CRAFTSMAN NO]
They couldn't've gotten far.
They've gotta be
hiding somewhere!
Search the perimeter
one more time. Got it?!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
Here. He's behind this wall.
[MASKED MAN]
Right. Now give me a push.
Huh...?
Incredible. I had a feeling that
you'd be coming back for me.
But I can't believe my eyes.
Is this how you
came in last night?
How is that even possible?
[MASKED MAN] It's the
power of the Door-Door Fruit.
Where a normal man sees a wall,
I see a prospective entryway.
No matter how thick it may be,
I simply touch it
and it opens for me.
[gunshot]
Hold on. It's not time yet.
[MASKED MAN] Relax,
it's not a fatal wound,
he'll still be able to talk.
I'm just giving him a
taste of what's to come.
Like an appetizer of pain.
What's more after that,
I don't think he'll be
running off anywhere
before we get the
signal to finish the job.
Or, perhaps I should say to
serve him the main course.
[ICEBERG]
I see.
So that's how CP9
handles things, huh?
[MASKED MAN]
As a matter of fact.
That is how we do it.
That poor Straw Hat boy.
[ICEBERG] He had nothing
to do with this, did he?
There's no need to beat
yourself up about it.
After all, you simply told the
truth exactly as you saw it,
and I was indeed
here last night.
That was all part of
your plan, wasn't it?
[MASKED MAN]
Right again.
You're alive for two reasons.
First, so you could
tell your story
of the failed assassination.
Placing a member of
the Straw Hat crew
at the scene of the crime.
Secondly, we were
trying to ferret out
an important document.
The blueprints
of a certain ship.
One that has been
passed down in secret
from shipwright to chosen
apprentice for generations.
We knew that with your
life clearly in danger,
you would pass
that document on
to someone you
trusted to keep it safe.
You made that choice earlier
tonight. Your foreman, Paulie.
Our associates are with
him this very moment.
It's all going as
planned, isn't it.
You must be very damn
proud of yourselves.
[MASKED MAN] I want you
to see this to its end.
Of course.
[MASKED MAN]
I'll go deal with the riff-raff
standing guard
outside the door.
When the blueprints are secured,
our associates will contact you.
At that time you will have full
clearance to dispose of Iceberg.
Do so at once.
[MASKED MAN] Make sure
he dies, without fail.
After that, the only remaining
loose end will be Paulie.
He dies, and the truth of what's
happened here dies with him.
The blame will remain
on the Straw Hats,
and no one's the wiser.
I know he doesn't listen to me.
It's crazy, but I thought maybe
he'd listen to his own advice.
We are talking about Luffy.
Hey guys. Do you
think that's Robin?
In the middle of all that
commotion down at Galley-La?
No matter what Luffy decided to
do, we still gotta be careful!
Yeah, I know.
But him rushing in like
that might actually work
in our favor.
If you think about
the way he does things,
is he the kind of guy
that's gonna go in through
the back or side entrance?
Not his style.
No way.
So I'm pretty sure
by now he's made a go
at barging straight
through the front door.
And it's safe to
assume that right now
he's running around
inside like crazy,
because he has no idea where
he's going, doncha think?
Oh yeah!
Sounds like him!
Uh-huh! From the
shipwrights' point of view,
he's the leader of the
group that attacked Iceberg.
So if he made it
in there by now,
all of those guys are gonna
be busy trying to catch him!
Which would mean the guards
have severely thinned out
at the front door,
or at the very least,
they're completely distracted!
So the safest way in right
now is through the front,
right behind all the
chaos in Luffy's wake!
So when he does it,
it's completely stupid.
But if we do the
exact same thing,
it's actually a
brilliant plan, huh?
Yeah, makes sense!
I say that we
should go for it then!
[NAMI]
The gate is right up ahead!
Okay! Ready?!
It's show time!
Here we, go!
This was a dumb idea!
[LUFFY]
Guh, crap. This sucks!
I wanted to jump right though
the front door like a typhoon.
But I'm totally stuck!
Gotta get out.
Gotta get Robin!
♪ ending song ♪
[ICEBERG]
After all this time,
I never thought we'd be
meeting here. Nico Robin.
[ROBIN] You say that as
if we were fated to do so.
What do you mean?
[ICEBERG] We might have more
in common than you think.
[ROBIN]
Explain yourself.
[ICEBERG] What I possess
and your existence
could destroy the world.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece :
"CP9 Takes Off Their Masks!
Their Shocking True Faces."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!