[NARRATOR] The first event
of the Davy Back Fight
is the Donut Race.
Luffy and the
Straw Hats managed
to overcome various forms
of sabotage, but even so,
Zoro and Chopper's boat
was knocked out of the race.
Now only the Cutie
Wagon , the Barrel Tiger,
and It's A Raft
remain in the event.
It will be a battle
to the finish line!
This race is
really heating up!
The next course obstacle,
the Long Coral Reef,
is dead ahead!
Leading the race is Porche
and the Cutie Wagon !
Pursuing close behind
are the Straw Hats
in the Barrel Tiger
and At Least It Floats !
Whoa! They're like
Chopper's antlers!
[ROBIN] Why is the coral
in this reef so long?
[SANJI] And why is it
sticking out like that?
Whatever, let's
just get through it.
Look! That weird
reef is causing
some unusual
currents to form.
Going in blind's
not a good idea.
Ugh! I can't believe this stupid
race has lasted this long.
We're counting
on you, Monda!
Shay!
[ITOMIMIZU] And, don't forget,
there's someone on land
looking for every opportunity
to sabotage this race.
Our boss, Silver Fox Foxy!
Just what does he
have in store for us?
Feh-feh-feh-feh!!
[RANDOM FOXY A]
Yeah! Get them, Boss!
[FOXY CREW B] Hahaha!
It's only a matter of time!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Wait, wait! What's this?!
The Straw Hats
are slowing down!
Come on, Nami!
Keep rowing!
[NAMI]
Not yet.
Not yet?! They're getting
further ahead of us!
I know, okay?!
We're not going in yet!
Sanji, you wait here too!
Anything you say, Nami!
The Cutie Wagon takes
advantage of this opportunity
and plunges forward
into the Long Coral Reef!
Let's go, Monda!
Shay!
Hey! Wait a minute!
What's happening?
Monda!
[MONDA]
Shay! Shay! Shay!
[USOPP]
Huh. They came back.
What?! The Cutie Wagon
has been pushed back
out of the reef! What's
happening down there?
I don't understand!
See? I knew there
was something weird
about those currents.
Now! Let's get moving, Usopp!
Right!
You too, Sanji! Pick up
the pace and follow me!
[SANJI]
Aye-aye!
Let's try
this again, Monda.
[NAMI]
Come on! This way!
[ITOMIMIZU] What's this?! The
Straw Hats are picking up speed!
All three boats
are about to enter
the Long Coral Reef
at the same time!
[ITOMIMIZU] Huh... The Barrel
Tiger and At Least It Floats
haven't been pushed back!
[USOPP]
Hey, what's that?
Feh!! Feh-feh-feh!!
[ITOMIMIZU]
Ha-ha! And there you have it!
The devilish interference
we've all been waiting for!
It's some kind
of smokescreen!
You gotta be kidding.
What's that idiot up to?
Hey, I can't see
where we're going.
Now the reef will
be far too dangerous
for the Straw Hat teams
to proceed any further!
And there you have it!
Operation White Out: Successful!
Let's see how you
navigate through this reef
when you can't
even see through it!
You sure it worked?
Puh-puh-puh!
What the hell?!
[ITOMIMIZU] They made it
through with no trouble at all!
How is that possible?
I called it. Puh-puh-puh...
[ITOMIMIZU] Incredible!
The Straw Hats sail through
the Long Coral Reef with ease!
But what about the Cutie Wagon ?
Oh, no! It seems they've
been pushed back again!
Hey, the boat is
moving on its own.
What's going on here, Nami?
This place is a
maze of currents.
Currents?
Right! That giant
whirlpool ahead of us
is causing smaller
whirlpools to form
within the reef resulting
in these strange currents.
Doesn't matter
if we can't see,
their course won't change.
As long as we take
the right entrance,
these currents will guide the
boat along all by themselves.
Incredible! You're a miracle!
That's what you can
do when you have
the best navigator on the
Grand Line in your crew!
Take that!
Nami-swan!
You're amazing!
Damn it!
[ITOMIMIZu] But they won't
be celebrating for long.
Once they're
out of the reef,
they head straight
into the Long Ring!
Long Coral Reef, Long Ring.
It's just one long
thing after another.
Usopp! Stop freaking
out and use it!
Use what?
The Impact Dial!
But I don't have
it with me though!
Oh yeah?
Then what is this?
What the? When did...
How did you...
Come on, hurry!
If you don't use it soon,
we'll be sucked down
into the giant whirlpool!
Why are you smiling?
You know what it's
like to use that thing!
If I do it again,
I'll break my shoulder!
That's a risk I'm
totally willing to take.
That's because
it's my shoulder!
--Impact Dial!
[USOPP]
Hey!!
[NAMI] Come on! We're
running out of time here!
So that's why you've
been acting so calm, huh?
You had this planned from
the very beginning didn't you?
Well, it's been a nice life.
Treinta Fleurs!
Now. Do it, Long Nose.
[USOPP thinking]
"Do it" my butt. Fine then!
[ITOMIMIZU] Oh! The Barrel
Tiger and At Least It Floats
have picked up some
tremendous speed!
No, wait! They're not just
going faster, they're flying!
They're leaping
right over Long Cape!
They have now taken
the lead! But wait!
Oh crap. Oh crap,
oh crap, oh crap,
oh crap, this isn't good!
Aaaaah!!
Whoops. It broke.
[crash]
At Least It Floats
has crash landed
on Long Cape and
broken into pieces!
It can no longer
continue the race!
Such a shame! At Least
It Floats is now disqualified!
I'm so sorry,
Nami, my dear!
Don't worry about us,
just continue the race!
Okay! We will!
[ITOMIMIZU] And with
that move, the Barrel Tiger
now has a commanding lead!
Does this mean defeat for
the indomitable Cutie Wagon ?
We were way too easy on them!
Okay, Porche! Hang on tight!
I'm counting on you!
Combine! Two! Fish! Engine!
[ITOMIMIZU] They're
not out of the race yet!
By fusing fish-man muscle
with the fin of a shark,
the Cutie Wagon has
doubled its engine speed!
They're blazing through the
coral and closing the gap!
[ITOMIMIZU]
The race is now half over!
Meanwhile, the Barrel Tiger
desperately paddles on!
Usopp! Wake up!
Huh? Where am I?
Get up and start paddling!
Your arm seems to be
bending the wrong way.
YAAAAAHHHH!!
What is that?
[NAMI]
Looks like a course marker.
[ROBIN]
"Turn right."
Ah! Guess we'll
turn right then!
Like hell we will!
[ITOMIMIZU]
What's this?! She broke it!
Our Boss' Ploy #18 "Operation
Lie to Them" has failed!
What a formidable woman!
Does she not believe in
anything in this world?
Can it, jackass!
She's foul-mouthed, too!
The race continues
with the Barrel Tiger
maintaining its strong lead!
[NAMI] What are these
columns of water?!
[ITOMIMIZU] They are now
clearing the Long Waves
that reach high into the sky!
Was that supposed to be natural?
Oh, Grandma.
Oh, Boss--I mean--oh, Grandma.
Ahh!! Maybe my time
on this Earth is over.
[ITOMIMIZU] The Boss
unleashes his third nasty trick!
Hey, you! A dying
granny over here.
Won't you stop and help me?
Unbelievable! She
completely ignores a child
and his sick,
helpless grandmother!
The only thing she cares
about is getting what she wants!
How cold-hearted!
The ice queen Navigator Nami!
I told you to can it!
I'd never fall for a
ridiculous trick like that!
Did I mention she
was foul-mouthed?
Hey, look! It's
the finish line!
[ITOMIMIZU]] This race
will soon be decided!
Not so fast! It's not
gonna be that easy!
[ITOMIMIZU] The Cutie Wagon
is closing in quickly!
These are the final moments
of Round 1's Donut Race!
Who. Will. Win?!
[ITOMIMIZU]
[CROWD cheers]
I told you.
These lame tricks won't work!!
[ITOMIMIZU] She even sees
through "Operation Fake Goal"!
Formidable! Truly formidable!
And now, I have a
question for her!
What is it like to go
through life so jaded?
Piss off!
[ITOMIMIZU] It's too late
for her! Her heart is cold!
She has no soul!
But the real goal is nearby.
We're getting close.
I'm not using
that dial again!
Yeah, yeah. I know.
[ITOMIMIZU] Meanwhile,
Porche and the Cutie Wagon
have tragically
stopped at the fake goal!
What's going on?
Who won the race?
What the?! Where
did everybody go?
[ITOMIMIZU] The purity of
your heart is astounding!
Pay attention, Porche!
You've been tricked!
Those guys are
complete idiots!
I'd die of embarrassment
if we lost to them!
They'd take one
of our crew, too!
That's worse!
Oh, no! This goal
is a complete fake!
What?! Who would
do something so evil?!
[ITOMIMIZU]
The Barrel Tiger is finally
approaching the
Long Bamboo Cape!
The goal is
just beyond it!
They're in
the homestretch!
Hey, he's right!
I can see the finish line!
Wait up!
[USOPP] But they're
catching up to us!
[ROBIN] There's no way we'll
beat them at this speed!
[NAMI]
I've got an idea!
Usopp, can you
shoot down that bamboo?
Bamboo?
All right.
Like that?
Yes! More! More!
Monda! Capote!
Move it! Full speed ahead!
We'll ram them and
sink that stupid boat
to the bottom of the ocean!
[USOPP] Take that and that
and that and that and that!
Whoa! Bingo!
Oh, no! Capote!
Say something! I've had it!
They're gonna pay for this!
Cutie Baton!
What's that? Some kind
of magic flower trick?
Flower... Shurikens!
Oh! Flower Shurikens.
Hey! Look out!
Oh, no! Looks like
we've sprung a leak!
Don't worry!
We can make it!
We're almost to the
goal! Keep paddling!
[ITOMIMIZU] Round #1
of the Davy Back Fight,
the Donut Race is
about to come to a close!
[FOXY CREW F]
Porche!
[FOXY CREW H]
Come on!
Stay strong, Monda!
We can't let them beat us!
Shay!
We're going to lose if
we don't do something!
Bring us up alongside them!
Right, Boss!
[CHOPPER] I can't see!
I wonder who's winning?
Made it just in time!
All right! Nami's
team is winning!
Robin, baby!
Nami, my darling!
You look so hot
when you're going fast!
[FOXY CREW A] Man,
you guys almost won.
What do you mean?
We're totally gonna win!
Hahahaha!
Not so fast. Take a
look over there.
Our Boss is coming.
[LUFFY] Yeah? So what!
What can he do?
Our Boss is just like you.
He has Devil Fruit powers.
Slow-Slow Beam!
[ITOMIMIZU] And the winner
is the Cutie Wagon!
The hero of the first round
of the Davy Back Fight
is our very own idol, Porche!
[FOXY CREW I]
All right! Way to go!
Thank you! Thanks, everyone!
[FOXY CREW J]
You're the greatest, Porche!
It's only natural I won!
Looks like we're about to
get another crew member.
There's nobody that can
beat the Foxy Pirates.
We always win!
Hoi-hoi-hoi-hoi...
Feh-feh-feh!
Now it's time for
you guys to pay up!
We're taking
one of your crew!
Are you guys hurt?
Is everybody okay? Robin?
Yes. We're all right.
What the heck
happened out there?
[NAMI] I'd like to
know the same thing.
We'd all like to
know what happened!
Did we really
lose somehow?
It looked like
you were gonna win,
but then you
suddenly slowed down
and they passed you.
Feh-feh-feh-feh!!
There's nothing
strange about that.
It was caused by
Slow-mo Photons.
Hey! What did you do to
Nami's team, you smug bastard?
What's a Slow-mo Photo?
They are particles unlike any
others known to modern science.
Whatever this light
touches, be it an animal,
a liquid, a solid,
or even a gas,
will lose a fixed
amount of its velocity,
while simultaneously
retaining all its other energy.
You're dumb. That
makes no sense at all.
He just mocked me!
Boss! Are you okay?
No way. Something
that ridiculous is just.
Impossible? Is that
what you're thinking?
Surely you know
that such a naïve,
childish claim has no merit
out here on these waters!
Everything they
touch slows down.
That's the power
of Slow-mo Photons!
Now that makes sense.
Why didn't you
say so before?
After I ate the
Slow-Slow Fruit,
I became a Slow-motion
man capable of
producing these
particles from my body.
Observe!
A floating cannonball!
The Slow-Slow Beam!
Feh-feh-feh!
The effect lasts
approximately 30 seconds,
after which, the object
will regain its original speed
as if nothing
had ever happened.
Feh-feh-feh!!
Can't believe your eyes,
I take it? This...
Boss! Oh, no!
I get it! So that's why
we didn't win the race!
It also explains why they're
so overly confident
about these games.
What a joke of a
Devil Fruit power.
It doesn't matter!
You guys lost!
You know all the rules and
you agreed to all the terms!
The Donut Race is over!
And we are the winners!
Awe! Too bad for you guys!
[ITOMIMIZU]
That concludes Round #1!
And now we shall commence
with the awarding of the prize!
The winning captain
will select a member
of the opposing crew!
My first selection
is none other than...
You! The doctor!
Tony Tony Chopper!
No! No, I don't
wanna go! No!
Oh, no! Chopper!
Such a rare creature!
You're even softer than
I imagined you'd be!
Feh! Feh! Feh!
Boss! May I hold him, too?!
He's just so damn cute!
And he's ours now!
No! No! Nooooo!
Chopper!
So, that creep had his
eye set on Chopper, huh?
Well, I suppose that he is among
the rarest of rare animals.
Or maybe he
collects cute things?
You know, I wouldn't
rule out a fur fetish.
Why does it even
matter?! Focus, people!
That freak over there
just took our friend!
You guys.
All right, Doctor Chopper.
Enough of all that.
You're one of my crew now.
You need to pledge
your loyalty to me!
And you can start by
putting on this mask.
You guys...
I'm so sorry that
we lost, Chopper!
We did our best! Fare well.
Feh-feh-feh-feh!
He is truly a rarity!
[PORCHE] Our very own talking
reindeer! He's so amazing!
Hahahaha! We're gonna
get along great! Here!
[FOXY CREW B]
Welcome aboard!
You guys!!
Listen! I only went out
to sea because of you!
I won't! No! I refuse!
Luffy! You invited me!
I set sail to be
one of the Straw Hats!
I won't go with them!
Please! No!
I am the ship's doctor
of the Straw Hat Pirates,
Tony Tony Chopper!
I won't go!
Quit your bellyaching,
Chopper! It's disgraceful!
Zoro.
[ZORO] You made the choice
to set sail as a pirate.
Only you. And now
you have to live
with the consequences
of that decision.
We agreed to the
terms of this game.
You, Usopp, and everyone
else did the best they could.
Not one pirate worth his salt
is going to sympathize
with those tears.
A man, would suck it up
and quietly watch
the rest of this game.
What's wrong with you?!
Don't you know how
he must be feeling?!
Boil me or cook me alive!
Gimme your worst,
you bastards!
Chopper.
'Atta boy.
[FOXY CREW K] Whoa! That
swordsman is totally awesome!
All right! You teach
them a lesson, Zoro!
Yeah! Get Chopper back!
[FOXY CREW F] Hey, Boss!
Let's take him next!
[FOXY CREW G]
That reindeer's got guts!
Let's get the
second event started.
So inspirational.
I can't stop crying!
Yeah. We still have
two rounds left of this.
There's no way we're
letting these jerks
take our emergency
food supply.
Sanji! We're counting on you!
[ITOMIMIZU] The exchange is
complete and the excitement
explodes as the Davy Back
Fight enters Round #2!
Hey. Wasn't Chopper
supposed to be
in the second round?
How can he compete
if they took him?
Good point.
[FOXY CREW A]
That's one of
the most thrilling
parts of the game!
Remember the rules:
You cannot change
your team's roster.
No replacements allowed!
In other words, only the
remaining two contestants
can participate in Round #2's
game: The Groggy Ring!
This gives the Foxy
Team an early advantage!
What?! That's not fair!
Actually, you could
sit this one out, too.
Nah, but feel free to do
the same thing, you loser.
[NAMI] It's hard to
believe that they're
gonna work
together as a team.
--What was that?!
Knock it off!
[ITOMIMIZU] I will now explain
the rules of the Groggy Ring:
We have a playing field,
and we have two goals.
Knock the ball into
the goal and you win!
However, The ball
isn't actually a ball.
The balls are people!
Both teams must select
someone to be the ball!
Make your selection!
You heard him!
Which one of you two
guys is gonna be the ball?
Ball marker.
Who said you get to pick?!
You're the ball, you
Moss-Headed bastard!
[CROWD] Hoom-gabba-gabba-gabba,
Hoom-gabba-gah!
[ITOMIMIZU] Ah, there it is!
Their entrance theme song!
It's time to welcome back
the undisputed elites
of the Groggy Ring!
They are undefeated,
unbeatable, unstoppable.
[CROWD] Hoom-gabba-gabba-gabba,
Hoom-gabba-gah!
[ITOMIMIZU] The famous
Groggy Monsters have
just taken the field!
Behold the kings
of the Ring!
[CROWD] Hoom-gabba-gabba-gabba,
Hoom-gabba-gah!
First up is
"Full-Dash" Hamburg!
Following behind is
"Tackle Machine" Pickles!
And last, but not least,
the half-giant half-fishman
himself, Big Pan the Wotan!
This is, literally,
a monstrous march!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Hahahaha!
What is that?!
That fishman is ginormous!
Oh crap! He's the one
wearing the ball marker!
Feh-feh-feh-feh!
You'll never beat them!
Disappointed?
Heh. Not at all.
♪ ending song ♪
[ZORO]
What are you doing?!
[SANJI] Huh?!
Look who's talking!
[ZORO] If they score,
I'm gonna chop you to pieces!
[SANJI] Shut up, and
don't try anything funny!
[ZORO] You get thrown
around too easy!
[SANJI] I don't need
you to give me backup!
[ZORO] I have to!
I can't count on you!
[LUFFY]
Hahahaha!
They even fight
during the match!
On the next One Piece:
"Round 2! Shoot it
into the Groggy Ring!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!