So soft! Yummy!
Whoa, really?
[PAULIE] Sorry, but you're
not making any sense.
[MIKAZUKI]
Need me to talk slow for you?
Here's the deal.
I'm not paying a single
berry for the work you did.
[MIKAZUKI CREW A] Thanks for
the repairs, they were great!
Listen, Sir, we take
our jobs very seriously.
It's not wise to mock
our shipwrights like that.
Oops. Sorry.
You're on shipwright turf.
This is what
happens when you try
to pull that pirate
crap around here.
[NAMI] It's that tower
right ahead of us.
Everything's huge! So cool!
[BUSYBODY MAN D]
They're strong.
They're skilled.
And they're the pride of
every citizen in Water Seven.
Scary!!
[CHOPPER]
What is that guy selling?!
It looks creepy!
[ROBIN]
It's just a mask shop.
[BLUNO]
CP9
[CHOPPER]
Robin?
[ZAMBAI] Pity, I was hoping
we could kill you in your sleep.
You got a lot of nerve.
Who are you?
You don't know
who we are?! Really?
'Cause we sure know
you, Pirate Hunter!
[ZAMBAI] Babies stop crying
when they hear our name!
A collection of bounty hunters.
We are The Franky Family!
Now, if you don't mind,
I think we'll be taking
that 60 million bounty
you've got on your head.
When we're done with you,
we'll wait inside
that cabin of yours
and ambush the rest of your
crew when they get back!
Hahahaha!
We're gonna be rolling
in the dough in no time!
It's my lucky day!
Lucky, huh?
We'll see about that,
now won't we?
Two-Sword Style.
Rhino...
...Cycle!
[sighs]
Back to sleep.
Ah... man!
[NAMI]
This is the place.
Hey, whatever you
want, make it quick.
We're kinda busy right now.
We need to cash in our stuff.
How much you think it's worth?
Ahhh!!
[panicked] Boss,
come here quick! Ah! Ah!
G-Gold! This much!
No, this much!
Then why are you wasting
your time talking to me?!
Escort them to the
VIP room right now!
We can't afford to
lose this deal, got it?!
[LUFFY]
Wow! Comfy!
After we cash in our gold,
we gotta get one of
these for the Merry.
I could bounce on this all day!
[USOPP] Hey you're not
saying anything.
Don't tell me you
think this stuff is fake!
[OWNER MAN A]
No, far from it!
I've been an appraiser
for 25 years, so I'd know!
This treasure is valued at...
[LUFFY]
O-One hundred million Berries?!
[USOPP]
Keep it down, stupid!
You want the whole
city to know how much
cash we're lugging around?!
[LUFFY] You're really gonna give
us that much money, mister?!
[USOPP]
Play it cool, Luffy!
You gotta handle these
things like a professional!
[OWNER MAN A]
It may sound like a lot,
but that's most
certainly what it's worth.
It has historical value
and high purity.
With a hundred
million we can make
the Merry even
better than before!
[USOPP] No kidding! And we'll
have plenty to spare!
Then we'll spend the rest of on
a big statue to put on the deck!
[LUFFY]
No. No, we won't.
[OWNER MAN A]
Well that's wonderful,
I'm glad you
accept the amount.
Now I need you thumbprint
and signature here.
After that, I'll prepare
your money lickety-split.
[LUFFY] You can have both
my thumbs if you want 'em!
[USOPP]
Mine, too!
The more thumbs
the better, right?
What's up?
Giving him a toe print?
Before we sign anything,
there are three things I'd
like to say. Mr. Appraiser.
First, I forgot
to mention this
but he's got a one hundred
million bounty on his head.
Second, I don't accept
the appraisal you gave us.
Third, if you try
to lie to us again.
It'll be the last lie you
ever tell. You got that?
[OWNER MAN A]
Please forgive me!
Three hundred million?!
This is like a dream come true!
Skypeia paid off after all!
I never thought
I'd see the day!
Y'know, I always
wanted to be filthy rich!
It's our money, too!
[OWNER MAN A] Uh... p-pleasure
doing business with you.
[USOPP]
I don't feel comfortable having
all this money in
one place, guys!
It's scary!
I mean, what if I trip
and it all falls
out or something?
That was great! You sure
were scary back there, Nami!
I estimated 300
million from the start,
but I figured he
wouldn't give it up easy.
You really gotta work
on your game face.
Good thing I was there.
Cut it out!
You're making me nervous
swinging that around!
Well, whatever, we got our money
now and that's what matters.
Aaaahhh!
You dropped it!
Don't let it fall in the river!
Phew! That woulda been bad
if the money got wet, huh?
If you lose my money,
you're paying in blood!
I'm sorry. V-Very sorry.
So please don't
break my face anymore.
[FRANKY FAMILY NONECK]
Whoa, did you hear that?
Sure did!
That's 300 million
Berries down there!
Ain't no doubt about it,
those are the Straw Hats.
I thought grabbing their bounty
was a sweet deal,
but this is way sweeter.
If we meet up with the rest
of the gang and
get 'em to help us out,
we can make twice the money
with only half the hard work!
Hahahaha!
[USOPP]
I dunno, Nami.
Maybe we should take the cash
back to the ship after all.
[NAMI] That'd be a
complete waste of time.
The shipyard is right
around the corner.
Come on. You don't
have to ride so far away.
Let me play
with the money.
Anyway, we'll probably head
back to the Merry soon enough.
After we meet
with the shipwrights,
I'm sure they'll need
to look at the damages
before they can
give us a quote.
I didn't think of it that way.
I guess I can watch
the money 'til then.
I've never carried so
much cash at once, that's all.
I don't know how to handle it.
[NAMI]
Well, that's only natural.
Just don't flail it around
and throw it in any
rivers and you'll be fine.
[LUFFY] Ooh! They're selling
water buns over there!
Let's buy a hundred of 'em!
[NAMI and USOPP]
Shut up.
[LUFFY]
How 'bout a thousand?
[NAMI and USOPP]
Shut up.
[LUFFY]
How 'bout--
[NAMI and USOPP]
Shut up.
[LUFFY]
Okay.
Right. Back to the shipyard.
And it looks like the
crowd's cleared out, too.
[USOPP chuckles]
Well, that's good.
We have enough to deal
with without the shipwright
fan club getting in the way.
[LUFFY] All we gotta do
is find that ice guy.
Uh wait. What's
his name again?
[NAMI]
It's Iceberg.
Oh yeah, now
I remember... Ice Pops.
The old lady back at
the train station said
that's who we
needed to talk to,
but now that
I think about it,
we don't know anything
about him, do we?
Well, it's the
only lead we've got.
I don't know even
how this place works.
Is it okay to
just walk right in?
[LUFFY]
That's what I'm doing!
[NAMI and USOPP]
Not again.
Hold it right there.
[KAKU] You've got
a lot of gumption
just waltzing in like that.
[KAKU] Why don't we
take a step over here.
Then we can talk.
Don't worry. It's not personal.
You're outsiders is all.
So you're not allowed
inside the plant.
[KAKU]
Upsey daisy.
All right champ, what brings
you to the docks today?
C'mon Usopp, I know it's you.
I'm right here, Luffy. Idiot!
Oh, now that I look
at it, his nose is square.
[LUFFY] That means he's
square Usopp! Awesome!
[USOPP]
I'm the only Usopp. Stop it.
Anyway that aside.
We came here to see
Iceberg, if that's all right.
Hmm... Is that so, little
miss? Are you customers?
Oh, that's nifty.
Not every day that
youngsters come here
with a letter of introduction
from Granny Kokoro.
Uh... Hold on,
how old are you?
I'm 23, why do you ask?
You know, for someone who's
hardly any older than us,
you sure do talk
like an old man.
Hahahaha!
I get that a lot.
So, do you know Iceberg,
or did we come
to the wrong place?
Well, of course I know Iceberg.
Why, I'd say that
everyone here knows him,
seeing as he's the
mayor of the city and all.
Wow. Ice Pops is an
important guy, huh?
[KAKU]
Darn skippy he is.
He's also the president
of our Galley-La Company
and manager of the
sea train on top of that.
I didn't know he
was such a big deal!
[KAKU] I had a feeling you
weren't from around here.
Iceberg is pretty
famous in these parts.
But do you know
where we can find him?
[KAKU] Hmmm, that's
the question, isn't it?
He keeps pretty busy, of course.
Hunting him down can
be a chore sometimes.
[NAMI]
But you work for him, right?
Can't you get in touch somehow?
I suppose I could,
but it seems like you're
in a hurry to get this done.
[NAMI]
Not exactly, but--
Hahahaha...
It's fine, I understand.
You're itching to have
your ship looked at, right?
Where did you anchor it?
Uh, it's over
by the rocky cape.
[KAKU] All-righty then. I'll
skedaddle over there real quick.
If I take a gander at
your ship beforehand,
you can start talking cost
with Iceberg right away.
As I said, he's very busy,
so I'm sure he'll
be grateful as well.
Wait, skedaddle like how?
On a Yagara or what?
[KAKU]
Hahahaha.
I thought we were
trying to save time!
If you folks can hang
tight for ten minutes,
I should be back in two
shakes of a lamb's tail.
Just ten minutes?
[KAKU] That's right.
Or your money back.
[LUFFY]
Whoa!
[USOPP]
He's fast!
[KAKU]
Alley-oop!
WHOA! He flew!
Wait, where's he going?
If he jumps off
the edge he'll...
[ALL THREE]
Fall!
No! Come back!
Hahaha!
So cool!
Yeah, but is he gonna be okay?
Don't worry.
He's always
soaring through town.
Huh?
[ICEBERG] They call
him the "Mountain Wind."
If you didn't know,
he's the Galley-La Company's
Dock 1 Carpentry Foreman.
Kaku.
[SANJI] I see. So this
is the city of water, huh?
Pretty impressive place.
Lives up to its name,
that's for sure.
I mean, look around!
Clean water,
clean streets, fresh food,
and most importantly,
plenty of cute girls.
This place has it all.
Take my word for it,
this is the
perfect place to take
that special someone
on a romantic stroll.
But why stop at one when
I have two lovely ladies?
This one is Nami and
this one here is Robin!
[SHOP LADY A] You're
scaring away the customers!
Stop making that creepy face
and tell me which water-water
cabbage you want already!
I'll take both of them.
Oh, and there was something
I wanted to ask you.
I'm looking for
some local specialties
that're in season right now.
So what've you got?
[SHOP LADY A] Water-water
apples and water-water pears!
I can tell you where to find
some fish too, if you'd like.
My hubby runs a stand
just like this one down
at the seafood market.
[SANJI]
And where's that?
First, go over there
to get back on land.
Take six rights and
then seventeen lefts.
You'll see it straight ahead.
Huh?
[SANJI]
Let's see uh this way?
This place sure is a
pain when you have to walk.
If I don't stop
running into dead ends
and start figuring out
where the hell I am.
This food's gonna go bad before
I make it back to the Merry.
Don't tell me
Zoro's brain fungus
is starting to
spread to me, too.
Oh!! Robin, boy am
I glad to see you!
It's me, Sanji! Yoo hoo!
Robin! Look!
Huh?
She disappeared.
Looks like another
dead-end to me.
The only way to go
is up, but there's--
Usopp?
Man, I don't know
what's up with this place.
I'm not going crazy, am I?
[KAKU] Well lookie here.
That must be the one.
[KAKU]
Pardon me.
[thinking]
Oh, it's just Usopp.
My goodness,
I know they told me
their ship needed repairs,
but I didn't think it
would be in shambles!
We should start by
replacing this mast.
[ZORO thinking]
Wait. That's not right.
Hey, I see you!
Don't move! You hear me?!
Oh pardon. I didn't
intend to disturb your nap.
[USOPP] Jeez! That was
a big surprise!
[LUFFY] I've never seen
someone jump that far before!
[ICEBERG]
Mmwell, my craftsmen are
the best in the
business for a reason.
Who is this guy?
Don't ask me.
[ICEBERG] Extraordinary
ships are not born
from ordinary circumstances.
They require a nearly
superhuman level of skill.
By the way, Kalifa.
I've already finished
the background check.
The one in the middle
is Straw Hat Luffy.
His crew also includes Pirate
Hunter Zoro and Nico Robin.
Their combined bounty is two
hundred thirty-nine million.
They have four other members
without posted bounties.
And their crew was
formed in the East Blue.
Named after their captain,
they're known simply
as the Straw Hat Pirates.
[thinking] They've really
got our number.
I see. Welcome.
My name is Iceberg.
I'm the boss here.
And this is a mouse
I just picked up.
Its name is... let's
see... Tyrannosaurus.
I'll need some
rodent food and a cage.
[KALIFA] I've already
taken care of that, Sir.
Mmwell! Amazing work, Kalifa!
Just doing my job.
Speaking of which.
You're due at a hotel
in Chiza for lunch
with a glassware
factory executive.
After that, you're
set to make a speech
at Liguria Square and
once that's finished.
You'll be meeting with
Mr. Bimine, the mayor of Pucci.
Their local newspaper
is scheduled to
interview you as well.
Oh, and when you
return to the office,
there's a folder full
of important documents
I need your signature on.
I don't wanna.
Very well, then I'll cancel
everything for you.
Hold on, you're
not serious are you?!
[ICEBERG]
What's the point in having power
if I don't get
to do what I want?
If that's how you run things,
you've gotta be the
worst mayor in the world!
Yeah Pops, that's pretty lazy.
So hold on, are you
sure this is the guy
that old lady
was talking about?
Uh-huh. He's the
guy, all right.
[KALIFA]
How dare you!
What's the big idea, lady?!
[NAMI]
That was scary!
I won't stand here and
let you insolent louts
disrespect one of the
world's leading ship engineers.
Hey, what's
going on over there?
Iceberg's
secretary just flipped out
on some pirates, again!
I wish she'd flip out on me!
Pardon me.
I get a bit carried
away from time to time.
Still, Iceberg is a respected
figure here in Water 7,
so try to show some courtesy.
Yes. Please don't
provoke Kalifa.
When she lashes out in anger...
...her aim sucks.
We might've hurt his feelings,
but you hurt his face!
You're way meaner than us!
Putting all that behind us,
if you're Iceberg,
you're the man
we're looking for.
Here, we brought a letter of
introduction for you to look at.
From Granny Kokoro?
Take a look at
their ship it says.
Aaaah!!
What?! Are you serious?!
There has to be something
we can do to change your mind!
If money's the
issue, we can pay!
If you're really the best,
then you've gotta be
the one to fix our Merry!
C'mon, we're begging!
[ICEBERG]
Okay.
That's it?! You don't
need to think about it?
[ICEBERG]
Nope.
Then why'd you
tear up the letter?!
The lipstick mark
was creeping me out.
Even so, Granny Kokoro and I
have been drinking
buddies for years.
Mmwell and since
Kaku has already gone
to make an assessment for me,
it would seem like a
waste to turn you down now.
Wouldn't you say?
Besides, it's not like
I had anything better to do.
Let me show you around
the factory, sound good?
[LUFFY]
Sweet! Bring it on!
Come along with me then.
Did he seriously
cancel all of his
meetings just
to give us a tour?
Yeah! You gotta let me sit
on all the cool ships, okay?
[USOPP]
Oh, right... the money.
Wait, what? No!
No, no, no, no, no!
NOOOOO!
Hey! What's wrong
Usopp? Come on!
The-The-The money...
It... it disappeared!
Aaaaahhh!
[NAMI]
Did you drop it somewhere?!
[USOPP]
I don't know!
Hey! Over there!
[USOPP]
Wait! Who are you?!
Why are you taking our money--
I mean, give it back!
We need it, you jerks!
Do you hear me?! Hey!
[chuckles]
Thanks for the cash!
[USOPP]
Give us our money back!
♪ ending song ♪
[LUFFY]
Hey, Usopp!
Why did you give those
guys all our money?!
[USOPP]
I didn't! They stole it!
[KAKU]
At any rate, about your ship.
[LUFFY]
Oh right. How is she?
[KAKU] She must've gone
on quite the journey.
[USOPP] That's why we
need you to fix her!
[KAKU] Well, I'm afraid
I have some bad news.
[LUFFY]
I can't get my statue?!
[KAKU]
Your ship can't be fixed.
[LUFFY and USOPP]
What?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece :
"Galley-La Company!
A Grand Sight: Dock #1!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!!