Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[NARRATOR] In search
of a coating mechanic
to help them reach
Fishman Island,
the Straw Hat crew visited
the Sabaody Archipelago,
with Hachi and Camie
as their guides.
However, Camie was abducted
and placed on a slave auction,
leaving the Straw Hats precious
little time to save her.
[LUFFY]
Time Limit!
The Human Auction Begins!
The "Dark King"
Silvers Rayleigh, huh?
Somehow nobody recognized him,
so they're about to
sell him off at an auction
like they would any
other normal old man.
[laughing]
[GARP] They're selling
the Dark King as a slave?
[laughing]
[MARINE OFFICER 395A]
It does seem farfetched.
To be honest,
my men aren't even entirely
certain it's actually him.
Tea.
[MARINE OFFICER 395A]
Yes, sir.
So how should we
handle this, Vice-Admiral?
Should I report it to
Fleet Admiral Sengoku?
[GARP] No. I intend
to handle this myself.
Don't tell anyone about this.
Not even Sengoku.
And make sure your men
keep their mouths shut.
But sir,
what if it really
is the Dark King?
Oh, it's him, all right.
There's no doubt about it.
This isn't the
first sighting of him
on the islands
that's been reported.
He's probably racked up
some gambling debt
and sold himself
in order to pay it off.
Rayleigh may be an old man,
but if we don't
approach him carefully,
the military will lose an
unthinkable number of men.
The timing couldn't be worse.
Do you really think
the Navy has the manpower
to take on two
legends at the same time?
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394A]
All right, ladies and gentlemen!
Thank you for joining us.
The moment you've
been waiting for
has finally arrived!
The monthly Great Human Auction
of Grove number one
is about to begin!
And here comes
everyone's favorite emcee!
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394A]
Here he is,
the Walking
Super Bazaar himself,
Mister Disco!
[BIDDERS cheering]
[DISCO]
Thank you, everyone!
As always, we've collected
the finest lineup of slaves
for your wants and needs.
And you are in luck!
We've got an extra special
item for sale today!
I pray from the
bottom of my heart
that each and
every one of you
will leave with the
slave of your choice!
Anything in particular
you're looking
to pick up today?
The last human slave I bought
didn't even last a full ten
months before it broke down.
So I hope to procure a strong
and durable male giant
I can really put to work.
I think I might pick up
a few lovely young ladies
for my eye candy collection.
It is an impressive collection.
I can't help myself!
One look at those cuties
and I open my wallet right up!
[laughing]
You...
[DISCO] But enough talk,
let's get this auction going!
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394D]
You heard the man,
get 2 and 3 ready to go.
Yeah, I'm on it.
[DISCO] Item number 1 hails
from Tora in the West Blue.
He's a proud pirate from
a long line of musicians.
And what a talent!
Hand him any
instrument you like,
name a song,
and just watch him go!
He's a living, breathing
jukebox for your home!
A jukebox that'll
mop up any unsightly mess!
You spill it, he'll clean it up!
And he's an expert wine maker!
He's a 25 year old
human in his prime!
Just look!
Six foot four, 286 pounds,
going by the name of Byron!
We'll start the
bidding at 480,000 Berries!
[DISCO]
All right!
Let's see those paddles
and hear your bids!
[RICH PATRON 395A]
Wow.
Anyone would be a fool
to pass up a deal like that.
Number 7 is opening it up
with our starting price!
Do we have another bid?
Keep it going!
500,000!
[DISCO] That's 500,000
Berries from number 82!
[BY-BIDDER 395B]
520!
[DISCO] Yes!
Number 105 bids 520,000!
That's 520,000 Berries!
And for that he'll fill
your home with music,
eradicate unwanted filth, and
with his pirate background,
he'll make one hell
of a guard dog as well!
Now! Let me hear it!
Any other bids?
Five hundred thirty!
Five fifty!
600,000!
600,000 from number 7!
Well? Any other bids?
[DISCO]
Sold for 600,000 Berries!
[DISCO] I've never had
a more brilliant idea
than filling the hall
with phony by-bidders
to jack up the prices.
It's this kind of savvy that'll
secure the Mr. Disco legend.
I'm a genius!
[DISCO] All right,
ladies and gentlemen.
We are just getting started
and have some incredible deals
on the way!
Trust me,
you don't wanna miss out!
Now on to the next item!
[SANJI]
What a sick joke.
Duval, is this list
what I think it is?
Yes. Market prices.
This is insane.
[SANJI] Standard starting price
for a human is 500,000 berries.
Male giants start at 50 million.
Holy crap.
Female mermaids are
worth 70 million berries?
That's why everyone
goes after mermaids.
It's their
get-rich-quick scheme.
[DUVAL]
That's a lotta berries.
Naturally, once they get bought,
they lose every ounce
of their freedom.
They usually wind up as
decorations for some rich snob,
living out their lives
in cramped fish tanks
as exotic eye candy.
[SANJI] Why the hell
are you even telling me this?
Well...
I say "living," but you really
can't call it that, can you?
If that's how you feel,
hurry up and find her!
We've done a thorough search
of all the kidnapping rings
in Grove number 20, sir.
They seem clean.
No one's heard anything about
a mermaid getting taken.
[FISH RIDER 395B] Nothin'
on the grapevine here, either.
[FISH RIDER 395C]
Damn. Same here.
Nothin' even close to a lead.
Make this thing go faster!
Will you get off my ass, kid?
She ain't a bird.
She needs a running
start to get going.
Camie! Where are you?
[MONKEY CAPTAIN]
It pisses me off!
Geez! It was a damn giant!
How often do you
find a giant sleeping?
It was the easiest
catch of my life,
but it was still a pain
hauling the thing here!
A giant like that
would normally be
the main attraction and
we'd all be billionaires!
But no!
Some jerk's gotta go
and bring a mermaid in
at the last minute
before the auction starts!
Ah, I need a drink!
Hold on!
Now who brought in the mermaid?
This is Fish number 5 here!
Attention all Rosy Life Riders!
Come in, Riders!
We've got an ID
on the kidnapper!
It was Peterman!
Word is he sold the mermaid
to the auction house
on Grove number 1!
Wait. It was Peterman?
Do you know where to go?
Yes I do!
Yohohohoho!
Must we fly so fast?
It's terrifying!
I just hope she hasn't
been sold off already.
Hurry up!
Grove number 1
is right around the corner!
Just leave it to me!
[FISH RIDER 395C] We're
headin' for the auction house!
[HACHI]
Nyuu!
You mean we know where she is?
Thank goodness!
Camie!
[LUFFY]
Get a move on!
[ZORO] I'm tryin'
to get back to my ship.
You fellas know where
Grove number 1 is?
[BOUNTY HUNTER 395A]
Well, sure we do!
[ZORO]
Really? Mind tellin' me?
Oh, I'll tell you all right,
but don't go thinkin' that means
you're walkin' away from here,
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Your one hundred twenty
million bounty is mine!
Uh, lemme think.
Which way's Grove 1?
[DISCO]
All right! Moving right along!
Up next. Entry number 6
for your consideration!
A ten pack of stout and
sturdy male human laborers!
[DUVAL]
Calling all units!
Head to grove number 1!
And someone read off
the auction schedule.
[FISH RIDER 386A]
It started at four.
It's been going
for 30 minutes now.
Are we gonna make it in time?
[DUVAL]
Oh, we'll make it.
A mermaid's always considered
a big ticket attraction,
so they won't auction her
off until the second half.
Nothing to worry about!
[SANJI] Just take the
fastest route you can.
You're a lot slower
than the flying fish.
Sure, you just sit back
and take it easy there,
young master.
There's a reason why I'm
the boss of this team, y'know.
Did you notice me
change direction
back when we found out
where the mermaid was?
Uh, no, I didn't.
[DUVAL]
And that's because...
I've been steering us
toward grove number 1
since the very beginning!
Just look!
That's the auction house!
The boss is always gonna be
the first to crash the party!
How the hell'd you
know where to go?
Have you got some
kidnapper intuition?
All right, little buddy!
This is it!
Thank you, sir!
Oh, hey! It's Sanji!
First one there my ass!
[NAMI]
Sanji! Chopper!
Nami!
Hey. We made it!
Camie!
[FISH RIDER 388B]
Good luck, man!
Yeah! Thanks, bro!
[FRANKY]
What's with this guy?
[DISCO]
2 million Berries!
Any other bids?
This is it.
[SANJI] What the hell do you
mean you can't give her back?
[SANJI] I don't care
how things work here!
You have no right to sell Camie!
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394A]
You're the one
who's in the
wrong here, friend.
Keep harassing us and
we'll have to sue you for...
...obstruction of business.
This is crap.
[SANJI] Business my ass,
you heartless turd.
This isn't a business.
You're just profiting
off the misery of the weak.
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394A]
A lawless pirate like you
has no right to lecture
me on morality.
Slavery's considered
taboo the whole world over.
How much are you
paying the government
to get away with this?
That's not a very
nice thing to say.
But you're not too far off base.
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394A] I admit
that whenever the government
or the Navy stops by,
they have a very difficult time
hearing the words
"human trafficking."
Why, I get the impression
they don't have a clue
that we're selling
anyone at all!
What a load of crap.
We know you're in this together.
What the heck is the
government thinking,
letting this fly?
Who cares if they
look the other way,
you should be
ashamed of yourselves!
That's just the way
things are around here,
now accept it and move on.
Please don't make me
tell you a third--
[FRANKY]
I've heard enough.
[FRANKY] If we know
the mermaid's here,
we're wasting time!
Weapons Le--
[HACHI] Nyuu!
You can't do that!
There are Celestial Dragons
in there, remember?
And if they've got Camie,
you know they've put one of
those collars on her by now!
You mean the
ones that explode?
I guess we can't take
her out by force then.
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394A]
You're all welcome to leave now.
You're welcome
to choke on my foot.
Stop, Sanji,
calm down, we can't!
[SANJI]
Quit holdin' me back!
[CHOPPER]
Just let it go!
[SANJI] Dammit! You know
this creep deserves it!
Hey, Nami!
Where you running off to?
[CHOPPER]
You've got to calm down!
Is something wrong? Nami!
If we can't
beat them with our fists,
then we're just gonna have
to beat these bastards
at their own game.
Go ahead and prepare
number 15 and number 16.
You got it.
[LACUBA] Please don't!
I can't handle this!
Please don't make me be a slave!
I'll go back in the cage!
I don't care!
[LACUBA]
Help me! Someone!
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394E]
Sedate him already, will ya?
[LACUBA] Call the Navy!
I'll go to jail!
Please don't sell me to someone!
Hachin. Save me.
Hey, boss.
Isn't that the Straw Hat
crew that just walked in?
Yeah, but the Straw Hat
captain ain't with them.
Shame, since I'd like
to see if that bastard's
as crazy as they say.
Moving right along,
we've got entry number 14!
Our next item for sale
is a female human.
She's a great housekeeper,
and she's adept at a
countless variety of games!
From cards to chess,
there's never a dull
moment with her around!
We'll start the
bidding at 600,000!
Oh! This appears
to be an excellent deal.
Curse my luck!
Why did I have to go
and blow my entire budget
on the first female
human they carted out?
This one is clearly
so much better.
That really is a shame.
I do hope you take no offense
while I bid on this one.
700,000!
900,000!
1 million 200!
1 million 500!
2 million Berries!
Sick bastards.
3 million Berries!
[DISCO] Number 51
has bid 3 million Berries!
Do we have any more bids?
Any other bids?
[DISCO] Sold to 51
for 3 million Berries!
Is this what they're
gonna do to Camie?
I already told you.
We're getting Camie back.
I'm having a little trouble
seeing how
in this situation...
We've got a
good deal of treasure
back on the Sunny, right?
It's gotta be worth
at least 200 million.
[NAMI] And what's the starting
market price for mermaids?
Nyuu!
That's more than enough,
but there's no way
I can pay all that back!
[NAMI] What're you
talking about, Hachi?
Are you Camie's legal
guardian or something?
Nyuu, no, that's
not what I meant.
[NAMI]
Camie's our friend
and we'll do whatever
it takes to get her back,
no matter how much it costs.
Anyone got a problem with that?
Of course not!
Money's the last
thing I care about!
You guys! Thank you so much!
You're, like, the greatest
people I've ever known!
[SANJI]
I like it when she's spicy
but I love
when Nami's sweet!
[FRANKY]
Shut up. Come on.
[DELIVERY GUY 395A]
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
Has the World Government
lost their minds?
[PIRATE 395A]
This can't be real.
If they do that...
This spells trouble
with a capital T, captain.
[DRAKE]
Well that answers that.
I don't get it.
What are you talking about, sir?
[DRAKE]
It finally makes sense.
I wondered why there
were so few marines
stationed on an island
within spitting distance
of a Navy base.
I still don't understand.
[DRAKE] The commander of
Whitebeard's second division,
"Fire Fist" Ace, is to
be publicly executed.
[DRAKE PIRATE 395A]
But there's no way Whitebeard
won't retaliate.
This can only result in war.
[DISCO] Things are really
starting to heat up here
at the Great
Human Auction, folks!
Up next, we've got a deal
you simply cannot turn down!
[DISCO] Entry 15 is an amazingly
beautiful female human!
Just feast your eyes
on those curves!
She's a 20 year old
dancer named Pashia.
Just imagine waking
up to the sight
of this beguiling
vision every day!
Such transcendent beauty
is sure to convince you
you've died and gone to heaven!
[BY-BIDDER 395A]
800,000!
[DISCO] And we're already
off to a bid of 800,000
for the enchanting Pashia!
[RANDOM RICH PATRON 395A]
1 million!
[RANDOM RICH FEMALE PATRON 395A]
1 million 500!
[GENTLEMAN 395A]
3 million!
[DISCO] And the bidding
has jumped straight
to 3 million Berries!
Do we have any other bids?
This is too damn much.
The way they're treating
these beautiful ladies
is making me sick.
We will get Camie back.
I refuse to let her get taken
by one of these monsters.
Nyuu!
[LUFFY]
Faster! Faster!
I'm doin' what I can, kid!
Do it faster, dammit! Hurry!
I'm already at
Grove number 2, huh?
Not much farther to go.
[screaming]
Are you sure you're part
of the Straw Hat crew, buddy?
Because you've done nothing
but scream like a baby
for this whole stinkin' ride.
I can't help it.
This is even more terrifying
than the rides at Sabaody Park!
It's too much!
I feel like my heart will burst!
Although... I don't have
a heart in the first place.
Yohohoho!
You're scared?
I'm the one with a talking
skeleton on his bike.
I wonder if the others
are already there.
Just hang in there,
we're on our way!
We're gonna save you, Camie!
[AUCTION HOUSE MAN 394E] Bring
out number 17 and get her ready.
[CHOPPER] Oh no! They've
started auctioning Camie!
[NAMI] Don't worry.
We have 200 million Berries.
We'll get her back.
[CHOPPER] All these people,
including the Celestial Dragons,
they all want Camie!
It's terrible!
We can't let our friend get
bought and taken away!
[NAMI] This is one auction
we're not gonna lose!
We'll get Camie back
no matter what!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"The Fist Explodes!
Destroy the Auction!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!