[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[crunching, thudding]
[whimpering]
[BOTH scream]
[BROGGY bellows]
[LUFFY]
"Huge duel!
The Giants Dorry and Broggy!"
BOTH whimpering
[growls]
Well, what is the answer?
Could you repeat that?
I didn't catch it.
Please... sir?
I asked if you had any alcohol.
I drank mine.
We have a little.
Oh, you do?! That's perfect!
[NAMI]
Um, there's just one thing,
it's not the drinking kind.
It's for cooking
and disinfecting.
But, if that's acceptable...
...you're... welcome to it all.
[screams]
[NAMI, USOPP shriek]
[T‐REX growls]
[USOPP yelping]
A dinosaur!
[T‐REX growling]
[T‐REX growls]
[whimpering]
[BROGGY yells]
[NAMI screams]
[USOPP screams]
[BOTH shrieking]
I'm Broggy,
the Elbaf's strongest
warrior! Invincible!
[bellows]
[NAMI, USOPP gasp]
Now I have dinner.
And the two of you
are invited as my guests.
[NAMI, USOPP whimper]
[BROGGY]
Huh?
You okay?
[whispering] Just
pretend you're dead.
No matter what happens,
don't move a muscle.
[NAMI whispering] But playing
dead only fools bears!
It won't work!
[BROGGY]
Huh...
[LUFFY]
Whoa! What an amazing view!
This is a perfect
spot for our lunch.
We aren't here to
have a picnic, Luffy!
We need to keep moving!
Huh? Oh!
They have active volcanoes here!
Not only that! Look!
There's a mountain with
huge holes in it!
[LUFFY chuckles]
[VIVI]
It's dangerous up there!
Come down already!
Huh?
It may seem nice,
but it's still a dinosaur!
We have something in common!
We both love to eat!
Besides, the weirdest
thing I've seen all day
is this mountain.
It's really holey!
Come look!
Forget about critiquing
the landscape!
Just get off that thing! Now!
[LUFFY] Say, I wanna see
that weird mountain.
So if it's not too much trouble,
would you mind taking me there?
Hey...
You haven't listened to
a word I've said, have ya?
Gimme a ride, would you?
It's over that way! That way!
No, not over here, dinosaur!
‐‐Over there!
‐‐[DINOSAUR roars]
[KAROO, VIVI scream]
Idiot!
[horn blowing]
[rumbling]
[VIVI gasping]
‐‐[rumbling]
‐‐[horn blowing]
Oh, sorry about that.
I guess I got a bit
too carried away.
[KAROO, VIVI scream]
[laughs]
Wow!
[VIVI] Luffy! I told you
this is too dangerous!
Now get off that thing!
Hey, those other
dinosaurs are much taller!
That means if I hop on one,
I'll have an even better view!
That's not the point, you fool!
[LUFFY grunts]
Yep! Just as I thought!
I can see way better from here!
[LUFFY yelps]
[LUFFY grunting, yelping]
[gasping] B‐Be careful!
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY yells]
Vivi! You've really
gotta try this!
[VIVI gasps]
[yells]
[LUFFY]
Woo!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
Whew!
[LUFFY laughs]
The view from here
is the best yet!
Look at that!
[VIVI whimpers]
[grunting]
[laughs]
[yelps]
[LUFFY yells, laughs]
Luffy, no! This is awful!
He's been eaten alive!
Whoa. It got dark.
[LUFFY yelps]
[LUFFY]
Cool!
[gasps]
[yelling]
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[LUFFY yelps]
[LUFFY grunts]
[gasps]
[rumbling]
[GIANT laughs]
What fun! That was glorious!
Watching the likes of you
grapple with longnecks
is the most entertainment
I've had in quite a while!
You are my first
visitor in a long time.
Wow, you are huge!
Are you human?
Human? What a joke!
[laughs]
Greatest warrior of all Elbaf!
I am Dorry!
[laughs]
It's a... giant!
I've heard that they exist,
but I've never actually
seen one before.
Well, hi! I'm Luffy!
And I'm a pirate!
[laughs]
A pirate?! Well, good
for you, my friend!
[laughs]
[VIVI]
Karoo! Wake up!
We have to get out
of here while we can!
By the way, I'd like you to meet
Vivi and Karoo. Say hi to Dorry.
That's great, Luffy!
Just can't shut up!
[laughs]
Tell ya what.
You're all invited to my home!
[DORRY laughing]
Delicious dinosaur...
[USOPP]
How long do we have to lay here
pretending to be dead?
[NAMI]
I don't know!
This may fool
bears and raccoons,
but it isn't worth
a damn on giants!
[USOPP gasps]
[BROGGY]
Hm?
Hm...
Must've imagined it.
[whispering] We're supposed
to be dead, moron!
[whispering] I'm sorry!
I couldn't help it!
There're tons of
skulls everywhere!
The next ones he
takes'll be ours.
[USOPP]
This is the end.
He's gonna pick our bones clean!
Shut up! Get a hold of yourself!
Well, it's true!
[NAMI]
Enough!
I'll be damned if I'm just
gonna sit around here
and wait to die!
[BROGGY]
♪ Yummy, yummy, yummy!
♪ Dinosaur meat!
♪ Yummy in my tummy,
tastes so sweet! ♪
♪ Grill it on the fire,
take a big bite! ♪
♪ Eat all I can and
sleep good tonight! ♪
♪ Yummy, yummy, yummy!
♪ Dinosaur meat!
That way!
[USOPP]
Gotta go!
[NAMI, USOPP yelling, panting]
[NAMI, USOPP yell]
[BOTH panting, yelling]
[BOTH panting]
[panting]
We made it. Amazing!
[USOPP] Yeah... At least
we got... far away...
...from that giant's stomach!
[SABERTOOTH roars]
[screams]
But...
We ran from the belly
of a hungry giant
right into the belly of a tiger.
‐‐[SABERTOOTH growls]
‐‐[NAMI, USOPP scream]
[USOPP]
Help!
[thudding]
[NAMI, USOPP screaming]
[NAMI]
Please! I don't wanna die.
I cant die without my berries!
Please, someone help us!
[BOTH scream]
[SABERTOOTH, T‐REX yelp]
We're dead!
It's like no matter what
we do, we have no chance
of escaping this cursed jungle!
All we can do is
choose whose stomach
we end up in!
We did everything we could,
exhausted every option!
It's time we just
accept our fate!
Ah! I see the two of you
are awake at last.
The meat is done, so have some.
In appreciation for the alcohol!
‐‐[BROGGY laughing]
‐‐[NAMI, USOPP gasping]
Go on, eat hearty my friends!
It tastes delicious!
I... I think I've
lost my appetite.
Don't be shy now! Dig in!
[BOTH]
No, I don't wanna eat!
[BROGGY]
Huh?
Dinosaur meat is sweet...
I promise you, it's quite tasty.
Well, I guess he's
attempting to fatten us up
before he kills us.
We'll be plump and juicy.
I never thought
it'd end like this.
He's a typical barbaric giant!
[USOPP] We're too young
to die... Too young.
[NAMI]
Maybe that's the appeal.
[BROGGY]
What a waste. It's too bad.
You don't know what a
scrumptious meal you're missing.
We can't eat until
the Log resets...
If we can keep our hunger
and waistlines in check,
we might survive.
Yeah, but...
I don't know how much longer
I can hold out, Nami.
If I don't eat something
pretty soon, I'm not sure
I'll have the strength or
will power to resist his offer.
[USOPP sobs]
[NAMI] Broggy, sir? Do you
mind if I ask you a question?
What's on your mind, young lady?
[NAMI]
Um, how long will it take
to reset the Log on this island?
One full year.
[BOTH gasp]
A year... If we waited
that long to eat,
we wouldn't have
stomachs to feed.
It's over.
We have to admit defeat.
Don't tell me you're
gonna fall asleep again!
[laughs]
[DORRY laughing]
[LUFFY laughing]
[LUFFY] You sure know
how to cook, giant!
Why, thanks for the compliment.
Your pirate goodies
are excellent, too,
my little friend!
Although the portions
are a little small!
[laughs]
Yeah, I know what ya mean!
But the chef on my ship
made it especially
for this trip, so I'm
glad you liked it.
'Cause otherwise,
I'd have to beat you up!
[stutters] Was that
a threat... Shorty?
[VIVI gasps]
[laughs] I like you,
little pirate!
You're really funny!
[VIVI]
They're becoming fast friends.
Huh. I don't mean to pry,
but why do you choose
to live out here
all by yourself?
Don't you have a
village to call home?
I came from a village‐‐
a place of many
warriors called Elbaf.
It once was home, but I
no longer call it that.
[LUFFY]
Why?
There are certain
rules in Elbaf,
which must be obeyed.
What kind of rules?
[DORRY] For example,
if a fight breaks out
and neither side yields,
judgment is handed down
by Elbaf's god. Whoever he
deems to be righteous
will be declared the winner
and granted survival
as well as divine protection.
[LUFFY] So Elbaf's god decides?
That doesn't seem fair.
[DORRY]
Fair or not, all that matters
is this is our battleground.
As on Elbaf, our god will
decide who is righteous
and worthy of winning both
the duel and his life.
[laughs]
We've fought for a century, but,
Elbaf has yet to
choose a champion.
[laughs]
You guys have been fighting
for more than 100 years?!
From a human's point of view,
100 years may seem
like a long time,
but it isn't considering
a giant's average lifespan
is three times yours.
[laughs]
Even with all the
time in the world,
I'd think your desire would wane
after 100 years
of the same battle.
At this point, is there
any real animosity left
between you? Or are you
just fighting to fight?!
Well, I think there's little
risk of being outdone
by Zoro with this one.
I almost feel sorry for him.
With this slab of meat,
he doesn't stand a chance!
I've beat him.
With this haul...
...Sanji doesn't have
a chance of winning!
Hey, Zoro!
Hey, Sanji!
[BOTH]
I am the winner!
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH]
You've lost, dammit!
[BOTH growl]
[SANJI]
Look!
As you can see,
my catch is bigger!
Moron! This competition
is about weight.
How much meat we bring in,
not the length of the beast!
And mine is obviously
way beefier than yours!
Ha! Who cares how
husky your dinosaur is‐‐
all that matters is the
amount that can be cooked!
And that thing's all bones.
You're carrying maybe four
pounds of meat there!
That thing you're luggin' around
is nothin' but muscle and skin!
Ugh. This is pathetic.
I'm not gonna waste my
time arguing with you.
Tell ya what, I'll go
capture another beast
just to shut you up.
Yeah, well if you're gonna
go after a different one,
then so am I.
I won't let you
cheat me out of my win,
because of a dumb technicality.
[rumbling]
All right.
The next eruption from
that volcano will signal
the end of the competition.
You have till then
to secure your prey
and return to the Going Merry.
I can handle that‐‐you're on!
[gasps] Wow, that's
some explosion!
Well then... It's
time to get going.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[gasps]
[rumbling, explosions]
What was that?
An eruption...
[USOPP]
Huh?
[USOPP] I don't like that
look. He seems angry.
Please forgive me,
but there is something
I must attend to.
What? You're leaving?
No choice.
That's the signal my
opponent and I use to mark
the beginning of our fight.
[NAMI]
A fight?
[USOPP]
With who? Where?
And more importantly, why?
[BROGGY]
Why?
I don't remember.
[laughs]
And before we realized,
it became our routine.
That volcano is our marker.
Whenever it erupts, we begin.
It's senseless! How
could you have so much
hatred for someone that you'd
fight them for a century?!
What could have happened
to make you this mad?!
Vivi, that's enough!
That's not what
this is about, okay?
You're right.
This is about honor.
[yells]
I have forgotten...
[DORRY]
...the reason for our brawl!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[LUFFY grunts]
[VIVI]
What's the matter?
[sighs]
This fight. It's‐‐wow!
[rumbling]
Hey, if you're done...
Get out of the way.
Wait... I can handle this.
[roars]
[MISS VALENTINE giggles]
[MISS VALENTINE]
Ten Thousand Kilogram Press!
[Mr. 3]
Oh, hello, Mr. 5.
[MR. 5]
I'm impressed by the décor.
You have a talent for
turnin' even the most
savage environment into a home.
I admire you, which is
why I feel compelled
to remind both of you:
This mission belongs
to me and Miss Valentine.
Rest assured we won't slip up
like we did last time.
[MR. 3]
Slip up?
That's not why I'm here...
Mr. Five, Miss Valentine‐‐
the simple fact of the matter is
you are both weak.
[MR. 3]
Don't waste your energy pouting.
It is what it is.
Take a look at this.
I'd like to thank you both
for affording me an excuse
to come to this island.
I'll enjoy the opportunity
to hunt some truly...
...big game.
[MR. 3 chuckles]
Dorry the Blue Ogre and Broggy
the Red Ogre of the
Giant Warrior Pirates.
Everyone's heard of them.
It's ancient legend.
Hey, this poster is
over 100 years old!
Well, those two legends
are alive and well
on this very island...
battling over a century now.
Back when that poster was new,
the bounty on their heads was
100,000,000 berries apiece‐‐
200,000,000 for
the both of them.
[MR. 5]
Two hundred million berries
is an impressive sum.
But that doesn't change
the fact that they're giants.
There's a wise saying‐‐
Superior criminals are those
who execute their crimes
using superior intellect.
All you have to do is follow
my precise instructions.
With a smidgeon of forethought
and perseverance,
we can find the solution
to even the most
gargantuan of obstacles.
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I wrote you a
love song to let you
Know that I wanna be with
you 'til the end of time
Even when the sparkle fades
The doubts in vade our
once so trusting minds
Promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies
We built a castle of sand
And now we're watching
it wash away,
It doesn't have to end
We'll start again,
this time 'round,
we'll build a stronger love
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I just wanna hold you
and not let go
You know that I'll be with
you 'til the end of time
Oh, you've got me heart and soul♪
[SANJI]
Zoro, do yourself a favor
and capture a big one this time!
[ZORO] Ha! Are you gonna
bring back somethin'
bigger than the tiny lizard?
[USOPP]
Shut up, you two!
Can't you see the duel to end
all duels has started?!
[ZORO]
O‐Oh!
[LUFFY]
Whoa! The alcohol exploded!
[VIVI] That's the barrel
we gave them to drink!
What's going on?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Luffy gets angry. A dirty trick
violates the sacred duel."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!