[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
[LUFFY yells]
Gum‐Gum Pistol!
[CROCODILE] You were skewered,
buried alive, and dried up.
You may have made it
through all that,
but you won't escape
this time, Straw Hat.
There's no hope for survival.
The game is over.
This poison will spread
through you soon.
You know, Crocodile?
You just don't understand.
[USOPP]
We have to hurry!
Nami.
What's going on?
The Marines just helped
us out back there!
Were you able to
find the cannon?
We haven't confirmed it yet,
but this is the only
place it can be!
We must've passed it a bunch
of times before I realized it!
The cannon is up there.
I'm absolutely sure of it now!
Nami! Hey, Vivi!
[USOPP] Sanji, what are you
doing all the way up there?
[ZORO]
Sanji?
Hey! Where were you?
I was looking!
[SANJI]
Zoro? You're here, too?
[ZORO] What're all you
guys doing down there?
[MISS FATHER'S DAY]
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
[MR. 7 laughing]
[LUFFY]
"Magnificent Wings!
My Name is Pell, Guardian
Deity of the Country!"
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[BAROQUE WORKS MEMBER A]
Baroque Works?
I don't know that I've even
heard of such a company.
Are you sure it exists?
We're just ordinary citizens
of Alabasta, Mr. Marine.
You wouldn't wanna
hurt good citizens
just because
there's a rebellion.
[laughs]
Wait, Sergeant Major, they‐‐!
[TASHIGI]
Shut up!
Why were you hesitating, Marine?
If you wait for proof,
you won't prevent anything.
You should be able to tell
who the enemy is immediately!
Yes! We're very
sorry, Sergeant!
[TASHIGI]
We only have until 4:30.
We're running out of time.
The clock.
[MISS FATHER'S DAY]
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
Hey, listen, Mr. 7.
I think this is a very
important mission
the boss has assigned to us.
I think you're
absolutely correct
about that, Miss Father's Day.
And do you know what else?
I bet we'll get big promotions
for pulling this off
successfully, ribbit, ribbit.
[laughs]
I do hope that that is
the planned reward.
After all, this is quite
a difficult mission
when you think about it,
Miss Father's Day.
We're shooting a cannonball
into the crowd
using such a big cannon!
[lauging]
So the reward should
be just as big!
[laughing]
[MISS FATHER'S DAY]
Ribbit!
It's almost time
to go now, Mr. 7!
We're ready to fire! Yeah!
What is it you're saying?
What is it that you think I do
not understand, Straw Hat?
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum...
...Gatling!
I don't think you understand.
You're going to die
here very soon.
The poison from my hook
has entered your wound.
[CROCODILE]
Your body is probably becoming
numb right now.
It doesn't matter whether
you win or lose this fight.
Your body will still be
buried underneath the rubble
when this temple collapses.
[MR. 7]
Fifteen seconds until we shoot!
[MR. 7 laughing]
[MISS FATHER'S DAY] Cannon aimed
at the center of Palace Square,
ribbit, ribbit.
Fire!
[MR. 7 laughing]
Hey, Nami! What the hell is it
you're trying to do anyway?
We really don't have
time to play around!
If we mess this up,
we're gonna die!
Hey!
Thanks, Usopp, but I
already know that!
Now just shut up and stand there
quietly! I'm calculating.
Maybe I would shut up if I had
any idea what was going on!
Would you just explain
what the hell it is
you're planning already?
[NAMI] Calm down!
You'll know soon enough!
Are you ready?
[MISS FATHER'S DAY]
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
Hey, listen Mr. 7. This is
a very special occasion.
I think we should
do a countdown!
[MR. 7] That's a good plan,
Miss Father's Day.
A good plan, a very good plan.
Sounds interesting.
[MR. 7 laughs]
Forecasting... a typhoon!
[BOTH]
Here we go! Countdown!
Cyclone Tempo!
What?
But wait, Cyclone Tempo is
just a silly boomerang game
to play at parties!
Just head for the clock tower!
[wheezes]
[USOPP screaming]
What the‐‐? They're flying up?
Chopper! Jump up to where
Sanji is, all right?
[CHOPPER, VIVI]
Huh?
That's it? This is her big plan?
To make it all the way up
there piggy back like this?
Sanji, you know what to do,
right? We have to hurry!
[SANJI] I think I get the
idea, but it's risky.
Well, I guess I
just have to do it.
It's too late to turn
back at this point.
Tony, let's do this!
Okay, Vivi. Now just
hang on tightly!
I see. That's what
they're doing.
Chopper! Get on my right leg.
[CHOPPER]
Right!
[MR. 7. MISS FATHER'S DAY]
Eleven seconds!
[SANJI]
Here they come, Zoro!
[NAMI]
Good job so far!
[ZORO] So I just throw them
to the top of that tower.
[BOTH]
Ten!
[CHOPPER]
Zoro!
Yeah, I'm ready. Come on up.
Not swords!
It's the flat of the
blade, calm down!
Get your footing.
[CHOPPER]
Okay!
[BOTH]
Nine!
[ZORO] Careful! There's a
couple of weirdoes up there.
Yes, I know them.
Oops.
[MR. 7]
Hello, Miss Wednesday.
[MISS FATHER'S DAY]
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
I'd recognize that
little traitor
to our company anywhere!
They noticed!
They did?!
We're still in the air.
This is really bad!
If they shoot at us,
we're finished!
[CROCODILE]
Whatever it is you really want
can't be in this country.
Aren't I right? You're fighting
for somebody else's goal now.
And how can there be any
point in dying for that?
If only you would just get
rid of a friend or two,
you could easily avoid so many
of these inconvenient problems.
Loyalty is only for
idiots and weaklings.
[LUFFY]
Like I said,
you really don't understand
anything, do you?
Vivi...
[LUFFY] Vivi is always telling
people not to risk their lives,
but she's the first
to lay down her life
in order to save others.
If we don't help her,
she'll die. You'll kill her.
[CROCODILE]
You still don't get it.
That's what makes
her such a burden.
So why not ditch the princess
and save yourselves?
Because none of us
want Vivi to die!
Helping each other
is what friends do!
And that's why none of
us will leave her behind
or quit fighting you!
As long as she doesn't give up
on her country, neither will we!
Even if that means all the
rest of you end up dead?
If we die, we die.
That's all there is to it.
Adjust Ribbit‐Ribbit
Gun for attack!
This is an unexpected catch.
Adjusting Yellow Gun!
[laughs]
How nice. How nice.
This is good!
They are the perfect
prey for us!
What do you think
you bastards are doing,
pointing your guns at Vivi?!
This isn't good! The two
of them are a sniper team!
[ZORO]
Chopper!
I'll throw you guys up, anyway.
It'll change the direction,
but you need to
figure somethin' out!
[CHOPPER]
Huh? What do I do?
We have seven seconds!
Just figure something out!
[ZORO] Chopper, Vivi! Are you
ready? I'm sendin' you up.
Ready?
Aim and fire!
Our bullets are set to
crash into each other!
And then they're
going to explode!
[laughs]
[ZORO groans]
No!
What an idiot!
He's hit!
[CHOPPER]
Are you ready, Vivi?
[VIVI] Just throw me with
all your strength, Tony!
It's no use, ribbit, ribbit.
Dodging.
[BOTH]
Aim and fire!
Who's that?
Huh?
[CHOPPER screams]
Where'd Miss Wednesday go?
Oh! What now?
[VIVI]
Peacock String!
[MR. 7]
Up there!
[BOTH]
Go!
[BOTH yell]
[CROCODILE laughing]
You can talk as
tough as you want
and keep blathering on about
friendship if you like,
but your body is still
freezing up on you.
You look pathetic, Straw Hat.
[yelling]
[VIVI]
Slasher!
Ribbit. Well, Princess.
Looks like you missed us!
[VIVI]
Run Back!
[USOPP]
All right!
[CHILDREN]
Vivi!
[GATEKEEPER]
Hey! Out of here, you brats!
Did you sneak in through
the shortcut again?
Gatekeeper!
[CHILD C]
Run!
[GATEKEEPER] Would the two
of you please say something
to the kids to keep them away?
[PELL]
Hm?
Sure.
Vivi. Going somewhere?
[VIVI]
Mh‐hm. The secret base.
Right. Well, you
have a good time.
[CHAKA]
So, where did Princess Vivi go?
[PELL]
Huh?
Oh, I can't tell you.
It's a secret.
[CHAKA chuckles]
[CHAKA]
The clock tower, huh?
It stopped, right?
[ticking]
[ZORO coughs]
Oh, hey, you're still alive.
Yeah. What happened
with the cannon?
[MARINE B]
What was that?
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
What's the matter?
Apparently, somethin's
gone wrong up there.
It's Vivi. We still
haven't seen her.
Oh, no. You guys!
[NAMI]
What is it?
The cannon ball has
a timing device.
If we don't do something,
it'll explode!
[USOPP]
Ah! What did you say?!
A time bomb? No.
[CROCODILE chuckles]
[CROCODILE]
I was very well prepared, Cobra.
You have to be willing to
admit that much, surely.
The most successful
missions always account
for unforeseen circumstances.
In this case, for instance,
even if something happens
to the cannoneers,
the cannon ball will
still explode on its own.
The attack will only be delayed
by a few seconds or so.
Of course, I did
originally want it
to be shot into the
center of the Square,
but the cannon ball is big
enough that it should do
plenty of damage
from right where it is.
[CROCODILE chuckles]
[CROCODILE]
Stopping the rebellion.
Saving the kingdom.
All those worthless ideas
you've clung to for so long.
In the end, they just created
more victims for me.
[CROCODILE]
Let me tell you something.
[CROCODILE] You're never
going to save this country.
Damn it. This isn't right!
Stopping the cannoneers
should've stopped the attack!
A timer?
Considering its power, even
if it explodes from up there,
it'll still kill all the people
in the Square and the town.
[gasps]
Then what's gonna happen now?!
Oh, crap!
Does this just mean it
was impossible all along
for us to stop the explosion
from happening?
[VIVI] He made us spend all
this time looking for it!
He even announced the attack
so we would do just that!
Why?
[VIVI crying]
Just how far will Crocodile
insist on going
to make fools of us all?
It's not enough for him to
tear this country apart,
he has to mock us
while he's doing it!
[VIVI]
Crocodile!
Wait, was that‐‐?
Yeah, I think it's the bird man.
[VIVI]
Pell?
Wow, this place brings
back so many memories.
The Sand‐Sand Clan's
super‐secret base.
Pell, listen to me...
You certainly were a mischievous
little child, Princess Vivi.
You gave us no end of trouble
with all your pranks
and disappearances.
[ROYAL SOLDIER A]
It's Vivi!
What's she doing in
the ammunition bunker?
Hey! What happened?
What was that explosion?
[coughing]
Princess Vivi, how many
times have we told you
not to go near the
ammunition bunker?
You could get hurt!
[VIVI]
Pell!
[ROYAL SOLDIER B]
Sir!
I was trying to make some
fireworks, but I messed up.
I know it's the
anniversary of the day
you joined the army, Pell, so‐‐
[ROYAL SOLDIER C]
What are you doing?
[PELL]
I've told you a hundred times!
Never, ever come near here!
[IGARAM] Just what do you
think you're doing?
How dare you touch the Princess!
You're through! No
one dares hurt her!
Hold on, Igaram.
It's fine.
[PELL]
It could've been much worse.
What if you were killed?
[VIVI]
Faster!
And go higher! Higher!
[PELL] Vivi, I need you
to promise me something.
Never tell the king about this.
[giggling]
He made it clear that I'm
not supposed to do this.
He told me to never to go
flying with you on my back.
If you're scared, fine!
But I'll never forgive
you if you stop!
[VIVI ggigles]
[VIVI] After all, didn't
you say you'd do anything
I wanted you to?
[giggling]
[VIVI]
Hey, Pell?
[PELL]
Yes?
[VIVI] You train for
battle every day. Why?
[PELL]
Because I'm a guard.
It's my duty to
protect this country.
I have to stay strong.
So, who will you be fighting?
Who?
I don't know.
But I don't fight. I protect.
[VIVI]
They're different?
[PELL]
They serve different purposes.
[VIVI]
Hmm. I don't understand.
I'm so proud that I've
been able to serve you
all these years, Princess.
Protecting the Nefertari
family has been an honor.
[gasps]
[ALL]
Huh?
[inaudible]
[PELL]
I am...
...Alabasta's guardian deity.
[PELL]
The Falcon!
[PELL] And I am sworn
to destroy the enemies
of the royal family!
♪Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!♪
[VIVI] This bloodshed has
got to stop now!
[NAMI]
Why aren't they stopping?
[VIVI] Please! You have
to stop fighting!
[CROCODILE] Where is this brat
getting all of his strength?
[LUFFY yells]
[CROCODILE] Just who do you
think I am, Straw Hat?!
[LUFFY]
I don't care who you are!
I will defeat you,
no matter what!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"I Will Surpass You!
Rain Falls in Alabasta!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!