[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY] "Alabasta's Hero
and a Ballerina on the Ship!"
‐‐[CITY FOLK screaming]
‐‐[PIRATES laughing]
[MAN D groans]
[WOMAN A, CHILD whimper]
‐‐[CITY FOLK screaming]
‐‐[PIRATES laughing, yelling]
[WOMAN B whimpers]
[gasps]
[WOMAN B]
It's Crocodile!
[gasps]
Crocodile! He's here!
He's here to save us!
[PIRATE CAPTAIN]
Huh?
[CITY FOLK chattering]
Crocodile?
One of the Seven Warlords?
[CITY FOLK shouting]
[CROCODILE]
Calm down, ignorant peasants.
I only came to your
pathetic little town
for that pirate's head.
He's so great!
And modest!
He comes and saves us but he
won't take the credit for it!
Three cheers for Crocodile!
[WOMAN B]
The Guardian Angel of Alabasta!
[MAN B]
King of the desert!
[MAN C]
Crocodile!
[CITY FOLK cheering]
[CROCODILE laughs]
You peasants can call
me whatever you want.
But you.
You pirates should have
stayed out of this country.
Now you're gonna pay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! I think
you're underestimating us a bit.
What, are you gonna
take us all on?
There are a lot of us
and only one of you!
That's right!
And your just the
governments little dog.
Who do you think you
are acting like a hero?
For those who wish
to live, lie down now.
[PIRATE CAPTAIN] What an idiot!
Perfect for target practice.
Get this guy!
Every last Berry in
this town is ours.
[PIRATES]
Yeah!
[PIRATES grunt]
[laughs]
Nothing but a pathetic puppet!
[PIRATES grunting]
[PIRATE CAPTAIN gasps]
No...
[groans]
[CROCODILE] Hm. I'm a puppet,
huh? I don't think so...
...idiot pirate.
[MAN D groans]
[CITY FOLK gasp]
[MAN C]
We've been saved!
He's leaving now?
[CITY FOLK] Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile! Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile...
[CITY FOLK] ...Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile! Crocodile!
Looks like he
beat us here again.
[COBRA] Seems like he's
always one step ahead.
By the time we arrived,
the pirates had already
been taken care of.
[COBRA]
I see...
Well, as long as the
citizens are safe,
I suppose there's
no need to worry.
Crocodile has been a great help.
There's no mistaking it.
I hope you're ready!
We've almost made
it to Alabasta.
[VIVI]
Father... I'll be there soon.
[SANJI]
Don't lie to me Luffy!
Tell me what you know right now.
Don't look away from me.
I want to you to look
me in the eyes right now
and tell me the truth.
No idea what you mean, Sanji.
I don't know anything!
No clue.
Then let me ask you.
How did enough food
for eight people,
which I carefully divided
up so that it would last
until we reached Alabasta,
suddenly go missing in
the middle of the night?
Lying is pointless,
so just tell me the truth.
You have a terrible poker face.
[LUFFY burps, groans]
Oh hey,
it looks like you have something
around your mouth, there.
I forgot about the crumbs!
[grumbling]
I knew it was you!
[LUFFY groans]
Jerk.
Hey Nami, we need
to do something.
We need a better way of keeping
the food safe from Luffy.
Can we please buy a
refrigerator that locks?
Well, maybe.
Might be a good idea.
Since it could be a
matter of life and death.
[USOPP gulps]
Well,
we really do need to
catch something for Sanji.
[KAROO squawks]
[SANJI]
So how's the fishing going?
Uh... well, it's, uh...
[KAROO squawks]
[SANJI chuckles]
[USOPP, CHOPPER, KAROO
yell, mumble]
Pathetic.
I can't take my eyes off anyone!
[stomach grumbles]
[LUFFY]
Uh... I'm so hungry...
And the fish aren't
biting at all.
Really?! You do realize
this is your fault.
You ate all the
bait that we had!
The fish aren't ever gonna bite
if we don't give them a reason!
[LUFFY]
Hey, you ate some too!
[USOPP] But... I only
ate a little bit!
Just what was stuck to the lid.
Hey guys! so how's it going?
Catch anything yet‐‐
[KAROO squawks]
‐‐[VIVI screams]
‐‐[KAROO squawking]
‐‐Karoo?!
‐‐[VIVI wails]
‐‐[KAROO squawking]
Do you think we
could catch a shark?
Don't know.
I really want to
catch a sea king.
Stop fishing with...
...my duck!
‐‐You jerks!
‐‐[LUFFY, USOPP groan]
[KAROO squawking]
[VIVI]
Hmph.
[gasps] Over there you two...
What is that stuff?
Cotton candy...?
You guys wait here,
I'll go get Nami.
Nami there's something
wrong, come quickly!
Oh yeah, I see it.
Nothing to worry about.
It's just a little steam.
You're saying that steam's
coming up out of the ocean?
Uh‐huh.
A hot spot, that's all.
What's a hot spot?
An area of the sea
where magma's made.
Below the steam over there
is an undersea volcano.
There are volcanoes...
underneath the sea?
[NAMI]
That's right.
In fact, there are actually
more volcanoes under the sea
than there are on dry land.
[USOPP]
Oh!
So I guess we can't eat
the steam then, huh?
There will be a brand
new island over there...
...thanks to the volcano.
But the process will take
tens of thousands of years.
Oh wow, you're amazing Nami!
[LUFFY] I wonder if
I can live that long.
[USOPP] I'd plan on dying
sometime before that.
[KAROO squawking]
[SANJI]
Have you caught anything?
We're so hungry, can't you
cook us something?
You guys are just hopeless.
But I'll go search the
storage area anyway
to see if we have anything left.
[ALL coughing]
[USOPP]
Yuck! It smells like sulfur!
[LUFFY] I can't see anything,
there's steam everywhere...
[NAMI] Just bear with it, we
should be out of the steam soon!
[SUBORDINATE 1]
Excuse me! Mr. 2!
[MR. 2]
What is it now?
There's a whole bunch of
smoke at 12 o'clock!
I'm not afraid of
some smoke! Keep going!
No matter what, we've got
to take care of Mr. 3!
Or else the next
target's going to be me!
[SUBORDINATE 1]
Yes sir! We're going in!
What is this?
I have no idea.
[SUBORDINATES yell]
[SUBORDINATE 1]
We made it through!
[MAN ASUBORDINATE 1 yells]
[SUBORDINATE 1] Mr. 2 has
completely disappeared‐‐
Let's check the cabins!
[SUBORDINATE 2]
We can't find him!
[SUBORDINATE 3]
This is bad!
[SUBORDINATE 4]
Where did you go?!
[LUFFY, USOPP groan, gasp]
[USOPP stutters]
[KAROO squawks]
Now, really! This is
getting out of hand!
One of these days,
I need to stop
jumping on every
random duck I see.
What is that...?
[MR. 2 yells]
[MR. 2]
You have to help me, please!
Get me out of here
please, I can't swim!
[MR. 2 panting]
[MR. 2] I thought I was going
to die there for a minute.
Hey! You saved me!
Thanks!
I never imagined my
life would be saved
by a group of
complete strangers.
Thanks again.
I'll never forget
your kindness.
Although, could I trouble
you for a cup of warm soup?
Chicken noodle will do.
[ALL]
No way!
We can't even feed ourselves!
Oh hey... You're just an
absolute cutie, aren't you?
Oh yeah! Sexy!
He's so weird.
So, uh... you really
can't swim, huh?
That's right! You see
I ate a devil fruit
so I can't swim
even a little bit.
Yeah? What kind of fruit?
Let's see...
Well, since I can't go anywhere
until my ship picks me up,
there's no harm
in a little fun.
For saving my life,
I'll show you.
Now, get ready.
This is my power!
[LUFFY groans]
[USOPP gasps]
‐‐[ZORO] What're you‐‐
‐‐[LUFFY] Wait, wait.
[LUFFY]
Hold on a second!
This is all just for
a little fun, remember?
[gasps]
Hey now... mean guy! Relax!
Wait!
That's me‐‐
Fun, fun, fun, fun,
fun. fun, fun!
[laughs]
And if I touch my face
with my left hand...
...I'm back to normal.
Now that is the power of the
Clone Clone Devil
Fruit, you see.
[NAMI]
Amazing...
The body and the
voice matched perfectly!
‐‐[LUFFY] Wow! Just wow!
‐‐[MR. 2] You, and you,
‐‐and you and you!
There!
But honestly I didn't
really have to slap you
around like that.
'Kay! Now watch.
All I have to do...
...is touch my
right hand to you.
As you can see,
I can mimic anyone.
That's not all. I can change...
...bodies too.
[USOPP, CHOPPER, LUFFY yell]
[MR. 2 groans]
Stop that!
Uh guy, are you okay?
[MR. 2]
Well, I'm terribly sorry...
...but... I shouldn't
demonstrate my power anymore.
‐‐[LUFFY, CHOPPER cheering]
‐‐[USOPP whistling]
Okay! If you absolutely insist,
I guess I can
show a little more!
[LUFFY, USOPP, CHOPPER cheering]
He's really hamming it up, huh?
[MR. 2]
Well in that case,
I have something
even more incredible.
I'm equipped with
a memory feature!
[CHOPPER, USOPP, LUFFY cheering]
'Kay!
[LUFFY, USOPP, CHOPPER gasp]
[LUFFY, USOPP, CHOPPER laugh]
[gasps]
[MR. 2] And around and
around and around we go!
This is just boring.
[MR. 2]
And twirl! Open plie.
Well...
...did everyone enjoy my
very special secret talent?
It's quite impressive, but I
almost never show it off!
[VIVI gasps]
[LUFFY, USOPP, CHOPPER]
Oh yeah!
[ALL]
It's to good to be true!
Oh, whatever.
[sighs]
Huh?
[MR. 2] It's time to say
goodbye already? What a shame.
[LUFFY, USOPP, CHOPPER]
No!
No, you can't leave!
Please don't go!
[MR. 2]
Try not to be sad.
Journeys must always
include farewells.
And yet...
...I will never
forget you or today.
It's been brief...
...but true friendship
isn't determined by time.
Don't cry, friends!
See you, cool guy!
Now quickly let's be going!
[SUBORDINATE 1] Yes sir,
Mr. 2! Mr. Bon Clay, sir!
[ALL gasp]
Mr... 2?!
That guy... is... Mr. 2?
Vivi! You mean you didn't
know him just by looking?!
Uh‐uh... I've never met
Mr. 2 or Mr. 1 and his partner.
I don't know much
about any of them,
or what their powers may be.
Though I have heard
rumors about them all.
I've heard about Mr. 2.
[VIVI] Apparently, he's a
very tall ballerina
who talks like a woman.
And he always
wears a swan coat.
The coat says "Bon Clay"
on the back.
[ZORO, USOPP, LUFFY]
You didn't know?!
Is something wrong, Vivi?
I saw something in his memory...
...in the faces
that he showed us.
One of those faces...
...belonged to my father!
Cobra Nefertari...
...my father,
the king of Alabasta!
That's not good.
If he can mimic the face
of a king that easily,
Mr. 2 has the potential
to cause a lot of trouble.
Looks like we let a really
bad guy get away today, huh?
So that guy is our enemy?
Seems so.
And having him on the other
side is not a good thing.
If Mr. 2 realizes that we're
the ones Baroque Works is after,
then he can use the
memories he got earlier
to transform into any one of us!
We won't even be able
to trust our own friends.
[gasps]
Really? Uh...
I'll explain it again.
[ZORO]
No, hold on a sec.
Luffy's slow but he's
right not to be scared.
Just hear me out on this one
and I think you'll agree.
It's actually a good thing that
we ran into Mr. 2 when we did,
because now we can prepare.
And we can beat him
at his own game.
You sure seem to be in
a particularly good mood...
[MR. 2]
Un, deux, trios...
...how do you say four again?
[laughs]
It just so happens, I made
some new friends today!
[ALL yelling]
[LUFFY]
That thing is huge!
A sea cat!
[CHOPPER]
It's a sea monster!
It looks like food to me!
Yeah! Let's go!
We're on the right track.
Now... if we can just get
there alive, that'd be great.
Food for me!
[SEA CAT whimpers]
[ZORO]
It's backing away!
[LUFFY] Reverse!
Put the boat in reverse!
[USOPP]
No! We can't do that!
[SEA CAT whimpers]
[SANJI]
Hey! Don't let it get away!
If the two of you don't
capture it, I'll kill you!
[SEA CAT whimpers]
Now then, sea kitten!
How do you think
I should cook you.
‐‐[VIVI] No!
‐‐[LUFFY, SANJI, ZORO groan]
[SEA CAT sighs]
Vivi, what are you doing?
I'm hungry!
Why... just why? It was food!
Because you can't eat a sea cat!
I just can't let you!
Sea cats are sacred
animals in Alabasta.
Well that's good to know...
There are more animals in
the ocean than I thought!
[USOPP stutters]
If you're still
scared of that stuff,
then you have a long way to go!
So! Let me tell you about
the time that I, Usopp,
single handedly fought off
the sea kings of the Calm Belt,
young Chopper.
[CHOPPER]
Sea kings? Really?!
And big ones, too! Man!
They were really huge!
[cries] All our food got away!
Yeah, but don't worry, Luffy.
You'll be able to stuff
yourself full really soon.
Yeah? Really? Will we get
another cat to eat, Vivi?
[NAMI] Vivi! The wind and
weather seem to be stabilizing.
Uh‐huh. We're entering the
climate area of Alabasta island.
Seeing a sea cat come out of
the water is proof, as well.
And those things you see
behind us over there...
...are all the proof I need
that we're getting close.
[gasps]
That's a lot of ships, huh?
Who are they?
[USOPP whimpers] They're all
flying the Baroque Works symbol
on their masts.
This can't be good.
It looks as if all the
Baroque Works employees
have started gathering.
I'm guessing that these
are the billions.
They're the subordinates
under the officer agents.
Which means that
there are at least
200 enemies waiting for us.
The best that Baroque
Works has to offer.
The elite of the underlings.
This group will
surely be a lot better
than the bounty hunters
at Whiskey Peak.
[grunting]
[sighs]
C'mon, lets blow 'em
all away! If we're lucky...
[LUFFY] It'll be quicker
if we just go over there
and beat 'em up!
[stomach grumbles]
Hold on, though. I need
to eat something first.
Come on, they're not worth it.
Don't bother.
[SANJI]
He's right.
We need to keep our
eyes on the prize
or we might lose
this altogether.
After all, eight
against 200 sucks.
[grunting]
[ZORO]
Just make sure and tie it tight.
I don't want anyone fooled
by the enemy's disguises.
What a good plan.
We'll always know
who are friends are.
Just... look for the
bandage on their arm!
This Clone Clone Fruit guy...
So... is he that similar when
he turns into someone else?
You have no idea!
It's the same, not just similar!
It was crazy! Really!
You shoulda seen it, Sanji,
he changed into every one of us,
even Nami, and then we
got to dance with him.
I'm not really interested in
dancing with a male ballerina.
We know that someone with his
powers is among the enemy,
so we need to be really careful
to be on our guard at all times.
So, what should I do
to help against this guy?
Just do whatever
it is you can do.
You're not expected to do
anything more, Chopper.
And if you get overwhelmed,
then just run.
Sounds like the pep talk
he's always giving himself.
[KAROO squawks]
Whatever it is I can do...
...I got it!
[LUFFY]
I can see the island now!
[VIVI] Let's stop at
the town called Nanohana.
We have to hide the ship.
Okay.
No matter what happens on
that island, remember...
...this thing on all our arms,
is a sign of our friendship.
Now! Let's land, okay?
Then eat! Oh, and help Vivi.
[ZORO sighs]
[OTHERS]
That's a side note?
Now remember, our enemy is
a whole gang of assassins.
Uh, yeah. Sure is.
Just try to think before
you do anything stupid,
you got that?
[LUFFY]
Yeah, of course.
You're right, I got it.
No really, I will!
‐‐[VIVI giggles]
‐‐[LUFFY] I promise!
♪My life has been too still
My heart is unfulfilled
But you could be
the one to set me free.
Something has to change
My world can rearrange
I'll do anything as long
as you are with me!
I've grown stronger
having you by my side
We've started on
an everlasting ride
I'm invincible when
your love is near
When I'm with you
I have no fear!
Let's see how far
We can make this go!
The world is ours
Future's bright, I know!
I see it shine
In the distance, glistening
like water when the sun
Rises in the dawn!♪
[LUFFY]
Food, food, food, food!
[USOPP]
So this is Alabasta, huh?
[NAMI]
It sure is a lively town.
[CHOPPER] Yeah, but...
it's really hot, too.
[VIVI]
The town still seems peaceful.
[ZORO] So, when is the riot
actually going to happen?
[SANJI] We just have
to stop it, right, Vivi?
[VIVI]
Yes.
[LUFFY]
Hungry!
On the next One Piece!
"Off to the Desert Kingdom!
The Rain‐Summoning Powder
and the Rebel Army!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!