[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] Luffy grieved over
the loss of his brother, Ace,
in the War of the Best
against the Navy.
After recovering thanks
to Jimbei's encouragement,
he met with Dark King Rayleigh.
Well, then, that's it.
If you think I should,
I'll go back... to Marineford!
[NARRATOR]
One by one,
the rest of the Straw Hats
learned of the big news.
No way! I don't believe it!
Luffy!
[gasps] Luffy!
Oh, good. He's safe.
[SANJI]
It's in today's paper?
[gasps] Whoa!
[LUFFY] "Unexpected Relanding!
Luffy, to Marineford!"
[NARRATOR] At Navy Headquarters,
located on the Grand Line.
[BRANDNEW]
It's incomprehensible!
During the War of the Best,
it was revealed that Straw Hat
is the late Portgas
D. Ace's adopted brother,
on top of also being the son
of the Revolutionary, Dragon.
Which would make
him the grandson
of our own Vice Admiral Garp,
if you're paying attention!
So, tell me,
how did all of
this slip past us?
After the war, he went missing,
but lo and behold,
he was alive, as we expected.
Now, after everything
that's happened,
he has the gall to come
to Marineford again!
[NARRATOR]
A few days ago...
The damage is unreal!
[REPORTER A]
What did you expect?
It was an all-out war
between the Navy elite
and the world's greatest pirate.
It's a miracle that the island
is still standing, isn't it?
So, what brings you out
to this pile of rubble?
A story, of course!
I came from Alabasta to cover
Crocodile and Straw Hat.
Though, supposedly, Straw Hat
could already be dead.
I'm sure the Navy wants
you to think that,
but right now there's
no way of knowing,
what with everything
else that's going on.
I mean, look at what
they're dealing with here.
[REPORTER F]
That's true.
[WHITEBEARD]
The One Piece!
The One Piece is real!
[REPORTER F]
With his dying words,
Whitebeard inspired pirates
all over the world.
They're committing crimes
more often than before.
Every able-bodied
Navy soldier available
has to deal with the
increase in pirate activity.
Well, how unfortunate for them!
Huh?
Speaking of which, here come
some Navy soldiers now.
Huh?
What's wrong with them?
How come they're still out
there instead of docking?
Hey! The ship is acting funny.
[REPORTERS gasp]
[CROWD gasping, screaming]
A blank shot?
[MARINE B]
What's going on?
Have they contacted us?
[MARINE I]
No, sir!
He came back! But why?
Is that kid out of his mind?
Who came back?
[MARINE C]
Look! It's Straw Hat Luffy!
You've got to be kidding me!
[MARINE J]
He must've stolen that ship!
[MARINE K]
He's out for revenge!
[MARINE B] Pirates never
learn. Sink the ship!
[JIMBEI]
Fishman Jiu-Jitsu!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
[gasps]
[MARINE B]
It's Jimbei! That traitor!
There's someone else!
Uh-oh. This could get ugly, men.
They've got the first mate
of the Roger pirates with them,
Dark King Rayleigh.
[MARINES, CROWD gasping]
[REPORTER F]
Look!
It still hasn't come
any closer to the shore.
They circled around
the island once.
It's like a funeral at sea!
It's a taunt. Without
our main forces here,
they think they
can bury us alive.
Enough! Barrage them
from all directions!
Fire at will!
[CROWD gasps]
[MARINES gasp]
[LUFFY grunts]
You've made it this far,
might as well get to work.
Right!
[CROWD murmuring]
Don't let him get away!
[JIMBEI] If you want someone
to fight, I'm ready and waiting!
Not too fancy to fight
an old man, are you?
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
--[MARINES groan]
--...Whip!
What is Straw Hat doing?
It seems like he's
looking for something.
That, or he came back
to bring the whole island down!
[MARINES yelling]
He's up at the Ox Bell.
What is he up to?
[LUFFY grunts]
[bell tolling]
[CROWD gasping]
[MARINE F grunts]
[MARINE F whimpers]
[MARINES gasp]
--[MARINES] Huh?
--Flowers?
[REPORTER F gasps]
[CROWD gasping]
Now this is gonna make
for a great photo!
[CROWD gasping]
[MARINES gasp]
[MARINE L]
Don't let him get away!
And now he's leaving?
What was that all about?
[REPORTER E] Dark King Rayleigh,
the Warlord Jimbei...
Are they forming an alliance?
Rayleigh used to be a crew
member of Gold Roger's.
Could Straw Hat be
Roger's successor?
Straw Hat may be Ace's brother,
but he's not Gold Roger's son.
This whole thing is weird.
Wow, no matter how you spin it,
this story's gonna be huge!
This article's already
been circulated
throughout the entire world!
Those journalists are so
starved for attention,
they even mentioned
how Straw Hat escaped!
This is humiliating!
If we take this appearance
of his at face value,
all Straw Hat did
was pay tribute
to his brother Ace, Whitebeard,
and all the other people
who died in the war.
The moment of silence
and trip around Marineford
support that notion,
but he rung the bell
not twice, as is customary,
but a whopping 16 times!
Sixteen bell tolls!
There's no doubt in my mind
that this is a challenge to us!
Oh, honestly! For such a rookie,
this Straw Hat Luffy
is certainly controversial.
But the boy is Garp's grandson,
so I suppose I shouldn't
be surprised.
I'm curious as to how he
and Rayleigh know each other.
I highly doubt Rayleigh
intended to rejoin the fray.
A pity Jimbei decided
to turn against us.
His allegiance to
the World Government
as a Warlord acted as
a symbol of intertribal peace.
It's disappointing to lose him.
Thanks to this turmoil,
the Three Great Powers
are completely unbalanced.
Also, how should we take care of
the vacancies among
the Seven Warlords?
First we need to observe what
will unfold in the New World.
Relationships and
hierarchies among pirates
are sure to change.
We must take great care
in ensuring we pick
the most powerful ones.
[ELDER STAR D]
Blackbeard already made
his first move in
the New World, by the way.
He knocked off
a promising rookie--
one that had a bounty of
over 100,000,000 berries.
[ELDER STAR A] And thanks
to his time with Whitebeard,
he knows all about
the old man's territory.
[ELDER STAR E] He certainly
has a lead over any other pirate
who's aiming to become
one of the Four Emperors.
[ELDER STAR E]
No one else in history
has ever eaten two Devil Fruits,
yet he seems to have
absorbed Whitebeard's.
[ELDER STAR B] The only ones
with the power to stop him
are other Emperors.
Actually, perhaps
Marco the Phoenix
and the other
Whitebeard survivors
have a small chance as well.
It's always the D's who
stir up the most trouble.
First Roger, then Portgas,
and now, with Monkey D. Luffy,
those names are
exposed to the public
far more than they should be.
[KONG]
I tried to talk him out of it,
but as far as we're concerned,
Garp is practically retired.
[KONG] Though he does
technically hold his title,
so he's still a Navy officer.
We need him to stay onboard
to train our young soldiers.
If you intend to resign from
your position as fleet admiral,
could you at least
do that for us as well,
Sengoku?
Yes, sir. I can
accept that offer.
It's not the worst way
to spend retired life.
[sighs]
[KONG] The two central
figures who have led the Navy
since Roger's era are
finally stepping down.
This will make
quite a splash I fear.
Needless to say,
you'll be missed.
Including the prisoners
that were set free
from the sixth level
of Impel Down,
there's still a mess of
dangerous pirates on the loose.
[SENGOKU]
Before his death,
Newgate was at
the top of the list.
[SENGOKU] The Great Pirate Era
is in a period of transition.
Old Navy officers shouldn't
keep clinging to power.
The basis for justice
changes from era to era.
It sounds like you're
ready to step down.
Oh, Kong, while I'm here,
I would like to recommend Aokiji
to take my place as
the next fleet admiral.
He'd do a fine job.
[sneezes]
[COBY panting]
[FISHBONEN]
They call this power "Haki."
[FISHBONEN] I'm certain
that's what you've got.
[FISHBONEN] Perhaps it
was awakened by the trauma
you experienced during the war.
Normally, the only way you
can obtain the power of Haki
is through vigorous training.
Haki? Are you sure, Doc?
You're pretty lucky, kid!
It's the same power
that the Navy vice admirals
have in their possession.
Really?
[COBY whimpers]
[MARINES chattering]
[COBY] I can feel all those
people echoing in my head.
I can't make it stop!
You two are apprentices
to Vice Admiral Garp, right?
Ask him about it.
Hey, Doctor!
You think I might
pick up some Haki, too?
I doubt it.
[HELMEPPO grunts]
[COBY chuckles]
It's not fair! Damn it!
We were partners
and all of a sudden
you're way cooler than me!
I don't know how
to feel about all this.
[COBY] But I do know
how I feel--weird!
It's like I'm a completely
different person!
But if this thing that
happened to me really is Haki,
I might be able to
use it to get stronger.
Much stronger than
I am right now.
Maybe even as strong as him,
for real this time.
I'm sorry, Admiral Aokiji!
We couldn't hold the fort!
--[AOKIJI] Huh?
--[MARINE B cries]
[AOKIJI]
Uh...
It's fine.
Huh?
[AOKIJI]
Alive after all.
Would you look at that!
You hear about Straw Hat
going back to Marineford?
Crazy kid.
Yeah.
The War of the Best is still
fresh in everyone's minds,
and now Straw Hat
rings the bell 16 times.
Is he trying to send some
kind of message or what?
[SMOKER]
Beats me.
Anyway, did you ask
them about my transfer?
Not yet, but I'll be sure
to bring it up with Sengoku
when I have the chance.
Are you serious about this?
Not really the sort of thing
somebody would make
a joke about, is it?
[AOKIJI]
No, especially not you,
but either way, people aren't
exactly clamoring to join G-5.
I'm sure you've
heard the stories.
It's not pretty.
So, transferring to the fifth
branch on the Grand Line, huh?
The New World. You realize
how wild things get over there.
[SMOKER] For me, it's better,
to be closer to my target.
[NARRATOR]
The news about Straw Hat Luffy
quickly spread through
countless waters.
[NARRATOR] Word even
spread to the New World.
Straw Hat Luffy.
Turns out the
punk is still alive!
"He rang the bell 16 times to
mark a new era in Marineford."
So, what the hell
is this Ox Bell thing?
[KILLER]
A relic, you might say.
It's a sacred bell
from the Ox Lloyd,
a Navy warship that was quite
impressive back in its day.
At year's end, they ring
the bell eight times to signify
the passing year,
then eight more times
as a sort of good omen
for the coming year.
So, that's the
meaning of 16 rings.
Some crusty old Navy custom.
Nothing special.
[KID]
Heh.
[KILLER] But since
the year hasn't ended yet,
maybe Straw Hat
did it to announce
the end and beginning
of a new pirate era.
He came outta
Marineford pretty cocky.
Whitebeard's era is over
and he's acting like he's
in charge of the next one.
Let the brat do what he wants.
Everyone knows his
brother's death hit him hard,
so he's gotta make
a good showing
before people
think he's washed up.
[KID chuckles]
He's gonna be a real
pain in the ass!
His bounty's through the roof
and it's only going up if he
keeps pulling stunts like this.
Well, that's his plan, I'm sure.
Too bad!
I'm gonna teach him the hard way
that he can't do whatever
he wants! Not here!
[KID]
The New World.
From how they talk place up,
I thought it'd be more fun.
Not full of cowards like you.
What's the big idea, huh?
Untie us right now! We didn't
cause you any harm, did we?
This place is a living hell,
we were trying to sail away!
Please let us go back
to Paradise alive!
Paradise, ah?
Do you mean your boring
home that's pirate-free?
You just got here,
so you don't know how
horrible this sea really is!
Free us and leave while you can!
Straw Hat, huh?
Yes, Faddah. He's cookin'
somethin' up again.
No need to bother
over that fool.
If he keeps playing
his cards so early,
he'll burn out before
the end of the game.
[rumbling]
--What is it?
--[FIRETANK PIRATES gasp]
Boss, come quick! It's the ship!
It's not in the water.
It's in the air!
[CAPONE]
What do ya mean?
What's goin' on?
How's this possible?
Control the ship, damn it!
Look, Faddah! Something
is coming down from the sky!
[gasps]
[FIRETANK PIRATES gasp]
[FIRETANK PIRATE A]
It's not comin' down.
We're goin' up!
[FIRETANK PIRATES screaming]
[HAWKINS]
Wait, who are you?
I'm sorry, could
you say that again?
I wasn't really
listening to you.
I'm Brownbeard!
There's a bounty of over
80,000,000 berries on my head!
Are you listening now?
This is my territory, so when
you hear my name, you bow!
You think you can sit your ass
on my men and get away with it?
You gotta pay for that
with your own blood!
[HAWKINS] I see. I thought
I had misheard you,
because it's such a stupid name.
I'll tell you two things.
Number one is I do not
appreciate your jokes.
Is that so?
[HAWKINS]
As for number two...
...I can see the shadow of death
crawling upon your face.
[gasps]
[BROWNBEARD PIRATES gasping]
[UROUGE]
And you're absolutely certain
that's the island the
Log Pose is pointing to?
Just look at it!
It's raining lightning!
This isn't going to work.
[FALLEN MONK PIRATES gasp]
Uhh...
How the hell do
we get to the shore?
[NARRATOR] There is
a realization that comes
to all men who set foot
in the New World.
[FALLEN MONK PIRATE A] High
Priest! Somebody is approaching!
[UROUGE]
Huh? Who goes there?
[NARRATOR] All their
struggles in the first half
of the Grand Line
suddenly seem petty.
Is that a young man
waiting to greet me?
What do you want
from us, old lady?
[NARRATOR]
Because compared to this,
those waters were like paradise.
Would you like an umbrella
for your journey?
[PIRATE A] I'm telling you,
if we stay here, we'll be dead!
Every last one of us!
Let us sail back to paradise!
I promise we won't get
in your way! I beg you!
Man, this guy's
a real wet blanket.
Didn't you choose
the life of a pirate?
If you're not prepared
to die for that...
[gasps]
...maybe you should've stayed
away from the New World!
[KID yells]
[screams]
[thud]
You wanna throw down
the gauntlet, Straw Hat,
that's fine!
But don't cry when I come for
you, 'cause it won't be pretty!
[KID cackles]
[NARRATOR] Luffy's latest
incident in Marineford
quickly becomes worldwide news.
Although his
exploit was a sucess,
it seems to cause little but
bewilderment to all who hear it.
His strange message
has met its target,
but will his friends understand
the next stage of his plan?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"With Hopes it Will
Reach My Friends!
Big News Spreading Fast!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!