Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece, the
legendary treasure left behind
by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR] While Buggy and Mr. 3
made their way up to Level 4
in an attempt to break out
of Impel Down,
Luffy, who had been poisoned
by Warden Magellan,
was injected with
a Healing Hormone from Ivankov,
which will cure him, but rob
him of ten years of his life.
[LUFFY]
Meat!
All better!
Let's go!
[LUFFY
"Luffy Back in Action!
Iva Begins the Breakout Plan!"
[gasping]
[sighs]
[ALL]
Whoa!
He absorbed all those calories!
You can't be human!
What the heck are you?
[PATRON A] Nobody survives
Magellan's poison!
This is straight up bonkers!
Just 20 hours and
he walked out on his own!
It's a miracle! It has to be!
Miracle? It's something
far greater than just that.
[CROWD laughing]
[LUFFY grunts]
[CROWD]
Straw Hat! Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
I'm so happy!
[LUFFY grunts]
It's Bon! Glad to see
you're alive!
What? Like I'd die!
Stop yanking my chain! You're
the one who made me worry!
[groans]
[LUFFY gasps]
Hey, Bon, what's wrong?
He didn't die just now, did you?
Say something! Hey!
Bon Boy's all worn out.
Better to let him rest.
Yo, 'sup Iva?
[CROWD]
Show some respect!
Thanks, buddy.
That did the trick.
Oh, and thanks
for helping out Bon, too.
Well, I do my best, but I'm not
the one you should be thanking.
Bon Boy worked hard for you.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Yes, I nudged you along
in the right direction,
and, yes, my powers
are certainly wonderful,
but this one's the hero.
Bon Boy stayed with you
all night long,
struggling and suffering
for hours and hours,
never relenting.
He lost his voice,
he could barely stand,
he even spewed blood,
but he never stopped.
He shouted, "Hang in there!"
and, "You have to live!"
again and again!
Your recovery was
far beyond miraculous.
I can only imagine that it's
thanks to all of his efforts.
[gasps]
I see.
[POINTY CHEEK PRISONER]
Wait a minute, is he--?
Naked?
[BON CLAY shivering]
Straw Boy, I've come here
to rescue you!
In the name of our
everlasting friendship!
[PRISONER A]
Who the hell is that?
He's covered in blood.
Before... I--
[LUFFY groaning]
I ran away!
Hey, pal, how do you know him?
[LUFFY groaning]
[BON CLAY]
He's my friend!
Straw Boy, I'm not
letting you die!
Thank you, Bon. You're awesome.
I owe you my life.
--[footsteps]
--[CROWD gasping]
I have your clothes,
but I'm afraid you're not ready
to up and leave just yet.
It will take several days
of rest and recuperation
before you're back
to your old self.
I don't have time for that!
I've already wasted too much!
Sorry to ask, but would you mind
looking after Bon for me?
I'll be back for him later.
[LUFFY groaning]
--[CROWD gasping]
--Be careful!
You see? Like he said,
you've got some healing to do.
[LUFFY groaning]
[gasps]
Looks like the paper's
still pointing down.
Ace is close.
By the way, where am I?
What's that thing?
It's a Vivre Card, I believe.
But, to answer your question,
you're on a floor
between Level 5 and 6.
I assume now you want
to go rescue your brother,
regardless of what advice
we might give you.
Well, it's your life, after all.
You can do whatever
you want with it.
[LUFFY] Are you gonna
make an escape too, Iva?
Before Bon and I
got all messed up,
he was plannin' on breaking
your butt outta here.
[CROWD]
Don't talk about his butt!
[LUFFY]
If you are gonna leave,
can you show me where
Ace is on your way out?
Wait, what did you say?
Bon Boy sought out
yours truly to help rescue me?
Huh. Wow.
How charming of him.
And a sweet gesture, indeed.
But, alas, I have
no need to be saved.
Heh. It is not my time
to break out just yet!
[LUFFY gasps]
I know what's going on
in the world right now.
There's been a shift in the tide
and big changes are coming.
The Navy and the Whitebeard
Pirates are taking center stage.
Even so, the "big man's"
still waiting things out.
I'm of course referring
to my comrade,
the leader of all
revolutionaries in the world.
[LUFFY gasps]
You may know him as Dragon!
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
Yes, that's the plan.
When your dad makes a move
with that army of his,
then I shall do some
maneuvering of my own.
Call it my grand comeback tour.
If I were to escape
from this place now,
I'd just end up on
a sea of wanted lists.
Hm?
D-D-D-D--!
"Dad"?!
[ALL]
Dragon's your dad?!
[IVANKOV]
What?!
[IVANKOV groaning]
Your dear papa...
and I never knew!
Goodness!
D-D-D-Don't be ridiculous!
Dragon doesn't have
any children!
That's just crazy talk!
Huhh. Maybe I shouldn't
have said anything.
Ah, whatever.
Grandpa didn't keep it a secret.
[GARP]
The name of your father
is Monkey D. Dragon,
the revolutionary.
I don't really know
that much about him.
I've never even seen
his face before.
What?!
[IVANKOV]
But wait, this might be legit!
He doesn't come across as the
kind of person who would lie,
and he is a rather impressive
pirate, in his own way.
Plus, the vitality he's shown
is the stuff of legends.
An extraordinary father
and an extraordinary son!
Please, tell me,
where did you come from?
Huh? The East Blue.
[IVANKOV gasps]
Say, Dragon.
[DRAGON]
Hm?
When you step out for air,
you always seem to face
in the same direction,
no matter where we go.
Do I?
Huh, I suppose I never
gave it much thought.
Bit strange that you would
bring it up, isn't it?
Well, I wondered if it was
some sort of homing instinct.
You know, the same
thing animals have.
Thinking of home? Perhaps some
family in the east. Maybe?
That's enough. Don't stick
your nose in my past.
[IVANOV]
Ha-ha. As you wish.
[IVANKOV]
Hang on. Oh, no!
If Straw Hat Boy
really is Dragon's son,
this could be a disaster!
Inazuma, check to see when
they're taking Ace Boy away!
Yes, of course.
There isn't much time.
The Vivre Card
was pointing down,
which means he's still here
and still alive, thank goodness.
Get me that info
as soon as possible.
I'm heading to Level 6
with Straw Hat Boy right now.
Yeah? You're really
gonna show me the way?!
Hey, wait, you just said
Level 6. I thought Ace was on 5.
Actually, you're already
below Level 5.
Okay, whatever.
All right! Let's go!
[IVANKOV]
I wasn't paying attention.
It didn't occur to me before!
If Straw Hat Boy is
Dragon's son as he claims,
then that means so is Ace!
Is this why the Navy captured
him and planned his execution?
But that's ludicrous!
Not to mention suicidal!
There's no way
they'd pick a fight
with Whitebeard and
Dragon at the same time!
What does the World Government
hope to gain from all this?!
[IVANKOV] In any case, I have
no choice but to make my move!
Bon, rest. I'll be
back later, okay?
[IVANKOV]
Straw Hat Boy!
Listen closely. You need
to keep that a secret.
Do not let people know
that Dragon's your father.
Yeah, I just figured that out.
I'm his dear friend,
as well as one of his
trusted commanders.
That means I'm a revolutionary.
That's the reason
I was arrested.
So, it's my duty to help you,
whether you like it or not!
I can't just stand around
and let my friend's son
die before my eyes!
Listen up! Tell everyone
in the New Kama Land!
We're going to move fast
and rescue Ace Boy
before his execution.
And then, we'll
break out of Impel Down!
Does everyone understand?
--[CROWD gasping]
--It's so sudden!
I don't know if I'm ready!
[CROWD chatter]
[CROWD gasps]
[IVANKOV] A crossroad in life
comes without warning!
If you're prepared to fight,
then be prepared to die!
Get ready for action
and wait for our return!
[CROWD murmuring]
[PATRON G]
All right then! Let's do it!
[PATRON H] I'll follow you
wherever you lead, Iva!
[PATRON I]
This is a new beginning
for the people of New Kama Land!
[CROWD cheering]
All right! I'm coming to
save you, Ace! Now, let's go...
[CROWD gasping]
[ALL gasping]
[CROWD yelping]
[crying]
[CROWD gasping]
His pulse is--
[CROWD]
What?! What is it?! Tell us!
His pulse is--
[CROWD gasping]
Just fine.
[CROWD]
That's not funny!
But the treatment
he went through
to cure Magellan's poison
was harsh and
shortened his lifespan.
It's only natural he's still
an eensy bit pooped.
[IVANKOV]
Emporio Energy Hormone!
[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY grunting]
It's a matter of adrenaline.
I just injected you with
enough of it for a full day.
[LUFFY growling]
[yelling]
Just to let you know,
you're gonna feel the side
effects several days from now,
but, by that point, let's hope
it won't really matter.
[yelling]
[HANNYABAL sighs]
Vice Warden, Warden Magellan
won't be pleased
if he hears you've been
sitting in his chair.
And don't think we won't
mention it in our reports.
You guys are mean,
you know that?
[HANNYABAL groans]
Mr. 2, Mr. 3, and
Buggy the Clown.
Mr. 2 just waltzed them
into the Freezing Hell
and that was the last
you saw of them?
[GUARD A]
Yes, that's right.
His disguise was perfect, sir.
We searched for them,
but all we could find
was that headdress
covered in blood.
From the lack of remains,
we assume that they took
Straw Hat out of the cell,
but were eaten up
by the wolves afterward.
[sighs] I see.
Look at me, sitting in
the warden's chair,
wearing his special
order headpiece thing
and yet I feel so empty.
You know why?
'Cause I haven't earned it
until I've crushed Magellan.
Right, good luck with that.
And let me remind you, if we
get tricked or beaten again,
not only the warden's job, but
your job will be on the line.
[yelping]
My position, too?
[BOTH]
Yeah, of course!
Surely the staircase to Level 3
is somewhere close by!
[laughing] Level 4 is
a lot easier this time!
I haven't seen a single jailer!
They must be busy
somewhere else!
[laughs] It's like a victory
lap! Let's pick it up, partner!
I said pick it up, not stop!
Just hold on a minute.
[BUGGY]
Huh?
[MR. 3] It's a Surveillance
Transponder Snail. Be careful.
If it notices us, all of our
efforts will have been in vain!
Good eyes, partner, nice find!
[MR. 3] We'll just have to be
extra sneaky from here on!
[BUGGY chuckles]
[BUGGY choking]
[BUGGY yelps]
[BUGGY]
What is this stuff?
[MR. 3] M-My eyes
are itching like crazy.
This-This must be
Magellan's work.
[BUGGY]
Huh?
[MR. 3] That poison he used
when he was fighting Straw Hat
is still floating around
in the air here.
[BOTH groaning]
[BOTH sneeze]
[BUGGY]
Oh, crap!
[MR. 3] The guards will
see us for sure now.
[BUGGY] We're right
in ihis line of sight!
[BOTH sigh]
[BOTH]
That was a close one.
[BOTH sneeze]
You're late, sir.
[MAGELLAN sighs]
And you're strict, Domino.
Try to empty your bowels
faster next time.
Not possible.
[stomach grumbles]
[groaning] Not again!
You'll have to hold it in.
I can't!
We need to be at the
front gate at 9 AM sharp
to officially transfer
the prisoner.
That is the mission
placed before us.
If we don't make it in time,
we'll ruin the reputation
of Impel Down.
[groans]
All right, listen up.
Our mission is to take custody
of Portgas D. Ace,
and then transfer him to the
Marineford Navy Headquarters.
Got it?
Until the moment that we
hand over that prisoner,
I need each and every
one of you on full alert!
[MARINES]
Yes, sir!
[ONIGUMO] So that we're ready
for any possibility,
we're moving him
in a convoy of five ships
under the direction
of five Vice Admirals.
We cannot afford a single
slip up! Understood?
[MARINES]
Sir!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY] I don't know why,
but I got a crap ton of energy!
Good, you're going to need it.
We can't afford
to waste even a second.
There's no security here,
so flex those leg muscles
and run like crazy,
Straw Hat Boy!
Nothing can stop us! Go!
[LUFFY yelling]
[growls]
Hey, what's going on over there?
[PRISONER B]
Huh?
[PRISONER A]
Who are those weirdos?
Ivankov? No way!
I thought he was dead!
No, it can't be!
[ARMY WOLVES growling]
[LUFFY]
Outta my way!
No time for you!
[ARMY WOLVES whining]
[IVANKOV]
Death Wink!
[ARMY WOLVES whining]
Inazuma, open it up!
[INAZUMA]
Right!
They'll be monitoring us
from now on.
Who cares? Let 'em come!
[alarm]
[GUARD C]
We have intruders!
[GUARDS yelping]
[GUARD C] They're running
down the staircase
between Level 5 and 6!
Wait, the guy with the big head!
He's that "Queen of the Queers"
that went missing years ago!
Name's Ivankov.
[GUARDS gasping]
[GUARD C]
Where's he been hiding?
We gave up on that guy ages ago!
[GUARD D] The one running next
to him is Straw Hat Luffy.
I thought the warden
took care of him,
but he looks as healthy as ever.
[GUARD C] The third one is
another missing prisoner!
Inazuma! A revolutionary
from the South Blue!
What the hell is goin' on?
[GUARD F] Looks like they're
heading straight for Level 6!
[GUARD G] I think they're trying
to save "Fire Fist" Ace!
Domino and Warden Magellan
are also on their way
to Level 6 for the
transfer as we speak.
They're all gonna
bump into each other!
How can they all still be alive?
[GUARD C] Vice Warden,
when'd you get here?
[growls] Activate the
passageway traps immediately.
Call all the jailers on Level 6.
Tell them to get ready.
They'll need to stand their
ground until Mistress Sadie
and the Demon Guards arrive
as reinforcements.
Report everything
that's going on
to all floors and
Warden Magellan.
[HANNYABAL] You have
your orders! Get moving!
[GUARDS]
Right! Yes, sir!
[GUARD C] I've never seen the
Vice Warden so serious before!
Maybe it's the imposter again.
We have to stop
these troublemakers.
Since I can't blame
the warden for this one, I mean.
[GUARD C]
Uhh! Nope! He's the real deal.
We can make it! We can make it!
[GUARDS panting]
--[LUFFY grunts]
--[GUARDS yelping]
Hang on, Ace!
I'm comin' for you!
[MAGELLAN]
This is it, Portgas D. Ace.
You're going to be
transferred to Marineford.
Upon your arrival there,
you will be taken
to the execution grounds.
[NARRATOR] "The public
execution of Ace is in...
...6 hours."
[NARRATOR] Luffy finally reaches
the lowest level of Imepl Down,
the legendary Level 6.
Unfortunately, he finds
that his brother
has already been taken away.
Desperate to catch Ace
before he leaves the prison,
Luffy makes chase,
but is stopped dead in his
tracks by Hannyabal's trap.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Ace's Convoy Begins.
Battle on the Lowest
Floor, Level 6!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!