I don't know why
you're doing this.
I told you very clearly
that I wouldn't see you again.
I said I would never
return to the Straw Hats!
You think they'd
be happy to go on,
knowing that one
of their friends
had thrown her
life away for them?
Now that they know why you left,
they'll follow you to the
depths of hell if they have to
and they'll bust every skull
they can on the way there!
How many times do
I have to tell you this?!
Even if you think you can save
me, I don't want your help!
Don't you care how I feel?!
Hey, keep it down in there, you!
Now Ramen Kenpo!
Noodle Nail Knockout!
Epluchage!
Convert!
No way, that's ridiculous!
Franky Centaur Mode!
It's backwards!
Your head's supposed to be
in the front, not your crotch!
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
...Rashomon!
We're not done yet.
What the hell is that?!
It's a Sea King!
There's someone
waiting on this railway.
Someone who can
cut Sea Kings in half.
Everyone get back to
the front cars right now!
This is a trap!
What the?!
How foolish to fall
for the enemy's scheme!
No!
How shameful!
Have a safe trip, gentlemen!
Say hello to the
Sea Kings for me!
I must catch the train.
I must rectify my mistake
and capture the prisoners
before their evil is once
again set upon this world!
I cannot allow
the blood and tears
of innocent
civilians to be shed!
I'll show them that
there's justice yet
in this cruel and
unforgiving world!
I don't care if my body
is torn to shreds
by these raging waves.
I swear!
No matter the cost,
I'll protect the future of
law-abiding citizens everywhere!
Huh?
No, it can't be!
It seems there's
another sea train!
I see someone.
What the?
Hey, there's a guy out there!
It's the Ship-Slasher!
That's not good!
Ship what?
They call him
"Ship-Slasher" T-Bone.
He's from the Navy.
His sword cuts
through pirate ships
like a knife cuts
through a steak!
Whoa!
That sounds awesome.
Maybe it'd be awesome if it
was somebody else's problem!
All right men, let's go!
We only get one shot!
Set your sights on T-Bone!
You ready?
Yeah!
Hold on!
Huh?
What?!
We don't have time to hold on--
he's gonna cut
Rocketman in half!
Jeez, there's
nothing to worry about!
Zoro's got this.
Just watch!
I'm only gonna tell
you this one time!
Get the hell out of the way!
There's no other track.
I'm sure they passed
by my men on the way here.
What did those
monsters do to them?!
They must be
Nico Robin's crewmates.
In that case, that swordsman
is the pirate hunter!
Those who defile this path
of justice will face my wrath!
I am a proud
Captain of the Navy!
I shall not let you pass!
Be it wood or steel,
I'll slash your ship in two!
Good luck with that one.
We won't stop 'til
we reach our goal.
And I'll cut down
anything in our way!
This guy is fierce.
En garde!
I hate crooked swordplay.
Right Angle Flying Bird.
Three-Sword Style Bull Demon!
Bone Phoenix!
He cut right through it!
Bold Hooves!
No way!
He beat T-Bone!
He must've come from
one of the loose cars.
Gotta hand it to him.
It takes a lot of guts to
keep going in a storm like this.
But still that's not
enough to stop us.
I'm sure the burden
of justice is a heavy one
but we've got a
few burdens of our own.
Hurry! Hurry!!
Captain T-Bone is out here!
He needs our help!
What if he already got
hit by that sea train?
Hey, don't even joke
about something like that,
you bastard--our
captain would cut
that crappy train in
two and you know it!
But that pirate hunter guy
from the Straw Hats is scary!
Full speed ahead, men!
We owe Captain T-Bone our lives
after he protected us
from that giant Sea King!
We have to save him!
Yeah!
Roronoa Zoro.
How vexing.
You think it was Sanji?
Of course!
How else do you think those
train cars got detached?
Good strategy, huh?
So you think
we'll catch up soon?
Seems like it.
Yeah!
I'm ready for a fight!
Go, Rocketman!
We're gonna beat up
that pigeon guy!
That was close.
I can't believe our
plan actually worked.
No it's not just my imagination.
That's right!
I know this smell!
This is the stench of filthy
pirates if I ever smelled it!
Something's
definitely wrong here.
Yeeek!
Is something wrong?
What?!
He's coming back?!
Why?!
You... You cut me!
Huh? You didn't cut me?
Sure peeling onions
may not be glamorous,
but you have to put love into
every aspect of your cooking.
Kitchen knives aren't
for cutting people.
You don't treat
them like swords.
However, they did a fine job
of cutting down that armor.
Kitchen Knife Throw!
Punk!
Oeil!
My eyes! They're caving in!
Let 'em.
Now, shut your
mouth and give up.
Yeah, you wish!
I don't get it.
Why do you want to
save that terrible woman
so much in the first place?!
Or maybe Nico Robin's
got you all fooled.
You want me to tell
you the truth, huh?
Think you can take it?
Nez!
Joue!
Bouche!
Dents!
Menton!!
If you keep talking like that,
I'm gonna re-arrange your face.
Hold on a sec.
Anything but the face!
Cut it out!
Everyone knows she's bad news.
It's no secret!
She's evil!
A monster!
Better off dead!
Parage Shot!
Damn it, I think
my face caved in!
I need a mirror.
How could you?!
You fiend!
You ruined my beautiful eyes
and my fabulous teeth!
Too bad!
You're the devil, aren't you?!
Hey, your face went back!
You're right!
Look!
My inner beauty is shining!
It was but a fleeting illusion.
You're guilty of three sins.
Let me list them.
First off, you dared to call
yourself a chef in front of me.
Second, you were
disrespectful to your food.
And third, you
insulted my friend.
For that, you'll pay.
Hiss!
You put on a big show, but
you're all bark and no bite!
Whether you've got
two legs or four,
you still seem pretty
useless to me, centaur.
Ah! No!
Lookin' pretty pathetic, buddy.
Shut up!
Shall I give you a hand?
No, no, no!
Don't you dare!
Just kidding!
Give me a hand?
You oughta be
ashamed of yourself,
using a line like that!
And what was that about
four legs being useless?
I just needed to catch you!
You can't run now!
I hate you, you jerk!
I just want to be me!!
Give me my individuality back!
Right on the other side
of that door behind you,
my friend is waiting
to be rescued.
In other words,
get out of the way.
When I say no, I mean no!
Ramen Kenpo Secret
Move Poison Pasta Cutter!
Touch it and die!
Go, go, go, go, go!
You people are pathetic!
Nico Robin has you eating
right out of her hand!
She's betrayed every
person she's ever met,
and you're here risking
your life to save her?
You're beyond help!
It's time to die!
Three-Spot Decoupage.
Hiss! I didn't think
you'd use such a dumb trick!
I let my guard down!
Right!
Oh, yeah, cause I'm
the dumb one here.
Instead of making excuses
why don't you tell me
what you want written on
your gravestone, brother.
Oh, I get it.
You don't think this
fight is over yet, do you?
What?
Since you dodged all
my punches so far,
I can't really blame you.
You have no clue
how hard I can hit.
It's gonna be a nasty surprise!
Here's my Ultimate Hammer!
Wow, some entrance.
What the hell have
you been doing?
Ow!
Well as per usual, I've been
kicking ass and what about you?
Been kicking ass.
So it's you, huh?
You're the bastards
who kidnapped Robin.
Robin, my sweet,
how I've missed you!
Let's go back together, okay?
Forgive me for intruding Sanji,
but I think the lady
objects to your plan.
Robin, why?!
Worry not, I know
just what to do!
Believe in my strength, friend!
On the next One Piece:
"Scramble over Robin!
A Cunning Plan by Sniper King!!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!