[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[LUFFY]
Hey! Fortress Guy!
My crew.
I rescued 'em.
[USOPP]
Run!
[LUFFY laughing]
[UNIT 55 CAPTAIN] ♪ We're
55, and you better fear it! ♪
[UNIT 55 GUYS]
♪ We're 55! ♪
[UNIT 55 GUYS shouting]
[UNIT 55 GUYS groaning]
[USOPP yelling]
[LUFFY]
Bazooka!
[DRAKE]
We're in place at Dock 88
and ready to carry out
the capture operation!
We're ready for those
lousy Straw Hats, sir!
Remember, these
pirates are crafty.
[CHOPPER] Think that's where
Luffy and the others are headed?
[NAMI]
We've got no way of knowing,
but I'd say it's a good bet.
Dock 88 it is!
Lead on!
[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY]
"Breaking Through the Siege!
The Going Merry is Recovered!"
[STRAW HATS panting]
I'm gonna rip your nose off
if you sent us in
the wrong direction.
Don't worry! We're definitely
headed the right way!
Just keep moving!
Hurry!
Yeah, yeah!
I recognize that wall!
Merry's dock is just
around the corner!
[ZORO]
Something's wrong.
This is way too easy.
[LUFFY]
All right, everybody stay alert!
No one's gonna stop us from
stealing our ship--!
[LUFFY gasps]
We're busted.
I knew it was an ambush!
[DRAKE]
Sniper Team 7, to the front!
Shooters take aim!
No. Don't aim!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
[DRAKE]
Fire!
[LUFFY]
...Balloon!
[USOPP groans]
[SANJI, ZORO]
What the hell are you doing?
Cannon Team 12, to the front!
Great. Bazookas!
Fire!
[LUFFY]
Duds?
[LUFFY shrieks]
[SANJI coughing]
[SANJI]
Ah, my eyes! What is this?
The burning, oh, the burning!
[USOPP]
Those were flash bombs!
Sword Unit, to the front!
Attack!
[coughing]
[SANJI grunts]
Bastards!
[MARINE C shouts]
[USOPP grunts]
No worries!
Wow. Nice equipment
you got there.
You can borrow these!
Thanks.
[ZORO]
Dragon...
...Twister!
Blinders doesn't work on me
unlike a certain
love sick moron.
[SANJI growls]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
[LUFFY]
And... Whip!
[ALL groaning]
He, he, now that was fun!
Huh, where are the guys?
You whipped 'em along
with everyone else!
--[LUFFY] Sorry.
--You, think next time!
All right, you dimwitted moron!
What'd you say to me?
[ZORO growls]
[BOTH yelling]
In case you two forgot,
there's still an army here.
Fire!
--[shouts]
--[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY groaning]
Luffy!
[DRAKE]
Stay right where you are!
[gasps]
[DRAKE] It says "dead or alive"
on your wanted posters.
Here at G8, we lean
towards "alive."
However, if you insist
on meeting us with
further resistance, I'll be
forced to amend that policy.
[USOPP]
Luffy, you've gotta try harder!
We're in real trouble here.
[LUFFY groaning]
I'm trying but it's no use.
It won't budge,
and I'm all worn out.
Sea Prism Stone?
[DRAKE]
Precisely!
A specially designed
Prison Net Bomb.
So, Straw Hat.
What do you think?
How'd I know he'd be here?
[MARINE H]
What're you doing?
This isn't a drill!
Get to your station!
Ah, blow it out your rifle!
[USOPP]
Not good!
Look at this!
There's a sea of them left,
after all the ones we took out!
Make this easy and give up.
Escaping here alive
is impossible!
[DRAKE]
Positions!
Damn, we've got no choice!
Attack!
[KOBATO, NAMI yelling]
[USOPP screams]
What the hell?
Wha--? Usopp?
[USOPP]
Somebody, call a doctor.
Usopp!
Look what they've done to him!
He's injured!
He could die, people!
It's all because of
those soldiers!
[SANJI, ZORO]
Settle down, Chopper.
Huh? Kobato?
Lieutenant Commander?
Identify yourself!
[screaming]
What's the matter with you?
We've been taken hostage!
We're gonna die!
Huh?
Please save us!
It wasn't our fault!
We were forced here
against our will!
Kobato?
[NAMI screams] This giant
is one of the pirates!
[KOBATO, NAMI screaming]
[ZORO]
Did I miss something?
[SANJI]
Uh, who's that other girl?
[ZORO]
How should I know?
[CHOPPER]
Stop it! Stop yelling!
We can't afford
to go in blasting.
Not with the hostages there!
Curse those cowardly vermin!
This is precisely
why I hate pirates!
Sir, this means that giant
beast must be the fake doctor!
He has to be! Look,
he's carrying his crewmate!
[CHOPPER growls]
That's right!
I'm a rough and tough
member of the Straw Hats!
Crying babies even
shut their traps
when they get a load of me!
Better do exactly as I say,
or these hostages are dead!
[KOBATO, NAMI scream]
All right!
Order your buffoons to stand
down and let us board our ship!
[DRAKE grunts]
Now I get it.
Interesting.
Do it!
Double-time, or I'll snap
these girls' necks like twigs!
And their blood'll
be on your hands!
I'd do as he says, guys.
He's serious. If you haven't
seen the neck snap thing,
it's pretty messy.
[grumbles]
How would it look if you,
the righteous arm of justice,
let two women die?
Chopper!
What are you doing?
That's not helping.
Plug it, you idiot!
[grumbling]
[yelling]
He's gonna kill us!
Please, do what he says!
I can't die
before I get married!
[DRAKE groans]
No, no!
Faster!
How many times do I
have to go over this?
We have 1,000 mouths to feed!
Speed is of the essence!
Pick it up, or pack it up!
You didn't need to hit us.
Oh, really? So you
have a grievance?
Because let me be clear.
First, you two muttons need
to prove yourselves worthy
of being in this kitchen!
Now get over here and peel
the potatoes! All 3,000!
Is it just me, or is
Jessica a little tense?
She's having trouble
coming to terms with the fact
that our star cook
turned out to be a pirate.
And the fact that the
real new guys are nothing
but incompetent losers.
Another word and I'll
boil your tongues!
[BOTH]
Yes, ma'am!
Hey, Billy.
Why don't ya do me a favor and
try out the special sauce!
Pretty amazing stuff, eh?
--Well?
--It tastes good.
Honestly, it does.
Not to be a jerk,
but isn't that our House sauce?
Precisely. Yeah!
Ya know what? That pirate
may have lied about his name,
but there's absolutely no
questioning his culinary skills.
I mean, we are good cooks,
but he had real flair.
He did have flair,
that's for sure.
A shame...
[SHINPACHI] Damn it!
What did he do different?
[VICE HEAD CHEF]
Jessica?
[JESSICA]
Hm... Yes, what?
Perhaps this could
be of some use.
It seems he left some
detailed notes and
recipes for various
dishes he prepared.
--That pirate left us what?
--You said, full recipes?
Ah! Yeah, come to think of it...
Hey, thank you. I'll be sure to
write down some of my recipes.
What makes you think I care?
Uh, I, um, I was hoping that...
Well, since he did leave it,
what would be the
harm in using a few?
Idiot! Give me that!
Utterly pathetic, all of you!
And you dare stand
there and call
yourselves loyal to Navarone?
If you accept this pirate's
help, if you use one note
on this page, then you
betray our heritage!
Sorry...
Forgive us, madame.
It's just that...
[JESSICA growls]
[JESSICA]
What the hell is this?
Can't you fools even handle
a simple task like
peeling potatoes?!
Uh, well, our men did it.
Exactly, they always
turn out that--
Listen! This kitchen
is a battlefield!
In case you hadn't noticed,
we don't have any food to waste!
Every single scrap is
a vital resource!
Are you okay?
[JESSICA] Silence! Report to
dishwashing duty immediately!
[clanging]
[CHOPPER yells]
[KOBATO, NAMI screaming]
[DRAKE growling]
Um, Commander?
Fine. You win.
Lower your weapons and withdraw!
Stand down, now!
I said withdraw!
Please, sir!
We can't risk it.
[SANJI]
Wow. They actually complied.
[ZORO]
Let's hope so.
[LUFFY]
Thanks, Zoro. I owe you one.
Hey, guys! Call me nuts,
I swear I just
heard Kobato's voice!
Yeah, man, I heard her, too!
Mechao!
What's going on up there?
[MECHAO]
Kobato's being held hostage.
[MAINTENANCE GUY A screams]
Are you kidding me?
Oh, Mechao,
that's terrible news!
[MECHAO] Eh, there's
nothing to worry about.
I can tell when my
daughter's really upset!
What makes me nervous...
[MECHAO] ...is all those
sword-wielding grunts.
We have complied
with your demands.
Now, release the hostages!
It worked! We did it!
Chopper! Speak!
Listen! You don't
give the orders here!
These women will be released,
only after we've escaped!
You spineless...!
It's done, sir.
Unit 17 is on standby
and awaiting orders.
Good, stay alert and
wait for my signal.
We won't try to stop you!
You're free to go!
Very accommodating.
But, is it true?
[LUFFY groans]
Hey, would you hold it together?
[ZORO]
Nami. Chopper. Lover Boy.
Run to the ship on my signal.
Luffy, I need your help
to get us out of this.
You've gotta stretch your arms
and get everyone on board.
Okay.
I get it.
[MARINE I]
Lieutenent Commander?
[DRAKE]
Easy, soldier.
The situation is dire.
If it doesn't work, the
responsibility is mine alone.
[MECHAO grunting]
[DRAKE grunts]
[MARINE L]
Whoops, how clumsy of me.
Pay attention!
You scared us half to death!
[KOBATO grunts]
[NAMI gasps, yells]
Stupid girl! What'd you do?!
Crap! Nami!
Make a run for the ship!
You're on, Captain!
[LUFFY groans]
Fall in, men!
Bring me those pirates!
I knew he'd try something!
--[MARINES yelling]
--Come on this is it!
[LUFFY groans]
[SANJI, CHOPPER, NAMI screaming]
[ALL]
Huh?
[MECHAO]
Go, kid!
[LUFFY]
Okay, all aboard!
[SANJI grunts]
[CHOPPER, NAMI, SANJI screaming]
Are they still alive?
Good question. Let's find out!
[ZORO yelps]
[LUFFY laughs]
Don't let them escape!
All units, open fire!
[MARINE Q] Sir, they're
still holding a hostage!
[DRAKE]
Warning shots!
[LUFFY laughs]
It worked! We did it!
You'll have to
forgive me, Captain,
my gratitude's lacking now.
Give a girl some
warning next time, huh!
All right, everyone! Look alive!
[siren blaring]
[CANNONEER A] Straight ahead!
Isn't that the pirate ship?
[CANNONEER B] Yeah, and we've
got her dead in our sights!
Why won't they give
the order to attack?
[CANNONEER A]
I hear they have a hostage.
Some nurse they captured.
Poor woman must be losing her
mind being handled
by such filth!
Pirates! I could sink
the whole lot of'em!
[CANNONEER B]
Think I've spotted her!
Yeah! The hostage is safe.
And givin' 'em orders?
What a fiasco!
Are the ships ready to launch?
[MARINE I]
Almost! A few minutes more!
[KOBATO]
Daddy!
[MECHAO]
Kobato!
Now this is how I like
to see my baby girl.
Safe and sound.
[KOBATO giggles]
[DRAKE] You released the
ship, didn't you, old man?
You've caused
a real mess this time!
And I can assure you,
you will be punished.
What father in his right mind
would sit idly by and watch
his daughter fall in
harm's way when he can stop it?
[DRAKE] A plan was underway!
Kobato had been rescued!
We had it under control!
And the other girl?
You completely
botched her rescue!
[DRAKE grunts]
[MECHAO] I wasn't willing
to risk my daughter
as collateral damage!
You could learn a thing or two
from Commander Jonathan!
[DRAKE grunts]
Sir, I have some more
information about the hostage!
Intel suggests the hostage
may actually be a crewmember
of the Straw Hat Pirates!
She's what?
[MARINE M]
Halt, inspector.
What's your destination?
I'm under orders to
investigate all passersby.
I don't believe that I'm
required to report my actions.
[MARINE M]
Yes, but we are.
Fine.
Tell the commander
I had fun playing him.
[gasps]
He was an easy mark. Heh.
[MARINE M]
Screw you!
[MARINE M gasps]
[ROBIN]
I guess I won't be needing
this disguise any longer.
[ZORO] Why are we hugging
the edge of this cliff?
[NAMI]
Protection!
We'd have cannons
blasting us from
both sides if we went
through the middle!
[USOPP gasping]
Where am I?
[LUFFY]
Oh, he's awake!
[USOPP]
This is Merry.
How did we get back?
[LUFFY] With a hostage
and a quick flight!
[USOPP]
I see! Nami was the hostage!
Nice touch!
[NAMI]
Wasn't it, though?
[USOPP] You are good
at tricking people.
[thud]
[ZORO] Still, Nami
didn't make the ship start
moving on its own.
How'd that happen?
[USOPP]
If I had to guess, I'd say
it was the old maintenance guy.
--[ZORO] Why's that?
--[USOPP] Just a feeling.
[SNAIL PHONE ringing]
Nami dressed as a
nurse is pure magic!
Well we escaped, but what good
are we without maps or charts?
We were way better off
with you guys in jail!
What'll we do now?
[SANJI laughs]
Robin!
[SANJI]
Now there's a girl with style!
[JONATHAN]
Major Shepherd was a fake?
Where is she now?
[MARINE P]
I'm sorry, sir.
She got away.
You're not at
fault here, soldier.
I have a habit of letting my
guard down around pretty women.
[MARINE P]
Sir?
Anyway, this makes a total
of six accomplices.
We're currently searching
for the last one!
No need.
You can stop looking.
I've located her.
[MARINE P]
Sir?
I called the medical station.
They said their nursing staff
has all been accounted for.
[NAMI]
A map of the fortress!
I thought you might
find it useful.
It's amazing!
Wow, you just gave us
a way to escape here!
Good...
[cannon fire]
[LUFFY]
They're shooting at us!
I thought they weren't
gonna attack us
because we had a hostage?
We knew it was only
gonna be a matter of time!
Did we also realize they'd
send warships after us?
[DRAKE]
There is no hostage on board!
Open fire! I repeat!
All cannons are free
to fire at will!
[NAMI]
Look! There's our exit.
The Sea Gate.
Usopp! Prepare the bow cannon!
Chopper! Make extra certain
you follow my orders!
No problem!
This is the base's only way out!
We'll have to break
through that gate!
But these shoal markings
can't be right!
The water's just
way too shallow.
So why put a port here?
It's wrong!
Something doesn't make sense.
[JONATHAN]
I see.
It's all-clear on
your end? That's good.
Keep watch and don't fire
until I give the order.
Priority report, sir.
We have confirmation
that the pirate ship
has reached the Sea Gate.
[JONATHAN]
Checkmate.
Your time's up, Straw Hat.
And, inevitably...
...you will lose.
[NAMI] Are you kidding me? We
don't have a single cannonball?
Not a one!
No explosives of any kind.
Not even the boxes they came in!
Well, that's hardly surprising,
given that they
confiscated the Going Merry.
What'll we do?
We can't bust through that gate
without some serious firepower!
[ZORO] We can, but we have
to be smart about it.
All we gotta do is gain
control of that gatehouse.
[USOPP] Don't talk
like it's gonna be easy!
[LUFFY] It is!
'Cause I have a great idea!
[CANNONEER CAPTAIN]
Get ready!
Lock on target!
Attack!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Balloon!
[LUFFY grunts]
It worked!
That's one way to do it!
Good job, Luffy!
Now let's sail outta here!
[NAMI] Wait, if they took
all the cannonballs--
[gasps]
[NAMI screams]
[USOPP]
What's wrong?
Nami?
We've been had!
My treasure!
A future lies before us
waiting to begin
Let's take to the wind!
and search the world for answers
to all the questions
in our minds
Exploring day and night we'll...
...live out our
dreams in paradise!
And that's why...
We're running, and running,
traveling along an open road
Never letting go of
what we came to do
We're here to see this through!
We can't lose, can't lose,
nothing on earth
can stop us now
'Cause we're not afraid
of our own destiny
We Dream and live
our lives free!
[DRAKE] Where'd you disappear
to, you damn pirates?
It's impossible to sneak
past the cannoneers
and vanish in that short a time!
[JONATHAN] I know for certain
they won't try to escape.
[NAMI] Without the gold,
there's no point!
I mean, whoever heard of pirates
leaving treasure behind?!
It's shameful!
Right rudder, full!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Pirate Ship Disappears!
Fortress Battle, Round #2"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!