Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Hey, Robin! We'll save you!
No matter what!
Look! The drawbridge
is lowering!
Robin. It must have
been hard for you.
But you're not alone
anymore. You have us now!
Never in a million years
would Nami kill Usopp!
She wouldn't do
that to her friends!
What was that
about friends, Luffy?
Nami!
What are you doing here?
What are we doing here?
You're our friend!
We came to get you.
What a pest.
Nami?
Friends huh?
Don't make me laugh.
You're just pathetic enough
to deserve each other.
Geez Nami.
You sure know how
to trash a place.
Hey. What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just
resting a little. That's all.
You mean to tell me that
pouring over a treasure map,
after wrecking a
house is how you relax?
You're not fooling me.
Now fess up already.
What's bothering you?
Something happened to
make me mad. It's nothing.
Those guys. Who are they?
You know?
Yeah. I met some Captain guy.
He seemed kind
of liar-ish though.
Nami. I heard you
smiled with them.
We both know
that's rare for you.
As a matter of fact, I haven't
seen you smile in years.
C'mon! Tell me
who these guys are!
It's okay. You can tell
me anything, remember?
I had planned to
forget about them.
I thought I could just
erase them from my mind.
Don't you have any honor?
Those men are your friends!
If it were possible,
I'd join up with those guys
and sail around the world.
Now I see.
Yeah, that would hit her hard.
To think that someone
actually showed up for her.
Friends.
That word means pain.
It breaks her heart.
What's wrong, little girl?
I bet it's the village.
You want it left alone?
Then how about this?
Let's make an agreement, okay?
An agreement?
That's right.
Gather up 100 million
berries, then bring it to me.
Do so and I will
let your village go,
in addition to giving
you your freedom.
Promise?
I promise. And I'm
the kind of fish-man
who would rather die than break
an agreement concerning money.
I don't even care
how long it takes you,
I will honor our agreement.
I'm going to save
100 million berries!
Arlong!
Ah. What seems to
be the problem,
O-skilled-surveyor of ours?
Why the sour face?
Those Marine maggots
you keep on the payroll
stole every last berry I had!
What happened to all
that crap about dying
before you'd ever break a
promise when it comes to money?
Bastard!
Refresh my memory.
Did I break a promise?
Don't play dumb with me!
I know that you teamed
up with the Marines to--!
Just when did I break that
promise? Speak up girl.
Damn you. Damn you! Damn you!
Too bad. All your
stolen money got stolen.
That certainly is unfortunate.
But a deal is a deal, Nami.
If you can't come up
with 100 million berries,
then both you and
your village stay
in my possession indefinitely.
Well, you know the terms. Hmm?
You pig!
It's only 100 million berries!
Start saving again and
you'll have it in no time!
Or, are you gonna run out on me?
Listen.
If you do that, I'll kill
everyone in that village.
Do you understand me?
Nami.
We agreed we would never
tell you that we knew.
If you thought all of us
were counting on you,
you would be
bound by guilt never
to leave his gang for
fear of letting us down.
We've had enough!
Take up arms!
It's time to fight!
We promised we wouldn't
live our lives in vain!
No matter the pain
or humiliation we
endured under Arlong,
we swore to fight the long fight
so Nami could
meet their demands!
But they lied!
They never intended to
keep their end of the deal.
Instead they stole our
only chance at freedom!
So now.
We should make
those filthy fishmen pay
for the years they manipulated
that kind young girl!
Am I right?
We were always ready
to fight those monsters!
Yeah!!
Everybody! Wait!
Nami!
Calm down!
It's not that much money!
I can make it back in no time!
I'll take care of it,
don't worry!
It'll be easy this time!
I'm used to it! I'll be fine!
Just relax! Everything is okay!
Hey. It's nothing
compared to back then.
It's okay! You don't
need to save me!
C'mon everyone!
I'm perfectly fine!
You've done enough.
You have to know
that there is no point now.
You struggled so hard,
carrying our lives on
your back this whole time.
I can only imagine that
joining them must have been
more painful than being
stabbed through the heart.
You fought very well.
Genzo.
Set yourself free
from this village.
Genzo!
Nami. Do it.
What? Nojiko!
Nami.
Go on.
You are an exceptional
young woman.
And you have a dream.
Everyone! Listen!
I won't let you go!
Just stay right there!
I'm not going to let anyone
else get hurt by them!
You'll all die.
We know that.
Nami. It's no use.
We've made up our minds!
Get out of the way!
Move out!
We may not win but
we will give 'em hell!
Yeah!!
Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong!
Luffy.
What do you want?
You don't know
anything about this.
You don't know what's been
happening on this island
for the past eight years.
Nope. I don't.
This has nothing to do with you!
I told you to leave this place.
Yep. You sure did.
So leave! I told you to leave!
Just get out of here!
Get out of here now!
Go! Go away! Go! Go! Go!
Luffy. Help me.
Of course I will!
You better keep
your hands off my hat.
Luffy.
Let's go.
Right!
What the--?
Now which one of you is Arlong?
There's nowhere else to run!
You and me. Here. In the
highest level of Arlong Park.
What is this room? Lotta paper.
This isn't just any room.
This is the room
where I make Nami
draw all of her
sea charts for me.
The map room!
This is Nami's room?
These sea charts--
--are what she's worked
on all these years.
She will continue drawing her
sea charts for my own ambitions!
And once her charts give
me full knowledge of all the
world's oceans, we fishmen
will be totally invincible!
And the world
shall kneel before us!
The first step is this island.
Then we'll move on to
the whole East Blue.
You could never use her like me!
She would be wasted on you!
Use her?
What is that?
A desk?
What do you think you're doing?
Whoa! What's goin' on?
Why's all that stuff
being thrown out of there?
Stop it now!
The charts!
My charts!
Wow. This fight is
so freakin' intense.
Yeah. A fight to the death.
Definitely.
Thank you.
Now you've gone too far!
You keep jabbering on about
how much better fishmen are,
and how much you
need those sea charts.
I don't understand
anything about that stuff,
but I finally figured out
how to save her!
This room isn't
anything but her jail cell.
There's only one way
for Nami to escape.
I've got to tear
this place apart!
Gum-Gum...
...Battle Axe!
It's gonna collapse!
Everybody run for cover!
Big Sis! We gotta go!
But Luffy's still inside!
Big Sis!
We can't! Luffy's still--!
Luffy!
Luffy.
We gotta know who won.
With all that debris.
Looks like--
Luffy.
It's Luffy!
Big Bro!
He's just standing there.
What's wrong?
Nami!
Nami! You'll always
be my friend!
Yeah.
Back then, I was saved
by my truest friends.
This time, I'll be right beside
them, fighting for you.
So please. Believe in us.
Believe in Luffy!
He'll be sure to answer you.
Hey! Straw Hats!
Why are you all
just standing around?
Hey. What's with
that devious chuckle?
Let's go!
Oh, dear!
I'm out of soy sauce!
And here I was planning
on making some delicious
soy sauce meat steak,
meat salad, and meat
miso soup today!
Hello? I'm coming in!
Hey, Zoroyama!
I'm completely out of soy sauce!
Would you be a dearie
and spare me some?
Whoa! You startled me!
Are you training or something?
Heavens no, I wasn't training!
I'm preparing!
We are having sashimi today.
So, I was cutting up fish.
And the whole kitchen
along with 'em!
Oh, yeah! The soy sauce!
Unfortunately. I'm out, as well.
Sliced it in two, did ya?
Stop it, ma'am!
You can't do that!
Oh, my word!
This ham is exquisite!
And this one with
the cheese wrapped
in ham is
simply to die for!
Now be a dear and
get me some jam!
Ma'am, I'm afraid
I can't do that!
And you can't bring rice
into the sampling section!
And why not, huh?
I see Luffizaki
doing it all the time!
She's always causing
us trouble here, too.
Can it, missie! Now bring me
some jam to put on this ham,
and make sure it's sweet
and tasty, ma'am! Got it?
It's that grabby
pervert, Sanjida!
Ladies! What's wrong?
It's just us girls here, right?
Hey, you! Come over here!
I wanna touch your butt!
Knock it off, you two!
Thank goodness!
It's the middle-aged woman of
once-a-month justice, Namijima!
Pushing her own faults aside,
she tells off the middle-aged
woman pirate gang
once a month for some reason.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, Luffizaki! Great news!
The supermarket
by the train station
has some
amazing bargains!
Their meat is
freakin' cheap, too!
Even their meat?
Usokawa, are you serious?
Nope. Lying.
Here's the circular.
Aw, phooey!
But forget about all that.
Terrible news!
Chopamori and Sanjida
were caught red-handed.
I need some tea.
Oh, dear me! Is Namijima
out for monthly justice again?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Robino! Please let us hide here!
That crazy Namijima's
gonna kill us!
Oh! Excellent timing, you two!
I've been warning
you girls for months now
about how you handle your trash.
Please, separate and
sort out what's burnable.
It's better for the environment.
They can burn all of
it if they try harder!
Yeah! That's a
good point, Luffizaki!
It's a matter of spirit,
not the incinerator!
What a bunch of nonsense.
Goodness! Pickled vegetables?
Your pickled vegetables
are the best, Robino!
Really! I love them!
Oh, my! Then let's take
a break and have some,
along with this barley tea
I found in the fridge!
Robino speaking.
Yes, they're here. Sure.
Oh! Who was that, Robino?
Who called?
It was Namijima.
So, mind telling me what's up
with this month's rent?
Lovely landlord Namijima.
Would you be a
sweetheart and wait
until after the town
raffle tomorrow?
Hell no!
I'm going to go to
each of your employers
and collect the money
directly from them!
No, please!
Don't do it, Namijima!
Anything but that!
If you do, then tomorrow
will be our last day to live!
Fine by me.
Even as middle-aged women,
the strongest of all
of them is Namijima!