[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man...
As long as there are people who
seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[LUFFY]
"Coby and Helmeppo's Resolve!
Vice‐Admiral Garp's
Parental Affection"
[USOPP]
Ahh! I can see it now!
Thousands of people
from Little Garden
are cheering and waving
as they flock to greet
the great Captain
Usopp and crew!
Listen to the girls'
high‐pitched cries
as they blow kisses
to the brave captain.
Ahh. I'm so popular
and adored by all
that it really
should be a crime.
No, do not fall in love
with me, my sweet one.
You'll only end up
getting heartbroken.
[ZORO]
You're totally delusional.
[USOPP] I heard that, Zoro!
Who you calling delusional?!
Knock it off!
Can't you please just
be quiet for once?!
Morons! I'm sorry. What?
Oh, yeah.
So what I was saying: if you
just look over here.
In this area there
aren't any islands,
but you have to be
careful of the reefs
because they get pretty tall.
Okay. Thanks a lot.
That was a big help!
Of course! You're welcome!
Wow! That smell!
Now then.
Ladies, I present today's
dessert: tartes aux poires.
Bon appétit!
[ALL gasp]
Yummy!
[VIVI, NAMI]
Uh...
[SANJI]
Your dessert is over there!
[USOPP]
Hm? Oh, yeah!
Jeez.
Hm? Where'd Luffy go?
Him? I asked him to draw
some water earlier.
I need it so I can
take a shower.
He's probably at the
water‐drawing machine.
So that's why he's
being so quiet now.
[crash]
I spoke to soon.
[LUFFY]
Whoa! That was a close one!
That thing is kinda scary!
Hey? What happened?
[USOPP]
Ahh!
Luffy! Look at that!
You broke it!
Come on, it was a mistake!
I was just trying to
draw the water faster.
[USOPP]
This is bad!
The belt's been burned up,
and it's broken completely!
Right. That's strange, huh?
[LUFFY yelps]
No, it's not, considering
your freakish strength.
Jeez!
Can it be fixed?
Yeah. But we'd need
to stop somewhere
and get the materials.
For now, anyway,
it's probably better
if I don't ask Luffy
to try it again.
Usopp, will you go
get me some water
with the other water
drawing machine?
I still need a shower.
Yeah.
Hey! Nami, you ever thought
about doing it yourself maybe?!
Huh?
Oh... I can smell some food!
[USOPP]
And you!
Can't you at least
say you're sorry!
[LUFFY]
Okay, I'm sorry.
But there's another one,
so what's the big deal?
Hey, Nami! Look!
[NAMI]
Hm?
Oh! It's the newspaper.
[USOPP] Why can't Nami
do anything herself?!
[NAMI] Seriously, I can't
believe the morning paper
doesn't get here
until the afternoon.
[VIVI]
Well it certainly can't be easy
delivering a newspaper on
time in the Grand Line.
We should really
just be thankful
that we get the newspaper
here at all, you know?
I guess that is true, huh?
[NAMI whimpers]
Do ya notice something
interesting in there?
Uh! Oh. No, it's
nothing. Really.
Oh.
[LUFFY grunting]
Oh. What is it?
Hold on a sec.
Zoro, come look!
[ZORO]
Hm?
At what? It's just a picture
of some marine guy.
Yeah!
But it isn't just any marine
guy they took a picture of.
That's Coby, right?
Yeah!
[NAMI]
Coby?
He's that friend you were
talking about the other day?
Yeah. So what's the
paper say about him?
Let's see. Uh. Here it is.
"Vice‐Admiral Garp arrived with
his crew at Marine Headquarters.
The picture shown here
was taken just after
they crossed Reverse Mountain.
Garp, of course, was
relaxed and in control.
Some young marines
didn't fare as well
as their commander, however.
They sat huddled
together on the deck,
their faces frozen in fear."
[LUFFY]
Whoa.
So Coby's here in the
Grand Line now, too!
[ZORO] And it said at
Marine Headquarters.
Not bad for the kid.
[LUFFY]
Yep!
Coby's going to be a Marine
Mayor one of these days.
[ZORO]
No, he'll be an officer, idiot!
The marines don't have mayors!
[LUFFY]
Yeah, that's what I said.
This is great!
I bet Coby's working
really hard right now.
[BIRD squawks]
[INSTRUCTOR]
Drop and give me 200 push‐ups!
[MARINES groaning]
[INSTRUCTOR] One hundred times
across the rope!
[INSTRUCTOR]
Two hundred laps!
Those of you girls who can't
finish within an hour
will run a hundred more!
[INSTRUCTOR]
Practice matches!
Fight until you drop or die!
[HELMEPPO yelps]
[COBY]
Helmeppo, are you okay?
[HELMEPPO] So this is
Marine Headquarters, huh?
[MARINES chattering]
[COBY]
Okay.
No one can see us here.
You can rest a little.
[HELMEPPO]
Thanks. Sorry.
Um. Coby?
Yeah, what is it?
I was thinking.
Maybe it's too soon for us to
have come to headquarters?
Huh?
You saw them out there.
With the shape that
we're in right now,
we have no chance
of making it here.
[COBY]
Huh?
[HELMEPPO] Some things just
take a little more time.
Maybe we should just
come back here
after we've trained
ourselves up a bit.
[COBY]
Uh?
[HELMEPPO]
Yeah, that's it. Let's do that.
Really, if we're missing
no one's even gonna‐‐
[COBY]
Hey! Come back here!
Helmeppo, I don't understand
what you're saying!
I thought you decided you
were gonna beat your father!
Well. That's what
I was thinking,
but I'll die if I try
to do that stuff!
But wouldn't that be all right?
[HELMEPPO whimpers]
Once you've decided
to do something...
Well, I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!
Once you have a dream
like that in your sights.
I decided that a long time ago.
So if I die...
If you have to die fighting
for your ultimate dream,
then that should be
all right with you!
[HELMEPPO] That's kind of
extreme, don't you think?
[COBY]
You have to fight.
You can't give up!
Please don't ever say
that you're going to
run away, all right?!
‐‐[HELMEPPO] Well...
‐‐[GARP] Running away, huh?
[GARP]
Idiots!
Boys, you aren't planning
to disgrace me
after I brought
you here, are you?
Pathetic wimps!
I can replace two
chore boys very easily.
So go ahead and run
away if you want.
Please wait, sir!
We won't run away, I promise!
[GARP]
Hmm?
We've come with you
to headquarters
fully prepared to
die if necessary!
We'll carry out any orders you
give us, Vice‐Admiral Garp!
[HELMEPPO gasping]
[GARP] You're ready to
carry out any orders.
Is that what you two
are telling me?
You're willing to die here?
Is that what you said?!
[BOTH whimpering]
Yes... sir.
[GARP] Then quit hiding in
a corner and get to work!
[HELMEPPO, COBY]
Yes!
[GARP]
Continue keeping an eye on them.
[BOGART]
Right.
[RIKA]
What?!
Marine Headquarters?!
Yeah.
Vice‐Admiral Garp can be
very unpredictable at times.
[RIKA'S MOM] He's pretty high up
on the food chain though, right?
Yes, very high up.
Then those two must have
been very promising
to have caught his
attention like that.
[RIKA]
Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
[MARINES muttering]
Why did you let them go
without saying goodbye?!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
[RIKA] I still wanted to play
with them some more.
And I wanted to
talk to them more.
I was even learning how to cook.
I wanted to make them a yummy
lunch next time they
came over but...
...but now I can't!
I didn't even get to... to say
goodbye before they left!
[MARINE A]
Uh... I...
[RIKA]
Why did they have to leave?!
[MARINE A] Ahh! I'm sorry.
Please forgive me!
[RIKA'S MOM]
Rika, that's enough.
Leave him alone now, dear.
You don't have to be so sad.
They'll come back after they've
become fine marine officers.
[HELMEPPO]
Uh, what good is this?
How are we supposed to become
marines by mopping floors?
Did you ever think that
maybe this is just a hobby
that old geezer has?
A hobby?
Yeah.
A new hobby called "tormenting
poor chore boys just for fun."
I'm telling you, the
old man's crazy enough
that it might be true.
Think about it for a sec.
Would you birds stop chirping?!
[HELMEPPO] The old man sure is
quick to resort to violence.
[COBY]
His name's Vice‐Admiral Garp.
[HELMEPPO]
Hey,
did you know that his nickname
is "Garp the Fist"?
Apparently he's real
strong and powerful!
Supposedly, everyone's
afraid of him‐‐
even in the marines!
[COBY] No wonder his punch hurt
even more than Alvida's!
No, that isn't the point!
Can we just quit talking
about this stuff?!
Now isn't the time!
We have studying to do!
If you wanna get in trouble,
don't take me down with you.
[HELMEPPO] Jeez, I was just
trying to blow off some steam.
I thought you'd understand.
We're friends, aren't we?
You only say that whenever
it's convenient for you.
If you're really my friend,
then you'll take this
work more seriously.
[HELMEPPO]
Okay, okay. I'll try.
Never mind. I quit.
[COBY]
Huh?!
[HELMEPPO]
I really just want to go back to
what my life used to be like!
No! There's no point in even
thinking about that right now!
Of course, if we
were marine officers,
it would be a much
different story.
[HELMEPPO]
Hm...
There you go!
[COBY]
What?
[HELMEPPO] We can't run
away, and if we slack off,
we get punched, so there's
really only one way
for me to get my life
back to how it used to be.
I have to become an important
person really quickly!
You haven't thought
this through.
There is no way things
will happen that easily.
We have to build up over time,
working steadily and patiently.
There isn't always
an easy way out.
What are you doing?
[HELMEPPO] Mopping floors
and waiting around
isn't going to do
us any good here.
I'm going to go and
do some real work.
Right, yeah.
We're already way too wiped out
from doing a thousand chores
during the day to start
working out at night.
Let's just go to bed.
I've already decided.
[COBY]
What?
I'll become a big‐shot officer
and go back to my old life,
and I'll be stronger
than my dad.
That's what I've decided.
Well that's a nice idea...
But there's no way your
body can handle it!
Never, never, never, never,
never, never, never!
It won't work.
You're gonna die first!
[HELMEPPO] Once you've really
decided to do something,
if you die fighting for it,
that should be all right
with you. Right?
[HELMEPPO]
Well, I've already decided,
and I'm ready to start fighting.
Okay, so maybe I don't
really want to die.
But there's no turning
back for me now.
I'll go as far as
I can from here.
I'll see you later.
[COBY]
Wait! Please!
[HELMEPPO]
Hm?
What is it, Coby?
I'm sorry, Helmeppo.
I was beginning to sound like
my old, scared self once again.
You're right.
The question we have to answer
isn't whether or not we can
do it, but whether or not
we have the will to do it.
So I've come to a decision, too.
You're right Helmeppo.
If we really try
we can succeed.
So come on! Let's go do this!
[HELMEPPO]
Huh...?
Fine with me if you
want to come.
Now we can compete to see which
one of us will last the longest!
[COBY]
Well, I'm up for it,
but I sure hope
you're ready to lose!
Oh, yeah.
I'll see you down there.
‐‐You'd better hurry!
‐‐[COBY] Huh?!
[COBY]
You can't just leave me behind!
[HELMEMPPO]
Really, why not?
It's not like we're
friends or anything,
so I don't have to wait
for you to catch up.
[COBY]
Hold on a second!
That's not what you were
saying earlier, Helmeppo!
[HELMEPPO panting]
[COBY pants]
[COBY grunting]
[HELMEPPO groaning]
[COBY, HELMEPPO grunt]
[HELMEPPO, COBY]
One.
Two.
One. Two. One. Two.
One. Two. One. Two. One...
[MARINE B]
So this is Straw Hat Luffy,
the pirate whose head is
worth 30 million berries.
[MARINE D] We have to capture
such a dirty criminal like him
quickly and execute
him right away.
[MARINE C]
Absolutely!
[COBY] There's a bounty
on Luffy's head!
I don't know how that could be!
[HELMEPPO] Don't you get it?
A pirate is a pirate.
They'll catch him, and once
they do, they'll execute him.
[COBY] I know that, but it
doesn't mean I have to like it!
It's not that easy to accept!
Luffy and I became really
good friends, you know?
[HELMEPPO]
Shh!
Don't be dumb!
No marine has a
pirate for a friend!
You can't ever say
that out loud again.
You'll be kicked out of
the marines for sure!
Yeah, I figured that out myself.
It's not like I'd say that
if there was anyone else
around here
but you, Helmeppo!
That better be true.
Jeez.
[HELMEPPO, COBY shriek]
[COBY, HELMEPPO]
V‐V‐Vice‐Admiral Garp, sir!
What's this?
You boys were talking about
something interesting.
I think I'd like
to hear about it.
What was that about your friend?
[HELMEPPO, COBY whimper]
You'll be coming with me now.
[GARP]
I'll ask you again.
The two of you are
friends with the pirate
known as Straw Hat Luffy?
[COBY]
Helmeppo isn't, but I am, sir.
Luffy and I are friends‐‐
even if he is a pirate
with a 30 million berry
bounty on his head.
All right.
Surely you're aware that we
simply cannot allow a marine
to be friends with a pirate.
But fortunately for you, chore
boy, I'm the only one who knows.
Tell me, do you want
to be a marine?
If you would please
just listen to me.
It's true that Luffy
and I are friends,
but Helmeppo doesn't know
anything about it, really.
[HELMEPPO]
We do want to be marines.
We're working
as hard as we can.
What are you doing?
Moron.
He isn't the least bit
interested in our explanations.
We're in this together.
Isn't that what we decided?
[GARP]
And what about you, Coby?
Do you want to be a marine?
[COBY]
Yes, I do!
[GARP] Then quit standing
there and prove it!
Let's see if you can fight me!
[GARP]
Heh.
[HELMEPPO, COBY yell]
[COBY, HELMEPPO gasping]
[GARP chuckles]
We're... not done!
[HELMEPPO]
That's right!
[GARP]
You fail!
[HELMEPPO, GARP groan]
[COBY gasping]
We aren't done yet!
[HELMEPPO pants]
Yeah.
We aren't even close
to dead yet!
You wanna die that badly?
[COBY] I've decided to
become a marine officer.
And if I have to die
fighting for that dream,
that's fine with me.
No way we're giving
in so easily!
I will become an officer!
Do you hear me?!
[laughs] A marine officer?!
That's the best joke
I've heard in years!
[GARP laughs]
[GARP] People around
here have been saying
that I'm a bit eccentric
for quite a long time.
They had even more
to say this time,
when I decided to bring
you two to headquarters.
Since I brought you here,
I'm the one responsible for
training you to be useful.
I tested you two tonight to see
what you were really made of.
[COBY]
What we're made of?
[GARP] Although it certainly
appears that you've been working
to strengthen your bodies.
I thought that inside your minds
and your hearts,
you might still be weak.
So I tested you to see how truly
determined you have become.
[HELMEPPO]
So, what's the verdict then?
[GARP] I'm willing to
acknowledge your determination,
but that said...
[laughs] You still have
a long way to go!
When it comes to weakness,
you boys are truly impressive!
You'll have an intense special
training session every day.
So be prepared!
[GARP laughs]
[GARP] And I'll keep an eye
on your friend's situation.
But don't tell anyone.
This will just be
our little secret.
[BOTH]
Right!
Thank you Vice‐Admiral
Garp, sir!
[GARP laughs]
[inaudible]
Let's go! Now!
On... to... Little... Garden.
[SANJI, USOPP, ZORO]
Yeah...
♪Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I wrote you a
love song to let you
Know that I wanna be with
you 'til the end of time
Even when the sparkle fades
The doubts in vade our
once so trusting minds
Promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies
We built a castle of sand
And now we're watching
it wash away,
It doesn't have to end
We'll start again,
this time 'round,
we'll build a stronger love
Oh, you've got me heart and soul
I just wanna hold you
and not let go
You know that I'll be with
you 'til the end of time
Oh, you've got me heart and soul♪
[LUFFY]
So this is Little Garden, huh?
[ZORO] I don't see what's
so little about it.
[USOPP] Yeah, it looks like
a jungle out there!
[LUFFY] I wonder if they have
a barbeque restaurant?
[SANJI]
Why the heck would they?!
[NAMI] This place
is definitely freaky!
[USOPP] There's no way
we're going on shore here.
Right...?
[LUFFY] I can smell
adventure in the air!
On the next One Piece:
"An Ancient Island! The Shadow
Hiding in Little Garden!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!