[NARRATOR] This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates
go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure
left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after eating the
Gum-Gum Fruit,
sets sail to become the
next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew
conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the
unwanted attention
of the World Government,
which will use any means
necessary to stop them.
[LUFFY]
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what
kind of adventure's up next!
[NARRATOR] With a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue.
The crew will cut a path across
the Grand Line to the New World!
[NARRATOR]
Separated from his crew,
Luffy and his newfound cohorts
have hijacked a Navy ship
in order to rescue
his brother, Ace,
who's been transported
to Navy HQ for execution.
[MAGELLAN] You've been condemned
and your sentence is final.
There is naught but despair
on the path before you,
however you may struggle.
Can't you see you're
wasting your time?
For filthy criminals
such as you...
...the Gates of Justice
will never open!
You're sure?
You want to open the Gates of
Justice at a time like this?
All this time, and you knew...
I got you! [laughs]
You silly man!
[LUFFY]
Bon! Answer me!
[LUFFY] This is it.
The gate's about to close.
We have... to go.
[whimpers] So thank you!
[MARINE H]
The gate is closing!
[MARINE I]
Keep firing! Take them out!
[MAGELLAN] Any last words
before I eliminate you?
Have at me!
[NARRATOR] Luffy has
successfully broken out
of the world's most
impenetrable prison, Impel Down.
Although, the end of his
battle is nowhere in sight.
[LUFFY]
"To the Navy Headquarters!
Off to Rescue Ace!"
[SHIRYU]
Living dangerously is one thing,
living carelessly, another.
If I'd lacked the foresight
to bring an antidote,
I'd be stumbling over
your corpses right now.
Don't ever underestimate
Magellan.
[BURGESS laughs]
But, we're here!
You shouldn't dismiss
your own inclusion.
Your presence is a factor
in our fate as well.
Ha, ha, ha. Though, he's right.
I was sure I was a dead man.
We're lucky we're all
[coughs] still alive.
Well, It ain't up to us
whether we live or die.
Fearin' death is the
fastest way to lose.
[laughs] Just live while ya can,
even if it kills ya. Right?
Still. Don't think I ain't
grateful for ya help.
'Cuz I am. And again,
welcome to our gang.
I bet we'll make a great team.
I don't see much future
for myself in this crypt.
You're exactly the sort of
person I've wanted to meet,
for some time.
[BLACKBEARD laughs]
Gather round, men.
The time has come.
Let's raise a toast to
our unprecedented escape
from Impel Down! To us!
[CREW]
To us! To us! To us!
Damn! Missed that!
I'm afraid we'll have to do
without Inazuma from here.
[MAN A]
Wait, are you trying to tell us
the infection is that serious?
I was lucky that Magellan hit me
with only one type of poison.
I was able to flush
it out of my system
using my healing
and energy hormones.
[inahles] Hee-haw!
[IVANKOV]
It's an ambivalent fix, though.
One hormone will
take years off my life
while the other causes
severe side effects.
So for him, the best thing
possible is good old-fashioned,
bed-rest and natural
rehabilitation.
Nothing can help you
to regain the years lost
by using the hormone.
Inazuma is an indispensable New
Kama of the revolutionary army.
We need him healthy.
So we have to make sure
he recovers slow and easy.
[MR. 3 sighs]
Now that I think about it,
he wasn't such a pain
in the butt after all.
He was such a good guy.
And he got caught saving us.
Brother Bon!
Brother Bon...
[CREW]
Brother Bon!
Hey, c'mon, guys,
it's sad and all,
but ya can't waste yer
whole lives mourning.
He was great, but now he's dead
and that's the way it is.
So, all we can do is party!
That's what he would want!
[BUGGY laughs]
So, there ya go, it can double
as a funeral for Mr. 2.
[BUGGY groans]
What's the big idea?
It's the truth and you know it!
Hey! For all we know,
there's still a chance Bon
didn't even get killed.
You big nose!
Whoa, hey, what did
you just say to me?
You got a big stupid nose to go
along with your big stupid face!
Oh?
Well, how 'bout I stretch your
stupid face until it snaps?
Oh, blow it out
your giant nose!
If you ask me, they
both look like idiots.
[CROCODILE] Fancy trick how
you rallied those sharks.
How'd ya do it? I was under
the impression only mermaids
had the ability
to speak to fish.
But that impression
is clearly incorrect.
Is that odd?
A fishman being
friends with fish?
Well, it's not the
usual, I know that.
You're a strange one, huh?
A misfit of the savage species.
Fine. I'll take that as
a compliment of sorts.
Yes, it's true, fishmen
do have a violent nature.
Bon is not dead, dammit!
[BUGGY groaning]
[PRISONERS] Whoa! Captain Buggy
grew another big, red nose!
[JIMBEI]
Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[JIMBEI] I wouldn't be here
if it weren't for you.
You gave me the chance
to rescue Ace.
And I owe you a great debt.
Don't think about it
like that. We're even.
And besides,
you're super strong.
I'm just happy to have
you on the team!
[JIMBEI] I wish I could
thank him properly,
and apologize for my involvement
in that unfortunate situation.
But no, this isn't the time.
We have enough to worry
about for now. I only hope
my strength will be enough.
I may be one of
the Seven Warlords,
but they'll strip me
of my title after this.
Now let's make Navy
Headquarters regret
they ever laid hands on Ace!
We must do right
by our fallen.
We'll make your friend proud
and rescue Ace at any cost!
Warlord?
Navy Headquarters?
[BOTH]
What?!
Whoa, really?
You-You're seriously
a Warlord? Jeez!
No wonder you're so strong!
Yes. I suppose I should've
told you sooner.
Everybody else knew that.
[BUGGY] Hey! What's all this
talk about Navy Headquarters?!
Don't tell me we escaped
from the bowels of hell
just to head straight back
into the jaws of the beast!
I'm afraid so.
Screw you!
Nobody is that crazy!
Surely you guys heard
about the war brewing
between Whitebeard and the Navy!
Uh. War?
Navy Headquarters?
Don't act like it's
a big surprise.
Not our fault you're so dense.
[BUGGY]
Say what?!
Well, we passed through
the Gate of Justice.
Isn't that right?
Our destination is Enies
Lobby or Navy HQ.
This Tub Current is restricted
to Government passage only.
It's one giant whirlpool
that connects
the Government's three
major facilities.
The reason we busted out now
is cause we have a role to play
in this war. So you
best get used to it.
[BUGGY, MR. 3 gasping]
Yeah! The real fight's
about to start.
[BOTH]
Real fight?!
Then what do you
call that back there?!
[PRISONERS] No way!
No one told us about this!
Stop!
Turn this ship around,
you bastard!
Please, stop!
There's no stopping and
there's no turning around.
Not while the ship's
on the current.
If you're scared,
just get off.
[BUGGY]
Okay, good idea...
[MR. 3] Yeah! Good
luck with your war!
[BOTH]
We can't do that, moron!
That would kill us! We both
have Devil Fruit powers!
Navy HQ, the Warlords, and...
the Whitebeard Pirates
all fighting each
other at once?
Nobody can survive that!
I've heard enough.
Please take me back!
I'd rather be in prison
than this war!
[PRISONER E crying]
All of us from New Kama
Land knew about this plan.
Uh! Then why the hell
didn't you tell us?
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL A]
Pudda Pudda Pudda Pudda.
This's it! We're all dead!
Mommy!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL A]
Pudda Pudda Pudda Pudda.
Hey. What is that?
You guys hear it?
Uh.
It's a Transponder Snail.
But who's callin'?
Don't you get it? Think!
We're on a Navy ship.
Huh?
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL A]
Pudda Pudda Pudda Pudda.
[gasps]
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL A]
Pudda Pudda Pudda Pudda.
[ALL]
Huh?!
Let's just act
like no one's here.
Pudda Pudda Pudda
Pudda Pudda, cuh-lick.
Uh. Hello?
[CREW]
He answered it!
[MARINE A]
Greetings from Navy HQ.
Hey, Luffy here.
[CREW]
Idiot! Don't say that!
Listen, kid we're aware
that the ship has been
hijacked by escapees.
We received a report from Impel
Down. So let's be honest here.
Before contact was lost, we had
insider information being fed
to us. Based on this,
we've determined
who the two ringleaders
behind the breakout are.
Two?
[MARINE A] You, the pirate
known as Straw Hat Luffy.
And another notorious
pirate. Buggy the Clown.
[BUGGY]
Uh... Huh?
[CREW]
What?
Wait, what? Ringleader?
[PRISONER N]
Seriously?
[PRISONER O]
We've got Warlords here,
and their main suspect
is Captain Buggy?
Who the hell are you?
Come clean with us!
No! Why me?
[MARINE A]
Pass me the documents.
--[MARINE B] Here.
--[MARINE A] Thank you.
At first, we just assumed
that the clown was another
two-bit criminal. But to
be frank, we... were wrong.
We learned he was a crewmember
on the ship of Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Ah! They found me out!
[CREW]
What?
[PRISONER Q]
You crewed on the Oro Jackson?
[MAN C]
Unbelievable!
[WOMAN D] You're a star!
A star among pirates!
[MARINE A]
Oh, and there's one other thing.
He's an ally of one of
the Four Emperors.
His name is Red Haired Shanks.
[CREW]
Are you serious?!
[MARINE A]
So if you can hear us, Buggy,
we don't know how someone
with your background has
laid low for so long,
but you've most certainly
stepped into the spotlight now.
Well...
[MARINE A] We haven't
defined your connection
with "Fire Fist" Ace yet, but
we're sure you share the same
goal with Straw Hat Luffy,
to rescue him from execution.
Not... really...
[MARINE A] We know that you're
accompanied by Jimbei,
Crocodile, Ivankov. Not to
mention the more than 200
average, run-of-the-mill
ruffians you tricked
into following your lead.
Now let me explain your future.
Your fates depend on whether
we open the Gate of Justice.
As long as we leave it closed,
you can't get to Marineford.
You can't even get out
of the Tub Current.
You will be completely stranded.
There is no sea for
you to escape to.
[BUGGY whimpers]
[MARINE A] Better get used to
your surroundings. That's all.
Hey! Wait! Navy!
[MARINE A]
Huh?
[inahles]
I'm gonna rescue Ace
no matter what!
Better keep your
potatoes peeled!
Our what?
--[TRANSPONDER SNAIL] Cah-lick!
--[CREW] Ah!
[LUFFY]
Hmph.
What? The saying's
keep your eyes peeled!
[PRISONER R] Now I'm
gonna be craving potatoes!
Thanks a lot, pal!
He just tried to pick
a fight with Navy HQ.
Forget the potatoes!
[MAN G] Wait. I've gotta
know, Captain Buggy...
Were you honestly a member
of Gold Roger's crew?
[PRISONER S] And a sworn
brother of Red-Haired Shanks?
You should've said!
You're one hell of a
pirate, Captain Buggy!
[CREW cheers]
[BUGGY]
Now. Hold on! Aw, dammit!
The Government's never gonna
let me outta their sights
now that the truth's out!
Not the background I
was expecting from him.
And yet he's so weak.
[CROCODILE grunts]
That pedigree,
and he's so petty?
Every ship has one.
A little blemish, I mean.
[CREW]
Mm-hm.
Shut yer mouths!
You know. Actually...
Perhaps you've heard of a pirate
named Buggy from the East Blue.
[LUFFY] The old Vice Captain
guy said somethin' about you.
Huh? The Vice Captain?
[LUFFY] Yeah, the old guy,
Rayleigh. You know him, right?
Do I! Are you saying that you've
actually seen Rayleigh?
Oh, man. I miss that guy.
Where'd you see him?
They're talking about
Dark King Rayleigh.
Like it's no big deal.
Holy crap! Captain Buggy.
I knew you were
the genuine article!
[BUGGY]
No! Look, not so fast!
Everything is true, yes, but!
You can't go spreadin'
this around willy nilly.
We gotta think about
my future as a pirate!
[PRISONER V]
Wow!
I can't believe you were a
member of such a legendary crew!
[CREW]
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Hey, listen to me, you
fools! Shut up, already!
I was an apprentice, that's all!
You can't worship
me for that! C'mon!
Knock it off! I'm not
bein' humble, just stop!
[BUGGY groans] I don't feel
as bad as I thought I would.
Oh. Wait a minute! Sure,
the Navy has completely
overestimated me, but maybe
that's not such a bad thing.
Maybe. That's because
it's all true!
I've got a pretty good
reputation goin' for me here.
If only there was some way...
If I could defeat Whitebeard,
maybe I could become one
of the Four Emperors! Hell yes!
Wait, no, no, no, no.
I would need to become
the King of the Pirates!
It's perfect! Some of
these guys've probably
got higher bounties on
their heads than I do.
If I play my cards just right...
[BUGGY]
I can do this!
[PRISONER W]
Captain Buggy!
We'll follow you until
the day we die!
[CREW cheers]
Just give us an order!
Like steal this ship from
the guys who stole it!
We don't have to go to Navy HQ!
That's right! And then...
we'll be free!
[PRISONER Z]
Sorry to do it, Straw Hat!
But we're takin'
control of this ship!
We already broke outta prison,
and we don't want dying
to be the next thing we do!
Surrender now. We've got
Captain Buggy on our side!
--Tell 'em, Captain Buggy!
--[CREW] Buggy! Buggy!
Not good...
Only one way to
handle this. Kill 'em.
I'm good. I've got this!
I really think I can do it!
[CREW]
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
That's enough!
Don't get too flashy!
You guys are high on power
and acting impulsively.
No matter what, this
ship's not stopping!
We're headed straight
for the heart of the war.
And you guys are already
on board, aren't you?
Think about what that
means for a second!
In no time at all,
we'll come face to face
with the man standing with
his foot on top of the world!
Chances like this
don't come around
more than once in a lifetime.
So listen, I want all of you
to live out a dream with me.
For today... I'll
conquer Whitebeard,
and thus, rule the world!
[CREW]
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
[PRISONER DD]
Captain Buggy! Thank you,
the darkness of hell
had beaten us down.
You've saved us.
Gave us light!
We almost lost the
most important thing!
[PRISONER FF]
Yes! Our dreams!
You've let us dream again!
[PRISONER GG] I'll follow
you anywhere, Captain Buggy!
[PRISONER HH] To hell with
living a peaceful life!
[BUGGY]
All right then!
Now let's win this war,
you guys! To Navy HQ!
[CREW]
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
So I guess the
mutiny's over?
Then he's not entirely
useless, I suppose.
[PRISONER II] You're gonna rule
the world, Captain! I know it!
[PRISONER JJ] I'm with
you to the bitter end!
[BUGGY laughs]
That's right, you are!
Let them have fun
while they can.
[MARINE C] The ship
transporting Portgas D. Ace
will arrive at
Marineford shortly.
Ah. Perfect.
[MARINE E] Right this way,
please board the ship.
There's plenty of room,
so don't worry.
We'll get everyone on board.
[MARINE F] Prepare to
receive the prisoner!
[NARRATOR] Nami, traveling on
the Sky Island of Weatheria,
heads for the Grand Line.
But the pace of the island's
travel makes it unlikely
that she'll ever reunite
with her friends.
Meanwhile, will
Franky be stuck
as a tea-drinking
gentleman forever?
[LUFFY]
On the next, One Piece.
"The Friends' Whereabouts!
The Weatheria Report and
the Cyborg Animals!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!