[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[NARRATOR]
We last saw our heroes
in God Eneru's land,
the Upper Yard.
Zoro clashed with the priest
Ohm in the Upper Ruins.
[ZORO] Three lives hold
108 worldly desires!
Three swords...
108 Caliber Phoenix!
[NARRATOR] Luffy and the
others found themselves
in the belly of a giant snake,
and it seemed Wyper
would soon join them.
[ALL screaming]
[NARRATOR] Upon finding
the ruins of Shandora,
the City of Gold, Robin
encountered the god Eneru.
While Conis learned of
Eneru's horrifying secret.
[MAN A] Skypiea will be dropped
back into the Blue Sea world,
and this entire nation
will no longer exist!
[CONIS gasping]
[CONIS yelps]
Father!
[LUFFY] "Collapsing Upper Ruins!
The Quintet for the Finale!"
[CONIS whimpering]
[SUU]
Suu...
Suu.
[CONIS]
Suu...
[CONIS cries]
[MAN A]
There's no time to lose.
You must tell everyone.
Soon our lives will be over.
Eneru will eliminate
everything from the sky.
[ENERU laughing]
[gasps]
Skypiea's going to be dropped
back into the Blue Sea world,
and this entire nation
will no longer exist!
[CONIS]
I can't.
I can't just sit here and cry.
There's no time to lose.
I must take action.
[CONIS] I have to do
everything I can.
I have to tell the people
what's going to happen.
[SUU]
Suu.
[CONIS] I want you to stay and
take care of these two, Suu.
Because there's something
important I have to do.
[CONIS] I have to warn them,
no matter what it takes.
I won't let your death
be in vain, Father.
[SUU]
Suu Suu!
[ZORO] Huh. That took
a lot longer than expected.
Guess I need to do a
little more training.
That's weird. Got awfully
quiet here all of a sudden.
Huh?
[ZORO grunts]
No!
[panting]
[ZORO]
...huh?!
You mean this dog
obeys anyone?
[barks]
[sighs]
In that case, just knock
yourself unconscious.
[thud]
There's no time to waste.
I gotta hurry and take care of
that snake and the bazooka guy.
I don't have time for this
fight to drag on forever.
Why don't you just die already?
[roars]
[WYPER growls]
This battle ends now!
I'm through dealing with you!
No matter what I do I can't
seem to damage this thing.
[SNAKE roars]
I guess it's up to me
to put an end to this.
[ZORO yells]
That attack didn't
even faze him.
Dammit. It's like his scales
are made of steel.
[roaring]
Jeez... What in the world
is going on out there?
If this keeps up much
longer I don't know
if we'll be able to
make it out of here.
[LUFFY]
Hey! Someone help me!
This is killing my face!
Get me out!
[ZORO] Nami had better
still be alive in there.
[gasps] What exactly
did you just do?
I showed mercy.
A pitiful worm was in
a great deal of pain,
so I saved him by releasing
him from his torment.
I performed my duties as god.
It seems the young woman is
still behaving desperately.
But desperation is the most
interesting emotion.
[ROBIN gasping]
Soon enough, true despair
will be something
everyone fully understands.
[ROBIN]
This man, he has Logia Power!
And now, I must say that what
little time we have left here
is coming to a close.
This is the beginning
of the end.
I will now set into motion
a series of events
that will reveal
my ultimate plan.
What plan? What do you mean?
[ENERU]
The Sky Lord is calling to you!
Heed my call, lowly
beings, and come to me!
[ROBIN gasps]
[ENERU]
Sango!
What the...?
What are you doing?
[ENERU laughs]
[ENERU]
It was I who brought you
and your friends
here to Shandora.
I beckoned you.
[ROBIN] I've never seen
anything like this before.
This man possesses
such tremendous power.
[roaring]
The whole place
is falling apart.
[WYPER]
It's Eneru!
He's the only one
who's powerful enough
to do something like this.
I better think of something.
[gasps] Chopper!
[ZORO yelling, gasps]
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO groans]
What's that...?
There's a hole at the base.
[ENERU laughing]
And now this brings us
to our climactic finale.
[WYPER yelling]
[WYPER, ZORO yelling]
[SNAKE growls]
[GAN FALL] I suggest we
attempt our escape now.
Right. Yeah.
It's now or never.
Luffy get over here and
grab hold of the waver.
I'm gonna finally get
us out of this snake.
Right. Hey, you, hang on to me.
Ready. Start the engine.
Here we go!
[engine revs]
Yay. Can't wait to get out.
[AISA, LUFFY yelp]
[GAN FALL] Man overboard!
We can't leave them!
Pierre, go back! You have
to save those two!
[GAN FALL screams]
[PIERRE squawks]
[NAMI screams]
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI gasping]
How'd we get so high up?
[GAN FALL]
I have no idea!
Pierre! Don't worry about me!
You have to save the others!
Pierre!
[NAMI] So what are we gonna
do now that the bird's gone,
you weird old man?!
[GAN FALL]
My name's Gan Fall.
It's Gan Fall!
[NAMI]
I don't care! Just save us!
[whimpers]
[screams]
What just happened?
Why did all these ruins
fall out of the sky?
[panting]
[ROBIN]
Swordsman!
[ZORO]
This is not my day...
[ROBIN] Don't tell me you fell
down here with all of this.
[ZORO grunts]
Yeah, I did.
And it almost killed me.
[ROBIN]
I'm amazed it didn't.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah. Good to see ya, Robin.
Where am I?
What is this place?
[ROBIN] It's the city of gold
we've been looking for.
[ZORO]
City of gold, huh?
It doesn't look much different
than the ruins up above.
Did you find the treasure?
I didn't. There's no evidence
that gold was ever here.
[SNAKE growls]
[LUFFY, AISA screaming]
[gasps]
Wow! That was one crazy ride
if I do say so myself.
I think I wanna go again.
[AISA]
Are you stupid?!
Why in the world did you hold
onto the waver's jet?
[LUFFY laughing]
Sorry.
[AISA]
Everyone else managed to escape.
And we've been left behind
because of your stupidity.
It's all your fault!
[LUFFY]
Eh. Don't worry.
[AISA]
Get us outta here!
I've got an idea. Why don't
we make our way down
to the back of the snake and
escape out its butthole?
Think again jerk!
That's not gonna happen!
[LUFFY]
Look. It's the horse.
That's a bird!
[squawking]
[LUFFY] Uh? Are you trying to
tell us to get on your back?
[squawks]
[neighs]
How in the world did he do that?
[LUFFY laughs]
[screams] You're a freak, too!
I ate a Gum Gum Fruit and it
turned me into a rubbery person.
That's why I can stretch
myself out like this.
Freaks! The both of you
are freaks of nature!
No, I'm a pirate.
Now come on. Let's go.
[gasps, screams]
Better hold on tight, okay?
Uh.
Now, I think it's time
we made our escape.
Let's go, horse!
Full speed ahead and don't
stop till you see the sky.
[PIERRE whinnies]
[NAMI]
Ow!
Thanks, Mr. Weirdo.
We just got lucky when
we landed on these clouds.
[NAMI]
We left Luffy and Aisa behind.
I hope they're okay.
Pierre's gone to
fetch your friends.
And when push comes to shove,
he's a very reliable
bird or horse.
Hey. Where did we end up?
What is this place?
Well, to be perfectly honest,
I have no idea where we are,
but it looks like we
fell through the clouds.
Thank you very much.
I've traveled all across
the Upper Yard in my lifetime,
but I've never seen
this place before.
[WYPER gasping]
Could it be? Is this
really our homeland?
[SHANDORIAN WARRIORS]
Light the fire of Shandora!
In the name of the
Great Warrior Kalgara!
Light the Fire of Shandora!
[SHANDORIAN WARRIORS yelling]
[SHANDORIAN WARRIORS]
We're going back...
...to our Homeland!
[WYPER] I've finally found
what I've been looking for!
The proud city that my
ancestors protected!
[WYPER]
Shandora!
[gasps]
[NAMI] I think the snake is
looking for something.
Either that or Luffy's doing
something that's bothering it.
Huh. That snake sure
is acting strangely.
[gasps] I think it's crying.
[roars]
What's the meaning of
this ridiculous outburst?
Just what are you getting
yourself so worked up about?
You've always been
an annoyance to me.
[ENERU]
But no longer.
El Thor!
[NAMI gasps]
Aisa!
Oh, no Nami! She's dead!
There's no way she
could have survived that!
Robin and Zoro?
When did you guys get here?
[ZORO]
Wait, what are you doin' there?
How'd you get outta
that snake's stomach?
Phew, glad to see you're
all right, Navigator.
Yeah, I think I'm all right,
but I'm not so sure...
about... the others.
Luffy was still in there.
Wha--?! What was he
doing in there?
I tried to get him out,
but he fell off the waver.
[ZORO] Uh! That brat is
nothing but a pain in the ass.
Is he aware of how much
of a hassle he is?
How am I supposed to know?!
[WYPER]
Just one hit.
That's all it took.
Eneru destroyed him
when my bazooka
couldn't even scratch the snake.
And Aisa. I can only hope
she somehow survived.
[growls]
[ENERU]
Ball Cloud!
Eneru!
[ENERU laughs]
That's no way to treat your host
now is it, Shandorian Warrior!
I thought that you'd be happy.
After all, it was I
who brought you here
and returned you
to your homeland.
[WYPER growls]
[ENERU]
Don't get so worked up.
There's time for that later.
This is the beginning.
You don't want the fun
to end so soon, do you?
This is a game to you?
Yes.
And a truly petty game at that.
For all of you will be
competing against each other
for my entertainment.
[WYPER growls]
Well done. I'm happy so many
of you've made it this far.
I extend my welcome
to you survivors.
[ENERU laughing]
[laughs]
[ENERU]
And now the fun truly begins.
This is a survival game
to see how many people
out of an original 81,
including myself,
are still standing after
three hours on this island.
The last person left will
of course be the winner.
Among you are a few participants
who entered late into the game,
but I've decided to
allow them to stay.
It will make it all
the more interesting.
Now the five of us
will continue on
in the final stage of the game.
[NAMI]
Did he say five people?
Zoro, Robin, Gan Fall,
Bazooka man, and Eneru.
That's exactly five people.
Phew. Good thing he hasn't
noticed that I'm here.
[ENERU] In just a few minutes
the three hours will be up.
Which means that the six
people we have present here
are one too many.
[NAMI]
He knows I'm here.
The one thing I know
is that God's prophecy
will never falter,
because he is absolute.
I'm curious to see how this
person is going to die.
Will you all fight each other?
Will you gang up on one
of the weaker ones?
Of course, you could all resist
your fates and force me to pick.
What do you want to do, Robin?
I'm not going to kill anyone.
I won't either.
I won't compete
in your sick game.
And I too refuse to take part.
[yelps]
Why do you gotta
drag me into this?!
[gasps]
[ALL]
You're the only one dying today!
[ENERU laughing]
[ENERU]
Insolent fools.
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[LUFFY]
What's gonna happen to us?
[NAMI] I don't know,
but that guy's dangerous.
[ENERU] Only survivors are
allowed to come with me.
[ZORO] I think you're
messed up in the head.
[GAN FALL] I won't let you
have your way, Eneru!
[ENERU]
Now let's set off, shall we?
To the Endless Vearth.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Showdown in the Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!