[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
I will...
[VIVI crying]
[VIVI]
I...
I will remain here
and fulfill my duty!
If we ever meet again...
No matter how
much time's passed,
will you still call me "friend"?
[LUFFY]
"Scent of Danger!
The Seventh Member
is Nico Robin!"
[HINA]
Yes, we sank one ship.
Just one, belonging
to some Bon Clay,
a Baroque Works agent.
The other ship
was able to get away
[SMOKER]
So you let them escape.
[HINA] To think that I fell
for such a cheap trick.
[SMOKER] Running away
is what they do best.
‐‐[SUBORDINATE A grunts]
‐‐[MARINE GUARD grunts]
Miss Hina, watch out!
[HINA] But it's so infuriating.
Hina's angry.
[SMOKER]
Anger at your own incompetence?
[SUBORDINATE A yells]
[HINA]
No, that's not it.
[SUBORDINATE A grunts]
Whoa! Outstanding!
Cage‐Cage Fruit is intense!
She has the power to
bind any part of the body
she touches!
There's a skill!
C'mon, say it!
Say the killer line
just one time!
[SUBORDINATE A groans]
What the hell did you do to me?
I'm mad at you, Smoker.
Hina's mad.
[SMOKER sighs]
[SMOKER]
Care to elaborate on that?
[HINA]
It's just that...
You actually seem to be
happy about the Straw Hats
getting away.
[SMOKER]
Hmm.
Me? Why would I be?
[HINA]
Who knows.
[COBRA] At which point my
dearest Vivi said to me,
in a very formal manner,
"I have something important to
talk with you about, Daddy.
I mean Father."
At that moment, I remember
thinking to myself,
"King or no,
it makes no difference."
No man gives up
the title "Daddy."
[IGARAM] Your Majesty,
what are you saying?
[COBRA] Watching children grow
is a bittersweet experience.
[CHAKA] Try as I might,
I cannot accept your death.
Can't even shed one tear.
Why is that?
Old friend.
[OFFICER]
Cannons fire!
[TOTO laughing]
[YUBA MAN 1]
What's so funny, Toto?
You've been laughing
ever since the speech.
[KOZA] Yeah.
Let us in on the joke, old man,
'cause right now
we're in the dark.
[TOTO laughs]
It's a secret!
But trust me, guys,
it's a good one.
[KOZA]
You're not making any sense!
[TOTO laughs]
Now have a good journey, Luffy!
You're welcome to drink
Yuba's water anytime!
[TOTO laughing]
All right, that's enough jawing.
There's work to be done!
Dig the well! Dig!
[YUBA MAN 2]
Okay, okay.
[KID A crying]
‐‐[KID C] Come back!
‐‐[KID B] You stupid bird!
It took the satchel!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
(La la la la)
Day after day...
(La la la la la)
No matter what may come,
there's nothing
that can take away from me
(La la la la)
My only dream...
(La la la la la)
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
[NANOHANA 1] Does anyone have
a clue who Princess Vivi
was talking to?
Nah, but who really
cares anyway?
[NANOHANA 3] Yeah, what she
said makes us happy.
[WOMAN A] And it's our
duty to respond to it!
She's right. Well said.
Even though we're
simply peasants.
Speak for yourself, peasant!
[ALL laugh]
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[RAINBASE 1] As expected,
Alubarna seems to be
in bad shape.
[RAINBASE 2]
Perfect. We should go there.
[RAINBASE 1]
But we also have to restore Yuba
as quickly as possible.
It's an important
crossroad in the west.
[RAINBASE 2] And don't forget
we still need to repair
all the canals along
the Sandora River.
[RAINBASE 3]
What about the casino?
[RAINBASE 2]
It'll be closed.
Let's go, everyone!
[RAINBASES]
Yeah!
Um, why's he getting
special treatment?
'Cause. Princess Vivi
told us to, I guess.
He wants to join the
Supersonic Duck Squadron.
[SOLDIER 1]
He's a camel.
What gave it away?
[PELL]
Well I'm off.
Thank you for everything.
Too hasty for your
own good, huh!
Someone with your
injuries shouldn't even be
out of bed!
[PELL]
I'll be fine.
[DOCTOR] Just promise me
that if you make it home,
you'll take things
easy and rest.
[PELL]
Okay, I get it.
[DOCTOR]
Hey, wait!
Here. You forgot this.
[PELL]
Oh, thank you.
[DOCTOR] I'd still feel better
if you let me take care
of you here, but I'm a realist.
Just remember, you don't
have to do everything.
Let the others handle
your workload.
And don't skip meals.
[PELL]
Um, I'll be fine. Really.
Whoa! Those Marines are fast!
Or, rather, we're
beginning to slow down!
We're not gonna make
it much further like this!
Water's flooding
in from the holes!
[USOPP grunting]
[USOPP] Hey, Chopper!
I need more panels!
We'll be in big trouble
if we have to‐‐
Chopper!
Here they come.
We gotta fight.
Then let's go!
What's this?!
[NAMI]
Oh, that?
Usopp said to hold
onto 'em in case
we needed 'em for something.
Who knows.
‐‐C'mon!
‐‐They're in our way!
I'll get rid of 'em.
[OFFICER] Take your positions.
Once we pull up,
everyone attacks!
[LUFFY]
Okay! Now we ready?
Now's our chance!
Full‐speed ahead! Shake 'em off!
[VIVI]
Now, Karoo.
[KAROO squawks]
Let's go to Alubarna!
[VIVI] Although my adventure is
over, a new challenge awaits.
Restoring Alabasta.
I'll need more courage
than I've ever found
if I'm to succeed in
bringing my homeland
to its former glory.
This once proud nation
is like a battered ship
wandering aimlessly at sea.
But I believe no
cause is hopeless,
not as long as you
give it your all
and don't give up!
Alabasta may be
adrift right now,
but I know my people!
They will face the oncoming
waves of fear
and uncertainty with bravery!
We will never be discouraged!
The path ahead, though long
and rough, is clear.
We will push forward,
straight ahead,
with confidence and vigor!
Just like the Going Merry
and her crew!
The Straw Hats.
We will see them again someday,
won't we, Karoo?
[KAROO squawks]
Hey, Captain Smoker.
[SMOKER]
Tashigi. So how are your legs?
They're doing fine.
Change the subject.
[TASHIGI]
Thank you.
I saw the new bounties
on their heads.
[SMOKER] The amount's no
surprise considering the catch.
Have you heard what
his swordsman buddy did?
You mean Roronoa?
He cut down one hundred bounty
hunters in Whisky Peak,
and then, in Alubarna,
he killed Daz Bones.
The assassin? No way!
[SMOKER] He used to be a
bounty hunter and was known
throughout the West Blue.
In Baroque Works, he went
by the alias Mr. 1.
Considering Crocodile had
so many famous warriors
at his command,
you'd think they'd be
unstoppable against
any opposition.
However, fate was not kind.
One day we'll have a rematch.
Damn Straw Hats.
[TASHIGI] Yes, and I will
defeat you, Roronoa Zoro.
[ZORO] Looks like the Marines
have stopped following us.
[GROUP groaning]
[ZORO] That's good news,
we shook 'em off!
[GROUP groaning]
Stop it!
What's with the pathetic groans?
I miss her!
[ZORO]
That's enough whining!
If you wanted her
to join that bad,
then you shouldn't
have let her leave!
Ah! You savage!
Blockhead!
Idiot.
Three Swords Style.
Saying "Three Swords Style"
isn't an insult, Luffy.
Four Swords Style.
[USOPP] It's not the number
that's the problem.
An effective insult must
involve some personal detail
about the recipient that's
rude or disparaging!
[ROBIN] Looks like we finally
escaped the firing squad!
[ZORO]
Yeah.
Excellent work.
[GROUP gasps]
Here to avenge your friends?
Just try it!
What the hell
are you doing here?!
‐‐[USOPP] Warning. Warning.
‐‐[CHOPPER yelling]
[CHOPPER]
Who's she?
I don't know,
but she's so damn beautiful!
[weapons clatter]
Didn't I tell you before?
Don't point such
dangerous objects at me.
Are you always so slow?
How long have
you been on our ship?
[ROBIN]
Quite a while.
These are your clothes, right?
I'm borrowing them.
Just a minute, lady!
Who in the hell
do you think you are?
Monkey D. Luffy.
It hasn't been so long
that you've forgotten
what you did to me, has it?
[SANJI growls]
Luffy!
What'd you do to
that beautiful woman,
you lousy bastard?
Tell me! Confess!
[USOPP] All stowaways must
leave the ship immediately!
Wait a minute! Stop lying!
You know I didn't
do anything to you!
Wrong.
And what you did to me
was unbearable.
Go ahead. Admit it.
[CHOPPER] Who's that woman
and what's she talking about?
[USOPP] ...all mystery chicks
vacate the ship
or we'll be forced
to call the Marines.
Thank you for voyaging
on the Going Merry.
[SANJI]
...tear you apart!
You're not makin' any sense.
What do you want me to do?
I want to join you.
[GROUP]
What?!
[ROBIN]
Use that, immediately!
It can neutralize the poison
from Crocodile's hook.
Even if he was
buried in this rubble,
there's a chance
he might survive
since he's actually rubber.
[COBRA] You looked me straight
in the eye and told me
that the only thing
written here was history!
Why did you lie to me?
You knew?
How cruel.
[COBRA] The truth is, this
country's history isn't written
anywhere in there.
Instead, it has everything
about the weapon
you wanted to get your hands on.
The description, location.
It doesn't make any sense.
If you had told Crocodile
this information,
this country would now
be his for the taking.
Isn't that right?
I'm not interested.
Whether people in
this country live or die...
It really makes
no difference to me.
I had already decided
from the start
not to give Crocodile
the weapon.
[COBRA]
I don't understand.
Then why did you come here?
I don't really know anymore.
Chasing a dream, I suppose.
An empty dream.
The last remaining
Poneglyph in the world
that still carries
the true history.
The Rio Poneglyph.
What do you mean by
the "true history"?
[ROBIN]
Nothing.
It doesn't matter now.
For 20 years I've searched,
and I've never had
a better lead than this.
This was my last hope.
And it didn't work out.
So if I'm going to die here,
it's the perfect time.
I'm tired of this
fool's crusade.
It's over.
All I wanted was
to learn our true history
and to share it with
the whole world.
So then, you're saying
that it's possible our lost
history could actually
be uncovered?
And the Poneglyphs
are the key to unlocking
these records?
[COBRA]
You mean, all this time...
'Kay. Let's go.
[ROBIN]
Hold on!
I no longer have
a reason to live!
Just leave me here!
You're coming with me.
Do what you want once
we're out of here.
[ROBIN] I wanted nothing
more than to die
at that very moment.
But you forced me to live.
That's your crime!
There's no place for me
to go, or return to.
So I've decided
that I'll join you.
I see your problem.
Guess there's no other choice.
‐‐Welcome.
‐‐[GROUP] Luffy!
There's nothing to worry about.
Trust me.
She isn't a bad person.
[laughing]
[USOPP]
Pay attention!
I want some straight‐up
and honest answers!
I'll ask you one more time.
What's your name?
My name's Usopp. Hello.
Nico Robin.
Okay, Nico Robin.
So what's your occupation?
Archaeologist.
Are you serious?
Archaeology runs in my blood.
I come from a long line of them.
[USOPP]
Hmm. I see.
So, your family has a
scientific background, huh?
[ZORO]
What in the hell?
[USOPP]
Go on!
It was when I was 8 years old
that I decided to pursue
archaeology as my career.
Shortly thereafter,
I found myself wanted
by the World Government.
Since then I've spent
the past 20 years
hiding from the world.
You've been alone?
Ever since you were 8?
Then one day,
I heard the calling of the sea,
but there's no way
for a child to survive
alone on the water.
The only option I found
that ensured my protection
and the ability to
achieve my goal was...
I chose to work
for various rogues.
Not an ideal solution,
but it brought me this far.
And here we are.
And I'm guessing you
incorporated Crocodile
into your gallery of rogues.
Of course.
I used him to get to
the Rio Poneglyph.
[USOPP]
Hmm...?
I'm good at maneuvering
through obstacles
to achieve a goal.
I'd be a great asset
to you and your friends.
Huh. You're full of confidence.
What's your specialty?
Killing.
Luffy! My investigation
has concluded that she is
far too dangerous!
[LUFFY, CHOPPER laughing]
You guys listening to me?
[NAMI]
Seriously!
I'm disappointed.
You two are pathetic!
Until recently, she was
the vice president
of a crime syndicate.
And you really think such
a woman should join us?
You may've fooled these idiots,
but I'm not convinced!
You pull anything, and I'll
personally kick you out!
All right.
I'll keep that in mind.
Oh, I just remembered.
I brought along some of
Crocodile's jewelry with me.
[NAMI squeals]
Wow, I love ya, sister!
You're the best!
[USOPP, ZORO]
Oh, boy, here we go.
Nami's been had.
This chick's bad news.
She's following her lead
like some kinda pet!
Ah, love. Bold.
The likes of which
I've never seen.
I'm captured by your spell.
Held prisoner in your eyes.
[NAMI]
Treasure!
[SANJI]
I was driftwood floating at sea
until you struck me
like a thunderbolt
igniting my soul.
A snack.
Ah, thank you.
[ZORO] Look at him.
Falling all over himself.
[USOPP]
Yeah.
Well, he was a lost
cause from the start.
[ZORO sighs]
Looks like you and
I are the only holdouts
on this ship of insanity.
We shouldn't blame the others.
Their simple minds
can't resist her charms.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Usopp!
Chopper.
[CHOPPER laughing]
[LUFFY, NAMI, CHOPPER]
[SANJI]
What should I call you? "Robin"?
Or something more daring
that declares my love?
Leaving?
[SANJI sighs]
She's great!
With an adult charm.
She's far different than Nami.
This ship has charm.
Is it always this lively?
Yeah, it usually is.
[ZORO]
This woman's up to something.
But what?
What's the forecast, Navigator?
Is it smooth sailing ahead?
[NAMI] The wind is calm
and the weather's beautiful.
There's no problems
on my end, Sis!
[ZORO] How would you know?
You haven't stopped gawking
at that jewelry!
[LUFFY]
Sanji! Is our snack ready?
[SANJI]
Be patient!
[LUFFY]
But I'm hungry!
[CHOPPER] Oh, yeah! Me too!
Me too! Me too! I want food!
[PELL]
It's... my grave...
♪Can somebody point to
the course I should
sail through,
where I can discover
a new tomorrow?
I found direction,
a map of perfection
I secretly held in
the depths of my heart!
I aim for sky air
and follow my dreams there
although, there were times
I was lost and lonely
I know it's real too,
because when I met you,
you brought out the
finest me I could be
And when I overcame my fear,
I gained something
so wonderful here
Now the time is at hand for my
wish to be turned to a pledge!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
We'll sketch out a tale of all
the stories yet to be told!
I fill the sails with all
that I'm feeling now
See how the winds are changing!
Shining Ray!
Find your brand‐new way!
A never‐ending journey
to be together!
I'm gonna go wherever you
go, my Shining Ray!♪
[NAMI]
We can see an island!
[LUFFY]
Let's explore it!
[NAMI]
First, we'll go look for food!
We'll decide who's gonna
watch the ship using this.
Okay, Chopper stays.
Look after the ship.
[CHOPPER]
Everyone! Be careful!
I'm all by myself today.
I wonder how Doctorine
is doing right now.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The First Patient!
The Untold Story
Of The Rumble Ball!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!