[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[CARMEN]
Sanji, I've searched for you...
...for ten years.
Behold the amazing Carmen!
The greatest cook
in the East Blue.
I am passion... Some have
called me "Fiery Carmen."
[ALL]
Ole!
I am the first apprentice
of Carmen, and my name is Leo.
And I am her second, Jose.
[LUFFY] "Fiery Cooking Battle?
Sanji vs. the Beautiful Chef!"
You... are beauty itself!
[CROWD screams]
[SANJI] It is my
deepest dream come true.
Yes, beauty has come
searching for me.
It is truly an honor,
wonderful Carmen
[CARMEN]
Don't you dare!
Oh my. You are so passionate.
But tell me, Carmen,
how is it that you
and I know each other?
Oh, boys!
Tell the story.
[JOSE, LEO]
Ma'am!
Please look.
Okay.
These are pictures of cooks.
[laughs] True!
These are the most famous
cooks of the East Blue.
And the great Carmen
defeated every one of
them in competition.
Yes.
I truly am the most amazing
cook in the East Blue.
[CARMEN laughing]
[CARMEN]
The cooks who have challenged me
have all been
disappointing simpletons.
And I was beginning to think
that there was no one left
to challenge my skills.
But then...
[CARMEN]
I came across an article
on the Baratie Sea Restaurant
from when you still
worked there.
A cook at the Baratie said
that his prior Sous Chef
was the best cook
in the East Blue.
He said that in all his years
in the restaurant business,
he had never met your equal.
[CARMEN]
From that moment until now,
I have spent every minute
of the last ten years
searching the entire
East Blue for you.
Actually it has been ten days.
Carmen has a weensy
bit of trouble
with a thing we call the truth.
Shut your mouths!
Now I challenge you, Sanj!
If you dare,
bring your spices to the market
place cooking competition
at one this afternoon.
You will be minced like garlic
before heated oil in a pan.
[CARMEN laughing]
[ALL gasping]
[LEO]
Okay then! We'll see you later!
Ah, finally. A woman with
a passion like mine.
So, kid, are you gonna
compete in the marketplace?
Huh? Nah.
I don't like contests.
[BUGGY]
Damn that rubber boy.
I can't believe
we can't find him
anywhere on this entire island.
Hey, Cap'n, I've been
meaning to ask.
Why are we wearin' cloaks?
"Why are we wearin' cloaks?"
Why are you so stupid?
There is a Marine Captain
in this town named Smoker.
If he finds us before
we find Straw Hat,
then I'll never get my revenge.
Agh! This sucks!
Go and find that Straw Hat
before I totally lose it.
Phew! Man, I'm stuffed.
Loguetown might be
our last chance
to get a good meal for a while.
I was starving.
I was starving too.
But I was also
completely outta money.
I'm glad I ran into you.
Huh? But I don't have any money.
You don't?
[LUFFY]
Are you sure you don't?
Of course not!
Where would I get any money?
[laughing]
You are always broke!
[BUGGY]
Agh! I hate that damn Straw Hat
and I want to crush
him like a bug
the next time
I see his ugly face.
[MOHJI]
Yes, sir. Which way did he go?!
Then how are we gonna
pay for this meal?
He will pay!
Maybe we just won't pay.
I swear he'll pay!
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
Ooh.
Whoa. That's cool.
[chuckles]
Hey, you didn't have to buy us
our lunch, but thanks.
[BUGGY grumbles]
[LUFFY]
You're the best!
[ZORO]
Yeah, thanks a lot, buddy!
Yeah, whatever. You're welcome.
[WAITER]
Come again!
[LUFFY]
We will.
[BUGGY]
Uh. Wait, I know that voice.
Oh yeah. I think that
was the Straw Hat guy.
[BUGGY]
Take one more bite and die.
Don't just sit there.
Go after him, you flashy idiot!
A market.
[SANJI] Loguetown's market
is incredible!
They have everything a great
chef could possibly want.
These are superb.
You sure know how to pick 'em.
You're looking at
some Coastal Fish
we just caught
early this mornin'.
[SANJI]
Coastal Fish?
They certainly are
firm and fresh.
Are you sure they were
caught in the East Blue?
I've never seen them before.
What kinda fish did
you say they were?
Ah. You definitely know
your way around seafood.
You are correct.
These fish are different.
They're from the West Blue.
People from the East Blue
don't usually know this type.
The West Blue? Then why do
you call them Coastal Fish?
Young man, is this your
first time here?
[SANJI]
Uhh... yeah.
Just look at this.
You won't find fish like
these in the East Blue.
But we got tons of 'em.
You can pull them right
outta the water all day long.
[SANJI]
So how does that happen?
[NESS] The crossing ocean
currents bring them in
from all the other
seas out there.
Loguetown is just
in the right place.
[CROWD gasps]
Hey. Sounds like they
caught something good.
Let's go check it out.
So what is it?
Ah! Holy‐‐!
Nice catch! It's an
Elephant Bluefin Tuna fish!
[FISHERMAN]
That's right.
It must've gotten mixed
in from the South Blue.
I got her with pole and line.
Just a pole and line?
Bluefin Tuna fish.
[chuckling]
Hey, look. This fish,
it's a weird one.
[COOK GG] What are you doing
with that cookbook, Sanji?
You studying different
kinds of fish?
[COOK HH] That one's the
Elephant Bluefin Tuna.
[SANJI]
You ever seen this fish?
Sometimes it's called
the gem of the ocean.
Some people even say
that it's a miracle food,
but nah, I've never seen it.
[COOK GG] Of course not.
That one's from the South Blue.
You'd never see it
in the East Blue,
unless you can
find the All Blue.
[COOK HH] Ha! The All Blue.
Now that would be impossible.
[COOK GG]
Heh. I know. I know.
Tell me about the All Blue!
[COOK HH]
It's a legendary sea
where all the fish of
the world swim together.
[COOK GG] Careful or he'll
believe every word you say.
Where is the All Blue?
[COOK GG] I told you.
Now he thinks it's real.
[COOK HH]
It's a joke, Sanji.
The All Blue doesn't
really exist.
[COOK GG] Forget about it.
Just keep studying.
The All Blue.
Okay, let's go. Lift it.
[FISHERMEN]
Right.
Hey, hold on a second.
How much for it?
Sell the fish to me!
What?
[SANJI]
I've got money.
Please let me buy that tuna!
I'm sorry, but I can't
sell this to ya.
This fish is gonna be the
grand prize for the contest.
It's... a prize?
[NESS]
That's right.
The annual cooking
contest happens today,
so cooks from all over the East
Blue will be here to compete,
and this fish is going to be the
Grand Prize for the winner.
It is an Elephant
Bluefin Tuna after all.
Any champion cook would be
honored to have it as a prize.
If you really want it, then
you should enter the contest.
You are a cook, aren't ya?
[SANJI]
Yeah.
Registration is
right over there.
You should give it a try if you
still want a shot at the tuna.
If I were you, I'd hurry
before it closes.
See ya.
A cooking contest. Yeah.
[SANJI]
Huh? Wait a second.
Now I challenge you, Sanj!
[SANJI]
Oh well...
[NESS] The annual Cooking
Festivities are about to start.
The greatest cooks from the East
Blue are here competing today.
It's so crowded.
I wonder what's going on.
[NESS] This year's grand prize
is an Elephant Bluefin Tuna.
It's the gem of the ocean
and a miracle food.
Who is going to win this
truly spectacular prize?
[CARMEN laughing]
[CARMEN]
That'll be me.
I'm so glad you decided
to show, Sanji.
But the title of "East Blue's
Number One" is going to be mine.
This'll be fun.
I've never had any real
competition before.
Oh, my Carmen.
It's so good to see you again.
My lips are so close.
[CARMEN]
Don't you dare!
Yeah! That's the fiery
passion I crave.
Hey. Look over there.
Sanji's here.
[USOPP]
Hm?
You're right.
[NAMI]
Of course.
[USOPP]
Hey! Over here!
[NAMI, USOPP]
Sanji! Hey!
[SANJI] Nami! You came
to watch me compete!
Heck no.
I was just walking by.
So what made you wanna compete
in a cooking contest, Sanji?
Usopp, when'd you get here?
I'm the one who yelled
out your name first, jerk!
Who's ready to
start the cooking?
Just for fun we picked one
of you out of the crowd
to join our panel of judges.
Say hello to Sam, who was
just on his way home
to sleep off the rest of his
daughter's wedding reception.
You ready, Sam?
Yeah!
[NESS]
The rules are very simple.
Each cook competes
in a blind draw,
head‐to‐head elimination round
where the highest
total score wins.
Whoever ends up undefeated
though all the rounds
will be the new
East Blue Champion!
First up, from the easternmost
part of the East Blue...
...Shoo the Lizard!
Facing him, representing our
very own Loguetown, Broccoli.
Ready? Let's go!
What's up, Sanji?
You really wanna be known as
the best cook in the East Blue?
No. Don't be stupid.
I'm just after one thing
and that's the fish.
A fish?
Yeah, that looks
like a nice fish.
It sure does,
but the confusing part
is trying to figure out exactly
how I can get that fish to talk.
Now, it's the final round!
[CROWD cheering]
Oh wow. These people
are really excited.
Your right.
[NESS] With his instinctive
skills and sense for food,
we have in the finals, Sanji!
Facing him with her
gorgeous presentation
and culinary acumen, Carmen!
Who will be the winner of the
glorious Elephant Bluefin Tuna?
Start your cooking.
Time to rinse.
[laughing]
[NESS] Carmen's cooking with
outstanding showmanship
while doing things which
are relatively simple.
Meanwhile her two cheerleaders
are trying to distract
her opponent.
And how is Sanji doing?
He is rockin'.
Knife blades flying.
[NESS] And it looks like
Sanji's whipping up
a creation of
delectable delight.
[SANJI]
I know it's for real.
[COOK GG] You don't really
believe that do you? It's silly.
[COOK HH] What would a kid
like you know anyway?
I know a lot more than
you do, you bastard.
That'll be enough, Sanji.
Can't you see we're
busy cooking?
We don't have time for
these silly games.
Why don't you go
set out the plates?
[SANJI]
I know that theoretically
this is an impossibility.
The North Blue, South Blue,
East Blue, and West Blue,
they're separate seas that
shouldn't be able to mix
because of the Red
Line Continent
running from north to south
and the Grand Line ocean
current running west to east.
A place where you can find fish
from all four seas
should be impossible.
[SANJI] But I know it exists.
It has too!
[SANJI]
That's right.
Otherwise how do you explain
the West Blue fish
and the Elephant Bluefin Tuna?
That old geezer might not've
been just telling stories.
I don't have a choice.
I have to look for it
in the Grand Line.
[SANJI] I don't care how long
it takes. I will find it.
[SANJI]
The legendary sea.
[BOTH]
The All Blue!
Sanji is moving on to
his final preparations.
Carmen is finishing up as well.
She just has to plate
up her creation!
This is it folks, the moment
we've all been waiting for.
Who will win the
Elephant Bluefin Tuna?
The decision is
only moments away.
[NESS]
He did it.
Sanji's masterpiece is finished.
And here comes Carmen
with her final touches.
[NESS]
The contestants are done,
so now it's all in the
hands of the judges.
Well then, here goes.
The winner of this year's
cooking championship is...
‐‐...San‐‐
‐‐[CARMEN] Wait!
[ALL gasp]
[CARMEN]
I can't forgive myself.
I can't believe I thought
I could beat you.
I watched you cook
when you were young.
You were driven even back then.
They wouldn't let me in
the kitchen like you,
and it made me so resentful.
I've trained so hard
for so many years...
That's why I wanted to find you
and show you what I'd learned.
But after all this time,
you've only gotten better...
I don't know what made me
think I could beat you.
The truth is... You beat
me fair and square.
You are the number one
cook in the East Blue.
Carmen!
That's the best compliment
anyone's ever given me.
‐‐I'm so happy I could‐‐!
‐‐[LEO] Don't you dare!
Why'd you do that?!
I'm forfeiting this round,
but be ready for the
next time we meet.
I won't lose to you again.
Well, if it's a challenge
from you, Carmen,
I'll definitely accept.
[USOPP, NAMI chuckle]
[NESS]
And the winner is... Sanji!
[NAMI]
Yeah! Way to go, Sanji!
We need you could do it!
Wow, that was fun.
I don't know why but I
just love competitions!
How did I get stuck carrying
the heavy end of this thing?
[SANJI] Wow, an actual
Elephant Bluefin Tuna.
I wonder what it tastes like.
I'm gonna use the fins
for stock I know that,
but what am I gonna
do with the ears?
I just can't wait to cook it.
[NAMI]
Huh?
Huh? What's up, Nami?
It's... the air.
The air?
[NAMI]
It's going to rain.
[USOPP]
But it's so nice.
I'm sure of it. Let's hurry.
Huh? Wait!
[LUFFY]
My hat!
Wait!
[LUFFY]
Stop hat!
Uhh... Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Good! My hat.
Ah. I found it.
Here goes!
[CABAJI]
We found him. This way.
Are you sure about that?
He's there now?
Yes, we were watching the
square as you had ordered
and he just showed up
out of nowhere.
[SMOKER]
Perfect.
[BUGGY]
Let's go flashily.
[SMOKER]
So he finally showed up.
It took him long enough.
[LUFFY]
Woohoo!
So this is what the King of
the Pirates saw when he died.
♪All that's in my
heart confuses me,
I cannot understand,
As I face what I must do,
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand.
I'll set sail alone,
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near,
As I drift away,
I pray you watch me
as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise,
I began to wonder,
What could be the reason,
It's so hot inside.
No answer has come,
But I can't get away
from what's true,
It's because of you...
Show me how to
catch those feelings,
Get 'em to come back to me,
I'll do what I must,
Because they're
everything I wanna be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back
from yesterday,
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we
can make the way.♪
[USOPP] What?!
Luffy's gonna be executed?!
[NAMI]
No way!
[ZORO]
By Buggy?! What a shame!
[SANJI] So all we have
to do is beat them?
[LUFFY]
Yep! Help me!
[ZORO] Okay, then! We'll bring
down the execution platform!
[SANJI]
Lets do it.
[LUFFY] Zoro, Sanji, Usopp,
Nami! Sorry! I'm dead.
On the next One Piece!
"Buggy's Revenge.
The Man Who Smiles On
the Execution Platform."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!