[CRAFTSMAN G] Come on pirates!
I dare ya! Bring it on!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
I give you my word, sir.
I swear. I won't let you down.
[ICEBERG]
You're a good man.
Wow so many.
[LUFFY] If we try
to barge in swingin'.
We'll just be
askin' for trouble.
[NAMI] Says the guy who
charged-in in broad daylight!!
Then it has to be
tonight or never.
Yeah.
Something blew up!
[CHOPPER] Whoa things are
getting crazy out there!
Hey, where's Luffy?
AAAh!
[BULL MASK]
In any case,
we need what Iceberg
was trying to keep hidden.
We need to take
your life, as well.
[PAULIE]
I get it.
This ain't just some
assassination plot, is it?
[BULL MASK] Yes, from the
darkest corners of existence
we bring with us
the light of justice.
We are Cipher Pol No. 9, an
undercover intelligence agency.
[ZORO]
When he does it, it's stupid.
But if we do the
exact same thing,
it's actually a
brilliant plan, huh?
Yeah, makes sense. Let's do it!
Okay! Ready?!
This was a dumb idea!
But I'm totally stuck!
Gotta get out.
Gotta get Robin!
Damn! Where'd they run off to?
[SHIPWRIGHT A]
I don't know.
All I know is that we're looking
for two people and one animal.
[SHIPWRIGHT C] Think we
should go guard the bedroom?
Nah. I'm sure the
foremen can handle it.
There's no such thing
as too much security.
Let's go back them up!
[strangled moans]
Huh?
[SHIPWRIGHT A] Huh??
What the hell's going on?!
[TILESTONE]
RAAAAAHHH!
[SHIPWRIGHT A]
Hey!!!
We need help on the third floor!
Somebody come to the
president's room, quick!
The guards were wiped out!
I need backup!
What d'you mean,
"wiped out"?!!
Tilestone!
Kaku and Lucci should be there!!
Well, come see.
What?!!
RAHHHH!
What?!! No way!!
[MASKED MAN]
Still no word.
I'm getting tired of dealing
with all these idiots.
[TILESTONE]
How dare you!!
I'll kill you!! Bastard!!!
[MASKED MAN] You're a
noisy one, aren't you?
If you laid a single
finger on Mr. Iceberg,
I'll tear you limb from limb!!
[MASKED MAN]
I'd like to see you try.
Iron Body.
Raaaahh!! Raaah!!
[SHIPWRIGHT D]
Whoa!
He crushed that giant hammer!
[SHIPWRIGHT D.5]
That's not good!
You!
Get your hands of me!!
[MASKED MAN] Hmph!
Are those muscles just for show?
[thinking]
I can't move my arm!
How is this guy
stronger than me?!
♪ opening song ♪
[LUFFY]
Raaaahh!! Raaah!!
[SHIPWRIGHT D]
Whoa!
He crushed that giant hammer!
[SHIPWRIGHT D.5]
That's not good!
You!
Get your hands off me!
[MASKED MAN] Hmph!
Are those muscles just for show?
[thinking]
I can't move my arm!
How is this guy
stronger than me?!
[SHIPWRIGHT A] He's taken out
three foremen all on his own?
Ahhhh!!
[SHIPWRIGHT A] We'll get
reinforcements downstairs!
[MASKED MAN]
Shave!
[sounds of fighting]
[SHIPWRIGHT X]
We found them!
[SHIPWRIGHT F]
It's Roronoa Zoro!
[SHIPWRIGHT G]
They finally showed up!
[SHIPWRIGHT H]
Don't let them get away!
[SHIPWRIGHT I]
That woman is one of them too!
[SHIPWRIGHT J]
After them!
If Luffy isn't here,
then where is he?!
I don't know, why
are you asking me?!
Aaaaaa!
What now?
Well, they've already found us,
so there's no point
in trying to be sneaky.
The only thing left to do
now is to go on the offensive!
[NAMI] Wait, what do you
think you're doing?!
[ZORO] Running circles
around the building
won't do us any good.
If we want to find Robin,
then we're gonna have
to force our way through.
Huh?
Yeah, but those are
just shipwrights!
They're not the bad guys!
[ZORO] Then I'll use
the back of my swords!
[ZORO] If you want
a fight, you got one!
[NAMI and CHOPPER] You can still
kill people like that, you know!
[ICEBERG]
Mwell, what a surprise.
After all this time,
I never thought we'd be
meeting here, Nico Robin.
[ROBIN]
Am I supposed to know you?
[ICEBERG] No, last night
was the first time we met.
But for a long time
I've wanted to see you.
I even put your wanted
poster up in my room,
so I'd never forget.
Shall I give you
an autograph, then?
[chuckles]
If you sign it in blood!
You wanted to kill me?
That's right. Before
you destroy the world.
Tell me... Why are you
looking for the Poneglyphs?
You must know the risk.
For as long as
anyone can remember,
the World Government has
made it a serious crime
to research them.
Why is that knowledge
so important?
If they're so bad, then why
do you know about them?
Knowing that the Poneglyphs
exist is hardly a crime.
But deciphering
them is another matter
and you're the only person in
the world who's capable of that.
That's why the World Government
put such a large
bounty on your head.
Even though you were only
8 years old at the time.
They fear what
you're capable of.
Because you
alone have the power
to revive the ancient weapons.
So, you already know.
Yes, but I never
would've thought
that CP9 was actually real.
And if that's the
case, that means
you've already
left the Straw Hats
and you're helping the
World Government now.
A strange choice for a woman
whose been on their most
wanted list for 20 years,
but, mwell, I suppose
that's not my concern.
If you decipher the Poneglyphs
and rebuild one of the
weapons it doesn't matter
if the person who uses
it's "good" or "evil."
It's all the same in the end.
A weapon can never be used
to bring peace to this world.
All it can bring is destruction.
We've buried the evils of
the past, now let them lie.
You may be right
and I don't disagree.
But you don't know
why I'm doing this.
You have no right to tell
me what I'm allowed to do
or not do with my research
or what knowledge
I can or cannot learn.
Mwell, I see what you mean.
But the truth is we might have
more in common than you think.
Perhaps you didn't know.
But I possess the blueprints
for the ancient
weapon known as Pluton.
[ROBIN]
Then they still exist?
[ICEBERG] Pluton is the
name of a battleship built
on this island many
years in the past.
The shipwrights who
created the weapon
passed on the blueprints as
a sort of insurance policy.
They feared that another
battleship of equal power
would be necessary if Pluton
ever fell into the wrong hands.
Thankfully, the ship was lost
to history before
that could happen.
And now the government
wants to revive that power,
when there's no force
strong enough to oppose it.
A part of me hopes that
you didn't know that
when you agreed
to help them out
but that doesn't
really matter now.
A man named Tom entrusted
those blueprints to me.
And he also told me
about a young girl
who was the sole survivor of
the Ohara incident 20 years ago.
He said despite her age,
she was still dangerous,
because she had
the same ideology
as the devils from Ohara.
In honor of Tom and
the other shipwrights,
it's my responsibility
to stop you!
Of course, now that
the government knows
that the blueprints exist the
logical solution would be
to burn them and
be done with this mess.
But I can't do that because
as long as you're alive,
there's a chance that the
weapon could be rebuilt!
[ROBIN] Is that all you
want to say before you die?
Oh, and with all due respect,
even if you had killed me,
nothing would've changed.
The government doesn't need me
to steal the blueprints from you
and I'm sure they've already
accomplished that anyway.
Mwell, let's not get
ahead of ourselves here.
You're the ones
who've fallen for my trap.
Aaahhh...
Oh!
That's it!
I thought I'd never
get out of there!
Man, that was terrible!
Okay. Let's get
it right this time!
I'll find Robin for sure!
Gum-Gum Rocket!
[BULL MASK] I'm afraid you're
no match for our martial arts.
[BULL MASK] Now stop resisting
and hand us the document
before you soil
it with your blood.
[thinking]
Damn it...
I really thought
I could beat them...
[PAULIE]
I shoulda known better.
This was all my idea.
Iceberg didn't
tell me to fight.
He told me to get
the hell out of here.
To run and leave
the blueprints behind.
[PAULIE]
Ya know why?
'Cause those are
nothing but fakes.
[SKULL MASK]
Wha...?
[BULL MASK]
What?
[SKULL MASK]
He can't be serious.
[BULL MASK]
What a waste of time.
[PAULIE]
I don't know who you are,
but this means your
plan's a bust, huh?
Too bad. Sucks to be you.
Funny thing is
I don't even know
what you bastards were
looking for in the first place.
If you think you've
outwitted CP9, you're wrong.
You're merely
delaying the inevitable.
[BULL MASK] At any rate, even
though you're only a decoy.
Now that you know the truth,
we can't let you live.
[loud crash]
Damn it! I got stuck again!
Stupid walls getting
in my way all the time!
I hate 'em, I hate 'em!
What? Straw Hat.
Hey, it's the rope guy!
What's going on in here?
Whoa, are you okay?
You're covered in blood!
You sure did surprise me!
[PAULIE]
Look who's talking!
At least I'm not
crashing through walls.
[BULL MASK]
Straw Hat Luffy.
How kind of you to come here
to take blame for the crime.
Oh! I get it! You guys in
the masks must be the ones
that're forcing Robin to
do all this bad stuff, huh?!
You give her back, you bastards!
If I wasn't stuck right now,
you'd be in big trouble!
[SKULL MASK]
Tempest Kick.
Uhn?
He cut right through the wall!
Hey, behind you!
What are these...?
[BULL MASK]
This is an emergency situation.
We don't have time
to deal with you.
I can't move!
[BULL MASK]
Restrain Paulie too.
He's given us enough
trouble already.
[SKULL MASK]
Right.
[PAULIE]
Hggh... Hgggh... Haaaaaaah!
[TRANSPONDER SNAIL]
Puru-puru. Puru-puru.
Click.
[BULL MASK] It's me.
We've hit a snag in the plan.
Everyone head to the
bedroom immediately.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
You understand?
I absolutely need him alive.
[MASKED WOMAN]
This has been a delight,
but I'm afraid our time is up.
Hmm?
[MASKED WOMAN] You see, I have
a pressing matter to attend to.
Running away, are you?
[MASKED WOMAN]
Not at all.
[MASKED WOMAN] I'm just
finishing you quickly,
that's all.
[SHIPWRIGHT J]
Lulu!
Come back!
[SHIPWRIGHT K]
She's flying again!
[PAULIE]
Hey, you all right?
[LUFFY]
You kidding? This is nothing.
[PAULIE]
That's good, I guess.
But why did you come
here in the first place?
Everyone still thinks you're
the ones who attacked Iceberg.
Sorry about that, by the way.
I realize I mighta
jumped the gun a little.
[LUFFY] No big deal.
We are pirates, after all.
Anyway, the point
is those weird guys
in the masks took
one of our crew.
So we're here to get her back.
Nico Robin.
So, you're good at
fighting, aren't you?
Hell yeah!
Then you can beat
those guys, huh?
You bet.
Good.
We can do this thing together.
'Cause I'm ready to fight!
Oh yeah?
Of course I am!
I mean you think
I'm just gonna let
some weirdoes
waltz in outta nowhere,
kick my ass and
then kill Iceberg?!
Not a chance!
Who do those punks,
think they are, anyway?!
To hell with all this
secret agent crap!
Iceberg is...
...more than just my boss.
He's my teacher.
He made me a shipwright.
I can't let him die.
But look at you, you're a mess.
I told you, I'm ready
to fight those bastards,
and I'm not giving up!
I don't care what happens to me
as long as I can save Iceberg!
Auugh!!
But I can't even move,
cause I'm stuck to
the floor! This sucks!
Yeah! I know! This sucks!
Auuugh!
Auuugh!!
Auugh!
Go home! I have nothing
to give you people!
[BULL MASK] Then we have
a problem, don't we?
[BULL MASK] What does one say to
a man who's marked for death?
First, let me be frank.
You disappoint me.
[ICEBERG]
Lucci!
[SKULL MASK]
This is your own fault.
You should've handed
over the blueprints
when the government
asked nicely.
[ICEBERG]
Kaku!
Pity. I was hoping
we could walk away
from this story without
resorting to violence.
[ICEBERG]
Kalifa.
It's a shame you're as
hard-headed as your master.
[ICEBERG]
Blueno, from the bar.
That means you've been with
the government all this time.
Indeed.
Needless to say,
going undercover was
like second-nature to us.
Now since everyone's
being so honest
with each other,
let's try this again.
I don't have time to play games.
Tell me before someone
else gets hurt. Where is it?
Where are the blueprints for
the ancient weapon Pluton?
♪ ending song ♪
[ICEBERG] To think
that CP9 really exists.
[LUCCI] Just tell us where
we can find the blueprints.
[ICEBERG]
Not a chance.
If we restore one of
the ancient weapons,
it'll only cause more
violence and destruction.
[LUCCI] It seems you
don't have any faith
in the power of the Government.
[ICEBERG] It's human nature
I don't have any faith in, boy.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece :
"Secret Bond!
Iceberg and Franky."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!