Hey, is it true?
We've got a Navy ship
on the island?
What?
I haven't heard about that!
Yeah, it must've
anchored here over night.
Why would the Navy come here?
I know.
We're pretty remote.
Weird thing is, when people
went to look at the boat,
they didn't see
any marines there.
Wow, that is weird.
It was like a ghost ship.
Not a single person to be found.
C'mon, now you're
just fooling with us.
Professor!
Professor Clover!
Hm?
My goodness,
did something happen?
I hope it's nothing to worry
about, but I just heard that
there's a huge navy ship
anchored at the seashore.
We should take precautions.
It might be an investigation.
Better let the
other scholars know.
The raft is done!
All right!
So you're leaving already?
Now what's with that face?
You put those puppy dog
eyes away, little missy!
Actually.
I s'pose my raft
could use a flag, huh?
Guess I'll just have to
stay a little bit longer!
I'll be darned.
So you're looking to
set out to sea, too, huh?
Mm-hm.
My mom's been away
from home for years
thanks to all her big
archeological research.
But whenever she finally
comes back to the island,
I'm gonna ask her to take
me along on her next trip.
That's why I've been
studying so hard.
I got my archaeology
doctorate just like her.
You got a doctorate?
A tiny little girlie like you?
Mm-hm!
But hold on a sec.
Didn't you tell me you
don't even remember
what your mom's face looks like?
Yeah, but she's still my mom.
I wanna see her.
Hey, Saul.
Huh?
Did you know that
our world has a period
of 100 years that nobody
knows anything about?
Uh-huh.
I believe folks call that the
"Blank Century" don't they?
I'm curious about it myself,
but the government says it's
illegal for anyone to look into.
That's right.
But I heard my mom
is traveling
all over the world
investigating it in secret.
But don't tell anyone, I don't
want her to get in trouble.
What?
Are you telling me that your
mom's going around looking
for them ancient stone tablet
things they call Poneglyphs?
You've heard about Poneglyphs?
Yeah, but that ain't
the point here, okay?
You can't go
around talking about
this kinda stuff in front of
other folks outta the blue!
And if yer mamma's out
there looking for them,
you especially gotta be--
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Robin, do you happen to
know your mother's name?
It's Olvia. Nico Olvia.
You okay?
Robin is Olvia's daughter!
Wait, so does that mean--I've
been on Ohara all this time?
Mm-hm.
That's terrible! Oh no!
Why did I end up in
Ohara of all places?
This is no time to be
sitting around, Saul! Robin!
Yes?
This may come as a shock,
but you gotta listen
to me and listen good!
Navy battleships are on
their way to Ohara right now.
They may even be here already!
The Navy? Why?
They're gonna wipe out every
last scholar on the island!
That can't be. No.
So listen, whatever you do.
You're lying.
You can't let those government
guys know you're a scholar.
You're lying!
You gotta promise me that, okay?
Stop lying to me!
It's true, I swear--
I wouldn't joke about
something this serious!
Get to town as quick as you can
and see if anything
strange is going on.
I know it sounds crazy, but
your mom might be there, too!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
It's Olvia.
You came back.
We'd heard news that you'd
been captured by the Navy!
Don't tell me you
came back on their ship!
I hate to have to tell
you this as soon I return,
but the news you heard is true.
It's not your fault--we
knew the government
would set its sights
on Ohara eventually.
I'm not sure how much you know,
but the Poneglyph search
team that set off six years ago
was annihilated by the Marines.
33 researchers were killed.
I was the-- the only survivor.
Fortunately,
I was only captured,
but I overheard the Marines
talking after they had rummaged
through the search
team's belongings.
They soon realized that
we all came from Ohara.
I won't make any excuses,
all of you are in danger
because of my carelessness.
Stop it! Thinking like
that won't do any good!
Those who set out to sea
and those who stayed behind
are all part of the same team!
After what happened, if anyone
should apologize, it's us.
We know how much
you've suffered.
Professor.
For years now,
the World Government has seen
Ohara as a threat to their rule.
But all we can do is believe
in the truth of history,
and its value to
all generations to come.
Be that as it may,
they've put us in quite
a compromising position.
I just don't know how we're
going to get out of this one.
I admit, it doesn't look good,
but we're fortunate to have
discovered this information
when we did.
We know that the
government is hunting down
all the scholars on the island.
So before they
make it to the library,
we have to escape from Ohara!
You have a point.
This time, I have a
feeling we won't be able
to slip past their investigation
like we have before.
And if they're
committed to killing us,
they won't listen
to reason, either.
Then hurry up and run!
I'm sorry, Olvia.
I can't let myself
escape and leave
one of mankind's
greatest treasures behind.
You should know that.
Everyone else here
feels the same way.
Yeah.
Are you sure?
We still don't know what
the government's gonna
do when they get here.
But we do know, if we run,
we can't protect all
this precious knowledge.
We're not planning
on dying here.
Don't worry.
More importantly.
I know you have something
else weighing on your mind.
I can't.
It's too late for that.
Make up your mind, Olvia!
Are you going to
board this ship or not?
If you want to stay
with your daughter,
we'll settle your husband's
unfinished business for you.
No, I'm not turning back.
I'm a scholar of Ohara.
It's my duty to
carry out the will
of those who came before me!
Forgive me Robin.
I swear I'll solve
these mysteries
and come back to you some day.
Where's my mommy?
Where'd she go?
Your mom had to go
out to sea for her job.
You'll be staying here with
us for a little while, okay?
That's enough!
If you don't shut up,
I'll hit you!
Honey stop it, she's only two!
And so is our daughter!
Listen, I don't care
if she's your sister's child,
she's a burden!
This was a mistake!
Who's there?
What're you doing here?
Uh, I was--I--I mean, I just--
I'm so sorry!
If you want to read a book,
all you have to
do is ask, all right?
But I can't, 'cause
I don't have any money.
Well, then looks
like you're in luck,
because you can read
everything here for free.
For free?
Uh-huh! After all, this library
is the best in the world!
Is it really?
It sure is! Let's see,
unless I'm mistaken,
you're Olvia's daughter.
You like to read books?
She looks just like you did
when you were that age.
And I'm proud to say she's
every bit as clever, too.
If she's safe, that's enough.
When I decided to join you,
I severed all bonds with her.
I can't let her become
the daughter of a criminal.
Bad news!
Another ship came with
the World Government's flag!
One of their high-ranked
officials coming
all the way here
to the West Blue?
My goodness. It seems this
is quite serious indeed!
All right everyone, listen.
From now on,
you and I are neither
colleagues nor acquaintances.
You have to stick to
that no matter what.
Farewell!
Olvia, wait! What are
you're going to do?
All right,
tell HQ we've arrived.
Let's move it!
I wanna get this over with!
What a pain.
They better give me a promotion
when this crap is over.
Hey! I want you to
hunt down every scholar
on the island and restrain them.
Yes sir!
What's going on?
Some woman is running
around with a gun!
This is an awful mess!
I'm sorry, Robin!
Vice Admiral Kuzan!
Huh? What is it?
We've been informed
that CP9's Chief, Spandine,
has arrived in Ohara.
So what?
Did you really have to wake
me up just to tell me that?
I'm sorry, sir!
What's the matter, Robin?
You have to tell me.
Did my mom come by here?
Now hold on a minute.
Where did that come from?
Why would you think your
mother was back in Ohara?
I've severed all bonds.
No matter what,
I can't let her become
the daughter of a criminal.
I wish she was here,
too, but she's not.
Oh yeah! We're in trouble!
I heard there are
Navy battleships coming
to the island right now!
They're trying to get rid of
all the scholars on Ohara!
The people in town must
be stirring up bad rumors.
Huh?
The truth is,
that's no battleship
and they won't be
"getting rid of anyone".
The Government is
paying us a visit, though.
And that means
the library will be
under an investigation,
a harsh one.
So listen up.
No matter what those
government agents say or do,
you absolutely
cannot let them know
that you're an archaeologist
like the rest of us.
Since you're so young,
as long as you keep quiet,
no one will think
you're a scholar.
You understand?
Move it!
Stop what you're doing!
Put your hands in
the air and go outside!
Don't you think you're
being a bit violent?
The researchers here at the Tree
of Knowledge are being charged
with the heinous crime
of deciphering Poneglyphs.
We'll be investigating
the library,
so everyone get out of our
way and leave the building!
You'd better treat
this place with care.
The value of this collection is
well beyond your imagination,
I assure you.
I don't have to listen
to a word you say!
Take 'em outside!
Yes sir!
Attention, citizens of Ohara.
I regret to inform you that
the scholars of this island
may be devils in disguise,
plotting to destroy the world!
What?
But why?
Our scholars are the pride of
every person in Ohara-
they would never dream of
doing something like that!
From this point forward,
we will be conducting
a large-scale search
of the entire island!
During that time,
all those who are not related
to the research center must
take a form of identification
and head to the evacuation
ship on the west seashore.
Evacuation?
That's ridiculous!
Even if the scholars
did do something wrong,
that still has
nothing to do with us!
You can't kick us
off our own island!
Our only obligation was to
pass on this message to you.
Disregard our
warning if you like,
but we won't be held responsible
should any unfortunate
"accidents" occur.
You heard him!
Everyone, head
to the west shore!
I don't want to have
any part of this mess!
I've been shot!
This is it for me!
I'm a goner, damn it!
A goner! Contact the higher ups.
Tell them I want my
son to take over for me!
Calm down Chief--just
take a look.
The bullet went through
your sleeve, that's all.
Oh. I see.
I'll aim to kill next time.
Well, if it isn't Nico Olvia!
I find it hard to believe that
a devious criminal like you
would end up on this island
completely by coincidence
after your daring escape!
In other words,
despite the fact that
you've denied your connection
to the scholars of Ohara, you've
shown up at their doorstep
just in time to warn them
of our little investigation.
Now in my humble opinion,
that very clearly labels
them as your partners in crime.
You've no idea why I'm here.
That doesn't prove
one single thing.
Hmph.
I'm sure you've cooked up plenty
of excuses to cover for them.
You're a clever
woman, after all.
But that doesn't really matter,
because we don't have
to prove your connection
to the Ohara scholars anymore.
Now that we're here,
we can search every
little nook and cranny.
I doubt it'll take long
before we find evidence
of their Poneglyph research.
The government's
quite confident in this
and you know
they're never wrong.
This has been in the
works for a long time.
Capturing you after
6 years of hide and seek
was nothing more
than the final push.
There are plenty of Poneglyph
researchers around the world
and each time we captured one,
we tried to find any connection
they might have to Ohara.
Can you guess why that is?
Don't tell me, you're
making an example of us?
Exactly!
If we crush this
"holy ground of archaeology",
the entire academic
world will take notice.
It's the perfect opportunity
to show the world
exactly what happens to those
who research the Blank Century.
Then, the battleships
from headquarters
waiting on standby are here to--
Well look at that!
You are a clever
woman, aren't you?
Yes, as you might guess,
they're to ensure that not
even a single criminal escapes.
However, as a matter of form,
we still need to
verify their guilt.
We aren't pirates, after all.
So, I came all this way
to conduct a
compulsory investigation
of the island and chase off
anyone who's not involved.
It's curtains for you
and your friends.
There's no escape.
Take her down.
Hey, what're you doing?
All the books here
are world treasures!
Take him outside
and shut him up!
Move it!
You bastards!
They must have a secret room
somewhere around here!
Don't stop until you find it!
This is worse than I thought!
The battleships are here already
and there's a whole mess of 'em!
That should be everyone!
Good! Now don't
let them go anywhere!
Look! They're rounding
up all the scholars!
What did they do wrong?
They say they were cooking up
a plan to destroy the world!
That can't be true!
Where is the evacuation ship?
It's on the west
seashore! Hurry!
Everyone run!
Who knows what might happen!
Robin. They said there's
an evacuation ship waiting.
We don't know
what the government
is going to do anymore,
you should get
out while you can.
No way!
There's nothing but mean
people on that stupid boat!
I'm staying here
with my friends!
Robin.
I'm the same as you--
That's enough, just go!
Looks like you have the
situation under control!
Thank you very much, chief!
I was quite surprised.
Nobody warned me there were
such ferocious beasts
wandering the island!
But it makes for
a fine trophy, huh?
Olvia.
All right, listen carefully.
This woman is
an escaped prisoner.
We executed her
comrades after we found out
that they'd been
deciphering ancient texts.
But we still have a couple
of matters left to clear up.
So let me be frank here.
If she's your partner,
just come out with it already,
so I can get this
over with and go home.
How awful of them to
hurt someone like that.
Robin, for the
last time, go! Hurry!
Robin?
Robin!
My little girl.
You've grown so much!
Olvia.
Wh-what are they doing?
If they're not careful, they're
gonna burn the whole tree down!
I never thought they would
take such drastic measures!
Wow, they aren't
holding back, are they?
Puru-puru-puru... Click.
Hello? Is this the Chief?
Yeah. It's me.
We found a hidden
room in the basement!
They have a huge tablet there,
probably a Poneglyph,
and a massive collection
of research documents
discussing the ancient texts!
Nice work!
Click.
Well, scholars of Ohara,
I'm afraid your death sentence
has already been decided!
It's a pity. I hate to
lose so many fine scholars,
but you're really
forcing my hand, here!
Wow, what a letdown.
I came all this way
just to say that?
Guess we'd better report
to the Five Elder Stars.
Roger.
Professor, they aren't
really going to kill you?
They wouldn't do that
to someone just for learning
about history, would they?
Stupid brat!
What do you know?
They may say they're "learning
about history", but the truth is
they're learning how to
revive an ancient weapon
so they can commit mass murder!
You're wrong!
They would never
do anything like that!
Don't bother, Robin.
It's pointless to
discuss the matter
with an errand boy like him.
What's that?
Is it really the
ancient weapon itself
that the World Government
is afraid of?
Professor!
Be careful!
They're on the line now, Chief.
Good.
Hold on!
Huh?
Before you put
all of us to death
allow me to speak to
the Five Elder Stars.
Although we still
have much to learn,
we have proudly continued
our research for many years.
So at the very least, I would
like to share our hypothesis
on the Blank Century
with the world's leaders.
Stubborn old fart. Hey!
Yes sir?
I'm begging you,
please get out of here.
If you hear what I have to say,
you'll become a criminal.
Professor.
Hey, it looks like they found
the people from
the library guilty!
You gotta be kidding me!
Bad news!
There's a bunch of
Navy battleships closing in
on the island from the east!
This is about to get real ugly!
We'd better evacuate now!
What is that?
It's a giant!
Where are you, Robin?
You gotta get off this
island before it's too late!
Saul, please take care of Robin.
You have to help her
escape, no matter what!
What about you, Mom?
Aren't you coming with me?
I'm afraid there's still
something that
I have to do here.
No! I don't want to lose you!
I want to stay
together from now on!
Please!
On the next One Piece:
"The Tragedy of Ohara!
The Terror of the Buster Call."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!