[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
You'd have to be a fool
to disregard a
navigator's forecast.
Now.
[KALIFA]
Not again.
Thunder Lance Tempo!
You might be remarkably strong,
but I can predict the weather,
and I'm never wrong.
[NAMI]
My friends are waiting for me.
I'll be taking your key now.
Back off, Chopper, it's us!
Please, Chopper, don't kill me!
How do we know that
thing is really Chopper?
Why the hell doesn't
he recognize us?
I've got no idea,
but that is Chopper!
Who else has antlers
and wears a hat like that?
[FRANKY]
Step aside, you guys!
[ZORO]
It's you!
Hey, hold it!
What do you think you're doing,
the deer monster is on our side!
I know what I'm doing.
Shut up and move.
[FRANKY] This is the only way
there is to deal with him.
Power holders have one weakness.
I'll knock him into the sea.
Sorry, pal, but this is
for your own good.
Coupe de--
Vent!
That's the last straw, Franky-
you're not gonna
get away with this!
Nobody treats
my friends that way!
[NAMI]
It's okay, guys.
We came up with
this plan together.
You finally managed to
free yourselves, huh?
[ZORO] You better stop
laughing and start running.
You blew your only
chance to kill me.
And you're not getting another.
It's my turn and I'm
taking you all down.
The entire World Government.
[LUFFY]
[screams and panicked shouting]
[SOLDIERS]
Evacuate Enies Lobby!
They're gonna start shooting!
[SOLDIER] The Buster Call's
gonna wipe us out
along with the pirates!
You get back here, Nico Robin!
Even if you make it
out of this tunnel,
all you'll find are
your friends' corpses!
I've had enough
of this nonsense.
Let's teach her
a lesson, Funkfreed.
[ROBIN]
Luffy is just up ahead!
But don't kill her, understood?
Ivory Dart!
Idiot! You will never escape!
Don't underestimate me!
Now, come along, you wench.
Through the gate of dreams.
He's finally back to normal.
Doesn't look like he's dead.
This is weird.
Not even his friends knew how
to handle this guy
after he changed.
Do you wanna get
Nico Robin back or not?
I do! Robin!
Well. Whatever.
At least you managed to
take out one of the CP9 guys.
Kinda lame how you turned
into that giant thing
and tried to kill me,
but if your friends are willing
to stand up for you,
then I won't hold a grudge.
We'd better get moving.
Now that I think about it,
even if we hurry,
how do we get to
the Gates of Justice
without a bridge?
We'll show you the way!
Meow! Meow!
It's you guys!
Look! We found Franky!
Meow! Meow! Meow!
[FRANKY]
Wait.
You found a tunnel that
leads to the Gates of Justice?
Sure did!
And we'll take you right
through, if you like!
Meow! Meow!
I showed Granny!
She's down there now!
All right then,
let's get moving!
I'll fill you in on the plan
after we meet up
with the old lady.
Got it?
Roger!
Meow!
He's unconscious.
But I'm pretty sure
he's gonna be okay.
Stop that, you old hag!
And give that bottle a break!
Oh, yeah. No time to waste.
I need to get these
keys to Nico Robin
before they take
her through that gate!
You guys grab the
deer and follow me!
All right?
Yep!
Okay! Good luck, Franky!
Meow! Meow!
We don't have a choice.
That's the only way
we can stop Chopper.
Oh, and here, take these.
Once we get him back to normal,
you'll need to get
the number three
and four keys to Robin.
One of them should be able
to unlock her restraints.
Soon as you get the cuffs off,
call me on this transponder
snail I swiped from blondie.
Right.
Meanwhile, I'll take this key
and get the cuffs off Zoro and
Nose-King.
Seems like a solid plan, but
what do we do after that?
Even if we're able
to free everyone
and rescue Nico Robin,
that drawbridge
is still locked up.
We'll be running
around this damn tower
with no way to get
back to Enies Lobby.
We're stuck here.
Yeah.
There's the Buster Call
to deal with, too.
If we tried going back
the way we came,
we'd get blown to bits.
So?
What do you think?
The choice is pretty
clear now, isn't it?
A waterfall of death behind us;
a mysterious path ahead.
Which way would you go?
The mysterious
path ahead, of course.
Exactly.
So once we've freed everyone
and we're done in this tower,
we'll meet at the
Gates of Justice.
After that, just
leave everything--
[FRANKY]
To you?
To luck!
Aw, that's just great!
[KAKU]
Come on.
We've wasted quite
a bit of time here.
[NAMI]
Damn right, you have!
I can't believe you two!
How can you be screwing
around at a time like this?
[USOPP and ZORO]
Because!
He wouldn't stop
acting like an idiot!
You're both acting like idiots!
Hurry up and get those keys!
Tempest Kick.
Straight Line!
[USOPP] Just as I instructed!
Nice going, Zoro!
Fight, Zoro!
You guys fight too, dammit!
That long neck of yours,
sure looks like a
weak spot to me.
Sorry, but that's
where you're wrong.
The abilities
I've gained allow me
to freely control
my neck with ease.
Plus, I have a new attack.
Nose Pistol!
[USOPP] Whoa! We're all
the way over here
and I can still
feel the shockwave!
A square-shaped hole?
That's an impressive nose!
Even more so than Sniper-ssop's!
Sniper-ssop? What the hell?
And lay off the nose, got it?
[JABRA]
At any rate.
Looks like Kaku's
really getting the hang
of using his
Devil Fruit abilities.
Fast learner.
Alright, wolf!
I'm the one you
gotta deal with now!
So bring it on!
Don't get so worked up.
Listen.
You guys wanna save
your friend, right?
Yeah, that's right!
And I'm gonna take
your key to do it!
Then go save her
while you still can.
[USOPP]
What?
You heard me.
Take that key and
go save your friend.
I don't get it. Why?
I don't like killing people.
The sight of bloodshed
makes me sick to my stomach.
I'm a pacifist.
Oh. Okay, then.
I'll just--Take
this key and, uh--
No! Look out!
Ten Finger Pistol!
Never let your guard down!
I'm a wolf, understand?
I outsmart my prey
and then I eat it!
Usopp!
[USOPP]
Dammit!
What am I-- What am I doing?
That mask can't
hide your stupidity!
Why don't you just
run around screaming
and crying like you did earlier?
You were great at that!
Don't you make fun of me!
Huh?
[USOPP] We don't have
time for crap like this.
New weapon, Kabuto!
Special Attack Sunflower Star!
Oh.
Wow. A fireworks show.
[NAMI]
No! Usopp!
[JABRA]
Moon Walk!
Leave him alone!
[JABRA]
Just like I promised.
I'll kill you quickly.
There won't be any pain.
It's too bad, really.
You were so much better off
when you were connected
to that green-haired
shepherd over there.
But since this little lamb
has wandered off on his own,
things are a bit different.
Now you're nothing
but a tasty morsel
for the big, scary wolf.
This is the end!
Let him go! Damn wolf!
Please, don't kill him!
Keep your key! We don't need it!
You stupid girl!
You're gonna be
the next one to die!
[KAKU]
Tempest Kick!
Oh, no!
And now it's over!
[ZORO and NAMI]
Usopp!
Who the hell are you?
I'm the hunter.
[JABRA]
And now it's over!
[ZORO and NAMI]
Usopp!
It's Sanji!
Sanji.
How did you get your
body back to normal?
[SANJI]
Some big bathtub fell
from the sky and
smashed to pieces.
Water went everywhere.
It must've broke the spell.
But more importantly, Nami.
Did you just fall in love
with me all over again?
I wish that bathtub had
dropped right on your head.
[NAMI]
Nose-ssop!
[USOPP] Now it's to the
point where not even
Sniper or King
is in my name, huh?
I'm-- I'm sorry, Sanji. I--
I tried. But I couldn't--
You're alive,
that's what matters.
Everyone has things
that they can do
and things that they can't.
Yeah, but--
Both of you.
Take a look outside.
Oh, no.
It's The Gates of Justice.
They're starting to open!
Robin.
[SANJI]
If those gates open up
and Robin goes through them,
we won't have any
way to follow her.
She'll cross waters
infested with Sea Kings,
and beyond that is either
the undersea prison
or Navy Headquarters.
Everywhere on the other side
of those gates is
beyond our reach.
We'll lose her forever.
[NAMI] But I thought
Luffy would have caught up
to her by now.
[LUFFY]
Dammit! I can't get through!
Robin's waiting for me!
Just give it up.
You'll never see
your friend again.
This is as far as
you're going to get.
Now Gum-Gum Gatling!
[LUCCI]
That isn't going to work on me.
Come on!
I said come!
We're going to the bridge!
Am I gonna make it in time?
I sure hope either this
number three or four key
will unlock those
damn handcuffs.
But no matter what,
I gotta stop them!
Go this way. Go this way.
[KOKORO]
Come on, Chimney! Hurry up!
This tower's in
the line of fire, too.
Hold on, Granny!
If I don't show 'em the way,
everybody's gonna get lost!
Meow! Meow!
[KAKU] In hindsight, picking
me as your opponent
wasn't the best idea,
now was it?
From the looks of it,
I think you would have
been better off fighting Jabra.
When you see 'em, I want you
to pass on a message for me.
"You're all fired".
You got it.
No.
I'm happy that it's you.
Feeling a little cocky, are we?
[SOLDIERS]
Run! Hurry!
Hey! Let us on!
Impossible! This train is full!
You'll have to find another way!
[ZAMBAI]
You bastard!
I thought you were
just playing it cool!
You were pretending
to be tied up
with your own rope
the whole time?
Yeah. Was just
waiting for a chance.
"Waiting for a chance"?
This whole island's
gonna go up in flames!
We just got left behind!
There's no way out!
Well, look at it this way:
we were able to get away
from the Marines,
now weren't we?
We don't have time for
this kinda crap, Galley-La!
They said something
about a "Buster Call".
And considering how
panicky they got.
I'd say we don't have much time.
What about Big Bro?
What about the Straw Hats?
Those guys are all unstoppable!
There's no need
to worry about them!
They'll be fine!
We need to hurry
and get off this island!
Yeah!
Ten battleships just departed!
They set sail towards
the island of Enies Lobby!
This is the worst
situation I can imagine.
But in every situation,
even one as bad as this,
there's always a chance.
Sanji.
Leave this guy's key to me.
Changing my opponent, huh?
Doesn't matter to me.
For now, I'm gonna stay here
and do what you can't do.
You need to do what I can't do!
[USOPP]
Huh?
[SANJI]
Think carefully.
Read the situation.
As long as we have you,
there's still a chance
we can save Robin!
You hear me, Usopp?
I want to live!
[USOPP]
What I can do?
[JABRA] Don't waste all of
your precious time pitying
that hopeless fool of a woman
when you should be busy
trying to think of a way
to get out of here alive.
[SANJI]
Hey! You watch your mouth!
You don't want to see me mad.
I tend to overheat when I'm mad.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Fiery Kicks!
Sanji's Full Course
of Foot Techniques!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!