[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Come on, guys! Listen to me,
you gotta stop!
We're running
straight to our deaths!
The water's gonna
hit us head on!
[USOPP] Can't you hear it?
It's getting closer!
Even if there was water
and this place was gonna flood,
turning around at this point
wouldn't do us
much good, would it?
Hey, you can
hear it, right Zoro?
Yeah. I think you're right.
I have a bad feeling about this.
[USOPP] Then stop already!
[SANJI]
There's no other way to go!
We gotta keep moving
no matter what!
[ZORO] Huh?
[SANJI gasps]
I knew it!
[ZORO] Hey, it's Nami!
She's with the weird old lady.
[ALL scream]
Hey check it out, the pirate
guys are here, too!
[GONBE] Ah ha ha!
Don't just stand there,
do something about this water!
[ALL yell]
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum Rocket!
[RANDOM MARINE 305M]
What is it this time?
[RANDOM MARINE 305N]
Is that a balloon?
Yeah right!
My Bone Balloon's too strong!
[LUFFY] Gum-Gum Giant Axe!
[LUCCI growls]
[LUFFY groans]
[yells]
[groans]
[grunts]
Now, Gum-Gum...
[LUFFY] Giant Whip!
[LUCCI] Finger Pistol! Sting!
[groans]
Tempest Kick Victory Bird!
[LUFFY groans]
[MARINES yell]
[MARINE 305I] That plating
was made of solid iron!
This ship ain't
gonna last, guys!
[LUFFY panting]
That was close.
He almost split me in two!
♪
[ONIGUMO] Now fire!
[LUFFY]
"A Mysterious Mermaid Appears?
As Consciousness Fades Away."
[LUFFY] Uh! I'm shrinking!
[panting]
Too close.
[LUFFY] What's the deal with
them shooting their own ships?
Are they that dumb?
[panting]
Well, great.
I got small again.
Third Gear's a pretty cool idea
and it is really powerful,
but talk about
lousy side effects.
I was pumped up
and big for about a minute,
so I guess I'll be shrunk
down for a minute, too.
[LUFFY] I gotta hide
'til this wears off
or he'll stomp
on me like a bug!
[LUCCI] Is that a side effect
or some kind of bad joke?
Whatever it is,
he's still alive.
[LUCCI] Well, this would've
been a waste of time
if he'd died in a
measly cannon attack.
[OIMO and KASHII
breathing heavily]
[KIWI] Look, everyone!
You can see the front gate!
[MOZU] We're almost there!
[FRANKY FAMILY cheers]
Keep running!
[KOKORO] You remember your
old pal, Franky, right?
He got taken away by
the bad guys, too, like Tom.
So, you up for
a fight, or what?
[wails]
[laughs]
[SPANDAM] Your precious
Straw Hat was rampaging
aboard that battleship,
and now he's a pile of ashes!
[laughs]
Your captain is dead!
Go ahead and give up already!
What the hell?
That ship was filled
with their own men.
[SPANDAM] You're
starting to understand
the merciless nature
of the Buster Call!
This is the face
of justice, Cutty Flam!
Now, do yourself a favor
and hand over Nico Robin.
If you cooperate with us,
I'll see to it that you're
pardoned for your crimes.
[SPANDAM] Why are
you even bothering to
protect this woman anyway?
What's in it for you?
You're not even a pirate!
The World Government
is devoted to protecting
normal citizens like you
from people like her.
Do you really
trust her more than us?
This woman with
blood on her hands?
[SPANDAM] If you
choose to defy us--
well, you remember
what happened to Tom.
[SPANDAM yells]
[MARINES gasp]
[SPANDAM] Uhhh...
My face. I didn't think it
could get any more swollen.
[FRANKY] Keep your mouth shut,
I've heard enough of your crap!
Oh, crap! He's using
the elephant sword!
That thing's unstoppable!
Okay. Listen, Funkfreed.
This has gone on
for far too long.
I want you to
fatally wound Nico Robin
while her guard is down.
[FUNKFREED] Mm.
[SPANDAM]
Take this! Elephant Chop!
[FUNKFREED] Mm.
Bastard!
[FRANKY groans]
[ALL gasp]
[SPANDAM] He stopped it?
[ROBIN quavered exhales]
[FUNKFREED mummbles]
[FRANKY] You just keep diggin'
your grave deeper and deeper.
Aaahhh...!
What're you
doing, Funkfreed?
You're an elephant, dammit,
how are you losing?
Get mad and
slice them to pieces!
[FUNKFREED] Mmm.
[FRANKY] You best make your
nose normal again, elephant.
Unless you want a
couple of new nostrils
in the middle of your forehead.
[FUNKFREED] Mm-mmm.
[FRANKY] Okay.
There ya go. Smart move.
Nico Robin. You think
Straw Hat and the others
are still coming?
[ROBIN] Without a doubt.
They'll be here.
[grunts]
[FRANKY] I already told you
once before that I'm betting
everything on them, Spanda.
You what?
Funny. I never dreamed
this day would actually come.
[FRANKY] If I'd only
had the power before,
we wouldn't even be here.
I'm amending the charges.
For the crime of designing
and building a ship
for Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates.
Tom and Tom alone
will be apprehended
and taken to Enies Lobby.
That is all.
[groans]
What in the hell got into
that old geezer's head?
Whatever. I don't
need his lackeys.
Release those
two apprentices!
[KOKORO] Tom can't be
saved from this.
It's the government
we're up against.
There's nothing
we can do! Endure it.
[KOKORO] Tom traded
his life for yours!
If you make them your enemy,
you won't be able to win,
no matter how many
lives you have to give!
Enies Lobby is
the government's
personal judicial island.
[KOKORO] Not one single
person who's been sent to
that dreadful place
has ever been seen again!
He's out of his mind!
What should we do, sir?
Are you out of your mind,
too? We keep on going!
That's what he
wants us to do, right?
[SPANDAM]
Don't worry about him!
Right! Yes, sir!
All right, Puffing Tom.
That's far enough!
[FRANKY (TEEN)] What do
you think you're doing?
Where are you
taking your creator?
[grunts]
Gero, gero, gero, gero!
I won't let you pass!
[grunts]
[train wistle blows]
Give me Tom back!
[train whistle blows]
Even if it killed me,
I had to stop them
from taking Tom.
[FRANKY] Everyone knows the
reputation of Enies Lobby,
and everyone knows the power
of the World Government.
[FRANKY] But the
Straw Hats didn't care.
They knew what
they were up against
and they still pressed on.
[FRANKY] In order to
save their friend,
they were willing to take on
the entire world
without hesitation.
And that's my kind of people.
[FUNKFREED] Mm?
I've never forgotten
the role you played
in Tom's death
and I never will.
[FRANKY] Every time I
pictured your stupid face,
I dreamt of smashing it.
[FRANKY panting]
Smashing your face.
[SPANDAM]
What are you doing?
Don't come any closer!
Stop this!
[FRANKY] Until there was nothing
left but bloody hamburger!
[yells]
[groans]
[whimpers]
That's a pretty good start.
[FRANKY]
Thanks to the Straw Hats,
I finally get to
live out this dream.
[MARINES whimper]
How 'bout some Weapons Left?
[MARINES yell]
I've died before
and it wasn't that bad.
I'll do whatever it takes to get
the Straw Hats out of here.
Even if it means me
dying for a second time!
[MARINES yell]
[FRANKY] Hand over your
escort ship right now!
I'm makin' them an escape
route and you're helping!
[ROBIN gasps]
[ROBIN] And I'm helping, too.
I'm all right now.
[FRANKY] Hm?
Don't look back, just go!
If you stay on
this island, you'll die!
Take my raft and go out to sea!
But what about you?
[SAUL]
He's got me, little lady.
I'm afraid this
is the end. Hurry!
No! Everybody I
care about is here!
Now you listen to me.
You may be lonely at first.
But one day
you'll find true friends.
True friends?
Yeah. The sea's a
vast place, so I guarantee.
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
No matter who you are,
ain't no one
born into this world
to be alone!
[sobs]
[SAUL] It's time to go, Robin.
This is goodbye!
[ROBIN (YOUNG) sobbing]
[SAUL]
Share your life with them,
and never let them go.
This is different.
This is nothing like Ohara.
And I've got nothing
to be afraid of this time.
I'm not alone. This time...
I've got my friends.
♪
[ZAMBAI] Hurry!
[FRANKY FAMILY] Whoa!
[TILESTONE] The main gates
are just ahead!
We're almost off this island!
It's just a little further!
Run, giants! Give it
all you've got!
[OIMO and KASHII]
Just leave it to us!
[KIWI] We can finally
get out of here!
We're gonna be safe!
[BOTH yell]
Made it to
the other side!
Giant doors
don't do nothin'
when ya got
giant muscles!
[BOTH laugh]
[OIMO] Oh, crap.
[FRANKY FAMILY 306A]
Three freakin' battleships?
[FRANKY FAMILY 306B] They
must've been waiting for us!
Look! They made it out!
How'd they get free?
We left them tied up
in the courthouse!
[MARINE 306C] They're
stronger than we thought!
Vice Admiral, sir.
I know. Aim the
cannons at them.
Sir!
[RANDOM MARINE 306B] State your
unit, your marine code,
and have your
picture ID ready to show
before you can board the ship.
[RANDOM MARINE 306C]
You're good. Go on.
[RANDOM MARINE 306D sighs]
What a relief.
I thought we were gonna
go down with the island.
[BOTH wince]
[STRAWBERRY] Resistance
is futile, pirates.
You make one move, and we'll
empty our ammo on you.
This couldn't get any worse.
Oh, man. I doubt they're
gonna offer us amnesty.
And we can't go back,
the island's burning.
We've got nowhere
we can run to.
[CHUBBYCHEEKS]
Every one of their weapons,
all of 'em, aimed at us.
So what's going through
your head right now, huh?
I'm thinking
back on my life.
You shouldn't talk like that.
[PAULIE] It's either that.
Or what?
[PAULIE] What comes next--
the afterlife.
[YOKOZUNA] Gero.
[STRAWBERRY] All of
our remaining personnel
have boarded.
All ships retreat to
a safe firing distance.
[FRANKY FAMILY 306B] They're not
really gonna shoot us, right?
[OIMO and KASHII]
[ZAMBAI] This--This is crazy.
[BOTH whimper]
♪
[PAULIE grunts]
He sniffed me out.
[LUCCI] So that power of yours
demands as much as it gives.
Seems like a pretty
fair trade though.
One must always pay a great
price for a great power.
Life Return, Paper Art:
Fighting Form.
[LUCCI] Finger Pistol!
[yells]
[LUCCI grunts]
[LUFFY yells]
[LUCCI] Time to give up.
If you continue these
ridiculous attacks
I'll have to--
[LUFFY grunts]
[growls]
[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY] I can't move!
Not good! Oh, man!
[LUCCI] I apologize,
but I've gotta kill you
in that stupid form. Now, die!
[groans]
[LUCCI] Finger Pistol! Spots!
Change back, body!
Come on! Hurry up!
Or we're gonna die!
[LUCCI groans]
[LUCCI] That blow from
earlier damaged my legs.
Hey. It's changing.
I'm changing back!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[LUFFY] Ya see? It worked.
Looks like I messed
you up after all.
[ZORO] Is there really
nothing we can do?
[SANJI] I've gotta
think of something!
If I don't, then
we're all gonna drown.
And we haven't even made
sure that Robin is safe yet!
[USOPP]
Is this really the end?
I suppose I have
lived a good life.
There's no denying that
I've had some fun times.
No! I'm not ready to die!
I can't drown in a tunnel!
This is not a fitting death
for the brave warrior
of the sea, Usopp!
[short grunts]
[CHIMNEY] I can't
hold my breath any longer!
[NAMI] It hurts too much.
Everything's starting
to go dark. Someone help.
[KOKORO] It's alright.
Just hang in there.
I'm not gonna let you die.
[ZORO] What? What's going on?
It feels like
something's pulling me.
[SANJI] Uh--Uh...
Am I hallucinating?
That's gotta be it.
[SANJI] It's just like those old
tales that sailors talk about.
Just before they drown,
they see an elegant tail fin.
[SANJI] They look up, surprised
to see long flowing hair.
I've never seen
anything so beautiful.
It's like she's something
out of a dream;
a legendary mermaid.
[SANJI] If I'm dying,
and this is just a dream...
then I don't wanna wake--
I'm swimmin' as fast
as this tail will let me!
None of you are gonna
die on my watch!
Ah...
Aaah...
Bah...
[BOTH] Aah...
Aaahhh!
[SANJI] She's the mermaid?
[laughing]
[FRANKY]
The hell? Seriously.
What kind of madness
is this Buster Call?
Hey! Hurry it up!
C'mon, Straw Hat!
Your friends--
your friends are here!
They're waiting for ya!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece"
"Cannon Fire Sinks the Island!
Franky's Lamentation."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!