It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
In the Tower of Law,
Robin learned that Luffy
and the others had
come to rescue her.
Hold on!
That wasn't part
of our agreement!
In exchange for my
cooperation and surrender,
you promised that you'd let
the Straw Hats escape safely!
After allowing them
to leave Water 7 safely,
as promised, the Straw Hats
decided to come here.
These dirtbags are
the lowest of the low.
Not a shred of decency
in any one of 'em!
Huh?
What did you say?
Shut up, you
filthy piece of trash!
We're not under any obligation
to keep our promises
to a bunch of criminals!
You hear me?
Take that, and that, and that!
You, too!
Don't get cocky
with me, understand?
You coward.
The receiver is off the hook.
There's a Sea Prism Stone
lock on her restraints.
Make sure it's secure.
Cutty Flam goes to Impel Down
and Nico Robin to
Navy Headquarters.
As soon as the ship's ready,
we'll set sail through
the Gates of Justice.
You can return to
your quarters for now.
Thanks to this catch,
CP9 will be the toast
of Navy Headquarters.
And they're very
good at what they do.
Quite dependable.
As long as I have
them working for me,
there's nothing
I can't accomplish!
I'm invincible!
Meanwhile, with the help of
the Franky Family's King Bulls,
the Straw Hats pushed toward the
courthouse in pursuit of Luffy.
Get outta here!
Beat it!
Smooth sailing.
These two make it easy.
Keep going until we reach
our Captain, King Bulls!
He said, "By the way,
the masked guy
that was with you never
made it on board my back.
Is that okay?"
He's talking about Sniper King!
Where is he?
Lieutenant Commander!
Terrible news!
What is it?
It's Straw Hat Luffy, sir!
We can't find him anywhere!
He gave us the slip!
Go!
We must find Straw Hat
at any cost, men!
After finally
evading the Marines,
Luffy reached the
roof of the courthouse.
This is the last building.
She's gotta be here.
Right.
What the heck?
Air Door.
Hey!
You're the bull who's working
with that stupid pigeon guy!
To be honest, it did
seem a little suspicious.
No way you only
took out 5 marines.
Man, you really surprised me!
An invasion like
this is unprecedented.
This is the furthest
anyone has infiltrated
into the mouth of the World
Government but that ends here.
Tell me.
How long do you
plan to keep fighting?
Until I die.
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
What're we gonna do?
It's too late now.
Even if we wanted to,
it's not like we could
go back and pick him up.
I'm sure he'll figure out
something or other.
But the whole island
is swarming with Marines.
He's not Luffy, after all.
He can't fight
them off on his own!
Even if we don't
realize it at first,
we've gotten stronger with
every challenge we've faced.
You may not think he's tough,
but he's survived as
well as anyone else.
No one from our crew would
die at a time like this.
Don't worry.
"From our crew?" Huh?
What're you talking about, Zoro?
Sniper King may be here to help
but he doesn't replace Usopp.
You don't know if he's
gonna be okay or not!
He'll be fine.
He is a super hero, after all.
You're right.
Sniper King would never
let evil triumph over good.
He can't lose!
Why'd I have to not
land on that King Bull?
What am I gonna do?
I'm way behind
everyone else now.
Battleship Cannon!
These shipwrights are awesome,
but I should probably
catch up with the others.
Then again, I did
leave the crew, didn't I?
Maybe I should just run away.
No, running is the
last thing I should do!
It doesn't matter whether
I'm a part of the crew or not.
I put on this disguise so
I could help my friends.
If Robin is willing to
sacrifice herself to save us,
it's the least I can do!
My manhood is on the line, here!
All right, there's only one way
to get back to the
others at this point.
I call it
"Operation Disguise Myself
as One of the Government
Agents and Walk Straight
to the Courthouse
Without Anyone Noticing."
Okay, let's do this.
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
They're flooding the island!
We're all gonna sink!
Huh?
The giant woke up!
We tried for
50 years and blew it.
We let our bosses down!
You mean the government?
We're a disgrace to
all the giants in Elbaf!
Elbaf. Giants?
Bosses? Wait a sec!
Are you saying
you're from Elbaf?
Like, the
Warrior's Village, Elbaf?
Who the hell are you, runt?
I'm Sniper King
from Sniper Island.
I'm interested in your story,
by all means, continue!
Never heard of you, and never
heard of Sniper Island either.
I don't gotta tell
you anything, okay?
Hey, calm down.
The warriors from Elbaf
are the proudest men
in the world, right?
I know you wouldn't be crying
if it wasn't a really big deal.
So tell me what's going on.
I won't judge, I promise!
Take your time.
There's not much
point in telling you,
but I guess it can't hurt.
Kashii and I used to
be pirates 100 years ago.
Our crew traveled
the whole world.
Back then, no one could stop us.
But everything changed when
we visited a certain island.
Cheers!
It's not every day someone
bags a huge Sea King!
And they each got one!
Now that's impressive!
Yeah!
Take us for example!
We're Elbaf giants!
No greater warrior exists!
But even we don't come close
to taking down one
of those massive beasts!
Wouldn't you say
that's fair, men?
I bet no one's ever slain
a bigger Sea-King than us!
A conquest destined
to become legend!
Awesome, so which
one was bigger!
Which?
One?
Look at them
side-by-side, Broggy!
Mine is slightly bigger, see?
Keep dreaming!
Mine beats yours by
three whole centimeters!
What?
You're joking!
You wish!
Bosses, please!
Stop bickering!
Since they couldn't
come to an agreement,
our two bosses started a duel.
They put their pride on the line
and would keep fighting
'til it was settled.
Who were we to stop them?
The signal for the duel.
We had to split up the crew.
We were at a loss.
All we could do was go
back to our hometowns.
He's gotta be talking
about Little Garden.
What else could it be?
A warrior's battle is
life-or-death but as soon as
it's over the winner is supposed
to come back to their village.
We waited for fifty years and
never heard from either of them.
Something was wrong.
So Kashii and I set out to
sea to go back to the island
and find out what
happened with the duel.
But on our way there, we got
captured by some Marines.
They forced us to answer
all kinds of questions
about our crew.
Then we found out the truth.
Even though our bosses
were strong fighters,
they got caught by
Marines just like us
and were stuck in
some big government jail!
Huh?
All of that stuff happened
about 50 years ago.
The government
made a deal with us.
They said if we would work
for them for 100 years,
they'd set our bosses free.
All we had to do was protect
this gate from intruders.
As long as we didn't
let anyone through,
when our time was up, our bosses
and us could all go
back to Elbaf together.
Since giants live
to be 300 or so,
we didn't think it was so bad.
So we agreed to the deal
and kept our end of
the bargain for 50 years.
But then those pirates
came through the gate
and ruined everything.
That's why I'm so ashamed!
That's why I'm crying!
It's not fair.
Now our bosses are gonna
be stuck in that dumb prison
for the rest of their lives!
Hey, hold on, wait a second.
There's something
funny about that story.
You think this is funny,
you little jerk!
How dare you laugh at our pride?
I don't mean like funny "ha ha."
I mean funny "weird."
And what's so weird about it?
Before we came here, my crew
met those bosses of yours.
And we saw them
fighting their duel!
Their names are
Dorry and Broggy, right?
The warriors from Elbaf.
Fighting in an
evenly-matched duel,
over and over again,
for 100 years!
How?
How do you know their names?
You must be lying.
If you need more
proof than that,
I can tell you
anything you want!
And then...
You still don't believe me?
What do I have to tell you?
Their weapons, maybe?
How they fight?
Seventy-three thousand, four
hundred and sixty-six duels.
I know everything about them!
Seventy-three thousand, four
hundred and sixty six draws.
We really met them.
I swear it!
Every one of you
fought like true warriors
in order to protect
the pride of our duel.
And because you
were willing to do that,
no matter what enemy
you may face--
We will never let them
destroy your pride, friends!
You must go straight ahead.
Have faith in what we say!
Let's meet again someday.
Absolutely.
Go straight!
Go straight! Go Straight!
What does it matter?
We've already been eaten!
Straight, okay?
Keep going!
Hakoku!
We're flying!
They cut the sea itself.
The strength of Elbaf
is just too amazing!
Friends!
Take care!
I looked to them as
my teachers, my masters,
and I swore to myself that
I would become a great man
of pride like them someday!
And you still don't believe
me when I tell you this?
They weren't
captured 50 years ago.
That's nothing
but a big fat lie!
Then our bosses
are still out there?
They're still
fighting their duel?
I'm so glad.
They're still okay.
Even after all these years.
Look! We're almost
to the courthouse!
This oughta stop 'em.
We've been hit! No!
All right!
We finally got one!
Sodom!
No. This is bad!
He needs my help!
Grit those teeth
and hold on, Sodom!
You can't fall yet!
Guys, you're gonna have to jump!
Get off him, quick!
Sodom can't go on!
That mortar hit him
square in the chest!
He's about to go down!
You gotta keep moving
no matter what!
You're the only
ones who can do this!
He says "go!"
He's coming down!
Nobody's riding it!
Where'd they go?
C'mon.
Let's go, Gomorrah!
So Robin is in that
building behind you, huh?
Outta my way, bull guy!
Listen boy.
Perhaps you haven't realized
this, but what you're doing
right now is nothing short
of a world-class crime.
Hm?
Just get to the point already.
The power of the World
Government stretches across
more than one hundred
and seventy nations.
This island is a symbol
of our strength and resolve.
Attacking it is not simply
an act of rebellion,
but a declaration of war against
every country in our alliance.
We are bound by our
honor to strike you down.
You will not only
face a merciless death,
but serve as an example
to the entire world.
You're, at most,
a few dozen men.
You should have thought
this out more carefully.
I said "outta my way."
So you gonna move, or what?
It doesn't matter
if I move or not.
The point is that
you condemned yourself
to a death sentence the second
you set foot on Enies Lobby.
You understand that?
Fighting is a waste of time.
You got a taste of our
strength at Iceberg's mansion.
You cannot defeat
our Six Powers.
The difference between
us is simply too great.
Yeah, maybe that's true.
But y'know, for some reason,
I have a feeling
I'm gonna win this time!
Here we go!
Iron Body.
Gum-Gum Rifle!
This doesn't make any sense!
He wasn't like this at all
when I fought him before!
How is it that he's so
much stronger now?
Gatling!
Shave!
I don't care about your honor,
or your Government,
or any of that.
You do what you
want with that crap.
All that matters is
getting Robin out of here!
Gomorrah's down!
This is bad.
We've got marines
closing in on all sides!
There's gotta be
like a million-bajillion
of those guys out there!
If we let them surround us,
we'll never break through!
Wait! What is it, Chopper?
Gomorrah! Gomorrah's
trying to say something!
On the next One Piece:
"Don't Stop! Hoist the
Counterattack Signal!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!