[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny... Fate... Dreams...
These unstoppable
ideals are held deep
in the heart of man...
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NAMI]
I need to rest.
[VIVI gasps]
[VIVI]
Hey, everyone...! Come quick!
What's wrong, Vivi?
Are you okay?!
[VIVI]
Nami has an awful fever!
[pants]
[VIVI]
I have to ask you all a favor!
As a passenger on your ship,
it's not my place to ask
this but I have no choice...
My homeland is in jeopardy
of being destroyed,
so I would really appreciate it,
if we could move even faster...
Every minute I'm out here,
puts more of my people in
danger of losing their lives.
We need to head for
Alabasta at full speed!
Of course, we will...
Just like we promised.
Then it's settled.
Let's find an island with
a doctor on it right away!
[NAMI]
Huh?
So, first thing's first...
We need to get Nami healthy...
Then we sail home...!
After all, we need her at the
helm to move at top speed...
Right!
No one makes this
ship move like Nami!
[LUFFY] "A Raid! The Tin
Tyrant and Tin Plate Wapol!"
[pants]
She needs medical attention
as quickly as possible.
At this rate,
she won't last much longer.
[ZORO]
Hey!
[LUFFY]
See any doctors yet?!
[USOPP]
Luffy, you can't be serious.
Guys... ya think...
...people...
...can stand on
top of the ocean?
[LUFFY]
What; do I think it's possible?
[USOPP]
What kind of question is that?
It's impossible, of course!
[ZORO]
Yeah...? So what's that?
What's what?
Say what?
[CHESS]
Hello! Sure is chilly today...
[ZORO]
Hmm?
[LUFFY, USOPP sneeze]
Yeah, it is chilly today!
Definitely! It's very chilly.
In fact, I would even
say it's freezing...
Really?
Ah?!
Increase buoyancy!
Right!
What is that thing...?!
A watermelon?!
Wh‐Why are we shaking?!
Hold the rudder steady!
If anything happens to Nami,
I'll hold every one
of you responsible!
What the hell is that...?
Is that a ship?
Uh?!
Oh, crap...!
It's... a pirate ship!
It's huge!
Great, just when
we needed to hurry.
[WAPOL laughs]
What's the matter?! Don't tell
me our underwater raid ship,
the Tin Tyrant, surprised you?!
[WAPOL laughs]
Huh?
Vivi! You're in charge!
All right!
Hey!
What's going on...?!
[SANJI]
So... what's going on?
Well, we're under attack,
and it's still snowing...
Well, yeah...
The guns pointing at my face
kinda gave that one away...
What next?
You all consider yourself
a band of pirates...?
That's amusing...
I only count four of ya.
Huh?!
Sort of strange...
...that your group would
have so few members.
'Kay, that's just weird...
What kind of guy
likes to eat knives?!
Ugh! My gums are
bleeding just watching!
All right...
I'll keep this simple...
See, my men here and I wish
to travel to Drum Kingdom...
You wouldn't happen to have
an Eternal Pose or
a Log Pose, would ya?
Nope, can't help...
Sorry, but I've never even
heard of this Drum Kingdom.
Well... Now that
we have that all settled...
Would you guys
just leave already...?
We're in a hurry and we don't
have time to deal with all this.
[WAPOL] You'll never enjoy life
if you're always in a rush...
But if you have neither Pose,
what can be done...?
I suppose I'll have to settle
for your treasure and this ship.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[WAPOL]
First things first!
I'm feeling a bit hungry!
Ah?!
He's a ship‐eating monster!!
Hey, our ship isn't your lunch!
Be quiet!
Wapol doesn't like to be
disturbed while he's eating!
Shut... up!
Damn pirate!
We're under attack!
Shoot him!
Now things are finally
starting to get interesting...
Perfect! This is more like it!
Stop it! Can't we discuss this?!
They took it upon
themselves to start this.
What fools...
They got a death wish?
Huh?! Gunfire!
Karoo! Stay here and watch Nami!
I'll be right back!
Quack!
[SANJI] You shouldn't take
on anything you can't handle!
Reception!
Hmph! All bark, no bite!
Hey... um, Wapol...!
We need help!
You still eating?!
[WAPOL] This ship
doesn't taste half bad.
[LUFFY]
Hey, you!
[WAPOL]
Huh?
You fool!
You're no match for Wapol!
Now you'll be eaten by the
power of the Munch‐Munch Fruit!
Luffy no!
What's this?!
Oh, hey there, Vivi...
Everything okay with Nami?
I'd prefer someone less chewy.
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
I said...
[WAPOL]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
...leave!
[CHESS]
Wapol?
[USOPP snickers]
This is bad!
He sent Wapol flying
out into the ocean!
Bad...?! It's worse...
It's a disaster!
Wapol's gonna drown.
He can't swim!
[CHESS]
Recall the troops!
There's no time to waste!
We have to rescue him
before he sinks to the bottom!
Go, go, go!
This is far from over...!
You'll pay...!
I promise you'll pay!
Your dead! You brat!
[CHESS] You'd better
hope Wapol doesn't die!
[KUROMARIMO]
Or it's your blood we'll spill!
Remember that!
We'll get you for this!
Wow... Crazy...
Those guys are really upset...
What were they callin' that
ole garbage can, "Wapol"?
[SANJI] Who cares about
what his name was.
Don't worry about it...
The guy's obviously a moron.
Best to just forget about him.
[WAPOL laughs]
I know him...
But from where?
[SUBORDINATE]
Captain Smoker!
I've just intercepted
a very intriguing signal!
[SMOKER]
What is it?
Ah!
Such an incredible, full temper!
The legendary... Kashu!
[SMOKER]
Tashigi! Tashigi!
Only here in the Grand Line
could I find such a prized
sword as this so quickly!
Tashigi!
Come here!
Are you deaf...?
Ah!
Yes, sir! Coming, Captain...
[TASHIGI shrieks]
[SMOKER] Stop clowning
around and get over here!
I need you to listen to this!
Oh, neat...
A Black Transponder
Snail listening device!
Listen close...
We just picked up this
conversation minutes ago...
I've got it all queued up...
Ready, Sergeant major?
Uh... Yes...
Play it back please...
[MR. 0] It's Mr. 0 now quit
fooling around, you jack ass...
Have you eliminated Princess
Vivi and the Straw Hats...
Straw hats? Straw Hat Pirates!
[SANJI]
Oh, yeah...
The mission was successful...
[MR. 0]
From this point on,
all my orders will
be sent via letter
following the usual protocal...
That will be all Mr. 3...
And the rest of the message
is undecipherable static.
It's a faint signal...
But there are key
names and phrases
laced in their conversation
that clearly stood out.
Princess Vivi...
Straw Hats...
Orders via letter...
And Mr. 0.
Mr. 0? Could that be
a codename for somebody?!
In fact, it's quite possible
he could be connected
to that suspicious swordsman
we caught earlier in Runess.
What'd he say his
name was? Mr. 11?
[SMOKER]
Possibly...
Part of a criminal organization
that uses numbers for codenames
and sends orders via letter...
Sound about right?
Ha! Mr. 0...? Organization...?
I have no idea what
you're going on about.
Then how do you explain
the letter of detailed orders
we found in your pocket?
[MR. 11]
Uh! Damn letter!
I thought I burned it!
Wait... That's not... not mine!
That's funny...
Because we didn't actually
find anything in your pocket.
Ah!
[SMOKER]
Hmm...
All right, then...
Princess Vivi...
If I remember correctly,
she's from Alabasta
and reports say
she's currently missing...
Excuse me for interrupting,
but isn't the Alabasta Kingdom
in the middle of a coup...?
I wonder if this mysterious
criminal organization and the
Straw Hat Pirates could somehow
be involved in the uprising?
Who knows...
All I know for certain is that
this is the only clue we have
to the Straw Hat's whereabouts.
This means...
We're going...?
[SMOKER]
Yes...
I want you to
contact Headquarters
and get an Eternal Pose!
[SUBORDINATE]
Yes, sir!
It's time we pay
a little visit...
...to Alabasta,
the kingdom of sand.
[pants]
Maybe...
Are you sure she
isn't just hungry...?
If that's really the reason
that Nami's like this...
Then maybe we should try
feeding her lots of meat...
Shut up...
Come on, Nami!
Cheer up!
Look, check this out!
You're gonna love it!
No change... at all.
I know...
Douse her in water...
That'll fix her.
You idiot!
This isn't good.
The sun's about to set
and she's still the same.
Yeah... right...
Maybe it would be best if
we drop anchor somewhere...
We can't navigate
at night anyway
without the help of
Nami's instructions.
That's true.
Ah! You want my autograph
because I'm so famous?!
Sure is a cold one...
Almost a full moon...
[hammering]
Crap, I fell asleep!
You're up early!
Can't just sit
around doing nothing...!
We gotta find a way out of
this jam as quick as possible!
You're right...
That's a good point.
[LUFFY]
C'mon, Nami!
Would ya look?!
This is weird.
Why won't you wake
up and smile?!
C'mon, just one tiny smile...
What's goin' on, Luffy?
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[gasps]
Quit it... You're
freakin me out!
Say, Usopp...?
Does this area seem
unusually calm and cold?
[USOPP] Yeah, now that
you mention it, it sure does...
To be honest,
it's freaking me out.
The Grand Line just
keeps getting stranger.
That's not necessarily true.
[USOPP]
Huh?
Maybe...
There's an island nearby...
Hey, Sanji...!
Will you check the horizon
for any sign of land?
Sure thing.
There's a winter island
somewhere nearby... I think.
[SANJI]
Winter island?
Scattered within
the Grand Line...
There are four basic
types of islands,
made distinct by
their varying climates.
You've got summer
islands, spring islands,
autumn islands,
and of course, winter islands...
Each one has its own four
independent seasons.
When traveling
on the Grand Line,
there are at least 16 different
types of weather patterns
you must be prepared to endure.
Ranging from summer
island summer all the way
to winter island winter,
and everything in between.
There can always
be exceptions to this,
and you could even
encounter unknown climates
at any given moment.
[USOPP]
I think I get it...
The Grand Line has all
these different islands,
one after the other, and
that's the reason why the seas
between them have such crazy,
unstable weather patterns.
[VIVI]
Correct.
And the closer
you get to an island,
the calmer the
sea is around you.
Which is why I asked Sanji
to start looking for land.
That's it...
I see it!
[gasps]
Huh?
Quack?
[SANJI]
Island dead ahead!
Are you serious?!
Oh! An island...!
We found an island!
Hey, Nami! Did you hear that?!
This means we can
get you to a real doctor!
He'll fix you up!
Wake up! Wake up!
Just go look.
I've got her covered.
Ahhhh! There it is!
Nami's saved!
All white...?!
It's snow...!
A snow... island...
Whoa... Luffy, wait...
Just so there's no
misunderstanding between us,
we're stopping to
find Nami a doctor!
We're not here to
have an adventure!
Are we clear...
I love snow... It's so white!
It's no use. He's gone.
H‐H‐Hold on!
You sure this is a good idea?!
There could be snow monsters!
Besides, we don't even know
if there's people there or not!
Oh, no! I'm having a relapse
of my don't‐go‐
to‐the‐island disease!
Ah, snow...!
It's so white and beautiful!
Guess I'll get ready
for the inevitable.
I'm so happy!
Look at the... snow!
Look at the mountains.
They're unlike
anything I've ever seen.
[USOPP]
Say, Luffy.
Aren't you cold,
dressed like that?
[VIVI] It's ten degrees
below freezing out here!
That's when bears
get ready to hibernate!
Huh? Oh, boy...
Cold!
You just figured that out?!
It's a stream of melted snow.
This may provide a
good spot to disembark.
'Kay, guys...
Doctor search‐‐who wants in?
Guess we gotta
find people here first.
I'm in!
Me too!
Fine...! Go have fun!
[DALTON]
That's far enough, pirates!
[gasps]
People! Well, that was easy.
Yeah, nice...
But, they don't
seem too friendly.
I'll only say this once.
Your kind is not welcome here.
Leave immediately!
We only came here
to find a doctor!
We have someone who's sick!
You'll have to do
better than that!
We won't fall
for that old trick!
[VILLAGER B]
This is our island!
We won't let any
filthy pirates land here!
[VILLAGER C]
Raise anchor and leave now!
Or we'll blow you and
your ship out of the water!
That's great...
We barely said hello,
and they already hate us...
[VILLAGER A]
Get outta here!
Look out!
That was a big mistake!
‐‐[VIVI] Sanji, stop!
‐‐[SANJI] Jerk...
[gunshot]
[LUFFY]
Vivi!
♪If there is a treasure
out there to be found,
The odds that you'll
find it are slim to none.
The world's such a big place,
the oceans are wide,
Dumb luck alone
won't help you find it,
Just give up, it's astronomical.
Even so.
If someone tries to
keep us from moving on,
The laughter behind our
backs, it keeps us strong
It's too bad 'cuz we're still
sailing forward, so bon voyage!
Just leave us alone!
It may be foolish
chasing impossible things,
But I just gotta try!
The crazier the dream,
the more ambition
I'm gonna need!
It may be foolish
travelin' on, but I know
That I just gotta fight!
The farther the sea,
the greater paradise
We're gonna find!
Don't give up,
just keep on trying,
And you'll see that
you're closer to...
The horizon of your dreams!♪
[LUFFY] Okay! We're gonna climb
that mountain and see the witch!
[USOPP] You might make it
up there, but Nami won't!
[LUFFY]
She needs treatment, right?
[VIVI]
It's too high! We won't make it!
[LUFFY]
We will!
[NAMI]
I'm counting on you, Captain.
[LUFFY]
Let's go! Before Nami dies!
[SANJI]
Shut up! You're gonna jinx us!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"An Island without Doctors?
Adventure in a Nameless Land!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!