[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[SANJI] Excuse me!
A couple of water-water
candies, please!
[PRODUCE GUY 319A] You got it!
I must say, ha ha,
that BBQ yesterday--
It was the best
I've had in ages!
Thanks!
I'd expect no less since
you use the best ingredients!
Yep! Only the best
will do. See ya!
[CHIMNEY] Goodbye, grocery guy!
[PRODUCE GUY 319A]
Thanks! Come again!
Look! The pirate
ladies are over there!
[SANJI] Uah! They are?
[hollers]
Nami-swan!
Would you mind telling us
how you two ladies
came to be a part of
the Straw Hat pirates?
--Nami, Robin!
--What difficulties do you face
--Mellorine!
--being a pirate and a woman?
--[SANJI] I'm over here!
--[NAMI] It's hard to say.
That's more of a private
matter, don't you think?
Doesn't look like we'll
get much shopping done.
What do you like?
What are you into?
I don't know...
[SANJI]
Oh, but I do!
Nami's going to say
that she likes me!
--[SANJI] Over here, Nami! Look!
--What's that crazy pirate cook
--Yoo-hoo!
--yelling about?
--Anything come to mind?
--Meow!
Thanks for the photos!
Now, do you think we can
get a few of you two
in swim suits?
[SANJI] Swim suits?
[REPORTER 319A] It'll be a
big hit! What do you say?
Hmmm.
[MEN gasp]
[NAMI] I can't believe you!
What kind of a girl
do you think I am?
[REPORTER 319A]
Uh! I'm so sorry, ma'am!
If you want something,
then you have
to talk price first.
Huh?
[giggles] Are you serious?
Well, of course I am!
Luffy's party cost
100 million Berries!
We have to make
that money back somehow,
and this is
an easy way to do it!
Wait a minute.
They wanna take some pictures of
Nami and Robin in swim suits?
[SANJI] Meaning "bikinis"?
And sexy poses?
[ALL giggle]
Perverts!
I can't believe you'd
ask these ladies to do that!
Ah! This guy's
part of their crew!
I'm sorry, sir!
[NAMI] Where'd he come from?
[MEN yell]
[SANJI] If I catch any
of you bothering them again,
you're dead! You hear me?
Take your pictures and your
questions and get outta here!
[SANJI grunts]
Aaah!
Dear Nami. Sweet Robin.
You ladies shouldn't have any
more trouble from that bunch.
I took care of it.
Well, so much
for the photoshoot,
but at least we can
do our shopping in peace.
[SANJI] Just like that,
an opportunity for
a date presents itself!
[SANJI] So since all of our
schedules have opened up a bit,
might I suggest we
take a break from shopping,
--Hey. Mr. Pirate Cook!
--enjoy the city a bit and find
--Hey!
--a nice restaurant where the
--three of us could--
What? What is it?
[CHIMNEY]
I'm hungry. Can we eat?
[SANJI] I just gave you
some water-water candy
a few minutes ago!
I'm hungry!
I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
Now listen to me.
If you wanna eat,
I'll give you some money
and you can find something.
[SANJI] I'm trying to set up
at date, get the picture?
I need alone time.
[CHIMNEY]
I don't wanna eat... alone!
[CHIMNEY and GONBE] Wa! Wa!
You're not fooling anyone!
Aw, it's okay, Chimney!
Sanji may seem rude
from time to time,
but he'd never really
be mean to a girl.
That's true!
He's not the type of man
who would ever
let down a lady in need.
Aw, come on.
Robin, I---
[BOTH giggle]
Then it's settled.
Be good, Chimney!
Do whatever Sanji says, okay?
[CHIMNEY] Okay!
[ROBIN] Bye!
No way!
[SANJI] Why'd they
have to put it that way!
My date plans are ruined!
[SANJI]
Well, it's a lady's request.
So, you know where
we can get something
good to eat around here?
[CHIMNEY] All right!
[GONBE] Meow! Meow!
--[SANJI] Lead the way!
--[CHIMNEY and GONBE] Yeah!
[LUFFY] Sanji's Shock!
Mysterious Old Man and
His Super Yummy Cooking!
[SANJI] You sure
this is the right place?
Doesn't look like there's
much food around here.
[CHIMNEY] Yep!
It's a place run by
a friend of Granny's!
[SANJI]
A friend of Kokoro's, huh?
I gotta say, even though
your cooking is really good,
Grandpa's cooking
is way, way better!
Meow!
Oh? Is that so?
[CHIMNEY] Ah! There it is!
That boat at the
bottom of the stairs!
Man, did that food
taste weird or what?
Yeah, sorry--I heard this
place was s'posed to be good.
And here I thought
I was finally gonna get
[CITIZEN 319A]
a decent meal around here.
[CITIZEN 319B] I know, right?
Tastes weird?
[CHIMNEY] Step! Step! Step!
Here we are!
--[CHIMNEY giggle]
--[GONBE] Meow!
Hey! Grandpa Cook!
Make us something to eat!
This drunk old man
can really cook?
You sure this is the right guy?
Hey! I'm hungry!
Wake up!
Meow!
[sighs] Just let him sleep.
He's got ingredients, so I'll
prepare something myself.
I gotta say, he's got a
really nice kitchen here.
Hungry! Hungry! I'm hungry!
I thought he was
just an old drunk,
but these knives are nice.
He might be good after all.
[SANJI] Here we go!
[snoring]
Uh?
Sorry, old man.
I started helping myself.
[CHIMNEY]
Good morning, Grandpa Cook!
[GONBE] Meow!
Hey, kid. That's an interesting
cutting technique there.
Where'd you learn how to
do something like that?
Ah. I learned when I was
working on the Baratie.
It's ready. Here you go.
All right! Thanks a lot!
[CHIMNEY] Delicious!
Heh! I'm guessing you're
Zeff's apprentice, then?
No way! You mean you know
that worthless old geezer?
There's no mistaking
that knife technique.
That kid Zeff used to cut
things the exact same way.
"Kid," huh?
That "kid" used to be
the captain of a
pirate crew, you know.
Heh! To me,
he's nothing but a kid,
and that's all he'll ever be!
[chuckles]
So, what the heck
are you doing way out here
in Water 7, anyway?
Did you get tired
of Zeff's attitude
and run away
from his restaurant?
No, it's not that.
I'm searching for the All Blue.
The All Blue, huh?
[SANJI] Yeah, if the waters
there have marine life
from all over the world,
that means they have
the best ingredients, too.
In order to find it, I set
sail and became a pirate.
[laughs]
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Crazy, right?
I suppose you think it's a
legend, just like everyone else.
[OLD COOK] No, sir. It exists.
Huh?
If you're a true cook,
you must have seen it
at least once in your dreams.
If you're determined
and motivated,
there's no place in
the world you can't reach.
[sighs]
[OLD COOK] You're not the first.
Since that legend was born,
many have searched for
that miraculous place.
It's a cruel sea
that destroys the dreams
of those who seek
to discover it.
[SANJI] Hold on a sec.
Sounds like you're awfully
familiar with all of this stuff!
Old man, have you
actually been there?
Did you... find the All Blue?
No, I didn't.
[SANJI]
Don't tease me like that!
I was simply describing
the picture of it
I had in my mind
in my younger days.
Then you should have
said so from the start. Jeez.
You're off your rocker, old man.
Come on! I'm already
out of sake again?
That was amazing!
Meow!
Take it. As payment for
letting us use your kitchen.
Heh. Thanks! Much obliged!
[SANJI] All right, you two.
Let's start heading back.
Awe... But I'm still hungry!
Meow!
[SANJI] What? You're like a
couple of bottomless pits.
[laughs] Hey, kid. Hold on.
To show my gratitude
for the sake,
let me make you some food.
[SANJI] Aw, don't do that.
Feed me!
Meow!
[OLD COOK] Don't be
so polite! It's no problem!
[SANJI] Whoa!
Take it easy there, gramps!
Listen! I'm the best chef
in the whole darn city
and you're gonna--
[groans]
[SANJI] Come on! Don't
get so worked up!
I've got a good doctor
on my crew who can
take a look at--
Don't do that yourself!
[OLD COOK] Oh. Heh.
He can barely stand up! Is he
really gonna try to cook?
Aye!
Aah!
[panting]
Hey... Seriously,
you don't have to do that.
Listen, if you'd like, I could--
Stop trying to
interfere, you brat!
What?
I was just trying to--
Stay on that side of the
counter and let me cook!
[SANJI] Fine. Whatever.
Have it your way.
[SANJI] You gotta be kidding.
Look at his hands shaking.
[SANJI] Forget the vegetables,
he's gonna chop his fingers off!
♪
[SANJI]
Not bad for a drunk old man.
--[OLD COOK] Here you go! Enjoy!
--Yay!
Thank you! Time to eat!
So good!
[SANJI] He's got skills,
I'll give him that.
But it didn't look like
he used a lot of seasoning.
What's wrong, kid?
You scared it's gonna taste bad?
Not at all.
I appreciate
any food given to me.
Thanks so much for making it.
[SANJI] This stuff is amazing!
[SANJI] Our cooking
styles were the same.
Our ingredients were the same.
But the flavor!
Why does his taste so damn good?
Hey, what's the matter, kiddo?
You never had food
this tasty before?
--Thanks again, Grandpa!
--Meow, meow, meow!
[SANJI] No, actually.
So are you able to pinpoint
what makes it so delicious?
No, I'm not.
[chuckling]
That's too bad.
I'm disappointed in you, kid.
If you can't understand
something as basic as that,
the All Blue might just be
out of your reach forever.
Chimney. Gonbe.
[SANJI]
Wait here for a bit. Okay?
--All right.
--Meow!
I'll find that secret flavor.
No matter how long it takes me!
[chuckling]
[SANJI] If it's not about
the cooking or the ingredients,
then there's gotta
be something else!
Well! Unless I'm mistaken,
you're the cook from
the Straw Hat crew, right?
How may I help you?
[SANJI] These spices...
Are they the only ones you have?
Yeah.
We're a little short
on stock, unfortunately.
That's not it.
That's not it, either.
[SANJI] You sure you
don't have anything else?
Yep, pretty sure!
Water 7 is more
of a trading town.
So we're not really
known for our own exports.
That would include
any seasonings.
[SANJI] No luck at all.
Maybe that old geezer makes
some kind of spice himself.
What if I combine--
No, that's not right.
Dammit! What is it?
Hey, Sanji!
That's strange.
Believe it or not,
I don't think he noticed us.
That is strange.
Maybe he's playing
some kind of game
with Chimney and Gonbe.
Didn't realize I'd
wandered this far.
What a mess.
Man, Aqua Laguna really
did a number on this place.
[SANJI] Looks like
Galley La's helping out.
Hey! It's that guy
from the Straw Hat crew!
Thanks again
for the great party!
We appreciate it!
Right! That's enough for now!
Let's take a break
and have some lunch, okay?
[SHIPWRIGHTS] Yeah!
[SHIPWRIGHT 319B]
I've been waiting for this!
Delicious!
Care to join us?
We're more than happy to share!
He's the cook of the Straw Hats!
He's got a refined palate!
I'm sure he doesn't
want any of this stuff!
My apologies!
[laughing]
Well, actually, I'd love to!
All this running
around and thinking
has built up an appetite!
[SHIPWRIGHT 319B]
Oh! Then please, join us!
You can go ahead and
have as much as you'd like!
[SANJI] Sounds good.
You Straw Hats are
legendary around here.
You broke into Enies Lobby
and lived to tell about it.
Bet the government loves you!
[SHIPWRIGHT 319B] Whoa.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Are you all right?
Do they taste weird?
I bet that cranky old man
added something strange
to these rice balls
while he was
drunk out of his mind.
Wait a minute!
Are you saying these rice balls
were made by that old
geezer on the food boat?
Yeah, he did!
What's the problem?
If something's wrong with them,
take it up with him!
Nothing's wrong.
I just think I discovered
the secret of his flavor!
I'm so glad I tasted this!
Thanks a lot!
You've helped me
more than you'll ever know!
[CHIMNEY] Your turn!
Meow!
[OLD COOK shushing]
[SANJI] Old man!
I think I found my answer.
Don't scare me like that!
Welcome back,
Mister Pirate Cook!
Meow, meow!
Right. Listen.
That unique flavor of yours
doesn't come from
any sort of special spice.
The secret?
It comes from the very
basis of all seasoning.
From salt.
Those rice balls you made
for the Galley La workers,
they had the same flavor.
So is he right?
Basically, yes.
But there's a bit more
to it than that.
The problem is even after
everywhere I've sailed,
I've never come across
a salt quite like this one.
[SANJI] It's not
a matter of quality.
There's something fundamentally
different about it.
So why does
such a unique salt
seem to exist
only on this island?
The answer is simple.
It's Aqua Laguna.
That storm is troublesome,
there's no doubt about it.
But as it grows,
its waves carry minerals
from seas all around the world,
making a unique seawater.
[SANJI] And a salt made
from all of those minerals
would be equally as unique.
That is your secret.
You got it!
That's the answer, kid!
[SANJI]
But that's not the end of it.
In order to make salt,
you need a
whole lot of seawater.
But here, the seawater
you're extracting it from
comes in on a storm.
There's gotta be
some special method
to do something like that.
Listen to me.
I always want my crew
to eat the very best food.
Not only should it be
healthy and nourishing,
it should be delicious, too.
[SANJI] I know it's
your own special recipe,
and I have no right
to ask, but please!
I need to know the
secrets of your salt!
My, my.
Lovely weather we're
having today, isn't it?
[SANJI] Yeah.
[OLD COOK] Each year,
right after Aqua Laguna,
we're blessed with
beautiful, sunny weather.
There's a place
close by I'd like to go.
You think maybe
you could take me there?
I guess, but why?
Up there.
I'd like you to take me to
the rooftop of that building.
Okay.
[SANJI]
This the right spot, Old Man?
[OLD COOK] Yep.
Oh! Looks like it's ready!
What's ready?
The salt? Stop kidding around.
[OLD COOK]
No, I'm serious. Look.
This is where it comes from.
Aqua Laguna rolls in
and covers all the rooftops.
[OLD COOK] After a while,
when the storm finally recedes,
the salt left behind from those
giant-sized waves starts to dry.
[OLD COOK] After it completely
dries up, what remains is this.
Of course! I get it!
It makes perfect sense, but--
hey, wait a minute!
Are you saying every
rooftop in Water 7
is covered with this stuff?
[OLD COOK] That's right!
Nothing special about this one.
Every roof in the
city's the same way.
The salt is dry
and ready for use.
Incredible!
There's so much of it!
Hey, kid.
Don't forget:
Not just any seawater
could've created salt like this.
Only one sea in the world
could've combined
all these elements.
The All Blue.
Look at you!
Quite a haul you've got there!
Is all of that salt?
Meow!
There's still a long
journey ahead of us.
I need this to last.
Oh, and I was curious.
When we first
arrived at your boat,
there were two men walking away
complaining about the food.
[CITIZEN 319A] Man, did that
food taste weird or what?
Yeah. Those two.
I remember.
[CITIZEN 319A] Hey! Old Man!
[CITIZEN 319A]
Think you can make me
some more of that
food I had earlier?
[CITIZEN 319A] I thought it
tasted kind of weird at first,
but I haven't been able
to stop thinking about it!
Guess I wasn't
used to the flavor.
That doesn't make
any sense to me at all.
This happens from
time to time with sailors.
These boys get so used to
eating bad food on their ships,
it becomes the expectation.
Then their taste buds
awaken again
and they come back for more.
I think I'll take a double
order this time, please!
Come on, Old Man!
We're begging you!
[chuckling]
Hey, Old Man.
You've got some
amazing cooking skills.
Why do you stay hidden
away out here in Water 7?
[chuckling]
I can't bear to leave all
that delicious salt behind!
Kinda crazy, huh?
I see.
Well, for what it's worth,
the next time
I come through here,
I'll bring you some directly
from the All Blue itself.
Sounds good! I'm gonna
hold you to that, kid!
[PRETTY GIRL 319A] Hey Gramps!
Good to see you!
Is your shop open?
Yes!
It's always open
for you lovely ladies!
[PRETTY GIRLS]
You're such a cutie!
Water 7 has the best women!
Nothing like them
anywhere in the world!
Beautiful!
That's the real reason
you won't leave, you pervert!
[CHIMNEY]
Thanks for everything today,
Mister Pirate Cook.
I had a blast!
[GONBE]
Meow!
I'm the one who should
be grateful to you.
If you hadn't taken me
to that old man, I--
Huh?
Nothing. Nevermind, Chimney.
[CHIMNEY giggles]
We're gonna head on back
and meet up with Granny.
See you later!
Meow!
Okay!
Goodnight! Be careful!
[SANJI] Is that Usopp?
What's that? Really?
You want me to rejoin
your crew, do you?
Well, I understand.
It must be rough without me.
If I'm not around,
things really start to
fall apart, don't they?
Okay, then.
If you insist, I'll rejoin
the Straw Hat Pirates.
Yeah. That does seem to be
the best way to go about it.
Then that makes 23 scenarios.
Hey, Chopper!
Nice weather we're having, huh?
Let's go fishing!
Hey, Luffy! Care to join us?
Yeah, not bad.
And there's always the
"just pretend
like nothing happened
and hop onboard
the ship" strategy.
What else?
[USOPP] "I've decided to set
out on my own to visit Elbaf!"
"No! Please don't go!
We need you to stay!"
"I was just kidding!
I totally understand not
wanting to live your lives
without me."
"So, does that mean
you're staying, Usopp?"
Of course I will, dummies!
Man, I didn't know
anybody could love someone
as much as you guys love me!
What the hell's he doing?
What an idiot.
[SANJI] And dinner is served!
[LUFFY] Whoa!
[LUFFY] It's even more
yummier than usual!
[CHOPPER] This flavor's amazing!
I'll say!
Delicious!
[LUFFY] Man!
This is super tasty!
Hey, Sanji?
[SANJI] Yeah?
Thank you so much!
This food is incredible!
Thank you, Sanji!
So... Who wants seconds?
Me! Fill 'er up, Eyebrows!
You can get more
food your damn self!
Over here!
Me, too!
[NAMI] Count me in!
[ROBIN] I'd like more, as well!
[SANJI] Coming right up!
[OLD COOK] Kid, the unknown
seas are waiting for you!
[ZAMBAI] Straw Hat!
We've got bad news!
Have you seen
the wanted posters?
[LUFFY] Whoa!
They're finally out?
[ZAMBAI] You've got a huge
bounty on your head, Straw Hat!
The whole crew is wanted!
They're gonna
hunt you down for sure!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Everyone Finally Has A Bounty!
A Pirate Group
Worth Over 600 Million!
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!