[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are
turning on each other.
The once green city of
Erumalu now lies in ruins.
To stop the rebel army,
Luffy and company now
head into the desert,
seeking the oasis town of Yuba.
[LUFFY] "Adventure in
the Country of Sand!
The Monsters that Live
in the Scorching Land!"
[LUFFY groaning]
I'm burning up.
I don't think can't
even sweat anymore.
Will you please spare us
the melodramatics, Luffy?
You're only gonna
wear yourself out.
[LUFFY groans]
Gee, I guess he's not listening.
[CHOPPER groaning]
Can't go on.
Can't take hot weather.
I'm fine in cold weather.
It's because of all that fur.
Why don't you take off that
stupid reindeer costume?
What did you just say
to me, big nose?!
Don't make fun of reindeer!
Monster!
Chopper!
Don't turn yourself big,
or I'm gonna quit pulling you.
Who are you callin' a monster,
you bird‐nosed freak?
You better take it easy on the
nose, or I'll have to get tough!
Turn small, will ya?
Hey, the desert doesn't
seem to bother you much, Vivi.
Well, I was born and
raised in this country,
so I guess you could
say I'm used to it.
[USOPP] So... what's
with all these hills?
I was expecting a desert
to be more flat.
[LUFFY]
Ugh!
[VIVI]
This is a very old desert.
Some of the sand dunes here
are over 900 feet high.
Nine hundred feet? Oh my God.
No. That's... Ugh.
That's a mountain!
[LUFFY]
So hot. Water.
[NAMI] Just one drink, Luffy.
Just one mouthful.
Don't drink so much!
Idiot! You'd better save some
of that water for Usopp!
Hold on! You just had some!
I'm next! Gimme...
Stop it, you guys!
You're only going to
wear yourselves out
if you keep it up!
[LUFFY]
Hey, she started it!
[NAMI]
It's your fault!
[USOPP]
It's always his fault!
[LUFFY]
I'm so hungry.
[SANJI] Don't be such a
greedy pig. It's still raw!
Don't eat that!
Your dinner will be ready
in just a minute, Nami!
Hey, that looks good!
‐‐Can we eat?
‐‐Get away from that!
Ah! Jerk! We're starving!
Give us food!
Back off!
What happened?
It was so hot all day and now
all of a sudden it's freezing!
I know it seems strange,
but it's caused by the
lack of cloud cover here.
With nothing to
act as insulation,
it's scorching by day
and freezing by night.
The desert is full of
unpredictable dangers.
[sighs]
Just look at all those stars!
[USOPP] Couldn't you see
stars back on your island?
The skies of the Winter Islands
are almost always covered
by heavy snow clouds,
so I've never been able
to see this many before!
I am way too cold to
enjoy the stars right now.
Cold weather doesn't bother me!
That's because you wear
such a nice fur coat.
Back off!
It's not my fault you're
all soft and fluffy.
Quit making fun of me!
[USOPP yells]
Monster!
[ZORO]
Chopper, don't turn big.
We have to huddle for warmth.
[LUFFY]
Yahoo!
So warm!
[USOPP]
Cuddle closer!
[LUFFY]
See? Isn't this cozy?
[CHOPPER]
Yeah...
[VIVI] I suppose you're
surprised, aren't you?
I mean, by Luffy, that is.
I have to admit, I was a little
surprised too, at first.
After all, he doesn't
seem very much
like a pirate captain, does he?
I mean, normal pirate captains
are respected or feared
by their crews.
Just this afternoon,
a simple drink of water
led to that big fight.
Well, I think that's just
the way Luffy does things.
Took me a while
to understand that.
He's been like that as
long as I can remember.
Huh?
[ACE] He hasn't changed
a bit since he was a kid.
He seems like a fool,
but people have always
gathered around him.
He may be my little brother,
but he has this mysterious
charm about him.
[VIVI] I guess I wasn't
telling you anything
you didn't already know.
He and I do go way
back, you know.
But I appreciate it.
[BOTH snoring]
[ACE] You thought I was worried
about him, didn't you?
[VIVI] Yes. But I guess my
concern was a little misguided.
[LUFFY]
Ah! I found a shrimp!
You sure it's a
shrimp? That's neat!
[USOPP] But shrimp don't
live in the desert!
Look!
I stand corrected.
It's a desert shrimp.
Looks yummy!
[USOPP]
Ha. I wonder if it's edible.
[LUFFY] Why not? Crawfish
are edible, aren't they?
[CHOPPER] I've never seen
a real live shrimp before!
This is really exciting!
[VIVI screams]
Luffy, are you crazy?
Get rid of that thing, quick!
Nuh‐uh. That would be wasteful.
It's a scorpion!
Don't let its small
size fool you,
the poison in its stinger
can kill in seconds!
Really? I guess I don't
want it, then. You?
Hey, now, keep that
away from me!
Yeah, okay.
[VIVI] I'm sorry. I should've
mentioned it earlier.
[USOPP]
That's for sure!
What's wrong? What's
goin' on, Chopper?
Something's coming. And quick.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[USOPP]
Something? Like what?
Huh. It looks like the
wind is picking up.
[gasps]
Everyone!
Hide behind the rocks, quick!
How come?
[VIVI]
A sandstorm is coming!
[ACE]
Ah...
[LUFFY]
Whoa! Now that's cool!
Okay. Enough with
the sand already.
I'm not impressed anymore.
[VIVI] I should've
mentioned it earlier!
Sandstorms are another
of the desert's dangers!
[USOPP] You've gotta start
remembering this stuff!
[ACE]
Hm?
What the hell was that?
Can't a guy sleep in?
[USOPP coughing]
[USOPP]
Damn it, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Hey, Sanji!
Let's have one of
those box lunches!
[SANJI]
Not yet. Not until Vivi says so.
Come on, Vivi, how 'bout it?
Lets eat! Doesn't
that sound good?
But we're not even a tenth
of the way to Yuba, Luffy,
and we have to make our
supplies last the whole way.
Don't be silly, Vivi. Haven't
you heard the old proverb?
"Make sure you eat
whenever you're hungry!"
Oh, quit makin' things
up, you big fat liar!
Okay, if you're that hungry,
I'll tell you what,
why don't we stop and eat
at the next group of
rocks we come to?
All right, rocks it is!
Onward to the next
group of rocks!
'Kay, guys, whoever wins
at rock‐paper‐scissors
has to carry everybody's stuff!
[USOPP]
Quit deciding things!
Don't you mean the
loser carries the stuff?
And ready... go!
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
[SANJI]
Wait!
[NAMI]
Now just hold on!
[ZORO]
Hey! You started late!
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
I win!
[NAMI]
Idiot.
[LUFFY]
Heavy... So heavy...
Why am I doin' all the work?
[SANJI]
You said the winner carries all.
Now shut up and haul.
[NAMI] Make sure you
don't drop anything!
Hey, guys! I spotted
rocks, dead ahead!
You mean it?
It's lunch time! Let's eat!
Whoa! That's so fast!
[LUFFY]
Shade! It feels so good!
[groaning]
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[gasps]
Hey! Say something!
I'll go get you a doctor!
I need help!
[USOPP] That's weird.
Why is he coming back?
There's a whole flock of injured
birds here that can't move!
We need a doctor! Chopper!
[LUFFY]
All right! Let's go, Chopper!
[CHOPPER]
Coming!
[LUFFY]
We gotta help those birds!
What birds?
Wait a minute, Luffy,
those birds might not be
what you think they are!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[LUFFY yells]
[ZORO]
All of our stuff is gone!
[NAMI]
We've been had!
But I saw them!
There was a whole flock of
dying birds lying right there!
I'm so sorry. I should've
mentioned this earlier.
Warusagi birds are desert
bandits that deceive travelers
and steal their belongings.
[LUFFY]
You've gotta be kidding!
You mean these birds play dead?
What a lousy buncha crooks!
[VIVI]
This is all my fault!
Those birds tricked me!
Luffy, you dolt, is that all
you have to say for yourself?
There were three days' worth
of supplies in those packs,
and you just had to go and
let a bunch of stupid birds
rob us blind in the
middle of a desert!
How are we supposed to
get across this wasteland
without food or water?
I hope you're proud of yourself!
Come on, it's not my fault.
I mean, they outsmarted me!
You mean you're
dumber than a bird?
What's that?
Knock it off, you two!
[SANJI]
No, you're not that smart!
Just save your energy.
At times like this, it's better
just to let them have it out.
[SANJI]
You're just a moron!
Fine with me.
Let's just take a break.
This heat is just startin' to
wear on everybody's nerves.
I'm sure we'll manage
food‐ and water‐wise.
It's nothin' that'll
kill us right away.
Let's put it out of
our minds for now.
Yeah, that's a good idea,
because when I think about
it, I get really thirsty.
[CHOPPER]
Mh‐hm.
[cawing]
‐‐[LUFFY yells]
‐‐[SANJI gasps]
Give us our stuff
back, you thieves!
[WARUSAGI BIRDS laughing]
No, Luffy! Don't chase them!
That idiot.
[NAMI] Wait! Will you be
able to find your way back?
[USOPP]
Get back here, you dope! Luffy!
[LUFFY panting]
[LUFFY] Stop! You can't
get away from me!
[LUFFY]
Get back here!
I said come back!
[LUFFY]
What is this?
What is this thing?
A mystery desert plant?
Man, that is so cool!
[grunting]
[LUFFY]
Huh?
What are you doing?
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY]
That's funny!
Huh? You want me to help you?
'Kay, Gum‐Gum...
...Pistol!
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY] Good thing you
didn't get eaten, huh?
Dammit, it those
stupid birds got away
while I was busy beatin' up
these mystery plants!
The desert sure is full
of strange creatures.
So, pal, how'd you manage
to get stuck out in the desert
all by yourself?
Hm? What's wrong?
[roaring]
Did you see somethin' out there?
[LUFFY]
What the heck is that?
Come on, Luffy. Hurry it up!
Um, you don't suppose he
could be lost, do you?
He has absolutely no
sense of direction,
but he's always running off.
And there are still so
many desert dangers
I haven't had a chance
to warn him about yet.
Not to mention the
moron was hungry,
so you know he's
not thinking straight.
That guy is so hopeless.
You can say that again.
[ACE]
I'm sorry.
I know my brother
can be a flake.
I apologize.
[USOPP]
Good luck finding him!
[SANJI]
Yeah.
[CHOPPER]
What's that?
What on earth is that rumbling?
[LUFFY laughing]
[USOPP]
Is it another sandstorm?
No, wait. That looks like‐‐
[USOPP gasps]
It's Luffy!
Oh, no. It can't be!
[NAMI]
Huh?
Why is he on a camel?
[BOTH screaming]
Someone wanna tell me what
the hell's chasing him?
I can't really tell,
but it looks like there's
something in the sand
burrowing after him!
[LUFFY screaming]
[USOPP, CHOPPER,
VIVI, NAMI screaming]
What is that?
It's a Sandora Dragon!
[USOPP]
It's a what?
[VIVI]
A Sandora Dragon!
They're the biggest reptile
that lives in the desert!
They wait under the
sand for their prey,
and then ambush them!
They have razor sharp
fangs and claws,
but they hardly ever use them.
Because they're so
incredibly huge,
they usually just end up
swallowing their victims whole!
I gotta admit, that boy
does have a talent
for attracting trouble.
Right, and all of us have
the scars to prove it.
What kinda crap
star was he born under
to attract trouble like that?
[LUFFY] Stop, camel,
you're going too fast!
[ZORO]
Is he too much for you, Luffy?
[SANJI]
We'll lend a hand!
Thanks, guys! I brought home
a little somethin' for dinner!
Gum‐Gum...
‐‐[ZORO] Tatsu...
‐‐[SANJI] Epaule...
‐‐[LUFFY] ...Whip!
‐‐[ZORO] ...Maki!
[SANJI]
...Shoot!
[ALL gasp]
[roars]
You didn't have to go that far!
Whenever those guys fight,
it almost makes me feel
sorry for the monsters!
[CHOPPER]
Huh?
[USOPP, CHOPPER screaming]
Another one?
I'm sorry, I guess I must've
forgotten to mention
that Sandora Dragons
always hunt in pairs!
[USOPP, CHOPPER, NAMI]
Get with it!
[ACE]
Hm?
Ace!
Look out!
Lotta pests in these deserts.
You wanna play?
Well, all right,
if that's what you want.
This is convenient.
These rocks are just like
a natural frying pan.
[ZORO]
So, now that we have a moment,
what's the deal with the camel?
[LUFFY]
I dunno.
It was gettin' eaten
by the mystery plants
while I was chasin' those birds.
[NAMI]
It's obviously not a wild camel.
[VIVI] No, not with
a saddle and bridle.
[CHOPPER]
Uh?
Yeah! It is you!
[CHOPPER]
Really? Good for you!
Wait, so you guys
know each other?
[CHOPPER]
Uh‐huh!
He gave me a ride when
I escaped from Katorea!
[USOPP]
Hm?
He's a passenger‐carrying camel?
That's sure gonna
make things lots easier!
Yeah, that oughtta
be a real help.
It looks like he
could carry two.
Camels do go hand‐in‐hand
with deserts.
Great, I'll take
the first shift.
[LUFFY]
Ow!
"I'm a freedom‐loving,
hard‐boiled, yet compassionate,
son of the desert!
I'm very grateful to you
for having helped me
outta that jam back there,
and I'll be glad to give
some of you a ride,
but I'm afraid I don't accept
male passengers!"
[USOPP] Yeah, at least
give Chopper a ride!
[CHOPPER]
"I'm too macho!"
[USOPP] Why you! Why, I oughtta
punch you in the nu‐‐!
[NAMI]
I'm so sorry that my crewmates
are a bunch of ill‐bred louts!
Now, what should we call you,
you great big
precious camel, you?
[LUFFY]
Idiot!
[SANJI]
Moron!
[USOPP]
Doofus!
"Eyelash" it is then!
[ZORO]
Uh, how'd you arrive at that?
[NAMI]
Okay! Climb on, Vivi!
No, I'm fine. I can
still walk. Thanks.
Just get on.
[LUFFY]
Pervert camel!
[USOPP, SANJI, LUFFY]
Pervert camel! Pervert camel!
This is great.
We should be able to
make better time now!
We need to get to Yuba
as fast as we can
so we'll be able to talk
to the rebel army.
Giddyup, Eyelash!
[ALL]
Hey, wait for us!
[NAMI]
Hurry up, guys!
If you get separated, you'll
never leave the desert alive!
[USOPP]
Well, thanks a lot!
[SANJI]
I like this side of Nami too!
[ZORO]
What else is new?
[ACE]
After them! Hurry!
[ZORO]
Chopper! Hop on!
[CHOPPER]
Right!
[BOYS]
Wait for us!
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[LUFFY]
Ugh... So hot!
[SANJI]
Nami! Where are you?
[USOPP]
We're completely separated now!
[ZORO]
Hey, has anyone seen Ace lately?
[CHOPPER]
Do you think he got lost?
[LUFFY] My big brother‐‐
nothin' but trouble!
[USOPP]
Hey, what's that?
[ZORO]
Do you see Nami?
[USOPP] A ship!
A pirate ship in the sand!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Enter the Desert Pirates!
The Men Who Live Freely!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!