[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!♪
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
Hey! Apis, where'd you
put all the pork buns?
[APIS]
Stay back! Don't come near!
Wait a minute.
I thought Lost Island sank
into the sea a long time ago.
Lost Island will surface
again eventually.
Grandpa Ryu was absolutely
certain about that.
Grandpa believes the island
will reappear any day now.
But he can no longer
remember where it used to be.
It's not his fault.
Grandpa's just gotten old
and lost the energy to fly.
But I have to make sure Grandpa
Ryu gets back to his home,
no matter what it takes.
It's the only way to save him.
I'll find a way to
get him there,
no matter if it takes
me a lifetime!
Right! If he wants to go home,
then I'll take him!
[APIS]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
To Lost Island!
Luffy! Wake up!
You can't take him home!
Lost Island sank into
the sea. Remember?!
Look at him. This is a
legendary Millennial Dragon.
He really exists, which
means Lost Island does too!
Luffy, the island sank!
I know! Let's go find it.
[LUFFY] "Eric Attacks! Great
Escape From Warship Island!"
It sure is hot. Huh?
What the heck is that?
The Marines again?!
[LUFFY] Guys, you're not gonna
believe what we saw!
It's so cool!
[NAMI]
Um, what's going on?
The 1200th king... was succeeded
by the 1201st, and then the...
Oh, brother. His story
still isn't over?
Rise and shine, sleepy‐head!
[USOPP screams]
What the...?
Were we here all night?
[SANJI]
Guess so.
With that old guy rambling on,
we must have all
just dozed off.
[VILLAGER 2]
Bokuden!
We've got trouble!
Apis, where is she?
What's the matter?
[VILLAGER 2]
Y‐You're those pirates, right?
A Marine fleet just arrived!
They're blockading the harbor
and coming ashore!
Oh, no! We've got to get
to Apis before they do!
Why are the Marines
after a little girl?
Guys, I need you to come
with me right now! Let's go!
[SANJI]
With pleasure, Nami!
[LUFFY]
We gotta go now?
[NAMI]
Yes! Move!
[ZORO]
What do we do with the old man?
[NAMI] Well... it looks
like he's sound asleep,
so I think we should
just leave him be.
Hey, when he wakes up,
tell him not to worry.
We'll protect Apis
and keep her safe.
Yeah, all right.
[MARINE A]
Sir! The pirates!
Their ships been spotted
off our starboard bow!
Right! Listen up, men!
The landing party will
accompany me onto the island!
The rest of you will seize and
secure that ship! Understood?!
[chuckles]
Hey! You're all here!
Guys, this is one of
those Millennial Dragons
that Bokuden was talking about.
Hey! Let's see if he can fetch!
He's a dragon, not a puppy!
I guess the closer you
get to the Grand Line,
the more you run into
things like this.
Well, if things like those Sea
Kings we encountered can exist,
I guess anything's possible.
Oh no. Are we safe
around this thing?!
Will he try to eat us?!
Um, normally he doesn't eat
people, but he is forgetful.
If he starts acting like
you're food, get away quick.
Now you tell me!
It doesn't hurt though, does it?
[LUFFY chuckles]
Don't worry about it,
I think he likes you.
[USOPP] That's easy
for you to say, Luffy!
You're not the one with
your head in his mouth!
[ZORO]
Maybe we should let 'em eat you.
[USOPP]
Zoro!
[SANJI] And give this poor
thing food poisoning?
[LUFFY laughing]
[USOPP]
Why, you lousy! I oughta‐‐!
Anyways, this dragon is
the reason why the Marines
have been chasing after Apis.
We can't let the Marines
get their hands on him.
I brought you here because
we need to help Apis
take him back to his
home on Lost Island.
Are you nuts?!
In case you forgot, Nami,
the Marines are after us too!
With that blockade,
we're gonna have enough
trouble escaping ourselves,
let alone with a
ginormous lizard!
[APIS]
Please, listen!
Grandpa Ryu just
wants to go home.
Luffy said...
Wait, don't tell me.
Luffy said something like,
"Sure! We'll take him
to the Lost Island!"
[LUFFY]
Hey! How'd you know I said that?
Ah! You always
say stuff like that!
Without asking us first!
And without having a clue
how to find the place!
[LUFFY]
Ah, we'll work it out somehow.
Oh, please!
It's okay, Grandpa Ryu.
I'll find another way
to get you home,
and I won't let those
Marines get you.
The problem is we don't really
know where Lost Island is,
but the dragon should have
migratory instincts,
which'll help us find it.
Yeah! So what are we
waitin' for? Let's get goin!
But, Luffy‐‐
[ZORO]
Hey. Don't worry.
We'll work it out.
[USOPP]
Zoro!
I agree, but first things first.
How are we supposed to
bring our big friend here
down the mountain and
onto the Going Merry?
Heh. It's easy we're
gonna build a cart.
One big enough for Grandpa
Ryu to ride. Let's move.
[groans]
[APIS]
Thank you!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum... Gatling!
[LUFFY] Hmm...
Do you think that's enough?
Yep! That's good.
Well, I guess I better start
slappin' this thing together,
not that I have any real choice!
That's it, guys!
It's finally done!
[APIS]
It's so strong and sturdy
even Grandpa Ryu
couldn't break it!
[LUFFY]
Uh‐huh!
[LUFFY, APIS laughing]
Speaking of breaking,
how are we supposed to get
through that Marine blockade?
And back to the ship?
I dunno. We'll work
it out somehow.
[SANJI]
Yeah, but how?
[ZORO]
An attack?
You know, that's not a bad idea.
[NAMI]
Yeah, but that's impossible
with a giant dragon in tow.
I've got a better idea,
but it's gonna require more
stealth than strength.
One of us has to
go to the harbor,
sneak aboard the Going Merry,
and sail it to the
rear of the island.
[USOPP] Well, since my good,
personal friend Kaya
gave us the ship,
I should be the one to go!
[APIS]
He's so brave!
[USOPP] However,
Zoro is coming with me!
[ZORO]
Me? Why?
[NAMI]
That's fine by me.
[USOPP chuckles]
[USOPP] Great! Nightfall is
when we should move out, Zoro!
[NAMI]
No, now!
We're running out of time!
Get the ship and bring it
to the edge of that cape.
The one that looks
like your nose!
[LUFFY laughs]
Oh, that's funny!
It does look like his nose.
Okay, but that still
doesn't explain how you're‐‐
[NAMI]
Leave that to me.
This cave seems
pretty well‐hidden,
but those Marines will
find it sooner or later.
Get moving, you two!
[USOPP] For a navigator,
you sure give a lotta orders!
[NAMI] Sanji! Luffy! You guys
get Grandpa Ryu on the cart!
[LUFFY]
Right!
[SANJI]
Whatever you say, Nami!
[LT. COMMANDER]
All right, old man! Spit it out!
Tell us where you're
hiding this girl!
He was... followed by the‐‐
Hey! Old man!
Huh? Oh yes. Did I
mention the 1231st king?
Uh... What are
you talking about?
[MARINE B]
Lieutenant Commander!
We found some tracks!
Looks like something was
dragged from the backyard!
[LT. COMMANDER]
Eric! Those tracks, is it them?!
I'd say so, and they appear
to be pretty fresh.
They lead up that mountain.
That must be where
they're hiding.
[LT. COMMANDER] Then that's
where we're going! Move out!
[USOPP yelps]
See! This is exactly why I
wanted to come at night!
What the heck are you doing?!
Meet me on the deck.
[USOPP]
Hey, wait! Hold up!
[clunking]
[MARINE C]
Hm? Halt!
[USOPP] Ah! Help, Zoro.
Anybody help...
It's a pirate!
Stop him! Fire!
[MARINE C]
What the hell?!
[MARINE D] There must be another
pirate onboard that ship!
[MARINE E]
Hurry! They're getting away!
[MARINE F] The wind's pulling it
out to sea! Grab the ladder!
[MARINE C]
It's too late!
[MARINE D]
Dammit!
What the‐‐?!
They're trying to ram us!
All hands, evasive action!
[USOPP] What?! You're gonna
ram 'em?! Are you insane?!
[MARINES yelling]
[MARINE G]
It's headed right for us!
[MARINE H]
Unfurl the sails!
[MARINE I]
It's too late! Brace for impact!
Follow those pirates!
[MARINES]
Yes, Sir!
[OFFICER]
Hoist the anchor!
Unfurl the sails!
[OFFICER]
I want those pirates' heads!
[MARINES]
Yes, sir!
[NAMI]
Hmm...
They made it!
O‐Oh no!
The bird told me that the
Marines are closing in!
They didn't waste any time.
They got here quicker
than I thought.
What are we gonna do?!
They're getting close!
It'll be okay. Don't worry.
Remember, we've got
these two with us.
[NAMI] Plus, we're about
to get outta here.
We just have to wait until the
Going Merry's reached that cape.
[ERIC]
Hm?
There she is!
Ah! What is that thing?!
[MARINE K]
It's a monster!
[ERIC] Dragonite, the Elixir of
Immortality. I finally found it.
Don't panic, men!
That beast is the Millennial
Dragon we've been looking for.
We can take it! We'll sneak up
closer and get the drop on it!
Let's make Commodore
Nelson proud!
[MARINES]
Yes, Sir!
[USOPP]
Come on, you stupid thing!
Why'd you have to a ruin an
otherwise flawless escape?!
[ZORO]
We haven't escaped. Not yet.
[USOPP]
Huh? Ah!
Faster, men! Overtake
and board that vessel!
[USOPP] Ah! Zoro!
I'm gonna man the rudder!
You go take care of
the sail! Go! Go!
[ZORO]
Right! I'm on it!
Man, that ship may be as big
as a whale, but it's fast!
[gasps]
No! Stop! Please don't
shoot Grandpa Ryu!
Apis!
No, wait!
[MARINES gasp]
I had a feeling if we
followed that brat,
she might possibly lead us
to some Dragonite.
But I never expected
to encounter
a living, breathing
Millennial Dragon.
This is quite the surprise.
She is no longer of any
importance to us now.
That dragon is now our priority!
Within it lies the key
to immortal life.
Fire!
No! Don't shoot!
[LUFFY]
Back at ya!
[MARINE A]
What the hell was that?
[MARINE B]
How did he deflect the bullets?
I see you have
Devil Fruit powers.
Uh‐huh. I'm a rubber man.
[MARINE C]
Rubber man?
[MARINE D]
Devil Fruit?
[MARINE E]
What's that?
‐‐Use‐‐!
‐‐Use your swords men!
Bullets won't work
against rubber!
[MARINES yelling]
Sanji!
Never fear, Nami!
[LUFFY]
Gum‐Gum Gatling!
[MARINE T screams]
[ERIC]
Hmm...
You call yourselves Marines?
What a joke. The whole
lot of you are pathetic.
A knife?
I dunno.
My name's Eric the
Whirlwind, Straw Hats.
I was hired by Commodore
Nelson of Branch 8.
I have no business with you.
That Millennial Dragon,
on the other hand,
is a different story.
Stand aside.
If you don't, you'll fall
victim to my wind slash,
the power of the
Sickle Sickle Fruit.
[SANJI]
Did he say "Sicko Sicko"?
[LUFFY]
I think.
[SANJI]
What do we do?
[LUFFY]
I dunno.
Hey, Nami!
Can we go now?
[NAMI]
Not yet!
[SANJI] Nami's gorgeous even
when she's checking
on Zoro and Usopp's progress!
[LUFFY]
I wish they'd hurry up!
Hey! Straw Hats!
Are you listening?!
Did you hear what I said?!
Yeah, we heard you.
You're Eric, the Sicko.
[ERIC]
No! I said "sickle," you moron.
Sickle like the sharp thing
that cuts, not sicko!
[LUFFY] Well, we're already
"sicko" hearing you talk!
[LUFFY laughs]
[growls]
Let's see how
much you laugh
after you've gotten
a taste of this.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Sickle‐Sickle...
...Whirlwind!
What was that?!
His wind slash.
Creep really packs a punch.
[chuckles]
The winds I create
are just as sharp
as the keenest blades
in the world.
Even the fiercest fighters
don't stand a chance.
I can rip anyone to shreds
in a matter of seconds.
[ERIC laughing]
Let's get out of here!
Not yet! They're not ready.
Now, move it! That
dragon's mine! Stand down!
No way!
All right, don't move then.
It's your funeral, Rubber Boy.
What about now?! Well, Nami?!
[NAMI]
Finally! It's time!
Luffy! Sanji! Let's go!
We're on our way, Nami!
[ERIC]
What the‐‐?!
[SANJI]
We'll be right there!
Hey, Nami! This kick's
dedicated to you.
[APIS screaming]
[chuckles]
[ERIC]
No, you don't!
Now Gum‐Gum...
Sickle‐Sickle...
‐‐[LUFFY] Pistol!
‐‐[ERIC] Whirlwind!
Nice try.
[LUFFY]
Woohoo!
[APIS screaming]
We're gonna hit that rock!
Luffy!
And Gum‐Gum... Gatling!
This is stupid! It's crazy!
We're all gonna die!
Not if we keep our heads down!
[NAMI]
Take your own advice!
Yeah.
[LUFFY chuckles]
[LUFFY, APIS laughing]
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
Woo! Yeah!
[USOPP]
Nami wanted us to bring the ship
to the edge of that cape, right?
[ZORO]
That's what she said.
Just perfect!
We couldn't outrun 'em, huh?
[ZORO]
I guess not.
Well, I've been itchin'
for a fight anyway.
What the hell?! Ah!
‐‐[APIS] Faster! Faster!
‐‐[LUFFY] Woo!
[LUFFY]
Hold on!
[BOTH scream]
That crazy plan actually worked!
Well, he said he'd
work it out somehow!
[laughing]
I told ya so!
[laughs]
[OFFICER] After them!
Move! Capture that ship!
[MARINE Y] Sir, we can't!
Not with our main mast snapped!
And it's wedged against
the ship! We're stuck!
[OFFICER]
What?!
[USOPP]
That should do it.
[LUFFY]
Man, that ride was fun!
[APIS]
It sure was!
Sure you're okay
after that ride?
[APIS]
Mh‐hm.
Well, now that Grandpa
Ryu's all secure,
we can raise anchor.
Yeah!
We're goin' to Lost
Island, guys! Set sail!
[USOPP]
Uh‐huh. And where's that?
[LUFFY] Hmm...
That way? Or that way?
Or maybe it's behind us?
He wouldn't be able to find his
head if it wasn't screwed on.
Eh. We'll work
things out somehow.
I hope so 'cause
it's not on the charts.
Nami's gorgeous,
even when she doesn't
know where the ship is going!
[USOPP]
Oh, no.
[LUFFY] It's out there
somewhere, guys,
so let's go find Lost Island!
♪All that's in my
heart confuses me,
I cannot understand,
As I face what I must do,
I'll say goodbye
and squeeze your hand.
I'll set sail alone,
But always know
I'm gonna keep you near,
As I drift away,
I pray you watch me
as I disappear.
As I watch the sunrise,
I began to wonder,
What could be the reason,
It's so hot inside.
No answer has come,
But I can't get away
from what's true,
It's because of you...
Show me how to
catch those feelings,
Get 'em to come back to me,
I'll do what I must,
Because they're
everything I wanna be.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
And pull 'em back
from yesterday,
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we
can make the way.♪
[USOPP]
Just where is this Lost Island?!
[LUFFY] Grandpa Ryu's
sleeping, so be quiet.
[USOPP] Eh, some help
he turned out to be.
[NAMI]
It's not on any of the charts.
[USOPP] Agh! There's another
ship in front of us!
[NAMI] What the‐‐?!
That's the Going Merry!
[ZORO]
Hey, could this be it?
[SANJI] Is this it? Is this
the legendary Lost Island?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Solitary Island
in the Distant Sea!
The Legendary Lost Island!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!