You can say what you want.
If you wanna die,
or whatever, that's fine.
But when you say it,
you say it as part of our crew.
From now on,
leave everything to us!
Those fools braved
Aqua Laguna to get here.
They're determined,
if nothing else.
Humph. Either that,
or they're just lucky.
Remember, we have
permission to kill this time.
But if we kill them, it'll be
over before we have any fun.
The drawbridge?
Yeah. The Franky Family's trying
to get that under
control right now.
Once they bring it down,
we should be able to get to
the other side, no problem.
What a pain.
She's right there and
all we can do is wait.
Damn it.
What is her deal? She must be
hiding one hell of a secret.
Hey! CP9! Here are your orders!
Kill the intruders,
but only engage them
here at the Tower of Law!
My life and my promotion are the
most important things right now.
I have to be careful about this.
If I let all my
underlings run off,
who's gonna protect me
if something goes wrong?
Stupid pirates!
You may act tough,
but you don't know what
you're getting yourselves into!
Open your eyes!
Come on!
You don't think you can
beat all of CP9, do you?
And what about
the Gates of Justice?
You don't think you
can open them, do you?
Even then. If things
go wrong, I have this!
The Golden Transponder Snail,
giving me the authority
to issue a Buster Call!
A Buster Call?
Yes. That's right.
I'm sure you
remember its power well.
After all, it did destroy your
homeland 20 years ago.
What was it, "Ohara?"
Hard to recall the name
since it was wiped off the map!
Robin's homeland?
He's pissing me off.
There's no place left.
Nowhere for me
to go or return to.
Anything but that!
I'm begging you!
Ooh. Begging for mercy,
I like that!
What's wrong?
You don't want me to press this
and annihilate all your little
friends with a Buster Call?
Is that what you're saying?
You're insane.
If you push that button, do you
have any clue what will happen?
Of course I do!
This button will eliminate
any chance your friends
possibly have of
leaving this island alive!
All it takes is
one little press.
It couldn't be more simple!
If you think that, you
don't understand a thing!
Are all those old memories
coming back to you now?
Let's see.
Maybe I should
press it after all.
It might be fun.
This isn't a joke! Stop it!
I'm the one who makes
the demands here, wench.
You say Ohara was
wiped off the map,
but your map doesn't show you
the lives of the
people who lived there!
Your view of the
world is so distant
and so twisted that you've
lost sight of your humanity!
There's a limit to how
much you can sacrifice
in the name of justice.
A Buster Call is going too far.
You can't use it.
Anything but that.
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
All right, get her!
Nice throw! Wow!
Yeah! Bullseye!
Take that, monster girl!
Gross! You're so creepy!
Monster! Monster!
The monster girl hit me!
She's scary!
You'll be sorry!
Hey, you!
My kids came home crying because
you hit them on the head!
What are you thinking,
acting like that?
You stay away from
them, you hear me?
Don't you have anything
to say for yourself?
You really are a little
monster, aren't you?
Hey! You come back here!
I'm not done talking
with you yet!
Mommy, mommy, what're we
having for dinner tonight?
Well, what would you like?
Um-- um--Rice omelet!
You sure like rice omelets, huh?
Yep!
Then we'll pick up some
eggs on the way home, okay?
Okay!
Sorry I'm home so late.
Hello, is anyone there?
Aunt Roji?
"To Robin. Today--
--as you must know, is
my little girl's birthday.
So the family is going out
for a special dinner tonight,
just the three of us.
We left some bread
out on the table,
so you can eat that for dinner.
Don't be too
greedy with the jam.
When you're done eating,
and before we come back,
I want you to do the dishes,
scrub the floors,
take the laundry inside,
and go straight to bed
as soon as you're
finished with your chores.
Mommy, mommy, what're
we having for dinner tonight?
Well, what would you like?
Um-- um--Rice omelet!
You sure like rice omelets, huh?
Yep!
Then we'll pick up some eggs
on the way home, okay?
Okay!
Oh! Look! Here comes Robin!
Seems she's stopping
by to return a book.
Everyone get in place, quick!
Hello? Professor Clover?
I finished the book you lent me.
One-- two--
Congratulations, Robin!
You're amazing, Robin!
A real genius!
We've got a cake
for you, by the way!
Robin. That doctoral exam
you took the other day,
you passed with a perfect score!
From this day forward, you
are an official archaeologist!
And since you're one of us now,
we can all work on our research
together, starting today!
Here, this proves
that you're a scholar.
Wear it with pride!
It looks great on you, Robin!
We're so proud!
Now listen up, you must
understand what it means
to be an Ohara archeologist.
Right!
I'm ready to learn!
Our knowledge, in particular,
comes from the past.
And this library, known
as the Tree of Knowledge,
has stood for over 5,000 years,
collecting countless documents
and literature from
every corner of the world.
This is a treasure for
all humanity to share
and nourish for
future generations.
As the world's largest library,
knowledge is our pride and joy.
Under the branches of this tree,
the finest archeologists from
every sea have gathered!
With this vast wealth of
information at our disposal,
there is no historical
mystery that cannot be solved!
Are you ready to join us?
Yes sir!
In that case, I look forward to
seeing your research take form,
and watching all
the contributions
you will make to the world.
Professor, what I'd
really like is to find out
what happened in
the "Blank Century"!
No! You can't!
I strictly forbid it,
just as I always have!
Huh? I don't get it.
If we want to solve the
mysteries of the world,
shouldn't we study
the Poneglyphs
to find out what
happened back then?
What?
How do you know about all that?
Did you use your powers to
peek on us in the basement?
I just--
Any attempt to decipher
or study the Poneglyphs
is considered a criminal act
by the World Government!
I see.
So that's why you
don't tell anybody.
That's why you study them
in the basement at night.
You were spying on us!
So how much do you know?
This is a very serious matter
we're dealing with here!
Explain yourself, Robin!
I know it's bad, but
even if I asked nicely,
you still wouldn't
let me join you!
That's why I studied so hard
to become an archeologist
because I thought then you would
finally treat me
like everyone else.
I just wanted to learn.
Robin.
I know this is hard.
You've studied with all
your heart and deserve
to be called a scholar as
much as anyone else here.
However, you're
also still a child.
If word gets out, then every
one of us could be put to death.
Harsh as that sounds,
it's something we're
willing to accept.
Since this became the law
of the world 800 years ago,
countless scholars
have lost their lives,
as many as there
are stars in the sky!
But we can't stop now,
and I'll tell you why.
Of all the scholars
who ever tried
to decipher the ancient texts,
we of Ohara are the only ones
who have met with any success.
For us, there is
no turning back.
I swear on the
Tree of Knowledge,
if you ever come close
to the basement again,
you will be forbidden
from entering the library or
conducting research with us!
You understand?
Robin!
I hate to say this,
especially now,
but she's just like her mom.
It's only a matter of time
before she uncovers
that secret, too.
Her mother Olvia was only
captured by Marines
a few days ago.
But it's already clear
what fate she'll suffer.
Wa-- water.
Wawater?
Perfect!
Guess I'm still alive after all.
I just wonder
if she's okay, too.
Anyhow, thank you for
your help, but I gotta ask--
is there a town or village
somewhere 'round here?
Mmhm.
That's a shame.
I 'spose beggars
can't be choosers,
but a deserted island
woulda been nice, y'know?
You can stare all you want,
but ain't nothing gonna happen.
As you can see, I hurt
my leg, so I'm stayin' put.
'Least for the time bein'.
After I feel a little better,
I'll build a raft or somethin'
to get me outta here.
This your first time
seeing a giant, Missy?
Yeah.
I'll tell you one thing,
I may be big as those guys from
Elbaf, but I sure ain't as mean.
Just as sure as
there's war-like giants,
there's peaceful ones, too.
Huh.
I know this is a long shot,
but I gotta ask anyway.
When you get home, you
think maybe you could--uh--
not tell anyone that a giant
washed up on the beach?
Okay, sure.
Well, that was too easy.
Of course you're
gonna tell people.
I said I wouldn't.
Yeah, you're tellin' a fib.
Ain't no way a kid can
keep a secret this big!
Don't worry about it.
I'm not really
interested in you.
Dereshishishi. Dereshishishi.
"Dereshi"? What does that mean?
It don't mean a darn thing!
I'm just laughing!
That's the way you laugh?
You sure are a
funny little girl!
You're the funny one!
I gotta admit,
all my life people been
tellin' me my laugh is silly.
But you, you're pretty
cute when you laugh!
You should do it more
often, I say! Dereshishishi.
Anyhow, I go by
the name of Saul.
Jaguar D. Saul, if you like.
"D"?
Yeah.
I don't much know what it
means but from what I hear,
everyone in my family has
it for their middle name.
Anyways, what about you?
My name's Robin.
I see.
Well, truth is, Robin, some guys
are chasing me down right now.
So, uh, if someone
finds me, I'm in trouble.
I said I wouldn't tell!
Good!
Here's another one.
Mighty kind of you, Robin, but
you go ahead and take this one.
My stomach's pretty full as-is.
As you can see, I caught
a real whopper last night.
Well, I better get back
to work on that raft.
Should be done
pretty soon at this rate.
I don't mean to pry,
but it seems like you have an
awful lot of time on your hands.
Not that I don't
like your company,
but you've been sticking
with me for days now.
Ain't your parents and
friends gonna get suspicious?
I don't have any parents.
Actually, I do have a mom,
but she set sail for work
years ago and never came back.
I don't even remember her face.
I'm sort-of-friends with the
archaeologists around here,
but they won't let me
join in on their research,
so I don't know anymore.
The other kids say I'm creepy,
so even if I wanted
to play with them,
I don't think
that they'd let me.
Ah, so you have
Devil Fruit powers, huh?
You aren't scared of me?
I used to sail all over the
Grand Line back in the day.
I've seen plenty of folks with
powers tons scarier than yours.
To be honest, I'm kinda jealous
of your little arm thing.
It looks pretty handy!
Dereshishishi. Dereshishishi.
That laugh of
yours is really weird!
Dereshishishi.
It don't matter if
your laugh's weird,
all that really matters,
is when you laugh,
all of a sudden,
your problems disappear!
Why?
What d'you mean "why?"
Everyone knows you laugh
when you're having fun, right?
So if you're not having fun,
all you need to do is laugh
and everything'll
work out just fine!
You're just a kid,
but it seems like you're
having a tough time.
When you're feelin'
down, just laugh.
There ain't nothin'
a good laugh can't fix.
It seems awfully silly
to laugh when you're sad.
Don't knock it tell you try it!
Here. "Dereshishi!"
Do it just like that and I bet
you'll feel better in a flash!
Deresh!
Not bad! Now, with more gusto!
Dereshishishishi!
Dereshishishi!
Now that's more like it!
This is Navy Headquarters here.
Once again, we're hoping we
could speak to Chief Spandine.
You heard 'em, Chief. What now?
Ignore them.
They probably just
want a status report.
We'll contact them
when we see the shore.
That's good enough.
Ohara, Opera,
O-whatever, who cares?
Why are they wasting my time,
making me trek all the way out
here to the West Blue, huh?
Let's get this over with, then
get the hell outta this dump.
So wait, you said you don't
even remember your mom's face?
No, but I'd like to see her.
And is she an archaeologist
by any chance?
Yep. She's traveling in
search of the history
no one knows about.
Wa-wait a second.
What did you say
her name was again?
On the next One Piece:
"Fated Mother and Daughter!
The Mother's Name Is Olvia!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!