Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
[NARRATOR] Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER] You want my
treasure? You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
[MORIA] Shall we begin?
[MORIA] I see you're
just as energetic
as your master, little shadow.
But now I am
your new master.
[MORIA] And yet fear not,
for I shall grant you both voice
and body so that you
may live on as a zombie.
Abandon your memories
and abandon your
remnants of humanity,
so you may serve me
as an undying soldier!
[MORIA] Now, awaken!
[MORIA] Your 500 years of
slumber has come to an end!
Beautiful!
A work of art.
A masterpiece. Just great!
Meat!
I'm hungry!
[NAMI] No! Let me go! Stop it!
I can't move he's too strong.
Well, boys, say goodbye.
Because today,
I'm gonna marry her.
No, not me too!
What's going on?!
Now Nami's disappearing?
[CHOPPER] Nami!
[LUFFY] "A Belief Worth
Begging to Live For!
Brook Defends His Afro."
[RYUMA]
♪ Yohohoho. Yo-hoho.
♪ Yohohoho.
[BROOK pants heavily]
[RYUMA]
Nyohohoho!
You just don't know
when to quit, do you.
[BROOK] I'll never quit!
[BRROK] Until I regain what
I've lost. I'll keep fighting.
[RYUMA] Don't you
remember who I am?
Men cower in fear
at the mere mention
of the Swordmaster Ryuma.
Silence! You're nothing
more than my shadow!
Nyohohoho. Yet my
body is much stronger.
I'll return you to
where you belong.
Beneath my feet!
[ZOMBIE 352A] What the hell?
I don't believe it!
Someone other than that Humming
Swordsman knows our weakness!
This sucks!
"We can't die" doesn't really
work so good as our motto
if we're all running
around scared of dying!
[ROBIN] We were told
they use this staircase
to transport people whose
shadows have been cut.
That makes sense.
They took Luffy here.
We were headed this way to
before Nami got kidnapped.
[CHOPPER] I'm so
worried about her!
Do you think she'll be okay?
[USOPP] Yeah.
If they wanted her dead,
they wouldn't have captured her.
We'll get her back, no doubt!
The best thing
we can do for now
is get back to the Sunny!
We'll regroup there
and wake up the other guys
then take back their shadows!
But this place is
crawling with zombies!
That won't be easy!
Oh yeah, I forgot to ask.
How'd you beat
those zombies, anyway?
It's another
one of the secrets
that skeleton guy told
us about. Check it out.
[BROOK] Both of you. Take this.
[ROBIN] What is it?
[BROOK] The weakness
of these zombies.
[BROOK] You've seen its power.
This was the weapon I used
to defeat that Spider Monkey.
Their weakness, huh?
What is this stuff, anyway?
It's ordinary salt.
Even these zombies
have something
that can hurt them.
So by throwing
it in their mouths,
if "purifies" them?
Yep! You just
saw it in action!
By the way,
do you have any idea
what that monstrous roar
was we heard earlier?
We couldn't see anything.
Yeah.
We were trying to
see where it came from,
but then we ran into you.
That roar was Luffy.
Huh?
What'd you say?
[USOPP] Don't worry, we'll
tell you everything we saw.
I don't think you're gonna
like what you hear, though.
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352A]
Keep it coming!
He's nowhere near done!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352B]
How much food
can this special zombie eat?
He'll knock out this
island's entire food supply!
My! That's quite
an impressive appetite!
[PERONA] Kumacy!
Would you care to
explain the reason
you were hiding
those pirates? Huh?
[KUMACY] Well...
You see... It's because...
[PERONA] Stop talking!
It's not cute at all!
Oh, uh, thanks onion guy.
Still, if you're gonna
feed me, get more.
This isn't enough.
Also, this food kind
of sucks. Hahahaha!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352C]
Dammit, special zombie!
That's rude! Don't be so cocky!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352D]
Who do you think gave us
the ability to move!
That includes you, too!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352E]
How could you be
so rude to the ruler
of Thriller Bark!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352F]
Yeah! The Master
is pretty much the
king of the island!
[OARS] What?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352G]
Sorry about that!
This guy over here was the one
who was being a jerk to you!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352H] What the?
Don't sell out your
friends like that!
Not enough food.
Still hungry.
Then we shall
give you more!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352I]
Sorry Master,
but we've already brought nearly
all the food on the island.
You did?
[CINDRY] I have some
food stored in the mansion
that was being saved
in case of emergency.
You may use it as you please.
Well done!
That's our Cindry for you!
Always ready for anything!
Ohhhh!
[HOGBACK] To think you were able
to prepare for something like...
Hold on. If they
bring it here now,
it defeats the purpose
in having emergency food!
Even if you starve,
it's fine.
Come now, Cindry.
That's hurtful!
[MORIA] Gyoro! Nin! Bao!
Go to Hogback's mansion,
retrieve the provisions,
and bring them here!
[BAO] Right! You got it, Master!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352J]
We'll go with you and help!
[GYORO] We gotta try not
to be seen by those pirates!
Or the humming guy!
They're bad news!
[BAO] After what happened
to the Spider Monkey
and his underlings,
you can't be too careful!
What is it?
Did you see them?
[NIN] I thought I dropped
it somewhere, but look!
I found the store room key!
Don't scare us like that!
[GYORO] Down here!
This way to the storeroom!
[GYORO] Everyone grab
what you can! Take it all!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352L]
Hurry! Go!
[NIN] Master! We're back!
[MORIA] Good! Now feed him!
Hey! This stuff tastes
better than that other crap!
[CINDRY] Among its contents
is some salted fish.
I'm sure he would love that.
Sal-Salted?!
[NIN] If that special zombie
finds that fish and eats it,
then his shadow will.
We can't let that
happen, got it?
If it does, the Master
will punish us mercilessly!
Come on!
We've gotta find that
thing before he does!
[KUMACY] Mistress Perona.
Shut up!
I told you not to talk!
[NIN] Fish! Fish!
Where's the fish!
Hey! What are you doing?
[NIN] Help me!
[BAO] He found the fish!
[NIN] Huh. Is this salt?
[BAO] Idiot!
That's the salted fish
we've been looking for!
No doubt about it!
[OARS] That fish
looks really tasty!
[GYORO] Oh, uh, this
old fish isn't really suited
to your tastes,
Mister Special Zombie.
Yeah! Yeah!
Ha ha! I won't know
that until I try it.
Come here, fish.
What are you fools doing?
Careful! Are you trying to
get yourselves eaten, too?
[KUMACY] Uhh... Uhhh...
[PERONA] Shut up!
[GYORO] We can't let him
swallow this, no matter what!
[OARS] Why you!
Why are you getting in
the way of me and my food?
[GYORO] We uh,
we just thought
that you'd like
this much better!
Yeah! Yeah!
Oh. Really?
Dried meat! Very tasty!
[ZOMBIE 352C] All that hard work
really built up an appetite!
Whoa! I gotta have
a bite of this!
[MORIA] While you're eating,
listen up, Oars,
500 years ago, you were a
notorious and legendary villain.
And now, you have been
reborn through my power
and will serve as my underling.
Underling? What?
No way. I have a dream.
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352M]
The audacity!
I've never seen such a zombie!
[jeering]
[OARS] This place
is small and stupid.
I'm'a go outside for a while.
Or maybe, I should go out
to sea and check out the world.
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352N]
You? On a boat?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352O]
You idiot! That's impossible!
Besides, this special freezer
is made of dense sealed steel!
You'll never get out!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352P] Slam your
fists into it all you want.
Now, Gum-Gum Pistol!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352Q]
What the hell?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352R]
That's amazing!
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352S ] Hey!
Wait! What are you doing?
[RANDOM ZOMBIE 352T]
This is bad! Oars is escaping!
Somebody do something!
That's weird, I thought
my arm was gonna stretch.
Oh well. I'm gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
[RYUMA] It'll be
just like before.
You talk big, but you'll
end up begging for your life
while screaming,
"Anything but the afro!
Anything but the afro!"
[BROOK]
Wrong! This time is different!
[BROOK] I don't stand a chance!
There are terrifying
zombies at every turn!
Even when I summon up the
courage to cut them down,
they get right back up!
But they must have some
sort of weak point, right?
At this rate, even if I found
the zombie with my shadow,
I wouldn't be able to do
anything to get it back!
On top of that. Zombie
faces are too scary!
[ZOMBIE 352D] Whoa! One of
our buddies was purified!
How'd that happen?
[ZOMBIE 352D] It looks like.
It looks like he ate
some salted grilled fish!
[ZOMBIE 352E] Idiot!
Was he a new guy or something?
[thinking] Did he say
"salted grilled fish"?
Could this be the weakness
I've been searching for?
Oh! You bastard!
You're the guy whose shadow
we stole a few days ago!
How did you get back here?
Just answer my question!
Which of your zombies
has my shadow in it?
If you don't tell me,
I'll scatter fish
all over this island!
Eh? Fish, huh?
Fasfasfasfasfas!
What the hell good
is that gonna do?
Uh... Hold on.
The only other thing it
could be is the salt, but...
What? Salt? Ah!!
But, what the hell good
is spreading a bunch of
salt around gonna do? Huh?
It's salt!
[BROOK] Zombies are
still scary after all.
Especially at night.
[BROOK] Thank goodness.
Just a grasshopper.
That scared me.
Even so, it's dangerous
for me when the sun is up,
and I'd be much easier to spot.
Wait! A song!
When you're scared,
you should sing something
to take your mind off things!
Now if I run really fast
so I can't see their scary
faces and purify each one,
I'll eventually find
the one with my shadow!
[BROOK humming]
[ZOMBIE] What's that sound?
What's that creepy
song all about?
nd who's the
one humming it?
Huh? Ahh!!!
What is this?
Ahh!!
Aaaah!
[humming]
[ZOMBIES scream]
[BROOK screams]
[ALL scream]
Aaah!!
[BROOK]
Aaaaaaa!
What happened?
What the hell is going on here?
He hides in the
darkness of the night!
All you hear is the humming!
A swordsman with a terrifying
face is going around
killing zombies one by one
trying to find his shadow!
He's devastated our ranks
purifying every zombie
he's come across!
It's a nightmare!
[KUMACY] Mistress Perona,
there's been an incident.
[PERONA] Shut up!
Don't wake me when
I'm sleeping, Kumacy!
Nyohohoho!
At last, we meet.
Yohohohoho!
[thinking]
Why is he so strong?
I thought he was
supposed to be me!
[RYUMA]
Nyohohoho...
Yohohohoho!
[BROOK thinking] Even though our
swordsmanship is evenly matched,
I can't keep up with him!
[RYUMA] Give up.
No matter how many times
you try to defeat me,
the outcome will
always be the same.
But I think I know
what's slowing you down.
Why don't you let me cut off
that bothersome afro of yours?
What? No! Stop it!
Anything but that!
Don't you dare
even touch this afro!
You hear me?
Don't you understand?
If you're my shadow,
then you have to know
how truly important
this afro is to me!
Because of the fact
that my body has stopped
growing my afro
would never grow back!
It would be gone forever!
Nyohohoho!
So? Who cares?
And though I am your shadow,
I've forgotten everything about
the days we spent together.
As of now, Moria and
Absalom are my masters!
They give the orders, not you!
[RYUMA] A walking skeleton
that treasures his afro?
Do you realize how
ridiculous you are? Pathetic!
[BROOK] Stop it, please!
Not the afro! No! Don't!
Anything but the afro!
[RYUMA]
Nyohohoho!
Yohohohoho!
What a foolish trick!
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
You say whatever you like.
There's a reason why
I can't lose, why I must fight!
Nyohohoho!
Ahh!
[RYUMA] How pathetic
you are, my former master.
It seems that I have lost,
I accept defeat.
[BROOK] Yet, I beg of you.
Please. Let me live.
I'll leave this
island immediately.
[RYUMA] Go. Get out of my sight!
[RYUMA] If you were to die,
it'd be a problem
for me, as well.
[RYUMA] I've never
seen such a pitiful scene.
[BROOK] I don't
care what you say.
Arrrgh!
Nyhohohoho!
[BROOK] During
these past 5 years,
I've been thinking of nothing
but this second chance.
And I've trained
to become stronger!
Huh? Oh!
Good evening, Master Absalom!
[ABSALOM]
Have you gotten everything
in order for the ceremony?
[ZOMBIE WEDDING PLANNER]
Ah, yes!
Everything's ready
whenever you are.
My, my! What a beautiful bride!
Then start at once!
Put her in a dress and
bring her to the wedding hall.
Of course!
[USOPP] I see!
So that skeleton gave us
a lot of useful information!
[FRANKY] Yeah,
I really misjudged him.
Even though his whole
crew got wiped out,
he's stayed alive
these past 50 years
to keep a promise to a friend.
To a whale that's been waiting
for him all this time
at a cape far away.
[USOPP] A whale?
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
"A Man's Promise Never Dies!
To the Friend Waiting
Under the Distant Sky!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!