[GOLD ROGER] The world.
What a glorious place!
Seek freedom and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it!
Raise your flag, and stand tall!
♪(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!)
I think back to the time
when my search first began‐‐
I left behind those
shores of sand‐‐
For the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have searched
for everywhere (ere‐ere!)
When the summer sun is shining,
shaking the sails
of my heart, I know...
(Fly away glum blue sea)
A brand‐new world
that had been hiding
has opened up its
doors for me to go...
(Fly away glum blue sky)
Swaying in the troubled waves‐‐
From all despair,
I can be saved‐‐
For the horizon
on the other side is‐‐
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Is what I aim for!
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began‐‐
Over seas of green
and shores of sand‐‐
Through the endless,
everlasting world out there...
I know that with this
burning passion driving me‐‐
Someday, somewhere,
I'll finally‐‐
See the light I have
searched for everywhere!♪
Take your two friends
and get out of my sight
before I decide otherwise.
You got that weakling?
[BLACKBEARD]
The sky island does exist.
[MAN C]
What are you talking about?
Huh? Luffy?
This new era they keep
rambling on and on about
is a load of crap.
The era when pirates dream of
treasure will come to an end?
Yeah, right!
[laughs]
The dreams of pirates
will never end!
[LUFFY] "Legendary Family!
Noland, the Liar!"
[USOPP]
I can't believe our luck.
Seriously.
That orangutan almost sunk us.
And now it's up to me to fix it
all and keep this thing afloat.
[ZORO] Seems to me
that this busted old ship
is on her last leg.
We need a new one.
How dare you even consider
replacing this boat?
Yeah, how dare you!
[USOPP]
You are aware
of the origins of this
ship, aren't you?
You do know what
she's capable of, don't you?
[CHOPPER]
Yeah, don't you?
We all know the story, Usopp.
And try not to be so defensive.
The Going Merry is an
important part of our crew,
and we all know we have
to take care of her.
You shouldn't take
everything so personally.
You're right. I'm sorry.
[LUFFY]
Oops!
[screams]
What are you doing?!
We're trying to save
the ship, not sink it!
[LUFFY]
Sure thing.
Here, I'll fix it.
Oops. That didn't work.
[CHOPPER, USOPP]
Luffy!
[NAMI] We left Mock Town
and headed east
by circling around the
northern shore of the island.
Our destination is here.
We're supposed
to meet that man there.
What's his name?
His name is Montblanc Cricket.
[NAMI]
And you're sure that
he'll be able to
help us out, right?
Whoa! Amazing!
[LUFFY]
That's where he lives?
It's a freakin' palace!
[USOPP] I've never seen
a house that big before.
This Montblanc Cricket
guy must be really loaded.
Ugh. Look closer.
It's really unattractive.
A guy's gotta have some serious
guts to build a house that ugly.
Hmm? What's that?
[screams]
This isn't a palace at all!
[CHOPPER, USOPP]
What?
[ZORO] The actual house
is only half that size.
What you see is a facade.
A fake.
[SANJI] This guy's even
more vain than I thought.
Why exactly did Cricket
decide to leave his home
and come live here?
[ROBIN]
I don't know all the details.
But I think it has something
to do with his belief
that a large amount
of gold rests somewhere
in the hills of Jaya.
G‐Gold?
Do you think he's here searching
for some sort of
buried treasure?
Well, I just don't know.
[NAMI]
Gold!
Try over here, Chopper.
Dig up this spot.
[CHOPPER]
I'll be right there, Nami.
[SANJI] It must be hard to live
alone in such a remote area.
[LUFFY]
Hello!
Don't just barge in there.
Huh. Looks like nobody's home.
Anybody here?
I guess he's gone.
Get out of there, you idiot.
This guy could be dangerous.
[LUFFY]
Hey, you guys.
Nobody's home.
Huh... What's this?
A book.
And it looks pretty old.
It's called "Noland, the Liar."
Huh. Sounds like
it could be good.
I sure like the title.
[SANJI]
"Noland, the Liar"?
Yeah, have you heard of it?
It says here,
it was originally published
in the North Blue territory.
It was!
I was born in the
North Blue territory.
I'm certain I must
have told you guys that.
No, that's news to me.
I always thought that
you were born in the East.
[SANJI]
I grew up there.
Enough already, Chopper.
What are you doing?
[screams]
Where I come from,
this is a famous story.
It's a fairy tale supposedly
based on the life of Noland,
who lived in the
North Blue a long time ago.
[NAMI] This is a story
of ancient origins.
The events herein transpired
more than 400 years ago.
There once was a man by
the name of Montblanc Noland
who lived in the
North Blue countryside.
Noland, who was an explorer,
always regaled the crowds
with stories of his
incredible exploits.
But nobody knew whether or not
to take Noland's
tall tales seriously.
One day, upon returning
from yet another adventure,
he reported to his king
all that he had seen.
"I saw a city of gold on
an island in the great sea,"
declared Noland.
And the courageous king decided
that he must have this
treasure for his kingdom.
The king set out with Noland
and two thousand
of his finest soldiers.
Along the way they
endured treacherous storms
and battled many
ferocious sea creatures.
At the end of their journey
only the King, Noland,
and 100 soldiers
survived to set foot
on the island that
housed the city of gold.
And all they found
for their troubles
was a normal island covered
with an ordinary jungle.
And so, upon their return,
Noland was sentenced to death
for the crime of
lying to his King.
His last words were as follows.
"I can only assume that the
city of gold sunk into the sea."
The King and his
court were dumbfounded.
Nobody believed Noland anymore.
And the last of his days were
spent in shame and ridicule
before his sentence
of death was carried out
before a cheering crowd.
It says here that
the book is based
on the true story
of Noland, the Liar.
[BELLAMY laughs]
Montblanc Cricket
is a descendant
of the infamous
Montblanc Noland?
I heard that fairy tale
all the time as a kid.
But I never knew that
Jaya was the island
where he thought
he saw the city of gold.
When we were growing up
in the North Blue,
we were always warned
that if we lied, we'd suffer
the same fate as Noland
and be ridiculed until we
were eventually put to death.
[laughs]
It makes sense that
Cricket's related to that fool,
but I can't believe that Jaya is
the island from the fairy tale.
Pardon the intrusion,
but if I heard you correctly,
you're saying a descendant
of Noland is here,
400 years after the fact,
looking for that gold?
He's gotta be doing this
to clear his family name
and regain some
small amount of respect.
[laughs]
This story keeps getting
better and better.
[laughs]
Can he seriously
hope to wipe away
over 400 years
of embarrassment
by bringing back
a few pieces of gold?
What a joke!
Sounds like he's a
few bricks short of a wall.
[NAMI]
Alas, the Liar died
before he could prove
himself to the people.
[sighs]
All he ever really wanted to do
was live the life
of an adventurer.
[USOPP] That last part's
not in the book.
Don't try to tack on your
own sentimental nonsense.
[LUFFY screams]
Did he just fall in the water?
What's going on?
[CRICKET]
Who the hell are you?
You've got nerve,
relaxing at someone's
house without permission.
This is my land,
and I suggest you leave.
Hurry, Usopp. Move it! Go and
fish Luffy out of the sea.
[USOPP]
You got it!
I know why you're here.
You're after my gold!
Sanji!
Sanji, no!
Don't worry.
This guy's a terrible shot.
[SANJI]
Hey! Cut it out!
Idiot.
Never underestimate your foe.
[ZORO] Out of the way.
I'll handle this.
You really need to
learn to be more careful.
But I thought I saw...
...bubbles in the water,
so I looked closer and
then a chestnut appeared.
But it wasn't a chestnut.
It was a guy,
and he pulled me in.
[LUFFY]
What's with him?
[CHOPPER]
I need more cold towels.
And open up those windows.
[ZORO]
What's Caisson disease?
[LUFFY]
So this guy is really sick, huh?
Yeah.
Caisson disease is an illness
that sometimes afflicts divers.
Though it's called a disease,
it isn't actually
a chronic condition.
It's caused by a lack
of decompression
when surfacing from the seabed.
The nitrogen in the
blood releases too quickly
and causes gas bubbles to
form in the circulatory system.
And when those
gas bubbles expand
they can cause considerable
damage to muscles and joints
and seriously
decrease blood flow.
So it's a mystery disease.
Think you can help him?
[CHOPPER]
I'm not sure.
My guess is he kept diving
everyday without allowing time
for his body to recover and
it finally caught up with him.
That's why he passed
out during the fight.
But why in the world
did he do that?
[CHOPPER]
I don't know,
but he was taking a big risk.
In some cases,
Caisson disease can cause death.
So he's lucky to be alive.
[SHOJO]
Oh hey, Masira.
I guess you're
still alive after all.
[MASIRA]
Why do you say that?
[SHOJO]
Forget about it.
Do you know what all that
gunfire was about earlier?
[MASIRA]
I'm not sure,
but that's where I'm
headed now, to find out.
[SHOJO]
Well, come on then.
I'm worried about the old‐timer.
Hey, Old‐timer.
Are you all right?
[screams]
They've come to kill us.
What in the world are
you people doing here?
And just what are
you doing to our friend?
We're trying to help.
So I suggest you
either lend us a hand
or find someone else to bother.
Don't antagonize them, Luffy.
You know what
they're capable of,
and now there're two of
those savages to deal with.
[CHOPPER]
They're savages!
[USOPP] Everyone, jump out
the windows and run away.
Thank you, guys.
[USOPP]
What did they say?
[LUFFY] So you guys
live on this island, too?
Yep. This old‐timer's house
is the official headquarters
of the Saruyama
Alliance of Jaya.
We call this home,
but we spend most of
our time on our ships.
We're more comfortable at sea
'cause this place
is too small for us.
[LUFFY] You guys are
too big for your own good.
But it's all in how
you look at it, I guess.
To a giant you'd still look like
nothing more
than a ball of earwax.
[laughter]
Well, those three sure
are getting along well,
now, aren't they?
Yeah, seems like they
have a lot in common.
I'm pretty impressed you managed
to get Masira
here off your ship.
It's quite a feat for someone as
small as you to overpower him.
[LUFFY]
Eh, it wasn't really that hard.
Huh? What's that?
[LUFFY]
I'm sure you could kick his ass.
Luffy! He's waking up!
He's awake?
[SHOJO]
He's right!
I can kick Masira's ass!
[LUFFY]
Hey, chestnut head.
I got a question for ya.
[sighs]
I'm sorry I attacked you.
I thought you were nothing more
than another group of bandits
who had come to steal my gold.
Did someone say
something about gold?
Just calm down, Nami.
What exactly was it
you wanted to ask me?
We're searching for sky island
and were told you might be able
to tell us how to get there.
[CRICKET]
Are you serious?
[laughs]
Don't tell me you really
believe that place exists.
Hey! Stop it.
You can't attack a sick man.
You mean there's no sky island?
Are you sure?
I don't know. See...
Nobody knows if the
sky island really exists or not.
I know of only one man
who claims to have seen
the island for himself.
But he's considered
a liar of epic proportions.
Wah!
What are you looking at?
[CRICKET]
There's an old fairy tale
that the people of the
North Blue know very well.
It's called "Noland, the Liar."
Wah!
Stop looking at me, Luffy.
My name's not Noland.
Now that I think about it,
Noland's family name
was also Montblanc.
Does that mean that
two are related somehow?
Is he right?
And is this island the one
mentioned in the fairy tale?
Hmph. Yeah,
Noland's my grandfather's,
grandfather's grandfather. He's
a distant ancestor of mine.
I am his descendant.
But we're so far removed,
I doubt there's even a single
drop of his blood in my veins.
The Montblanc family
was driven out
of the North Blue country
a long time ago,
and we've managed to keep
a very low profile ever since.
People still denounce
the family name.
But we've never
despised him for this.
[CHOPPER]
But why?
Because Noland,
contrary to popular belief,
was an very honest person.
That's not what
the fairy tale said.
[CRICKET]
As the story goes,
Noland's last words
were as follows.
"I can only assume that the
city of gold sunk into the sea."
This line is accompanied
by an idiotic face
in the illustration.
But Noland was no idiot.
He knew what he saw,
and I believe he
wasn't lying about it.
Noland was sure the
island he stumbled upon,
where he found
the ruins of a city of gold,
was the island of Jaya.
But when he returned with
the king, there was no gold.
Unsuccessful, he insisted
that the ancient city
had submerged due
to shifts in the earth's crust.
But everyone dismissed this
as the last‐ditch excuse
of a doomed man.
Noland was given
a public execution.
When he died,
so did his discoveries.
Only the legend
of the liar remained.
I get it.
You're trying to find
the ancient city of gold
at the bottom of the sea
in order to finally clear
the Montblanc family name
and prove Noland right.
Don't be ridiculous.
[CHOPPER]
Usopp!
[CRICKET] I don't really
care if the ancient city of gold
exists or not.
The actions of my ancestor
have nothing to do
with me and my life.
You can't possibly begin to
imagine what it's like as a kid
for everyone to laugh
at you and ridicule you
because you're a descendant
of that idiot, Noland.
That's what I've dealt
with my whole life.
[CRICKET]
Anyway, over the past 400 years
a great many of my family
have set sail to find the city
of gold, prove Noland right,
and restore the Montblanc name.
But each and every one
of them went missing.
I was ashamed to be a member
of such a pathetic family.
So I decided to leave
home become a pirate.
Wow! So you're
a pirate just like us?
I didn't even really
want to become a pirate.
I just wanted out
of Noland's shadow.
To be my own man.
But over time I came
to assemble my own pirate crew.
Finally, I was seen as a
leader, not a laughingstock.
And I spanned the world
looking for adventures.
Then ten years ago as
my crew and I sailed a calm sea,
we discovered this island
purely by chance.
And ironically,
of all my family members
who sought out this place,
who lost their lives doing so,
it was I who found it.
I who despised
the Montblanc name.
We came ashore, but found
no trace of the city of gold.
I stood on a cape of the island
and felt I was
destined to be there.
Let's settle this, Noland.
Once and for all.
[UNDERLING A]
You're on your own.
We don't want anything
to do with this.
We're setting sail and leaving.
[UNDERLING B]
If you wanna stay here
and search for gold that doesn't
exist, you're doing it alone.
[UNDERLING A]
So long, Captain.
[CRICKET] I don't care
if I find the city or not.
I'm not here to prove
Noland right or wrong.
I have no interest
in rewriting history.
All I'm doing is following
what I believe is my destiny.
This is between me and Noland.
I'm facing what I fear,
and whatever the outcome,
the act is all that matters.
Wow. What a sad story.
But what about the monkeys.
How did they come to be on
this island with you anyways?
[USOPP] I'm sure that's
another story of bravery
and the face of incredible odds.
Your life reads like a great
book you know, Cricket?
They were just
fans of the fairy tale.
They're fans?
[NAMI]
How did they find you?
I think it was
five or six years ago.
They heard a rumor
and set out to find me.
Those two truly believe that the
city of gold exists somewhere.
And they're helping me find it.
Ahhh!
Shojo, you have no idea
what you just got yourself into!
Bring it on you big ape.
I'm ready when you are.
Just step up and
you'll get knocked down.
[CRICKET] The sea surrounding
this island is very deep.
And in those dark, cold depths,
you're surrounded by a
profound sense of solitude.
[CRICKET]
When I first arrived here,
I spent my time searching
the sea bed alone.
They entered my life
without permission
and assigned themselves
as my crew without asking.
And they do nothing
but fight all the time.
But having these idiots
around puts me at ease.
And truthfully,
I enjoy their company.
You understand?
I understand completely.
True friends lift each other up
and give each other
strength in times of need.
Are you just about finished
telling us your life story?
Shut your mouth
you ungrateful brat.
[screams]
Stop it.
Look, all I really want to
know about is sky island.
[CRICKET chuckles]
You're a pushy guy, aren't ya?
But like I told you earlier,
the only person who's ever
seen the sky island is Noland.
And nobody knows
if he was telling the truth
or if it was just
another tall tale.
[LUFFY] Is there any record
of his trip to the island?
Officially, no, but he
does mention it in here.
What do you have there?
That isn't
Noland's logbook, is it?
[CRICKET]
Yeah, it is.
Read from the
bottom of that page.
[NAMI]
Amazing.
This logbook is
over 400 years old.
June 21st, year 1120.
A sunny day on the
Sea of Ephemeris.
Upon departing
from the Jolly Villa.
We left the harbor and
sailed into the rising sun
at a heading of
east by northeast
with the wind at out back.
At midday we happened across
a bumboat carrying a rare item.
A single person contraption
called a sky waver.
This small, mysterious vessel
can generate its own wind
and sail at great speeds
even on a still day.
But the ski‐like ship
was not easily maneuvered.
I couldn't control it,
although my crew has
taken quite a liking to it.
I gotta get one of those things.
Keep going!
Don't stop reading!
[NAMI] Uh, we were told the
vessel had been manufactured
on the sky island,
and that many more interesting
devices could be found there.
It brought to mind
an explorer friend of mine
who once showed me
the most unusual specimen,
a living sky fish.
I have never seen a fish with
such a bizarre appearance
‐‐in all my years.
‐‐Sky fish?
[NAMI] This island remains
the only unexplored domain,
and as a sailor and adventurer
I feel it is my destiny
to one day reach
the sea in the sky.
Montblanc Noland.
Do you know what this means?
The sky island
must really exist.
Just like Robin said it did!
Now we just gotta
figure out how to get there.
[CHOPPER]
The sky island does exist!
[MASIRA]
You're up?
You feeling all right?
Better than ever.
Glad to hear it.
[MASIRA] This jerk snuck up
on me and attacked me from‐‐
[CRICKET]
Shut up.
I need to ask you something.
What do you think of those guys?
Why you askin', Old‐timer?
It seems that they're
determined to get
to sky island no matter what.
Sky island?
You know there's only
one way for them to get there.
And if they try
to get there on their own,
they'll die.
Exactly.
I think we should
help them along.
So, what do you
guys think about that?
♪Now, I look up and see,
there's something out there,
beyond the endless
clear‐blue sky...
Possibilities,
of just what could be,
a "someday" I'll see if I try...
When I am alone
all of the memories go
racing through my mind...
The things that
I've said and done,
the ones I've lost,
the dreams I left behind...
Sometimes I felt like
I would defeat myself
until I recalled...
That there was a warm place
I could always go
if I happened to fall...
With friends and family...
Who'd pick me up...♪
[LUFFY]
And we're off!
Finally!
To the sky!
[USOPP] I hope this
place has nice beaches.
[LUFFY]
To the sky!
[USOPP] Now this is
the kind of adventure
Captain Usopp deserves!
[NAMI] You know it's a
life‐threatening journey.
[USOPP] So? That's
what makes it exciting.
I guess.
[NAMI] I've heard of a scaredy
cat, but not a scaredy captain.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"Steer for the Clouds!
Capture the South Bird!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!