It's the One Piece
treasure giveaway!
The first key letter to be
on the lookout for is...
We'll tell you how to enter
at the end of the show!
That's why I think you should
stay behind once we get there.
Give us five minutes,
then charge through to the
main island in Rocketman.
The Franky Family and
Galley-La will go in first
and break open the Main Gate
and the Main Island Front Gate
so the train can
pass right through.
Our best chance is for you
Straw Hats to concentrate
on CP9 and leave the
rest of the marines to us.
Right.
I got it.
What?
Why the hell is he
going in on his own!
That crazy Straw Hat didn't
understand the plan at all!!
Bring it on, pirate!
I'm in a hurry.
But you'll have more
people to fight later!
See ya!
Don't let them open that gate!
Fire!
Shut up!
Move it!
All right men, let's go!
We made it through
the main gate!
By the way, Sniper King.
Hey!
That hurt!
You think you could
teach me how to use
the cold air feature
on this thing?
Sure.
It's simple--I mean.
Why are you asking me?
I hate waiting.
I hope everyone's okay.
All we can do is
be patient, Chopper.
Even if Luffy jumped the gun,
we gotta sit tight
and stick with the plan.
These pipsqueaks
don't look like much.
C'mon.
You wanna get back
to bed soon, right?
Let's make this quick.
Sounds good.
Whoa.
They-they're giants!
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
How many friends did
you bring with you, huh?
We've got 10,000 soldiers
here at Enies Lobby!
Sorry, but it's just me.
Now get out of my way!
[LUFFY READS ALOUD]
This is a dead end,
little twerps!
This is your last chance to
turn around and go home.
One more step
and we'll stomp you!
We can't turn back now!
Just remember,
our Big Bro's waiting
on the other side of that gate!
Our bro Franky wouldn't
give up at a time like this,
and neither will we!
Don't give in!
We gotta clear the
way for Rocketman!
Bust down those doors!
Forget about it--I won't even
let an ant through this gate!
The Destroyers!
What happened?
You bastards.
Took out our strongest guys
before I even got here!
You'll pay!
What is that?
Zambai!
Kiwi!
Mozu!
Galley-La!
Sorry we're late!
Took a little longer
than I thought
to get Sodom and
Gomorrah ready for land!
Zambai!
They beat the Destroyers!
Yeah, I know.
But we don't have time
to patch them up right now.
The only thing that matters
is getting through that gate.
We came here to
rescue our big bro
and that's just
what we're gonna do!
Let's rock.
Yeah!
We'll send those
big lugs crashing down!
Come on!
You got it, Kiwi!
Here we go!
Hull Dismantler.
Slash!
Rope Action.
Timber Hitch Tug!
Kashii no!
Tilestone!
Treenail Lock!
It's a job well done!
Little runts!
I'll crush you!
Kashii!
All right!
How dare you.
Don't let up, men!
We got one more to go!
Yeah!
What's the current status?
Sir.
Well, Kashii and Oimo
should be dealing
with the intruders at the
main island gate right now.
I don't suspect they're
having any trouble.
Naturally.
But what about Straw Hat?
Where are we at on that one?
"Where are we at?" Ah.
This is just an estimate,
but I'd say about four hundred?
Four Hundred?
What're you talking about?
Our casualties, sir!
You're not making
any sense, man!
You're telling me Straw Hat
has defeated 400 of our guards?
Looks like we lost about
a hundred more just now.
No, that number's wrong.
I'll correct it, sir.
You'd better!
Our guards are well-trained.
I'll be damned if one man
could take that many out!
If we have casualties,
at least report them properly!
Right.
Then allow me to report again.
I'd estimate our current
casualties at five--
Five men?
We've only lost
five of our guards?
Jeez!
How in the world could you
make such an obvious mistake!
Five hundred.
Seems Straw Hat's
no threat after all.
He's just running around the
island, making a lot of noise.
Well, that's no surprise.
Even he's not stupid enough
to take on that many
guards on his own.
Either way, it's only a matter
of time before he's captured.
Good to see you all back.
Chief, Mr. Lucci's
party has arrived.
Excellent!
Well, what are you waiting for?
Show them in already.
It's been quite a while, Chief.
Hasn't it?
As promised, we've
brought Cutty Flam--
the criminal responsible
for assaulting
government officials in
Water Seven, 8 years ago.
And of course.
We also have Nico Robin,
the last surviving
resident of Ohara.
Who we've been trying to capture
for the past two decades.
They're both waiting outside
if you would like to see them.
In short, the mission
was a huge success.
It's good to have you back.
Lucci.
Kaku.
Blueno.
Kalifa.
That's harassment.
All I did was say your name!
Just like old times, huh, Lucci?
Actually, I think that you might
be even more smug than before.
But sadly, you're
not any smarter, Jabra.
What?
Oh, come on!
We've hardly even
gotten off of the train
and the first thing you
two do is start bickering?
Yoyoi!
Kaakuu is riiiiight!
Can't we alllll
just get aloooong?!
Fooor fiiive loooong years we've
awaaaaited theiiir reeetuuurn!
Chapapa.
Cha -papa cha-pa.
Ow.
I had a feeling you were going
to test us right away, Fukurou.
Six Powers Skill-Competition!
I'll use an armed guard as
reference for the ranking.
Let's say they're about a ten.
So your power levels are.
Ohhh, interesting,
very interesting.
Let's see here.
First is Kalifa.
Power level six hundred thirty.
Blueno is eight-hundred twenty.
Kaku is two-thousand,
two hundred.
And Lucci.
Power level 4000!
4000?
You gotta be making
these numbers up!
There's no such thing as
a power level that high!
Cha pa pa!
Well, maybe not before now,
but they've gotten stronger!
Since I measured
Jabra and Kumadori too.
I can finally rank all of CP9!
No way, Fukurou,
I want a recount!
Even if I ignore
the whole Lucci thing,
why the hell am
I weaker than Kaku!
'Because Cha pa pa!
Kaku got stronger
too, that's why!
I don't want you getting
a big head over this Kaku.
Just remember, the
"Competition" technique
only measures your
physical strength!
In a real battle,
I have my devil fruit powers
to help me out, too.
I can trash a guy like you
any day of the week, got it?
I don't care.
If it makes you feel better,
keep telling yourself that.
Exactly.
Don't pay any heed to the
yapping of that mangy dog.
So, I'm a mangy dog, am I?
Screw you, cat bastard.
Honestly!
Both of you, stop it!
Jabra certainly is
touchy today, isn't he?
Did something happen to him?
All the guards on the
island are talking about it!
Jabra's been in a bad mood
'cause he got dumped
by that waitress,
Gatherine the other day.
So that's it.
Hey, now hold on a sec!
That's a secret-why do
people know about that!
'Cause I told everyone here
how sad and lonely you are!
Chapapa!
I should've known!
Geez!
This is what you get for doing
that stupid ranking
nonsense right off the bat!
There's hardly any
point in bickering
over who's strongest when
your Six Powers training
has made you all superhuman.
Power Level 500 should be
more than anyone needs, right?
He's saying that
cause he's level 9.
Even weaker than
a guard, chapapa!
Who cares!
You guys are the muscle--I
just give the orders!
Besides, I have my special
sword to use in a pinch.
It's all right, Chief.
We've always known
how weak you are.
Come on now, Kalifa.
There's no need to
be so blunt about it!
That's sexual harassment.
What?
Because I replied to you?
By the way.
Huh?
What now?
That's sexual harassment.
My existence?
Yoiyoi!
Kalifa!
You are showing very poor form!
Allow me to apologiiize,
deaaar chiiief.
By putting this
blade to my belly!
Seppuku!
Iron Body!
I can't even die right.
If you wanna die that bad,
I'd be happy to help!
Or perhaps it is your
love that protects me.
Dear mother in heaven.
Is it not my time?
I see now.
I never knew you
lost your mother.
We have long fought,
but now we can find solace
in each other's plights.
Yeah.
Despite all the
cruel things I've said,
I understand your pain!
I know what it feels
like to lose a loved one!
Oh, Mother, dear!
Gatherine!
Am I not good enough for you?
I miss you!
Chief.
Uh.
Yes?
Their play is over.
We can continue.
Oh, right.
Although it's been a long time
coming, needless to say,
I'm extremely pleased with your
performance in this mission.
Of course, it's fantastic
that you've caught Nico Robin,
but catching that
bastard Cutty Flam
is the icing on the cake for me.
It's no exaggeration when
I say that the entire world
will praise your efforts when
word of this finally gets out.
Let me tell you, as your
Commander in Chief,
this is one of the proudest
moments in my life,
and I mean that.
By the way.
Although it isn't exactly a
reward for all your hard work.
I do have something
I want to give you.
Well, we can take
care of that later.
For now, let's
meet them, shall we?
The hope of the entire world.
You ready, ladies and gents?
The time has finally arrived.
If they don't have
those gates open by now,
it ain't gonna happen!
Hurry up and go!
Meow!
I'm gonna need you to take out
that iron fence,
okay Samurai Man?
Just leave it to me.
That hurts!
Hurry up!
There's no time!
We gotta open that gate!
Keep moving!
Go!
Wait, where am I?
This street sure is
a pain to walk on!
Ah!
Damn it, Robin, I'm coming!
Just you wait!
I'm not gonna let you
leave my crew that easy!
Look! He's over there!
Gum-Gum...
Capture him!
Yo-yo!
The Commander in
Chief will see you now.
Both of you go inside.
Hey, Moss-for-Brains!
What's going on out here?
They uh... They
closed the main gate.
They what??
This is bad! We're gonna crash!
Don't worry. I have a plan.
All right, Zoro!
We'll Just leave it to luck.
We're gonna die!
On the next One Piece:
"Find A Way Out!
Rocketman
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!