[GOLD ROGER]
Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth!
♪People tell me my
head's in the clouds
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreamin' of you
You are the treasure I've found
So bright, so bold,
yet so elusive
It's hard to look away,
even though it's blinding me
There are no words to describe
how I feel inside
I'm really really stuck
on you whoa, whoa!
I have to follow my dreams
however crazy they seem
And I won't stop 'til I
get there, you will see
You're all I need
to have the strength to believe
Believe in Wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem
I'm gonna share them with you,
a love so true
You're all I want,
together we can move on
Live how we want to!
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love
And we don't wanna
live ordinary lives
We have the chance
to live in paradise
Believe in Wonderland!♪
[NARRATOR] In three years,
not a drop of rain has fallen
in the desert kingdom of
Alabasta, the land of oases.
Desperate for rain and
prodded by outside forces,
the kingdom's people
have taken up weapons.
The land is at the brink of war.
With nowhere else to turn,
the people are turning
on each other instead.
Princess Vivi headed to Yuba
in an attempt to prevent
the coming fight.
Once there, however,
the rebel army
was nowhere to be seen.
Meanwhile, Baroque Works
agents began
to put the final stages
of their plan into action.
The final battle
between the royal army
and the determined
rebel army is drawing
ever closer.
[LUFFY]
"Luffy vs. Vivi!
The Tearful Vow to
Put Friends on the Line."
[USOPP] Well, great job
today, everybody.
Really, we did some good work.
Now, let's all lie down
in these comfy beds
and get some
well‐deserved rest, okay?
We'll need our strength.
Good night, you guys!
Oh, please. This whole trip
you've been nothing but lazy.
[USOPP]
Why, you‐‐!
Quit comparing me
to you and all the other
superhuman freaks!
Now you're annoying me.
[USOPP]
Ya!
I think blue nose here
wins today's award
for laziest talking
animal in the desert.
You try walking
around in a fur coat!
[VIVI]
Sanji, I think that's my bed.
I know. I thought you might
have trouble sleeping here
all alone tonight, Vivi.
And the award for
biggest perv goes to Sanji.
All right, slingshot boy.
I'm gonna shove that
pillow so far down
your throat you'll choke on it.
[NAMI] You guys don't
seem to understand
the concept of‐‐[yelps]
I hope you're ready!
[ALL yelling, grunting]
[LUFFY] Hey, old guy,
there's still no water.
My throat's drying up.
How can you stand to live here?
It's horrible.
[TOTO]
The water will come.
The Yuba oasis
still has life in it yet.
The dream of Yuba
can't be beaten
by a bunch of lousy sand.
The king left this
land in my hands,
and I will keep it alive.
I'll dig out the sand as
many times as it takes.
Oh.
Okay, then let's dig!
Hey! Would you quit?
You're filling
the hole up I spent
all this time on.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
I'll never get done
with you filling my holes!
But... I'm digging
just like you, old guy.
No, I'm digging holes
and you're filling them up!
The sand from the
hole you're digging
is going into the
hole I'm digging.
In other words,
you're not helping!
Huh...
Ah! A mystery hole, huh?
[TOTO]
I said knock it off!
Oh, I give up!
Well... Maybe he
figured it out now.
The sand stopped coming.
He was able to dig that
in such a short time?
Even as tired as he
must be from the journey?
[LUFFY snoring]
Sleep well tonight.
You've earned it.
[LUFFY snores]
Food and water.
[TOTO]
Pleasant dreams.
[MR. 2] Gimme a break!
You've gotta be kidding me!
How long are we gonna have
to wait around like this?
Are you at least going
to offer some refreshments?
I could be practicing my
dance instead of sitting here!
[MR. 4 chuckles]
Mr. 2, just sit still over
there and wait quietly.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Yeah, shut up, you stupid man!
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER] You calm
down, too, Miss Merry Christmas.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY chuckles]
I guess it isn't too surprising
that you don't all get along.
Oh, well, it isn't necessary
that you do, anyway.
Miss All Sunday.
[MISS ALL SUNDAY]
Thank you all for coming so far
to attend this gathering
of ours in Rainbase‐‐
the city where gambling
is the only king
and every man and woman
dreams of going home rich.
Welcome to Raindinners,
the largest casino
in the whole city.
Miss All Sunday,
could we skip the formalities
and get to the point?
Yes, I was just
getting to that, Mr. 1.
[MISS MERRY CHRISTMAS]
Let's get this started already!
Hurry hurry hurry!
Start start start! Now now!
Of course, but there's something
that needs to be taken care of.
It's time to meet our boss,
whose face you've never seen.
I have been acting as
his face and his voice
for some time now.
Delivering orders as he saw fit.
There is no longer any need
for such secrecy, however.
[CROCODILE]
Finally, the time has come.
For Operation Utopia.
[gasping]
It's Crocodile?
This will be the greatest
and the final operation
that Baroque Works carries out.
It seems you're
familiar with our boss,
or his public identity, anyway.
Yes, of course we are,
but why is one of the
Seven Warlords leading us?
Yeah, we didn't expect to
have such a big shot guy
for our leader.
Let me get this straight.
We've been working for a
pirate since the first day?
So then, you are
actually our boss?
That a problem?
[MISS DOUBLEFINGER]
It's not a problem.
But it is a bit confusing.
The Seven Warlords are pirates
sanctioned by the government.
Why would you need
a company like this one?
I do not seek money or status.
It is something more.
Military strength.
[MR. 1]
Military strength?
Allow me to explain myself.
Let me tell you
my true objective.
My goal, and the final operation
that Baroque Works
will be conducting.
You mean something
like that really exists
on this island?
And we're going to
steal the whole country
along with it?
This assignment is making
me tremble all over!
So these new orders
are the final pieces
of one giant plan
that Baroque Works
has been working towards?
Yes, that is correct.
Every assignment
performed as an agent,
every mission finished
since Baroque Works
was founded,
has been a part of this
single operation.
And those letters there
are the final orders
that you will receive.
The time has finally
come for Alabasta Kingdom
to disappear.
Once each of you has
completed the assignment
you have before you,
this desert kingdom
will destroy itself
from the inside out.
The rebel and royal armies
will have nowhere to go,
nowhere to turn.
As a result, they will fall
neatly into the hands
of Baroque Works.
If all goes according to plan,
in a single night,
Alabasta Kingdom
will become our utopia.
This mission is the final
and most important act
that Baroque Works
will carry out.
Failure is not an option.
We begin tomorrow at noon.
[GROUP]
Yes, sir!
I wish you luck.
About this Operation Utopia.
May I ask you to
postpone it for a while?
How did you get here?
The location of
this room is a secret.
So what little hidey‐hole
did you crawl out of
to get here, Mr. 3?
Now I will finally
complete my mission.
Hold on. Mr. 2.
I didn't crawl out
from anywhere,
thank you very much.
I merely followed you all
from your little meeting
at Spiders Café.
It was easy enough to do.
I just hitched
a ride on the back
of Bunchi's car, unseen.
Boss. At last we meet.
I have come here to humbly
beg for your forgiveness,
and to ask that I may
be given a second chance.
You see, Mr. 2,
I knew that it was
only a matter of time
before someone was
sent to eliminate me
after I failed to complete
the assignment that I was given.
That is why I made the decision
to change my course
slightly and head directly
for our headquarters
at the Spiders Café.
You said you had failed
to complete a mission.
What are you talking about?
[MR. 3]
Well, you know.
How I was unfortunately
unable to prevent
the Straw Hat brats
and Princess Vivi
from escaping, remember?
[CROCODILE growls]
You're telling me
that they got away.
All of them?
You're saying that
they're still alive?
What were you talking about
on the transponder snail?
You said that they were dead.
Princess Vivi and her
bratty little pirate friends.
You did deal with
them, didn't you?!
[MR. 3]
A Transponder Snail?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I never used a transponder
snail the entire time
I was on Little Garden,
not even once.
What?! [growls]
[SANJI] Yeah, hello, you've
reached the crap café.
Can I take your order?
This isn't good news.
Although it does explain
why the Unluckies
haven't returned
from Little Garden.
I assume you at least got
rid of one or two of them.
No, not exactly.
Wait! The information I was
given wasn't entirely accurate.
There were four pirate
escorts with Princess Vivi,
and then on top of
that there was this
really funny‐looking man
with a long nose.
Damn it!
Please, Boss. Can you
explain to the rest of us
what's going on
with all this insanity?
None of this makes any sense!
All of them!
I met all of these people!
Yes! I ran into them
on my way to the cafe.
Really?
There was this guy.
And this guy.
And this girl.
And this thing, too.
Plus, one more.
So Miss Wednesday
is really a princess
posing as an agent!
You mean these people
are all actually the enemy?!
That's correct. These people
have uncovered who I really am.
They need to be taken care of,
or they'll interfere
with the plan.
Mr. 3, you are
right about one thing.
It does seem like
they have added
one person and one animal.
Their group is
increasing in number
as they continue
to move forward.
Setting the pet aside,
I think there is something
that we can safely
assume at the moment.
Princess Vivi and her
four little friends
are very likely
in Alabasta already.
Now, to prepare.
Mr. 2, make photos of those
faces you displayed.
But... But, Boss, I promise
that I will eliminate Vivi
and her friends with
my own two hands.
[CROCODILE]
Just shut up, you damn fool!
Now, Mr. 3.
Listen very carefully.
Do you have any idea
why I gave you your rank‐‐
why you're an
officer agent? Hmm?
In terms of fighting skills
alone, even Mr. 4 has you beat.
Do you understand that?
I promoted you because
of your underhanded
tenacity when it comes to
completing an assignment.
You have gravely
disappointed me.
What's happening to him?!
He's just shriveling up!
Water... I need water...
Some water...
You can have all the water
you want, down there.
[MR. 3 screams]
[knocking]
It looks to be feeding time.
Where am I now?
Underwater?
It looks almost
like a giant aquarium.
A bananagator!
[MR. 3 screams]
Nothing but trouble.
But no longer!
[slam]
[CROCODILE]
Now the rest of you, listen up!
Take a good look at these five.
They are determined
to stop the rebellion
in Alabasta.
If we leave them alone,
they are bound to come to us.
I understand that.
But Boss, even if the girl is
the princess of this country,
do you really think
that she can prevent
the rebellion at this point?
[CROCODILE] Unfortunately,
she has a connection
that she can take advantage of.
Princess Vivi Nefertari
and the rebel leader, Koza,
were apparently friends
when they were children.
The rebels have seven
hundred thousand.
Even if the rebellion
can't be stopped now,
Princess Vivi is certainly
capable of bringing
real confusion to their ranks.
I've already sent
many of the Billions
to join with Koza's
rebel forces.
The fact that I
haven't heard anything
from our men must mean that Vivi
and her friends have
not yet taken any action.
This is good.
Whatever the cost,
they must be prevented
from making contact
with the rebel army
before the operation is
complete and we have won.
[CROCODILE]
Miss All Sunday?
Sir?
[CROCODILE]
Given the current circumstances,
we should use
transponder snails.
Contact the Billions
who're in Nanohana.
Tell them to kill on sight
without any hesitation.
Do not allow Princess Vivi
and the pirates into Katorea!
Vivi must not be allowed to
meet with the rebel leader Koza!
Yes, sir.
[CROCODILE] Now, the rest
of you get going as well.
You don't want to
miss the fun, do you?
We are very close to
realizing our utopia.
I'd hate to be
disappointed by any of you.
You understand?
Just leave it to us, Boss, sir.
♪ And, we're off!
Go enjoy yourselves.
[TOTO] I'm so sorry I didn't
have more to offer you,
Princess Vivi.
[VIVI]
No, please don't worry about it.
Well, we should
be off now, Toto.
[TOTO] Oh. Luffy.
Here, take this with you.
Wow! Water!
Water!
You found some, then?
Yes, it was last night,
a bit after you fell asleep
while digging that
huge hole of yours.
I finally reached a moist
layer under the dry stuff.
That water there is the moisture
that I was able to extract
from the damp sand.
[LUFFY]
Whoa!
That sounds pretty
complicated, but thank you.
That right there
is genuine Yuba water.
It's not much, but it's
all I was able to get.
Right.
Then I'll drink it with care.
[USOPP] Hey, Luffy, what
are you doing over there?
Luffy?
Um, is everything all right?
I quit.
[GROUP]
Huh?
What do you mean?
What's that mean?
Quit what, Luffy?
Oh, come on.
We don't have time
to put up with
every weird little mood
you have right now, Luffy.
Let's go.
Yeah, shouldn't we get going?
Yes, we should, and fast.
If we don't get back
to that Katorea place
the way we came
and stop the rebellion
that's about to begin, then
a million Alabasta citizens
are gonna start fighting
and things will get real ugly
real quick.
We're doing this for Vivi!
So let's go.
What is wrong with you?!
Vivi.
Yes?
Right now all I wanna do
is kick Crocodile's ass,
you understand?
Maybe we can keep the people
from starting a rebellion,
but that won't stop Crocodile.
Besides, we won't be
able to accomplish
anything in Katorea.
We're pirates.
Everyone knows things
are better off
without us around.
You gotta admit,
he has a way of getting
straight to the point
when he really wants to.
Well, yeah, but not often.
No, that's not true.
[LUFFY] You want it to work
out so that nobody dies
in this fight,
isn't that right, Vivi?
None of the citizens.
None of us, either.
We're up against one
of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea and a million
of your own people
on top of that.
And you still want
everyone to end up
all safe and sound.
You'll never win that way.
Come on, Luffy.
Can't you at least try showing
Vivi a little sympathy?
Wait. Hold on, Nami.
For what?
And what's wrong with that, huh?
What is so wrong
about not wanting
to see people die or get hurt?
'Cause people die, that's why.
Stop talking like that!
I won't listen to it!
Say that again and
I will really hurt you!
That's the whole point
of what we're doing here.
Don't you understand?
No one here in Alabasta,
not the rebel army,
the royal army, or the people,
is to blame for this!
None of them have
done anything wrong!
Why should any
of them have to pay
for what's happened?
When every last bit
of it is Crocodile's fault?
[LUFFY]
So you're saying it's only
all right for you to die!
Whoa, Luffy!
You've gone too far!
Damn it, Luffy!
Just being in this
country one day
and taking a look around,
even I can tell!
Tell what?!
[LUFFY] What this country
needs more than anything!
This oasis has life in it yet.
The dream of Yuba
can't be beaten
by a bunch of lousy sand.
You think that putting
just your life on the line
is enough to stop
this from happening?!
Well, what else exactly
should I be putting
on the line with
it then, Luffy?!
[VIVI] I can't let him
get away with this!
What, Luffy?!
I don't have anything else
I can put on the line.
Just... Just me.
Well, you can
at least try putting
all of our lives
on the line together!
Aren't we friends, huh?
[LUFFY]
Well, aren't we friends?
[VIVI crying]
[LUFFY]
There, now you see.
Now you understand.
Hey, you can cry.
We'll succeed.
We're going to stop this.
I know how much you hate this.
You wanna get
Crocodile the most.
[VIVI crying]
So now tell me.
Where can I find Crocodile?!
♪Remember when we
were kids we longed for
adventures greater than
anything we had ever dreamed!
Let's set sail,
it's not too late!
As I scoop up the sand,
watch it fall between my hands,
The sand, it flows like time...
I can hear it calling!
There's no other way...
the time is now!
I know that this is
what I'm born to do!
Don't look back,
let's keep on swimming now!
At breakneck speed, I know
we'll arrive there soon!
If we do not give up,
Someday we'll wash up on that
white beach we dreamed up,
It's really not
all that far away...♪
[SANJI] What?
The Marines are chasing them?
[NAMI] And they're
still running this way.
[VIVI]
Hey. Tony hasn't come back yet!
[ZORO] Leave him.
He'll manage fine.
[LUFFY]
The Marines are here, you guys!
[ZORO] Yeah, because
they're following you!
[USOPP] This isn't good!
Baroque Works is gonna spot us!
[ZORO] I think it's a
bit too late for that.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"The Battlefront of Alabasta!
Rainbase, the City of Dreams!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!