[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of
the Pirates, attained this
and everything else
the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured
men to the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they've ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
♪
[SWORDSMITH 318A]
You've got to be kidding!
There's no way
I'd repair your sword
for that pathetic amount!
So that's a "no."
Come up with some more
money or forget it!
[ZORO] Cranky old man.
Still can't believe it.
Huh?
[ZORO] Hey, I know them.
[HOICHAEL] Anyway,
good luck with the Navy!
And sorry again.
We shouldn't have
tried to mug you!
That was a mistake!
Ah, don't worry about it--
Thanks for showing me
the way here!
See ya!
[ZORO] It's those two kids
who helped me with directions.
Hey, Zoro! Hey, Zoro!
We want you to be
our brother! Pretty please?
[yowls]
[LUFFY] Mothers Are Strong!
Zoro's Hectic Household Chores!
No way.
[BOTH] You didn't
even think about it!
I don't know
what you're playing at,
but I got better things
to do than pretend to be
the brother of you two clowns.
Come on! Don't be like that!
After all, we're the ones that
helped our big brother Zoro
find the way back
to his friends, remember?
My name's Michael, by the way.
Pleasure to meet you.
And my name's Hoichael!
[BOTH] We know
every corner and street
in this neighborhood! Yeah!
[BOTH] Brother, you're
so rude! We weren't done!
Where are you headed?
We'll take you
anywhere you
wanna go, brother!
The meat shop?
Maybe the grocery store?
I won't.
You won't? Won't what?
Be your brother just because
you helped me with directions.
Get outta here.
Stop bothering me.
[MICHAEL] Hey, brother!
You were just looking for
a sword, weren't you?
I either want this one
repaired or a new one.
And I don't really
have a lot to spend.
Then you should try
the second-hand store!
Let us help you!
We know the best ones
in the neighborhood!
Yeah! Let's show our
new brother the way!
[HOICHAEL]
Come on! Follow us!
Hmph. Fine. Whatever.
Just remember,
I'm not your brother.
I only took you up
on your offer to help.
[BOTH]
Understood, brother!
[ZORO grunts]
Move it! Move it!
Get outta the way!
Make room for
our big brother Zoro,
the pirate hunter!
Stop it!
[CITIZENS whisper]
[grunts]
Hmph.
Augh!
[BOTH grunt]
Looks like those
little hoodlums are
up to no good again.
Their parents should
teach them discipline.
Keep them out of trouble.
Unfortunately,
I don't think these kids
have any parents.
As far as I know,
they're living on the streets,
on their own.
[clanging]
No good here, either. Hm?
What are you lookin' at?
Stop being rude
to our big brother Zoro!
[screams]
Hey. That swordsman with them.
Isn't he part of the pirate crew
that helped save Iceberg
from those assassins?
Yeah, I think you're right.
I figured he was a hero,
but I guess he's a total fake.
How disappointin'.
It seems you two have
quite the reputation.
Whatever.
Those nosy townspeople
don't know anything!
Besides, we don't care
what anyone says about us.
I see. Good for you.
Catch ya' later.
Wait! Where are you going?
You're not going to abandon
your brothers, are you?
I don't remember ever
agreeing to be your brother!
What was that?
What did he say?
I couldn't hear
a single word.
No way! Look! Look over there!
[MICHAEL, HOICHAEL]
What? Where!
Huh?
[MICHAEL, HOICHAEL] Aaah!
[ZORO panting]
There. That oughta do it.
[MICHAEL, HOICHAEL]
Big Bro!
[yells]
[ZORO yells quickly]
--[MICHAEL, HOICHAEL] Big Bro!
--[ZORO screams]
--Big Bro!
[yelling]
Big Bro!
[MICHAEL, HOICHAEL]
Big Bro! Big Bro! Big Bro!
[MICHAEL, HOICHAEL] Big Bro!
[ZORO wails]
[ZORO panting]
Like I said, we know
every street and corner
in this neighborhood.
Trying to sneak away
from us is pointless.
[ZORO]
Just shut up. I've had it.
I'm tired of you two punks
screwing around with me!
[MICHAEL, HOICHAEL]
Aah! That hurt, Big Bro!
I'm not your Big Bro!
Who the hell are you?
You keep your filthy hands
off my house's kids!
These kids are yours? I see.
[WOMAN yells]
Man, you are one tough lady!
Now would you
kindly get off of me?
[wails]
Hey! Not bad, kid!
My turn. Get ready.
Here comes--
My Bam Bam Tornado!
Whoa! Take it easy, Mom!
He's not a bad guy!
Yeah, he's our
new Big Brother!
Then that means you were
up to no good, again! Idiots!
[BOTH] Uh!
Sorry about all that.
But it's good to hear
they found themselves
a new Big Brother.
Glad you agreed.
Look, I didn't agree.
[WOMAN] Go ahead.
Introduce yourselves.
My name's Yoko!
And I'm Yuuya!
I'm Sho. Hi.
My name's Ayako.
Akihiro. Nice to meet ya!
Everyone! This is
the swordsman, Zoro!
He's our brand
new Big Brother!
For the last time,
I am not,
nor will I ever be,
your brother.
Whatever you say.
Either way, we've got housework
and lots of repairs to
take care of now that
Aqua Laguna's over.
Huh?
[YOKO, YUUYA, SHO, AYAKO,
and AKIHIRO] Big Brother!
Hey! Hold on!
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
I am not your
Big Brother! Stop it!
[WOMAN]
Let's take your brother home!
[ALL KIDS] Yeah!
Ah!
By the way,
what's all that junk?
Gathering that stuff
is Mom's job.
She takes as much as
she can carry to port
while we stay home and babysit.
Most of it goes to Galley-La,
and they sort it all out.
Yep, we all come together
and work like a big family.
[BOTH] Huh?
Well, give my thanks to
your mother for the drink.
[MICHAEL]
You're leaving already?
Sorry, but there's not much
reason for me to stay. So--
[yells]
[BABY yells]
Uh! Ngh!
Up we go.
Nice catch, Big Bro!
[BABY crying]
Big Bro!
[crying]
[grunts]
[KIDS clapping]
Looks like you're
a natural at that.
I told you he'd make an
awesome big brother, didn't I?
[grunts]
[yells]
He pissed all over me!
Ugh! Ugh!
Careful! Careful!
Here. Go change his diaper.
[HOICHAEL] Right!
Are you some kind of
pervert? What are you doing?
I'm gonna give it a wash.
Wear this until it dries.
This... must be a nightmare.
He's all yours. All right!
Everyone do your best
to finish up your chores!
[KIDS] Yeah!
Hey, Hoichael!
Listen. I'm sorry,
but I just can't--
Hey! No! Stop!
[giggles]
Michael, help me out.
I need you to do
something with these...
Huh?
[ZORO winces, coughs]
[ZORO] Come on.
Hoichael! Michael!
Where'd you go?
Hm?!
You're doing
good work around here.
Keep it up, son.
[ZORO] All right.
There.
You three sleep quietly now.
[WOMAN humming]
Hey. Gimme my shirt.
I appreciate you cleaning it,
but it's time for me to go.
What are you talking about?
You sayin' you've got
somewhere you'd rather be
than right here?
Yeah. I need to
rejoin my friends.
Come on!
Who's more important:
your family or your friends?
We're not family.
You didn't give birth to me
and we're not related by blood.
So cut the crap
and gimme back my shirt.
Shut your mouth!
Who cares if we're
not blood related?
What's so important about
a stupid blood bond, anyway?
[door opens]
I've got another matter
I need to discuss with you.
You were just
here two days ago.
I was here
the day before that,
and yesterday, too,
dammit! I won't give up!
Eh? And who is this?
I don't recall
seeing you before.
A new family member, perhaps?
--[WOMAN] That's right.
--[ZORO] Hell no.
Which is it?!
Who cares? It doesn't matter.
Listen, I'm wise to that
Paulie guy from Galley-La.
Ya know, he can't keep covering
for you forever, Auntie.
There's nothing to cover!
I returned the loan, didn't I?
You fool!
That loan generated interest
the moment you borrowed it.
That interest
generated more interest,
raising the total owed
to ten times the amount
you borrowed from us
in the beginning.
I returned the loan.
What else do ya' want?
That interest is yours to pay.
Dammit! That's not
how this works!
It's quite the fiscal
burden to take on a loan.
Maybe you could sell off one of
these kids to lighten the load.
After all, it's not
like they're really
part of your family, right?
What did you say?
Huh...?
[ZORO]
Now that he's mentioned it,
none of them look alike at all!
[LOANSHARK 318A groans]
Hey! That hurt!
What the hell are you trying
to pull here, Auntie?
Talk about my family again,
I'll knock
your head off! Got it?
[LOANSHARK 318A] Shoot her!
[LOANSHARKS gasp]
[LOANSHARKS whimper]
Well then! I've said
what I had to say,
so now we'll be off!
Let's move out, men!
[LOANSHARKS
318B and 318C whimper]
Hmph!
[KIDS gasp]
Awesome!
Way to go, Big Bro!
Good boy! You've made
your momma happy!
Right! Let's finish
the shopping,
then go home for dinner!
[KIDS] Yay!
Well... Guess I'll
get going then.
Yeah, you're going.
Along with us, that is. Come on!
[grunts]
[running footsteps]
[panting]
[MAN] I assume you
have some work for me?
[laughs intensely]
Come on! You call
that a discount?
We'll have to take our
business elsewhere
if you can't come up
with a better offer.
Can't you two
stay out of trouble?
Ughhh. No matter how I
look at it, this is just wrong.
What am I doing here?
I'll sneak away the first
chance I get, then I'll--
[yells]
Crap!
Why'd you have
to show up, stupid cook?
[grunts]
Then that would make
this way a shortcut, right?
Thanks for your help.
I gotta hide.
[yells]
There. I think I lost 'em.
Aaah!
Come on!
[grunts] Dammit.
I can't run anymore.
[ROBIN] Having a rough time?
Ha. You could say that.
I don't even know how I
let myself get into this mess.
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me!
[ROBIN chuckles]
Now, listen--
[NAMI] Robin!
[NAMI] I wonder where she went.
[NAMI] Robin?!
[ZORO sighs]
You don't have to
worry about anything.
Your secret is safe with me.
And, to be honest,
it suits you.
[chuckles softly]
[ZORO grunts softly]
I've had enough!
I'm outta here!
What's that?
You wanna head back?
Fine, then let me
give you the house key.
Make sure you
clean the toilets.
No! Look, I'm not
going back to your house!
I'm gonna go back
to where my friends are!
Stop talking that
crazy nonsense!
You're the crazy one, lady!
Show some respect!
How dare you speak to
your mother that way!
You're not my mom!
Shut up!
Rude little broccoli head!
It's not broccoli!
It's moss!
Ah! He's a moss head!
Big Bro the moss head!
[KIDS] Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
[ZORO grunts] Look, you brats!
I'm not a moss head!
I'm outta here.
[KIDS] Mm?
Just as I'd expect
from the eldest son.
Michael, Hoichael. Be sure
to bring him back later.
[BOTH] 'Kay!
Come on, kids.
Let's go home.
[KIDS] Okay!
Uh!
Well! Look at this!
Heh. It appears you've
lost your little bodyguard.
Now, as I recall,
we were discussing the matter
of the money
you still owe us.
Care to join me as our guest?
Hoichael. Go get Big Bro.
I think we know where
they're gonna take us.
Right.
[growls]
♪
We're not family.
You didn't give birth to me
and we're not related by blood.
So cut the crap
and gimme back my shirt.
Shut your mouth!
Who cares if we're
not blood related?
What's so important about
a stupid blood bond, anyway?
[HOICHAEL] Big Brother!
[ZORO] Hm?
There's trouble!
Our mom has been taken away
by that mean ol' loan shark!
Sorry, but that's got
nothing to do with me.
I'm sure Auntie
can handle herself.
But this time he had a bunch
of other guys helping him!
They took Michael and our other
brothers and sisters with her!
They what?!
Last time,
you conveniently had that
swordsman to protect you.
So, just in case
he happened to show up
and cause more trouble,
I brought a swordsman
of my very own!
Come on out, my friend!
[LOANSHARK 318A]
Currently wanted with a bounty
of 36 million berries,
the Captain of the Big
Helmet Pirates, Mikazuki!
All right, you kids stay back.
Let me handle this.
[laughs]
When I first met Mikazuki,
he was having his ship
repaired at Dock 1
and got into a
bit of a disagreement
with the foremen
of Galley-La.
They may have had the
upper-hand at the time,
but right now, they're
too busy repairing houses
and other parts of Water 7
to be able to do any--
So, I'm gonna give you
a couple of choices here.
You're either going
to fight me one-on-one...
...or you're going to
pay these guys
the debt you owe them in full.
[MIKAZUKI laughs]
Give it some thought!
I eagerly await your decision.
Oh! You wanna fight, huh?
You've got some guts!
But I simply must ask you.
What can you do to a man
with a bounty like mine? Huh?
[AUNTIE] Bam-Bam Tornado!
Go, Mom! Get him!
Your little tricks
won't stop someone like me!
You're sure this is
the way they went?
It's the same place
they always take her!
I followed them there
in secret one time!
[ZORO] Dammit!
[AUNTIE grunts, groans]
[laughs]
The government didn't
give me that bounty
for nothing, you know!
I thought I told you
to stay out of this!
Are you trying to
get yourself killed?
I'm not gonna let him hurt you!
We're a family, right?
We gotta look out
for each other!
[scoffs] They grow up so fast.
Brave little idiot.
Look, Big Bro! Over there!
All right, guys. I'll let you
handle the rest of the job.
[MEN chuckle]
[KIDS whimper]
[chuckles]
[HOICHAEL] Mom!
[ZORO grunts]
[MEN yell]
[ZORO scoffs]
Big Bro!
Gimme a break!
72 Caliber Phoenix!
Now Die!
[ZORO grunts]
[MIKAZUKI yells]
[LOANSHARK 318A]
Uh! Keep away from me!
[yells]
[splash]
--[KIDS clapping]
--[MICHAEL] Awesome!
That's our bro!
[KIDS cheering]
Good work! Nicely done!
I'd expect no less from my son!
Stop calling me that!
Now listen, Auntie!
Let's get things straight.
I have friends
waiting for me that--
That are just like
family to you?
Kind of like how everyone
at my house is for me?
Yeah, that's right.
It's a lot like that.
Then why didn't you just
say so in the first place?
I did! Like, a million times!
[KIDS laugh]
You're a very precious
member of this family,
but I suppose I can
let you leave the nest
for a little while.
I'm leaving for good.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Hey, Bro! Congrats!
You're a man now!
You'd better leave
before Mom changes her mind
about letting you go.
[ALL] Take care, big brother!
You, too.
--[MICHAEL] Bye, Big Bro!
--[HOICHAEL] See ya!
[KIDS chatter goodbyes]
Hey! Wait a minute! Come back!
[ZORO stammers]
Oh, no you don't!
Clean getaway.
Should be all right.
[AUNTIE] Wait!
[ZORO screams]
He'll never learn, will he?
You can't sneak away from us!
Idiot son!
I can't believe he left
without getting his shirt back!
What am I gonna do
with that boy?
No. No!
[AUNTIE] I said stop!
Wait! Come back!
[ZORO] Leave me alone!
Go away!
[SANJI]
Hey! Quit pulling, Chimney!
[CHIMNEY]
Granny told me about this place!
It's the best!
[GONBE] Meow!
[SANJI] What a dump.
[CHIMNEY]
Hey, Grandpa Cook! We're hungry!
[GONBE] Meow!
[SANJI] There's no way
this old drunk can cook--
Huh? I take it back.
This food is amazing!
[LUFFY] On the next One Piece:
Sanji's Shock!
Mysterious Old Man
and His Super Yummy Cooking.
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!