[LUFFY] Did you know
there's an awesome treasure
hidden at the end of this sea?
And anyone who finds it
will be King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
BON VOYAGE!
Have the courage, set sail
and believe and we will see
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons
Sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now
For together we found we look
through the spyglass and see,
And we know, that our
hearts have brought us here.
Where the compass
points our destiny,
There's no looking back,
take the helm with me!
Bon Voyage!
We cast off all our troubles,
forget the past.
Though the future's unclear
We still can smile
we know we'll get there.
No regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only
helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow!
[ENERU] God only knows,
and he's not telling.
[NARRATOR] Attempting
to escape from the Upper Yard,
Nami and her team were
heading for the east coast
when Eneru suddenly appeared.
He attacked and severely burned
Sanji and Usopp, then vanished.
Ha! You can call me Hotori!
Ha! And you can call me Kotori!
[NARRATOR] As if in his place,
Satori's twin brothers,
Hotori and Kotori, appeared,
seeking revenge.
[HOTORI]
Ha-ha-hah!
[NAMI] I'm the one who
has to protect my friends!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the four who headed south
in search of the ancient
ruins were separated
after an encounter
with a giant snake.
Its descendants built it,
after the great city fell.
Shandora, that was the
name of this ancient place.
Who's there?
[LUFFY]
Where am I?
But you're in the dirt 'cause
I hate being told what to do.
I will survive.
You watch.
[gasps]
So careless!
[CHOPPER]
What a dimwit!
[NARRATOR]
Each has encountered enemies
and been forced to
fight for their lives.
In the most recent battle,
Chopper fought and
defeated the Priest Gedatsu.
[CHOPPER]
My turn.
Cloven Cross!
[LUFFY] "Unbeatable Powers!
Eneru's True Form is Revealed!"
[SHANDORAN A]
You all right, Kamakiri?
[KAMAKIRI]
Don't worry about me!
Stay focused
on the surroundings!
There!
Look, in the clouds above!
I can see Giant Jack!
We're close to
the ruins of Shandora!
Eneru's got to be up
there somewhere.
[distant screaming]
[ENERU]
You called?
I'm right here behind you.
[chuckles]
Did you want something?
Brave Kamakiri of Shandora.
Eneru, you bastard!
Have you forgotten to
whom you are speaking?
I am God, you know.
[ENERU] And I know exactly
what you're thinking, warrior.
You're wondering
why I came down here.
Mantra?
[laughs]
[ENERU]
I don't need my mantra
to read what's written
all over your face!
[laughs]
But I don't blame you.
Normally,
I don't bother to fight,
but this time, I'm a player
in the Survival Game too.
Besides, I'll be
leaving this land soon.
I was just saying
good-bye to Gan Fall.
Professional courtesy,
you understand.
A game? A game?
I also don't need
my mantra to tell me
that you'd really like
to kill me right now.
[ENERU]
Very well.
I must admit you've shown
great courage in reaching me,
so I'd say you're
entitled to a reward.
Call it a display of God's
mercy. Heh, heh.
So, then,
I'll give you five minutes.
For five minutes,
I won't move a muscle.
[KAMAKIRI]
What?
[ENERU] I won't dodge your
attacks, and I won't fight back.
Fry me.
Skewer me.
I am at your mercy.
[laughs]
[KAMAKIRI]
Why, you!
[ENERU] But once
those five minutes are up.
You will know what
it means to face God
in the very depths of your soul.
[KAMAKIRI]
I've had enough of you!
[KAMKIRI]
Time to die, Eneru!
Ha-ha-hah! Ha-ha-hah!
Damn you!
You missed us!
No!
[HOTORI, KOTORI]
Ha-ha-hah!
[NAMI]
You've got to stop!
[HOTORI]
We won't stop!
[KOTORI]
[HOTORI, KOTORI]
Ha-ha-hah!
I said stop!
They're unconscious!
[HOTORI]
We don't care!
[KOTORI]
[HOTORI] These guys
killed our brother Satori!
[KOTORI]
Killed him!
[HOTORI, KOTORI]
They must pay!
Ha-ha!
Thanks for the charge!
[NAMI]
An Impact?
[farts]
Ha-ha-hah!
I stored my farts
in a Flavor Dial!
Ha-ha!
So that's it.
They have four different
types of Dials they're using,
instead of just one.
[HOTORI]
Ha-ha-hah! That's right!
Axe! Flame!
Impact! Flavor! Ha-ha-ha.
You won't be able to keep track!
Which one is Hotori
and which one is Kotori?
[HOTORI]
What Dial is in which hand?
It's so much fun to guess!
[HOTORI, KOTORI]
Surprise Dial Illusion!
Ha.ha-hah!
[GAN FALL]
We know what they have.
There's no time to waste!
I didn't care which
one of those puffballs
was which in the first place!
Suck typhoon, boys!
[KOTORI]
You missed!
[KOTORI, HOTORI]
Ha-ha-hah!
[HOTORI]
You missed!
[KOTORI] Guess which
Dial's in my right hand?
Ha ha ha ha!
I fooled you! More farts!
Were you expecting flames?
Ha-ha-hah!
He's going to ignite the gas!
Old man!
[HOTORI]
Ha ha ha-hah!
[KOTORI]
Fool! He's been blown away!
[BOTH shriek]
[GAN FALL] That was
a childishly obvious trick.
I'm afraid you
underestimated me.
[HOTORI]
Kotori!
[NAMI]
Return!
Cyclone Tempo.
[GAN FALL]
You, girl.
Retrieve my gauntlet from the
lower deck and finish him off!
[NAMI]
What's wrong?
Did your wounds open?
[GAN FALL]
Forget me!
He'll be back soon!
[NAMI]
Gauntlet?
Gauntlet, gauntlet, gauntlet?
Hey, what's a gauntlet?
[NAMI]
Oh.
It's heavy!
[GAN FALL] It's made of iron
from the Blue Sea World.
There's an
Impact Dial inside of it.
Use it as I instructed you.
Yeah, I get the idea, but
I can barely lift this thing!
[HOTORI screams]
Well, there's no time
to worry about that now!
First Satori and then Kotori.
You'll pay.
Now it's your turn!
[NAMI]
He's the one who uses fire.
He's sopping wet,
and the air is full of moisture.
Cool Ball!
[HOTORI]
Huh? What's this, just cold air?
Is that all?
[NAMI]
Yep! Cold air, and you use fire!
Are you mocking me?
Do you really think
a little breeze
can extinguish my Flame Dial?
[screams]
I'll burn you to ashes!
[NAMI] That hot air
flowing over the cold air
will cause the moisture
in the air to condense!
It'll form a mist!
Fog Tempo!
[HOTORI]
What's this?
There's fog everywhere!
I can't see anything!
What are you doing?
[HOTORI] What?
What is this? What's going on?
[NAMI]
I beg your pardon!
And Impact.
Ow!!
Argh! That thing
nearly blew my arm off!
What do you think
you're doing, you old fool!
The pain will pass, my dear,
but I must say, you were superb!
[NAMI]
Hey, yeah!
I protected the ship
and the crew!
[PAGAYA] Uh, do you mind
if I call you Aisa?
Can you really tell
which way the Gravity Blue
Riders' ship is heading?
[AISA]
Yeah.
[CONIS]
That's amazing.
Even from this far away,
you can hear the sound of
their voices inside the forest.
But are you sure
you're feeling all right?
You've been trembling
ever since we picked you up.
[AISA]
It's just...
It's just that I've never
ever been this afraid before.
Everyone's voices.
Everyone's voices keep
disappearing one by one.
[PAGAYA]
Yes, I am sorry.
We've got to hurry, Conis.
Yes, Father.
Hold on!
Where do you think you're going?
I'm sorry, but I've got
to locate Eneru.
You can't leave a lady
all alone way out here!
I already said I was sorry!
I must know why Eneru's chosen
to come down into the forest
and take a
personal hand in this.
It could be...
"It could be" what?
When Eneru first appeared,
he captured 650 members of the
Divine Squad under my command.
I don't have time
to explain my suspicions,
but I fear that my men's
lives may be in great danger.
No. This whole land
may be in danger.
Pierre, can you fly?
[squawks]
[NAMI]
Wait!
I'll leave you my gauntlet
with the Impact Dial inside.
You should manage just fine.
That's all?
Ugh! Hold it right there,
you, you heartless brute!
How could you?
And you call yourself a god?
Get back here!
Think this over!
[NAMI]
I'm gonna cry!
I guess the main thing
now would be
to give these guys
some first aid.
You guys are still alive,
aren't you?
Oh, Chopper, hurry up
and get back here!
[screams]
What? What? What?
[horn trumpeting]
Heso!
Conis?
[PAGAYA]
Heso!
[NAMI]
And her dad?
What are you doing here?
[horn trumpeting]
[NAMI] And would you knock it
off with that horn already!
Let me go!
[PAGAYA]
Wait.
No! You mustn't go!
Let go!
[PAGAYA]
You can't go into the forest!
You'll be killed!
I promise we'll only stay
for a little while!
[NAMI]
And that's?
[PAGAYA]
Oh, this young lady is Aisa.
Stand back, you Blue Sea
devil, or I'll smash you!
I'm a brave warrior of Shandora!
That's nice, kid.
You wanna fight me?
Have a faceful of Impact.
[CONIS]
This is terrible!
They've been burnt black!
They need first aid at once!
[PAGAYA]
At any rate, I'm sorry.
Now quick, turn your ship up
the path we just came on!
We used a Milky Dial
to create a new river.
If you follow it, you can exit
directly to the White-White Sea.
Quick, before the enemy
realizes we're here!
Then shouldn't
you have been
a little quieter getting here?
Oh, by the way,
I almost forgot.
I brought something to give you!
For me?
A Waver?
I hope you don't mind.
I repaired the Waver you
brought along with you
when you came up
from the Blue Sea.
Please take it.
It belongs to you after all.
[NAMI]
Oh! Really?
[PAGAYA]
Of course.
[NAMI]
Cool!
Perhaps I should
warn you, though.
This is no ordinary Waver.
[NAMI]
Huh?
It's far more powerful
than a normal Waver.
I'm sorry.
[yawns]
[roars]
What? Oh, are you still here?
I'm sorry.
I guess I must've dozed off.
Is something wrong?
You seem to be
in pain, Kamakiri.
I've kept my promise, haven't I?
I haven't moved a muscle.
I can't... beat you, can I?
[ENERU]
No, you can't.
Do you understand now?
I am living lightning.
Try as you might, no mere man
can defeat such divine power.
Surely, as a native of the sky,
you've seen it flashing
in the distance, haven't you?
Since ancient times
men have trembled
before the unknown
forces of nature
and worshipped
them as God.
Anything the fools could not
understand reduced them
to abject terror.
No matter what
happens to mankind,
whether it's for
good or for evil,
it is said to be
the work of God.
It's inevitable.
Mankind accepts that
it can never defeat
the disasters of nature.
I'm one of them.
That's what makes me God.
Do you understand?
Oh, a Breath Dial, eh?
[KAMAKIRI]
Burn Blade!
[KAMKIRI]
I have to tell Wyper!
We can't win this battle!
[KAMAKIRI]
This is suicide!
Even if he sacrifices himself,
the Reject won't work!
[ENERU]
It's too late to run now.
[KAMAKIRI] We've got
to fall back and regroup!
Or else... Or else...
[ENERU laughs]
Did you think that you could
move faster than lightning?
[laughs]
Your five minutes are up.
And now it's my turn.
One million volt, Vari!
[KAMAKIRI]
Wyper!
[chuckles]
[ENERU]
Hmm?
Did you hear that?
[screams]
What? What's happening?
What's wrong?
[NAMI]
Aisa!
[AISA] The voices.
They're disappearing!
Damn.
I guess my electricity traveled
down the Milky Road.
Another twenty voices vanished
after that lightning bolt.
The stupid fools.
[ENERU] On Upper Yard, 81
people began the survival game.
Two hours have passed,
and of that 81, 56 have fallen.
[ENERU] Thirteen of my
Divine Squad still remain.
Five members of the Straw Hat
crew are still with us.
And seven warriors of Shandora.
That means there are
25 players still in the game.
That's a lot more survivors
than I predicted there would be.
No matter,
They'll all fall in their turn,
one right after another.
The only real question remaining
is, who will come with me?
This necklace is solid gold!
Does that mean the City of Gold
is here inside this cave?
[stomach growls]
I wish there was a barbecue
shop in here too, jeez!
Oh boo!
Where am I? Where am I?
You can't stop me now,
I'm always going...
A to Z, I run
without stopping...
Sometimes I worry,
I'm not gonna make it...
But I know that,
it's just a little farther...
The sea's spread before us,
and our cares are behind...
The sunrise climbs to the sky,
what will we find?
Come with me,
follow the shining sun...
Watch the horizon,
the journey's just begun...
I, never treat you bad...
Even when we fail...
(It's) all right,
we still can't give up now...
('Cause) You and I both know...
(Through) every high and low...
We sail towards tomorrow...
So SMILE!!
Come back to your friends...
[LUFFY]
Argh! What's with this cave?
Where's the exit?
[NAMI]
For Pete's sake!
What are you doing there?
[ZORO]
Gimme a break!
Did you get lost?
[NAMI]
Look who's talking!
[ZORO]
What?
[LUFFY]
Ugh, I'm hungry!
[ENERU] Will any of you
people manage to make it
to the end of my
little survival game?
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece!
"A Mystical City!
The Grand Ruins of Shandora!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!