[LIZ]
You're adorable, Patty.
Thanks, Sis, that's sweet!
[panting]
[PATTY]
Sis, what?
[LIZ]
There's still plenty more.
Yum!
[LIZ]
Patty.
This is lame.
How about we ditch class
and go find somewhere to smoke?
I've got a C-note, so I say we
grab some honeys and tear it up.
You down with that?
Uh, You guys. Maybe we
should tone it down considering
we're in Master's shop.
Yeah?
You want some of this, do ya?
[MEME] I'll bust a
cap in you! Bring it!
Man, I wish I'd never
introduced them to that show.
The hell are you from, girlie?
I'm the hell from
CSI, that's where!
[INVESTIGATOR]
Hey, you! Get over here and
analyze the soil trace
on the bottom of this shoe!
[YO-YO GIRL] How did I end
up stuck here collectin' prints?
You punks!
You better stop screwin' around!
The hell are you
from, anyway, girlie?
Wha, me? The DWMA.
Yeah? And where's that?
I never heard of
that place before.
You know Meme,
given your memory problems,
that doesn't necessarily
come across as a joke.
It's not.
What is the DWMA?
[TSUGUMI] The
academy the three of us go to.
[LIZ] Hey!
You gonna order
something already?
Oh, yes, of course.
I'll just have a
Napolitan, please.
Today's lunch special, please.
Um, er....
Huh?
I, um. Uh-uh-uh-uh-um.
Okay.
The order's ready.
Here you go.
Go on, Patty.
[ANYA]
I wonder who they are.
I don't think they're
faking the "tough guy" routine.
Those gals are the real deal!
[ANYA] We better keep our
peepers on 'em just to be safe.
Oh, good.
We're still doing that.
[ANYA] You shouldn't
slam plates down like that.
Also, I ordered a Napolitan,
not whatever this sandwich is.
Huh?
You want a Napolitan?
[PATTY]
Never heard of it.
Okay. Well,
everything Master prepares
is delicious, so I
suppose this will suffice.
Just shut up and eat what's
in front of you, princess.
You'll regret it if you don't.
All right, our shift's
over. We're takin' off now.
Okay. Well, good work today.
Who are they, Master?
[MASTER]
Oh, them?
[MASTER] My new hires.
The Thompson sisters,
Liz and Patty.
They're on probation,
so do me a favor
and go easy on 'em, okay?
What do you
mean, "on probation"?
Well, interestingly enough,
they're like our Tsugumi here.
They have the ability
to transform into weapons.
[MASTER] When they were just
children, they were abandoned
on the streets of
Brooklyn, New York. In order to
keep themselves from
starving, they had to
dirty their hands a little.
[MASTER] Of course, a
crime is a crime, whether or not
it's a matter of survival.
[MASTER] However,
they caught the eye
of a certain VIP from the DWMA.
The sisters were wearing
bracelets around their wrists.
Did you notice that?
[MASTER] They're
equipped with GPS trackers.
By activating them,
the DWMA can always
know where the sisters are.
Well, that's a
relief. Those young ladies
seem like they ought to be
kept under close supervision.
[MASTER]
Here you go. It's on the house.
[ALL] Ooh!
[MASTER]
Sorry about today.
[ANYA] Everything
you make is fantastic,
but even for you the
Napolitan is something special.
[MEME]
Can we have some?
You're not going
to eat it all, right?
[ANYA]
Of course I'm not!
[TSUGUMI] You said
they were abandoned
when they were children.
Why would somebody do that?
[MASTER] It's not
something I've asked them about.
I just thought maybe their
weapon abilities were to blame.
They're alive
because of those abilities.
That's how they were able to
make it this far on their own.
If they didn't have
their weapon powers,
well, they're pretty
girls, and you know...
There's no telling
what could have happened.
Hmm. Weapon
abilities, pros and cons.
[ANYA]
Hey, Tsugumi!
We're going to finish
this off without you!
Huh?
Wait, don't! I'm coming!
[ANYA]
Watch it, Meme.
You're taking
more than your share.
You're right, I am.
[ANYA] Why! That's
absolutely shameless!
[MEME]
Okay, fine. Say "ah."
[ANYA] "Ah." Wha- whoa!
Hold on! What are you doing?
[ANYA]
That was delicious!
[MASTER] Good.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
[ANYA]
You know, Meme...
You look like you've put
on a little weight lately.
Maybe.
I don't even remember the
last time I weighed myself.
Oh. It's those
annoying customers
from earlier, Patty. You
know what I just realized?
We never did get
our tip from you.
Customers aren't
actually expected
to leave tips at
Deathbucks Café.
You don't even know that?
You must not be
very good at your job.
[PATTY]
Yeah?
Someone who's
dressed like a princess
really shouldn't
talk so tough.
It isn't very
good for your health.
[LIZ] Let's take
this somewhere else.
[LIZ] You guys are
DWMA students, right?
Why not show us your
fancy academy skills, huh?
No, no, no.
We're actually in
the NOT class rather
than the EAT
class, you see.
So fighting isn't our thing.
So you're not only annoying--
you're worthless, too.
[ANYA] Whatever class we may
be in, we won't just stand here
and let you talk
to us in this manner.
[TSUGUMI]
But Anya.
We're as good as
you are. We're DWMA students!
Sounds to me like they
wanna go at it, huh, Patty?
Yeah.
This oughtta be good.
You're up, Tsugumi.
Transform yourself.
[ANYA]
Do it now!
I don't want
anyone getting hurt.
Wait, Anya. You're
really going to fight them?
Aw, how sad.
[LIZ] Your blade
hasn't even come in yet.
Well, you ready, Patty?
'Course I am.
Let's do it, Sis.
[TSUGUMI]
I wonder what it'll be.
Since they're
street thugs, maybe
a bat or chain or something?
Or pocket knife
or brass knuckles.
She's a pistol!
Well, what's the matter now?
[LIZ]
What's wrong, princess?
Too scared to fight us?
Were you all talk, then?
[TSUGUMI] Well, considering
I'm a close-range weapon
without a blade,
and you've got a gun.
This isn't exactly a fair fight.
Who said it would be?
[LIZ] Some people are
born with everything,
and some people aren't.
Fair has nothing
to do with it.
This is a real
fight, not a fair one.
We aren't competing
in a ring for trophies.
This isn't a sport.
[LIZ] Anyone who agrees to
fight under equal conditions
is either a damned fool
or an arrogant jerk who's
underestimating her opponent.
You would be better
off at home polishing
your tiara and
playing with your dolls.
You shouldn't say that.
Not until after
you've defeated me.
Like I'm gonna be
intimidated by someone who
wouldn't last
three days on the street.
Okay, tell you
what. I won't shoot.
I'll just stand here.
I'll show you!
[LIZ]
Patty!
[TSUGUMI] Yeah, that's
right! They're both weapons!
Remember what my sister said...
We never fight under equal
conditions if we can help it.
[gunshot]
What did they do?
Are you okay?
We would probably get
in some serious trouble
if we messed you up
while we were on probation.
So we'll let you
off with a warning for now.
[SID] It's commonly held
that the first humans that
could transform into
weapons were born as a
result of witches' research.
[SID] Using witch souls and
their ability to transform,
the witches
joined weapons and people,
thus creating the genes
for becoming a living weapon.
[SID]
Those genes became atavistic,
and that is how you came
to be here. Additionally...
[bell chimes]
That's it, right?
We're all finished for today.
I say we go get some lunch.
We could go to Master's
shop. He always has good food.
You are joking
about that, right?
Uh.
[MEME]
Don't look at us like that!
Even I won't ever
forget how those two sisters
nearly popped a cap in
us. It was too terrifying!
Oh, that's enough!
I thought I told
you it's past time that
you stopped
using that street slang.
[ANYA] You were supposed
to forget those inappropriate
terms, but instead
you forgot to forget.
[MEME]
This is getting complicated.
What exactly did
I forget this time?
Ah, welcome back.
Hi. Anya and Meme are
really busy today so...
it's just me.
[MOUSTACHE MAN]
What's the matter with you!
I've never gotten
worse service than this.
I don't really care.
If you've got a problem,
take it up with
the guy who hired me.
[MOUSTACHE MAN] You're lucky you
have a pretty face, you brat.
[LIZ] Oh, yeah? Well,
shut it, you dirty old man.
It's you.
What do ya want?
I'm sorry!
Please don't be mad, okay?
I didn't come here
to bother you, I swear!
I like this place, that's all.
So I came to get something
to eat, like I usually do.
Don't mind me.
So hurry up and order already.
Oh, right! Of course!
I'm sorry! I've
already chosen something.
Um, what was it again?
[ANYA]
You're going there again today?
[TSUGUMI]
Yes.
But today is special
strawberry tart day, remember?
The three of us have
a date in the cafeteria.
Why are you set on this, anyway?
[TSUGUMI] Because
weapons should stick together.
[TSUGUMI] I had a
nice, normal childhood.
If I'd been
abandoned in Brooklyn,
I probably would have
been dead in under three days.
That's it!
I'm going to that café
and ordering whatever I want!
Hands down, that was
the worst service ever.
Yeah, they did
everything but spit on us.
All right!
Looks like the coast is clear.
Seriously?
You again?
Y-Yes, it's me.
And there's something
I came here to order.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
I would like one pilaf, please.
I would like...
[JACQUELINE]
Tsugumi?
Yo!
You heading out?
Yes!
Deathbucks or bust!
Wow, you sure
seem worked up about it.
Oh, I am!
I mean business.
I can make it on
the streets, they'll see.
Huh?
[TSUGUMI]
This is a real fight!
Yes, it's me again.
I, um...
I would like one pilaf!
Too bad I didn't
ask what you wanted.
Huh!
Why do you come down here
every day, you little freak?
Uh.
What do you think
I come here for?
You trying to start a
fight with that smart mouth!
[TSUGUMI] No!
I didn't mean it like that!
[glass shatters]
[SUIT MAN]
Hey! Be more careful!
Huh?
Some of it got on my shoe.
Go get something to
wipe it up right now!
Why don't you wipe it up?
Your face is raggy
enough to do the job.
What was that!
I'm a paying customer!
[SUIT MAN]
You watch yourself!
Why, you!
[TSUGUMI]
No, don't!
[crash]
I'm okay!
I promise, I'm fine.
I just slipped on some
coffee and took a little tumble.
[screams]
Anyway, I was bleeding.
That startled me,
so I sort of screamed.
And then everyone
was totally panicking.
After that?
[TSUGUMI] Don't be
so upset with her, Anya.
It was an accident.
These things happen sometimes.
You aren't taking
this seriously enough.
[ANYA] You have to
make it known that this
kind of violence is
absolutely unacceptable!
Are you okay?
Quick, Patty,
grab us a soft towel.
I'm on it.
[MASTER ] Liz, there's
a first-aid kit in the back.
Okay.
[SUIT MAN]
I'm not responsible!
You're the one to blame here!
I am, huh!
[MASTER]
Excuse me, sir.
You need to leave.
[SUIT MAN]
I'm never coming back!
Go on, Liz.
[LIZ] Where in the back
is this thing? Ow.
[giggles]
Oh, dear.
Why is she laughing?
She must have been
hit harder than we thought.
Should we be worried?
[LIZ] What the hell
are you doing here?
[LIZ] Are you
spying on us again?
[LIZ] If you're not gonna
order, then get out already.
[LIZ]
You're bothering the customers.
What customers?
Thanks to you, there
don't appear to be any.
You were supposed to
behave yourselves here.
What do you think
community service is for?
[LIZ] Just shut
up! Get outta here!
Excuse me.
Uh, what are you?
[TSUGUMI]
Shining, golden eyes.
[TSUGUMI] Um.
Hmm. Better.
[KID]
You're all symmetrical now.
I'll be on my way.
What does he
mean, "symmetrical"?
I'm so bored.
Ugh, what's the big deal?
We're doing everything
like we're supposed to.
We're even wearing these
frilly, degrading uniforms.
[LIZ]
We can't help how we are!
On the streets
you can't sit back
and take crap from anyone.
[LIZ] How are we
supposed to suddenly start being
all sweet to everybody!
It may not help, but I
know you're trying your best.
No one is expecting--
[LIZ] Oh, please.
Don't give me that!
Don't pretend like you
understand anything about us.
No one really does.
Sorry if I'm interrupting.
Why do you keep
coming back here?
I mean it. You already
got punched in the face once.
[LIZ] So why?
You messing with us?
I wouldn't do that.
What, then?
You want to prove
you're not scared of us?
[TSUGUMI]
No! That's not it, either.
I am scared! I'm terrified.
But even though I'm
afraid, there's more to it.
I can't help but
admire your strength, too.
I hoped that if
I kept coming here,
I would get to be
a little stronger,
like you two are, you know?
And also, if I'm
being totally honest...
I have to admit
I'm kinda jealous of
how cool you are.
[TSUGUMI] And
pretty, too, for that matter.
Eh, shut up.
What d'you know, anyway?
What's wrong with you, Sis?
[GREEN HOODIE MAN]
Is this the right shop?
[RED HOODIE MAN]
Yeah. This is the place.
Apparently the
waitresses are way hot,
but they're super rude
to everyone who comes in.
What is it with you
and getting told off
by pretty girls, man?
[RED HOODIE MAN]
And they never actually bring
you what you order.
[GREEN HOODIE MAN] Well,
this should be interesting.
Hey!
[TSUGUMI]
What are you doing here?
We just thought we'd
stop by and see you.
Fine by me. Come on in, then.
You know, Anya's been
pretty worried about you
and that head wound of yours.
[ANYA] That's not true.
I just came for some tea.
Wow! Everyone's here.
You said
something about a fight.
We wanted to see it.
The fight is
actually over already.
[KIM] And I bet you lost, right?
[TSUGUMI] I did not!
--[MEME] You lost.
--[ANYA] Yes, you did.
You're going to find this place
a lot different
than where you lived before.
[MASTER] There's no need
to be defiant, nor should
you try to ingratiate
yourselves to everybody.
[MASTER] Here we accept a
person's soul for what it is.
That's just how Death City
works. We are who we are.
People don't have
to like us to accept us.
[MASTER]
Now, get to work.
Go on, grab a seat.
We're ready to take your order.
Take our order, huh?
Don't you mean
decide what it is?
You may be right.
'Kay!
I would like one pilaf please!
That's gagantous!
Sorry to bug you
with this on your day off.
It's okay. We get it.
We're the ones who
brought him in, after all.
Besides, it's not like
you had any other plans today.
Might as well be here.
Oh, like you did have plans?
The suspect will be
transferred straight from here
to a special
area below the DWMA.
That's where you
two come in. I want you
to accompany the police
when they do the transfer.
[siren]
You two, after him!
[BOTH] Right!
Can you tell me
what happened here?
I'm not sure.
One of the men
just suddenly went crazy.
[POLICEMAN]
He got the suspect.
[WOMAN] Always remember.
While you are sleeping,
we are still
awake and we keep moving.
[ANYA] The Death Bazaar!
The incredible
festival where commoners gather
to sell of all the
junk they no longer want!
Oh, look!
A bear eating fish!
How neat!
[TSUGUMI] A bear-eating
fish or a fish-eating bear?
[MEME] Wait, who's
eating who? I'm confused.
[ANYA] This place
is like a garbage dump.