[ANYA'S BUTLER]
I have today's schedule
for your review.
Following breakfast,
from nine hour until
eleven hour, will be
liberal arts. The subjects
for today will be
mathematics and geography.
Next, from eleven
until twelve, will be
royal economics, and then
there is a change of clothing
which will be followed
by a state dinner at 12:30.
From 15:00 until 17:00 is
your royal karate training.
Wake up, Anya.
Are you with us, Anya Hepburn?
You know, you're actually pretty
adorable when you're asleep.
I wasn't sleeping!
I was just sitting there,
thinking with my eyes
closed, that's all, but I was
still wide awake. I heard
everything you were saying.
Okay you three,
if you'll follow me,
I'll show you to
the girls' dorm.
Oh, wow!
That's such a beautiful
brooch you've got on.
Hmm?
Oh. Yes,
it's my family crest.
Whoa!
Your family's got a crest?
Well. It's our custom
to wear it at all times,
so I put it on by habit.
If you've
got a crest like that,
you must be from a
real high-class family!
Well, I'm not!
Honestly, sometimes
I think you are just too common.
It is rather disappointing.
Gagantous! Ah!
[TSUGUMI] Um, excuse me?
My name's Eternal Feather.
Oh, well, do we have
much farther to walk?
Not at all. Once we pass through
the market ahead,
we're almost there.
Tsugumi, I'm all turned around.
Could you remind me where
we're headed again? I forgot.
Um, we're going
to the girls' dorm,
where we'll be
living from now on.
Oh, yeah!
That makes sense! Silly me!
[TSUGUMI]
"Silly" doesn't quite cover it.
Not a bad little town,
don't you think, Anya?
I suppose it's sufficient.
I can't imagine
the likes of you
would need anything more.
[ETERNAL FEATHER]
Now, then, the allowance
the school just gave you
has to last for a full week.
You'll be more than a
little sorry if you squander it.
Those funds are what you'll
use to pay for your
meals and any other daily
necessities, so
spend them wisely.
Even if you
account for meals and
whatever else, this
is way more allowance than
I got at home. I feel rich!
Keep in mind there
aren't any advances.
So if you somehow manage
to spend all your money between
now and tomorrow, you'll have
to get a job and earn your own.
It's either that or go hungry.
A real job?
Like, where they pay you?
I wouldn't even
know where to start looking.
I've never had a job
before. I don't know if
I'm really old enough for one.
Oh, yeah? Me too.
I was wondering
how old you were.
I'm 14.
Oh! Then
we're the same!
And different.
As it happens,
I'm fourteen, too.
Yeah?
[ETERNAL FEATHER]
Students' ages frequently vary
at this school, even
within the same class.
This is perfect, huh?
Uh-huh!
Here we are.
The DWMA girls' dorm.
[TSUGUMI] Wow!
[TSUGUMI] Amazing! What do
you guys think? Isn't it great?
I must admit
that I am surprised.
I was expecting
something much more modest.
One more thing
before we go in.
Something very
important that you should
all keep in mind.
Watch out for the witch
of the girls' dormitory.
Huh? There's a witch?
[crows]
All right, welcome to your
new home away from home!
A witch at the DWMA?
Preposterous.
It would be a lot like having
a cat live in a dog kennel.
Looks safe enough so far.
Ladies, this is Kana Altair.
Our resident fortune teller.
Nice to meet you.
As a token
of our meeting,
I'll read your fortune.
Cool.
The reading is
ready. It's not good.
Looks like you'd better
be careful here, new girl.
Hey, uh, do you think
you could be more specific?
A child playing card games.
I wouldn't set any
stock by what she predicts.
The Fool.
The Pig.
That card isn't
even in the tarot!
Go home!
Who is this girl?
She's tiny and insolent!
Take a deep breath, Anya.
Come on. Let's go.
Wait! I'm not done talking!
Hmm.
[ETERNAL FEATHER]
This floor is everybody's shared
living space, so
you'll want to keep it tidy.
The school provides basic
toiletries, but if there's
a specific shampoo or lotion
you like, you're responsible
for buying that yourself.
The kitchen is
also a common area.
Please feel free to
use whatever you find here.
All of the dorm's
furnishings appear to be
1884 Kukirita Arta,
and this is Meissen china.
This place seems to be full
of fine things. How very dull.
What's up, Tsugumi?
Huh?
Is something wrong?
You look flushed.
Oh. I was just wondering
where the witch is, that's all.
I apologize.
Your hair is so perfect,
I'm afraid
I couldn't help myself.
Girls, let me introduce
the dorm's housemaster, Misery.
You can almost always find me
in the housemaster's
room on the first floor,
so if anything comes up.
I'm Meme Tatane.
It's nice to meet you!
Sweet girl.
The pleasure is mine.
I'm really glad to meet you too.
I'm Tsugumi Harudori.
It's Mary.
Well. If you'll follow me,
I'll show you the
room you'll be sharing.
We're leaving,
Tsugumi. Are you coming?
Yeah. Be right there.
At long last,
Mary. I've found you.
[ETERNAL FEATHER]
Here you go. This is your room.
Wow. All this
space for the three of us?
This is awesome!
It looks like your things
have already arrived. Go on
and make yourselves at home.
Thank you so much
for your help, Infinite Plume.
That was a fantastic tour!
Actually, it's
"Eternal Feather."
[MEME] Oh, I'm so sorry!
Wow!
This is really soft!
If I take this
one, is that okay?
Oh. In that
case, I'll take the mi--
[ANYA] Ah! Meme!
What's the problem?
Did you want this one?
Well, I... Not really.
If that's the one you want,
Meme, then you can have it.
Anyplace is fine
with me. I don't care.
Okay, that settles it, then.
I always wanted
a room like this!
[MEME] I know! It's
pretty perfect for us, isn't it?
[TSUGUMI] Mm-hmm. I'm
so excited I may not sleep!
[MEME]
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
[TSUGUMI]
Do you really think so?
[MEME]
Well, I just said so, didn't I?
[TSUGUMI]
Yeah, but are you sure?
I'm turning off
the lights, okay?
Yeah. I'm all
ready for bed.
[TSUGUMI]
Good night. Sleep well.
[WOMAN] She lay down
on the cold stone floor.
Mary thought to herself. "It
was wrong for a commoner like me
to dream such grand
dreams, wasn't it?" And now,
the warmth of Nyaro, purring
in her arms, was the only
thing Mary
could call her own.
Her only comfort in
a cold, cruel world.
Huh? Misery?
What is this?
You know this
novel, don't you?
The Commoner of Flanders.
You, my dear, are exactly how
I've always imagined
the main character Mary Smith
would look if she was alive.
I'm sorry. I don't
understand what you're saying.
I will groom you.
By the time we're done,
you'll be the perfect
Mary, straight out of the book.
You're
the housemaster!
You can't be the
witch of the girls' dorm!
Unfortunately, I think that nose
of yours is a bit
longer than Mary's.
Don't worry,
though. I can fix it.
Great timing, Meme! Help me!
[TSUGUMI] Huh? She's asleep?
There, be a good
girl now, and go back to bed.
She's still sleeping?
Drunken boxing!
Uh, what're you doing?
No, that's wrong. Mary
doesn't need any new friends.
Meme, now would
be a great time to wake up!
Come on, Meme! You can do it!
Although, maybe
you fight better
when you're asleep, huh?
Okay, then. Stay
asleep, but keep fighting!
I get that you're new,
but do you have to be so loud?
I was sleeping.
If you wanna make
it here, you have to get
along with the housemaster,
even if she is a raging psycho.
Did that actually just happen?
Good morning.
How did you two slee--
Is that the sort
of thing they get up to
when I'm not looking? Trollops!
[yawn]
Thank you so much
for helping like you did
last night! I would've
been dead without you!
Can I ask what your name is?
Pay up.
I'm sorry?
You'd be dead if
I didn't help, right?
Doesn't that mean you owe me?
Your entire school
allowance for the week.
I think that's a pretty
fair amount, don't you?
Hurry up already.
Okay.
She's at it again!
It's the witch
of the girls' dorm!
I'll leave you a little
something so you can eat today.
Uh, thank you.
So scary! Whenever she talks,
it makes my skin crawl.
Okay, see you later.
I wanna go home.
Back to my mom and my dog.
I guess I'll have to
borrow some money from
Meme and Anya to get
me through the week.
Good thing
I have friends to help
or I'd be in real trouble.
Huh? What is this thing?
That's Josephine.
Isn't she just beautiful?
She's lovely.
I went into town this morning
and bought some new things.
All of this
stuff? Let me guess.
You used your
allowance to buy it?
[MEME] Hey, Tsugumi.
You know that envelope
of money Infinite Plume gave
us? Do you know where mine is?
I can't seem to
remember where I put it.
Well, it's not like
it's a whole lot of money,
right? I wouldn't
worry too much.
Yeah, you're right. We get
more every week, don't we?
You pop the top like this.
[MEME] Huh?
[ANYA] Pop! Pop!
Oh, hey, you're
brooch is missing.
Did you know?
Huh? Oh, it was
very clumsy of me.
I lost it somewhere
when I was out this morning.
It was such a
pretty piece of jewelry.
You must be sad that it's gone!
No, it's okay. I think I'll
fit in better here at the school
without it.
And, besides.
I don't need a brooch
when I have Josephine!
Yeah, why would you?
[TSUGUMI] Excuse me, an
order of noodles, please.
[COOK] You mean
three orders, right?
No, thanks. Just the one!
Everybody dig in.
It looks tasty, at least.
This reminds me of consommé,
but with some sort
of pasta added to it.
Doesn't stretch
very far, does it?
This isn't gonna work.
We have to find a
way to buy food until
next week's allowance.
So we're
getting jobs then?
We have no choice.
Yeah, you're right.
We'll pick something
that'll pay us every day.
A job. How quaint!
[MEME] Hey, look!
This one pays really well.
[TSUGUMI] It does, but I'm
not sure about manual labor.
We're girls, after all.
[TSUGUMI] Hey, Anya.
Is there any kind
of job that sounds good to you?
Well, menial labor is out of the
question for me, obviously.
In fact, I really
shouldn't work at all,
but I can accompany you,
I suppose. And I want
to make it clear that I have
no interest in cute uniforms.
Ooh! Uniforms, huh?
How about this one, here?
Working at a café.
Uniforms provided.
No experience necessary.
[TSUGUMI] "An ideal
job for female students,"
What about Deathbucks Café?
It's the little ladies.
Apparently they've all
applied to work there.
Our job is to
look out for them so does
that mean we have to
work at the café, too?
I guess there is one
other option available.
We could go drink
coffee there every day.
You know what? You're
enjoying this too much.
I still don't see
why I have to get a job.
Oh so, you've forgotten why
we're doing this, too, Anya?
Forgotten? Huh?
You don't remember
why we came down here?
According to the map,
it should be nearby.
[TSUGUMI] Is this it?
[MEME] Wow, it looks
really chic, doesn't it?
[TSUGUMI] Excuse us!
We're the ones who contacted
you about temporary work.
Yes, of course. I remember.
There were five of
you, weren't there?
Five?
Hey, girls.
Hey, how's it going?
Oh, we saw you
at orientation, didn't we?
Name's Clay. I'm a weapon.
I'm Akane. I'm a meister.
Are you guys
looking for work because
you ran out of
allowance money, too?
Yes. Unfortunately,
my friend here used
it all up at the arcade.
Hey!
[ANYA] It goes very
quickly, doesn't it?
[TSUGUMI] I've gotta
say, I'm a little nervous
about the idea
of working with boys.
[MEME] Yeah, so am I.
[TSUGUMI] How old
do you think they are?
Older than us, right?
The uniform looks
a whole lot different on you.
Your chest is
so, well, you know.
Yeah, I guess
it is a little tight.
It looks good, though.
There's something so
motivating about putting on
a uniform, you know?
You're a simple man, aren't you?
I suppose those vests
look sharp enough on you two.
Okay, Anya,
it's time to get to work.
Come on. What are
you waiting for?
[ANYA]
Just give me another moment.
I can't possibly wear
a skirt as short as this.
Please. You'll be fine.
I feel like I'm on display.
You have such
lovely, slender legs.
Why not show them off a little?
I'm a lady.
How precious!
She's so adorable,
I almost can't handle it.
If you ladies are ready,
shall we get started?
Most of our customers
will be coming here because
they want to get
a look at real, live DWMA
students like you. So, just
put your best foot forward
and you should do fine.
Now let's get to work.
[ALL] Right!
Hi, welcome to Deathbucks!
Are you new here?
Uh, yes, ma'am.
Good luck, then.
Oh, thanks.
That's so nice of you to say!
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, just don't talk
to me. I'm concentrating.
A ham sandwich,
bacon, eggs, toast,
a cup of hot coffee,
and an iced coffee, please.
Add on some
french fries, too.
[MEME] Ham eggs.
[BOTH] In a sandwich!
[MEME] Would you mind starting
over from the beginning?
This is the third
time we've repeated it.
Think those two are okay?
They're having a rough time.
Thank you for
your patience. Here's your
iced lemon tea. I
hope you enjoy it!
Another order, Master!
I need two more
iced coffees, please!
[MASTER] Coming up.
Welcome to Deathbucks Café!
She's really into
this, isn't she?
So has she secretly
been a nice person all along?
With her I'm guessing
it depends on the day.
Just one more thing
that makes her cute!
[MASTER] Your order is
ready. Come and get it.
Great, thanks. Come
on. We can do this!
Okay!
[TSUGUMI] One hot coffee. We'll
have that right out for you!
Thank you for
waiting. Your café au lait
and raspberry juice.
And twenty
cents is your change.
Have a lovely day!
Thank you for stopping by.
We look forward to
seeing you again sometime soon!
Hello! I'm back!
I thought it would be
nice if I bought us a little
treat with today's pay. No need
to make a big to-do about it,
though. Would you like some?
Uh-oh! There
you go, splurging again.
Wow! These are
about as fresh as they come!
Don't mind if I do!
It's so good!
Do it now.
Actually, we
bought something with
the money we got today, too.
To commemorate our
first day at work. Go on.
We wanted you to have something.
I'm sure
it won't take the place
of the brooch you lost,
but we hope you like it!
[TSUGUMI] So...
what do you think?
It's all right,
I guess, and since I lost my
other one, I'll wear it.
Oh, yeah! I wanted
to run something by you two.
Sure. What is it?
A lot of friends
have nicknames for each other,
don't they? Choose one for me!
Yeah? You
trust us to come up
with a nickname for you?
Of course I do!
I'm sure it'll
be the perfect one!
Well give me
a sec to think, okay?
[TSUGUMI]
All right, but just a sec!
Any ideas, Anya?
Me?
Yep!
Okay. A nickname,
huh? Well, maybe Tsu-mi.
[BOTH] Huh?
[NARRATOR]
That's not gonna work.
"Sue me"?
[ANYA] These commoners
lead such exciting lives!
Their existence isn't
without peril, however.
It's a good thing I know
royal karate.
[MEME] This is fun,
isn't it, Tsugumi?
[TSUGUMI]
Yeah, I'm having a great time!
[ANYA]
Must you get so cozy together?