[humming]
[TSUGUMI'S MOM] Tsugumi?
Hungry or not,
it's almost time for supper.
Why don't you put that away
and call your brother in?
Yes, Mom.
[barks]
[crash]
Huh?
What is this?
Oh, dear.
[GIRL STUDENT 1A] It's true?
Are you really
going to the DWMA?
Oh, yeah.
[GIRL STUDENT 1B]
That's so amazing!
[GIRL STUDENT 1A]
And super elite!
[GIRL STUDENT 1B]
Maybe you'll find true love
while you're there!
You'll be
fighting evil witches
and stuff, huh?
Oh, no!
I don't think I'll be
doing anything like that!
So, you can
transform into a weapon?
Well, uh, I wouldn't
say I can, so much as I do.
Do it now, then. Show us!
Just like that?
Uh, sorry, I can't
do it on command.
[GIRL STUDENT 1G] Why not?
[GIRL STUDENT 1B]
Come on, we wanna see!
[GIRL STUDENT 1A]
A human weapon!
[GIRL STUDENT 1C]
That sounds so cool!
[TSUGUMI] "Cool" isn't
really the word I would use.
Transform out of the blue?
No I can't do that.
[FEMALE FLIGHT ATTENDANT]
Excuse me, miss.
[MALE CABIN ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have begun our descent
and will be arriving at
Death City Airport shortly.
[FEMALE FLIGHT ATTENDANT]
We'll be landing shortly.
Could you please put
your tray table away?
Oh, sure.
[ANNOUNCER MALE CABIN]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have begun our descent
and will be arriving at
Death City Airport shortly.
The local weather
conditions are clear,
with a temperature of
eighty-two degrees Fahrenheit.
We know you have many
airlines to choose from,
and we would like to
thank you for flying...
[CABBIE] Hey there!
Sightseeing, are you?
I can offer you a
fair fare!
No, thanks.
You'll want a souvenir
to remember your trip by!
[TSUGUMI] I'm just
going to take the bus.
[PEDDLER] All right,
you drive a hard bargain.
I'll give it to
you for half-price!
[CABBIE] Looking for
a taxi, are you, miss?
I got one right here.
I'm afraid that's an
unacceptable mode of transport.
[MEME] Um, I'm sorry.
Excuse me, sir?
What can I do for ya?
Could you please
tell me where I came from
and where I'm going?
I don't quite remember.
[CABBIE] What?
The staircase
at the school's entrance
is famed for its enormous size.
Climbing it offers
students a daily workout.
I'll never make it.
I'll die on the way up.
It's so hot!
They should tell you to
bring some water with you.
It's just a
little farther now.
You can do it!
Well, see you!
Thanks. Guess
I'll see you around?
That girl is so amazing.
I wonder if she's one
of the students here.
So it's just a little farther?
Okay!
My... My knees are gonna
give out any second.
Hey, there,
knees, you can do it!
Yep, I'm officially
losing my mind.
The staircase has beaten me.
It's over!
Ugh!
This must be
from that girl.
What does it say?
"Turn around"? Why?
There it is.
Death City!
So, I made
it here after all.
My new school and my new home.
The DWMA!
I've never tasted
anything like this before!
It tastes like America!
Death Weapon
Meister Academy,
commonly known as the DWMA.
The school that trains heroes
to protect the world
and preserve peace.
Its students fall
into two categories.
First, there are the students
who possess the ability to
transform into weapons...
and then there are the meisters,
the students who wield
those weapons in battle.
[OX] That last
combination worked pretty well.
What do you think?
[HARVAR] We should
probably try it again soon.
I don't want to forget it.
[OX] Yeah. I'm sure we can
still tweak it a bit, too.
That guy was
talking to his spear.
The weapon is really a person.
I'm not gonna keep
any of the money I earn
from this latest
promotional event.
Every last dime of
it is going to charity.
Who is that guy?
I guess he must be famous.
And I will be donating
all my contract fees
to children in need.
You're so generous.
Would you consider
being my partner?
No. You should be my partner!
I'm a teenage girl
who's in love with love.
I've never even had a
guy who was a friend before,
and now suddenly I'm
part of a love triangle.
[BLACK STAR] Not you!
Not in a hundred years, punk!
[screams]
Watch yourself.
Sorry! Daydreaming!
I'll just get out
of your way now! Bye!
What was that?
I haven't
seen her around.
She's probably a freshman.
I'll bet
she came here hoping
for my autograph.
Somehow I doubt it.
I can already tell
this isn't going to be easy.
Why me?
Why do I have to be a weapon?
I wanna go home.
I wanna go home!
But I can't go home!
Better.
The halls here are
like some impossible maze.
Yep, I'm lost.
I managed to get away
from that cramped castle.
I was hoping I would
see the "real world,"
but I'm not certain
I chose the right place.
[ANYA] As a specialized school,
this academy doesn't
seem to be indicative
of the type of life
commoners generally lead.
I should have
researched more thoroughly.
[ANYA] The students here are far
from what one would call normal.
I found it! Finally!
Sorry I'm late!
The halls are so confusing here!
You're a new student?
Yes, that's right.
Tsugumi Harudori.
An authentic commoner!
Her hairstyle
is unassuming.
She has no figure to speak of
and despite her utter
lack of poise or charisma,
she has a sweetly
unconcerned blank smile.
[PUNK WEAPON ] Looks
like we just made it.
Ooh, squishy!
So comfortable! I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
Don't worry.
It was just a
little fall. I'm fine.
[TSUGUMI] Oh, your ribbon.
Here you go.
Great, thank you.
Why did you
decide to change it?
You had it on
your left side before.
Oh, did I? I forgot.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tsugumi Harudori.
[MEME] "Tsugumi."
That's a pretty name.
It means "Spring Bird," right?
That's right.
As for me.
Let me think. Um...
I thought I knew
it, but I guess I forgot.
Huh?
Your name? Really?
Ah! That's it!
I've got it! My name's Meme.
Meme Tatane.
It's nice to meet you.
[TSUGUMI] I'm sorry for
asking this, but how could
anybody possibly...
Perfect.
That's the type of
girl I came here to see.
Scatter-brained, huh?
Wow! That girl
is really pretty!
Almost like a princess.
Gagantous!
[MEME] "Gagantous"?
All right,
that should be everybody.
Welcome to DWMA.
I'm Sid, one of
the teachers here.
Some of you can
transform into weapons.
And some of you
wish to be meisters,
those who fight
with the weapons.
Your skills likely vary.
Some of you weapons may not yet
be able to transform at will.
Don't worry, there's no rush.
That's why we're
here, to teach you.
[PUNK WEAPON]
Are you serious, man?
You let people like that in?
[SID] Beginning today,
you will fight as partners.
Matching up is simple.
Every weapon
needs to have a meister.
So I need a partner?
[SID] If you're still a
relatively inexperienced weapon,
the meister you partner with
will be especially important.
Having a partner should
help the learning process.
Many weapons find it difficult
to transform unless they
have a meister to wield them.
Take your time and find
a partner you have
good chemistry with.
[PUNK MEISTER]
How should we play this?
[PUNK WEAPON] Don't know
about you, but I want a girl.
Far as I'm concerned,
the ideal partner is someone
who'll clean up
after me, tend my wounds,
and you know, other things.
I'm not a particularly
eloquent man,
and in this case,
I think showing will
be a lot more
helpful than telling.
You'll understand
better if you see partners
who have matching wavelengths.
You can come in now.
[SID] These are two
senior students here,
the meister Maka Albarn,
and the weapon Soul Eater.
Always good
to see new students.
Nice to meet you.
She actually
remembers me!
Go ahead and
begin the demonstration now.
What a smooth
transformation!
You're a weapon,
too, aren't you?
Is that how you do it?
Uh... Not really.
It's not that easy for me.
[SID] It's important to
remember that the weapon
and the mesiter are both people.
That scythe isn't a thing.
If we acknowledge
each other's wills
and synch our wavelengths,
fighting together's
natural as breathing.
Just watch.
They're incredible!
It's like they're
dancing together or something.
So, that's what a weapon
and meister pair looks like.
I hope this helped.
You'll learn more
as class progresses,
but for now it's best if
you try to listen to your gut.
[SID] That's all for today.
Class dismissed.
That was really neat, huh?
From what I've seen so far,
the upperclassmen here
seem to be pretty cool.
They totally--
I was wondering--
[PUNK WEAPON]
Hey, baby.
You're a meister, aren't ya?
How about partnering up with me?
It's hard to tell when
I'm not transformed,
but I make a fine
lookin' weapon.
[MEME] Well, uh...
Hey, what're you
starin' at, space cadet?
I'm just
standing not staring.
I guess you're good enough.
You wanna be partners?
Not at all.
I can't do this.
I want to go to a regular
school like I always have.
Like the normal teenagers do.
Just because
I'm at the DWMA
doesn't mean I'm
suddenly a hero.
That girl Meme
did seem kinda nice.
And if I walk away
and quit like I want to,
I'll never have the chance to
get to know her better, will I?
Maybe if I
think about her.
What would Maka do
in this situation?
Aw, come on. There's
no reason to be shy.
You wanna be my partner? Huh?
No, but thanks.
You're breaking my
heart, here, baby.
What's the harm in getting to
know each other a bit better?
[TSUGUMI] Hey, Meme!
Let's go!
Where are we going?
Are you
jealous because he wants
to be with her and
not you? That's pathetic.
Who'd want someone with
a chest like that, anyway?
You perv!
It's a lost cause.
You're gonna be puny
forever, I can tell.
She even has
commoner mammary glands.
The poor wretch.
Hey, what do you want?
Stay out of this,
'kay? We're all just
havin' a friendly chat here.
Hmph. You boorish fool.
[ALL] Huh?
What, are you lookin'
for a fight, blondie?
In this school, actions
do the talking, not words.
Wanna dance?
I do not wish to dance.
I'm happy to fight, though.
[shrieks]
I won't go
easy just 'cause you're a girl.
Let's skip the
puffed-up chatter if we may.
It's rather dull.
Harudori.
That was your name, yes?
Your nametag said
you are a weapon.
Please transform
yourself immediately.
Huh?
I can't do a
full transformation.
I don't really have
the hang of it yet.
[PUNK WEAPON]
If you can't even do that much,
then why are you here
in the first place?
Come on!
Let's hang back
and watch for now.
We're just settling
into these roles.
There's no need to rush things.
What are those kids up to?
Trouble already?
Well, I guess it is
that kind of school, huh?
You're not
going to do anything?
But you're an instructor.
Nah. Like I said,
it's that kind of school.
This fight's gonna be
over before we even get started.
Here we go!
See that?
I can completely transform
everything but my head.
Not bad, huh?
So close.
You should really transform
sooner rather than later.
We're in danger of losing.
But I told
you, I can't.
Not when somebody puts
me on the spot like that.
[ANYA] How disappointing.
I heard about commoners.
You're supposed to be
a proud, hardy people.
But, that doesn't
seem to describe you.
Most unfortunate.
Looks like little girl
doesn't have a weapon.
I don't require one.
Weapon or not, I won't be
bullied by the likes of you.
[SID] Try to picture it!
Imagine the sharp blade that's
lying dormant within your soul.
Then awaken it!
Do battle for the sake of
what you know to be right.
You are a
student of the DWMA!
Just picture it?
There's some kind of blade
lying dormant within my soul?
Being a weapon wasn't
something I ever wanted.
Why did this happen to
me? I hate being afraid.
I want to go home.
I can't do this. I can't!
Please just leave me alone!
Think, Tsugumi.
Why are you really here?
I'm here to learn.
I'm here to fight.
Okay, then.
Open your eyes.
You can't fight like that.
Always remember,
you are a weapon!
I did it! Is this me?
The new
girl is a halberd.
She just needed
to believe in herself.
One problem.
You've got no blade.
[TSUGUMI] I'm sorry
it took me so long.
Let's begin.
Keep calm, okay?
[TSUGUMI] Right!
The first
injuries of the year.
I need one of you get
to the nurse's office
and ask Medusa
to come down here.
Yeah, no problem. I'll go.
Thanks, Tsunami Hunky-Dory!
That guy was a mega jerk!
It's Tsugumi Harudori.
Oh... Of course,
that's right! I'm sorry.
Anyway, I couldn't
have done anything at all
if I didn't have help. If
you want to thank anyone.
My name is Anya.
[BOTH] Thank you
for everything, Anya.
You were fantastic!
Hmph.
Harudori, I
wanted to ask a favor.
Yeah?
I'm the most
forgetful person ever,
and I realize I might be
more trouble than I'm worth,
but I was wondering
if you'd consider being
my partner anyway.
Huh? Me? Really?
Yeah, if you mean it,
that sounds perfect! Oh!
But what about...
Commoners are interesting to
observe, but that certainly
doesn't mean I want
to partner with one.
Quite the opposite, in fact.
What if your abnormally flat-
chested condition is contagious?
Unacceptable!
Gagantous!
Okay, is that settled, then?
It sure is. Glad to have you!
[MEME] This is gonna be great!
I'm a teenage girl
who's in love with love,
but this isn't exactly
the kind of triangle
I expected to
find myself a part of.
[TSUGUMI] What dangers await
us at the girls' dorm?
Witches? Misfortune?
Hey! I'm not Mary!
Go away! Leave me alone!
[ANYA] What are you babbling
about now, Tsugumi?
[MEME] It's time to find a job!
[TSUGUMI]
A job? But why?