Yahoo!
[KIM]
Well?
[JACQUELINE]
She hasn't even made a sound.
[JACQUELINE] I get that
she's not supposed to leave,
but is it really
necessary to guard the door?
We should do what we're told.
[KIM]
Sid is dead, Meme's missing,
and Anya's being sent home.
Things are crazy around here.
We may not know
exactly what's going on,
but it seems nuts to me that
Meme's one of their suspects.
So, where is Anya?
Apparently her
escort's already here.
She'll be going straight
to the airport and then home.
[JACQUELINE] She's not
going to come by the room.
[knocking]
Who's there?
Only me, Princess.
Shall we take our leave now?
Oh, thank you, Alfred.
[NAIGUS] I'll be taking Sid's
place and heading things up
here for a while.
I'm sorry about this, but...
One last time, please.
[BOTH] Yes, ma'am.
[CLAY]
Traffic jam.
It's because of
the Battle Festival.
Great time for a party.
[AKANE] What, did you
expect them to cancel it?
[MEME] Kill them all.
Kill them all.
They must die.
At last, the real harvest
festival is about to begin.
[bell tolling]
Huh?
Are those DWMA students, too?
Keep your guard up.
[HARVAR] There's
something off about them.
They poisoned him?
What's happening?
It looks like
Shaula is making her move.
Damn witch!
[OX] I don't think you
understand what you're doing.
I am the
Lightning King Commander.
[CLAY] Ox!
You okay?
I can take care of this.
You get yourselves to safety.
You don't need to do that!
Hurry and get in the car!
Don't open it!
Injure without killing.
Come on, let's get outta here!
What's going on here?
[BLACK STAR] It's nothin' to
worry about I could take them
all down by myself
if I really wanted to.
Let's not get too cocky, okay?
Just tellin' the truth.
What's happening, people?
I want a status report!
The NOT students.
They're running amok on campus.
We can't make contact with
the Battle Festival grounds.
The police have called
for assistance several times.
Any witch readings yet?
Unable to verify.
Get Stein on the phone for me!
[MAN IN SUIT]
Right!
[BLOND MAN IN SUIT]
Call everyone in!
We need all hands on deck.
[STEIN] The Battle Festival
is a real riot this year, huh?
[NAIGUS] Keep your
jokes to yourself, Dr. Stein.
How's the antidote coming?
[STEIN] I've got some
excellent samples to work with.
It shouldn't be
too much longer now.
[NAIGUS] However fast
you're working, work faster!
You'd think she's
in a hurry or something.
They're locking down the dorm?
What's going on out there?
Unfortunately,
I don't have any details yet,
but from what
I've learned so far,
the Battle Festival grounds
seem to be under attack.
And they think there may
be danger of an attack here,
as well?
It sounds crazy, but
the attackers appear to be
students from the NOT class.
[MISERY] At any rate, to
reduce the risk of additional
casualties, no one
will be allowed in or out
of the dormitory until
the situation is resolved.
You think that witch
is responsible for this?
[muffled crash]
Where do you think you're going?
I really need
to get out of here.
[BOTH] Huh?
Meme could be out
there with the rest of them!
[JACQUELINE] Impossible!
The dorm's locked down.
No one's allowed out.
And you were already
not allowed to go anywhere.
One way or another, I'm going.
I don't care what you say.
Meme needs me!
What do you expect to
accomplish by yourself?
I won't be alone, though.
Anya will be coming with me.
No, she won't be. She's well on
her way to the airport by now.
I made them both a promise,
and I intend to keep it!
You don't understand!
I swore I would choose either
Anya or Meme as my partner
by the end of the day
today, and I still haven't
found a chance to tell
either of them how I feel.
Have you decided
between the two of them, then?
No, not yet.
Take a few deep breaths, okay?
You see. I've got this
feeling I just can't shake.
I honestly don't think
Anya is going to leave us
and go home like
they told her to.
Clay got upset after
Sid died and snapped at Anya.
I'm guessing she
was probably pretty mad.
I know I would've been.
[TSUGUMI] Mad about how
everyone was deciding things
without asking her, and mad at
herself for not realizing it
sooner.
It all happened so fast.
It must have
been really frustrating.
[TSUGUMI]
I was hurt.
I called out to her and she
didn't even look back at me.
But now I think she
didn't want me to see.
She was crying
out of frustration.
That's why I'm
so sure about this.
I don't think she would
feel right if she went home
without seeing things through.
[JACQUELINE]
Is it soul resonance?
Go on.
Listen.
This situation is serious.
[TSUGUMI]
I know it is. But please.
Well, your injury
doesn't look all that bad to me.
Right! It's all
about mind over matter.
I'll be fine.
Don't get too sure of yourself.
You're still a NOT student.
Think it'll work?
Well, I know what
she's going through.
Wanting to protect
someone who's important to her,
even if it means
breaking the rules.
[TSUGUMI]
Housemistress!
Where are you going?
I'm very sorry, but this is
something I have to do.
It's okay.
You have my blessing.
Huh?
Such determination!
It's exactly like a
scene out of The Commoner!
You're the Mary I've
always been looking for!
Sure.
You want this?
No, thanks. I'm good.
[ANYA]
Please stop the car.
Huh?
[ANYA] I need to stay
by Tsugumi's side right now.
That's where I belong.
We've already told you--
Oh, just be quiet!
[ANYA]
Don't you understand?
I feel as sad about
Sid's death as you do, Clay.
It was my friend who...
[ANYA] Right now, the people
I care about are suffering.
How can I possibly go home?
Yes, but--
And what were
you thinking earlier?
Why didn't we stop and
help Ox? He was in trouble!
You don't understand--
I am a student of the DWMA.
I'll thank you to stop treating
me like a helpless little child!
Stop this car right now.
I'm sorry, Alfred.
But that's an order.
Wait, Princess! Please, don't--
Hey!
Stop right now!
[PATTY]
We did so much decorating.
Why did everybody stop coming?
The Battle Festival
is in full swing, huh?
Oh, good!
You guys are still here!
Uh. Hey, Tsugumi.
Is something wrong?
[TSUGUMI] Please. I need
to ask you for something.
For candy?
[TSUGUMI]
Not like that.
Anya is being shipped
back to her home country.
She's headed to the airport.
I'm trying to find
a way to go get her,
but things
are so crazy here.
The buses aren't running.
I can't catch a cab.
Stop babbling!
Get to the point, already!
Hey, Master!
Trick or Treat! Happy Halloween!
Huh?
We need to borrow your scooter.
Is it naïve to
ask you to be careful?
We'll be fine, don't worry!
[LIZ]
Hey, pedestrians! Look out!
Get outta my way
or I'll flatten you!
[TSUGUMI] Slow down!
We're gonna die!
[CLAY] I don't see how
we'll get it running again.
[ANYA'S BUTLER]
No.
[AKANE] I'll make a call.
See if I can get us another car.
Well, I'm going
back to the school.
Huh? Hey!
[AKANE] Please,
Princess. Come back.
The mission that we were
assigned was to get you safely
to the airport.
It's our duty to see it through.
[AKANE] We cannot simply allow
you to walk off on your own.
Surely you understand that?
[ANYA]
No, I don't!
It sounds to me like
your real mission is to abandon
your friends. To sacrifice your
principles and act like cowards.
If I were you, I'd forget
about this stupid assignment!
I see we have little choice.
Akane.
Let me handle this, Clay.
The princess here is unarmed.
We can't very well
turn your blade against her.
This is an actual fight.
And I don't need any concessions
from you.
[AKANE] If this
was an actual fight,
you wouldn't have
had time to say all that.
Your pride'll get
the best of you yet.
I don't care what
it requires of me.
I am going to return to Tsugumi.
I can't let you go.
Over there!
Is that a witch?
Where?
That was a sneaky trick!
Let me go I'll scream
bloody murder if you don't.
Let's say you do go
back. Your friend's scared.
It's possible
she's given up already.
There's no way she'd do that.
Tsugumi knows I
would come back to her.
She's waiting for me right now.
[TSUGUMI]
Anya!
I found you! We need to go!
Why are you
just standing around?
We've got a crisis
on our hands, here!
This isn't a good time
for you to be making out.
Us making out?
I'm very sorry. I don't
know if you can forgive me.
Don't worry about it, okay?
Finding Meme is the only
thing that matters right now.
Then let's go.
[CLAY] What'll you
do when you find her?
Can you release her
from Shaula's mind control?
Because if not, you'll
just end up having to fight her.
Besides, for all you know,
the witch could be right there
with Tatane.
Shaula's using Soul Protect
to keep hidden from the academy.
That means she's
unable to use her own magic
which makes Tatane
a useful pawn to her.
She'll likely want to maximize
the strength of her powers,
so she'll probably
be overseeing the chaos
from a nearby location.
It doesn't matter.
Whatever might be waiting
for us when we get there,
we'll deal with it.
First, we need to
focus on finding Meme.
I agree.
Come on, let's get going!
[TSUGUMI] Except...
Sorry, ladies.
She can't seat three people.
All right, then. You try turning
yourself into a flying halberd.
But how? I don't know.
Remember the
demonstration Jacqueline did?
Picture it in your head.
[ANYA] I believe in you.
I know you can do this.
[ANYA] You can fly,
Tsugumi. Find your wings.
I knew you could!
[TSUGUMI] Whoa,
it's hard to balance.
Hold on. Are they?
Yes, they are.
That's soul resonance.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[AKANE] When a meister
and weapon are in harmony
they can feel
each other's emotions,
and are able to
share their imaginations.
So this is soul resonance.
Dr. Stein's got a
blood sample from Tatane.
He's using it to make an
antidote to Shaula's toxin.
What are you doing?
Knowing Doctor Stein, he'll
work swiftly and efficiently.
He should be nearly
done with it by now.
Hey!
[TSUGUMI]
Well, Anya hop on!
Yes, ma'am!
And one more thing.
Please, you two, be careful.
Right!
[TSUGUMI]
Here goes nothing!
[TSUGUMI] Um, Anya,
could you hop off and give
us a running start?
Okay!
[TSUGUMI]
Higher!
Don't hit the tree!
[LIZ]
Good luck you guys!
You've got a soft spot
for Harudori, don't you?
Me?
Well, you have to admit,
she is pretty adorable.
That doesn't make it right.
Yeah, all right.
Come on, we should get back.
Yeah.
[ANYA] Wah!
Tsugumi, go slower!
The brakes!
Hit the brakes!
[TSUGUMI]
What brakes?
[screaming]
[STEIN]
So you came here.
Yes, that's right.
Now please give us
the antidote and we'll go.
[STEIN] Straight to
the point. I like that.
Hmm.
So what should I do?
Well, how about you
start by being more decisive.
We can't afford
to waste any time.
[STEIN] There are two very
good reasons why I shouldn't
give this to you.
Want to hear?
[BOTH]
Hurry up!
[STEIN] Number one: This
antidote is only designed to
break down the toxin in
the blood. Its effect on any
magical mind control is
as yet unclear. Of course,
there's a chance
it won't work at all.
And in the worst-case
scenario, she could die.
Die?
Okay, okay, I'm
joking about that.
Your sense of humor
leaves a lot to be desired.
If you don't stop with
those stupid jokes...
What's the second reason?
This sample has actually
already been spoken for.
In fact, Naigus is
headed over from the DWMA
to pick it up right now.
She'll come here,
take this sample, and return
to the school. Then, after
verifying its effectiveness,
she'll mass produce it.
That should all take three
days or so.
No, that's too long!
What if something happens
to Meme in the meantime?
Dr. Stein, the sample!
What in the world
are you doing here?
What do you think?
We came for the antidote
so we could save Meme
from the witch!
As I recall, you're supposed to
be on your way to the airport.
Make this easier on all of
us and do what you're told!
We just want to
give the drug to Meme.
That should test its
effectiveness. Let us go!
Don't be ridiculous.
You two are little
more than children!
You need to leave this to us.
We're all fighting
the same enemy, here.
The enemy might be the same,
but I think our
priorities are different.
It should start neutralizing
the toxin immediately.
Well, get going!
[TSUGUMI]
Sorry about this!
We'll let you know as
soon as we have Meme!
Get back here! What
were you thinking, Stein?
You gave them the--
No one else understands
my jokes, but I enjoy them.
We have to find her
as quickly as we can.
[TSUGUMI] Searching randomly
like this won't do any good.
Probably not, but do
you have any other ideas?
[TSUGUMI]
I was thinking.
Yes? What is it?
Remember what Clay told
us earlier, about how it's
very likely that Shaula will
want to keep Meme by her side?
[ANYA] Yes.
What if we look for
Shaula instead of Meme?
Okay, do you know of some
special way to locate a witch?
We can use a messenger bat!
[ANYA]
Huh?
Well, that landing was
better than the first one.
How was that any better?
Oh, well, you know, heh.
We need to follow
that bat! Come on!
Hurry up!
[ANYA]
Geez!
[SHAULA] Yes,
kill each other.
[SHAULA] Paint the
town crimson with the blood
of your erstwhile friends.
Embrace chaos! Say
goodbye to order and harmony!
[MEME]
Kill them all.
[SHAULA] No one will
be allowed to sleep.
[SHAULA] Your precious
Battle Festival is over,
but the real fun
is only just beginning.
[ANYA]
Are you there, Meme?
We came for you!
We're here, Meme!
We're here!
Kill them all.
Kill them all. They must die.
[TSUGUMI] The witch is
using her mind control power
to force Meme to attack us!
[ANYA] Tsugumi,
stay back!
I'll find some
way to stop her!
[MEME] Please! I don't
want to hurt anybody else!
[TSUGUMI] All right,
everyone, here goes!
[ALL] We're
going to stop the witch and
take our lives back!