Look!
She's finally waking up!
Huh? What?
It feels like I'm
laying on a warm bosom.
Uh, well you aren't, sorry!
It's just my legs,
and before it was Meme's.
Hers started to
fall asleep, though,
so she asked me to take
over as the designated pillow.
Oh, well, thank you.
[TSUGUMI] I guess
this is the hospital, then?
[ANYA] Yes. They're
operating on her right now.
She needed surgery?
This is really happening.
I can't believe
it. It's horrible!
I was hoping all of
it was just a bad dream.
Sid asked us questions
earlier about Eternal Feather,
like you would
expect given what happened.
He wanted to know if
there had been anything
troubling her, or
if she'd gotten involved
with any bad
influences and so forth.
But we came up with nothing.
Can you think of
something we might have missed?
No, nothing. I'm sorry.
As far as I know, things
were completely normal with her.
What do we do? She
can't die! She won't, will she?
Don't say things like that.
That kind of
attitude won't do any good.
Sid told us not to worry. He
said everything would be okay.
Apparently, the DWMA
has their very own doctor.
And he's supposed to be
exceptional at what he does.
Sid said that? Really?
Yes.
And he said it's that doctor
who's doing
the surgery. It's okay.
I'm sure she's gonna be fine.
Whew!
However, he is
quite an unusual fellow.
He's made a lot of
modifications to his body.
There are even some
terrible rumors that he secretly
collects cadavers in
his ongoing quest to create
the perfect zombie!
Zombies? No!
[TSUGUMI] Wouldn't it
be better if she simply died
rather than turn into
one of those horrible things?
[MEME] We can't give up
hope yet, Tsugumi! Really!
You never know.
It's possible she could turn out
to be a super cute zombie!
Maybe she'll even
be happier that way!
[TSUGUMI] No one
is happy as a zombie!
There's no sense
in worrying about it now.
All we can do is
have faith and wait.
You're right. Have faith.
[AKANE]
Please be specific.
How would you describe
Eternal Feather's behavior?
It was really strange.
Like her body was there but
her spirit wasn't, you know?
People called out
to her, but she didn't respond.
It was almost like
she was being controlled.
Yeah. What about the crowd?
Did you see any
suspicious people around?
The bazaar was crowded
with all sorts of people.
I can't be sure.
[AKANE]
Take a look. Did you see her?
[MAKA] Oh! You've
already got a suspect, then?
Wow good job, Akane!
Yeah. I feel like
maybe I've seen her
somewhere before.
What's her story, anyway?
Why are you
guys asking about her?
Is she gonna be
EAT's next target?
Nothing's final.
Her case is under investi-
gation by Central Intelligence.
They haven't given the okay
to release any information yet.
Do me a favor
and leak it anyway.
My GPA could use the help.
Yeah, how much are you paying?
[CLAY]
Hey, you guys!
[MAKA]
No cheating, Soul!
Any minute now. They said the
operation should be over soon.
All three of you
are waiting for the girl?
Yes, that's right.
I've completed the operation.
How did it go? Was the
operation a success, Doctor?
[STEIN]
A good question.
Gagantous to the max!
He's got an
enormous screw in his head!
[STEIN] Your friend is
just over in the next room.
If you'll follow me.
You haven't turned her into
a zombie or anything, have you?
[STEIN] The
anesthesia hasn't worn off yet,
so she's still asleep.
Here's hoping.
Gagantous! Ah!
She has a screw
in her head, too!
How could you
do something like that?
Do you know how people
are going to look at her now?
And how's she supposed to sleep?
She can't roll onto her side.
Maybe she would be
better off as a zombie!
I can always design a
special pillow to help with any
sleeping difficulties.
It shouldn't be a problem.
Though.
She would have made
a good-looking zombie.
The girl could be right.
It's possible I
missed an opportunity.
I am glad that
she survived and all.
But she's going to
wake up sooner or later.
How do we explain this to her?
Just kidding!
Well, are you surprised?
Of course we're
surprised, you jerk!
Yes, we are, and relieved.
She's totally back to normal!
Yeah, she sure is. Maybe
a little too close to normal.
[TSUGUMI] You even
reattached her braid?
Unless, is that an extension?
[ALL] Her braid
has a life of its own!
Pretty cool, don't you think?
[ANYA]
Now what have you done?
Look, you two! Her braid! It's
trying to write something down.
[ALL]
Jesús Navas?
But why? What's it mean?
A message from beyond the grave!
But she isn't dead.
It's like a scene
straight out of The Thing!
[TSUGUMI] Move it,
Anya! Can't you run any faster?
[ANYA] Tsugumi!
Pick it up! Pick it up!
[TSUGUMI] No!
I can't! I can't! I can't!
[TSUGUMI]
Be careful where you step, Meme!
[ANYA] Wah!
The creep is smiling!
You cruel, sick, freaky
man! Her body isn't a toy!
How could you do this to her?
You fiend! You devil!
You pumpkin fetishist!
[STEIN] Oh, calm down.
That was just another joke.
Your friend is
actually behind these curtains.
Huh?
[ALL] She still
has a screw in her head!
[STEIN] Now, as you can see,
I was able to save her life,
but she'll need to remain
in the hospital for a while.
[STEIN] The wound
on her neck was very deep.
Much deeper than
I would have imagined
a self-inflicted wound could be.
I don't understand.
Why would she do such a thing?
Just because she
couldn't sell her clothing?
No, surely.
No doubt that matter
is under investigation.
It doesn't change the fact
that she injured others during
the incident. Depending
on what the reasons were
for her actions, it
may be a long time before
she returns to the DWMA.
♪
[ringing]
Yes?
Oh, hello, there, Sid.
[SID] You saved a life,
Dr. Stein. We appreciate it.
That's my job, isn't it?
Although actually,
it isn't supposed to be.
You were only going to send
me autopsy work to do, remember?
[SID] This is a poor, innocent
girl in the NOT class, Stein.
I'm sure she never
expected to get involved
in this sort
of thing. As far as I know,
you're the only doctor
who could have saved her life.
I know her
friends were grateful.
Terrified of you,
but still grateful.
That's worth
something, don't you think?
[SID] You know, we could
really use you at the DWMA.
It would be a tremendous help.
Back to that again, are we? You
know me better than that, Sid.
I'm more suited for labor-
atory research than teaching.
[SID] Yeah. Well, anyway,
was there anything suspicious
left behind on the girl's body?
[STEIN]
Now that you mention it.
[STEIN] As you requested,
I conducted a thorough
examination, looking over
every inch of her for clues.
I found a strange wound
on her left index finger.
It was tiny, as if she'd
been pricked with a needle.
[SID] Any toxins
in her bloodstream?
[STEIN] No. Nor was
there any sign of mental
imbalance. She has no
memory of the event, either.
If I had to guess,
I'd say, she was injected
with an undetectable
amount of toxin, and
then most likely subjected
to some sort of mind control.
You're talking about magic?
[STEIN] Well,
I can't say for sure.
[STEIN] But there's absolutely
nothing abnormal about her now.
I believe returning her
to her regular life as soon as
possible would be the best
way to ensure a swift recovery.
It is definitely summer!
The sun is a lot brighter
in Death City than back home.
I'm roasting out here!
[TSUGUMI]
It's summer-style Kana!
I suppose.
That's adorable! Do you
like those ears you've got?
[KANA]
Not really.
I dunno. I think
she likes them okay.
[ANYA] What are
you up to out here?
Aren't we a little old
for playing in the water?
I'm not playing.
I'm doing something called
water sprinkling.
You just scatter water around.
It cools things off a bit.
I hate to tell you this,
but I don't really
think it's accomplishing much.
It really helps,
I swear! True,
it doesn't dramatically
lower the temperature or
anything. But it's pretty.
It sets a scene, you know?
It sets a scene?
What kind of scene?
I don't get it at all.
Well. Um, let me think, here.
[crackling]
[crickets chirping]
See?
Sorry. It still
makes no sense to me.
Hmm. Maybe it would
help if you changed.
That outfit looks way
too hot for this weather.
There's nothing wrong
with my outfit, thank you.
[TSUGUMI]
If you say so, here.
Setting a scene.
I'm setting a scene.
[ETERNAL FEATHER]
Ah! Please stop.
[TSUGUMI]
Eternal Feather, you're back!
You were discharged
from the hospital today?
If you'd told us, we
would've come to get you!
[ETERNAL FEATHER] Don't worry
about it. I was fine on my own.
I'll probably
always have this scar,
but I figure at the
DWMA, that's a badge of honor.
I promise it's
no big deal, really!
I feel great!
She has an enormous
screw in her back!
It was Doctor Stein's idea.
I wasn't sure about it at
first, but he thought it would
be amusing to wear
this when I saw you again.
Oh, really? Tell me, does
this face look amused to you?
I'm so
tired of that joke.
[MEME] Hey! You're home!
They finally let you out, huh?
I'm so glad
you're feeling better now!
Thanks, me too.
How are you doing, Meme?
I'm great! Oh, except...
You're back home. We should
throw a party or something.
[ETERNAL FEATHER]
That's a sweet thought.
Hey Jackie, is
something bothering you?
[ANYA] You look like
the world's coming to an end.
Me and Kim. We just broke up.
[JACQUELINE]
Huh? Hold on, Kim!
What do you mean?
Why would we split up?
[KIM] It feels
like we're rushing things.
We got together too quickly.
I just don't
think we know each other
well enough for
this kind of commitment.
[JACQUELINE]
That's why we teamed up!
So we could
understand each other better.
If I'm doing something wrong,
you can tell me what it is.
I'll do my best to fix it.
It's not like that. It's
nothing you've said or done.
I just don't feel like
this is something I can
deal with right now.
Something you can't deal with?
I knew it! I have
done something wrong!
[KIM] Let it go. I need
some space right now. Goodbye.
I don't
understand what happened.
We were doing so
well together, too.
What am I going
to do without her?
[ANYA]
Think about it this way.
Ultimately all she asked
for was a little space, right?
Yeah, Anya's right.
Maybe some time and
distance is all you need.
That works for a
lot of people, so I hear.
Right. Or maybe a
change in temperature?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
You know, cool down some.
That'll probably make it
easier for Kim to talk to you.
Yeah I guess I could do that.
Hey!
I actually have something that
might help with that right here.
[MEME]
A wind chime!
A wind chime?
What's it for?
That'll help?
Oh! Yeah!
Let us all take a moment
now to listen to its song.
[chiming]
Ah, just listen to
it sing. Isn't that nice?
Such soothing sounds.
I'm getting cooler already.
Huh?
How is listening
to a bell supposed
to make you feel any cooler?
That's not what bells are for!
They don't cool
you off, they just ding!
Come on, don't you feel it?
Setting a scene. Remember?
[ANYA] Leave them
to their wind chime.
We'll go inside
and get a cold drink.
[JACQUELINE] That's a
great idea. I'm dying of thirst.
[TSUGUMI]
Save some for us, you guys!
[MEME]
We're thirsty, too!
Hey, Tsugumi!
Hi!
[TSUGUMI]
It's Meme.
[ANYA]
Hey, Tsugumi!
[TSUGUMI]
And Anya.
What's up, Tsugumi?
Have a minute to talk?
Talk to me.
Come over here!
[MEME]
No, over here!
[ANYA]
This way, Tsugumi!
Well, hurry up Tsugumi.
Get down and come here!
Come on, Tsugumi! That's
a good puppy! Here, here...
[ANYA]
Pick me, Tsugumi!
I've got some
yummy cake for you!
All right,
Tsugumi. Here we go!
Fetch the stick, girl!
[MEME] Go on!
Go get it! Get the stick!
What do you
people think I am? A dog?
There, do you see
now? This is what happens
when you take
forever to choose a partner.
She's right,
you know. It's been a while.
I know.
I'm really sorry.
I sure hope you don't
think we'll keep waiting
on you for the
rest of our lives.
Actually, I'll be waiting.
Ooh, sneaky!
Yeah, okay, whatever.
I'll wait for you, too.
But still, ultimately,
this is a decision that only
one person can make.
[TSUGUMI] I don't know.
Both of you are so strong.
I've basically done
nothing since I've been here.
I don't feel like I deserve to
be partners with either of you.
Really, what's the use of a
weapon who doesn't have a blade?
I wouldn't even be
able to protect my meister.
[ANYA] Those are excuses.
What do you expect, huh?
That you'll magically
get stronger overnight?
Do me a favor.
Transform into your
halberd shape, okay?
[TSUGUMI]
Um, all right.
Over here!
You two are
amazing. You see now?
This isn't something
I just picked up one day.
I've received fighter
training my entire life.
Meme, too, I'd guess.
Probably. Though
I've forgotten about it.
Expect too much
from yourself too soon
and you'll be dis-
appointed. It will come in time.
But if what you really
want is to improve your skills,
then you should
decide on a partner,
and grow stronger together
with whoever you choose.
Don't you see?
You have to
make a commitment.
You've taken the
easy way out long enough.
Making excuses and
running from your responsibility
won't help anything.
You have no resolve, and you
will have no blade until you do!
I didn't know.
But right now, to choose between
the two of you, just like that.
No one's saying to
choose right this second,
and we aren't even
saying by the end of the summer.
Huh?
There's a harvest
festival on October 31st.
I believe you commoners refer
to it as "Halloween," right?
[ANYA] That's the same
date when the academy holds its
Battle Festival.
That is when you'll choose.
It's either Meme. Or it's me.
Until then, we'll keep
switching off, day by day.
I, okay...I understand.
And remember that weapon
and meister are two in one,
which means there's no
burden you have to carry alone.
Thank you, Meme.
You're getting
the jump on me again!
Oh no you don't!
[stomach growls]
Sounds like
someone's ready for dinner.
After all this bother, I think
you should cook for us tonight.
Okay.
[MEME] That sounds
great. I'll give you a hand.
[ANYA] Ah! In that case,
I'll give you a hand, too!
[TSUGUMI] All right,
then, what's up next on
Soul Eater Not?
[ANYA] Sweltering Nights!
[MEME] Oblivious!
[ANYA] Three-man Baseball!
[TSUGUMI] From Death
City with Love! Four stories!
[MEME] Hey, did you
know pumpkins grow better
when you sing to them?
[ANYA] What?
Now that is gagantous!