The visitor
who came from far away
made a few new friends.
However...
Dammit, she looked
more like a cosplayer!
An alien shouldn't
look like that;
it should be some type
of mind-based creature!
A silicon-based lifeform with
a bio-acceleration device,
or a sentient
mechanical being,
maybe even something with a
radiosymmetrical exoskeleton,
but not like her!
Come on!
An alien's appearance
should be so awe-inspiring
that you know without
a doubt it's an emissary
sent from the cosmos!
Instead, I encounter one
that even Trekkies
would have a hard time
accepting as real!
We will achieve
Beautiful Contact!
And rest assured, ma'am, this
creature that you've described,
She will not be mankind's
first contact with alien life!
I love this food!
It's so delicious!
By what term do you
call this dish again?
Well, here in Okinawa,
we call it yakiniku.
The meat's so tender, and
I love the grilled taste!
Plus, the so-called
teriyaki sauce
and the grease from the meat
give the rice a yummy flavor!
It's "purr-fect!"
This particular dish It's
the yummiest one yet!
Oh, I'm so happy
that I came to Earth!
So, Eris, what led your
people to explore space?
We thought it was time
to extend relations
to the other planets
in the universe.
We inhabitants of Catia
felt like our world
had come to a standstill,
not just genetically,
but culturally as well.
Oh, so that's why?
Yep. For seventy thousand years,
our society stayed the same,
so it was time to wash
off the stagnation.
We journeyed into space,
to give other races
a peek at our culture,
and to get
an eyeful of theirs.
We're really hoping that
if we show you ours,
you'll show us yours!
This looks and sounds more
like a late-night cable movie
than a surveillance feed.
What's our
next step, Jack?
We launch an op to
nab the alley cat
who's moved in with
your little friend there.
Oh, and before I forget,
I did get permission
for you to tag along.
Space exploration, huh?
I'm really jealous.
But why, Kio?
You've got a cool job
you seem to really enjoy
I must be the only
person I know who
doesn't have a
profession picked out yet.
Really?
Yeah. Manami's even
trying to get a position
at the American Air
Force base in town.
I'm not yet familiar
with your world's economy,
but I'm sure you'll find
a job that you'll like
and that compensates
you well.
You really think so?
Yes. Just don't
give up, 'kay?
That reminds me.
Hey, Kio, speaking
of compensation...
Yeah, what?
Ahh... You've done so much
for me since I arrived here
and given the social
structure of your planet,
it's only fair that pay I you
some form of compensation.
That's not necessary.
It is, but until our worlds'
relations are formalized,
I can't offer you
any money.
I can only offer you
an alternate form
of payment instead...
And according to
the materials I read
and the scenarios they
depicted, the optimum way to do
that would be by sharing
my body with you!
Huh?
Our reproductive systems
are actually quite similar.
I don't mind performing
the various acts,
but do you have to wear
that leather mask?
What mask?
Where did you learn
this stuff from?
It was in the magazines
I found under your mattress,
and those are guides to
human behavior, right?
Uhhh, no!
Those things are more
like, well, fiction!
What? You mean that's
not how I should behave?
What a relief!
You see, I've only just
reached my sixteenth cycle.
And to be honest,
I don't have any reproductive
act experience yet.
Hey. You know
who also doesn't?
Me.
Really?
Nope!
Barf!
Here, I insist.
No, that's okay!
Why you?
Why'd you have to get
involved in this
and with her
of all people, Kakazu?
Yo, Kio!
Are you planting
something?
Eris said she wanted
to introduce me to someone.
But back here?
Alright,
everybody, fall in!
Operations check.
Dance!
Stand proud!
Look sad!
Now sing!
They all appear to be
functioning normally.
Great!
Yeah, but... what are they?
They're called
Assistroids.
Here, look
They're created
by scattering these
nanomachine capsules.
And they use the soil to
fabricate the Assistroids.
I'm going to use them
to help me with my research.
Can those little
guys wash windows?
Why does it have
to be so hot?
I know the perfect
thing then.
Yeah.
And you'll love it!
Here. Trust me, a bite of
this'll definitely cool you off.
What is it?
Just try it
and find out.
It's cold and sweet
and so very delicious!
What is it?
This?
It's ice cream.
You've got a different
kind than me!
Wanna try it?
I'd love to, but only
if you don't mind!
Be my guest.
Can we move on this?
Too many civilians around.
We'll have to wait, which
is a big part of field work.
At this rate, I should be able
to gather all the important data
on your planet
within a week.
Wow That's amazing.
It's still
so hot and muggy.
Yeah, even with the sun
going down, it's still warm.
Wanna get some
more ice cream?
Yes!
They're out.
It's time, Momiji.
Activate System.
That's weird.
There's nobody around.
Hey. What gives?
Freeze!
What the?
We bring a message
from the Beautiful
Contact secret society!
You, Alien!
Um, yes?
To preserve the uniqueness
of mankind's first contact
with intergalactic life, we
refuse to recognize your race!
Remove yourself from
our planet or we will!
The situation's
changed; stand by.
What now?
Let's wait and
see what happens.
Um, sir... Excuse me, but who
did you say you represent?
We're representatives
of mankind.
Yes, but...
there are billions of people
who live on this planet,
so which particular ones
do you folks represent?
You don't need
to know that!
Actually, I do because
I'm performing an assessment
and need current data on
this world's organizations.
Therefore I need to know all
the details on your group,
its membership roster,
and your identities, too.
So if you don't
mind, please tell me.
What? No!
But why not?
Because we're a secret
society, you dingbat!
Oh!
So when you say "secret"
You really mean secret.
I can't let an alien
this obtuse live!
No, stop!
Move it!
Kio, no!
No!
Kio!
What?
Equip S-1!
The target's your priority!
Yeah. Copy that.
Wait! No! Stop!
You're nimble! But dead!
Stop!
You leave her alone!
Kakazu.!
Kio! Get out of there!
Eris hasn't done
anything wrong,
so why are you and those
other people doing this?
Uh... Thank you.
Oh, thank goodness;
are you okay?
I'm fine. Forget me;
what about you?
Back to base!
We gotta go!
Momiji!
What are you doing?
I'm suspending the mission
based on my assessment.
That's not your call to make!
Eris, no!
Kakazu!
Kio!
She didn't have
to shoot Kio.
What the?
You okay, Kio?
Uncle Yuichi?
Where's Eris?
She was taken away
before I could get to you.
What?
We've gotta find her!
It sounds to me like she's
more than a friend now.
No, it's not just that.
Eris is a visitor
from another planet.
She's been threatened
and kidnapped,
what kind of impression about
Earthlings has this made on her?
We have to help her.
We have to show her that
someone on this planet's
on her side.
Manami?
Kio.
Hey, what's up?
Tell me where
they've taken Eris.
Huh?
What are you
talking about?
"Taken?"
Where is she, Manami?
Why are you
asking me this?
I saw your watch
back there.
Uh...
Whoever took her had the
same type of watch as you
and it had a crack in
the exact same place.
That was you,
wasn't it?
Yes.
Why'd you do it, Manami?
I wanted to get some
field experience.
I'm trying to get a job at
Kadena Air Base, remember?
Or to be more precise
I'm trying to get a job
as a CIA field operative
on the base, Kio.
But still...
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Look, what's done is done.
You can make things
right, though.
Just tell me where
Eris is being held.
She's locked up in Hangar F
at Kadena Air Base.
That's not exactly the
easiest place to get into.
I've got a plan, but things
are sure to get hairy.
Uh. What is this?
Smith and Wesson M686.
It shoots tranquilizer rounds;
I use it for work.
Um... Uncle Yuichi what
do you do for a living?
You're done here.
This operation is now
under our jurisdiction.
Wow, you Defense Intelligence
Agency boys sure
have some nerve.
Come now.
Both your CIA and my DIA are
both servants of the people,
aren't they?
But I serve
a different breed.
Hello, are you
the lieutenant?
Yeah, Lieutenant Fujioka.
Hi, Aoi speaking.
Um, hey, Aoi, it's Kio.
Oh... Hi!
Listen, I know we made plans
to get together tomorrow.
But I won't be able
to make it now.
What?
I'm sorry, but I've got
to take care of something
and I don't know
when I'll be back.
What's going on?
It's a long story.
Look, I'll give you
a call once I get back
and explain it, okay?
Um. Sure.
Thanks, Aoi.
We blew it.
Even so, one of my
sources told me
there's no way the
government's going to enter
into diplomatic relations.
Now they know she's Earth's
first alien contact!
Sorry to interrupt, people,
but make like ice and freeze!
Wait a minute;
who the hell are you?
Miss Itokazu?
Say "cheese!"
What are you doing?
We're gonna post these
photos on the net,
so the membership of the
Beautiful Contact secret society
isn't gonna be
so "secret" anymore.
Unless.
I'm sure Kio must
hate me now.
You.
That was easier
than I thought.
It's due to his
special access plate.
It's also got something
to do with the hour, too.
Most of the guys
on base are Trekkies,
so when "Star Trek's" on, they
don't pay as much attention.
Where am I?
Excuse me?
Hello?
Why won't they answer?
You have questions, huh?
Very well.
I'll answer them.
First, why am I here?
So we can terminate you.
Your arrival is
problematic, you see,
and I've deemed you detrimental
to our national interests.
But why the secrecy?
Why don't you officially
refuse relations with my people?
Do you have a deal
with some other race?
I don't have
to answer that.
No, you don't.
The stench
on you already has.
You smell of dog.
Not good!
Dealing with the Dogishuans.
That's against galactic law.
Guess you didn't know that, huh?
The only thing that you're
going to know, and very soon,
is a quick death!
What's going on?
Ka-Boom!
And Kerblooey!
So what now?
What do you plan
to do next, Kio?
Bust Eris
out of Hangar F.
No, wait!
You could get killed!
I'm willing to take
that risk for her sake.
Sorry, but from here on, you
two are gonna have to walk!
Well, it looks like that
got their attention.
I guess I can kiss my chances
of ever joining the CIA goodbye.
Yeah, ditto for my career with
the Immigration Bureau of Japan.
Oh, that's for you.
It's just like the MGC.
Sweet!
Yeah, I think so, too.
This is it! Hangar F!
Would someone find out what
the hell is going on outside?
Um, instead of that
I'd worry more about
what's going on inside!
What?
But how?
My outfit.
It's a scaled-down
power suit.
I only used a tiny iota
of its strength
to break free just then.
Now allow me to show
you its maximum power.
What the?
Oh, my!
Hi there!
Eris!
Um, Kio?
What are you doing here?
I heard you were captured
so I came to rescue you.
Wait, you mean you risked
your life to save me?
Yeah, but seeing
what's happened in here,
I think you might have
been fine without me.
Oh, thank you so very much Kio!
Please,
I can't breathe! Stop!
I would just smother
you with appreciation!
Stop! Eris!
You're smothering
me with your boobs!
Ugh!
Ah, well.
Wasn't my van!
Get in here quick!
Where's Kio?
Where are you, kid?
Eris is safe and sound.
We're headed to the runway
with Miss Itokazu right now.
Huh?
You lost the van
but you got a ride.
Hey, wait, did you say
with Aoi and Manami?
Sure did. I think they've
got a thing for ya.
Please tell me you have a plan
on how to escape from here.
A helicopter's picking
us up any minute now.
As long as those little
guys can fly it, that is.
What little guys?
Of course
they can fly it.
See, look?
Just keep her steady,
guys, you're almost here!
Uh-oh!
Aw dammit!
Talk about lousy luck!
Got any more weapons
stashed away, Aoi?
I do, so just leave those
mechanized battle machines
to us!
Hey, the Assistroids
survived the crash!
Well, guys, prepare to
demilitarize those vehicles!
Those things
are our targets!
Move forward and charge!
But they'll be destroyed!
No, they won't be Kio.
And neither will I,
trust me.
Eris, no!
Activate quasi-antimatter
hammers now, everybody!
Let's knock their socks off,
among other things!
The authorities covered
the incident up
by calling it an explosion
at the base's fuel depot.
So the truth was kept from
the eyes of the world.
And so, almost as if
nothing had happened,
the rest of Kio's summer
vacation went back
to how it was before
the incident.
Now that all the data's
been accumulated,
your duties will change.
Oh, you're not going
to the library today?
No. We've copied all
the pertinent Earth
materials already
My report's finished
so I'm done here.
Does that mean
You're leaving?
Yes.
Thank you for all
that you've done.
You're welcome, Eris.
I was really happy to help.
I also want
to let you know
how appreciative I am
of you coming to save me.
It was incredibly
brave of you,
and I can't tell you how
touched I was by your gesture.
Oh, don't mention it.
I mean, we are friends
after all, right?
Yeah. About that.
Pretty soon, I'm going
to be reaching a milestone
of Catian womanhood,
my first mating season.
Uh, mating season?
And well, um.
I've been kinda
wondering, Kio.
If I get to return to Earth,
would you mind becoming my mate?
Your mate?
Wait, you mean like
do it with you?
Kio!
Turn it on!
The TV.
Now. Hurry.
Whoa.
The Catian mother
ship's on Earth.
Hey, Eris! Are you here?
Melwin?
Chief Chaika?
Why are you here? I thought
you were still observing!
Well, after we got
the taste analysis data
for all of the Earth food that
you described in your report.
Everybody on the mother
ship said they couldn't wait
to try it for themselves.
And in fact, it was the food
that led to the big decision.
Catia has decided to formally
establish relations with Earth,
and we're the advanced party.
We hope you can provide
us with accommodations here.
Here in my house?
You're not
prepared for guests?
Don't you know
the Catian motto?
I'm going to drop by!
Just as I expected,
they failed.
I swear. These humans
are as useless as a dog
that won't hunt.
When a gaggle
of girls move in,
life gets more
chaotic for Kio!
Who's prowling around
the house, and oh, my!
Why aren't Aoi and Manami
wearing any clothes?
Next time:
"We've Come to Stay."
I'm coming to
drop in on you!