Space: the final frontier.
These are the voyages
of the starship Catia.
Its continuing mission: to
explore strange, new worlds.
To seek out new life
and new civilizations.
To boldly go where no sexy
alien cat woman from a
planet full of sexy alien cat
women has gone before.
The Saitama Super Arena.
A premier event center
that can accommodate up
to thirty-seven
thousand people.
A location currently
packed to the rafters
with members
of a top-secret society.
Who've gathered for
an important meeting.
Mee-ow!
Meow!!
My brethren!
We've all gathered together
because we're fans of cats!
Amen!!
Amen!
Whether it's their pointy
ears, furry tails, whiskers,
button noses,
their sweet purrs,
or the way they
rub up against us,
we're huge fans
of all things kitty cat!
We treasure them!
No! It's
more than that!
Only one word can describe
how we feel for them: L.O.V.E!
We want to be just like them,
right, brothers and sisters?
Yeah!!
But...
Unfortunately,
we're all phonies!
We can only dress like
cats, but we're not them!
Why is that?
I'll tell you why;
it's because we descended from
the lowly ape not the holy cat!
That's the curse of our race.
Awwww!!
Wait!
There is hope,
and the other day,
the Good News
was made manifest!
Behold!
Genuine kitty ears!
A real tail!
Hallelujah!
My friends, we
may not have been created
in a cat's own image.
But this beautiful,
and supreme being was!
The answer to our prayers
and what we've been seeking!
A real-live cat girl who
deserves our total devotion
and unceasing praise!
I proclaim to each and every one
of you. The kitty-eared members
of the Underside of
the Kitten's Paw
that this Divine Embodiment
is our one true cat god!
So then begin.
"Operation Cat's
Meow" immediately!
Mee-ow!
Meow!!
You can't let
your past prevent you
from going after
your future.
Just have a little more
faith in yourself, 'kay?
That's a lot easier
said than done, Manami.
Uh. Coming!
Huh?
Movers, huh?
Good morning, all.
Oh, yeah!
Fry-fry, fry-fry-fry!
Whee!
Fry-fry, fry-fry-ooo!
Fry-fry...
Eris?
Oh, hi there,
Kio, good morning!
Isn't today the most
wonderful day or what?
What are you
so jazzed about?
Oh, didn't
I tell you?
I'm about to fry up some
breakfast potstickers!
I'm so
incredibly happy!
I can't stop
singing and dancing
and I don't know
what's come over me!
Fry-fry, fry-fry-fry!
This is my fault.
I was cleaning out the pantry
when I came across this stuff.
I was about to throw it
away since your cat ran off.
But then I thought Eris
might like to try it.
Cat nip?
You gave her some?
No, all I did was let her
take a little whiff of it!
When my cat used
to have this stuff,
she never acted like that.
Hey!!
Don't hog
all the happy magic
good time powder
for yourself!
Eris, stop! You've
had too much as it is!
No more!
I know when I've had
enough, so gimme!
Eris, get a
hold of yourself;
you're acting like someone on
one of those rehab shows on TV!
Hey, quit acting like a basket
case and knock it off, Eris!
Kio isn't gonna
give you any, 'kay?
Alright, well then why
don't you give me some,
and I'll give you
a cat bath instead?
What?
Yoink!
Now how 'bout that tongue
bath I promised you?
No, stop!
My, my, what a scene.
Doctor Durel!
So what was that you
injected her with?
It wasn't a shot.
It was a taser charge.
It sent an electric pulse
directly to her nerves,
and calmed her down.
Um. Sorry, I don't
know what came over me.
I do.
Your first mating season
is right around the corner.
Mating season?
It's a common occurrence
amongst our race.
Once one reaches
their sixteenth cycle.
They begin
to go into heat
and start to have regular
seasons of fertility.
And...
As their mating
season approaches,
even the most minute
traces of a stimulant
can affect their
brain chemistry,
and cause them
to go wild.
Does that
explain things?
Wow, so a little whiff of
catnip caused all that?
You're really quite
fortunate, Eris.
We rarely have partners
for our first mating seasons,
but you already do here.
Otherwise, you'd have to make
do with the virtual simulator
Doctor, you're
embarrassing me!
Wait, what partner?
You didn't know?
Why, Kio, of course.
Are you crazy?
On this planet,
it's illegal to have sex
with somebody
underage like him!
Ah, But you forget
This house is the
provisional Catian Embassy,
so Earth law
doesn't apply inside it.
So there's no problem.
There's a gigantic one!
But it's my understanding
that Kio isn't romantically
involved with anyone at all.
So what's the problem?
Um, well, it's, uh...
Help me out here and tell 'em
why this is so wrong, Kio.
Y'know, I'd love to,
but I almost forgot
that I've gotta go clean my
room, and like right now, too!
Hey!
Don't run away, you
spineless, little coward!
We're talking
about you here!
Are you positive you
want to be with him?
Yes!
Without a doubt, Kio
is the bravest person
that I've ever
known, doctor.
He wasn't all that
brave just then.
Did you come here just
to help my condition?
Or was there another
reason you came?
I have a request
from the captain.
She wants you
to go to Tokyo.
Tokyo, huh?
"First, begin by licking the
master key memory terminal,
and then press the
transmit button.".
'Kay.
"When you hear the chime,
you have now been recognized
as the default commander.
Next is the startup test.
Please give an order
that is possible
for the Assistroids
to perform."
Um... Stand up.
Alright then Your name
will be Nakamura
and yours Chiba.
Got it?
Now then, please do a small
jump and hop to the side.
Twirl three times
and do a beckoning cat.
"Now, please give them an order
that is impossible to follow."
Okay then,
let's see here.
Hmm. You guys do a
quick-draw, okay?
Just like Joe the
Ace in that movie.
Take this.
"If your units are
functioning properly.
When given an
impossible command,
they will quickly
terminate each other."
"Issue a command within
ten seconds to abort this."
What? Stop!
Abort!
Wow, your first day with me
was almost your last, huh?
I'll be more careful
from now on, okay?
The cats are
going to Tokyo?
Yes ma'am.
We aren't certain if it's
a diplomatic mission yet.
But their existence could
become even more widely known
because of this excursion.
This is pretty aggressive,
even for them.
Oh, well, guess
I'm off to Tokyo, too.
Wow!
Hey, Kio!
Huh?
Did you know this is my first
time travelling in an aircraft
that flies by
aerodynamic lift?
I'm incredibly
excited about this!
I can't wait!
Uh-huh.
I can tell.
As if her outfit
wasn't bad enough
Now she's gotta make a lot of
noise to attract attention, too?
Just calm down Manami no
one's noticed her so far.
I just hope it
stays that way.
Um, excuse me?
Folks?
--Yeah?
--Yes?
I need to ask about your
travelling companion.
Your little pet robot
friend or whatever.
That thing
Oh! No, please
don't worry.
That unit is friendly
and won't harm anyone.
Nor interfere with
the plane's electronics.
Oh, no.
What I meant was the plane
is about to take off.
Before we can leave,
it needs to be stowed.
Oh, sure thing!
Hey, come over here!
Can you please put him in
the overhead bin, ma'am?
Oh, yes
I'm sure everyone's
noticed her now.
Wait, don't
put him in there.
We've got some empty
seats available.
Put that adorable little
guy in one instead.
Right.
Thank you so much!
Now what do you say
to these nice ladies?
How sweet!
Cat Planet Cuties.
Aoi checked them
with her luggage?
So, are we headed to
some place important?
Yes, very much so.
Wait a minute.
Here?
Wow, the epicenter
of geek commerce, huh?
You were ordered
to come here?
Yes. The arts
research team requested
that I observe this
renowned marketplace,
and acquire certain
items for study.
This will allow them to better
understand your world's culture.
What are your
specific orders?
To purchase toys and several
volumes of the literature
known as "manga."
--What?
--Huh?
Well, you see,
the position of Catian
cultural anthropology is this:
the level of a world's
culture is defined by
what its inhabitants
dismiss as "lowbrow,"
even moreso than what they
consider to be highbrow.
Say, Kio.
We Catians are the
first race of cat people
that Earth has ever
encountered, right?
Yep, you guys are
the only ones so far.
Well, then how do
you explain this?
Um, gee, where to start?
Hey, why don't we talk
about this later, 'kay?
We've got shopping
to do, remember?
Aoi?
Excuse me, sir, but do you
have the items on this list?
Let's see.
One moment,.
I can't believe
he wasn't weirded-out
by Eris' appearance
Oh. Excuse me, Miss?
Does this thing
belong to you?
Sure does.
Well, if you don't mind,
I need to move it.
Thanks.
He didn't find the Assistroid
to be strange, either.
As a species, you humans have
a much higher adaptability
to different cultures
than I thought.
I guess you're right.
Wait, where's Kio?
Hey!
What the heck are
you doing over here?
I thought you supposed to be
Eris' bodyguard on this trip!
Yeah, I am,
but here, look!
I've never seen a real
BC-FX game system before!
Yeah?
Well, it's gonna be
the last thing you ever see
if you don't get over
there and do your job!
Aoi?
Um, yes, Manami?
It's just that Kio--
I meant, uh...
Kio and I are gonna
keep watching over Eris;
catch up with us
when you're done.
Yeah, sure!
I'll be there
in two minutes!
Okay!
You two want that one?
Man, how can one person be
so crazy about something?
Holy crap, a Chiappa
Rhino 357 Magnum!
It says it's a
replica, but still!
That's a first-rate piece,
and probably the best-looking
one I've ever seen!
Oh, what I wouldn't
give to hold
that sexy piece in my
hot little hands!
Will it be cash
or credit then, miss?
Where is everyone?
No, it couldn't be!
A Nikkatsu Colt that was
actually used in a movie?
Want a closer look?
These props are
hard to come by.
Oh, are they now?
They sell out quick.
Thanks. We'll ship them
out promptly, ma'am.
What a great place!
And you know.
The items here were
very affordable!
Wouldn't you guys
agree with me?
I blew my
whole allowance
It sounds to me like you're
having buyer's remorse.
Stop sounding so
mopey, would ya?
You're one to talk.
So how much did you
spend back there, Manami?
I take it that translates
to "everything I had."
Uh-oh, guys Are you
having regrets, too, Aoi?
I think this is a trap.
Huh?
It's a Saturday afternoon
This train station should
be bustling, but it's empty.
If you're right, just who
or what are we dealing with?
They're using Taoist
wizardry or a western style.
I can't exactly say yet But
there's a magician at work,
and they've cast a
spell to keep everyone
but us away from here.
What do we do?
You get on the train
with Kakazu and Eris.
I'll catch up once I've taken
care of who's responsible.
Chiba, Nakamura.
Look after them.
Ohh, a barrier created
with spiritrons?
It's keeping folks
out of that station.
Setting that up in the middle
of Tokyo is impressive.
And the Japanese government
isn't responsible?
No, ma'am.
I've been scanning
all the government
comm channels for days
and there's
been no chatter
or activity regarding
the Catians at all.
If not them,
then who?
Four-eyes has
taken the bait.
Short-hair, the three
runts, the tagalong,
and the target are currently
in transit aboard the train.
Phase two complete.
We're initiating
Phase three, everyone.
Team A, you'll carefully
obtain both the target
and the tagalong.
Team B and I will eliminate
Charmed Momiji
Permanently
Roger.
They were glamours!
Attention all passengers:
there will be a
thirty-minute delay
on the inbound central
line due to an accident.
We apologize for any...
Wait, that's the train Kakazu
and the others are on!
Hey, is something wrong?
There aren't any
ads on this train?
What?
Yeah, you're right.
What is this stuff, gas?
I'm feeling really
light-headed.
Eris!
Manami,
are you okay?
Hey, let go!
Kio! Eris!
Guys, go after them!
Oh, crap!
What is this junk?
It's like I'm in a roach
motel or something!
Oh, no!
Aw! Damn!
They're in the car
ahead, go get 'em!
On it!
Apport!
Uh-uh!
What have you done
with my friends?
We don't take
any fare jumpers!
Ow.
I'll find you, Kakazu
Oh, I love having
embassy duty!
I'd give anything
to trade places with Eris!
Catian Embassy,
Chayka speaking.
Wait, what do you mean
Eris has been kidnapped?
Unfortunately we can't
officially send
in Catian forces.
We still haven't formalized
our treaty with your planet yet.
Yeah, I thought that
might be the case.
Even though you guys
can't do anything now,
me and Manami can, right?
Yeah, you're Earthlings,
and I can unofficially
provide you with tech.
Can you send an
Assistroid programmed
for electronic warfare?
Gimme the phone!
Can you also send
my unit along, too?
Sure thing!
Manami, that's your
personal Assistroid?
Uh-huh.
I call him Yun-Fat.
What the heck is that?
It's one of the Immigration
Bureau's secret depots.
Things might get
a little rough,
so let's help ourselves
to the goodies inside.
Brethren!
Behold the sacred catnap
of the Divine Embodiment!
this is the holy vessel
sent from Heaven above!
The guiding light adorned
with real kitty ears and a tail!
She is the chosen one who
will lead the Underside
of the Kitten's Paw
into a new world!
A world that we will
build with our paws!
Mee-ow!
Mee-ow! Mee-ow!
The Underside of
the Kitten's Paw?
It's officially considered
a religious organization,
but it's more
of a cult, really.
It's grown rapidly and it
sounds like they're the ones
who nabbed your friends.
Its founder is Antonia
Lirimonie Norfederas
Papanorgas Arecroteles
Cnorses Morfenoss.
Turns out she's
the granddaughter
of a multimillionaire.
Michael J.C.D.A.E.
Morfenoss, a guy so rich
that he's called
"The Second Onassis".
Her cat cult's main base
is a luxury liner
called The Androala.
It has a displacement of two
hundred and fifty thousand tons.
That's even larger
than some oil tankers.
So that must be where Eris
and Kakazu are being held.
Are you kidding?
The time is at hand.
At last, the dawn of
our age has arrived!
Mee-ow!
There's sexy swimsuits
on a luxury liner
and helicopters and missiles
flying thru the sky!
Can the gawky love interest
compete with a girl
who out-beautifies
even flowers?
Next time:
"We've Come to Rescue You."
I'm coming to drop
in on you!