The space vessel
Red Cat,,
having traveled
many light years,...
is now all alone,...
more or less.
The ship's Captain lies
soon-to-be-shipwrecked
and comatose.
The Acting Captain is Melwin,
who happened to survive...
And her partner is Luros,
who's been turned
into a hologram.
And the Catian crew
who evolved from cats?
They'd have fun, fun, fun,
in the sun, sun, sun,...
if they weren't
frozen, that is.
Sweet Christmas!
They sure made a
mess-a-things, didn't they?
Uncle Yuichi...
Miss Itokazu.
What in the world
is going on here, Kakazu?
How about we go buy
him a new movie...?
And this time we'll make
sure to get a romantic one.
Something that'll lead
to lots of kissing
while you watch
it together...?
That's fine...
Christmas gifts aren't
really my thing anyway.
It's not that big a deal.
Aoi...
Really, don't
worry about it.
But if the mothership
crashes,...
what's gonna
happen to Earth?
It depends on the
velocity at impact,
but... more than likely,
given its size,
it would wipe out
your planet completely.
But there's no real
reason to be concerned...
The mothership will never
even make it out of orbit
because it's been
programmed to self-destruct.
Whoa.
Are you sure?
Large-scale spacecraft
are built with certain
precautionary fail-safes...
If a ship approaches
a planet without slowing...
The crystalline structure of
the hull will fragment itself...
And then,...
turn to vapor,
preventing any damage.
But wait,
what about the crew?
Under normal circumstances,
they would eject
in escape pods...
But in this case,
they're frozen in time...
There's no chance of survival.
The bridge is isolated in a
completely separate dimension,
so there's no need to worry
about an attack on us.
Hold on. Why can't ya just
change the ship's trajectory?
To do that-...
To do that we'd have to bring
the main systems down
and restart them...
And the only way that
would be possible is with
Captain Qoone's top-level,
secret command codes.
And the Acting
Captain can't do that?
The codes are
a part of her being...
Down to the cellular level.
Before the command
can be fully executed,
the Captain's genetic identity
must be officially verified.
Even though I've taken command
as the Secondary Officer...
As long as the
Captain is still living,
there's no way I'll be
able to do this for her.
Guess that explains
why they went to the trouble
of rendering her unconscious
instead of just killing her.
But, you guys...
You do realize if we
don't figure out a way
to rescue the rest of the crew,
then no one will.
If we can just find a practical
way to get into space,
then at the very least,
we'd have a fighting chance.
But with my personal
ship now destroyed...
Getting there doesn't
seem possible at all.
It's not like there's a good
way to get the Captain there,
anyways.
And even if there was,
she's unconscious,
so she can't really
order a restart...
Sorry, looks like
it's game over.
Look, Captain Qoone's bell!
What...? But-
Wait--Now that
I think of it...
As the Captain
was collapsing,
you were holding onto
her bell, weren't you?
Uh...
Did she say anything
when she gave it to you?
But not much; all she said
was "please take this."
Then that means...
as of this moment,
both the mothership's
crew and I...
are now serving under
your command, sir...!
Captain Kio Kakazu!
Wait, I'm the Captain?
Goodness...
Yes, that's quite
the predicament...
Of course, you know I'll
gladly do whatever I can.
If it's for you, Miss Eris,
no matter what it is,
there's no limit
to what I'll do...
We'll speak again very soon.
Maya...!
It's shopping time!
Yes, of course...
But for what?
I want a rocket...
I want it now.
As you wish, My Lady.
I just spoke with Antonia,
and she volunteered
to buy us a rocket.
Seriously?
Must be nice being
a multimillionaire.
And now all we need is for
our newly appointed Captain
to give the official
restart order
and we can get ourselves
out of this mess.
But Eris, our rockets don't
have the ability to make it
into deep space
like yours do.
That's all right...
I still have Luros.
Hold on, I thought you said
your ship was destroyed.
Mostly, but it was only
the engine and outer hull...
Luros is tough;
it'll take more than that
to destroy
the central core.
The central core?
What's that?
It's Professor Jameson!
Professor Jameson
was a mechanical man
from old science
fiction stories
who looked pretty
much just like this.
I'm home!
It's Luros!
This is the core
I just mentioned...
If we can help get her up to
a standard satellite orbit...
Then, with a little help
from the Assistroids,...
she'll be able to construct
a simple warp engine
centered around herself.
After that, we can jump
to where the Mothership is,
no problem at all!
Yeah, but the crew...
Ya still haven't told us how
we're supposed to unfreeze 'em
and manage
an actual rescue.
Don't worry; I'm formulating
a plan about that now.
Well, there are certain
low-life individuals
who've been selling
technology
to illegal
traffickers, lately.
I'd say it's very
likely they used cards
purchased on
the Black Market...
So, here you go.
I bet those'll do the trick...
You'll be able to unfreeze
that frozen time, no problem.
This is perfect...
Thanks, Ichika.
Tell ya the truth,
I'd love to be able to tag
along with you guys...
But unfortunately, I've got
a lot going on, so I can't.
What, do you have a deadline?
Oh, you know me...
There's always something
important to do.
I would like to pay you
back for the cards...
I'll give you the
copyright license
to a D-I-Y Assistroid kit...
I can promise you this:
you won't be disappointed.
Can't we do better
than that...?
I don't know what we'd do
without these Accel Card things.
According to the Galactic
Sentient Federation,
copyright law violations
are a serious offense, Kio...
If we were caught
doing this,
the Orzonians would punish
us with a Thought Freeze.
Oh... That is serious.
Looks like all the pieces
are coming together, huh?
With a little luck, we might
actually pull this thing off.
I hope so...
As long as Antonia can
get us that rocket,
we should be in good shape.
This is bad!
Quick, turn on the TV!
Roughly four hours ago,
the Catian mothership
left its orbit around Jupiter
and started
to rapidly accelerate
to an extremely
dangerous speed.
Based on the observed
explosions,
it is presumed
to have lost control
after an unknown
accident...
Due to the lack of response
to our attempts to make contact,
we believe there
are no survivors.
If the ship continues along
its current trajectory,
it will collide with
Earth in two weeks.
It's predicted the impact
will be equivalent
to a several kiloton
nuclear explosion.
Hello...
This is Kio.
Oh, Kio,
I've got bad news.
We're in trouble...
I've been looking
for rockets everywhere,
but all of them
are booked up.
We have no way
to get into space!
Antonia says she's done
everything she can,
but she still
can't find one.
We've exerted our political
influence to the fullest,...
pressuring nations to mothball
their space-worthy rockets...
None of them would dare try
to intercept the Catian Ship.
See that, little kitties...?
Seems when the cats are away,
the dogs get to play.
What can we do?
We don't necessarily
need a rocket;
if we find a workable engine,
we can build everything else.
Sounds kinda risky,
are you sure?
Yes...
Once we have that,
Kio can construct
the rest of the rocket
with his newfound power.
Wait... That's nuts, I don't
know how to build a rocket!
Sure you do; just use
the multitasking organizer!
You can rearrange matter
at the molecular level,...
which gives you the ability
to create anything you want to!
You mean this?
Problem is,...
it won't work unless
you can precisely envision
what you're trying to make.
And there's simply
no way you're gonna know
all the intricate details
of a rocket engine
on a part-by-part level...
But I bet you
have an idea
what the fuselage
looks like, right?
My lady...
If all we need is
the engine--...
What, do you know of one?
I do...
It's in a chilly location,
but it is for sale.
Huh?!
How chilly?
Russia.
Huh?!
Cat Planet Cuties!
It's not working.
The main system
defenses are impeccable.
It's going to take a lot
more than that to hack in.
Looks like our only
choice is to rush 'em.
Unfortunately, I don't think
that'll be an option...
We're not gonna be able
to access the computer
room regardless.
Without the Captain here
to execute command codes,
nothing we do can alter
the ship's course.
Yeah, you're right...
Eris and the others are
doing everything they can.
All we can do now is wait
for them to get here
and try to back them up.
Right.
Oh gosh...!
.. I'm so... cold, Kio.
Well, it is below zero.
Hello, there...
I am General Arushkowa.
Long time no see, Mina.
Guess our kind just
don't know when to die...
Maya.
Guess not...
But all the same...
Thanks for your
help on this thing.
Yes, we appreciate
your kindness.
What is this place?
It's an underground,
rail-mobile missile base.
What's a
'rail-mobile missile'?
They're train-mounted ICBMs
with mobile launch sites.
They were built
to hide launches
from surveillance
satellites...
Strategic complexes
to prevent preemptive strikes.
Now, it's nothing but
a relic of a time gone by.
The warheads
have been removed,
but the rockets
still function.
What say you,
Miss Eris...?
Think it'll work?
Sure will...!
Thank you again very much!
Your asking
price is fair,
sounds like we're
in business...
We'll also provide you with
safe passage out of the country
if you require it.
You've got a deal...
I've been thinking it's
about time I get out of here
and see the big
bad world again.
Wow, we're actually
going to space in these.
Enough talk, people,
we'd better get to work...
If the dogs find out
we're here, they're sure to try
and throw a wrench in our plans.
While that's true...
We did leave those
body doubles
behind to keep
'em off our scent,
so we should be
okay for a while.
This is so not right!
Why should I, of all people,
have to wear this?
Eh, no one's gonna
even know it's us.
Besides, they say
most foreigners think
all Japanese people
look alike anyway, right?
Let's see...
There's the fuselage...
And then there's
the cockpit...
Wait, does a spaceship
need to have wings...?
Ah, might as well
include 'em for now...
Imagining a whole spaceship sure
takes a lot of concentration.
Hey, Kio, ya got a sec?
Manami, hey...
Yeah... Actually,
I was about to take a break
right before you came in...
What's up?
Truth is, I'm in the middle
of a real mess here...
And I wanted to ask
you something now,
while I still can.
Uh, what's that?
It's just... What exactly
do you plan to do?
Oh... Well, after I master
this mind trick thing,
I figure I better
build that rocket
so we don't
all die, right?
That's not
what I'm asking!
I mean about
Aoi and Eris!
Huh?
Aw cripes...
Do you know how Aoi
feels about you;
do you have any clue?
What do you mean?
Girls, for future reference,
do not risk their lives
and throw away their careers
for a boy they're
only interested in being
'just friends' with!
Think you can guess who they
would do that type of thing for?
Oh, you've got
to be kidding me!
Come on. A child
could answer this...
Are you really
that dim-witted?
Let's see, uh...
best friend?
Geez...!
Just think about it...!
Use your head!
Ow, Manami, okay!
Knock it off;
that hurts!
You don't have
to figure it out now, but...
After this crisis, you
will have to make a choice.
Think about
how she must feel.
Man, that's big...
"Think about Aoi,"
she says...?
Oh, there you are...
Hey.
What were
you thinking?
Wh-what do you mean?
Why would you ask Kio
something like that?
Well?!
Oh, that...
I don't know, it's just
Kio can be so dense...
Way things are going,
Christmas is gonna be ruined.
I had to do something,
otherwise he'll never
come around to you.
No one asked you
for your help...!
Do you realize the severity
of the situation we're in?
Well of course,
but I thought-...
You didn't think...!
We're about to get launched
into space for
crying out loud...!
And there's no telling
what'll happen up there!
Yeah... I know.
But you bring that up now.
Kio needs to focus
on the task at hand...
I don't wanna cloud
his judgment...
What if he gets hurt, huh?
Then what?
You should think things
through a little more!
Maybe so...
But what about you, Aoi?
We're in a situation
where we don't know
what's gonna happen...
What if it's the worst
case scenario...?
Are you sure you can live
without getting
an answer from him?
And what if we succeed...?
Maybe Eris and Kio
will become closer
than they ever
have been...
I know you feel I'm meddling
in your business...
But...! How would
that make you feel?
Having everything end
without him knowing the truth?
How would that
make you feel?
Because, Manami...
I know that you're
in love with him, too.
Come on, you don't really
think I'm stupid...
You can't tell me
you're okay with him
not knowing how you feel...
Never getting
a final answer...
Won't you be sad if it ends
before it ever began?
You don't know how to tell him
the truth either, do you...?
Sometimes it's okay
to be selfish...
But pushing your fears
on someone else
instead of facing them...?
You're not helping,
you're being a hypocrite!
Intruders...!
All units, alert status!
They're spies!
That's impossible!
Take the left!
I'll go right!
Got it!
Let him go!
Aoi, careful!
Don't move.
I've littered this whole
complex with bombs!
Wait a minute...
You lived...
My mistake.
So it's you...
That assassin from before...
I wouldn't throw
stones if I were you.
Back off!
You an' I are nothing
alike, girly...
You don't fight
for a cause or a country;
you're just
a ruthless killer.
I have a cause.
Oh, please...
Is it worth dying for?
You serve a country
you don't love...
You protect a planet
you know nothing about...
Makes you no more
than a mercenary...
Killer for hire.
Don't listen to him!
Lose the weapon!
But do it slow, I know
all about your power...
Any funny business
and the kid gets it!
Do it!
Yeah, do it!
You can thank
Catia for that!
They think death is the
abandonment of potential...
Their weapons don't kill.
There you are!
Restrain that man,
right now!
Thank goodness
we found you... You okay?
I'm fine.
Aoi...
Thank you...
You saved me.
Damn... I'm sorry.
I had no idea an enemy
had infiltrated my ranks.
The only enemy here is you,.
filthy traitor!
This base is property
of the motherland...
Selling it off on your
own is high treason!
Turncoat!
Miss Eris,
we've got a problem!
NATO forces are on their
way here right now!
Two NATO tank battalions
that were out on maneuvers
have steered in this direction
and are on the move...
They're closing fast.
According to the intelligence
reports I received,.
they've been ordered
to destroy a missile base
that's been taken over
by a terrorist cell.
Don't they realize...
that we're trying
to save the world here?
They should arrive roughly
three hours from now.
We're short on time,
we better move.
That's nowhere near enough...
Doesn't even give us
time to fuel it up.
Ready, Kio?
I did it!
Nice one, Kio!
Thanks...
Holy crap...
I can't believe it!
It's purr-fect!
You did great!
The design's totally retro,
don't you think?
Yeah, I bet Miss Itokazu
would totally love it!
They're coming...!
We're out of time!
Everyone get ready
for take-off...
Leave the rest to us.
That's right, Miss Eris...
They won't come between
our kitty-eared friendship...
My girls and I will handle
everything down here.
Right... I can't thank
you ladies enough!
Now go...
Quickly, everyone.
Right!
It's time
to release the hounds.
And so, overwhelmed
with emotions,
the youngsters
board the rocket...
Feelings shared,...
and feelings unrequited...
As each of them bears
their own confusion,
they head off to battle.
But what will
the outcome be?
Kio and the gang
rocket off to space
to stop the plummeting
Catian mothership!
Will the dogs have their day,
or will Kio and the girls
put them back
in the dog house?
Next time...!
"I Came to Find You!"
I'm coming
to drop in on you!