Kio, a high school student
and would-be astronaut,...
is inexplicably
marooned
on a very un-school
like desert island,
where he finds a most
unusual magical bottle...
He gives it a rub, and in
a massive puff of smoke,...
emerges the sexy
cat-alien-genie-girl, Eris...
With a quick blink
of her cat eyes,
she transports
them off the island
and safely back
to Kio's place...
She declares him her
master and vows to help him
by granting
his every wish...
What tomfoolery will she
blink her way into this time?
"This is the
Cock-a-Doodle-Doo House...
A Restaurant in
the city of Okinawa.
In addition to its
unique arrangement
of South American recipes,
it's famous for having
the best roasted chicken
in all of Japan."
No way!
You stupid jerk!
You're trying to cheat
again, aren't you?!
I'm not cheating,
I'm just winning.
Whoever's got the six of
hearts, cough it up right now!
Wow, it's Kio...!
I see my friends,
I'll join them!
Add one more plate for me,
and give me two of everything!
Hey...! You guys sure seem
like you're having a good time!
Ho boy.
What's going on?
It's nothing.
A friendly game.
By the way you
guys are acting,
you'd think it's a
matter of life and death.
Yeah.
Huh? What the...
Oh! That's my cue.
"This is our story...
It all began this morning."
There are four each of thirty
four different kinds of tiles...
So, from one hundred
thirty-six total tiles,
each of the players
draws fourteen of them.
That's three hundred
billion tile combos.
And then from that number, you
create specific combinations...
Then we all compete with
each other by earning points
based on the
difficulty thereof.
Therefore, any points earned
in a half round with two innings
make for a
zero sum game.
And don't forget...
A sound strategy
which leads to victory
is more important than
going for a quick win.
It's also important
to try guessing your
opponents' tiles...
Do that based
on what they discard,
while keeping them guessing
about what you're discarding.
And you're allowed to talk
during game play...
So it's more than just a game,
it's a communication tool.
It's a surprisingly deep
pastime, huh...?
Riichi! Ron!
I win!
Wha-- Big
Three Dragons?!
Plus, I'm the dealer!
Whoa...!
A Yakuman bullseye...!
Even with uncapped scoring,
this is pretty dramatic.
And even worse,
the Captain's wall is broken...
So she gets double points!
Aww...!
Guess I'm sunk, huh?
All of it, right?
The rule about stripping when
you lose is the one thing
I'm having a hard
time understanding.
Now that you mention it,
it is kind of strange...
And these Mahjong outfits
look like school uniforms.
Well, according
to Eris's research...
this is the way humans like
to play games on Earth.
There's still so much more
for us to learn about them.
I bet if we just keep at it,
we'll figure them out.
That's all the
clothes I have...
What now?
There's nothing
left to take off.
Here!
According to the rulebook,
if you've got negative points,
you put on the box!
You know this reminds me,
I wonder how
Eris's survey is going.
Oh... She said she'll be
doing a field exam with Kio
and the gang today.
What kind of field exam?
Yum...! This golden-brown
chicken skin is so crunchy...!
And the garlic and spices
inside are so rich...
The flavor they give
to the meat is so...
ohhh, so good...!
The best!
Yeah, yeah, yeah...!
So, what's on for today?
You mentioned you wanted our
help with your survey, right?
Oh, yes,
thank you.
Wanna swallow and
try that again?
Yeah... What Eris
wanted to do is survey
how we Earthlings play games.
A survey of how we play?
Yes...! It's a part of our
customs and culture study...
We formulated a list of
Earth's pastimes for analysis...
But there're some things
we have to actually do
in order to
understand them.
So if you're okay with it,
I was hoping to
play with you guys.
That makes sense...
When it comes
to fun and games,
I say the more
the merrier!
But... Why did you
choose this place?
Well, since we're all
gonna play together,
we wanted to invite
Antonia to come...
After all, she really
hasn't had much chance
to play many
games with others.
Since the beautiful Miss
Eris invited me along...
I thought it'd be nice
if we ate together, too.
Yes, that's right...
One time, during
a camping trip,
My Lady dined
in this restaurant,
and was quite
taken with it...
It's been a mainstay
for us ever since.
Oh.
Here's the plan.
I've gathered up
some fun games
we should all be able
to play together.
Mahjong,
cards, backgammon,
chess,
shogi, Pop-Up Pirate,
Crocodile Dentist...
Wow...!
Looks like fun.
I'm not so sure
about this, you guys.
Huh?
If we play them just
to explain how they work,
then it won't be fun.
You know?
It'll be about as entertaining
as reading a rule book...
Eris won't gain
an understanding
of the real reason
we play games.
So then,
what should we do?
Why, there's gotta be a prize
for the winners, of course.
Um... Okay...
That sounds great...!
Surely, if there's
a prize at stake,
then we'll all play
like we mean it,
and get more into
the game, won't we?
But... What
will the prize be?
Since you were nice
enough to invite me...
I can help
you out with that.
Not enough?
In that case, we'll
need some surety bonds
from my Swiss account.
No, please...
That's okay!
With those stakes, it
wouldn't be a game anymore.
Okay...
But then,
what should we do?
My Lady.
Maybe this could
serve as the prize?
A model of the
Divine Embodiment,
crafted by the Kitty-Ear
Order of the Underside
of the Kitten's Paw...
A fan collector's item we
recently had commissioned
by a world-famous artist.
Sorry, this just
isn't doing it for me.
I think it's great.
Well, if that's no good,
how about we try this?
Here, look...
It's a behind-the-scenes
making-of documentary
for a film Kio and
his video club made.
Don't you have anything
better than that?
Hey...! That's the movie
I helped you guys shoot, right?
I wanna copy!
It has great shots
of Kio taking a nap...
And some shots of
Kio having a snack...
And some shots
of Kio laughing...
Some shots of Kio making
a mistake and crying...
And other shots of Kio...
Like the ones where
he gets naked!
Yes...! I managed to film
you changing clothes a lot!
Hey...! You never
mentioned that before!
Now that's more like it...!
Think we found our prize.
What...?
Manami...
No way!
Now don't
be such a baby...
Come on, what does it
matter if we see it, huh?
Kio changing and
getting naked!
It's not fair for me
to just be a taker...
The right thing to do would be
to prepare some kind of prize
from the Catian
Embassy, but...
Um... What in
the hell are these?
It's a three-piece
set of Iriomote cats,
a very rare species that came in
the chocolate eggs Kio gave me!
That's just stupid.
They're not stupid,
they're said to be quite
elusive and precious.
Sorry to rain
on your parade,
but that's the worst
prize I've ever seen.
We have a package?
What is it?
Oh,...
it appears
to be a DVD.
It's Aoi and Manami!
"These chicks get down and dirty
in this action-packed epic...
A compilation of
girltastic action...
"Full Metal Feast of Debauchery
Series Number Seven...
Amazon Bunnies
from Hell vs.
Slavegirl Naughty
Maid Squad"...
Directed by Takao Kawasaki,
starring Manami Kinjyo
and Aoi Futaba."
You don't mean...
It's...
From when we--...?
It was the movie they
appeared in as a condition
for borrowing
the powerboat...
Taking a cue from
director Lars Von Triers'
'Dancer in the Dark,'
many hidden cameras had
been placed on the boat...
Of course, at the time,
neither of the girls
was fully aware of the mess
they had gotten themselves into.
That bald bastard!
"Thanks to all
your amazing work,
our little production
was successfully completed.
I'm sending you a copy
for your review...
I hope you enjoy it...
Takao Kawasaki."
Wow... That's amazing!
Well since you didn't like
my initial offering...
what do you say
to the Catian Embassy
submitting this as a prize?
Sounds good!
W-Whoa, no...!
Gimme...!
Y-you can't watch that!
Oh, come on...
What does it matter, huh?
Since you put up a DVD that's
embarrassing to me as a prize,
I'd say we're even.
Plus, I'm guessing
with this on the table,
you two are going to play
with everything you've got,
aren't you?
All right, we have all
the prizes accounted for!
And if you want 'em, you're
gonna have to win 'em.
So that's why--...
They're so serious.
Still, it's really exciting...
When you add probability
to gamesmanship,
it takes more than just making
the most favorable moves to win,
which makes it more fun.
All right, which one of you
has the six of hearts, huh...?
Man, without the stupid six of
hearts, I can't get anywhere.
Where is it?!
I'm not talking
about you, you moron!
Ca-- Cat Planet Cuties!
Royal flush, ladies!
Well, looks like Doctor
Durel wins again.
People who don't show emotion
are too good at this.
On Earth there's
a name for it...
"Poker face."
Sure wish I had one!
This is an extremely
fascinating game...
Though I'm still not sure
why you have to take your
clothes off when you lose.
I'm hoping if
we keep playing,
we might eventually
figure that out.
Hey...! You may be
winning right now, Doctor,
but just you wait...
Yep! Before this day is done,
you're gonna strip down
'til you're naked as the day
you were born, I guarantee!
Hah... Do you wanna put
some money on that?
Eventually, they started
to get the hang of it...
more or less.
Meanwhile, back at the
'Cock-a-doodle-doo.'
Eris and her friends were
in a heated battle
over a game
of 'Rhyming Doubt.'
Tricks...
Here's a six.
Jive... A Five.
More...
Here's a four.
Me...
I've got a three.
Blue...
Here's a two.
Maids...
Ace of Spades.
No way.
Say 'I doubt it'
if you don't believe me.
Whatever,
that's fine...
Uh,...
Ring...
'cause I've got a King.
Doubt it!
Gotcha!
So, I'm next, right?
Nine...
I'm still fine.
Eight...!
Sorry I'm late.
Yes... Seven
I'm in heaven.
Six... Time
to pick up sticks.
Let's see...
What now...?
Okay... Five,
and I'm still alive!
Doubt it!
Finally, the six
of hearts shows up.
All those cards and you
don't have a five, huh?
Just shut your mouth!
I tried my best
to keep a straight face.
You realize
every time you lie,
your eyes get all shifty...
Si--.
Six... All treats,
no tricks.
Five, Ichika's
hunger's ali--
Four... She
should eat more.
Three...
And I'm free.
Doubt it!
And, Kio wins!
All right!
Okay, then.
Now, the winner
will decide
which of the prizes
to claim as their own.
Huh...
Let's see here...
Which one do
I want the most?
Mm... truth be told, I sure
would like to watch this DVD.
But...
First I need to recover
this guy right here.
Hold on...! It's not
time to relax yet!
Man... I wanted to watch
that making-of movie.
What is wrong with you?!
All right, moving
onto the next game!
The next
competitive event is-
Next time, I'd like to
shoot something like this.
What is it...?
A sci-fi piece?
Sci-fi's just the backdrop...
It's actually more of a drama.
But there are still
aliens and explosions
and lots of ray gun battles.
This type of thing is
all the rage right now.
Well, it's an
independent film,
so feel free to think
outside of the box
and do what
you like, okay?
The alien life forms don't
necessarily have to look
like humans, either...
They could be sub-beings
who have inverse dextro-rotatory
isomeric amino acids...
Or creatures that
are silicon-based
rather than carbon-based...
Or life forms made of hot,
flaming matter that live
on the surface of the sun...
Just don't forget, there is
always room for imagination!
Yeah, but...
That doesn't sound
realistic to me.
Not realistic?!
Not scientific.
Not scientific?!
Yeah no, not after you've
seen the real thing.
Yeah, right?
Honestly, when
I hear the word 'alien,'
all I can think of
is someone like Eris.
Totally!
I'm afraid this is doing
irreparable damage
to the sci-fi genre.
Hey, everybody!
Uncle Yuichi in the hiz-ouse!
Oh, Mr. iyagi...
It doesn't look like
Kio's gonna grace us
with his presence today.
Ah, that's okay...
As a matter of fact,
I'm not here to see Kio...
I'm here to see
these two, actually.
Wait's over, girls.
All right!
Obviously we need to
mortgage the railroads
and then have
the bank finance it.
Right!
I want that property, put
in the winning bid for it.
Right!
Put up some hotels, and get
the electric company, too.
Right!
File a formal complaint.
To the courts!
Right!
But I don't have
any more money left!
The rest of the players
are bankrupt...
So Antonia wins the day!
Of course.
This game is a microcosm
of capitalist society, right?
She's a pro at this...
I guess being a
millionaire has its perks.
My Lady, since
you're the winner,
now it's time to choose
your favorite prize.
Well, let's see here...
Honestly, I like them all.
I think I'll take back the
figure of the Divine Embodiment,
it's so cute.
Are you absolutely
certain about this...?
It's what you want?
Yes, of course.
I couldn't bear
to part with it.
We're saved again.
All that's left is the DVD
and the cat things...
If we lose this time, someone's
definitely gonna see that film!
Now then.
Time to move onto
the next round...
The next competitive
event is-
It's... Oh my.
You're careless.
Check.
Wait... Hold on!
No, I take it back!
Very well then.
I bravely placed myself
in the way of battle...
I'll accept my
defeat gracefully.
But I can promise
you this much,
I won't surrender
so easily...
Now...
Play me again!
O-kay...
So... Manami,
you're up next...
Right foot red, please!
Ah...!
I can't!
Whatever you do,
don't move!
All right...!
Kio, you're up next...
Right hand blue.
Um... Let's see...
Blue, huh...?
Oh... There's one ri-
Hey!. She said "blue"
not "boobs," jerk!
Please, don't look!
Uh... Sorry.
Okay... Eris
gets a bonus move...
Do whatever you
like on yellow!
'Kay!
What is this...?
Come on, you can't do that,
that's cheating!
But... She said
whatever I like!
Your hand or foot,
okay...?!
Besides, the rest of us
don't even have tails!
Oh yeah...
Well then...
Here!
Hey! Cut that out...!
Eris, what in the hell do you
think you're doing?!
What?. But...
Manami, you said-
Get your boobs
out of his face!
Sorry, I can't help it!
You guys, what the heck's
going on back there?
Fine...! You can use your
tail, just call off the jugs,
okay?!
All right,
that sounds fair!
Yes...! And Eris
wins the game!
Let's see...
Which one to pick?
I think I'll go
with this one!
Eris, are you sure?
Yes!
I couldn't part with these.
They're a treasured
gift from you, Kio.
I'm worn out.
The DVD is the
only prize left.
Yeah, last chance...
One of us has to win this.
All right... Let's move
on to the next game.
The next competitive
event is-
Strip Janken.
Out...! Safe...!
Ready, set, go!
Gah...!
This sucks,
I lost again!
Well, well...
Janken not your
game, Doctor?
How can anyone possibly be
good at a game of chance
that doesn't
require thinking?
You're wrong...
It requires lots
of thinking...
Like what tactic to use when
there are ties, for example.
You know...?
It's strange; all the games
of Earth seem to center
around the players having
to wager their clothes...
I imagine it's
an old tradition
from before
they used money.
All right...!
It's finally time
for naked Doctor!
Yeah!
Out...! Safe!
Ready, set, go!
Well... Did I win,
guys...? Tell me.
Yeah, yeah...
You won, you lucky punk...
Stop bragging.
Come on, do I really have
to take this off, too?
You sure do...!
It's the rules, after all.
This is so humiliating.
Kio's really good at this,
even with a blindfold!
Could be...
Or maybe it's because
of his blindfold
that he's having
so much success.
All right then...
Last round, people...
Let's go!
Yeah!
Out...
Safe...
Ready, set, go!
Good job, Kio,
you won that round, too!
How in the hell did
he beat us again?
Can't believe
I got shut out.
Disgraceful.
Honestly!
I'm such a loser.
The thrill of victory,
the agony of defeat...
Oh well... Time to get
rid of the cat ears!
No fair...
You can't do that!
One article
is one article.
Come on,
that's cheating!
Hey! You gotta complaint,
take it up with the rule book!
Oh no...! You're
getting naked, too!
Ah! Let me go!
Let go of My Lady
right this instant!
What the-...?
Guys, what's going on?
Hey...! Back off...!
Let her go!
Okay, then.
Last prize left;
to the victor
goes the spoils.
Well, here it is, Kio!
You have done well...
So claim what's yours...
I now present you
with this pervy DVD...
Ta-da!
All is lost.
Man, if Kio sees that,
we're toast.
Here.
You guys want
this movie, right?
Uh... Yeah, we do.
You're sure...?
Really?
Well of course.
After all, you two are
the stars, aren't you...?
I kinda figure you'd wanna be
the first people to see it.
Kio.
That's so nice.
Just promise me...
you'll eventually let
me watch it with you.
These crazy earth games
sure are a good time.
It's the possibility
of losing...
That's what makes the
competition so thrilling to us.
Oh, My Lady...
You're growing
up so quickly.
But...
Aoi and Manami's sleazy film
crisis was far from over.
It's time to unleash
the big guns!
Okay!
Take this, you freak!
Roar...!
Roar.
Roar!
R-r-roar!
The rockets,
they don't work...!
What is that thing?!
No choice, we have
to use our last resort!
Roar...!
You're goin' down!
Wow...
I'd say they turned
out pretty cute, huh?!
You could compliment our
amazing vocal performances,
you jerk!
You girls were awesome...
Hey... Y'know...
You two should really consider
getting into voice-over.
We rock!
In that case, do you think you
could get us some more work
with the sci-fi
visionary who made this?
Yeah, do you think this might
have a chance of getting
into some film festivals?!
Ooh...! I hope so!
What is the sci-fi
world coming to?!
I'm bouncing!
Yeah, me too...!
I'm bouncing everywhere!
Hey! I--
I'm bouncing, too...!
Look! I am!