Eris of Catia in...
"Be Scratched!"
Life for young
newlyweds can be tough,
but try being
married to an alien!
With a nosy neighbor,
a pushy mother,
and a husband played
by two different actors,
Eris has her hands full.
But a twitch of her nose
can wish her problems away!
Shojo manga...
Huh.
Wait, what time...?
Oh, no...!
I'm gonna be late.
Summer vacation
is over...
And, as of today...
The second semester begins.
Another sunny day!
Now, then.
Before we get started...
I'd like to introduce
some new transfer students.
Come on in!
Wow!
She has a tail!
This is Eris,
an extra-terrestrial
who will study with us.
Please make her
feel welcome, class.
I still don't
know much about Earth,
but I can't wait to learn...
And I'm very pleased
to make your acquaintance.
Eris, um...
Why are you...?
Ah. Gotta
love shore duty.
There's just
nothing better...
It's so relaxing...
Yep, this is the life.
So, anyway, Captain...
what's with this whole
Eris going to school thing?
Oh, yeah, that...
Well, the poor thing had her
mating season cut short,
so I approved it.
I figured as much...
She's acting unusually
serious about it, though...
She seemed to accept
it at face value
that she's "just there to survey
Earth education systems."
She is kind of bumble-headed
when it comes to that subject.
There's always so
much stuff going on...
It's impossible for her
and Kio to find some time
to be alone together.
Are you referring
to Aoi and Manami?
Oh, please.
If only it were just
the two of them.
Antonia...
Lirimonie...
Norfederas Papanorgas...
Arecroteles
Cnorses Morfenoss.
Since I am not yet accustomed
to this country...
I'll kindly ask you
all for your regards.
Antonia...
What the...?
Eris, did she
follow you here?
Oh, come on...
A world-class millionaire like
her coming to our school...?
This can't
be safe... No way.
Look.
From the American
Justice Department.
NIJ dash zero one zero
eight, point zero one...
This is level three
bulletproof glass.
She's pulled some strings.
Yeah, and that's not all...
Bodyguards, too.
Now say hello to Antonia's
special friends, Maya and Sara.
My Lady...
Can you explain why
we currently have bread
hanging out of our mouths?
This is a custom for transfer
students in this country.
Oh, I see...
You are indeed
most knowledgeable.
If I may inquire,
where did you hear
of this particular
tradition, My Lady?
I first learned of it
when I read a book labeled,
'Shojo Manga."
She's totally right.
Kio, is something
the matter?
Oh... Uh...
It's just everyone's
staring at me...
I'm not used to it.
It's bothering you...
We can't have that, can we?
What say you,
Miss Eris?
Better?
Uh... Sure!
Yo! Kio!
Hey, are you-
No, it's all right...!
Don't shoot;
they're in my video club!
It looks like the rumors
about you are true...
You do live a rough and
tumble life, don't you?
I'm real sorry about that.
So what's the story...?
Are you gonna
be able to come to camp?
What is this camp
you're talking about?
Oh, it's something the
club does every semester.
It's cool...!
And you're welcome to come.
Thank you...!
That sounds fun!
What? Great...!
All you have to do now
is fill out this form.
We'll take some
of those, please.
If Miss Eris joins the club,
then the Lady's joining it, too.
Hey...!
Four-Eyes!
We want some forms, too!
But... Manami!
We just hit the
jackpot here...!
Our girl to guy ratio
just shot through the roof!
Explain to me why we
just joined their club?
Oh, come on,
get with it, Aoi...!
You don't seriously
want to leave
that cat-in-heat alone
with Kio, do you?
Oh, no, what if she
shares a tent with Kakazu?
Whoa...! This bad boy
has some pick-me up...
Talk about
a need for speed!
I take it you like it?
That's not all
I like, honey...
Oh, yeah!
Good morning,
everybody!
Oh, yeah, good
morning, Kakazu.
Hey, what's wrong?
I thought we were
going by bus.
I'll give her this much:
the girl does live in style.
Attention all squadrons...
Maintain current
positions and stay alert.
We're now assigning cars!
All units, follow your
leader's instructions...
There are five
people per vehicle.
Are you sure we
should do this?
Administration said
suit ourselves.
Someone please tell me why
people like this only show up
when I'm in charge?
What's the big deal...?
Our food and travel is free,
plus we got hot maids
taking care of us.
Try and divide
yourselves up equally...
And I'm sorry.
One of you poor things...
is gonna have to
ride with her.
Hittin' the road!
With a little kitty!
Move out!
We're so glad
you joined...
Having a few more girls around
will be nice for a change.
Before you two, Arisa and
I were the only girls...
It'll be nice to see things
a little bit more evened out.
Well... For me and Aoi,
it's just our job.
But it must be
pretty difficult.
Oh, come on...
You're both
after him, right?
You can try to play dumb,
but we can tell...
You two are both in love
with Kio, aren't you?
That... That isn't even
close to the truth...
Kio and I are friends and that's
all we're ever gonna be...
And besides, Aoi's the one
who's in love with him, not me!
What...?!
Manami!
Yep, totally called it.
No...! That's so not true,
I swear...! You're wrong...!
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
Uh... Okay,
take it easy.
Come on... Are you sure you
don't like him, Aoi...?
People have been saying
they see you guys
hanging out alone a lot.
And he is quite the catch...
Seems like he's especially
popular with the girls, lately.
Huh?! But he's nerdy,
and wears glasses,
and he's so
wishy- washy...!
And all he ever
wants for dinner
are those stupid
cup noodles.
Well, he may be a nerd...
But he's an individual,
and that's rare.
He's sweet, and kind,
and decent...
Sure he's not perfect,
but he has got the potential
to grow up into
a really great man.
Having an alien around
must make you nervous...
I wouldn't want to have
to compete with her.
I know, right?
A sexy alien cat girl...?
That's basically like
winning the nerd lottery.
Kio really
does have it made!
Intelligent cheela living
in a neutron star...!
Oh, joy...!
Those are
what I call aliens!
She's fallen asleep.
She was so excited
about coming with you.
I don't think My Lady
slept a wink all night.
She is quite taken
with you, Miss Eris.
She's really been looking
forward to this, then?
Oh, yes...
It's been a long time since
I've seen her this happy...
For that matter,
Sara, too.
My precious kitty!
Are you too cold
out here?!
Oh, that's wonderful!
I love you so much!
So much, in fact,
that Sara didn't realize
she took the
wrong highway.
Attention all units,
attention all units,...
This is the tenth incident.
Computer, television,
cell phone,
and a DVD player.
Why, the nerve of
those criminals!
Everything they took
was brand spanking new!
Could it be a ring
of kid thieves?
You'd have
to be a kindergartner
or smaller
to get in there...
And it's weird they
didn't touch the money.
All they were after
was electronic stuff.
If you ask me, it was imps
or gremlins that did this!
I haven't heard that
one in a good while.
Should we nail voodoo dolls
to a tree to fend them off?
Bombshells From the Sky.
So pretty!
Well, I suppose we should
pitch the tents...?
We'll need a good place
to change into our swimsuits!
Swimsuits?!
Nobody said anything
about swimsuits!
Yeah, this is video club...
Not swim camp!
Oh, we still plan
to shoot some video...
But that doesn't mean
we can't fun while--
Why the hell'd you fail
to mention this until now!
Manami, please stop!
You're choking me...?!
I can't breathe!
Seriously, I'm sorry!
Okay!
How dumb are you...?
Don't you know girls have to
plan for these types of outings?
I said sorry.
Jeez, why are you always
so violent with me?
What am I gonna wear?
Don't ask me.
I didn't bring a suit, either.
No need to worry.
Arrangements have been
made for both of you.
If I could be in that
tent right now...
I swear... I could die
with no regrets.
You'd be dead long
before you got that far.
Those sexy maids would shoot
you without thinking twice.
I like that one!
That one's nice, too!
This is the one!
Um, I think, no.
Miss Eris...
See this one?
It's so cute...!
I like it much better
than the others!
Since we're here,
I might as well try it on.
Amazing...
These are designer
brands, aren't they?
Antonia...
Is it okay if we
try some on, too?
Uh... Well...
It's fine, as long as
Miss Eris doesn't need it...
She gets what
she wants first!
You mean it?!
Thank you so much,
you're the best!
This one is okay...
But it might be a
little too subdued.
It's cute, but not
really your style.
Jackpot!
This is just the kinda
thing you're looking for!
You want me to wear
this...? No way.
Oh, relax...
Sure, it's a bit risqué,
but I've seen you wear
much, much worse.
No, please!
Not again!
Sorry to keep
you waiting.
Hey, Kio!
What do you think
of my swimsuit?
Uh... Well, I...
It looks very nice.
What are you
blushing for, huh?
Listen, you've gotta
wear something sexier,
or you're gonna lose
him to the cat girl!
I'm sorry...
But this swimsuit is all
that I'm comfortable with.
Miss Eris,
you look great...!
Like flowers springing
up on the beach!
Ta-da!
Okay, be honest:
How do we look?
Whoa...
Wasn't expecting that.
Was I right, or
was I right...?
I told you these
suits were great!
Aiko...! You put your
suit on backwards!
Eris's tail hole, it's-
Wait, then that means ...
I don't wanna know
what that's for.
You're really
good at this.
Better than a pro.
Only 'cause you're
such a good teacher...
Thanks, Kakazu.
Well, well!
They're getting
on just fine.
I just hope...
It isn't too late.
Oh, this is so delicious!
The flavors of the
high-quality meats
brought out by simple
seasonings are amazing!
Here, Miss Eris...
Say... ah!
Ah!
This meat is
so incredible...!
It's the best thing
I've ever eaten!
Uh, ma'am...? I think
there's enough for everyone.
Don't care.
This is spectacular!
Here you go, Kakazu.
Thanks, Aoi,
that's nice of you.
Oh, please, I should
be thanking you...
You really did teach
me a lot today.
Ah... no biggie...
Oh...!
Almost forgot.
What?
Nothing important,...
but I do have a favor
I wanna ask of you.
You mind?
Uh...
A favor, huh...?
Is it something you have
to ask me right here and now?
What...? Not really,
I guess it can wait.
In that case...
You mind if we take a walk?
The moon's pretty, huh?
Sure is.
I'm sorry, Aoi.
But this can't wait.
Look, here's the thing.
I've been thinking about
this for a good while...
But I don't think I can keep
it to myself any longer.
It's you...
You're the only one.
Kakazu, you-
Point is...
And this is kind of
embarrassing, but--
Go on.
I want you.
I want you to teach
me how to fight!
Huh?
The project is complete.
Finally...
A new model of Unya,
one closer to an
actual Assistroid.
Unatan!
The Lady is waiting
for this... Hurry!
Right...!
Prepare start-up tests!
Hey...
Where's Aoi?
Oh, uh...
She said she wanted to
be alone for a bit...
Wonder what's going on?
Oh, Kio... What did
you say to her.
I'm so dumb...
Why would he like me,
I'm a cold-blooded killer.
It's too late for me.
There's no way.
Better hurry and eat
or it'll all be gone...
Here, these are for you.
Hey...
Where'd Kio go?
Uh... Wait!
Don't you want some?
No thanks.
But they're delicious.
You wanna know something?
I hate you!
All of you...
With your curves in
all the right places.
Your stupid, alien cat
ears and furry tail.
And you always being so cute
and nice to everybody
all the time...!
And...
Kakazu just
freakin' eats it up.
Aoi, I'm sorry.
You're horrible...
You are...
Because I was in love with
him before you ever got here!
You ruined everything.
And you don't even
have a clue...
Since you showed up,
things have been terrible...!
Fine, so I don't know much
about TV or manga...
And I can't cook...!
I don't have friends...
I can't compete
with you at all!
I understand, Aoi...
Kio means more to you
than anything else.
Yes, he does!
I could get
through any mission
because I knew Kakazu
would be there...!
And I gave it up.
I threw away my
whole career...
I sacrificed
everything for him...!
Which is...
why I...
Aww...
We're the same,
you and I.
Kio always makes
me feel at ease.
I can... relax,
I guess would be the word.
When I'm with him,
it's like I'm in my
favorite ray of sunlight.
Dammit, you're right!
We are alike!
This is so good!
The meat's so tender,
it melts in your mouth!
Wow!
What is this,
Grade A...?!
It's delicious...!
This stuff has gotta
be real expensive, right?
Yeah, uh...
Who might you be, exactly?
Hello. It's a pleasure
to meet you, my name is Ichika!
Ichika?
Sure is nice being young...
This fella must
be quite special
to be this
infatuated over.
That's none
of your business.
Oh, so...?
Should I not tell
you he needs help?
Kio, no!
Hang back just a sec.
Enemy attack!
Mountainside, two o'clock!
All units,
defensive positions...!
Sara, move out!
Roger!
An old tire?!
That's my camera!
Yun-Fat...!
After them!
Hey, wait!
Guys!
Kio, look...!
Over there!
What do you think you're
doing to my little kitties?!
Is everyone all right?
Yeah, we're all just fine.
Thanks, you saved our butts.
How'd you do that?
It's all thanks to these
things I got from Ichika.
Who's Ichika?
Love those Accel
Form cards.
They work like a
charm every time.
What is this thing...?
A homemade catapult?
Pretty crafty design.
They made a winch using
suspension springs
and a starter from
a car or truck.
I swear we've seen these
Assistroids before...
They look like the ones that
got aboard Antonia's ship.
But the ship sunk; didn't
they go down with it?
They must have traveled
here along the sea floor...
Unlike our Assistroids,
they don't have the ability
to self- regenerate...
So it looks like they're
using Earth electronics
for repairs.
That explains why they were
trying to steal the cameras.
Crafty sons-of-bitches.
Wow... Looks like
there's someone out there
who doesn't leave
their friends behind.
Aoi,...
I wanted to...
What's up...?
Is something wrong?
I meant what I asked you...
Teach me to fight.
I need-- because of
things like last night--
I need to be able
to protect you guys.
"They were all brilliant,
admirable and beyond heroic...
Though inorganic, worthy
of praise they are...
See that thou know this
and rebuke them not"...
Ichika.
What the hell is this?
Aoi and Manami play cat
and mouse in the woods,
but things become
dog-eat-dog
when Janes sends a
sniper after them.
Will the girls defeat the
snipers or become dog meat...?
Next time...
"We Had a Duel!"
I'm coming
to drop in on you!