Good morning, Eris.
Your mission, should
you choose to accept it,
is to investigate
planet Earth with the aid
of your Catia: Impossible force.
This tape will self-destruct
in five seconds.
Good luck, Eris.
Oh, Kio!
It's so wonderful to
wake up next to you!
Come on...!
This isn't right!
I'm sorry, Kio...
I'm deep into mating season
right now, I can't help it.
What am I gonna
do with you, huh...?
Hey, um, where do
you think we are?
I don't know, but it
looks pretty plush.
You like the
accommodations, then?
Excuse me, where
are we right now?
You are in the private room
of the Divine Embodiment,
aboard The Androala,
headquarters of the
Underside of the Kitten's Paw.
Is that so...?
And what exactly is this whole
'Divine Embodiment' thing?
Oh... But don't
you know...?
You're the
Divine Embodiment.
Huh? What?!
I'm sorry,
but you can't do this...
I apologize,
but unfortunately,
it is against regulations
for me to pose as a deity,
or be given any special
attention by a religious order.
Long have we prayed that a
being with genuine kitty-ears
and a tail would manifest
itself to us in our world...
Our leader predicted
you would come...
And now you're
here with us...
The prophecy is coming
true before our eyes
and for this
we are thankful.
There's no doubt:
You're the Divine Embodiment.
Well, in that case,
I have an order for you...
Release my friend and me
from this place at once!
Sorry, but I can't do that...
My orders come direct
from the Founder.
That doesn't make sense.
However, I do have
something to offer you.
So, do you like?
Uh... Yeah!
Hey, Kio, how 'bout
you and I stay here
just a little
bit longer, huh?
Oh... Sure!
The Divine Embodiment
has awakened.
Good...
Treat her with
the utmost respect.
Yes, as you wish.
What do you think...?
It's such a perfect replica...
I can get as close
as I want to,
and the Divine Embodiment won't
suspect a thing, will she?
My lady.
It's wonderful.
The kitty cult?
The Underside of
the Kitten's Paw?
Obviously, I've heard
of religious sects
that worshipped cats
in Ancient Egypt...
But, for them to worship
the ears and tails...
Contact Yokota.
Tell them I said to ready
the 'Peanut Vendor.'
Right!
It's about time these kitties
and their little feline wannabes
took a permanent cat nap.
No, no, no...!
The PBR is one thing,
but a powerboat is completely
out of the question.
A boat with no speed
just won't cut it...
A powerboat...
And we're gonna need
the fastest one you have
to get this job done.
Look, I'm a weapons dealer...
And a powerboat isn't a
weapon, you understand me?
Well... Word on the street is,
you have a fully-tuned,
converted powerboat
that was used
by the Miami
Police Department.
People can't keep
secrets, can they...?
I'm sorry, but the
boat's already booked.
Booked...?
But by who?
If you wanna make
a bid on it,
then you'll have to deal
with the guy, directly...
Ah... speak
of the devil.
Well, well, well, look
what the cat dragged in.
Uncle Yuichi?!
Wait a second, you mean
you have the powerboat?
Well, I sorta do...
A movie director friend of
mine said he needed one...
Check it.
I brokered the deal.
It's got guns on it, too?
Bad ass, huh...?
Of course, those are
just props for the flick.
The boat... Where
isit now, is it nearby?
Chichijima.
But the film's
shooting in Ogasawara.
I'm so full...
Ah...
So delicious!
Wow...
I don't think I've ever eaten
this much food before, have you?
Hey, Kio.
Now that we've eaten
this amazing meal,...
I'd say it's about
time we left.
Um, just how are we
supposed to do that?
You see this outfit?
It's a scaled-down
power suit...
I can break through a
bulkhead like this easily.
Let's call
the Assistroids.
They'll help us escape.
Okay then...
Now!
Eee-yow!
It hurts! Oh, it
hurts so bad, Kio!
Yeah, it sure
looked like it did.
I don't know
what happened...
It didn't work.
Normally, I could do
it with one punch.
Oh, no!
What's the matter?
It says, 'strength enhancement
function restricted
due to mating season.'
This is bad...
My power suit won't work
'cause I'm in mating season.
What do you mean?
When I'm in heat, I can't
make rational decisions,
so my suit's functions
are restricted
to protect both
myself and others.
Wait, what?
Yes...!
Now I can't even call
Luros or my Assistroids!
There's no reason
for you to worry.
We have our own research
and development team...
So, we've built you
something that's identical
to the Assistroids...
See for yourself.
What the...?
His name is Unya.
Please allow him to
serve at your side.
Is this just a guy
in a suit?
Oh, no...
He's a robot.
There is nobody
inside of it.
Listen up,
here's the deal...
The Androala plans
to rendezvous
with an escort fleet standing
in a nearby sector...
We've got to rescue
them before then.
Got it.
Our first order of business
is secretly replacing
the prop guns on the
powerboat with real ones.
Look, I like the plan...
But, do you think he's
gonna accept our terms
for borrowing it?
Of course not...
Once we're out at sea,
he can't stop us.
I really hate doing
this to Uncle Yuichi...
But, unfortunately, I don't
think we have a choice here.
You're right, I guess we
gotta do what we gotta do.
Stand by, we're almost
at the drop point.
Good luck!
Whoa...
It's so amazing!
You would never guess we
were on a boat, would you?
Wait, whaddaya mean,
'everything?'...
Oh...
Hey, where are
you taking me?
Is that a
merry-go-round?
Wow...
I see, this must be a primitive
horse-riding simulator, right?
Such elaborate
decorations...
I wonder if it
belonged to royalty.
And look at all these lights,
so beautiful and bright...
It's just so wonderful!
She really is
having a good time.
Oh, cool...
We'll have to play
each other on this!
Hey, wait...
Are all of these
single players?
What about the
guy in the suit?
Doesn't he ever wanna
play with someone?
There's no one
inside the suit...?
It's a robot made to serve
the Divine Embodiment...
It's just gears and circuits
and nothing else, got it?
Uh... Right...
But, these games are
all single player,
doesn't your Founder ever get
bored just playing by herself?
In a game, there is a
winner and a loser...
And it would be extremely
disrespectful for us
to beat our own Founder...
Even more so to go easy on
her so she can always win.
Tell me: What kinda
person is your Founder?
She has obtained
everything.
Everything, huh?
After her grandfather
passed away,
she inherited
his wealth...
Expanding her ever-increasing
estate is her only job,
and one she takes
very seriously...
But, she's very young...
Her future is long...
The internal flames
of her passion
have only just started
burning brightly...
You see... ever since she
discovered kitty-ears,
she found her first love,
and with it, her purpose.
I'm just about
finished up.
Yeah, same here...
I didn't think
swapping dummies
for the real thing would
be this easy, did you?
We've gotta be ready.
The Androala should be
passing by here pretty soon...
And I think we should set
off before the guy
who rented this shows up.
Hey, Aoi?
What is it?
I'm dying to know, what
do you like about Kio?
Uh... Where'd
that come from?
Come on...
Spill the beans.
I guess I just like him...
He's kind and cheerful and
the most decent person I know...
He is the complete
opposite of me...
Hey... Can I
ask you something?
Yes?
I want you to tell
me the truth,
are you positive you don't
have any feelings for Kakazu?
Oh, that is
such a laugh...
Yeah, right...!
There's nothing
to like about him.
Uh... Oh,
it's nothing.
Right.
A visitor?
Hey, stop!
Quit it!
Let go of me, creep!
You sure do have your
character down pat...
I should've known Yuichi
would find the right girls.
Hey...
Wait a sec...
That means you're-
Oh, yes...
I'm Kawasaki,
the famous director...
And this is my
powerboat, girls!
Oh, no...!
We're too late!
Kawasaki,
the director...?
Oh, wow!
Hold on,
you know this guy?
Mr. awasaki is a
cult film director
known for making
B- grade action flicks
that feature skimpy plots,
and actresses in even
skimpier bikinis.
Now, let's hurry up
and get dressed, you two.
Get dressed,
but-No way!
Well, I hope you're
not having second thoughts
about doing my film...
Our morning location
shoot is coming up soon!
Cat Planet Cuties!
This shot will be from
directly below them...
We want to highlight
their assets!
What do we do, Aoi?
Well...
The show must go on.
Let's get a move
on, girls...!
The sun's up,
no time to waste!
Ah, geez!
Oh, my!
You look wonderful...!
Beautiful, ladies... This scene
is going to be piping hot,...
Manami.
Let's go.
Do it, boys!
Hey, you two!
We're not doing
that part yet!
Come back!
Roll those
cameras now...!
This is great...
Just keep shooting, boys!
You're worn out from
playing, aren't you?
Looks like someone
had a lot of fun.
How nice... It's been
a really long time
since I've seen
her so peaceful...
As hard as she works,
she deserves it.
Wait, I thought
it was a robot.
Status report!
We've got a problem.
There is a small watercraft
approaching our ship
at a dangerously
high speed.
There it is.
Yeah, that's the stuff!
Nice shot!
This footage
is solid gold!
What's the situation?
The boat just entered
our visual field...
But, Miss Maya, don't you
think this is a bit much
for just one boat?
No, not with Charmed
Momiji on board.
No way... After her fall
off the train in Tokyo,
I thought she'd
be too injured.
If she were just
a human, maybe...
But I guess she
really is charmed.
Stop her!
Take fire
control, Manami!
You got it!
Fire!
Go! Now!
Okay!
It can't be...!
Our targeting is off!
They've cracked it...
Someone has hacked into our
fire control system
and shut everything down!
Well?
Bad news, looks like
it was a direct hit!
Radar...
Tell me what you see?!
I didn't pick up anything!
The hell happened
to the missiles?
They're our latest
secret weapon...
They're absolutely
classified;
so don't mention
them to anyone...
Move in and
finish them off.
Prepare for battle!
It's so sad...
Seems like having
everything in the world
is not too different
from having nothing at all.
The bullets inside
Yun-Fat's toy guns...
are quasi-antimatter...
They're dangerous weapons
capable of obliterating
any non-living matter by
means of quasi-annihilation.
Here we go!
I'll try and create
a diversion...
Go after Eris and Kakazu.
Don't worry, I'll rescue them
if it's the last thing I do!
Ma'am, there's a
breach in the hull...!
We're being flooded...!
Location 'C Seventy-Six'
and 'C Seventy-Seven!'
That doesn't make sense,
that's not where
the missiles hit.
There's a boarding
craft inside the ship!
Intruders...!
Take defensive positions!
I'm going down there.
This suit
is so awesome!
Good job, Kio.
You were right, it doesn't
detect that I'm in heat,
so when I put it on,
the functionality
restrictions are lifted.
Perfect... Do us both a favor
and contact the Assistroids.
Right.
Move.
This way!
Time for you to pay
your boarding fee!
Executive Officer Sara
is a sucker for cats
and all things cute...
As a result, she left a career
as an up and coming SAS elite,
and ended up a cult member
on a boat full of lunatics.
How cute!
That should shut down the
power and buy us some time.
She looks just...
... like me.
Japan's filled
with monkeys!
And, from the looks of things,
you do 'monkey see,
monkey do' pretty damn well!
Why, you...!
I can't move.
Aw, that's
really too bad.
Didn't you know?
Things built with canine
technology are designed
so they can't
attack dogs.
This is goodbye,
Charmed Momiji.
Apport.
You really thought
it would work
as long as you didn't
directly attack me?
Wishful thinking.
No, not exactly.
What the...?!
My suit has the same
drawbacks as yours...
The hard-soft powered
suit is flexible armor...
But with the controls shut down,
it's a human shaped coffin.
You think
you can beat me?!
Doggie ears?
Time to die!
War Dog, it's Pack
Leader, come in...
Destroy my current
position in thirty seconds.
Deploy the rockets.
All hands,
abandon ship...
abandon ship!
The ship is lost, my lady.
We must go.
So, we're sinking?
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Manami!
Kio...!
Thank goodness!
Hey, what's
with the outfit?
Um, what's
with your outfit?
I don't think you're
in a position to judge.
Manami...
I like it!
You look like a sexy
bunny-eared rabbit alien.
Look, I'll explain later...!
Hurry up, we gotta go!
There they are...
This is your fault!
Says you,
the kidnapper!
Hand over the
Divine Embodiment!
Lady, there's no way in
hell we're gonna do that!
There's no time...
Turn her over or I'll shoot!
That's not gonna happen!
Just stop it...!
The ship is sinking, there's
no time to be doing this!
Stay out of it...!
You may be her tagalong,
but you'll get no mercy!
It doesn't matter how badly you
want something you can't have,
it doesn't give you
the right to take it!
You're wrong; the lady can
have anything she wants to!
Yeah...? Then why doesn't
she have any friends?
She has loyal servants
waiting on her, hand and foot.
Who cares...?!
A friend is someone
you laugh and cry with,
someone you get mad
at and fight with,
but you always make up in
the end, no matter what...!
People who follow you and submit
to your orders aren't friends!
You know nothing of us!
After all...
what good is a video game
if there's nobody
to play it with you?
Bastard!
Please...
Stop... Maya.
Yes, but...
My lady...
The things we've done to
Lady Eris and Mister Kakazu
are not right...
So, I ask for your
forgiveness...
Please.
But, my lady...
Maya and I are abandoning
ship in a lifeboat...
Please come with us.
Thank you very much, that's
such a nice offer, Unya.
Uh... I'm sorry,
but I think you've mistaken
me for somebody else.
Well, all the same, thanks.
Sure.
Hold on... I can't
get a signal on Aoi!
She's unconscious
in the engine room?!
How do you know that?
Because, the Assistroids
have the ability
to monitor the vital
signs of their masters!
Oh, no...!
What are we gonna do?!
The engine room's
too far...
There's no time
to rescue her.
The ship is going down!
Oh, this is
just wonderful!
Keep those cameras
rolling, people!
Next time.
I'll make you pay for this.
Aoi...!
Aoi!
Where are you?!
Aoi...!
Kakazu...
He's saving me.
Oh, wow.
This is a dream...
It must be.
I love you...
Kakazu.
Cooking can be a drag...
But, virtual Kio's
are lots of fun...
Of course, nothing
ruins a video shoot
quite like a good
old-fashioned cat in heat!
Next time...
"I've Practiced!"
I'm coming
to drop in on you!