It's "Manami and Aoi!"
Two tough detectives
kicking butt
and taking names
in the urban jungle!
Thugs, pimps,
and pushers beware!
If you see their bad ass
Gran Torino pulling up,
these two hellcats are
coming to knock you down!
And with the aid of streetwise,
jive-talking informant,
Kio "Huggy Boy" Kakazu,
these foxy mamas are
cleaning up the ghetto,
one crook at a time!
Starring Brittney Karbowski
as Manami Kinjyou...
and Monica Rial,
as Aoi Futaba...
Featuring Aaron Dismuke
as as Huggy Boy...
and Tia Ballard
as Captain Eris.
The Saitama Super Arena...
A premier event center
that can accommodate
up to thirty- seven
thousand people......
a location currently
packed to the rafters
with members
of a top-secret society
who've gathered for
an important meeting.
So sorry about the typos.
It should read, "The Founder
was supposed to be here, too,
but some things came up,
and she couldn't make it."...
Well, not in person, anyway.
However, she is able to join
us via satellite uplink...
I proudly present to you...
Our Founder.
It's been too long,
my brothers and sisters!
As you all know...
The Underside of the Kitten's
Paw was blessed recently
by the appearance of Miss Eris,
who we worship as
the Divine Embodiment...
However...
Eris has just given us
two new commandments
that we are to follow...
And they will
both be difficult.
First, she has selflessly
asked that we not worship her...
Second, we've viewed
cat's ears and tails
as the pinnacle
of perfection...
But Miss Eris says we are all
perfect in our own way,
so we will do
this no more!
Brothers and sisters, she has
proclaimed that as of today,
we accept ourselves
for who and what we are!
Furthermore...
regarding our faith...
she says in order to
follow in her footsteps,
we have no need for
real ears and tails...
All we have to do
is act as she does...
And that's by being kind
to everybody we meet.
Now to tell you more
about the new path
we're going to follow...
Miss Eris?
Uh...
Hi, um...
I hope you're all well...
My name...
is Eris.
It's like Antonia said:...
Be nice to people and be
accepting of yourselves.
Okay, I hope that was
good enough for you.
It was more than good;
it was perfect!
By doing that, the Underside
of the Kitten's Paw
will become a secular order...
Instead of a religion
that worships you,
it'll be more
like a fan club.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah, 'cause those "meows"
they were chanting sounded
a lot more like
"amens" to me.
This is a quasi-antimatter
round that was supplied to us
by the Catians.
Unlike standard ammunition
made on Earth, this thing
is designed to eliminate
only non-living matter.
Like the hammers Eris
and the Assitroids used
to destroy those tanks?
Right. It allows you
to disarm an opponent
without hurting them...
You can shoot at
them without worry.
Speaking of shooting...
Are you ready?
Alright...
You wanna aim with both
of your eyes open...
If you close one, you
lose depth perception,
which affects accuracy.
Well that's a relief.
They're getting along.
Oh, you're talking about
spiritron force, right?
Yup. That's what
powers the cards
and what gave
Aoi the ability
to beat those Dogishuan
Assistroids at the beach.
So even one of these Accel
Form cards, as you call them,
can give you
incredible powers, huh?
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say these were "magic."
Well, any sufficiently
advanced technology
is indistinguishable
from magic...
Both concepts are
universal principles...
So at their root,
they're the same.
Tea and cookies?
Great.
I thought you were
off training today.
Well, I was...
But I'm letting Aoi
learn a few things.
Hang on...
I thought Aoi was supposed to
be the one doing the teaching.
Let's just say there's some ways
she could learn to fight, too.
I still don't
understand it.
Maybe I shouldn't
be so dogmatic
about the situation
here, Matrey...
The cats and the humans
might have made dog food
out of our soldiers...
But I have to remember
those dogs were thought
to be casualties from
the The Androala's sinking.
Instead, they marched forth,
determined to carry out
their mission on their own.
Plus, we did manage
to retrieve enemy data.
Back to the primary
matter at hand...
We have to keep the cats
from getting cozy on the laps
of this planet's leaders...
Forcing the Earth monkeys
to shoo the Catians off
would also work.
We need to show
both of them
that continuing their
little relationship
is not in their
best interest...
Nor does it make
a lick of sense...
Like this.
I still don't understand
the doggone thing.
Stop, I give!
I hope I didn't
hurt you too much.
No... But fighting's not
as easy to pick up as I thought.
Oh, you'll get
the hang of it.
The key, of course,
is to practice every day.
How 'bout we take
a quick break?
I'm exhausted.
Okay, so tell me,
what made you wanna learn
to fight all of a sudden?
You girls all know how...
But I'm a guy and
I'm totally worthless...
And with all the weird stuff
that's been happening...
I need to know that
I can help defend you
if thing's ever
get to that point.
So chivalry's not dead.
And besides...
All you girls have special
skills and abilities
that I really envy.
You envy...? Us?
Well, Eris has
traveled thru space.
Now she's an
ambassador to Earth...
Manami was training
to be a CIA agent,
and now she's a
security guard...
And as for you, Aoi...
You worked as a secret agent
for a long time, didn't you?
You've all had these
awesome jobs already...
You clearly knew what you
wanted to do with your lives...
But me?
I don't, and I've got
no special skills.
Well, as strange as
this might sound...
There are things
about you that I envy.
Huh?
I envy your normal life.
Being special is why
my family abandoned me.
Hey...
I just noticed,
Manami isn't here.
Guess she must've run off...
And she was the one who
suggested we train today...
Cool...
Crisp...
Refreshing...
And made with the
same pure spring water
it has been
for centuries...
Hey, Eris.
There's dessert in the
kitchen if you want some.
What are
you doing here...
Manami?
Oh, you know...
Taking a little break.
Taking a break from what,
because you didn't
train with us at all.
Yeah...
I left 'cause I didn't
wanna get in the way
of Kio's training, see...?
And you two
looked so focused...
Manami...
Besides, I've
trained enough...
I don't really need it.
What the hell?!
You left yourself wide open...
If I'd been shooting real
bullets from this gun,
you'd be dead right now.
No way.
I would have dodged it.
Oh, then why
didn't you try?
Duh, 'cause
I didn't need to...
I could tell you weren't
aiming directly at me.
Too bad you can't
shoot a revolver
if I grab the
cylinder like this.
Apport.
No fair!
I liked that bra!
Nothing's unfair when you're
in an actual gun fight.
My glasses.
Alright...
Let's finish this.
Agreed. But how
about we up the stakes?
I say whoever loses
has to do one thing
the winner
commands them to.
Sounds like a plan.
Just a good fair fight.
Leave all the personal
crap at the door.
Hey, what's
going on in here?
Stop looking at
my boob, you perv!
It's hard not to with
it hanging out like that!
We'll show 'em there's
more than one way
to skin a cat
and their friends.
Cat Planet Cuties.
War game?
Yes. It's an exercise that
replicates combat conditions.
It sounds to me like what
you're having is a duel.
No, no.
It's just practice.
'Sides, it'll be good to get
some training out in nature.
That's the area with
the best vantage point.
I'm sure Aoi's already
lying in wait on that hill
for me to pass by...
So I'm gonna have
to outmaneuver her
and go in from behind.
I'm sure Manami thinks I'm
on that hill, lying in wait.
So she'll try to sneak up
on me from behind...
The question is, which way
will she be coming from?
The river's to the south,
making an attack from
the north most likely.
So that's where I'll aim.
Well, this terrain
certainly takes me back.
It reminds me of all those
survival training sessions
I used to have with Dad.
I'd say that gives me the
upper hand in this fight.
I've gotta win this game.
I need to show Manami the
importance of training...
Because if she keeps blowing
it off like she has been...
It's gonna get her killed.
I can't believe Aoi...
She has no idea what
I'm trying to do here.
Manami means well,
but she doesn't
understand my situation.
Doesn't she realize
my whole point
has been getting her and
Kio alone together...?
Man, for an elite,
former assassin,
she can be
dense sometimes.
I've worked as a
professional killer...
I've carried out countless
black ops missions...
That's the reason why
someone as sweet as Kakazu
shouldn't get
involved with me,
somebody with
such a dark past.
And anyways...
It's too late for me.
I let my chance
with Kio slip away.
Rain?
Should I move now,
while I won't be detected?
Or, should I...
Well...
I guess I'm stuck then.
I waited too long...
Didn't I?
I wonder why I didn't
realize it sooner...?
The fact that...
I love Kio...
Whoa... It's really
coming down out there.
Poor girls'll be shivering
when they get home.
Not for long!
Sadakichi, will you give
me a hand in the kitchen?
An Okinawa rail...?!
It must be looking for
a new watering hole.
Aw, jeez...! Totally just
gave away my position...
But then again, so did Aoi!
She dodged it...!
You're fast, Manami!
Damn!
Crap! C'mon...!
I'll blast ya
'til your naked!
Guess it's a draw.
Hardly, since
you're out of ammo.
Nice bluff, though.
I'm impressed
you knew that...
How'd you
know I was empty?
You dropped your
last full clip.
Yeah, thanks to our
endangered friend.
Tough break...!
Now seeing
as you've lost this...
Time to pay up and
do something I say.
Those were the agreed terms.
So get it over with.
Let's see...
I know; when we get back, you
have to give Kio a big ol' kiss!
Did... you say "kiss?"
Oh, yeah...
A nice,
tender smacker.
I can't...!
Please...!
Don't make me!
I don't know. Sounds like you're
trying to welch on our deal.
I know...
But that's just-...
Alright, wimp...
Something less
embarrassing...?
Fine.
How 'bout changing the
way you address him?
Wait, what?
"Kakazu."...
Stop calling the poor
guy by his last name.
From here on out...
Call him "Kio,"
like everyone else!
No way!
I couldn't!
Oh, yes, you can...!
And you will, or the
distance between you two
will never get smaller.
It's that or the kiss.
Manami...
Are you sure about this...?
What about you?
What do you mean?
Well, you know...
The way you really feel -...
Get down!
Shooter's got an
infrared lasersight...
Saw it aimed
at your forehead.
It's live ammo.
Where are they?
Five o'clock south.
Judging by the report
and its impact...
Three hundred meters away.
Hell of a shot from
that distance...
Especially with
these obstructions.
This wasn't some
hunting accident...
We're dealing with
a professional.
Then we better be careful.
You gotta plan?
It'll take both of us.
Let me guess: One's the bait
and the other's the shooter?
Not quite...
You're going to be both
the bait and the shooter.
Huh?
Now I gotcha.
We're home.
Welcome back...
I've got a surprise
for you two.
Yep, dinner is served...!
Hope you brought
your appetites.
This looks incredible!
You made this all
by yourself?
Not quite...
None of this
would've been possible
without the help
of these guys.
Right, but it was Kio's
idea to make you a hot meal.
He thought you could use one
after getting drenched
and cold from the rain.
Wow, Kio, that's really
considerate for you.
Yes, Kakazu...
Thank you.
Sorry, what was that?
I meant...
Uh...
Thanks a lot...
Kio.
Again.
Thank you so much
for the meal, Kakazu!
I mean, thanks, Kio!
Forget it, it was
no big deal...
Did you guys
get cold today?
What?!
Not really...
'cause...
the action got hotter than
expected out there, Kio.
Moron!
You didn't even notice that Aoi
called you by your first name!
Well... let's eat up
before this gets cold.
Thank you again, Kio.
It's delicious!
I can't believe
you, Kio...!
I'm gonna make you pay
for this, you ignoramus!
Huh...?!
Wait...! What are you
so angry about now?
Is the food bad?
Sorry. But it's still
no reason to get violent.
That's not it at all!
Manami...!
Stop, it's okay.
Not 'til genius
here wises up!
I'll wise up...!
I swear...!
Even though I don't
know what about!
I'm gonna strangle the
cluelessness outta ya!
Assistroids are all just
cutesy little robots, right?
Wrong!
You won't believe what
the original one looks like,
but you're gonna find out
because it's coming to Earth!
Next time:
"The Grand First Assistroid?"
I'm coming
to drop in on you!