Space: the final frontier.
These are the voyages
of the Starship Catia.
Its five-year mission:
To explore strange, new worlds.
To seek out new life
and new civilizations.
To boldly go where no sexy
alien cat woman from a planet
full of sexy alien cat
women has gone before.
After arriving on Earth,
the Catian leadership proceeded
to an exchange center
to formally establish
diplomatic relations with
the government of Japan.
But, the cultural barriers
between the two groups
were considerable.
The negotiations with Japan
proved to be tricky,
as their differing wills
became extremely apparent.
I understand.
Basically, your
nation is considering
whether or not they want
to enter into negotiations
with the government
of Catia.
And while your leaders
are making their
final determination,
we're more than welcome
to remain on your planet
as unofficial guests.
Is that about
right, gentlemen?
Well, uh, you see, yes...
Very well then.
By the way, in regards to our
accommodations while here.
We won't require assistance
as we're currently staying
at the residence of a
private citizen.
Oh, well, while
this is unofficial,
it is nonetheless
considered state-funded.
On behalf of the
people of Japan,
we would like to cover your
expenses while you're here.
No, that really
won't be necessary.
But, as an annual outlay
and a gesture of kindness,
we'd ask you pay
us this much.
What? Two you say?
Yes, two.
We are not willing
to negotiate.
But we can't just--
I would like
to remind you gentlemen
that our advance
surveyor came very close
to being killed while
in your country.
But, what's done is done,
there's no sense crying
over spilled milk.
Our people will not be
seeking a formal apology.
I do beg your
pardon but, um...
May we have some time?
Of course, we know
you must be very busy.
We'll return at a later time
to hear your final answer.
Till then, have
a wonderful day.
Oh! I've never felt so
embarrassed before in my life!
Eris!
Are you sure this was
proper for us to wear?
I would say they were
extremely effective.
You bowled right over them
and left them laying there
like cats in heat,
Captain Kune.
What's the harm?
I like this outfit actually,
it makes me feel frisky.
But Doctor Durel!
It looks "purrfectly"
fine on all of you.
But it rubs my
fur the wrong way.
Oh, Executive
Officer Melwin,
what you lack in size you
make up for in charm.
That's right!
There's more to
breasts than just size.
The small ones
can be fun, too.
Besides, who even
needs big breasts
when you've got
a really nice tail,
am I right, Melwin?
Regardless of the relative
merit of breasts,
our plan to establish
diplomatic relations
between Catia
and Earth has begun!
Now let's all keep
this momentum going!
Yeah!
Did they really say two?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
Catians can drive
a hard bargain.
I guess it's about time.
I'm ready to move
when you are.
Leave the escape
route to me.
Our cell phones
can be traced.
More details to come.
Bye now.
No choice but to
leave them behind.
Sorry for the burden.
But until we hear
back from them,
we'll need to stay
here for awhile.
Would that be alright?
Yeah, sure.
That's cool with me.
Kio, that's great!
Thank you so much
for your generosity!
It's fine.
But how come you're
all wearing swimsuits?
Eris said putting these on
would help us negotiate
with the male earthlings.
It's true.
And apparently, on Earth,
school swimsuits are
everybody's favorite thing
to wear to a
business meeting.
Is that right?
And where did you
read that, huh?
Oh, I read it in one
of those magazines
you hide under
your bed, Kio.
Hey, give that back!
Whoa, Kio you
naughty boy, you!
It looks like we picked
the right attire, ladies,
the human men in these
magazines look very satisfied!
It's not like that.
Listen to me: these
magazines are fiction!
Don't tell me you're
at this again?
Manami,
where'd you come from?
I take my eyes off
you for one minute,
and you convince these alien
chicks to dress up like this?
You pervert.
You've got it all wrong!
It's not like that!
Hello.
Pardon me,
but is Kakazu here?
They're like coconuts!
All right,
that's enough!
Everyone change!
Kio's right.
Since the negotiations
are done,
we should all change back
to our usual uniforms.
Don't look!
Must be nice.
You senior officers
have it easy.
Hey. So, what's up with
all the luggage, Manami?
What's going on?
Everything okay?
Oh, yeah.
Listen, about that.
The truth is
we've come to say
goodbye, Kakazu.
Manami Kinjyou.
Currently under consideration
to become a CIA field agent.
Aoi Futaba.
aka 'Charmed Momiji'.
Special Interrogator for the
Japanese Immigration Bureau.
Maki Itokazu.
Member of the Japan branch
of the Beautiful Contact
secret society,
a group that fantasizes
about the first contact
with alien life.
As a result of the havoc
created by these three women,
each of whom are
connected to Kio Kakazu,
a young boy the Catian
has had contact with,
the subject ended
up escaping.
Most of the organizations
those three represent
have been assisted
by us in the past.
Ingrates.
Indeed.
It appears the dog is biting
the hand that feeds it.
Was that some sort of joke
or attempt at sarcasm?
Because I don't
find it funny.
Oh, no, I...
Please continue.
The incident was written
off as being an accident.
And the subject still
remains holed up
in the exact same
place as before.
You do realize the
severity of the situation.
As a result of this fiasco,
the covert dealings
between Dogishua
and your country
have been made known
to the cats.
Yes, ma'am.
The cats intend to use
Japan as a starting point
to begin formal diplomatic
relations with Earth.
And if they succeed.
The exclusive benefits your
country has come to enjoy
will no longer
be possible.
We won't let
it come to that.
Earth belongs to the dogs,
we marked our territory
by coming to you first.
If they think they can prance
in like they own the place,
they've got another
think coming!
If they try to test us,
we'll show those pesky furballs
there's more than one
way to skin a cat!
See, that was a joke.
Oh... Of course.
Wait, you're leaving?
But why?
Look, Kio, in
our line of work.
Once you've turned your
back on the organization,
you're as good as dead.
Plus. I bet they're
watching us right now.
So, that's it?
It's okay,
don't you worry.
I promise, we won't go
down without a fight.
Just trust us, Kio.
We've been trained to
maintain a low profile.
We know how to protect
ourselves and stay alive.
But you can't just--
Hey! We know
you'll miss us.
But you'll be fine.
Just keep on
being yourself.
Kakazu.
Be careful.
But, you guys, you
can't just leave!
Hey, can't you
do something?
Unfortunately,
we can't.
We still haven't formally
established a treaty
with this world.
Currently, there isn't anything
we can do to intervene,
right, Captain?
Nothing?
Actually, that's
not entirely true.
Technically speaking,
for the moment at least,
the Kakazu residence
is serving
as the provisional
Catian Embassy.
I get it.
You're right,
Captain Kune!
Wait, whaddaya mean?
You're onto something.
This place isn't
Earth or Japan.
It's under extraterritorial
jurisdiction.
And governed exclusively
by Catian law.
And if someone tried to harm
anyone inside these walls.
It would be the equivalent
of an unprovoked attack
on a foreign nation.
It would be a huge incident,
which might even lead to war.
Our laws can protect you.
Not even people from
your organizations
will be able to lay
a hand on you.
Hold on a sec.
So you mean--
You two girls
can move in with us
and be our brand
new roommates!
Huh?
We've got business to attend
to on the mothership.
You hold down
the fort here.
Sound good?
Yes!
No fooling around, got it?
Oh, except for a little
hanky-panky with Kio,
we're totally
okay with that--
If you discover any new
data about this world.
Send it on at once.
Roger that!
Wow, there they go.
So, let me make
sure I understand
what's happening here;
the four of us
are living together?
Don't worry,
it'll be fine!
Relax guys; the Assistroids will
do all the housework for you!
Housework is the
least of my concerns.
Oh!
Cat Planet Cuties!
Yeah. My pajamas
and some clothes.
Also my cell phone charger.
Yep. Bye, bye.
So What did your
Aunt say, Manami?
She told me to stay
out of trouble.
It's so close;
I could go get them myself!
Please, just let me
take care of this one.
We don't have a choice;
if you go outside
we can't claim
extraterritorial rights.
But my house,
it's just.
right across the street.
Until negotiations are
settled, the four of us
are gonna sit down
and have some fun.
There's no reason to stress,
we're in a safe zone.
I guess you're right.
Things could've
been much worse.
I could get
used to this.
Oh, come on.
Aren't you overdoing it?
We've been neighbors
forever, Kio.
This has always been
my second home,
and I see no reason
to change that now.
What about you?
Oh... Uh...
What were you
saying, Kakazu?
You might not be able to leave
here for a really long time;
you should call
your parents.
Well, the truth is,
I don't really have
any family, or relatives.
Oh. Uh...
Plus the identity I had here
was false to begin with
due to my job.
I didn't know. I'm sorry.
Oh... No, it's...
Don't apologize Kakazu,
it's not your fault.
I really do appreciate
your concern, though.
Let's see.
You and you have dinner
so you go to the kitchen.
Yours is clothing so
go to the bedroom.
You two I won't need for
awhile, so I'll store you...
Why bring over stuff you're
not even going to use?
Hey.
Don't you find it inconvenient
that they don't have names?
Well, we could assign
them numbers for now
if that would help?
There. From now
on you'll be Number Six!
Oh no, we've got
two seventeens.
Things have really gotten
out of hand here lately.
You'll do that?
Thank you!
Maybe this was
a bad idea.
The stuff with
Manami and Aoi.
I feel awful, it's not like they
can go back to their jobs now.
They had goals
they were pursuing
and careers they were developing
and now that's all gone away.
I owe them.
They really saved my skin
back there, you know?
If anything, I should be the
one sticking my neck out
for them this time.
But what can
I do for them?
No way.
I'm nothing special.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, Kio.
Could you use some
help with your back?
Huh? Eris?
No thanks!
Please, I insist.
A woman is supposed to wash a
man's every nook and cranny!
I read it
in your magazines!
No.
Please stop.
Haven't you ever
heard the phrase
"you can't believe
everything you read?"
What's all the
racket in here?
No! Let me explain!
please Manami!
Once again your
perverted nature
has gotten the better
of you, Kio!
I just can't leave
you alone, can I?
This is the last straw!
It's time I scrubbed
that filthy mind of yours!
Wait! Manami!
Help me!
What's with
all the yelling?
Please.
Don't be mad.
Hey there!
It's not my fault.
Wanna help me scrub Kio's
hard-to-reach spots?
Eris, please. Stop it!
Why you...
Sick peeerveeerrrt!
These girls will
be the death of me.
Geez!
The nerve of that
guy, I swear!
You know,
I just don't get it.
I don't understand
what you see in him.
You are into him,
aren't you, Aoi?
Umm. Well, I... I don't know.
I was sort of under
the impression
that you liked
Kakazu like that.
Please, you must be joking!
Yeah but, the two
of you are so close.
I've been stuck with
that moron forever.
I did come close to
liking him once, though.
Well, what came of it?
Did he turn you down?
No, of course not!
Truth is, Kio was
really shy back then.
He didn't exactly know
how to talk to girls.
Not even me, and we've known
each other our whole lives.
Eventually though,
things changed.
He got comfortable around
me and started to treat me
like I was one of the guys.
Once I realized he
thought of me that way,
I really didn't
care anymore.
We're just friends.
And I wouldn't want
it any other way.
Right.
You, on the other hand, might
actually have a shot with him.
Trust me, I've known
Kio my whole life,
and I know when he
likes somebody,
and he's totally
into you.
Twenty one hundred hours.
Looks like the cute objects
are changing the guard.
Number seventeen
is relieving number...
Wait, how can that be?
What's going on?
Yeah, but.
He can't like me;
I'm not an ordinary girl.
Huh?
Here, watch this.
Apport.
Whoa.
Hold on a second.
How did you--?
It's my special power.
I've always had it.
For as long as
I can remember,
I've had the ability
to teleport objects
within a
fifty-meter radius.
But because of my power,
no one wanted anything
to do with me.
Not even my family.
Eventually, I found my place
as an agent of the underworld.
I've stained my hands
with blood many times
for the mission's sake.
That's terrible.
The fact is...
I come from a world that
Kakazu will never understand.
What's with
the alarm, huh?
Guys! Intruders!
Apport!
Cover me!
Hey! Hold on!
Let's go!
Since they have two
of the same kind,
they won't miss this one!
Apport!
Oops.
Sorry about that.
You idiot!
What if something had
happened to the kitty?
Don't move!
State your
affiliation and rank!
Are you CIA?
Or did the Immigration
Bureau send you here?
I'm insulted you would lump
us in the same category
as those low-lifes.
But let's just say we're
servants of a nobler master
and a much higher cause.
They threw
a stun grenade!
Oh, no!
They got away!
Don't worry,
we're coming!
We're almost there!
Hey, guys,
are you all right?
Ahhh! How dare you, pervert!
You're gonna hit me!
I'll kill you!
It's good
to have you back.
I knew you were a sicko!
Stop looking!
He's such an idiot!
I swear, he drives me nuts!
It's not his fault; we were the
ones who were naked, you know?
It's not a question of
whether he's at fault or not.
He shouldn't have come running
when we were undressed.
Well, we were in the
middle of a gun fight.
The only reason
he came running
is 'cause he was really
worried about us.
You really do like
him, don't you?
No, I... I don't.
Oh, please.
Here's a friendly
piece of advice.
Kio's kind of wishy-washy,
so if you don't stand
up for yourself,
that alien cat chick is
gonna steal him away.
Hey. Look.
I've got your back
no matter what, 'kay?
No way I'm gonna let that
alien get the best of you.
Yeah but... How do I...?
You can't let your past
prevent you from going
after your future.
Just have a little more
faith in yourself.
You're right.
Thanks, Manami.
Anytime.
Now let's get some sleep,
alright, roomie?
Okay.
And so, the new roommates
slept together under one roof.
For the moment at least,
they were peaceful and content.
There's something important
I'd like to discuss.
How would you three like
to become official employees
of the provisional
Catian Embassy?
We'd work here?
What would we do?
Well, for starters, we could
definitely use the help
of people who know their
way around this planet.
Plus, because of your
special abilities,
I was thinking you two
would make really good--
I don't know what to call it,
'safety-keepers' maybe?
Safety-keepers?
Security.
But we can't.
Hello Manami.
Jack! It's you!
Why are you calling me?
I have something you
might wanna hear.
Manami, there's
an organization
targeting your
alley cat friend.
Tell her to watch out.
You be careful too, okay?
Hold on, Jack!
Listen, I know
I interfered with your work.
My responsibility was
to apprehend the target
and that's it.
Anything that happened
after that wasn't on me.
Look girl, you just took
the wind out of the sails
of one of my least favorite
people in the entire world.
Don't worry, we're fine, okay?
If I hear anything else,
I'll be in touch.
Manami?
Yeah Aoi? Whats up?
I know this might seem
hard to believe but,
what if they weren't
coming after us?
Kio, who is this
Jack person?
Oh, that's the guy
Manami's going out with.
Jack is not a guy!
She is a woman, moron!
Oh! You like girls.
It's Janice Allectus
Carotinas Kalinart.
Or 'Jack' for short.
She's my boss at
the CIA, you idiot.
Or she was, I guess.
Oh, I see.
I was confused
'cause of her name.
Plus, every time you get
a phone call from her,
you're always whispering.
I thought you two were secret
boyfriend and girlfriend.
Idiot.
That's funny.
Here I was thinking you were
in a serious relationship
this whole time.
Well, I'm so sorry
to disappoint you.
Can I ask you something?
What's that?
Uh. Oh, it's nothing.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Just leave me alone.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
please forgive me.
I was unable to
bring you your gift.
I swear, I will
get it next time.
And the Divine
Embodiment, too.
Spending the day in Tokyo
is always a great time.
Well, unless you run
into a bunch of cat
worshipping nutjobs
that randomly attack you and
kidnap your friends, that is!
Next time...
"We've Come
to Kidnap You!"
I'm coming
to drop in on you!