She came to visit
from far away,
in search of new friends
and experiences.
Yeah, but nothing
concrete yet.
...have been receiving
for the last six months.
Sure, Jack.
If I find anything out,
you'll be the first to know.
A message from the
depths of outer space
might sound like something
straight out of a B-movie.
But an investigation
by the SDF,
The Ministry of Internal Affairs
and Communications, and ITU-R,
the International
Telecommunication Union,
has verified
that space is exactly
where the message
originated from.
Relayed around the world in
several different languages,
this message
has been confirmed
to have the same
meaning in each one:
"I'm going to drop by."
All right!
Next up! Let 'er rip!
Good.
You're ready?
What are you doing?
That Browning Nine
millimeter you're holding
is a surprisingly
cumbersome pistol.
I hear that if you do this,
it becomes temporarily
unable to fire.
They're shooting at us;
your orders, captain?
Fire a warning
shot across their bow
and then order them
to shut down their engines
and surrender immediately!
They're launching
rockets at us!
I'm moving out.
Not yet.
People will
die if I don't.
That won't
change if you go.
I know, but it will
change who dies.
Wait for orders!
Activate System 7.
Momiji! Wait!
Equip S-1!
What the?
Stop!
Their cargo's weapons
and illegal drugs.
No one's aboard
but the crew.
It's a covert ops ship.
Take control of it.
Roger that.
Now aren't you glad I
insisted on coming aboard?
Equip K.
There's nowhere to run.
Surrender!
Trust me,
that won't work!
Apport!
I said it wouldn't work.
What was that?
A UFO!
What the hell's
going on?
No, don't!
Lots of military
jets today.
Hope you got the party
favors I asked for, Kio.
Uncle Yuichi.
Here.
Thanks!
Um, no offense but, should
you really be drinking today?
AHH!
We're celebrating
the anniversary
of our great-great
grandfather's death,
and if you just grieve,
they can't cross over.
C'mon, grab a brew and drink
to the departed old dude!
Uh, no thanks,
I'm underage.
Ah, who cares?
You're in high school
now, aren't you?
Yeah, but.
Got a girlfriend?
No, I don't,
at least not yet.
Get with it kid!
These are your golden years
and you're wasting them.
There's nothing like
your first girlfriend.
So come on, Kio, we're
gonna go get you one, 'kay!
Right here and now!
No, wait a minute!
Uh-uh, you've waited
long enough now,
so it's time to bag
you a babe.
What about that one?
She's pretty nice.
Check her out.
Smoking hot figure,
cute face,
and look
at those ears.
What the?
No kidding.
So did I.
A tail?
Well, hey, little lady,
can I offer you a
refill on your drink?
Yes! Thank you for
the tasty beverage, sir!
Uncle Yuichi, stop,
what are you doing?
Are you nuts?
You can't give
alcohol to minors!
You look underage, so I can't
let you have this, 'kay?
That's fine. I'm very
happy with these dishes.
They're all so tasty.
Such as this one here.
By what term do you
call this again?
It's so delicious!
Oh, that's Taro Dengaku.
I've never dined
on it before today,
but I just love it!
Like those kelp wraps.
And that rafute!
So soft and tender!
Oh, they really
get me purring!
They're the cat's meow!
So then I guess.
You've never had
Okinawan cuisine before?
Nope! But I'm
glad I have now
because it's been so long
since I've eaten anything!
Why's that?
I forgot to load
food onto my ship,
so when I finally arrived,
I was starving.
Luckily, I met a cat
named Aura near the beach
and she told me
if I came here,
there'd be good food
and nice people.
Boy, was she right!
She was a real lifesaver.
That's funny, I actually
have a cat named Aura.
Well, at least I used to,
until she ran away
from home recently.
Pleased to meet you;
my name is Eris.
Oh. Likewise!
My name's Kio Kakazu. Uh...
Is something the matter?
Um.
No.
Everything's great!
This is beer.
What the...
I'm home?
What happened to
the commemoration?
The last thing I seem
to remember is being there
and Uncle Yuichi
offered me a beer.
He did the same to
a girl in cat ears.
Then I managed to get
it away from her
before she could
take a swig of it.
But then I did!
Oh, man, that one swig
must have made me pass out!
What a lightweight.
Better sleep it off.
Huh?
Meow.
Did Aura come back?
You! You're that girl!
Oh, no, did you injure
your cranial mass?
Just hold on, okay?
You did.
But thankfully it's
nothing too severe.
Hey. It doesn't
hurt anymore.
That's because the device
I just used on your head
is a tool we employ to heal
injuries where I come from.
Oh. Well,
thanks a lot.
You're red;
are you still ill?
Uh, no, but do you think
you could button up.
And maybe explain to me
what you're doing in my bed?
Your uncle told me I could
sleep wherever I liked,
and curling up next to you
felt like the optimum spot.
Kio!
Manami?
Do you want me
to get that?
No!
Just wait here, 'kay?
Oh, crap!
If Manami sees her, I'm never
gonna hear the end of it!
Alright, just stay calm!
Think up an excuse and
get her out of here quick!
Hey, Manami.
What brings you here?
Oh, I just had
a quick question.
Who's that big-boobed babe
you drunkenly stumbled home
with last night?
Wait, how'd you
know about that?
Uh. I live
across the street,
so I see everything
that goes on around here.
I even know about
the secret stash
that you hide under
your mattress; namely.
Your porno.
So.
Do I get to meet
this girl?
Tell me what she's like.
Well, to be totally honest,
she's a little bit strange.
Ohhh!
I think I get it, Kio!
Some babe finds
you attractive,
and you call her "strange"?
C'mon, have you
looked in a mirror?
You're easy on the eyes.
Gee, thanks, Manami.
But she really is strange.
You two got hot and heavy
last night, didn't you?
Was it a night of
unbridled passion, Kio?
Did she proclaim
her love for you
as she smushed her
pneumatic knockers together
and did she ask you
if you wanted some fries
with her shake?
That's about how things
went down, right?
I bet your mystery girl's
still in bed right now,
and you're bringing her some
morning coffee, aren't you?
Aw, what a perfect little
studmuffin you've become.
Hey, what is it?
You've got a dirty mind,
you know that?
Wow, you're really
one to talk!
Might I remind you
that you're the one
who spent the night
with a strange girl?
You've got it all
wrong, Manami!
And who might this be?
They're like huge
cantaloupes!
Hey! What are you
doing down here?
Go put some clothes on!
Can I go get
my suit then?
It's hanging in the room
that you use for bathing
and waste disposal.
Uh. Yeah, sure.
Pervert.
I can explain!
No, there's no need to.
You've read so much manga
and played so many video games
that you've become
a deviant freak,
one that falls head
over heels and into bed
with a cosplaying cutie!
Well, am I right or not?
No, you're wrong and
you're totally delusional!
Oh, yeah?
Then why is a
practically naked girl
running around your house
wearing kitty ears?
What?
Is that true?
Miss Itokazu.
What are you doing here?
Don't you remember?
We were supposed
to meet this morning
to discuss the video
club summer camp.
But never mind that now.
And instead.
Please explain
what I just heard.
Uh. Look, Manami's
imagining stuff;
I can explain everything.
Um.
Is this suit okay?
They're hugepears!
Kio!
You're way too young for this;
you're still in high school!
If you've got a thing
for "furries,"
then wait until you're
an adult to indulge it!
No! Like I said,
I can explain everything!
Those ears and that tail aren't
parts of a cat girl costume;
they're both real!
Kio, I'm not an idiot, so
please don't treat me like one!
Look, I do know boys are
very curious at your age.
But still.
This fake cat girl
fetish is quite odd.
I'm not fake;
come stroke me.
If you have any
doubts, go ahead.
Feel!
See?
Like he said,
I'm real.
Enough,
that tickles!
Hey! Just who .
Or what are you?
I'm an alien researching the
planet that you people live on;
I sent a message saying,
"I'm going to drop by!"
A cat girl from space?
This is ridiculous!
I believe alien life
forms do exist out
in the cosmos somewhere.
But I doubt they'd have
the same shape as humans
and speak the same language!
Even the cheesiest sci-fi
movie would avoid such a cliché!
Get real!
To be honest, when
my people first saw
how similar your world's
inhabitants were to us,
we were equally shocked.
We thought it was a joke.
Stop!
I won't accept this!
And your costume
proves nothing!
If you're really an alien,
I need hard, irrefutable proof!
Irrefutable, huh?
Let me think here.
Hi, Luros;
what's the matter?
Emergency Miss Eris!
It appears the ship
has been discovered!
But I thought it
was camouflaged?
Affirmative, but it wasn't
in active camouflage mode,
Miss, just the passive one.
The ship; what's its
current status and location?
Well, it's been caught
in a fibrous net,
and it's been pulled up to
the water's surface, Miss.
Um, hey guys.
Check out the news.
Some have theorized that this
strange piece of metal
pulled from the water might
be an alien spacecraft.
When asked if it could be
related to the mysterious
"I'm going to drop by" message,
officials refused comment.
The cat's out of the bag.
It leaves me no choice.
Ready to carry out
your orders, Miss Eris!
Reactivate the ship.
Then initiate Program "A,"
number Twenty-Four, Luros.
And after that, start
"He," number Eleven.
Okey-dokey, Miss Eris!
What was that?
That was Luros,
my ship's navigation system.
We come in peace,
and we mean you no harm.
However, we cannot
allow you to detain us,
so we must be going now.
Pursuit would be futile.
Goodbye!
Um.
I'm not feeling
all that well,
so I really need
to be going.
Yeah.
I've gotta
get going, too.
So, Eris?
Did you come to
Earth to conquer us?
Is that it?
No, of course not!
I came to foster goodwill.
If I came to conquer, then
both me and my entire race
would be destroyed by the
Galactic Sentient Federation.
What's that?
An organization that oversees
interstellar relations.
It's led by the Orzonians,
mind-based lifeforms
who are one of the more
advanced alien races.
Oh, really?
Hey, what race
do you belong to?
My people actually refer to
our home planet as "Earth"
and call ourselves
Earthlings.
We knew that would be
confusing once we made contact
with your world,
so we now refer
to our planet as "Catia."
Wow.
Oh! This miso pork
is incredible!
It's yummy!
How do you make it?
Can you give me the recipe?
Yeah, sure!
You take some pork.
Cut it up real thin, and then
add a little miso, some mirin,
and a dash of sake,
and then you fry it all up
in a wok with some oil.
Hey, Manami.
What's the good word?
I've got some
killer info at last.
Really?
Alright,
then let's hear it.
I'll tell you, but only
under one condition.
You have to let me come
along on a field op.
It's way too soon for
you to be in the field.
Please! Having
field experience
will be a huge plus on my
Company entrance evaluation.
What am I gonna
do with you?
Alright, I'll put
in a special request
and see if I can
swing something.
Aw, thanks a lot!
You're the best and you
won't regret this, I swear!
I better not.
What's this "killer info"
you claim to have?
I just sent an image to you.
This is what you've been
talking about, isn't it?
Wow.
Nice work.
This is a major score.
Good morning
to you, Captain.
to you, Hal.
Hello,
this is Ender.
Hello, Ender.
This is Kerberos.
Did you see the TV?
We did.
This is a shame.
It would have been
so much more exciting
if it hadn't
happened like this.
Agreed.
I encountered
the life form
who piloted the spacecraft
that was recovered.
Where?
Are you serious?
Near identical to us.
Sadly, it was
rather unremarkable.
Oh, no.
Such a being cannot be allowed
to be mankind's first contact
with an alien race.
This is a serious
situation, Ender.
I suggest that you take action
on this issue immediately.
But how?
I can't accomplish much
without additional support.
We will send
you someone.
We have people in the
Navy and the Air Force.
Thanks,
I appreciate it.
Good luck
to you, Ender.
Ender, don't forget
to keep your chin up.
I won't fail.
We'll achieve
Beautiful Contact!
[repeating] We will achieve
Sooooo happy!
This has been more
like a vacation
than an intergalactic
mission!
Aura was telling the
truth about your species.
You welcomed me and served
me that delectable food,
and not only that,
but you also let me join
in on all the singing
and dancing, too!
You and your fellow
humans are so very kind.
Why thank you.
Thank you; and I hope I'm not
keeping you from anything.
Oh, no.
Not really.
So Is there anything
you wanted to do today?
No, I don't really have
anything specific planned.
I have to go return a couple
of things to a friend of mine.
I won't be gone long.
would you mind watching
the house while I'm away?
You don't have to answer
the phone at all.
And if anyone knocks
on the door, ignore it.
Okay?
No, I don't mind, but the
least I could do would be
to greet any visitors
who might stop by.
They might get
freaked out, though.
'cause of your look.
Oh, right.
Your species isn't
used to aliens, is it?
Just stay here and
make yourself at home.
Oh, and if you
get hungry,
there's tons of food
in the fridge.
Thanks!
Have a good time!
Why did Miss Itokazu
get so upset
when Eris claimed
to be an alien?
She almost sounded like
she was disappointed.
Kakazu.
Aoi! I was
looking for you.
Here you go.
Thanks again.
I appreciate you
loaning these to me.
Well.
How were they?
I thought that
"Koyaanisqatsi"
had some incredible
cinematography.
And as for "Gaia Symphony,"
it really made me think.
So you liked them, huh?
Yeah. And I'd love
to check out
anything else you feel
like recommending,
maybe something from the
director of "Rainbow Kids?"
Okay.
Then why don't I loan you
"Desperate Outpost"
the next time I see you?
Thanks!
Or if... you want to...!
Yes?
Go on.
Well!
If you want to you
and I could go
watch it today.
We could even stop off
at the DVD store
and buy some new releases
if you've got time.
Hey, Aoi,
what a coincidence.
Oh.
Hello, Mr. Endo.
You know, I was just on my
way to see your parents.
Would you like a lift?
Hey. Aoi, don't
you worry about me.
We'll just do the DVD
thing some other day.
'Kay. Thanks a lot.
How does the day
after tomorrow sound?
Sounds great.
I'll see you then.
Count on it.
See you soon.
Yep, take care.
Did I interrupt anything?
Isn't coming here
a contract violation?
There's an emergency
job for you.
I didn't want to come,
either, but I have orders.
I admit I found that
amusing back there.
Your behavior around him.
That wasn't
an act, was it?
I wonder what Mr. High School
Crush would think if I told him
what you really are?
Shall we find out?
Fine, tell him then,
I don't care;
I'll just transfer
to another high school.
However.
I'll be sure
to kill you first.
And I won't do it because
you obstructed my mission
or caused undue
complications.
Instead, I'll do it simply
because I want to kill you.
No, don't shoot!
If you do,
the car will!
It doesn't matter.
I'm called "Charmed"
Momiji for a reason.
I won't get
a scratch on me.
You, on the other hand.
I think it's time to add
another chapter to my legend,
don't you?
Please.
Don't shoot.
I was just joking.
What are the details of
this job you have for me?
Um. Here.
Same thing as always.
Eliminate a dangerous,
illegal immigrant
and those who've been
aiding and abetting her.
The target's Upper A-Class,
and you're free to use
any means necessary.
Timeframe?
ASAP.
We'd like to avoid the target's
presence becoming public.
We've obtained intel
that other organizations
are moving in as well.
We want
to avoid any chaos.
You're going to need
my assistance
on this mission, Momiji.
So please.
Don't kill me.
Dammit.
Why did it have
to be you Kakazu?
What happens when a classmate,
a childhood friend,
and a visitor from outer
space come together?
Chaos, a kidnapping,
a lot of people with guns,
and a bunch of explosions,
that's what!
Next time:
"I Dropped By."
I'm coming
to drop in on you!