[exhilarating music]
[narrator] Long, long ago,
in a meadow, far, far away,
a mother unicorn gave birth
to her babies.
Just as mother unicorns
had been doing
since the beginning of time.
[babies chuckling]
[wailing]
[narrator] Among the babies,
was one special little fellow.
With white fur
and a tiny white horn.
Whose name was Unico.
No one knew the reason why.
But this little unicorn
had a very special power.
Wherever he went,
Unico had the gift
of making all living things
light-hearted, and happy.
♪ The little fellow named Unico
As cute as cute can be ♪
♪ An innocent boy was Unico,
So happy and so carefree ♪
♪ What heaven!
Life as sweet as nature ♪
♪ Could have planned ♪
♪ What strange gift do you hold
In your hand ♪
♪ Is it true ♪
♪ That wherever you may go ♪
♪ Oh Unico ♪
♪ Across the land
The fighting will cease ♪
♪ And night will turn to day ♪
♪ All tears
will simply disappear ♪
♪ And the world will say
We love you ♪
♪ Oh Unico ♪
♪ We love you ♪
[narrator] Hard as it is
to believe,
there were certain individuals
who were not overjoyed
with Unico's wonderful powers.
The God's, who thought
that they alone had the right
to decide when people
should be happy.
Wherever that Unico goes,
people start laughing
and dancing like a big idiots.
Oh! Happiness should only
be the end result
of years of sacrifice,
and hard labor.
-He must be strapped.
- I certainly agree.
People are losing
all their respect
-for the God's.
- There is only one thing to do.
What? What?
Unico must die. Oh!
-Now, wait a minute.
- Oh dear, oh dear!
Let's not be hasty.
We're supposed to be merciful.
We could simple exile
him somewhere, hmm?
-We could, yes.
- Oh, a good idea.
We could get the West Wind
to do it for us, huh.
West Wind, come to us!
[fantasy music]
-I am here.
- We have a mission for you.
You must find
the creature Unico,
and carry him far away,
and cast him up
on the hill of oblivion.
[all gasp]
[God] No matter how many
thousands of years pass,
he must remain in exile
far from the side
of any living thing.
It must be
as if he never existed.
Your wish is my command.
Poor little one.
I must steal you
from your mother.
And take you to a place
where you'll be forgotten
forever.
[sad music]
[narrator] And it was
in this way
that little Unico's long,
long journey began.
[melodic music]
No, I cannot do it.
No matter what the God's
may say,
I simply cannot abandon you
to the hill of oblivion.
[West Wind] Here, in this land
of mist, this place at the edge
of the earth far from the sight
of men and Gods.
I'll leave you here.
Here. The God's will never
notice you in this place.
Provided you don't show yourself
by using your magic powers.
But then, there's nothing here
on which you could use them.
Farewell, Unico.
[waves splashing]
[groans softly]
[shouts]
Hey, stop it!
[water gushing]
What happened? Where am I?
Is anybody here?
[yelling] Hey, is anybody here?
[sobbing]
I am... lonesome!
[sobbing continues]
Wow! What's that?
[exciting music]
Uh.
[mysterious music]
It's... somebody's house.
[scary music]
[shouts]
[anxiously] What's that?
What... what is this place?
I wonder.
[Unico] Hello.
[screams]
-Ah!
- Who discerns my solitude?
Ah! Someone is there.
Hello, my name is Unico.
Why should I care
what your name is?
You must leave this place
at once.
[Unico] Who are you, Mr. Statue?
You dare to call me a statue!
Can't you see that I'm a devil?
Well, not like that I am
somebody else here.
-I am happy.
- Well, I'm not.
Get out of
this temple immediately.
Huh? Why do I have to go?
Because, I'm the devil
of solitude, that's why.
What is solitude?
The state of being all alone.
All alone?
But now that I'm here,
-we can be friends.
- Oh, don't be an idiot.
Why would a devil be friends
with the likes of you?
Go away!
[screaming]
[electric shock]
[shouting]
[loud rumbling]
Oh no! He broke himself
into pieces.
Mr. Devil?
[distant wailing]
[wailing continues]
Who on earth are you?
Oh! [shouts]
[devil] You get out of here.
You smashed my daddy.
Get out. [crying]
I'm sorry.
Do you really live here
all by yourself?
Huh! What could this be?
[shouts] Let go!
[devil] Whoa! You dummy!
Don't you realize that devils
are very ferocious?
And now that my dad
is all smashed up,
I'm the next devil of solitude.
So, hope you got that straight.
You better run away
before I get angry.
Oh, I wish you wouldn't
say that.
I just want to be friends.
[devil] Friends! [laughs]
Devils don't know the meaning
of the word.
It's the easiest thing
in the world.
It just means that we talk
to each other,
and play together.
[devil laughs] Does that mean
I can call you bad names,
-and punch you in the snoot?
- That's not really the idea.
I know, if you'll be my friend,
I'll give you anything you want.
Anything?
Anything.
Really and truly?
-Really and truly.
- Huh!
Really and truly and truly
and truly?
Yeah, just like I said,
really and truly and truly
and tru...
I think I lost count somewhere.
Anyway, I mean what I say.
[laughs] It's a deal.
Okay. What I want is that horn
on top of your head.
What?
Yeah!
That way I won't have to wait
until I'm grown to get
my devil's horn.
I can just use yours.
It's just that,
if you take away my horn,
I'll lose all my powers.
Come on! You expect me
to believe that?
What you just finished
telling me?
That if I became your friend,
you'd give me anything I wanted,
right?
Please, not my horn.
[grunts] I get it now.
You never really wanted
to be friends.
It was all a bunch of owing.
Scram! Yeah!
[devil] Now you've made
me angry.
[electric shock]
[screaming]
Huh?
After all, I'm Beezle,
the devil of solitude.
And devils of solitude
are supposed to be alone.
Naturally, goes without saying.
So, what do I want
with a friend.
Especially, some little runt
with a horn on his head.
I wonder where that little runt
went to.
Oh.
Hey, hi Beezle!
[shouts]
Why don't you come out,
and play?
Why should I want to play?
I just stuck my head out
for a breath of fresh air,
you know.
But listen,
since you're still here,
why don't you give me your horn?
I promise you will have
lots of fun.
Come on, give it here!
Let it go!
[grunts]
That does it. Get out of here!
[soft music]
Why should I be lonely?
I'm not lonely.
I'm not. I'm not.
[sighs]
[humming]
[grunts]
[devil] I don't even like
the little runt.
And I couldn't care less
if he doesn't comes back.
♪ Lonely all my life ♪
♪ I've been alone
for all my life ♪
♪ But not until today
Did I know ♪
♪ You've set me free
And you've made me see ♪
♪ That I don't have to live
With a cloud over me ♪
♪ You want to be my friend ♪
♪ And I've never had a friend ♪
♪ You're the first who ever
Stretched his hand out to me ♪
♪ But something deep inside
Makes me want to run and hide ♪
♪ I guess I'm just the kind
Who can't confide ♪
♪ Though I've tried
There's a part of me ♪
♪ That say no ♪
♪ Telling me to let you go ♪
♪ You may go ♪
[grunts]
If Unico had never come here,
I'd be just fine.
Now because of him,
I'm lonely all the time.
And I don't even like the guy.
I hate him, I hate him,
I hate him, I hate him!
And I hope I never see him
again, never!
[devil] Hmm!
[shouts] No! Got to go!
[grunts] What do you think
you're doing here?
I told you to never set foot
in here again.
It's just that... I thought
you wanted my horn.
What?
You mean, you really... uh,
you'll really give me your horn?
Yes, because I want to be
your friend.
But you've got to take
very good care of it, okay.
And... you're going to have
to make me a promise.
Well, what kind of a promise?
You've got to promise
to give it back at the end
-of one day.
- What! Just one day?
I only get it for one day.
You lousy little cheapskate.
I knew there'd be a catch
to it somehow.
Does this mean
you won't be my friend?
Uh-oh! No, oh, I'll do it, okay.
Ah! You will?
But of course, it means
that I'll only be your friend
-for one day.
- Oh, okay.
-Go ahead.
- How do I do this?
Does it come off?
[both grunting]
Well, what do you know?
Oh! Don't forget,
you have to give it back
at the end of the day.
Leaping Lucifer!
It came right off.
Oh! Hmm.
I wonder... will it go
on my head?
Hmm.
Ah! Huh!
Oh-uh!
[shouting]
[chuckles]
[blows]
[gasps]
Uh! Eh!
Oh!
Ah!
[shouts excitedly]
Giddy up!
Hey, stop it!
What are you doing?
-[Unico shouting]
- What do you think we're doing?
We're playing together. [laughs]
-Stop it you too.
- Help me! [shouts]
Ah, quit your bellyaching!
You wanted to play, didn't you?
Hey, would you please stop
hitting me with your tail.
-I don't like it.
- I'm having a great time.
-Be quiet and keep going.
- [Unico shouting]
-Oh!
- Whoa!
Hmm! [crying loudly]
Oh, what is it now?
What do you think
you're doing, huh?
Oh, don't you know
how to play with a friend
the right way?
Oh, well, what do you think
we should do?
Well, for example,
we could just have
a friendly conversation, or...
we could play a game
of hide and seek.
Have you ever played that?
[laughs]
We could have a friendly
conversation, huh?
Or play hide and seek, huh?
[chuckles]
[screaming]
Just watch this.
He-yea!
[laughing]
Oh, this is how devils play!
[banging]
Oh! Whoa!
[laughing]
Whoa!
[shouting]
[Beezle laughing]
[happy music]
This is what I call fun.
This is how devils like to play.
It's a lot more fun
than hide and seek. [laughs]
It's funnier than anything.
Uh-oh!
Oh!
[coughs]
Stop it! That's not funny.
You're going to ruin my horn.
Cut it out.
Huh! Uh! Stop it.
What are you doing?
[screaming]
I'm stronger than you are.
I'm going to poke you!
[overlapping chatter]
You aren't very good
at this game are you, huh?
Stop it! Stop it!
[Beezle] Whoa!
[Unico shouting]
[Beezle] Here I come.
I've got you now.
[playful music]
[Unico screaming]
[chuckles] Looks like
this is the end of the line
for you.
Oh! Oh stop it.
This game's gone too far.
-[Beezle] Oh yeah?
- [screaming]
[coughs] Beezle, help me!
Hmm?
[yelling] Without my horn...
I have no powers.
Please help! Help!
What do you mean by help?
My daddy never taught me
about that word.
Oh! It means help me.
You've got to reach out,
and rescue me.
Oh, you got to be kidding.
Devils don't go in
for that kind of thing,
you know.
I'm drowning!
[shouts]
Hmm.
[yawns] This is getting boring.
I think it's time for a nap.
[yelling] Help!
[hourglass ticking]
[sighs] Oh, leaping Lucifer!
I can't get to sleep.
Oh! [whines]
[humming]
Maybe, I should help him.
No. Devils don't do
that kind of nice stuff.
Still I do got to return
his horn to him.
I made a promise after all,
and devils have to keep
their promises.
Daddy was always very strict
about that.
[sighs]
But I still got the rest
of the day,
before I get to return
it to him.
[grunts]
[mumbling]
Time sure drags on
when you're having fun.
Can't it go any faster?
[breathing heavily]
I won't be able to keep
my promise
if you don't hurry up.
[mumbling]
[shouting]
Well, according to
the hourglass, the day is over.
Now, I get to keep my promise
to Unico,
and return his horn.
[Beezle] Here I come!
[exciting music]
Oh! Unico! I'm here to give
you your horn back.
Oh, look how far out he is.
What a dummy!
Okay Unico, don't worry,
here I come.
Turn! Whoa! Slippery Satan.
I almost forgot the ocean's
dangerous to us devils.
Oh!
No. I made a promise,
and I've got to keep it.
[speaking indistinctly]
[Beezle] Unico!
[sad music]
[coughs]
[Beezle] Think you can
stop me, huh?
Unico!
[coughs]
Well, the day is over,
and I brought your horn back.
Whoa!
[coughs]
Didn't you hear me?
Here's... your horn.
The horn... you dummy.
Unico?
Hang on, Unico!
Open your eyes.
Here's your horn.
[Beezle sobbing]
Oh! Oh, Beezle.
[Beezle] I told you
I'd give you your horn back.
I'm just keeping my promise.
-[Beezle] Whoa!
- Beezle, thank you.
[Beezle] No need to thank me.
[bubbling]
What is it?
What's wrong?
[coughs] Unico... the sea
is poisoned to devils.
You mean, you knew that,
and you still saved me?
Who said anything
about saving you?
I just kept my promise.
[Beezle] Goodbye, goodbye Unico!
Oh!
[horn tinkles]
Thank you, Beezle.
[positive music]
[horn tinkles]
Wait a minute.
What's the big idea?
I'm still alive.
Hey, just what the devil
is going on?
[Beezle] Huh! Unico?
If someone truly loves me,
I have the special power
to turn into that mighty unicorn
you saw.
And I think you love me, Beezle.
Huh? What did you say?
Love! [shouts]
Yuck! Stop it, stop it!
Yuck! That word makes me itch
all over.
I love you.
What a disgusting idea!
-[shouts]
- Oh, come on Beezle.
You know it's true.
You do love me.
And I love you too.
Are you trying to kill me
all over again?
Stop it! I hate it.
Here, I'll prove it to you.
[horn tinkles]
Whoa!
Huh?
What the devil! [shouts]
It's a horn!
My very own horn.
[chuckles]
[humming]
Thank you. Hurray!
♪ I've got a horn
I've got a horn ♪
♪ Just as good as my dance ♪
[Beezle] Now, I'm a real devil.
♪ Shala la la la la ♪
[Beezle singing]
[exciting music]
[God] Oh, no!
A severe case of happiness
is broken out on the island
of the Devil of Solitude.
-[God 1] It's Unicorn.
- [God 2] It has to be Unico.
The West Wind has betrayed us
I see.
Hmm.
We must call the Night Wind.
Night Wind come to us.
[all shout]
-Oh, she comes.
- [stuttering] She's coming.
The Night Wind
is at your service.
You must take Unico away.
Take him far away.
Take him to the land
where nothing is or ever was.
I hear and obey.
[Beezle] Hey, Unico!
Where are you?
Unico, come here!
[West Wind] Unico?
Unico?
[Unico] Oh, it's you.
Hello, West Wind.
Unico, the God's have discovered
your hiding place.
You must come away with me,
before they find you.
-You can't stay here any longer.
- No! No, I don't want to go.
I don't want to go
anywhere else.
You have no choice.
If they find you,
they will send you
to the hill of Oblivion.
Now come along.
There is no time to argue.
I don't want to go!
Hmm, I have a friend here.
I can't just go away.
You must forget him.
Forget all about him.
[Beezle] Unico!
Hey, Unico! Unico?
Unico... where are you?
Where are you hiding?
Hey?
Unico, is this a game?
U-Ni-co!
Hmm.
He's got to be here some place.
Hey Unico?
Where the devil are you?
[yells] Unico!
[Unico] Beezle!
[happy music]
[Beezle] Huh? Unico!
Where are you going?
Hey, hey, where do you think
you're going?
And just when I decided
to be your friend too.
I would call of a devil
if you're going to take Unico
away from me.
You'd better bring him
back here right now.
[sniffs]
Unico!
I won't let you get away
with this.
I'll come after you.
[Beezle] Now that I'm
your friend,
you don't get rid of me
that easy.
Beezle.
[fantasy music]
Where am I now?
West Wind?
[Unico] Where are you?
And who are you?
Oh!
Uh?
So, I'm all alone again.
What do I do now?
[cheerful music]
Huh?
♪ My ribbon's red
My whisker's long ♪
♪ My paws as white as snow ♪
♪ And everyday
I sing this song ♪
...What's that?
♪ No matter where I go ♪
♪ I'm a cat ♪
♪ And that is why I
Sing a song ♪
♪ A song of meow, meow, meow ♪
♪ Sing a song ♪
Oh!
Huh! What's this?
[cat] What do you mean
by blocking my way?
Let go of me, let go!
Oh!
Oh.
I'm free. Here we go.
♪ La la la, la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la ♪
♪ And everyday
I sing this song ♪
♪ No matter where I go ♪
Oh bother!
Oh, here we go again!
[cat grunting]
What do I do now?
Oh, let go, let go,
let go, let go!
Oh! Hey!
Oh! [shouts]
This is too much!
What do you mean by dropping
into my house boat?
[grunting]
Oh.
I thought I was going to fall
into the river.
Oh, have you know
you fell into my home?
Hmm.
Where you abandoned here too?
Well, of all the nerve.
Who in their right mind
would abandon a beautiful kitty
like me?
[meows]
What's the matter?
[cries softly]
[stuttering] It's true.
[crying] I was abandoned.
[meowing]
[soft music]
You know...
oh the whole thing was a serious
blow to my self-esteem.
I really thought
that they loved me.
But I don't care,
because what I really want to be
-is a witch.
- What?
I'd rather be a witch
than a cat any day.
I know just what I'd do
with my magic.
If anybody made me angry,
I'd just sap him,
and turn him into
a fish's feedstock.
In fact, I'm on my way
to find a witch right now.
But how do you know
where to go looking
for a witch?
Oh, that's easy.
I read all about it in a book.
[dramatic music]
♪ A magical broom
And a magical hat ♪
♪ I'm Caty the kitty witch ♪
♪ So if you have a need
A magical cat ♪
♪ Caty is the kitty to call ♪
♪ There are all kinds of cats ♪
♪ Some are wicked
some are good ♪
♪ And I know more magic
Than a good cat should ♪
♪ Wave your hands and shout
You won't scare me away ♪
♪ I'll do what I want
To you anyway ♪
♪ Moonlight or sunlight
There's magic to do ♪
♪ I'm Caty the kitty witch ♪
♪ If a red ribbon bow
is appealing to you ♪
♪ Caty's the kitty to call ♪
[animated music]
♪ I'll make clouds out of candy
With a wave of my hand ♪
♪ Wonderful powers
I'll have my command ♪
♪ Call out my name
Any time that you'd choose ♪
♪ I'll blow you above
Of full of ruby red shoes ♪
♪ When night's fallen
And the world's in bed ♪
♪ And you're feeling all alone ♪
♪ Remember the magical things
That I've said ♪
♪ Caty is the kitty to call ♪
♪ Caty's the kitty to call ♪
[animals screeching]
[calm music]
What?
This must be some kind
of a magic forest.
It looks just like the ones
in my picture book.
Look, there's a perfect place
to land.
Come on, Unico!
We're going to find ourselves
a witch.
Oh, well.
You really think
we'll find a witch?
You don't believe it?
Well, that's alright.
I'm perfectly capable of going
on by myself.
[hoots]
-[screams]
- [laughs]
Nothing.
What's wrong with you?
Are you a scary cat?
I happen to think
that at a time like this,
it's perfectly proper for a lady
to call on a gentleman
for support.
[screaming]
Oh, it's all right.
Take a look.
[exciting music]
[Caty] Oh!
[Unico] It's only
somebody's house.
That's a witch's house.
How lucky!
[Unico] It's kind of a mess.
It doesn't look like
anybody lives here.
Oh no! I guess the witch
went away.
I know what. She probably went
to a witch's convention.
She hoped on her broom,
and didn't have time
to do any cleaning
before she left.
You know, I think you've read
too many fairy tales.
[sighs]
[Caty] She'll probably be back
anytime now.
We'll just wait for her.
I hope there's something to eat
around here.
I wonder what witches
eat anyway.
Ah! My favorite, favorite!
Yeah! I've got you now.
-You want one?
- No. I don't eat bugs,
and either should you,
they're disgusting.
But my stomach hurts.
I'm hungry. [cries]
I'll go and find something
for you to eat.
-Huh!
- Huh!
[Caty whimpers]
Oh! [groans]
Yeah! See, what I told you.
It's a witch, and she's comeback
just like I knew she would.
Oh! It's a dream come true.
Oh, that ledge seems
to get higher every day.
-[Caty meows]
- Oh, look at that!
What a pretty house guest
I have.
[woman] You'll be hungry
I suppose.
I'll fetch you something to eat.
-[Caty meowing]
- [Unico] No, Caty. Calm down.
She's not a witch.
She's just an old woman.
What're you talking about?
I know she's a witch,
and I bet she's going to feed us
a magical witchy food.
Let go!
[woman] Ah, there you are.
I suppose you're tummy
is pretty empty.
Here you go.
Just for you,
some fresh sweet potatoes.
[poignant music]
I must admit I expected
something a little more magical
than sweet potatoes.
Now do you believe me.
She's just an ordinary
old woman.
No, I'm positive she's a witch.
She's probably too tired
right now to use her magic,
and she's just resting up,
that's all.
[sighs]
You're kind of strange,
but you’re a very nice cat.
Well, of course,
of course I am perfectly aware
that I'm a very nice cat.
But it's not enough for me
to be a cat.
Just forget about being a witch.
And you'll be much happier.
But I want to be a witch
more than anything in the world.
Get lots of rest old woman,
so you can teach me your magic.
No, no, thank you.
I've had plenty.
-What?
- If I eat another sweet potato,
I'm afraid I'll burst.
You're not listening.
[snoring softly]
-Why don't you give it up?
- No, I won't give it up.
[cries]
A kitty cat magician,
wouldn't that kind of strange.
I know some who would
find it rather cute.
Hmm, I guess it could be.
Anyway, the first thing
I'm going to have her do
is to change me
into a human girl.
Hmm, imagine Caty as a real life
human girl.
[soothing music]
Hmm, I wish I could grant
her wish for her.
[bird song]
Hey, old woman,
are you rested now?
Will you please turn me
into a human girl now.
-Come on, please.
- Be patient little kitty.
I'll feed you as soon as
I'm done with the laundry.
[Caty] Come on. When are you
going to turn me into a girl.
[woman] Alright, alright.
I'll go out right now,
and dig up some sweet potatoes
for you.
Hmm.
[sighs] She acts as if she
doesn't understand me at all.
Maybe she's isn't
a witch after all.
Oh, I'm so unhappy.
[meows]
[Caty] Oh! Ah!
Oh, please make Caty's wish
come true.
[horn tinkles]
[magical music]
[Caty] Oh!
Oh! Oh.
Huh? Oh, I better hang this
back up.
Oh!
[quaint music]
Oh! Oh.
Oh. Oh!
Oh, I think I've become a human.
Oh.
Oh!
[groans]
Oh! [crying]
[crying continues] Oh, Unico!
[Caty] Unico, come here.
[happy music]
Oh, Unico look,
look what I've turned into.
Can you believe it?
The witch used her magic on me,
and I've turned
into a real girl.
So I see. And now you really
should pay her back
for the favor.
Of course. She's a real life
witch, and I'll do anything
she says. Ah, how thrilling!
-Old woman!
- Huh!
Oh, what on earth
are you doing here young lady?
[giggles] Stop pulling my leg.
Here, I think it's only right
that I give you a hand
around here while you're
teaching me your magic.
Uh-huh?
♪ My ribbon's red
My whisker's long ♪
♪ My paws as white as snow ♪
♪ And everyday
I sing this song ♪
♪ No matter where I go ♪
Oh, you no need to do that.
I'm perfectly...
Oh no, I'll do it.
I've to keep up my
end of the bargain, don't I.
Hmm-mmm.
♪ My ribbon's red
My whisker's long ♪
♪ My paws as white as snow ♪
Oh!
[playful music]
Oh, my favorite, favorite!
-[Caty meowing]
- [Unico] Huh!
Hmm.
Stop it! Young ladies don't
catch bugs in their hands.
[groans] Oh!
[Unico] You see Caty,
since you become a human girl,
you have to start acting
like a one.
Some fun.
Oh!
[laughing]
Oh dumb!
It's not fair that you speak
as I'm a human girl.
I have to do all the dirty work.
[Caty] I'm going to find out
what else human girls get to do.
Caty.
Hmm.
[groans] Oh!
Oh!
Caty.
Caty?
[Caty singing]
[Unico] Caty, you really
shouldn't be out here
-just doing nothing.
- Oh!
Why don't you mind
your own business,
you little snoop.
Caty, what's happened
to you anyway?
Well...
I've become a girl, that's what.
Well, that doesn't mean
you shouldn't help out.
She's a very old woman.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
After all, she's a witch.
She can take care of herself.
Caty, listen to me.
That old woman isn't a witch.
It was me who changed you.
What do you mean you changed me?
Because I liked you.
It was my magic that did it.
What're you talking about,
you silly? [chuckles]
If it was your magic,
why don't you turn me into a cat
right now. That I'd like to see.
Oh!
[meow] What have you done?
How dare you do this to me?
You better turn me back
into a girl right now.
I'm afraid I can't do it again.
And it's all your fault Caty.
Huh! What do you mean?
I can only do it when I like
the person that I'm with.
So, that means you don't like
me anymore.
[crying]
Well then, I guess I'll be
on my way.
Goodbye!
Caty, even if she isn't a witch,
she's still a very nice
old woman. You're not just
going to walk out on her,
are you?
I don't know.
I know that I shouldn't,
but I... I just have to find
a real witch somewhere.
[woman] I wonder where that nice
little girl went.
Back to her own home I suppose.
[meowing]
Oh, there you are Kitty.
Where have you been
all this time?
You missed seeing the nicest
little girl.
Maybe she'll be back tomorrow.
[woman sighs]
[meow]
[coughing]
[knocking]
Huh?
Oh, you've come back.
[bird pecking]
[sighs]
[groaning softly]
The poor old woman.
She looks so lonely.
[soft music]
[woman] Oh, stop it now kitty.
Stop making a mess.
Uh! I was only trying
to help you.
Isn't there anything I can do
to help you?
Oh!
Oh.
[shouts] Oh!
[woman] No, no, kitty.
You mustn’t get them dirty.
[groans]
Huh?
Oh no! Now, what am I going
to do now?
[groaning]
Oh!
[tense music]
Oh no! I'll save you.
[magical music]
-[woman groans]
- Ah!
[Caty grunting]
Oh!
Huh? Oh, I've turned
into a girl again.
Caty, you're wonderful
whether you're a cat or a girl.
Oh! Thank you Unico.
[sneezes]
♪ My ribbon's red
My whisker's long ♪
♪ My paws as white as snow ♪
♪ And everyday
I sing this song ♪
♪ No matter where I go ♪
♪ I'm a cat ♪
♪ And that is why I ♪
[gasps]
[charming music]
[man] You have a lovely voice.
Tell me, do you live here
in this forest?
Huh... yes.
Your name?
I... it's Caty.
Caty? A childish name.
Do you know who I am?
How could I know who you are?
This is the first time
we've ever met.
Of course.
She's rather an innocent,
or a simpleton and livid
more than a child.
I am the Baron the ghost.
I'm the lord of this forest.
Huh! Does that mean
you live around here?
Where is your home?
[stuttering] Well, it's right
over there.
Tomorrow night when the sun
goes down, there will be a party
at my castle.
I would like you to come there,
and sing for me.
But tell me, what about
the old woman who lives
in the house with me?
May I bring her along?
An old woman?
No, you must come alone.
And see that you tell
no one of this.
-I forbid it.
- Oh, alright.
Until tomorrow night.
[horse neighs]
He-yea!
He's so handsome.
Oh, it's all so thrilling!
I could just die, oh!
[imitating] Do you live here
in this forest?
No, I'm just a kitty cat.
Oh, I'm glad I didn't say that.
What do I do?
Oh, I don't know
what I should do.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
[exciting music]
Oh, oh!
Oh! [water splashes]
[wind whistling]
[whistling continues]
Oh.
[yawns]
[thunderstorm]
[mysterious music]
[horse galloping]
Huh? Uh.
Oh!
Huh.
[groaning]
Hmm.
Oh golly, today is the day
I've been invited
to the Baron's castle.
Hmm. Yahoo!
Unico? Huh!
Good, the coast is clear.
Huh?
Caty.
What's she doing?
Huh. [gasps]
-[chuckles] I did it. Here I...
- [Unico] Caty!
Oh!
Where are you going?
Oh! [laugh]
I'm going for a walk.
If I were you,
I wouldn't go for a walk
in there. The forest feels
very strange today.
I don't know why,
but I feel something bad
is about to happen.
Oh, what do you mean
something bad's about to happen?
I've been invited, oh!
I mustn't say another word.
He told me not to tell anyone.
I've got to find a way
to throw Unico off the track.
Caty is acting very strangely.
[animal crying]
Huh?
He's been badly hurt.
[laughs] Now's my chance
to get away.
[mischievous music]
I wonder which way I should go.
Oh look.
They look delicious.
Ha.
[hiccups]
[soft music]
[sighs]
Oh-oh!
I feel like almost
like I'm walking on air.
[hiccupping]
[monkey groans softly]
You're all better. [chuckles]
Be careful now.
Caty?
Where did she go to?
Oh no! Did she... go into
the forest?
[mysterious music]
[Caty] Hello... is anyone home?
Maybe they can't hear me.
Oh!
[royal music]
Golly!
What a beautiful place!
It makes me want to dance.
[humming]
[Baron] Welcome, Caty!
[eerie music]
My dear, you look particularly
lovely tonight.
Oh!
Caty?
[Unico] This place sure gives me
the willies.
Uh-huh?
[shouts]
I'm jammed, I can't get out.
Oh.
[horn tinkles]
[grunting]
[invigorating music]
[shouting]
[whimpering]
[screaming]
Where did she go?
Huh? What's that?
A castle way out here?
I'd better investigate.
[royal music]
I don't like the feeling
of this place at all.
Remember, you were invited here
to sing me a song.
Wet your throat with a drop
of this wine,
and I promise you'll sing
as never before.
Huh.
Hmm, it smells lovely.
[slurps]
Ah.
Have another.
[hiccups]
Drink Caty. Drink as much
as you like.
[cheerful music]
This place is huge.
[Caty laughing]
[Caty] I feel wonderful.
[Unico] That's Caty's voice.
I'd like another,
please. [laughs]
Huh? Caty's having far too much
to drink.
[hiccups] No more wine?
What do we do now?
Now it's time for you to sing
me your song, Caty.
Yes, yes of course.
[stutters] Oh. Here's my song.
♪ My ribbon's red
My whisker's long ♪
♪ My eyes as white as snow ♪
♪ And every day ♪
And every... oh, and every.
♪ Oh every day
I sing this song ♪
♪ No matter where I go
I'm a cat ♪
♪ And that is why I ♪
... She doesn't know
what she's doing.
Oh, I learnt that stupid song
from a little cat
I used to know.
I never liked him much.
Do you have any fish, sir?
I'm hungry.
Oh! [groans softly]
[laughs] What a peculiar girl!
[casual music]
I hope your dreams are pleasant.
They are the last
you’ll ever have.
Oh!
[gasps]
[scary music]
He is a Oman!
[piano notes]
[Unico panting]
What's that noise?
Caty, wake up!
You go to wake up Caty.
Huh, if it isn't Unico.
Hurry. He'll be coming back
at any moment.
[hiccups] Oh.
Oh, I hope he does.
Hurry Caty. You've got to get up
right now. Oh!
Caty, we've got to get out
of here.
[shouts]
Oh.
[exciting music]
Come on! Move, move.
Hmm?
Little girl,
where have you gone?
[groans]
Oh!
[Unico] Caty, wake up!
We're not out of it yet.
Wake up.
[ominous music]
[shouts]
What do you think
you're doing here?
You!
[screams]
[epic music]
What sort of creature is this?
-Yeah!
- [grunts]
[both grunting]
[shouting]
[screaming]
[groans]
[sinister laughter]
[Caty] Unico!
Caty.
Oh, Beezle.
West Wind.
[water splashing]
[humming]
I'm... bored.
Huh?
[fantasy music]
Hey, there you are!
You come on God here, right now!
You're the one who took Unico
away from me.
[Beezle] Do you hear me?
You've got to tell me
where Unico is?
-Where is he? Where is he, huh?
- Unico is in danger.
What do you mean he's in danger?
What do you mean?
He's in great danger.
I'm on my way to him even now.
And I must hurry.
Ah, well, then I'm going too.
Unico is the only friend
I ever had.
You got to take me with you!
[gasps] It can't be.
Darkness is falling.
At any moment,
the Night Wind will be upon us.
If we're going to save him,
we got to get moving.
So be it.
I must take you
with me, little one.
[laughs] Oh, hurray!
Come on, let's make tracks.
She's moving faster than we are.
There is no way we can escape.
[West Wind gasps]
[Night Wind laughing]
[thrilling music]
Look! I can see daylight
up ahead.
Hurry up! We're almost there.
[groans]
They've passed the boundaries
of my domain.
I am powerless before the light
of day.
[Beezle] We're coming Unico.
When darkness come again,
the Night Wind will return.
I must carry Unico far away
from this place.
Look, down there.
[Beezle] Unico!
Unico!
[groaning softly]
[happy music]
Beezle, is that really you?
Of course it is,
you little runt.
Who do you think it was, huh?
[laughing]
Oh, where's Caty?
What happened to her?
Caty? Caty?
He must have taken her
back into the castle.
Huh! So, this is the greeting
I get?
And after I came all this way.
Beezle, how did you get
here anyway?
[laughs]
-She brought me.
- Who?
West Wind!
Unico, the Gods know
where you are now.
You must come away with me.
Huh? I can't.
Nothing has changed.
If they find you,
they will send you
to the hill of oblivion.
No, I can't go with you yet.
I can't leave this place
until I've saved Caty.
There's no time for that.
Come, hurry!
Wait here. I'll be back soon.
Oh, Unico!
Hey, wait for me.
Whoa!
[sniffs]
You know... this place...
is kind of creepy.
[Caty] Unico!
[energetic music]
-Unico!
- Oh no! Caty!
Huh?
[crack of thunder]
[gasps] There's something rotten
about that guy.
Let her go!
Where's he going?
Hey, you don't stand a chance.
Come back! Hey!
Yeah!
[shouting]
[screaming]
Oh!
[shouting]
[loud rumbling]
[whimpers]
[thunderstorm]
Oh well. Here goes nothing.
Unico, don't just stand there.
Get a move on. Come on!
[Beezle] Don't mind me lady.
I'm just a friend of his.
Come on!
[eerie music]
-Whoa!
- Panting.
Whoa!
[thunderstorm]
[loud rumbling]
[roaring]
Wow! That guy is even meaner
looking than my dad.
[all shouting]
[shouting continues]
Oh!
[loud explosion]
[all panting]
Quick, grab on!
[groaning]
[shouting]
[gasps] The old woman!
She's in danger.
[sighs] That young lady.
Where could she have gone?
All the animals of the forest
will be destroyed.
Beezle, look after Caty.
No, Unico!
Have you gone crazy?
Come back!
[exciting music]
[Unico groaning]
[shouting]
[grunting]
-[Unico wailing]
- Oh no, Unico!
Ah! Lightning, come to me!
[roaring]
Uh-oh!
[screaming]
[coughs]
[grunts]
[thrilling music]
[roaring]
[shouting]
[shouting continues]
Unico!
[Caty] Unico?
[crying]
Oh, no Unico,
I won't let you die. [sobbing]
[somber music]
[crying]
I'll give up being a human girl.
Just open your eyes.
[sobbing]
And I don't need
this stupid horn.
Look, I'll give it back to you.
Please open your eye.
[magical music]
Oh!
[shouts]
[epic music]
Thank you, Caty and Beezle.
I'm only able to take
on this form
because you've proven
that you truly love me.
Ah!
Oh Unico, Unico,
you're absolutely beautiful!
[exhilarating music]
[roars]
[loud rumbling]
-I don't believe it.
- Look at that.
[calm music]
[birds screeching]
[Caty and Beezle laughing]
Oh, I forgot about
the old woman.
I hope she's alright.
Unico, come on!
Get a move on!
It's all over now, Unico.
The Night Wind
will be here soon.
We must hurry.
[West Wind] Come, come now.
Caty, Beezle.
Goodbye.
[panting] Hello!
[emotional music]
-[Caty] Oh! [crying]
- Oh!
There you are.
I'll never leave you again.
Never.
[sobbing]
That's kind of sweet.
What the devil happened
to Unico?
Hey!
Hey, Unico!
Unico!
Where are you?
He wouldn't have gone again,
would he?
Are you ready to go Unico?
Caty... I hope you'll be
happy here.
Come to think of it,
whatever became
of that black kitty,
and that strange animal
with a little horn.
Oh, he'll be coming back,
don't you worry.
He saved my life, you know.
He used magic to do it.
He turned into a great
white horse with white wings,
and he flew into the sky,
-and killed the monster.
- A white horse with wings?
[happy music]
Then he was...
he was... a unicorn
without a doubt.
[woman] I've heard tales
of such a little unicorn
who has the wonderful gift
of bringing happiness
to any life he touches.
But, they say the little unicorn
is forbidden to stay for long
with those he has made happy.
What? What're you saying?
I can't believe that.
I won't let him go. I won't!
-Unico!
- No. Don't call for him,
my child. It won't do any good.
Neither he nor you
has any choice.
He must go away.
But he will protect
and watch over you from afar.
[gasps]
[yells] Unico!
Unico!
Where did you go to?
Oh! Oh, no, no, not again!
You can't take him away again.
[horn tinkles]
Whoa!
Hey, I don't want a horn.
I just want to go with you.
Take me with you.
Unico!
You can't get away from me.
I'll follow wherever you go.
Goodbye, Beezle.
[Caty] Unico!
Goodbye, Caty.
[bittersweet music]