[MARI]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[MARI] Our brillante
performance at the prelims
qualified Aqours for the
final round of Love Live!
[RIKO]
It's over?
This is really the end?
[MARI] But then we couldn't
get enough applicants
and the school merger
became final.
Our group took it pretty hard,
especially Chika-chi.
[YOSHIMI] You can preserve
our school's name.
You're the only
hope we have left!
[CHIKA]
You better believe!
We'll leave our school's
name in Love Live history!
We'll immortalize our
school and our memories!
[RIKO]
So cold...
I can't see!
The snow's too thick!
I don't think I can go on.
But we have to
keep movin', zura!
It's like a snow globe!
Bellissima ...
Don't go into the light, okay?
Come on, snow! Do your worst!
Yoshiko?
Yohane!
I'll dodge it! I'll dodge it!
[YOSHIKO groans]
I'm getting kind of tired.
Right there with you.
No! Wake up!
If you fall asleep out
here, you'll both die!
This is just a crazy dream!
A dream.
It has to be, because
there's no possible way
it could snow this
hard in Uchiura.
Well if that's the case
then I'll close my eyes,
and when I open them,
I'll be back home again!
Or not.
Because we're in...
[YOU, RIKO]
...Hokkaido!
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Wow!
I can't believe we're
really in Hakodate!
[KANAN] I never thought we'd be
watching someone else's prelims.
And as honored guests, too!
Brr, I'm cold.
Poor thing.
Maybe you should try
wearing more layers?
[YOSHIKO]
Enough standing around!
Come, little demon, Lilli!
Uh...
Let's... journey
forth, into the--
Oh no!
[YOSHIKO groans]
[RUBY] You should
probably wear shoes
that have better traction.
Sì, those shoes are terible !
Weather like this requires...
[BOTH]
...these!
Now our feet are toasty-warm!
You're always so prepared, sis!
[BOTH] With these
shoes, we can take on
even the biggest snow heap!
See, it's no problem at all--
--[RUBY squeals]
--[KANAN sighs]
--[RUBY] Are you okay?
--[DIA] Great, now I'm freezing!
[MARI]
My, my legs are stuck!
[HANAMARU]
Thanks for waitin', zura!
It took some work
but I'm finally warm!
[RUBY]
Hanamaru...?
I mean, I can barely move
but at least I'm not
cold anymore, y'know?
The heck is she wearing?
Oh no, I don't
think I can stop, zura!
[RUBY, YOSHIKO, YOU scream]
Ouchie.
[YOU, YOSHIKO, RUBY whine]
[HANAMARU]
I'm so sorry!
[chuckles]
[SCHOOL IDOLS chatter]
[YOU]
Hey! This is the place!
[RIKO]
Talk about a big crowd!
[CHIKA]
Cool! There's Saint Snow!
[RIKO] And it looks like
they're an event favorite!
[RUBY]
Wow.
Really.
Well if that's the case, then
I shall watch their performance
and pass my own judgement.
[IDOL A]
Excuse me,
but, you're the school
idol group Aqours, right?
Uh-huh.
Uh, would it be okay...
if we... maybe...
What I mean is, can we
take a picture with you?
Whoa, hold on a second!
Everyone just needs
to calm down, 'kay!
Um, you're the only
one freaking out.
[RUBY squeals]
[IDOL B]
Thank you so much!
I'm rooting for you!
Good luck at Love Live!
[CHIKA]
Thanks for your support!
Have a great day!
I guess advancing to the
final round's a big deal.
[YOU] Well yeah, in the
grand scheme of things.
[CHIKA]
For sure.
[knocking]
[CHIKA]
Hello, is anyone here?
Um, we just wanted to
say hi to Saint Snow.
[SARAH]
Come on in!
Hello, it's good
to see you again.
[RIKO] Sorry to intrude
right before your performance.
[SARAH]
Don't worry about it.
I'm glad you ladies
will get to see it.
Especially since it will
be a while before we all
compete in the final round.
Yeah, we're looking
forward to it!
[YOSHIKO]
Seriously?
They act like they know
they're going to the final.
They've got quite a
bit of confidence.
They also have a lot of
gifts and food, zura!
[RUBY]
That's not surprising.
After all, they did have
an overwhelming victory
in last year's prelims.
Which is impressive,
but it could also be that
Saint Snow is just
trying to show off.
Kind of like you did
last year, remember?
[SARAH]
No, that's not our intention.
Besides, I seriously
doubt there's
anything we could do that
would phase you all now.
What that's supposed to mean?
[SARAH] Well, Aqours
has improved remarkably
since the last prelims.
You've now moved on to be
one of the Love Live favorites.
We're... the favorites?
We were rude when we first met.
I'm so sorry.
Uh, no worries.
[CHIKA gasps]
We will see you again
at the finals.
Promise me something.
Make it a show that goes
down in Love Live history.
[YOU]
Chika.
You gotta shake her hand
to accept the challenge!
Go for it!
Hey, Leah.
Come say hello to everyone.
Leah!
[CHIKA]
It's okay.
We should let you
finish getting ready.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[CHIKA]
Wow!
Listen to all that cheering!
There's not a single
open seat here!
Actually, this is a
great opportunity.
We can learn how
we appear on stage
from the audience's
point of view.
And it'll give us some insight
on what entertains everyone,
so we can apply it to
our own performance.
Good idea!
When is Saint Snow going up?
According to the program,
they should be next.
It's starting!
[musica plays]
Go Saint Snow,
break a leg girls!
[IDOLS gossiping]
[YOU]
That was unexpected.
[RIKO] I still can't
believe it even happened.
[YOU]
Well, it is Love Live.
[RIKO]
I suppose,
and a mistake like that
is hard to bounce back from.
[YOSHIKO] Wait, do you
think that sort of thing
could happen to us?
[HANAMARU]
Absolutely, zura.
[CHIKA] But now
Saint Snow won't be able to
advance to the final round.
They must be heartbroken.
[knocking]
[IDOL C]
You can come in.
[CHIKA]
Sorry to intrude.
[IDOL B] If you're
looking for Saint Snow,
they left a little while ago.
There's supposed to be a
send-off party after this
for groups going to
the Love Live finals.
Yeah, and Sarah told us
that they'd meet us here,
but I guess they didn't
feel like staying.
Something seemed off
about them today.
[IDOL A] You mean, like how
Leah barely said a word all day?
[IDOL C]
I know right?
I've never seen them
like that before.
[IDOL C] They were so shaken
they couldn't even sing.
[IDOL A]
You know what else?
I think they were
fighting about something.
Still thinking about them?
[CHIKA]
Yeah.
[RIKO] They've been performing
together all this time.
But they slipped up
and had a fight.
It's so sad.
I agree.
I dunno, maybe this is a bad
time for us to go see them.
[YOSHIKO] For sure, what if
it's all awkward and stuff?
True, but even though
we feel bad for them
there's nothing we can do.
Yeah, you've got a point.
They're both strong girls,
they'll be okay.
They are sisters after all.
[CHIKA]
Mm-hm.
[MARI] Well then, I vote
that we go back to the hotel
and get settled in.
[KANAN] I heard the weather
will be better tomorrow,
so maybe we could do
some sight-seeing.
[YOSHIKO] Perfect! I can recruit
some new demons while we're out!
[HANAMARU]
Rejected, zura.
[YOSHIKO]
No fair!
[GIRLS]
Wow!
Amazing! So cool!
It's weird, but this view
kind of makes me hungry.
Indeed, it is amazing.
At long last,
I've finally discovered
the magic circle
I've been dreaming of!
Great, here we go.
Silence, you!
With this, I'll be
able to summon
the legendary,
colossal little demon!
That doesn't make sense.
Is it colossal or little?
It can't be both.
So cool.
It's not like we're
that high up.
[KANAN whimpers]
[DIA]
Hey! What's wrong?
[MARI] Wow, someone's
in the hugging mood!
[DIA] I don't think
that's it, Mari.
[CHIKA]
It's so relaxing here.
In a way, it kind of
reminds me of Uchiura.
It does.
They're both right on the ocean
and have the scent of
sea water in the air.
There's even a school
at the top of the hill.
[RIKO] It's funny how
places so far apart
can still be so
similar, you know?
[HANAMARU]
Thanks for waiting, zura!
[RUBY yells]
[YOU]
Not again!
Why are you wearing
so many layers?
[RUBY, YOSHIKO, YOU scream]
[RUBY]
My leg...
Anyone else have
déjà vu right now?
[CHIKA]
Brr, It's so cold.
[MARI] I say we
get some tea, then!
[CHIKA]
Sounds good!
[HANAMARU] I can't go on!
Clothes too heavy...
[YOSHIKO]
That's your own fault!
[CHIKA]
Whale soup?
[YOU]
That's unique.
[HANAMARU]
Zura?
Are you open?
Anyone here?
That's weird.
The sign says they're open.
[wind howling]
Well can we at least go inside
to figure it out, zura?
I guess we could.
Right, we're coming inside!
Brr, I can't wait
to get warm, zura.
[YOSHIKO] Zuramaru, take off
some of those layers, first!
[KANAN]
Here, let me help you.
[HANAMARU]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
[HANAMARU sighs]
Uh?
[GIRLS chattering]
--[MARI] It all looks so yummy!
--[GIRLS chattering]
[DIA]
Some hot soup would be divine.
[GIRLS chattering]
[LEAH crying]
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[RIKO]
Wow! It's so pretty!
It looks super tasty!
It'll warm you up in no time.
Don't let me keep
you from eating!
Thank you so much.
Your restaurant has
such a relaxing ambience.
For sure.
And your uniform is adorable!
Such a heavenly flavor.
It must be from
the divine sphere!
I'm ready for seconds!
[YOSHIKO]
Slow down!
I kind of expected for you
ladies to stop by our school,
but this was a nice surprise.
Yeah, sorry.
Funny story, we were out
doing some sight-seeing,
and we just kinda found you.
You live in such
a beautiful town.
Everything is so
calm and romantic.
That's sweet of you to say.
My sister and I both
really love our town.
So when we become adults,
we're going to
take over running the restaurant
and live here together.
You will?
[DIA]
I'm sorry about yesterday.
About your show.
Oh, that. It's fine.
Just finish your
food and get out.
What?
Leah! You're being rude!
Don't tell them what you saw,
or you'll be sorry.
[squeaks]
[SARAH]
Leah!
I'm sorry.
I guess she's still pretty upset
over what happened yesterday.
It's understandable. Well...
We heard you two got in a huge
fight right before the show--
[HANAMARU]
Hmph.
O-Oh, it's okay.
That's Love Live for you.
Things like that happen.
I don't have any regrets.
Next time, I'm sure
Leah will nail it.
[footsteps]
--[LEAH] No!
--[RUBY gasps]
I've made up my mind, sis!
I don't wanna be a school idol.
I'm seriously quitting.
Saint Snow is
officially disbanded.
[SARAH]
Are you sure?
You're only a first year.
You still have another chance!
[LEAH]
Yes. I'm positive.
I don't want anything to do
with Love Live or school idols.
[gasps]
[SARAH] We didn't mean to
make a scene during your meal.
I'm sorry.
[HANAMARU]
It's the future, zura.
No way.
Are you gonna unhinge your jaw?
Zura!
[YOSHIKO]
Hey, let me try a bite.
[HANAMARU]
Get your own!
[YOSHIKO] Don't be so
greedy! I'll share...
I don't get why she
wants to quit over it.
Well, for one thing,
if she continued,
she'd have to do
so alone, right?
No, she could always
recruit some new members!
Except it's not really
that simple to Leah, is it?
I guess not. Huh.
We've been in their
position before, though.
[KANAN] In the end, a mistake
that was made on stage,
can only be fixed on stage.
[DIA] But, feelings
aren't that simple.
You can't expect Leah to just
shift gears and be happy again.
Maybe... she lost
some of her confidence.
[RUBY]
I don't think that's it.
[RUBY] It's because Sarah
won't be there anymore.
I think she doesn't
like the fact that
she can't be a school idol
with her big sister.
Leah only wants to sing...
if Sarah's by her side.
Ruby.
[RUBY squeals]
Really?
You think so?
That would make sense.
It would be lonely.
Hold on! What I meant was,
I kind of saw Leah
crying earlier and--!
Crying?
[squeaks]
[whimpers]
[RUBY cries]
[DIA]
What a pretty view.
So did you and Leah
talk at the restaurant?
[RUBY]
Mm-mm.
I just...
[RUBY] ...thought that
must be the case, is all.
Because, it's how I'm feeling.
Ruby.
Because I know, when the final
round is done, so is our time.
Well, we can't do
much about that.
[RUBY] But... being a school
idol has always been your dream,
and you've worked
so hard to be one.
And yet, it'll all be over soon.
True, but here's a secret.
I'm very happy.
Because of you, Ruby,
and all the rest of Aqours.
You see, you girls
are the reason
I was able to fulfill my
dream of being a school idol.
We're going to the
final round of Love Live,
to the Akiba Dome.
My dream has come true.
[RUBY]
I know, but still.
I wanna keep singing
with you, Dia!
[RUBY]
I wanna follow your lead.
I wanna dance by your side.
I wanna keep training
with my sister!
I don't wanna be left behind!
[RUBY cries]
You're growing up so quickly.
And, you're so beautiful
inside and out.
You think so?
What will you do
after the final round?
[RUBY]
I'm not sure.
All I really know is that
our school will close down,
and you and the rest of third
years will have graduated.
[DIA]
Yes, that's true.
What about you?
Dunno.
To be perfectly honest,
I just haven't given
it that much thought.
Right now, I'm just
trying to stay focused
and continue preparing
for Love Live.
[RUBY]
Yeah.
[DIA]
But, you know what?
[YOU]
Big sisters.
What are they like?
Um, it's kinda hard to explain.
Especially since I'm not like
particularly close with
my sisters or anything.
And yet, maybe we're
close after all.
[YOU]
How?
Do you remember
the first concert
we ever held at our school?
Mito actually came out in the
rain just to watch us perform.
When she showed up I almost
lost it then and there.
I was so happy to see her.
Oh, that's cool.
I guess it's just something I
don't really understand though.
Yeah, well me neither.
Because it's just the way
it's always been, you know?
Your older sisters are there
from the day you're born,
watching over you.
[door opens]
[YOSHIKO]
Hey, where's Ruby?
[HANAMARU]
She went out.
She said she had an
errand or somethin'.
Okay.
Hang on a second, that looks
exactly like the hamburger
we bought Ruby for dinner.
[HANAMARU]
She said she wasn't hungry.
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
Your doom is inevitable.
What's that even mean?
You'll see soon enough.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
[DIA]
But, you know what?
I still remember the day
when you told me that you'd
decided to become a school idol.
I was glad, and also
it made me proud,
because of what it
meant for you.
It meant you were growing up and
learning how to
think independently.
In the end, becoming a school
idol truly was your decision.
[RUBY]
Excuse me.
You again?
I'm Ruby.
Uh, Ruby Kurosawa.
If it's not too much trouble,
I'd like to talk to you.
It won't take long.
[LEAH]
Hey, where are you taking me?
And what'd you wanna talk about?
[LEAH]
I'm not done with work yet,
so can we hurry
whatever this is up?
[RUBY]
Oh, uh... well,
just like you do, Leah,
I have a big sister, too.
Dia Kurosawa.
[gasps] How'd you know?
Well, duh, obviously I would
research the competition.
Naturally, I found out that
my sister is way better.
Not only is she pretty,
but she can also sing and dance.
[RUBY whines]
My sister is just as good!
If anything, she's better
than your big sis.
She can't even do a backflip.
No, but she's so good at
classical Japanese dance
that she could teach it,
and she plays the koto, too!
That has nothing
to do with being an idol.
That's not remotely true!
And Kanan even told me
that the basics needed
are exactly the same!
Who cares? My sister is
still better than yours.
[RUBY]
I get it.
You really love
your sister, don't you?
Well yeah, of course I do.
What the heck is
up with you anyway?
Normally you never speak.
It's because I love my sister,
and she gives me strength.
You know what?
I learned that my
big sister is very happy.
Well, so she said.
About what?
[RUBY] Even if Dia and I
aren't doing things together,
if I work hard to achieve
something without her help,
she told me that it
makes her really happy.
That's why...
...I think Sarah must
feel the same way.
[LEAH]
You think I don't know that?
Oh, you do?
The thing is...
...I've been trying, and...
...I wanted to show her
that I'd be okay without her.
That she wouldn't have to worry.
[LEAH]
But I failed.
I messed up at
her last Love Live!
[LEAH sobs]
Then you just need to make sure
it's not your last
performance, right?
--[LEAH gasps]
--[RUBY giggles]
[LEAH]
Wait, what do you mean?
--[LEAH pants]
--[RUBY giggles]
[BOTH]
Wow!
[RUBY]
Why don't we sing together?
Let's make our own song.
We can dedicate it
to both of our sisters.
And then we'll sing it,
in this light!
[DIA, RUBY]
Next time, "Awaken the power."