[RUBY]
Are you nervous?
[LEAH]
Mm-mm.
[RUBY] It's strange,
but I feel surprisingly calm.
Maybe it's because
our sisters are here.
[LEAH] Of course
I agree with you there,
but there's
more to it than that.
I've only come this far
because of you, Ruby.
Leah...
[BOTH] This song is dedicated
to someone special.
[HANAMARU]
A concert?
[YOSHIKO]
In Hakodate?
[RUBY]
Mm-hm.
Leah and I want to
hold a concert together,
kind of like a live, but made
specially for Sarah and Dia.
By yourselves?
Well, yeah, that's the idea.
Honestly though,
I'm not sure what to do.
I just thought maybe
it would help cheer Leah up.
How will you prepare for it?
I don't know...
Hey, sounds interestin'!
Uh-huh.
Wha--
I'd be happy
to lend y'all a hand!
Really?
Okay then, Leah and I
were planning on meeting up
to hash out the details.
Wanna come?
[HANAMARU]
Mm-hm!
Thanks, Hanamaru!
[HANAMARU] Hey Yoshiko, do you
wanna come and help out, too?
Uh, you're asking me?
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
I don't know,
my schedule is very booked.
After all, recruiting
more demons for my cause
is actually
quite time consuming.
I suppose I could
pencil you in though--
[YOSHIKO whines]
[YOSHIKO] Just kidding!
Wait for me, Zuramaru!
[knocking]
Hey, Leah?
I need to do
some grocery shopping,
could you...
watch the restaurant...
Mm?
[ALL gasp]
Look, no offense, but...
I thought you'd be alone.
About that, you see
Hanamaru and Yosh--
I mean, Yohane said that
they wanted to help us out.
I don't care.
Don't take this
personally or anything.
I'm just not a people person.
I get it, I'm actually
the same way, zura.
And Yoshiko is the
poster-child for solitude, zura.
It's Yohane!
I can't believe you
badmouthed me so casually.
"Zura"?
[HANAMARU] Oh, I guess you could
say that's a habit of mine.
For real?
Yeah, I know it's weird, zura.
By habit, she means
she says it constantly.
That's why she
used to shut herself
in the library with Ruby.
Seriously?
Uh-huh.
I wasn't too social till
last spring rolled around
and I met the rest of Aqours.
That makes sense.
I'm shy, too.
Like around school and stuff.
[RUBY giggles]
You should have seen Yoshiko
when she first started,
she wouldn't even come to class!
[YOSHIKO] She doesn't need
a play by play, Zuramaru,
and it's Yohane!
[RUBY]
We're sorry, Yoshiko!
[YOSHIKO] Now you're just
doing it on purpose!
[RUBY]
"I won't give into failure,
no matter what happens."
[HANAMARU] "I shall
stand on that summit
alongside the one I love,
and yell out in triumph
so all the world
may hear me roar."
What's that look for?
I told you
Sarah's usually the one
who composes all of our music!
But we haven't even
said anything yet!
Well look, this is
just my opinion, but...
...I feel like the song
is too straightforward.
You got a problem with that?
[HANAMARU] Anyway, it at
least gives us a good idea of
what kind of song
you wanna sing.
Don't worry, together
I'm sure we'll be able to
make a wonderful song.
I appreciate that,
but shouldn't you be
more worried about Love Live?
You don't really have time
to help write a song.
I know, but...
[rustling]
[HANAMARU]
Here's the thing!
This song is as important
to Ruby as it is to you, zura.
[rustling]
Talking to you and my sis
made me realize something.
I thought maybe if we
showed them that we can do stuff
on our own, then they
wouldn't have to worry about us.
They'd both be able to
graduate high school
with some peace of mind.
--[phone buzzes]
--[rustling]
[YOSHIKO]
Oh no, it's from Lili!
She wants to know where we are
and why we're not packed
to go back home yet.
[gasps] And she's
suddenly telepathic, too!
We lost track of time!
[LEAH]
So what are you gonna do?
[HANAMARU]
Well, we are on winter break.
[LEAH]
Meaning?
[HANAMARU]
Here's the plan.
[KANAN]
The three of you are staying?
You see, with poor Leah
being so down in the dumps,
we thought maybe she needed
some extra moral support, zura.
That's right! So we thought
we'd hang out for a few days
and try to cheer her up!
[RUBY]
Yeah!
But where will you stay?
[HANAMARU] Leah said her room
is big enough for all of us,
so we're gonna bunk with her.
That sounds super fun!
I have to agree.
Maybe we should stay as well.
[RUBY] Uh, well, the thing is,
her room's not that big.
[HANAMARU]
Not to mention, Leah's in a very
delicate emotional state
right now, so, y'know!
Oh, I see.
I'm really sorry, sis.
But I promise we'll be back
in just a couple of days.
[sighs]
Whatever.
It's not like I care
if you stay or not.
I think it's a good idea.
Yeah, 'cause I'm sure the first
years can connect with Leah
better than we could
anyway, right?
[CHIKA]
I'm glad we went on this trip.
[RIKO]
Me too.
And honestly,
I never really thought about
how hard other school idols
must be working
to prepare for Love Live.
Yeah, it's pretty
inspiring, right?
It's fun meeting others
who share your passion.
[DIA whines]
[sighs] Oh, Ruby.
[KANAN] Are you sure
you didn't say something
that ticked her off, Dia?
No, I would never!
Something wrong?
We're just fine, thanks! Ha, ha!
Let's be honest though, it was
pretty obvious those three
were hiding something from us.
Sì , it's weird they'd wanna
stay behind with Saint Snow,
am I right?
[MARI gasps]
Wait, don't tell me!
Sorry sis, but the truth is...
We are descending from Aqours.
Yeah, and now!
[ALL] Saint Aqours Snow
will be our new idol group!
Boop boop! Say it isn't so!
Please don't shout!
Jeez, calm down, Dia.
Sì , it's joke!
[CHIKA] I don't think
that's what's going on.
I think they're... prob'ly...
Probably what?
[CHIKA]
Hm...
Never mind.
I'm sure it'll all
be revealed soon enough.
[DIA]
No fair!
[RUBY]
So this your room, Leah?
Make yourselves at home.
Just don't touch anything.
[HANAMARU]
Whoa!
Check it out!
--[footsteps]
--[RUBY gasps]
What did I just tell you?!
Is that a snow crystal?
It is.
My sister and I
used to try and catch them
back when we were little kids.
Then we decided we wanted to
form an idol group together.
At that point, we both knew
that a snow crystal
would be the perfect symbol
to represent us,
and that's how
Saint Snow was born.
[LEAH]
And yet...
...I ruined her
last chance at Love Live.
[RUBY]
It's very pretty.
Well, naturally!
Sarah's the one
who bought it for me.
That's why she's
better than your sister.
[RUBY grumbles] Whatever,
Dia has great fashion sense
and puts together super cute
outfits that look perfect on me!
Sarah's great too,
and her clothes are
so much cuter
than Dia's could ever be!
No, they are not!
--[RUBY] Uh...
--[LEAH] Right.
I've never seen Ruby
argue before.
Yeah, it's kind of cool!
Oh, I'm sorry.
You can't imagine
how worked up this girl gets
when it comes to her sister.
Maybe, but...
you're that way too, Leah.
[LEAH]
Well, you're not wrong.
[ALL laugh]
[knocking]
[door opens]
Uh, sorry,
but is it true that you three
don't have to go back home yet?
Yes, that's right.
Uh, it might sound crazy,
but we actually have somethin'
really important to do and
the other members of our group
asked us to handle it.
Oh, I see.
And thank you again.
We're very grateful
for your hospitality.
It's no trouble, in fact it's
a pleasure to have you here.
If you need anything at all,
be sure to let me know.
[YOSHIKO]
We'll do that.
[door shuts]
See? That's how
it's done, ladies.
I can't believe my eyes.
Yoshiko was acting so normal!
It's Yohane!
Besides, one of us
had to act like a normal person
because if I'd
left it up to you two,
you'd have blown our cover!
Fallen angels happen to be
quite excellent at
blending into society.
Everyone has an
unexpected side, zura.
Um, you could at least
acknowledge my magical ability!
[HANAMARU]
Is that what you're calling it?
You might be onto something.
[LEAH]
Uh?
[RUBY] I've always felt like
the other members of Aqours
thought I was kind of helpless,
but lately I wanted to show them
that I can be strong, too.
'Cause deep down,
I think we all possess
a special kind of hidden power.
Right! Then it's all decided!
[RUBY]
Um, what is?
The theme of the song,
of course!
[MARI] What do you mean
they're staying longer?
[DIA]
They called earlier and said
they needed a little more time.
Seriously? Do you think
they're gonna
form a new school idol group
after all?
[DIA sighs]
I wouldn't put anything
past that fallen angel, Yohane.
I can't tell if you're joking.
[CHIKA]
Don't worry!
I bet they're just fine.
[YOU]
Oh yeah?
The other day it seemed like
you knew what was going on.
[KANAN]
Did they tell you something?
[CHIKA]
Nothing in particular.
Huh?
[CHIKA]
It's just a feeling that I have.
Like maybe there's something
they're trying to do
on their own.
[RUBY] "Once I've decided
to do my best."
[LEAH] The next line is
"I definitely won't lose."
[RUBY]
And then, we could do...
[LEAH]
Try this.
[RUBY]
That looks good.
[LEAH]
Then...
[RUBY]
Let's end it here.
We're finished!
Yup. This looks solid!
[BOTH laugh]
[BOTH]
Hooray!
Be quiet!
[YOSHIKO, HANAMARU mumbling]
[LEAH, RUBY giggle]
[RUBY]
Now.
[LEAH]
We just have to register.
[YOSHIKO]
So you have to be approved
in order to participate?
[LEAH]
Yes.
We have to explain the content
so they can decide
whether or not it's
suitable for the event.
Listen,
I'm not very good when
it comes to things like
talking with strangers.
I'm not either.
But you're up next.
[LEAH]
I always get really nervous
without my sister around.
I know it's tough, but you both
have to do this on your own.
Don't let your hard work
go to waste, zura.
Right, we'll try.
[CHRISTMAS EVENT STAFF]
We're ready for the next entry.
[BOTH]
Let's go. We can do this!
[LEAH]
Good afternoon.
[RUBY] So I... I mean...
the two of us are here...
Dia, help.
[BOTH giggling]
C'mon, hurry up!
[RUBY giggles]
[RUBY squeals]
[RUBY cries]
[RUBY]
Dia, help!
Ruby, you cry over everything.
Hey, you'll be okay,
now be a big girl
and show me your courage.
[RUBY]
That's right.
Oh, Dia.
You've always had my back
when I needed you most.
I can't give up.
We're school idols.
Although our groups
live far apart,
the two of us have decided that
we would like to sing together.
We'd like to put on a show for
the upcoming Christmas event,
and perform a song
we both created.
A song that's dedicated
to our loved ones.
[YOSHIKO crying]
[HANAMARU] I can't believe
you're cryin', zura.
Whatever, like you
have any room to talk.
Zura.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[HANAMARU]
You were both so amazin'
during the selection process!
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
Leah, I hearby grant
thee the title of
Little Demon Number Ten.
Wow, lucky me.
I just hope we didn't
bite off more than we can chew.
What if we can't deliver?
We had no choice!
If we didn't promise them
a giant crowd,
there's no way they
would've picked our group.
Okay, say no more!
I can always summon
my little demons for you--
[HANAMARU]
Which demons, exactly?
[YOSHIKO]
Silence!
Wait, are you eating again?
[HANAMARU]
What's it to you, zura?
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
The signs of your doom
are everywhere.
[HANAMARU]
Yoshiko.
Allow me to explain.
A school idol must always be
--[HANAMARU] Yoshiko.
--conscious about her weight.
--[RUBY] Yoshiko.
--So don't come crying to me--
Would you stop it!
My name is Yohane!
[OTHERS sigh]
What about your signs?
You're just as doomed.
Eh--
[LEAH] No offense, but it is
getting pretty noticeable.
[YOSHIKO yells]
You're mean!
That really hurt!
Oh yeah, did you ever
get a hold of Mari
to ask for her help, zura?
[RUBY] Mm-hm! She actually
just got back to me.
And she said not to worry,
they would handle
everything with Dia.
To Hakodate?
Sì , we need you to
bring those girls back home.
We recently found out
that those three are
too scared to be
by themselves after all.
Seriously? Heh.
I suppose I could
go rescue them.
[EVENT STAFF] Today, we're
highlighting some performers
for the Christmas Festival!
Uh...
We're going by
Saint Aqours Snow--
Okie dokie then, say hello!
[RUBY squeaks]
That name seems
a little straight forward.
Here's a fun fact, in the north
there's a night where...
Go ahead and make
the announcement!
We're going to hold a
concert Christmas Eve.
Ah, right!
Please come, zu--
I-I mean come, zura.
Ah, I messed up.
Please come zura us.
Oh.
[HANAMARU sighs]
I ruined everythin'.
Aw, don't sweat it, Hanamaru.
[gasps]
[HANAMARU]
It's those same girls.
[RUBY]
Who are they?
[LEAH]
My classmates.
Why are you hiding from them?
Because, I've never really
spoken to them before.
[RUBY] There's gonna be
a Saint Snow Concert!
And Leah's going to sing!
Wow, really?
Would it be okay
if we came to watch?
Of course.
I know it's late,
but I'm sorry about Love Live.
I messed up.
[CLASSMATE A]
No worries.
We're really sorry for you, too.
We wanted to come
see the performance,
but we thought
you didn't like us, y'know?
Everyone's still
super proud of you.
We know that you and Sarah
worked extra hard.
We love Saint Snow, all of us.
You're our school's
pride and joy.
[CLASSMATE B]
So you'll be performing
in the Christmas Festival?
Everyone wants to come see it,
if that's all right?
[LEAH cries]
[CLASSMATE B]
Don't cry!
[RUBY]
It's so strange,
but even when you're happy
you can still cry.
[RUBY]
I can't wait to see Dia again.
[DIA]
Sarah?
Hello. What are you doing here?
Uh, well.
It may sound odd,
but I was told to come here.
[SARAH]
Oh?
What a coincidence, so was I.
What is this?
Well, it's a present.
Yeah, for Christmas.
Leah and I are going to
hold a concert on Christmas Eve.
[LEAH]
We're taking the stage
with a number
we wrote ourselves,
using everything you taught us.
We wanted to show you
that we'll be okay.
[LEAH]
So you don't have to worry.
[HANAMARU]
'Scuse me.
My little demons would like
to come watch the concert, too.
Hey, you better not be
referring to us!
[RUBY]
Chika. Everyone!
What a surprise.
Mari offered to pay for the
plane tickets for us so, ta-da.
That's how we got here.
Well I had to!
I couldn't bear to miss out
on such a grande event!
You've got a big heart, huh?
Yoshiko's got
a big everything, zura.
Hey!
[GIRLS laugh]
[LEAH]
Sarah.
[RUBY]
Dia.
[LEAH, RUBY] Will you come
watch our special concert?
It'd mean so much.
Of course.
I can't wait.
[YOU]
Aw!
I wonder what the event
will be like?
[RIKO giggles]
Can't wait to find out!
Well okay.
I guess it's about time
to go and get ready
for the next
big surprise then, huh?
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
Though it's only
a surprise to those two.
The costumes are perfect, zura.
[giggles]
If their show is
as awesome as this view,
then we're all in for a treat!
Hey, Sarah!
And Dia!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Just you wait,
we'll shine brighter
than every star in the sky!
All for you two!
[BOTH]
Merry Christmas!
[music plays]
[singing in Japanese]
[LEAH]
Hey, sis.
I've thought about it,
and I'm going to
quit Saint Snow after all.
Huh?
[LEAH] Because, that's a memory
you and I made together.
Just like a snow crystal, there
can be only one Saint Snow.
But I was thinking, maybe I
could find a new snow crystal
by creating a different group.
It'll be a school idol group
that you and everyone will love.
One that you'll
be proud to watch.
Wait and see!
Right.
[SARAH]
Not long ago,
Leah would have been too shy
to sing with someone new,
but lately she's really matured.
[DIA] I guess our sisters aren't
little kids anymore, are they?
[SARAH]
Nope.
[DIA]
They're spreading their wings,
and that's something
worth celebrating.
[DIA, MARI, KANAN] Next time,
"Finding a Way to Shine."