[YOSHIKO]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[YOSHIKO] We journeyed to
the promise land in the north,
and there, Ruby and Leah decided
to perform a dark ritual.
[LEAH]
Good afternoon.
[RUBY] So I... I mean...
the two of us are here...
[YOSHIKO] At first
they were frightened,
but they were determined
to enact the ritual
using only their own power.
And then,
on that fateful night...
[LEAH, RUBY] Will you come
watch our special concert?
It'd mean so much.
[WOMAN A]
Please come back, Miss!
[WOMAN B]
Miss Mari, we beg of you!
Is this really okay?
Maybe we're
taking things too far.
Should we go back?
[MARI]
No!
We have to find
a shooting start to wish on,
or else it'll never work.
So where would be a good place
to look at stars?
I don't know.
This way!
[DIA]
Are you sure?
[KANAN]
Let's try up there!
[DIA]
It's cloudy.
Hold on, we should probably
check the star chart
one more time.
[KANAN]
Rain?
Oh no.
We can't see any stars
with this weather.
Now what?
[MARI]
But we came all this way.
It's not fair.
[KANAN]
Don't cry, Mari!
[marker squeaking]
[MARI gasps]
Ta-da!
[KANAN]
Now we can make our wish!
[MARI] I wish that
we'll always be together.
[SHIITAKE whines]
Ha!
[paper rustling]
[SHIITAKE whines]
See?
Happy New Year
to the best family ever!
Aw, Happy New Year!
Right back atcha.
Here's to good fortune.
Funny that you'd mention
good fortune, Shima.
Y'know, since today is special.
It's New Year's!
Right, Mom?
Wink, wink, nudge, nudge!
Mind your manners, dear.
Ahem.
While I may be just a
simple high school student
going into her third year,
in the big scheme of things
I'm technically still a child,
and we all know that children
get a little something
on New Year's.
Something that happens to be
round and valuable?
Aha!
I know what you mean.
Yay!
[CHIKA'S MOM]
Here! How's this?
This is kinda round.
Totally valuable.
Mom!
You know that I meant money!
[MITO] Aren't you a little old
for a New Year's gift?
--[CHIKA mumbling]
--Oh yeah, Riko told her family
she didn't need
New Year's money anymore.
[gasps]
Why don't you take a note
from her book, Chika?
Every family has their own
way of doing things, though!
At least that's
what you always tell me
when I say things like that,
so it can go both ways!
[YOU]
Hey, Chika!
Oh, it sounds like You's here.
Coming!
Listen up!
This conversation
is far from over!
We'll talk about this more
when I get back, okay?
Ugh, who died and
left her in charge?
Wow, they're even at it
on New Year's Day?
Absolutely.
They've got practice.
Aw.
They're all working
so hard for Love Live,
I'm very proud of them.
[yawns]
Aw, somebody's tired, zura.
So what if I am?
I was up super late
doing a live stream.
Fallen angels
don't get to take holidays.
It's cold today.
I wonder what's keeping Dia?
[MARI] Hey! That's probably
them pulling up right now!
[RUBY]
Thanks for waiting!
Hello, and Happy
New Year everyone!
Whoa! You actually came?
Obviously.
Wait, what the heck
are you all wearing?
All right ladies.
[GIRLS] Thank you both for
coming here and Happy New Year!
--[wind blows]
--It's freezing out!
Where's your idol spirit?
[CHIKA] Uh, maybe taking the
day off since it's a holiday?
[LEAH] No excuses,
and why would you wear your
New Year's clothes to practice?!
[CHIKA yelps]
You have a beautiful school.
It's even on top of a hill
like our school is, huh?
[CHIKA]
Mm. And you can see the ocean!
Unfortunately,
it won't be here much longer.
[BOTH gasp]
In the springtime,
this school will close.
In fact, we'll be merged
with another school entirely.
You're kidding!
But if Aqours does well
in the Love Live finals,
you could get more students.
Yeah.
That was our original plan,
but it didn't quite work out.
I'm sorry to hear
about your school.
Hey, it's okay, 'cause our
friends gave us a great idea.
If we can just win the finals,
then our school will become
part of Love Live history!
Then Uranohoshi Girls'
High School will live on.
While it may not be
what we had in mind,
at least we know our school
will always be remembered.
It sounds like you have
wonderful friends.
You're so lucky.
Well then, we won't hold back.
[HANAMARU, RUBY, YOSHIKO gasp]
We'll help out with your
Love Live training,
but it won't be easy, so prepare
yourselves for some hard work.
For real?
For real.
Really, zura?
Really, zura.
[RUBY]
Seriously?
[LEAH]
I'm seriously serious!
[DIA]
Is something wrong?
It's just time flies by
when you're with your friends.
[panting]
[GIRLS panting]
Honestly, I'm a little
disappointed.
[DIA]
Disappointed? About what?
About how out of shape
you are, obviously.
You really think so?
Zura?
What we need to do is
try and warm up your bodies.
I've got it! Dash back up
the hill, to the gate,
and give me three laps
around the school.
[GIRLS gasp]
What?!
Hey, I did warn you.
Lots of hard work.
[SARAH]
Right, on your feet!
[GIRLS groan]
Now this is my kinda workout.
[sighs]
[RIKO] I might die
before the Love Live finals.
Do you really think
this will help us win?
[SARAH] I think you've
got a good chance.
[CHIKA]
You mean it?
Absolutely.
When you're all up on stage,
you have a special way of
connecting with the audience.
If you're able to convey
the feelings you have
right now organically,
I have no doubt that you'll
put on a beautiful performance.
Right!
[RUBY]
Hey, where's Mari?
[CHIKA]
That's odd.
Oh yeah.
She stepped away for a moment
because she had a
phone call from her parents.
Do you think maybe her dad
decided to cancel the merger?
I say! That merger was a
wretched idea, old chap.
Let's cancel the bugger.
You should probably
lay off the television, zura.
[MARI]
I'm back!
[DIA]
How'd your phone call go?
Director?
That's right.
They decided to offer me
the director position
at the new merged school.
With so many
Uranohoshi High students
starting there next year,
they thought having
a familiar face like mine
might help the students settle
in a little bit better, ya know?
A director?
We probably should have
mentioned that
Mari's the director
for this school.
No way!
Wait, so that means Mari will go
to school with us next Spring.
Aqours will live on!
Chika, that makes it
sound like she's failing.
[MARI]
Actually,
I turned it down.
[GIRLS]
What?
I declined the position.
After graduation,
I've decided that I'm going to
attend a college in Italy.
It's a good school
that Papa recommended.
So I have
three months left here.
Then I'll be leaving Japan.
Well then.
I wish you both
didn't have leave so soon.
Yeah, me too, but we
have one more stop to make.
Where ya goin'?
[RUBY]
Oh, I know the answer!
They're going to visit
an amusement park!
You're such a blabber mouth!
[RUBY squeaks]
Take this.
It's a training regimen
my sister and I
came up with for you.
Wow, thank you.
Whoa! That's intense!
Do you wanna win
Love Live or not?
It's gonna take some effort.
This event is more than
just making a memory, right?
We believe you can win it.
So go get 'em.
'Kay.
We'll do our Rubesty!
Your what now?
It's Ruby's super-secret
technique, zura!
[RUBY whimpers]
[YOSHIKO]
You call that a technique?
[GIRLS laugh]
So Italy, huh?
You know what?
To be completely honest,
I actually thought
this sort of thing might happen.
But when that thought
becomes a reality...
I can't believe it's only
three months away.
Love Live will be over,
then Mari will graduate.
And not just Mari, either.
Dia and Kanan
will also graduate.
Once spring arrives,
there'll be no more going
home together after school,
no more long drawn out
goodbyes at the bus stop.
New uniforms.
New classrooms.
Where are you going?
[RIKO]
What will happen to Aqours?
[YOU] Yeah, after the
third years graduate?
[CHIKA]
I don't know.
I haven't thought about it.
Until Love Live is over
and until we know the
results of the finals,
I feel like, maybe we
shouldn't think too much about
what comes next.
For everyone's sake?
We'll focus on Love Live.
We'll put our
heart and soul into it.
And no matter what,
we'll find a way to win.
I bet our radiance will be
waiting on that stage.
Let's do it.
Then we can show them,
everyone at school.
Mari, Dia, and Kanan,
we'll make them all proud.
Uh, Riko?
Good idea.
--[CHIKA] Stop it.
--[RIKO giggles]
[YOU]
Sounds like a plan!
[GIRLS laugh]
[MARI] Wow, it's been forever
since we've been in this tunnel!
It's very relaxing.
I agree.
[MARI]
So. What's up, bellas ?
Now let me guess.
Are you two planning to try and
talk me out of going to Italy?
[KANAN] If this were a year ago,
yeah, we might've tried.
'Kay, then are you
upset I didn't tell you?
Is that it?
We're not mad about anything.
We have our own news to share.
Huh?
I'd been waiting to tell you,
but I've been accepted
to a college in Tokyo.
And I'm gonna travel overseas
to get my diving
instructor's license.
Well, after graduation.
Meaning?
[KANAN]
Mm.
Once high school's done,
we'll all go our separate ways.
None of us are
staying in Uchiura,
which will make visiting
each other rather difficult.
That's what we wanted
to talk to you about.
[MARI]
I see.
[KANAN] I can't believe we
made all these big decisions
without talking
to each other first.
Right? It is pretty ironic.
Considering we had
a fight about it, remember?
Of course!
Come 'ere.
Hug.
[KANAN] Gosh Mari, I remember
you used to sneak out a lot.
It's not as if you two
were any more innocent.
Actually, we had to sneak out
to keep you in line.
To be fair, if I had asked
for permission to come see you,
my parents would have said no.
As I recall, that's also why
your parents became so strict.
[KANAN] Yeah, they thought
moving your room
to the second floor
would stop you.
[DIA] Then they moved you
to the third.
[KANAN]
And when that didn't work,
up you went to the fourth floor.
[MARI]
I wound up on the top floor.
[DIA]
Looking back on it,
you must have been a real
headache for your poor parents.
Well, they probably
should have been
more willing to let me
play with you, then.
Wait, didn't they once
threaten to disown you?
Yeah, I said, "If you don't
let me play with Kanan and Dia,
then I'll disown you ,
mom and dad!"
[DIA] I'll never forget the
look on your parents' faces
when you threatened to do that.
It was priceless.
[MARI] Weren't you the one
who gave me the idea, Dia?
Did I really say that?
We were just being kids.
[MARI]
But, we had fun.
And every day, we had
nuovo adventures together.
[MARI] I won't say this again,
so you'd better listen.
Getting to know the two of you
taught me so many things.
I learned that
the world is a big place,
and that when you're
with your friends,
sometimes you have
so much fun that you
forget about time entirely.
I even learned how to fight,
and how to make up.
If I hadn't met you two,
and gone outside,
I would have never learned
any of those things.
Who knows?
I might not have
left that room at all.
[MARI]
Ever since that day,
I've always believed
that if we were together,
then we could
accomplish anything.
I still believe it.
What I'm trying to say is
thank you.
[DIA]
It's starting to rain.
Again?
Jeez, way to go, Dia.
What? How is this my fault?
Mari's the one
who attracts rain.
Hey! It's not me, it's Kanan!
Sure, whatever!
Know what I think?
It's always raining because
God just doesn't want
our wish to come true.
You mean the wish that the three
of us will always be together?
Well if we can disown my parents
then surely we can disown
a narrow-minded god.
[ALL laugh]
I wonder.
Should it end like this?
Huh?
[KANAN] Are we really okay
that we can't wish on a star?
Just like we couldn't make
our wish all those years ago?
Kanan...
Look, it isn't for me.
But you thought the three of us
could do anything
together, right?
So shouldn't we try?
Maybe.
Besides, it's not just about
the three of us anymore.
Let's go find a star
we'll all wish on.
A star that's only for us.
[MARI]
A star that's only for us?
Okay.
Oh!
Sweet! Money!
Let's see.
[CHIKA]
"Go to the hot spring"?
Yay, New Year's gift!
Huh?
[groaning]
[CHIKA]
Dad, have you seen my--
[CHIKA groans]
[CHIKA]
Oh, hey.
[MITO, SHIMA]
Hm?
[CHIKA]
Where's Mom?
Back in Tokyo.
Really?
Yep, that's right.
And she asked me to
pass this note along.
[CHIKA]
The ball at the front door?
That's so sweet.
Thanks, everyone.
[KANAN]
Chika!
Feel like going out?
Go out? Wait,
you mean in the rain?
[gasps]
What's going on?
We were all asked to come here.
Which is honestly
pretty annoying.
Because I had planned on
livestreaming tonight.
I think it's kind of exciting.
Where are we going, exactly?
[car screeches]
[GIRLS gasp]
Let's just call it
a night time drive.
[GIRLS gasp]
[KANAN]
All right everyone, in ya go!
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
[YOSHIKO] And so
the death drive commences!
[HANAMARU]
Don't say that, zura!
[RUBY]
You'll jinx us!
[DIA]
Scoot over, okay?
[RUBY whines]
[YOU]
Huh? Where's Chika?
[RIKO]
She went to get a jacket.
[CHIKA]
Sorry!
Thanks for waiting!
[MARI]
Too late!
Huh?
'Cause this ship is sailing!
--[GIRLS] What?
--[CHIKA] Whoa, Mari?
She'll be doing
a lot of driving overseas,
so she got her license
right after her birthday.
I've had a lot of pratica ,
so don't worry about a thing!
Where are we going, anyway?
Where else?
To find a shooting star.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[MARI]
Let's go!
[car screeches]
[GIRLS yelp]
Are you okay?
Just fine!
[KANAN]
It's kind of strange.
I never imagined that one day
I'd be sitting next to Mari
while she was
driving us somewhere.
I could say the same thing.
Because I never imagined we'd
be doing this together either.
[KANAN] Well, I suppose
it's more comforting
than the idea of Dia driving.
Oh yeah? I'd take Mari over
your driving any day, Kanan!
[GIRLS laugh]
[YOU]
Wow, look.
Wonder if those lights
are all boats.
They're pretty.
This is kinda exciting,
isn't it?
Yeah.
Because when you
really think about it,
we've never hung out
spontaneously like this before.
This is a first for us.
Yup, that's why we brought you.
Originally, it was
just supposed to be
me, Mari, and Dia.
Then we decided
we should all go.
[CHIKA]
I see.
I see stars!
[KANAN]
Really?
Where do you see them?
Hey, Mari!
[MARI]
I'm on it!
[rain falls]
[DIA]
It's raining, like last time.
[KANAN] What were you
going to wish for, Mari?
[MARI]
Isn't it obvious?
Could it be "I wish we'll
always be together"?
You mean as we're
about to be separated?
Exactly.
Which is why it's so important.
If I make that wish,
then we'll be together
again one day for sure!
But then, maybe that's silly.
It's not!
[MARI, RIKO, KANAN]
Huh?
I have faith we'll all
definitely be together again.
Hey Mari, can I see that?
[MARI]
Uh?
[CHIKA]
We just have to wait a little
for this weather to clear up.
When it does,
we'll see the stars!
So let's wait together,
and then we'll make a wish!
Okay?
It'd better clear up.
Otherwise, I might
disown the sky, too.
[GIRLS laugh]
[GIRLS gasp]
Amazing. It really cleared up.
Oh, look!
A fallen angel?
[HANAMARU]
More like a shooting star, zura.
[RUBY]
There's another one!
[YOU]
I can't believe it!
[YOSHIKO] They're the
tears of little demons.
[HANAMARU] Once again,
they're shooting stars.
[RUBY]
It's so pretty.
[RIKO]
Look at that one!
[CHIKA]
Our radiance.
I wished for...
our very own radiance,
and that we'd find it, together.
[GIRLS] Next time,
"Uranohoshi Girls' High School."