[CHIKA] Wow, my school uniform
almost looks like new today!
[SHIMA] I used heavy starch
to make it nice and crisp.
[CHIKA]
Thanks, Shima.
[CHIKA'S MOM]
Make sure you button it
all the way up to the top.
[CHIKA grunts]
[CHIKA]
Mom, it's too tight!
[CHIKA'S MOM]
Is it?
Well then, that can
only mean one thing.
[CHIKA]
What?
[CHIKA'S MOM]
You've gained weight.
[CHIKA]
Hey!
Jeez, talk about rude, mother.
[DOG barks]
[CHIKA]
Riko! What's with the dog?
[RIKO]
Good morning!
This is the newest member
of our family, Prelude.
Say hello!
[PRELUDE barks]
Now that I'm
over my fear of dogs,
I can't get over how cute
my sweet Prelude is!
--[CHIKA] I.. see.
--Who's a good doggie, huh?
[PRELUDE whimpers]
[SHIITAKE barks]
Look who it is!
[RIKO] Shiitake looks so happy
with her new puppies.
[CHIKA] Yeah,
they had already been born
by the time we
got back from Tokyo.
What a great surprise!
[PUPPIES bark]
That's for sure,
but who knew she was a girl?
Ahoy!
[RIKO, CHIKA]
You're in a good mood, You.
Well, it's the
last day of school.
Most of the others
are already here.
[YOSHIKO] ...commands you
to leave her alone!
You can't stay up there
forever, zura.
The ceremony's about to start!
Just leave me alo--
[yells]
[ALL gasp]
[YOSHIKO]
Don't look at me!
I hope she's okay.
[GIRLS laugh]
So, you feeling nervous?
Not at all.
Same, I'm actually excited.
We've worked hard for this day.
[YOSHIKO whines]
[HANAMARU]
Wow, you don't mess around
when it comes to bad hair days.
[YOSHIKO]
It's not a bad hair day.
I was trying to make it
look nice for the ceremony,
but it turned out like this.
[RUBY]
Aw, don't cry.
[HANAMARU]
Yeah, we'll help you, zura.
We'll just use this lil' baby
to get you sorted out.
Chop chop.
Okay, yeah,
that should probably work.
Wait, don't you dare, Zuramaru!
You know, this room
is actually kinda big.
Well, we did have
a lot of stuff in here.
Maybe if we had been
a little cleaner
the room wouldn't have
felt quite so small.
[CHIKA]
Probably.
Kanan.
I guess now it's all gone, huh?
[KANAN]
Not exactly.
It's still in our hearts.
That much remains.
[CHIKA]
Mm.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[DIA]
Mari.
Something up?
What's wrong?
No goofing off today.
This ceremony is important.
Promise me you'll
take it seriously.
[MARI]
I promise, bella !
And don't worry.
Everyone will be on their best,
most normal behavior.
Wait, define "normal."
It's my Rubesty! Heh.
[MARI giggles]
All done!
Using my dark powers,
I was able to revert to my
previous, more magnificent form!
Hear me roar!
Meaning we basically
re-styled her hair, zura.
[STUDENTS laughing, chattering]
Um, Mari.
What's happening?
[CHIKA]
Hey, girlfriend!
It's the last day of school
so everyone's writing messages!
Seriously?
Sì !
I decided to open the courtyard,
so the students could
have a little fun!
[RUBY]
Here. Come join us, sis!
[sighs]
Not to put a damper on the mood,
but the ceremony is starting
soon and we're all filthy.
To be fair though,
this is normal for our school.
The best things in life
are often messy.
[YOU]
Looking back on it,
we sure made some
fun memories here, didn't we?
[RIKO]
All of our practices.
The times we goofed off.
[RUBY cries]
[HANAMARU]
Keep it together.
Don't cry.
We all promised
that we wouldn't cry,
so you have to be
strong right now.
[RUBY]
'Kay...
That's right.
There's still so much
left to celebrate.
[applause]
[MARI] Next on the agenda,
we'll award the diplomas.
Please welcome the graduate's
representative, Kanan Matsuura.
[KANAN]
Thank you.
It feels a little strange,
having you give it to me.
You've worked hard for this
diploma, so be proud of it.
Congratulations
on your graduation.
[DIA] On this day,
we conclude an era.
Uranohoshi High School
will end its extensive history.
However, this school and its
memory shall remain forever.
We'll carry it with us.
I feel proud.
Proud to start on a new path
with those memories.
Proud to have been a student
at such a wonderful school.
Proud to have known you.
It's up to us now, to keep
this place alive in our hearts.
[DIA]
As of this moment,
I pronounce Uranohoshi High
officially closed.
Congratulations are in order!
We really won it!
We won Love Live!
[DIA] Well, it's about time
for everyone to head home.
So she says,
but no one's leaving yet.
I imagine that they'll stay here
until someone
forces them to leave.
Better watch out
for school squatters!
On the other hand,
they can't close the school
if there are still
people inside it.
If only it were that easy,
then everyone would be happy.
[CHIKA]
For real!
[KANAN]
Let's go close up.
It's only right that the
students are the ones to do it.
[CHIKA]
Whoa, awesome!
[RIKO]
It's beautiful.
[YOU]
I'll say.
Like it?
We all drew it based off our
memories of you at the finals.
[YOSHIMI] At least, this is
how you appeared to us
and to the rest of the audience.
[MUTSU]
You were shining!
[ITSUKO] Yeah, so bright,
it almost blinded us.
[CHIKA]
Thanks so much.
We saw you, too.
You were out there
shining, as well!
Lights dancing
in every direction,
across the entire stadium!
So it sounds like
everything was shining, then!
[CHIKA]
Yep!
I guess so!
It was super awesome!
[ALL giggle]
Okay, time to close it.
[HANAMARU]
That's the last of 'em, zura.
It's weird without
the books in here.
[HANAMARU] They weren't
thrown away or anything.
Rather, they flew off
to a new home, like birds.
[RUBY]
Like, flappity flap?
[HANAMARU]
Wherever they go next,
they'll have the chance
to be read by someone new.
I think that's
sorta beautiful, zura.
Just like the books,
we'll be in a brand-new place
next year, too.
I'm kinda scared, zura.
Yeah, so am I. But still,
after becoming a school idol
with you and everyone else,
I think we'll be okay.
[YOSHIKO]
Descend!
Huh?
[YOSHIKO] Come on,
let's get out of here
my faithful little demons!
[HANAMARU, RUBY]
Mm-hm!
[HANAMARU]
Let's close it together.
No thanks.
[HANAMARU]
I want us to close it together.
I said no thanks.
It's not a request, zura!
It has to be all of us.
If you insist.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
[RUBY giggles]
Dear library,
thanks so much for always
bein' a safe place for us.
[YOSHIKO]
We'll miss you.
[RUBY]
Goodbye.
[piano plays]
Hey, that sounds pretty.
Thank you, the piano here
has a really beautiful sound.
Maybe it's because
the room has an echo?
Possibly.
[YOU]
You know,
I'll miss this view.
[RIKO] Back when I first
transferred to this school,
I thought that there's no way
I'd find this kind
of view in Tokyo.
[YOU] So, hey, there's something
I've been wanting to say. Um...
[RIKO]
Hm?
It's that... it's that
I really love you, Riko!
Aw, I love you, too!
[BOTH laugh]
I had a lot of fun
with everyone.
It was a pretty good year.
Yeah, it was.
[knocking]
How long are you
gonna stand there?
[MARI]
As long as I want.
[DIA]
Mari.
[gasps]
Here, this diploma
is especially for you.
It's special?
[DIA] Diploma and
Certificate of Appreciation
for Miss Mari Ohara.
This certifies
that you've excelled
as a student and director
while serving this school.
Hence, in order to show
our sincere gratitude
we present you
with this certificate.
On behalf of all the students
at Uranohoshi Girls' High,
by us, Kanan Matsuura.
[DIA]
And Dia Kurosawa.
Really? But I...
It's all yours.
[KANAN]
Take it.
[KANAN] It's okay,
because the sky is connected.
We may not see each other.
We may be far apart.
But always connected.
[MARI]
Thank you.
[MARI cries]
Goodbye.
[CHIKA]
This is the last room.
Because of this place...
We were always
able to work hard.
[YOU] Because of this place,
we were able to move forward.
All the practice we did.
All the costumes we designed.
All the sore muscles.
The difficult dances.
The nerves and anxiety.
This room held
a great many things.
Through every single trial,
we had this place.
We'll go wait for you outside.
[CHIKA]
Thank you!
[CHIKA giggles]
[laughs]
[CROWD sniffling]
You ready?
Chika?
It's time.
[CHIKA cries]
[CHIKA grunts]
[CHIKA gasps]
[CHIKA cries]
[CHIKA]
We'll make sure our memories
are full of nothing but smiles.
I won't cry.
I'm not gonna cry!
[YOU, RIKO]
It's okay.
Let's close it.
Together.
Oh, why'd you pick that spot
for your flag?
Because I wanted it
to be in a place
where everyone could see it.
Whether you're coming or going,
it will always be there
to wave hello.
[MITO]
Hey! Chika! Guess what?
Your new school uniform
just got here!
[CHIKA]
Okay!
Spring has arrived.
Did the third years
already go on their way?
Yeah.
Mari, Dia, and Kanan,
they've all left.
[CHIKA'S MOM]
Say, do you remember?
You were such a worry-wart,
always stressing about
what people would think of you
if you failed at something.
You'd get so frustrated,
and then you would cover your
tracks by pretending to give up.
[CHIKA'S MOM] Kind of
like that paper airplane.
Hey.
[CHIKA'S MOM]
Yes?
[CHIKA]
Do you think... we found it?
Our radiance, I mean.
We found it at Love Live, right?
Is that what you've
been telling yourself?
[MITO]
You're as dense as ever, Chika!
[SHIMA] You can
throw that paper airplane
as many times as you want.
After all the hard work you did,
I'm sure you'll find the answer.
It's out there somewhere.
The Chika who didn't give up
is more than capable of
finding what she's looking for.
[CHIKA grunts]
[gasps]
Go!
Fly!
[CHIKA laughs]
Go, Chika! Go find it!
[CHIKA panting]
[CHIKA]
Hello, is anybody in here?
It's me, Chika Takami,
from Class 2-A.
[RIKO]
I'm so sorry.
[YOU]
No way. A uniform!
[CHIKA, RIKO]
Girl overboard!
[KANAN]
Let go! You're being ridiculous!
[MARI] I'm not letting go
until you say yes!
[DIA]
Both of you, cut it out!
You're acting like children!
[RUBY]
Please!
Without you
this doesn't feel right!
Be a school idol with me!
[HANAMARU]
I'm scared.
Can I even do it?
[YOSHIKO]
I might say weird stuff again,
and there might be some times
when I perform rituals.
What if I order you
to become my demons?
[KANAN]
1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4.
Try and speed up your movement
right there, Ruby.
[RUBY]
Uh... 'Kay!
[KANAN]
Oh, and Yoshiko.
[YOSHIKO]
Yohane!
[KANAN laughs] You need to
speed up a bit, too.
[YOSHIKO]
Understood. Teleportation mode!
You really are such a liar.
You promised everyone
you wouldn't cry.
Liar.
[CHIKA cries]
[CHIKA]
Why?
Why am I remembering
those things?
Why am I hearing their voices?
It's not fair.
It's not.
[GIRLS]
Roar!
[CHIKA] It was the miracle
that I desperately needed.
It could only be one thing.
Fate.
I wanted to be
captivated by something.
I wanted to do
my best in something.
I just wanted to put
my best foot forward.
But, my feet didn't exactly
know where they were going yet.
Luckily, destiny stepped in
and took charge.
It gave me a push,
and there it was!
That radiance was--
[groans]
[pants]
Chika!
Jeez, you're late!
Yeah, what took you so long?
[STUDENTS laugh]
But how?
I don't understand.
[STUDENTS]
Ta-da!
No way.
This isn't a dream.
We're here because we all
wanted to sing with you.
One last time.
In our old school.
We made a contract!
Yeah, we've been waitin'!
For you, Chika!
So let's sing.
[GIRLS]
Together!
[ALL]
[music plays]
[singing in Japanese]
I get it.
The radiance I've
been searching for!
Our own unique way to shine!
I've been struggling to find it
for what feels like forever,
but now I see it!
It was always there,
from the very beginning!
[CHIKA]
Everything we did,
every single step we took
and the long hours of
hard work we put in--
all that was our own radiance!
Shining from inside of us,
as a part of Aqours!
[singing in Japanese]