[CHIKA]
Sometimes I wonder...
..what exactly makes
someone shine?
[CHIKA panting]
[CHIKA grunting]
[CHIKA]
I can almost reach it!
Just a little more!
[CHIKA screaming]
[gasping, panting]
[barks]
[screams]
[thud]
[CHIKA groaning]
[sighs]
Chika! Why aren't
you dressed yet?!
You're gonna be late!
[CHIKA whines]
[MARI]
Buon giorno, everybody!
I hope all of you are ready,
because the second
season starts today!
The second season...?
She means the second term.
Well, more importantly,
where the heck is Chika?
[RIKO] She's late of course,
but that's what happens
when she tries to get herself
up in the morning.
[YOU laughs]
Mari! Didn't I tell you to speak
more like a proper director?!
You were supposed to say,
"Please behave in a way
that is befitting of an
Uranohoshi student
and study hard!"
Any of that ringing a bell?
In a befouling way?
I said "befitting"!
Heh...
Still, it's hard to believe
how close we were.
I know, a little more and we
would have made it to Nationals.
Don't let it get you down,
there's no point in
dwellin' in the past, zura!
Wait!
[RUBY, HANAMARU gasp]
[YOSHIKO] Why is the prize for
participating a two-color pen?
[RUBY] I wonder if the prize
for making it to Nationals
is a three-color pen?
[HANAMARU]
It's the future, zura!
[YOSHIKO]
It's just a pen!
Shut up!
[MARI clears throat]
Now then, I think we
were all a little depresso
about not making Nationals.
[BOTH laugh]
But still, we managed to
change a zero into a one.
We couldn't have done that
without all of your help.
[YOU]
And...
[RUBY]
There's more!
We surpassed our goal,
and turned one into ten!
You got that right!
[DIA] On top of that,
we have more news.
[MARI] Earlier today they
made an announcement--
it was about the next Love Live!
[KANAN]
Love Live?
[RUBY]
Really?!
[DIA]
Yes.
Like the previous ones,
the next competition
will be at Akiba Dome!
You're late!
But better late than never!
[CHIKA panting]
About Love Live...
You made it!
What do should we do?
I think this one is
pretty obvious, ladies!
But Yoshiko is dying
to know, zura!
[RUBY]
Mm-hm!
Yohane!
[CHIKA]
I say... we enter!
We enter Love Live!
And this time we'll go further!
Transform that ten,
and make it a hundred!
Yeah, and then--
[STUDENTS]
And then?
I believe... that we'll all
finally be able to shine
in our own way. I know!
[STUDENTS]
We will all shine!
[KANAN]
1... 2... 3... 4...
Wow, your body is
super stiff, Yoshiko.
Are you stretching
like I told you?
[YOSHIKO]
It's Yohane!
[YOSHIKO groaning]
[KANAN]
Still not good enough.
Here, I'll push you.
You're not helping!
Besides this meat vessel
is only temporary!
The fallen angel's
true form is--
[thud]
[YOSHIKO squeaks]
[YOSHIKO[
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
[RUBY]
Wow, Hanamaru!
You've become really flexible!
[HANAMARU]
That's because I stretch at home
every single day!
I'm also doing push-ups!
[RUBY]
Really?
[HANAMARU]
Check it out, zura!
One!
[HANAMARU grunting]
[HANAMARU yelps]
[HANAMARU]
See? Perfect form.
That was amazing!
I'm so proud of you!
Fantastico!
In what way?!
So we know where the next Love
Live is, but what about when?
I could be wrong, but I think
sometime in the spring.
Boop, boop! Wrong again.
There's something else we need
to focus our attention on first.
[RIKO, YOU]
Huh?
I can't believe you forgot.
We need to increase the number
of prospective students.
[RIKO]
Right, the school's open house.
[YOU]
Oh yeah.
[MARI] Si ! I've already
made an announcement.
This is the perfect opportunity
to put on a concert
for any participants
of the open house,
and then we'll show them all
exactly how wonderful
our school is!
--[CHIKA] Great idea!
--[DIA] Uh...?
I think that plan is
super awesome! Heh!
[YOSHIKO] Did you get
lost in the bathroom?
We had to go ahead and
start practice without you.
[KANAN] Says the girl
who should be stretching!
[YOSHIKO]
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
[GIRLS laughing]
[phone vibrates]
[YOU]
Aw man, I forgot the bus service
stops running earlier
in the fall.
That's right, it does.
The sun starts
setting earlier, too.
Is it possible our practices
might get shorter?
On top of that,
the school's open house
is right around the corner.
[RUBY]
I know, so what do we do?
[DIA] We need maintain our
practice schedule somehow.
[KANAN]
Why don't we just start
two hours earlier
in the morning?
[GIRLS groan]
Perfect, you agree!
No, we were groaning!
Hold on a sec, Yoshiko.
Didn't I hear that you have
an earlier curfew these days?
[gasps]
But how the heck do you know?
[RIKO] Oh, actually,
I heard it from my mom
who was talking to your mom at
the last Love Live competition.
And so, in the name
of the fallen angel--
Yoshiko?
[gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
[YOSHIKO]
It's Yohane, Mom!
[RIKO] Wasn't it because you
locked her out of your room?
[YOSHIKO] Uh, that's because I,
Yohane, am a fallen angel!
That makes my parental unit
merely a temporary housemate.
Anyway, what do you think
her mom is like?
I heard she's a school teacher,
and I also heard that all
the way up to kindergarten,
widdle Yoshiko wouldn't
let go of her ba-ba.
[GIRLS laughing]
Hey wait.
I wonder if the buses that head
this way from Numazu run later.
[GIRLS groan]
Probably, because people
are coming back from work.
Uh! What if we actually
practiced in Numazu?
With the later buses, we'd
have more time to practice.
What a great idea!
That settles it. Right, Mari?
[MARI gasps]
Nessun problema !
[laughs]
[CHIKA]
Yay! Then it's decided!
[RIKO] We could check out
potential locations tomorrow.
Maybe after school?
[YOSHIKO]
It'll be the perfect opportunity
to recruit more demons.
[HANAMARU] But Yoshiko, we have
bigger fish to fry, zura!
[YOSHIKO]
It's Yohane!
[GIRLS laughing]
See ya!
Pretty.
[footsteps]
Yeah, it is.
[CHIKA]
Hey, Riko?
Maybe it's silly,
but for a brief moment,
and I mean really brief.
I think singing together
with everyone at the prelims
helped me understand
what it means to shine.
Is that so?
[CHIKA]
Yep! And now...
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
[CHIKA yells]
[CHIKA gasping]
[CHIKA grunts]
[exhales]
[CHIKA]
Even if it's just a little--
I think we can shine.
And with hard work,
we definitely can!
I believe in us.
[RIKO]
Right, it may be tough, but...
But it's all worth it, yeah?
[RIKO laughs]
[CHIKA, RIKO laughing]
[MARI]
But Papa!
You promised me that you'd wait!
This is too sudden!
I'm begging you... please!
But... I...
[MARI]
Thanks for waiting, bella !
[KANAN]
So, what happened?
[MARI]
Oops, I'm so sorry!
Non parlo la tua lingua .
You know what I said!
Uh. Okay, hug attack!
Stop messing around.
[MARI grunts]
Fine then.
You want the truth? Here it is.
Just say it.
Well, I put on a few pounds
recently so I've been
a little bummed, y'know?
Uh! Oh... Hey!
Don't lie to me.
You weigh the same.
How would you know?!
I can tell.
Besides you wouldn't let
something as insignificant
as that get you down.
What's up?
Well?
What should we do, Kanan?
Mari...
[yawning]
[YOU]
So, Chika?
Were you able to find a place?
Ah... Not really,
everything's been a bust.
[YOSHIKO]
What about you, Zuramaru?
Couldn't we use your family's
temple or something?
[HANAMARU]
Are y'all positive
you wanna use our temple, zura?
[YOSHIKO, RUBY squeak]
Also, it's kinda way out
in the middle of nowhere.
[RUBY]
In that case,
maybe we should
practice at Yoshiko's house.
Uh, hold up. What makes you
think I even have enough space?
[laughs]
What the...?
Where did Dia, Kanan,
and Mari go?
[RIKO]
Strange, they were just here.
[RUBY] Oh, I think Mari had
to go take a phone call.
That's it. There's really
nothing more we can do.
Not true! Just watch!
Uh. Kanan.
Does Dia know about this?
No, what would I tell her?
[DIA] Maybe that you're horrible
at keeping secrets?
[MARI]
Dia?
You've been acting suspicious
for a while now.
Sorry, but--boop boop.
Game over.
[GIRLS]
Wow!
Awesome!
This is perfect!
Hey look! There's more!
Behind the curtain
there's a big mirror!
Right! Let's journey
into the mirror world!
Uh!
Let it go, zura.
One of my dad's co-workers
was renting this place,
but doesn't need it
for a few more months.
[CHIKA]
Thanks a lot, Captain!
[RIKO]
It's not like he sailed us here.
[CHIKA] Oooo! And there
are lots of awesome
stores on the way home!
[RIKO] I don't think
we'll have much time
for shopping after practice.
[HANAMARU]
There's a book store, too!
[RIKO]
U-Uh. There is?
[CHIKA]
Oh, Riko.
Well, then. Whaddya say
we check our formation
and get a little practice in?
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
Hold on a minute.
[ALL]
Huh?
[KANAN] Before that, there's
something we need to tell you.
[YOU]
Okay, fire away.
[KANAN]
Well, the thing is...
Mari.
Listen, about the
school's open house--
It's being canceled.
[GIRLS]
Love Live ! Sunshine !!
It's been canceled?
What does that mean?
It means exactly
what it sounds like.
They're canceling
the open house.
Uranohoshi will no longer be
recruiting new students
for next year.
[YOU]
No way...
Isn't this too soon?
Yeah, she's right!
I mean, the second term
has only just gotten started!
[RUBY grunts]
From your perspective,
I'm sure it seems that way.
However, the school has been
considering combining
with another school
for the past two years.
Mari had persuaded her
dad into postponing it
for as long as she could,
but we've run out of time.
[YOU]
But there have been more
prospective students
lately, right?
It used to be zero,
but now it's made it up to 10!
[RUBY] Yeah, and we'll
probably get even more!
Look, I told Papa all of that.
I'm sorry, but it just wasn't
enough to change anything.
[CHIKA]
Mari! Where is he?!
You mean Papa?
[CHIKA]
I'll go talk to him!
--[YOU] Chika!
--[RIKO] Wait! He's in America!
Just hold on, Mari's dad
is in America!
Isn't that right?
[MARI]
Si .
[CHIKA] Then I'll talk
to my mom and sisters.
I'll ask for an advance on my
allowance, and borrow money
if I have to.
I'll go to America, and...
...I'll ask him to wait
a little longer.
Oh, Chika.
You really think that'll work?
It has to!
Then I'll call on my
special abilities! Uh...
[KANAN]
Look Chika...
You know Mari loves our school,
and she adores our town.
So much so that she's put the
school before studying abroad,
and her own future.
[DIA] As the director,
she's been working hard
behind the scenes to
keep the school alive.
She's been trying
harder than anyone.
She knows what's at stake here.
[KANAN]
The thing is, if Mari herself
is telling us that there's
nothing we can do...
No, no!
Chika-chi. I'm sorry.
[gasps]
Don't be. It's just not fair.
It's not fair.
[CHIKA] I wonder if we'd won
at the regional prelims--
if we'd made it
to the nationals...
I wonder if we could
have changed things.
[CHIKA]
I wonder...
Would the future be different?
[MITO grunting]
[SHIITAKE growls]
Almost there!
To think your winter
coat'll be worse.
--[barks]
--Uh?
You're getting home late.
[CHIKA]
Yeah.
Hey. Mutsu and some of your
friends stopped by earlier.
[rustling, thud]
[CHIKA]
Oh.
Yep. Your friends left that
here when they came by.
They said everyone's
rooting for you girls.
Uh? Chika? Something wrong?
Nothing at all.
Everything's great!
[MARI]
And for that reason,
the school's open house
has been canceled.
Uranohoshi Girls' High will be
combined with another school
and officially
closed down next year.
No way.
[DIA] To those of you
who have been preparing
for the open house,
we're very sorry.
Unfortunately, we will need
to remove all posters
and promotional items around
the school immediately.
[ITSUKO] Is there really nothing
we can do to stop it?
Where would we even start?
A problem this big is way
out of our league.
If something could be done
don't you think Chika
and the others
would have already
thought of it?
[RIKO]
What a beautiful sunset.
You know what?
Even though things didn't
turn out the way we hoped,
at least we can still be proud
of how hard we all worked.
Unlike Tokyo, this is just
a small, rural seaside town,
but despite that, look how
far we were able to come.
Do you really mean that?
Because... if you
really mean that...
Then I...
I despise you.
You're awful.
[RIKO]
Huh?!
Roar!
[RIKO laughs]
Pew! Pew, pew-- Bang!
I'm the normal monster, Riko-pi!
Fire special weapon,
the Riko Beam!
Did I do it right?
[CHIKA laughs]
[RIKO]
There's a smile.
Uh!
I'm still here.
I'm an Aqours member, too.
I thought I'd continue
to sing with everyone.
I thought I'd make
lots of songs.
I'd never think this
was all okay. Never.
Oh, Riko...
I wish I knew
how to fix all this.
I'm lost, too.
[MITO]
Chika!
Don't you want some dinner?!
About the school's open house.
It's being canceled...
[RIKO]
I'm lost, too.
[gasps]
[CHIKA grunts]
[CHIKA]
Good morning!
And good-bye!
What the--?!
--[SHIITAKE barks]
--Ahh!
[CHIKA panting]
Roar!
[CHIKA] No matter what,
I will make a miracle happen!
And until I do... I won't cry!
Not one more tear!
[CHIKA gasping]
[YOU]
I knew you'd be here.
[gasps] You? But how?
I'm not sure, but look.
Ahoy!
[CHIKA]
You're all here?
Yeah, I just followed my gut.
[CHIKA]
Mari?
[HANAMARU]
We're on same wavelength!
[RUBY]
Yep!
[YOSHIKO]
Heh, heh.
Naturally, this is where
I happened to descend.
[YOU] I don't really understand
how this happened.
[KANAN]
You don't?
I think I might know.
I bet--
I bet we're just not
ready to give up yet.
Because it's still too soon!
I know Mari has been
trying hard all this time.
But, I haven't.
The rest of us haven't
tried anything yet!
You're so right.
It may be a waste
of time, but still.
I want us to fight to the end!
We might struggle.
But I want to search for
the radiance that I glimpsed,
and find it.
No surprise there, you've
always been stubborn,
but I'm used to it.
Well, look at the pot
calling the kettle black.
Says the pot!
[DIA grunts]
[DIA]
Are you saying I'm stubborn?
[RUBY]
...it's true!
[MARI]
It's joke!
So what should we do?
Chika-chi...
Thank you.
Let's do it.
Might as well shoot for
the moon, am I right?
I agree. I say
we make it happen.
A miracle?
A miracle!
A miracle.
--A miracle!
A miracle!
[ALL gasping]
[laughs]
[CHIKA grunts]
[BOTH]
Whoa, Chika!
'Kay! A miracle!
We'll struggle with
all we've got!
We'll never give up!
We'll keep trying!
And we will shine!
[GIRLS]
Next Time,
"The Sound of Rain."