[RIKO]
Previously on...
[GIRLS]
...Love Live! Sunshine!!
[RIKO] Aqours was just
starting to gear up
for the next
Love Live competition.
But then we received
some unexpected news...
Listen, about the
school's open house.
It's being canceled.
[RIKO] Our hopes of saving
the school were crushed,
and everything looked
pretty hopeless.
[CHIKA]
'Kay! A miracle!
We'll struggle
with all we've got!
We'll never give up!
We'll keep trying!
And we... will shine!
You think everything's
gonna be okay?
[DIA] Hopefully, but it's
not as if the number
of prospective students
has increased.
We need to be realistic.
Putting it that way,
it doesn't sound like there's
much hope to go on.
--[door clicks]
--[ALL] Uh?
Well, Mari?
How did it go?
Sorry, bellas .
He said that no matter how
many people are opposed,
the school can't survive
without students.
Just as we expected.
[MARI]
So, then I asked
if we got more prospective
students, would he reconsider.
[gasps]
And if he would, then how many?
Or more specifically,
how many in order to
keep the school open?
[YOU]
What did he say?
A hundred.
A hundred...
[MARI] Right. He said we would
have to recruit a hundred
new students by the end of the
year, and if we could do that.
Then they'll hold
an entrance exam,
and the school will remain open.
But as things stand, we
only have 10 students
who are interested.
How on earth will we ever
get a hundred of them?
[CHIKA] But... that means
there's still a chance!
It's not over.
It may seem difficult,
but none of that matters.
Because, at least we're
all still fighting!
Well, I guess she's
got a good point.
Thanks, Mari! You're the best!
[MARI]
Chika-chi?
As long there's still a
chance, just have faith!
Let's try hard for the school,
and for Love Live, too!
We can do it! A hundred!
From zero to one!
And from one, to ten!
From ten to... a hundred!
[CHIKA groans]
I don't know what to do.
What do you mean?
[CHIKA] I talked a
big game this morning,
but I honestly didn't expect
the Love Live qualifiers
would be held so soon.
Well, they'd have to with
so many groups entering.
Our district's qualifiers
are early next month, huh?
There's even gonna
be a special stage.
Evil spirits will congregate,
and partake in epic festivities!
But why is it such a big deal
if it's held sooner?
[CHIKA]
Because, um...
Because she probably
hasn't written lyrics.
For real?
Aw! This isn't fair!
I'm not the only one who's
behind, Riko complained
that composing two songs is
a lot of work too, you know!
[RIKO] Not just me.
You complained, too!
Heh. Nine costumes
is a lot of work.
Can't we just use the
songs we sang before?
[DIA]
Unfortunately, no.
Love Live rules state we
can't use previous songs.
We'll have to compose new ones.
They make it too hard.
It's so unfair.
Well, you have to
overcome that hardship.
Otherwise, how else
you would ever learn
to appreciate the view
from the summit?
Yeah, I know.
But I still wish it was easier.
So, just where are you
with the lyrics, anyway?
Uh! Uh, well, you know,
they're coming along.
[laughs nervously]
[HANAMARU] Look, I found Chika's
songwriting book, zura.
[CHIKA screams]
[CHIKA grunting]
Wow, it's amazin'!
And accurate! [laughs]
It's pretty awesome, huh?
I was up until
two AM last night!
[RIKO growls]
[RUBY, HANAMARU, CHIKA whimper]
Excuse me?
Sorry.
[CHIKA grunts]
You know, it feels kinda wrong
to make Chika and Riko
do all the song stuff.
Si , I agree.
Then maybe you could
help them out, Kanan!
[KANAN] Me? I don't think
that's a good idea.
[MARI] But you used
to write our lyrics.
[KANAN] Yeah, and you
used to do the composing,
so why don't you help them out?
Who made the costumes?
Oh, that was us.
[RUBY]
Yeah.
Ah! I forgot.
Ruby is pretty handy
with a needle and thread.
I'm okay, I guess.
[HANAMARU]
Look at this!
Ruby also made
this bag for me, zura!
How cute!
Did you also do the embroidery?
[RUBY]
Yes...
Uh?
Okay then, why don't we try
splitting up all the work?
[ALL]
Split the work?
[MARI] You, Chika-chi, and
Riko will work on the song
for the open house.
The rest of us will create
a song for the Love
Live qualifiers.
That will take some of the
pressure off of Chika-chi.
I guess. But hold on,
I don't know the first thing
about writing a song.
Which is why we're going
to work together!
I'm positivo we can do this!
Our song might even turn out
better than Chika's group.
Not "might." I know our song
will be better than theirs.
It's our responsibility
as senior idols.
Yeah! Tell 'em, Dia!
Sounds fun! So,
we'll compete to see
which group makes a
better song first, okay?
Let's do it!
Uh, right!
I'm in.
Okay! So, it's settled,
we'll split into groups
and start working
on our songs, pronto !
All right!
Best of luck, everyone!
[YOU, RIKO]
Mm...
'Kay, we're setting sail
for Chika's house, see ya!
Happy writin', zura!
[RIKO]
Did you remember...
Well then.
I guess we should find
a place and get to work.
If we wanna stick around here,
there's always the club room.
Personally, I'd prefer
a change of scenery.
That's fair enough.
Perhaps we should all
follow their example,
and go work at someone's house?
[KANAN]
How 'bout Mari's place?
[MARI]
What? Why mine?
For starters,
it's fairly spacious.
Secondly, it happens
to be close by.
Hey, is it true?
I heard a rumor that Mari's
family is super wealthy.
Far as I know.
Basically, we're entering
the secret lair
of high school royalty.
[laughs]
Well, as long as it's fine
with everyone else,
it's no problema for me.
[HANAMARU, RUBY, YOSHIKO]
Whoosh!
I vote yes!
Let's go to Mari's!
Yohane wishes to descend there!
Okay! Just follow me, bellas !
[HANAMARU, RUBY, YOSHIKO
gasping]
It's like a castle!
And yet it still feels
so cozy, zura!
My inner darkness...
it's leaving me!
Wow, really?
You acted the same way
your first time here.
I'm never going home!
Yeah, whatever.
Anyway, who's ready to do
some serious song writing,
say "aye!" Aye!
[ALL gasping]
[MARI]
Thanks for waiting!
Anyone up for a little snack?
It's the best future!
Please help yourself
to anything.
If you insist!
It all looks so tasty!
[HANAMARU]
It's simply amazin', zura.
[YOSHIKO]
You must resist, Yohane!
If you get mesmerized by this
mortal food, you'll be purified!
Purified, I say!
Gather up your pride as a
fallen angel and just say no!
[HANAMARU]
Say, "aah!"
[YOSHIKO]
Shock! I ascend!
How very odd.
Would you like some
macarons? Here.
[BOTH gulp]
[HANAMARU]
It's so tasty, zura.
[YOSHIKO] The chocolate stuff
is irresistible!
[HANAMARU]
I know, right?
Hold on.
I feel like... there's something
we're supposed to do.
Ah! How cute!
[elephant trumpeting]
Ahem! That's right!
As I suspected, Mari's house
is horrible for productivity!
Time to work!
[YOSHIKO, HANAMARU]
Aww...
Mari's house was better.
Yeah, this place is
lacking in popcorn!
[DIA]
Are you done complaining?
[BOTH]
Yes.
First, what's the concept
of our lyrics?
As in, what do we need in
order to pass the qualifiers?
Me!
I know! Nothingness.
What?
Exactly! That is of course
to say nothingness,
doesn't mean there is nothing,
but instead it means the state
of nothingness exists, zura.
That is true nothingness.
--[DIA] Huh?
--[MARI] What...?
[YOSHIKO]
Are you serious?
That's cool!
Right, Yoshiko. Pure nothingness
is indeed the end goal.
And once you're there,
you can finally achieve
the ultimate mental state, zura.
It's Yohane, and nothingness
is a divine power
which comes from total darkness.
[YOSHIKO, HANAMARU]
Clank!
Precisely!
I see. Enlightening!
[DIA] I'm not certain we could
win Love Live with that theme.
There's no way,
it's too confusing.
For sure. We totally need
something happier!
[YOSHIKO grunts]
Such foolish mortals!
They don't get it!
Okay, moving along, do you
have any suggestions, Mari?
Leave it to me!
I've got a super happy fun song
that will perk
everyone right up!
Prepare to be amazed! Ha, ha!
[MARI laughs] It's been two
long years since my songs
last had an audience.
I'm so nervoso !
It's the future!
Which song is it?
[laughs] Un momento !
[ALL]
Hm?
[MARI laughs]
[rock music plays]
[barks]
Yay! Ha!
This is cool. I will say it
makes me wanna move my body.
A little unorthodox,
but you'd have to admit
it'd really stand out
in the qualifiers.
[MARI]
Si! This is the kind of musica
that makes everyone
wanna get up and dance!
[KANAN]
And since it's for Love Live,
we'd definitely want to try
and show a lot of energy.
[ALL]
Uh?
Help, I can't hear myself think.
What's that?!
Did you say something?!
It's nothing but
loud noise, zura.
Flop.
Nothing comes to mind?
[CHIKA] I kind of feel like
"shine" is the key word here,
but I'm just not sure.
How can we use it, though?
[CHIKA] I dunno, but if we
don't think of something soon
then the other group
will beat us.
[phone chimes]
[CHIKA]
Ruby?
It says to come over.
No way! Did they
actually beat us?!
[DIA] We can't win Love Live
with a subpar song like that!
What happened?!
Are they done?!
Oh, and like your noisy
racket is any better!
Well, it's better than
Hanamaru's nothingness.
It's just...
I'm not sure your music is
really suited for Aqours.
There's nothing wrong with
challenging old ideas!
That's the only way to grow
and ultimately evolve!
[DIA] While we're at it,
we should add in a koto!
[HANAMARU]
How 'bout we add in
the state of
nothingness instead?
[KANAN] You mean
the state of boringness!
[RUBY whines]
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine !!
[DIA]
Maybe this was a bad idea,
and we can't create
songs together.
[ALL]
Hmph.
[RUBY] Our tastes
are just too different.
[CHIKA]
I see.
[YOU] I mean, it sounded
like a good idea in theory.
Why don't you try talking
it over a little more?
It's not as if we didn't try.
Turns out, that our differences
are actually pretty severe.
What a conundrum.
I guess, and it's true
the first and third years
don't have very much in common.
Maybe, but we can't
use that as an excuse
or else we'll never
work together.
So now what?
[DIA]
We have to figure this out.
It's only a thought, but what
this really comes down to
is a lack of communication
within the group.
[YOU]
You're probably right.
When I think on it,
I've never even seen them
interact that much.
[CHIKA]
Yeah, for the most part
Yoshiko and Hanamaru prefer
to keep to themselves.
And while they put up
a good front,
Mari and Kanan are
actually pretty shy, too.
[DIA]
I've got an idea!
[ALL]
Getting to know each other?
That's correct, and it's
a great starting point.
'Cause we need to create trust
if we're going to create a song!
Okay, so where should we begin?
Leave it to me!
What, have you got a plan?
[KANAN] Mm-hm! When you wanna
become friends with someone
you don't know,
you play together.
Trust me, it never fails!
Nice throw!
What... is this?
Dunno.
Right, it's my turn!
[HANAMARU, YOSHIKO yelp]
Mari's Bright Shining.
Ah! Zura!
I've got this!
[YOSHIKO]
Darkness consumes power.
By extinguishing the light,
its power is neutralized
and trapped in the depths
of darkness. Behold!
Tornado!
[YOSHIKO]
Dark-Consuming power!
[HANAMARU]
Uh!
[YOSHIKO groans]
Zura?
--[RUBY squeaks]
--[DIA] Ruby! Are you okay?
Speak to me!
My bad!
This kinda activity is a
little more on my level.
[RUBY]
Mine, too.
[YOSHIKO laughs] My heart,
which was defiled by light,
is now purified
through darkness.
[GIRLS laughing]
[HANAMARU, RUBY]
Look at your face!
Stop it! It's not funny!
It's a stigma!
[sighs] I'm bored.
Yeah, me too. Why can't we
just go to the beach?
Aw, I know that readin' books
is typically more of a solo
activity. Still though.
If we all read together,
then we can tell each other
what we thought of our books...
They're asleep?
I'm afraid their attention
spans are rather short.
So. I've been thinking,
and here's what I
figured out so far.
There are two groups.
Wow. This would be the perfect
day to go diving, dontcha think?
Si , I'll totally go
with you sometime!
The third-year students
prefer outdoor activities.
[gasps]
This is the perfect opportunity
to summon some new demons.
While the first-year students
prefer to be indoors--
reading books and such.
So, what are we gonna do?
I do have one idea.
Did you find a solution?
At a time like this,
what this group needs to do
is reveal our deepest selves!
In other words--we need
to open up to each other.
[ALL]
Open up?
How simplistic.
Yes, it's tradition.
Since olden times,
bathing together has been
a part of our culture.
Not only does it bring us
together, but it builds
communication while
encouraging team work.
That's nice, but it's
way too early for a bath.
A fallen angel would
never reveal her body.
I'm staying in here!
[HANAMARU]
Look, Yoshiko!
[YOSHIKO]
Uh?
[HANAMARU] They have a milk bath
of darkness over there, zura!
[GIRLS]
What is she talking about?
Oh, really?
[laughing]
The bath... It's creating a
pathos, and it's amazing!
You know, it sounds really
creepy when you put it that way.
Nuh-uh!
I'm like, so totally bored.
Yeah, I'm kinda over
this dumb bath idea already.
Seriously?! You could try
to be a little more patient!
Huh? Where'd Ruby go?
[RUBY grunting]
--Ah! This is heavenly!
--[drip]
[KANAN] We just wasted
all that time bathing,
and now it's raining.
[MARI]
Here, Kanan.
Thanks, Mari.
[GIRLS sigh]
It feels like we haven't
achieved anything.
Yeah, fat lot of good
that bath did us.
It did me good--I'm so relaxed!
Me, too.
In the end, I wasn't able
to solve anything.
--It's hopeless.
--Yep.
I think our differences
might be more obvious.
[RUBY] This is awful.
I don't even have my umbrella.
[YOSHIKO]
What should we do now?
Go back to where
we were earlier?
[KANAN]
It's kinda far in the rain.
[RUBY sneezes] But we probably
shouldn't stay out here, either.
[ALL sigh]
There's a temple. My family's
acquainted with it
and it's actually not
too far from here.
[ALL]
Uh?
You can come in, zura.
Oh. But, is it okay?
You sure?
[HANAMARU]
Uh-huh, I asked and they said
to make ourselves at home.
[DIA] But, wouldn't we be
disrupting the owner?
[HANAMARU] Not really,
since they don't live here.
We're all by ourselves.
[RUBY squeaks]
[DIA]
I guess we have no choice.
At least it's better than
standing in the rain.
[MARI]
Especially since it doesn't look
like it's going to let up.
[RUBY, KANAN squeak]
[YOSHIKO laughs]
The power of the darkness,
and the power of little
demons. I can feel--
It's a Buddhist temple.
Right, I knew that.
[YOSHIKO]
Uh. Where's the light switch?
[HANAMARU]
They don't have lights.
Wow, for real?
[GIRLS groan]
So, what should we do?
Not that I'm the least bit
scared, mind you.
--[creak]
--[yelps] Hug!
I guess we could work on
our song, if you want.
[RUBY] But what if you all
start fighting again?
Uh. I mean, we have
to write a song anyway,
so we might as well
all pull together
and give it a fair shot.
It's worth a try.
Who knows?
Maybe we'll crank one out.
That'd be wonderful.
Anyone come up with any lyrics?
I saw Yoshiko writing some.
I bet they're pretty good.
Hey, don't be so nosy!
Oh? That's great.
--Way to go!
--Good job!
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
I've hidden my lyric book
and to find where it is,
you'll have to solve a
complex set of riddles.
Each one more complicated
than the last!
I found it!
You cheated!
[RUBY]
What's it say?
[KANAN]
"The Ordeal of Shooting Scars"?
[YOSHIKO]
It's Order of Shooting Stars!
[DIA] What's with these
horrid ink blotches?
[YOSHIKO]
They're Black Blanks, duh!
[DIA]
I can't read them.
--[creak]
--[gasps]
[YOSHIKO] Well, maybe it's
because I don't want you to,
ever think of that?!
[HANAMARU] That sounds like
a handy excuse, zura.
[RUBY] So, how's the
composing coming along?
[MARI]
It's coming.
I bet Chika-chi's music is
super energetic as well!
What's this? A shrine kitty?
[HANAMARU]
How energetic is it?
[DIA] Hold on a second, this
Black Blank thingie moves.
How odd.
[RUBY]
Wait. Oh my gosh, it's a bug!
[RUBY, DIA scream]
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[HANAMARU]
Zura?
[GIRLS scream]
What are we going to do?
This is terrible.
We still can't work
together at all.
At the rate we're going,
we'll never be able to come
up with a decent song.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Well, this sucks.
It's just hard to believe
that we're so different.
--[drip]
--[BOTH yelp]
The roof's leakin'!
What'll we do?
Look, we can use these plates!
It's leaking here,
too! I need...
Here Mari, set one of these
bowls down under the leak.
[YOSHIKO] There's another one,
hand me a plate!
[KANAN]
Okay!
[HANAMARU]
I need one too, zura.
[RUBY] Sis! Do you see
a bucket or anything?
[DIA]
I'll check!
[GIRLS chattering]
[DIA]
Found one!
[rain clinking]
[clinking continues,
music plays]
[BOTH laugh]
Hear the tempo and the tone?
The way it sounds.
They're all different,
and right now they may
sound a little out of sync.
But they're coming
together, one by one.
And they're harmonizing,
one by one.
Together, it's starting
to make a song.
We can do it too, zura.
[GIRLS laughing]
[MARI]
Okay!
We'll have an impromptu
training camp here tonight!
--[HANAMARU] Zura?
--[GIRLS] What?!
[RIKO]
Chika!
Why on earth are you
up on the roof?
--I'm shining.
--[RIKO] What?
[CHIKA] I saw something,
and what I want to say,
what I've been thinking...
...I think it's the answer
to the question...
...the one that I've
been asking myself...
Finally...
That's great news.
[KANAN]
Chika!
Ah! Morning!
[YOU]
Did you finish your song?
Naturally! Of course, we did!
[GIRLS]
See?!
That's awesome!
[RIKO]
Now we just have to practice.
[YOU]
Since we have two songs,
we'll have to work
twice as hard!
[CHIKA] Yep! For our school,
and for Love Live!
[GIRLS]
Next time, "Rainbow."