[YOU]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[YOU]
Aye-aye!
With the deadline for the
merger quickly approaching,
Aqours decided to
try a formation
they couldn't previously master.
[MARI] You know, that
may solve our problem.
[YOU] However, it was way harder
than we could have imagined.
But Chika never gave up,
and we all cheered her on.
[RIKO] This isn't about us,
you don't owe us anything.
We're excited and ready...
...ready to find our
radiance together, with you!
[STAFF]
Okay everyone!
Are you ready to see your
finalists for Love Live?
Only three groups will
move to the final round...
Come on!
[STAFF 7A] And there they
are, the top three groups!
--[YOU] Yes!
--[AUDIENCE cheering]
--[CHIKA] No way, for real?
[AUDIENCE cheering]
Did we really do it?
It isn't a dream, right?
It's for real.
[CHIKA]
Seriously?
I mean, this is the final round?
The dome?
If this really is happening,
then it's a miracle!
[RIKO]
You're right, it is.
It is a miracle, made by us!
Yeah!
All right, here we go!
Full speed ahead, mateys!
[GIRLS]
Love Live, ho!
[YOU]
And, salute!
[HANAMARU]
I was just so nervous
I couldn't eat anythin'
the whole time, zura!
I can't believe it.
Next up is Akiba Dome.
I wonder what it's like inside.
[RIKO]
I'll compose a great song!
[YOU] And we should make our
next dance even more energetic!
[music plays]
Whoa, look!
Check out how many views it has!
[YOSHIKO, HANAMARU gasp]
[CHIKA gasps]
You're right, it's more
than I ever imagined.
[DIA] Turns out that
having fewer students
may have been an advantage.
People love the underdog.
That's why so many of
them were rooting for us.
[gasps]
So, did the applicants increase?
[YOSHIKO]
Hey, what's wrong?
[KANAN]
No way.
[DIA]
They didn't?
Maybe.
I'm sure my phone
is just frozen.
After all it was still
going up yesterday.
There's no reason why
that would change.
[RUBY] But the deadline Mari's
dad set is tonight, right?
What if we failed?
I wouldn't worry.
Besides, that means
there's still time.
If we look on the
school computer
then we should know
the exact number.
[MARI]
Mm.
[CHIKA]
Okay!
Let's go!
[MARI]
Hold on, I'll pull it up.
[keyboard clacking]
Well?
[MARI]
It hasn't changed.
For real?
So there's...
cosmic interference?
[DIA]
This really is it.
[KANAN] And there're
only four hours left.
[MARI] What's going on
with the video views?
[RUBY] It's been going
up this whole time!
I'm going to call my father.
It's been a while.
I'm worried.
Well, he's in a
different time zone,
so it's possible Mari's having a
hard time getting a hold of him.
[door opens]
Sorry that took so long.
Were you able to talk
to your dad at all?
Mm. Yeah, kinda.
I told him we were going
to the final round
and that our video is
getting a ton of views.
What'd he say?
[MARI sighs]
On the plus side, he did agree
to give us an extension.
However, just until
5 AM our time.
If we don't have a
hundred applicants by five,
then they'll shut down
the application page.
[KANAN] So this really
is our last chance.
Still though, at
least now there're
eight hours until the
deadline instead of three!
Ah! Look, we just got
one more person!
That's good news!
I bet they signed up after
watching our performance online.
At this rate, we
just might make it.
[YOSHIKO, RIKO, YOU gasp]
[YOSHIKO]
Hey, where are you going?
[CHIKA] The train station.
And when I get there,
I'll ask everyone to
support Uranohoshi High!
And then...!
I'll, uh...
Not at this time
of night, Chika.
'Kay!
Then we'll put on a concert,
and stream it online!
By the time we put it
together, it'll be morning.
Fine then, we'll--
[CHIKA gasps]
Just calm down!
It's okay.
It'll be okay.
But...
...I have to do something!
[KANAN] Then believe
in our performance.
And hope that it's enough.
I guess you're right.
Our video does have
a lot of views, so...
...I'm sure it'll work out.
[DIA]
Right.
With that settled, we should
all probably head home.
At a time like this?
I really don't feel like
being alone right now.
We'd never be able to relax.
We're too anxious.
Now what?
Well I can't force you to go.
So, it's okay if we stay?
If your parents give
you permission,
and if our director
will allow it.
Of course!
Let's see it through together.
[RUBY gasps]
Another person just signed up!
It hasn't changed.
We're still at 87.
You stupid, broken, computer!
Stop it.
There's nothing wrong
with the computer.
Unfortunately, this is reality.
We tried our hardest.
And now people know
the name "Uranohoshi."
[KANAN] Even though
our town is beautiful,
and the people who
live here are kind,
it's still out of the way
as far as schools go.
[stomach growls]
Hey, you know what?
I don't think any of us
have eaten a single thing
since lunch today.
--[HANAMARU, RUBY chuckle]
--[YOSHIKO grumbles]
[YOSHIKO] Seriously, do we
have to do everything for them?
I mean, managing my little
demons keeps me busy enough!
I don't mind, zura.
Chika, You, and Riko
started the current Aqours,
so it makes sense
that they'd wanna stay.
And my sister, Mari, and Kanan,
well, they were the ones that
created the previous Aqours.
[HANAMARU]
They feel responsible, you know?
I suppose, but they don't
have to feel that way.
I guess what I'm trying
to say is... I'm grateful.
[gasps]
[YOSHIKO]
Uh...
Grateful... 'cause Aqours
gave me the opportunity
to recruit more demons!
Takin' care of each other
is what friends do, zura.
I'm really glad I joined Aqours.
[RUBY]
Me too.
[laughs]
Because of Aqours,
we're all friends.
We'll always
support one another.
[HANAMARU]
We sure will.
[YOSHIKO] Hmph. As a reward
for saying something nice,
I'll give you a mocha-kinchaku .
[HANAMARU] Aw, but I'd rather
have a kuro hanpen , zura.
[YOSHIKO]
Sorry, that's taken!
[RUBY]
I want an egg, please!
[YOSHIKO]
Uh, that's taken, too!
--[RUBY, HANAMARU laugh]
--[YOSHIKO] Stop being so picky!
We're at 94.
Just six more.
How much time's left?
Less than an hour.
[CHIKA]
Please!
Pretty please!
We only need six more,
I beg of you!
So please!
Please go up.
Oh, Chika.
It's kinda hard to believe, but
even You can run outta steam.
Hey, I'm not asleep.
Still though, I am tired.
Waiting takes it out of you.
[CHIKA]
Fresh air!
Well, this is it.
Just six more, pretty please!
Yes, please, and thank you!
Hey!
Uranohoshi High is
the best school ever!
[BOTH giggle]
Also!
If you come to our school,
you won't regret it!
Yeah, and the students
here are like super nice!
[RIKO]
I guarantee it!
So come! Won't you?
[CHIKA giggles]
Wow, a Riko Guarantee?
Everybody knows you can
bank on my guarantees.
[ALL laugh]
[RUBY]
Chika!
Quick!
[CHIKA]
Only three more!
But look, it's almost 5!
Come on.
Please!
[CHIKA]
It's at 98!
[MARI gasps]
[KANAN]
But the time.
[CHIKA]
It'll be okay. We'll make it.
I know we will, it'll be fine.
[CHIKA]
We'll make it.
We'll be okay.
We'll make it!
Applications are closed?
[DIA]
The deadline has passed.
No way, it's gonna be fine!
If we had one more day.
No, even half a day would work!
Heck, just an hour!
We'd definitely make
it to a hundred, so...
[DIA]
That wasn't the deal.
But we just need
a little more time.
[YOU]
Yeah, she's right!
It's not like we need much.
Couldn't we ask
Mari's dad again?
[DIA]
We did ask.
We called him several times
throughout the night.
It's no use.
He'd already given
us two extensions,
and we couldn't
make the deadline.
[MARI]
Even my dad has limits.
He doesn't have the full
authority to make this decision.
He did everything he could.
Really?
So not even one day?
[YOSHIKO]
We're not asking much.
[MARI]
It's too late.
They've probably already
started the merger.
So...
It's over?
This is really the end?
It can't be, because... because
we haven't struggled enough yet.
We promised that we'd
struggle as hard as we could.
We all swore that we'd
try everything possible!
And that's what we did.
We even made it
to the final round.
No matter what, we
never stopped trying.
[CHAIR squeaks]
[groans]
Chika!
[CHIKA whimpers]
Then why'd we fail?
Why is our school closing down?
Why weren't our
efforts good enough?
It isn't fair.
It isn't fair!
[DIA]
Where are you going?
I'll ask my father
for one more extension.
If you keep asking him,
then they'll end up letting
you go as the director.
It's time we face the facts.
Our school... is closing.
[MARI] Starting next year,
Uranohoshi Girls' High School
will be merged with
another school in Numazu.
New adventures are
always challenging,
but I hope you'll
all flourish and thrive
at your new school next spring.
I sincerely wish you
the best of luck.
[FEMALE STUDENTS chattering]
[YOU]
Chika?
Earth to Chika.
Come on.
It's time to switch classes.
Oh, sorry.
[MUTSU]
Chika!
You all made it
into the final round!
Way to go!
Yeah, now show those other
groups who's boss at Love Live!
We can't wait to
hear your next song!
[CHIKA]
Yeah?
[ITSUKO]
It'll be at Akiba Dome, right?
Think of how much space
you'll have to perform!
We'll try to get good seats.
[MUTSU]
Don't worry!
We'll all be there, and we're
gonna cheer extra loud!
[YOSHIMI, MUTSU, ITSUKO gasp]
You okay?
That sounds awesome!
We're gonna do our best to win.
[MUTSU] Whoa, you kinda
scared me there.
[MUTSU, YOSHIMI, ITSUKO laugh]
Let's try and focus
on the next step.
We should probably start
prepping for Love Live.
[CHIKA]
I know.
[DIA] While it's unfortunate
that our school is closing down,
we need to focus on
practicing for Love Live.
Let's try and put
all that behind us.
It's time for a fresh start
so we can work hard on
winning that final round.
Count me in!
Performing in a den of evil
with 55,000 demons is my jam!
Oh, so you'll be performin'
your comedy routine, Yoshiko?
I-It's Yohane!
[RUBY]
Also, I'd like to add,
for all the third years here,
this will actually be their
final Love Live performance.
That's why... I want...
...to win!
No matter what!
Ruby.
Brava! We're totally
going to win!
[KANAN] That's a little
easier said than done.
[RIKO]
But...
We have to believe we can win.
I know we can.
[MARI] Well then,
time to get warmed up.
[KANAN] All right, we'll
start off nice and slow.
[GIRLS]
Okay!
[KANAN]
First, let's stretch it out.
And start.
--[GIRLS] 1, 2...
--[CHIKA] Yeah.
I guess all we can do is focus
on Love Live for right now.
[GIRLS] ...3, 4.
3, 2, 3, 4. 4, 2, 3, 4.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Something wrong?
You okay?
Chika.
[CHIKA]
What's up?
Why'd you stop?
You know what?
Let's just call it a day.
[gasps] What for?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
I thought we should
focus on the future,
even if we had to
force ourselves.
But feelings don't really
work that way, do they?
I'm seriously okay!
Besides, you heard
what Ruby said earlier.
This will be our
last performance.
So we...
...we need--
It's not just you.
[CHIKA gasps]
It's everyone here.
Look, we are only human.
Did you honestly believe
that we can all just
let go of our feelings?
[KANAN]
You know what.
I think it would be best if we
all took some time to think.
About whether or not we
should really perform
in the Love Live final round.
It'd be good for us.
Yes, that's a good idea.
Hey, what do you mean?
Of course we're going to
perform at Love Live!
How could we not?
What about the third years?
Do you really feel that way?
That's what you need to
dig deep and ask yourself.
Not just Chika-chi,
but all of us.
Why hello!
Morning.
[RIKO]
How 'bout that?
Looks like we're all here.
Indeed.
[MARI]
This proves it!
Everyone feels the
same way after all.
[RIKO] I would definitely
feel better if we performed.
[RUBY] But... we weren't
able to save our school.
Is it really okay to go to
the final round and sing?
[YOSHIKO] Winning
wouldn't save our school.
Well yes, you're
not wrong there.
Still though, let's face it,
that's not why we became idols.
What's the real reason
behind us forming Aqours?
We wanted to find our radiance.
Not just in each other,
but to find our own
individual radiance as well.
We can--
No we can't.
Because even if we
manage to win Love Live,
our school will still be gone.
If we had, by some miracle,
saved our school,
then I think we could've shined.
We could have
found our radiance.
But we didn't save our school.
So how are we supposed
to find our radiance?!
Right now,
I don't care about
winning Love Live anymore.
finding our radiance.
I want to save our school!
Because this is where we all
spent so much time together.
[MUTSU]
Then save it!
[gasps]
[YOSHIMI]
Yeah, go and save it!
Perform in Love Live!
[YOSHIMI, ITSUKO, MUTSU]
And win it all!
No way.
If I could, I'd do
it in a heartbeat!
If I could keep struggling
with everyone, then I would!
You would what?!
I would...
...I would keep
our school alive!
[ITSUKO] But is that the only
way you can keep it alive?
[MUTSU] The thing is, we asked
everyone here at school!
What they wanted the
nine of you to do,
and what would
make them all happy!
Everyone said the same thing.
We want Aqours to win Love Live!
Don't just win it
for yourselves,
but win it for all of us, too!
Win it for the whole school!
[YOSHIMI] You can
preserve our school's name
as the winners of Love Live!
Our school's name?
Everything is up to you now!
You're the only
hope we have left!
Please go to Love Live
and perform!
Aqours,
you are the Uranohoshi
High School Idols!
Win and make that name a
part of Love Live history.
Immortalize our school,
so the world will never
forget Uranohoshi!
[YOSHIMI, ITSUKO, MUTSU]
We want you. We want you.
We want you!
[ALL]
To find your radiance!
Right, if we win, they'll
record our school's name.
So let's win Love Live.
[CHIKA crying]
Hey, Chika.
[YOU, RIKO]
You give up?
[CHIKA]
How could I give up!
I can't do that, I can't
do that, I won't do that!
We're gonna win!
No, we won't just win, we're
gonna knock it out of the park!
We'll win at Akiba Dome
in that final round.
No matter who we face!
You better believe.
We'll leave our school's
name in Love Live history!
We'll immortalize our
school and our memories!
Yeah!
Come on Love Live, hit us
with everything you've got!
We're not afraid!
For real! I feel
like we could take on
the whole world right now!
I agree!
Attention my little demons,
the final battle has now begun!
It's time for Yohane
to descend at last!
[YOU]
Let's go for a run!
I gotta get rid of this energy!
Come on, everyone!
But I don't wanna!
--[MARI laughs]
--[RUBY] No!
Hey, hurry up, Riko!
So long "normal monster."
'Cause now there's a much
stronger monster in town.
Named Chika.
[YOSHIKO]
Wait for me, everyone!
Don't leave me!
[CHIKA giggles]
[GIRLS]
Next time, "Hakodate."