[CHIKA]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[CHIKA]
Mandarin oranges!
The day before
the closing festival,
all of the girls at our school
pulled together
to make it the
best event possible.
Oh wow, it's just Shiitake.
[CHIKA]
We were happy and humbled.
It was such a warm experience.
If only we could
freeze that moment in time.
But, all good things
must come to an end.
And now, after a long journey,
we've reached our destination.
We're ready!
[YOU]
Do you have everything?
I think so.
That festival was fun, huh?
[CHIKA]
Mm-hm. It was.
You know what?
We should channel that
positive energy into the finals.
Hi, Riko!
Hey, Chika.
I agree,
we've worked hard for this.
We have to give
Love Live our all.
[DIA] We practiced and put in
long hours every single day.
Early in the morning,
until the sun set.
Yeah, we always did our Rubesty!
[KANAN] Rain or shine, we never
skipped a practice session.
Even though we
whined about them.
[HANAMARU] It sure was hard
wakin' up early every day. Zura.
Right, Yoshiko?
It's Yohane!
But yeah, I'm so proud
of my little demons.
I praise you all!
Thanks, ladies.
We're heading out now!
[GIRLS]
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm not scared anymore.
So, what should we do now?
The finals
aren't until tomorrow.
I'm pretty sure Lili
wants to go hit up Bukuro.
What?! Why would I go there?
Bukuro?
They have trashy books to buy!
Time for my
secret technique,
"Silent Cherry
Blossom Nightmare!"
Riko's slowly
turning into Yoshiko.
First thing's first.
Let's go to the shrine, 'kay?
[GIRLS panting]
Oh!
It's super belissimo up here.
I forgot how many
stairs there were.
Yeah, but don't you think
it was easier to climb
this time around?
It was, huh?
Growth is often something you
don't notice until afterwards.
Right!
Let's say a prayer for tomorrow.
[clapping]
Please let our feelings shine
to everyone
sitting in the crowd.
Please let me perform
with everything I've got.
I hope that I don't
get stage fright.
say "zura," zura.
Please let us bring joy
to all my little demons.
I hope we'll all be
able to sing perfectly.
And convey the feelings
of everyone at Uranohoshi.
I hope that tomorrow
we'll give the best performance
we've ever given.
Let us win.
Please let us win Love Live.
[HANAMARU]
Zura!
[RUBY, HANAMARU]
Wow.
What's up?
Check it out!
[CHIKA]
That's us.
[YOU]
Look! There're more!
The girls from school
came here too.
[CHIKA] Not just once,
but several times.
They never told us,
but they came here often.
Of course.
The bellas at Uranohoshi
are always cheering for us.
[YOU]
Chika.
Look at these.
There are more schools.
[RUBY]
All of these school idol groups,
came here to pray for Love Live?
[HANAMARU]
There are so many of them.
Guess we're not the only ones.
Those girls also came here
to pray for victory.
[SARAH]
Long time, no see.
[CHIKA]
Sarah!
[RUBY]
Leah!
So this is it,
the Love Live finals.
If you show fear,
you'll lose tomorrow.
Um yeah, we know.
But it's Akiba Dome.
It'll be different
from other venues, zura.
Can't even imagine
what the place must be like.
It's unreal.
I still can't believe
I got to sing there.
It was so exciting.
Everywhere I looked, there were
tons of lights sparkling.
It felt like we were floating
above the clouds somehow.
Above the clouds?
That's why,
I'm not gonna forgive you
if you put on a half-baked show.
I would never do that!
Watch, I'll do my Rubesty!
[LEAH laughs]
Let's sing together again soon.
[RUBY]
Okay.
Those smiles are wonderful.
Yes!
[SARAH]
When I first met you,
I didn't think your group
stood a chance of winning.
But now, when I look at
the girls standing before me,
I see a group of
very promising idols.
[SARAH]
Do you want to win?
You asked me that once,
so now it's my turn to ask you.
Tomorrow,
do you want to win?
And...
...who exactly
are you singing for?
[HANAMARU]
Whoa!
This manju looks amazin'!
Huh?
[HANAMARU whines]
This is way fun!
It feels like we're on
a school trip or something.
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
This is destiny, of course!
If you say so, zura.
That's so unladylike!
Know what?
This kinda reminds me of
the last time we were here.
Do you remember that concert?
Yeah.
Since we had gotten
people's attention,
I thought we
might be pretty good.
But the truth was...
[YOSHIKO] It's too early
to start feeling anxious.
Should we practice?
We'll be okay.
We need to have faith.
I'm sure our hard work
will pay off.
They're both right.
Besides, at this point I really
doubt we'll lose tomorrow.
So we win, and our
school's name gets recorded,
forever in Love Live history.
[CHIKA]
That's why we're doing this.
Isn't it?
[door opens]
[rustling]
What's wrong?
[YOU grunts]
What the--?
Hey, what are you doing?
[HANAMARU, RIKO, YOSHIKO gasp]
--[MARI] Shining Tornado!
--[laughs] Take that!
[YOU gasps]
How do you like me now?
I won't be able to do
silly stuff like this
once I move to Italy.
Think fast!
[RUBY squeals]
I can't believe
you have the nerve
to throw a pillow at my sister.
This is ridiculous,
we have Love Live tomorrow--
Oh no!
That's funny, I guess the
pillows aren't the softest thing
in this room
after all, huh, Dia?
[DIA]
What did you just say?
Please don't.
[DIA] Get ready,
'cause I'm bringing the pain!
[KANAN]
Oh, was that supposed to hurt?
[MARI]
Shiny!
Zura!
Um, what is the deal
with the upperclassmen?
Well it turns out
that they actually
have a long-standing argument
over which one's
the best at pillow fights.
How childish.
I don't think you have
much room to talk, Yoshiko.
It's Yohane--
[YOSHIKO gasps]
[YOSHIKO]
That does it!
[GIRLS yelling]
Well, Chika?
You feel better?
Don't you it's great
that we're doing this
the day before finals?
It feels right!
I like that we can be
our normal... selves!
[MARI gasps]
[MARI]
Shiny!
--[GIRLS yelling]
--[DIA] You are all amateurs!
--[YOU] Pillow cannons fire!
--[RIKO] Take this! Ha!
[YOU sighs]
That was pretty crazy.
Just remember, you started it.
It might be spring,
but it's kinda chilly.
Did you wanna visit?
Huh?
Otonokizaka.
Your old school?
Yeah, maybe.
I thought it'd be nice
to see how I feel.
You know, after all this time.
Well, okay.
Wanna go tomorrow?
Nah.
Besides, we have a show.
But, are you sure?
[CHIKA] What if we just
met up at the venue instead,
so everyone could have
some free time before that?
Huh?
We can all do our own thing.
Go where we wanna go.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
Still though...
It'll be fine.
We can use the time,
you know, for self-reflection.
I want to do it, too, so...
[RIKO]
Sounds good.
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[MUTSU]
This place is amazing!
[ITSUKO] I can't believe
they're performing here.
[YOSHIMI]
I hope they'll hear us cheering.
Course they will!
We'll cheer so loud
they won't have a choice
but to hear us up on stage.
[MITO]
That's right.
[ALL]
Huh?
It's not just Uranohoshi, kids.
As it happens, the whole town
came out to cheer, right?
[YOSHIMI, ITSUKO, MUTSU]
Uh...
[CHIKA'S MOM]
Okay, everyone!
You ready to be
the best supporters ever?
Let me hear you say "yeah"!
[UCHIURA CROWD]
Yeah!
[RIKO'S MOM]
Wait a minute, where's Shiitake?
[CHIKA'S MOM] Holding down
the fort, of course!
[barks]
[piano plays]
[CHIKA]
Hey, Hanamaru.
Do you... wanna win?
Zura?
[CHIKA]
Love Live.
Do you wanna win?
Not long ago,
there was a time where I
would have been content to just
sit in the library with Ruby
and read books all day.
But one day I met you, Chika,
and then everything
was different.
Because of Aqours
I was kinda forced out of my
shell, but I'm glad it happened.
So yes, I wanna win.
Nothin' in the world would
make me happier, zura.
Thank you for lettin' me be
an idol and a part of Aqours.
[RUBY] Before, I couldn't
do anything on my own.
Then I became a school idol.
That alone would make me happy.
Then again, this is
the last Love Live show
for the third years,
so of course
I'd like for us to win.
But now, being able to sing
with the girls I love so much,
makes me even happier!
[YOSHIKO]
What? Are you serious?
Of course I wanna win tomorrow!
How else am I going to
demonstrate my divine power?
I mean, all my little demons
will be watching!
[chuckles]
That power plays a
crucial part in our victory.
We shall prevail in Love Live!
So, for Aqour's sake,
I suppose this fallen angel
can remain fallen
a little bit longer.
[CHIKA]
Thank you,
Yoshiko.
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
[YOSHIKO]
Yohane!
[KANAN]
Why are you asking that now?
[KANAN] We've worked hard,
so of course I wanna win.
I mean, who wouldn't?
But mostly,
I just wanna enjoy it.
Since this is my last
performance with Mari and Dia.
Knowing that after tomorrow
it'll all be over,
it's actually kind of a relief.
That's why I want us to win.
Because then,
I can enjoy this memory
that much more.
Do I wanna win?
As Uranohoshi's director,
I'd like to
for our school's sake,
and for all the people
who've supported us.
Plus, I'd really love to make
the girls at our school proud.
And yet, if I could be
just a bit selfish...
I'll admit,
I want to win for us.
This might be the last chance,
for the nine of us.
Let's do something grande !
[giggles]
[MARI]
Shiny!
[DIA] That answer
should be pretty obvious.
We came out here with the
feelings of our fellow students
on our shoulders.
We will win Love Live.
[DIA] Also, I want to sing with
all my heart as Dia Kurosawa,
a member of Aqours.
No matter where we perform,
I truly believe that my singing
should come from the heart.
If we do that, we'll be okay!
[EVENT STAFF] This is the moment
you've all been waiting for,
the Love Live Finals!
Which of these fantastic idol
groups will emerge victorious?
[YOU]
Here!
[CHIKA]
You.
Hey there.
So Chika, what brings you here?
For some reason,
I just wanted to see this place.
Wow, you too, huh?
Huh? So...
Because, this is
where everything started.
[YOU gasps]
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH panting]
[CHIKA]
I hope we find it.
You know, the radiance that I
wanted to find way back then.
I am certain that you will.
In fact,
I think you'll find it soon.
Don't worry.
How about you?
[YOU]
Hm?
[CHIKA]
Do you wanna win?
Love Live?
[YOU]
Of course.
This is something
I was able to do with you.
So it's okay to be normal,
and to just be yourself.
You don't have to be
afraid of the future.
Because...
[YOU sniffles]
...you aren't alone, Chika.
We're with you!
Thank you, You.
Ah! Hey, Riko!
Did you play the piano?
[RIKO]
I sure did!
I wanted to ask,
do you wanna win Love Live?
[RIKO]
Mm-hm.
Honestly, in my heart,
I know this was the path
I was meant to travel.
I believe it a hundred percent.
You saved me, when I was scared
and running away from the piano.
Meeting you and the rest
of Aqours, it was a miracle.
So the answer is yes.
I want us to win Love Live.
I want to prove that I made
the right choice in the end!
I want to savor
this moment with you.
With everyone!
Because I want to
be a school idol!
[RIKO cries]
[GIRLS laugh]
[YOU]
N' you, Chika?
[RIKO]
What do you want?
[YOU]
That paper.
We turned a zero into a one.
It wasn't easy, but we did it.
And I... well I was just normal.
But being a normal monster?
That's how I became who I am!
I wanna to do my best
to win today!
I'm going win Love Live
and find my radiance!
There it goes.
Thank you.
I think we'll be okay.
Are you ready? Shall we go?
[CHIKA]
Mm-hm!
So what did you write
on your votive tablet?
Sorry, but that is a secret.
Although, I'm positive
what I wrote will come true.
And then it won't
be a secret anymore.
[MARI]
Speaking of,
remember back when I was
going to transfer schools
a few years ago?
Didn't you wish...
we'd be together forever?
See? I'm good at this.
Are you sure?
We're about to be
separated again.
[MARI]
We'll be together.
Because the entire
sky's connected.
No matter how far apart we are,
we'll still be together!
Even if our eyes can't see it.
[GIRLS laugh]
Now, let's get going!
Yoshiko?
It's Yohane!
So, there's something
I need to tell you.
You too, Ruby.
[RUBY squeaks]
[HANAMARU]
What's up, zura?
I should think
it's fairly obvious.
With our school closing
and the Love Live finals
happening today,
your contract with me--
[HANAMARU]
You don't have to worry.
We're not going to
break the contract
between you, me, and Ruby,
because it's absolute, zura.
Yeah, even after we're
at a new school.
[YOSHIKO]
Hmph!
Why are you saying
my line for me?
Thank you!
[RUBY]
Yeah, I'm really grateful-uby!
[GIRLS laugh]
[CHIKA]
My heart is totally racing!
[YOU] I bet the stage
is gonna be huge!
[RIKO] It's hard to
even imagine, isn't it?
[HANAMARU]
Zura!
[YOSHIKO]
Looks like we're right on time.
[RUBY]
Our next stop is the dome, huh?
I can't wait!
[DIA]
So, are you ready?
[KANAN]
Akiba Dome.
It's one of the biggest venues
in the whole country!
[MARI]
Love Live is finally here!
[CHIKA]
I wonder how far we've run.
I wonder how far we've come.
How far we'll continue to go.
I don't have the answers.
Everything we've done
and everywhere we've been,
it's all led us to where we are
right now in this moment.
Sarah said that Akiba Dome was
like being above the clouds!
Let's enjoy this
as much as we can.
Let's go all out,
and let's win Love Live!
In order to find our own
radiance and finally shine!
Are you ready?
And one!
And two!
And three!
And four!
And five!
And six!
Seven!
And eight!
Nine!
[CHIKA]
From zero to one!
And from one
to something greater!
[GIRLS]
Aqours! Sun... shine!
[singing in Japanese]
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[GIRLS]
Next time, "Our Own Shine."