[HANAMARU]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[HANAMARU]
Zura!
Aqours found ourselves in a bind
when we had to perform
two concerts in one day.
And take flight,
eternal phoenix!
How far's the school from there?
[KANAN] It's over here,
but there's no bus or train
that goes all the
way there, so...
[HANAMARU] We did our
best to try and make it
to both concerts,
but it was a struggle.
Need a lift, girls?
Hop on board!
[HANAMARU]
Luckily, we had some friends
who were willin' to
lend us a hand, zura!
Thanks to them, our concerts
were a huge success!
[RIKO yawns]
[CHIKA]
Good morning!
And goodbye!
[RIKO]
You're up early!
[CHIKA]
Morning! I'm headed out now,
I hope everyone
has an awesome day!
That's weird.
[SHIITAKE barks]
I wonder if it's
going to rain today.
[CHIKA humming]
Chika seems like
she's in a good mood.
How is that possible?
Maybe she forgot what today is.
She must have, or she'd
never be this calm.
You think so?
Hey, Chika.
[CHIKA]
Yeah?
So uh, do you happen
to know what today is?
[CHIKA]
Hm?
The day they
announce the results
from the Love Live
qualifiers, right?
[GIRLS]
Huh?!
We thought you'd plum forgot!
But, aren't you nervous Chika?
No! I'm not!
Because, in the end
we were all together.
We were able to put on
such a beautiful show!
I just know we passed.
Actually, I talked to Sarah
about it yesterday.
As far as I can tell, you'll
prob'ly be the top-ranked group.
You really think so?
Yep.
Seriously?
Wow, I had no idea the
two of you were so close.
It's here!
[GIRLS gulp]
[HANAMARU]
I'm so nervous, zura!
[RUBY]
Okay, here goes.
[GIRLS gasp]
[RIKO] Wait, does this mean
we were the top ranked group?
See?
Hooray!
Celebration hugs all around!
[YOSHIKO]
High-five, girl!
[YOSHIKO, MARI]
Woo!
You get it, bella !
[CHIKA]
Wanna high five, Dia?
I don't know what to do.
Again?
[RIKO]
What is it this time?
[CHIKA] Well, you know
how we just performed
in two events back-to-back?
Because of that
we're kinda broke.
[KANAN] But didn't we all just
pitch in a thousand yen?
[RUBY]
Shows are expensive.
Wait, are you sayin'... that
we're basically outta money?
Meanin' there's only one way
to make it to the finals.
Okay!
Are you ladies ready
to set sail for Tokyo?
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
Travelin' by swan boat.
What if we sink?
How much money is there?
[MARI]
Wow!
Such a shiny coin!
[RUBY]
Oh no.
[KANAN]
Five yen?!
[YOU]
Maybe it's a lucky coin?
[MARI]
Fortunato !
[YOSHIKO]
This is serious!
Hey, is something wrong?
[DIA]
No.
[DIA] I just didn't realize
that Mari and Kanan
had become so close
with the underclassmen.
[HANAMARU]
Well, girlfriend?
Got any ideas?
[KANAN]
Let me think.
What now?
"Girlfriend"?
[KANAN] Are we seriously
asking the gods for help?
[RUBY]
Yeah, why not?
It couldn't hurt to ask, right?
[CHIKA] Please increase
our money five-fold.
No, ten-fold!
Wait, a hundred-fold!
You realize that's
still not much money.
[CHIKA]
Oh...
[gasps] Feel that?
A spiritual presence!
There's nothin' here, silly.
Hold up, how would you know?
Forget gods.
Perhaps what we really
need is a goddess.
[GIRLS]
Goddess Mari!
No, you can't sweet talk me
into asking my dad!
[CHIKA]
Are you sure?
[GIRLS laugh]
Goddess... Mari?
[CHIKA]
Toodle-oo, Kanan-roo!
[HANAMARU]
Bye-bye, girlfriend!
See you at school
tomorrow, zura!
[KANAN]
Later!
[RUBY]
Don't take too long, okay, sis?
[MARI] So, what did you
wanna talk to us about?
[DIA]
Me?
Uh, well I suppose it's not
really that big of a deal.
I just couldn't help but
notice how buddy-buddy
you two have become.
[KANAN]
Buddy-buddy?
Me and who?
Kanan?
[PORPOISE cries]
Not with each other.
I meant with the first
and second year students!
[MARI]
Huh?
[KANAN]
Oh, I get it now.
Dia's jealous!
[PORPOISE cries]
What? I'm not jealous!
Besides, as the
student council president,
I cannot afford to act so casual
with the underclassmen.
[KANAN] Why do you always
have to be so stubborn?
[MARI]
Tipico Dia.
I just...
[BOTH]
Go on.
[DIA]
I just...
[PORPOISE cries]
Nothing, forget about it.
However, you two need to
start remembering that
you are upperclassmen and
should start behaving as such.
Something's fishy.
Smells like a
jealous fire rages!
[MARI] Whatever it is,
I'm sure Dia will
come to terms
with it soon enough.
She's always been a blockhead
when it comes to
her own feelings.
[KANAN]
That's for sure.
[GIRLS chattering]
I wonder what they
would nickname me?
[CHIKA]
Part-time job?
[RIKO]
Yeah, we don't have much choice.
[RIKO, CHIKA, YOU sigh]
[DIA]
Oh?
Is something troubling you?
Uh, hello.
Are you looking
for the bathroom?
I'm fine, thank you!
Uh, anyway.
What are the three of you up to?
Not much.
We were just looking
for a part-time job,
like at a store or
delivering papers, maybe.
[DIA]
In that case,
Numazu might be a good place
to start the job hunt.
Hey, that's a pretty good idea.
There is a lot of work there.
Like café jobs!
Hello and welcome!
I'll be your server today.
[YOU]
Or work as a florist.
Yes, ma'am!
This is the prettiest flower
we have in stock right now!
[YOU] If we're really lucky, we
could even get jobs as models!
The camera loves you!
Oh wow,
that would be so awesome!
For real!
'Kay, let's find work in Numazu!
[YOSHIKO, HANAMARU gasp]
Boop boop!
Wrong again!
It'll never be that simple!
Even part-time work
is still challenging.
The normal work shift
is at least
four days a week or more,
including weekends,
which would make practicing
together extremely difficult!
Even if you made the shift work,
it wouldn't be as great
as you're imagining.
Think things through!
[RIKO] As usual, President Dia
makes a good point.
[CHIKA]
Dia's so mature!
[YOU] Guess that rules out
the fun stuff though.
[CHIKA] Any other ideas,
Madame President?
[DIA]
Uh, well.
[CROWD chattering]
[KANAN]
The flea market, huh?
[DIA] I thought it'd be a
good way to make some money
without using up
too much of our time.
What a great idea, sis!
[HANAMARU] For sure!
It's easy to see why you're
the student council president!
[YOU]
You really saved us!
Well, it was nothing, but
I agree.
As a token of thanks,
please accept this
fallen angel's feather.
Wow, I'm so honored.
[DIA]
All right!
Now all I have to do
is get closer to them
and gain their trust!
[CHIKA]
Wanna walk together?
Let's go, sweetie!
[HANAMARU]
Here, these look good.
Right, girlfriend?
[YOU] Look at this pic from
when we hung out the other day.
Here, matey!
[chuckles]
Uh, you okay?
[CHIKA]
Sorry I'm late!
[YOU]
Chika.
[RUBY]
Wh-What's with the costume?
[CHIKA] My sister said her
company doesn't need it anymore,
so now it's mine!
Yay!
I'm not really sure what
you're "yay"-ing about.
[YOUNG GIRL]
Excuse me, Miss Orange.
Yes! I'm a mandarin orange!
Fruit is good for you!
Vitamin C Power. Citrus!
Uh, how much for the penguin?
Huh?
I haven't set a price yet.
Well then, would this be enough?
Oh, um...
Um...
[YOUNG GIRL]
Thanks, Miss Orange!
[CHIKA]
Take care!
All right! We made a sale!
Thanks a lot, goddess Benzaiten!
I know right?
What on earth
are you celebrating for?
[CHIKA]
Hm?
That was abysmal.
We are here because
we need to make money
to fund our club activities.
We have to be more firm
on our prices,
or we will never get anywhere!
But Dia.
[CUSTOMER A]
Excuse me,
would you take
a thousand yen for this?
Watch and learn.
Unfortunately, ma'am,
considering how much
the item originally cost,
I'm gonna have to
boop boop a lower price.
Um, why's that?
Frankly speaking, even though
these items aren't brand new,
they've barely been used at all!
In order to sell these things,
we had to clean them
carefully, one by one.
They were once our
dearest treasures, and yet,
even at the current price
we're practically
giving them away to you!
You really shouldn't
point at the customers.
[HANAMARU sighs]
We're gonna have to
take a swan boat to Tokyo.
For real?
Today was a bust.
[RIKO] At least someone was
firm on the prices we had set.
[YOU]
Just our typical Dia, right?
[CHIKA]
For sure!
[chuckles]
Well, I still can't believe Mari
brought that abomination along.
Didja think you were
gonna sell it?
Don't pick on me!
Yoshiko's stuff
didn't sell either.
[YOSHIKO]
It's Yohane.
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
Look at them fly
off into the world,
perhaps to find
their own fallen angels.
Good luck out there.
Stop babbling and
go pick them up already!
[YOSHIKO]
Yes, ma'am!
[RIKO]
A bunch flew over that way!
[GIRLS chattering]
--[DIA sighs]
--[GIRLS chattering]
[GIRLS chattering]
[CHIKA]
Hey, Kanan.
Is there something
going on with Dia?
[KANAN]
What makes you ask?
[CHIKA]
Just a hunch, I guess.
[KANAN chuckles]
You know, it's a little funny,
but you actually
have good intuition.
Why does that
sound like an insult?
It's a compliment.
Anyway, back to Dia.
Don't worry about her.
Mari and I will take care of it.
[RUBY]
Okay, we're going on ahead!
[DIA]
Be careful, see you at home.
Well? You two said
you needed to talk to me?
What is so important
that it couldn't wait?
Oh, come on, it's obvious
you're hiding something from us.
If you wanna get closer
to the underclassmen,
why don't you try
just talking to them?
That's so not it!
I don't care what they think.
Verdict?
Totally guilty!
Huh?
Whenever you try
to hide something,
you start scratching
the area around your mole.
[DIA]
Uh. It's fine.
Nothing to see here!
We've caught you red-handed!
That's right, now start talking!
[DIA clears throat]
[DIA]
You see, the thing is...
...I just...
[BOTH]
Go on.
I just...
Promise you won't laugh?
Laugh at what?
We're your friends,
we won't laugh at you!
[DIA]
Promise?
Aw, jeez.
After everything we've
all been through together?
[DIA]
Okay, I'll tell you.
[KANAN, MARI laugh]
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[KANAN, MARI giggle]
So, the way you've
been behaving lately.
Is because you want the others
to call you girlfriend?
[MARI, KANAN giggle]
Like I've already
told you both countless times,
I don't care what they call me.
But they seem friendlier
with you than with me.
Stop stressing.
It's no big deal.
It most certainly is!
What if there's a huge crater
forming in our group?
We need to be proactive about
closing it before it gets worse.
So, you're geloso .
I am not geloso !
[MARI]
Stubborn as always.
[DIA]
More importantly,
why did you ask me to come
to this place today anyway?
[KANAN] Oh, I can't believe
I forgot to tell you.
[MARI]
We got a text from You.
She managed to get us all
a temporary job for the day.
We're supposed to help out
at a special event.
[DIA]
Oh? And where is this event?
[KANAN]
Right Here.
[DIA]
Really?
[KANAN]
Yep, and we'll be working
pretty closely together all day.
[MARI] This is your chance to
get closer to the underclassmen
and earn that nickname!
My very own... nickname?
Well, who cares?
I couldn't care less what the
other girls wanna call me.
Sì , so you say.
But the truth is written
all over your face.
[ALL]
Wow!
Dolphins are super amazing!
[YOU]
Hey, everyone! Ready to work?
[CHIKA]
Huh? Was that You?
Where is she?
[YOU]
Over here.
[CHIKA]
Whoa! She's a walrus.
[YOU] To start with, we're all
gonna work in groups of three.
[GIRLS]
Right!
Wow, look at that.
You seems like she's
right at home here.
Actually, she did say
she's worked here before.
Now, we'll need to split up
if you're going to get
closer to the other girls.
[MARI]
Yep, so hurry up, bella !
Oh. Right behind you.
Here's your order!
Thanks so much for waiting.
Thank you!
We need another order of udon.
Noodles aren't really
my thing though.
Enough, this is no time
to be slacking off, ladies!
--[HANAMARU] Zura.
--[CHIKA] Okay.
[DIA gasps]
[DIA]
I almost forgot.
[MARI] Like I said, you can
come off as a little obstinate.
[KANAN] Try starting off
with some small talk
to get things rolling.
[DIA]
I can do this.
So. Chika.
Yes?
How... about this
weather, am I right?
It's... weather?
Hey, Hanamaru.
You don't like udon?
[HANAMARU gasps]
What's up?
She's acting kind of weird,
don'tcha think?
[HANAMARU] I don't have a clue,
but she looks kinda...
Heh, heh.
[BOTH] Like she might be
mad about something, zura!
[DIA] Does my face just
look angry all the time?
I can't seem to
get anything right.
Hello, Dia.
I thought you were
on food duty, sis.
Oh.
I was, but since
the lunch hour is over,
it's not as busy anymore,
so I came here to help clean up.
What's with the bucket of fish?
It's food for the sea lion.
Yeah, we get to feed it,
and the trainer even
loaned us her whistle.
That's sounds like a lot of fun.
[splashing]
Well, speak of the devil.
[barks]
[RIKO, RUBY gasp]
Don't worry, he's probably
just ready for his lunch.
But I can't help it, now that
we're face to face with him.
It's just that he's...
bigger than I thought.
And on top of that...
He's got dog... whiskers.
--[SEA LION A barks]
--[RUBY, RIKO yell]
[RIKO]
Retreat to higher ground!
Run for your life!
--[SEA LION A barks]
--[RUBY screams]
This isn't good!
[RIKO]
I got you!
[whistle blows]
That's enough!
Back into the pool, mister!
--[whistle blows]
-- [SEA LION A barks]
[RUBY sighs]
Incredible!
Saved by my sister!
[sighs]
This is great.
Not what I wanted!
If I keep it up, they'll
think I'm a control freak.
[MARI]
Things aren't going well?
[KANAN] Honestly, I can't
say I'm all that surprised.
[DIA]
Should I even ask why?
[KANAN]
For one thing,
you're not exactly what I would
consider to be outgoing.
[MARI] Sì , ever since
elementary school,
you've mostly just
hung out with us.
Hey. I wasn't that bad.
Nothing's gonna change
unless you go to them .
Okay then!
Tell me what to do...
[MARI]
It's easy-peasy!
First.
Hey, what's up... buddy?
[YOSHIKO]
Yohane! Descend!
[YOU] Did you say
something just now, Dia?
Who, me?
Nuh-uh.
Wanna help hand out balloons?
[DIA]
Sure thing... girlfriend.
--[YOSHIKO laughs]
--[DIA] Hey, Yoshiko!
Let's keep working
hard together, okay?
It's Yohane.
For real?
Yeah, what's up?
Wait, did you also just
get a chill down your spine?
Something's amiss!
I agree.
It's as if a messenger
from the celestial sphere
has materialized
into a new world.
Okay, I take it back.
[HANAMARU]
Dia seemed really upset, zura.
I know.
Hey, what's going on
with all the bubbles?
I added all the
detergent in there
so it'll get cleaned faster.
Great idea!
Zura.
[BOTH]
Uh--
[BOTH gasp]
Be careful.
Someone could get hurt.
[CHIKA, HANAMARU]
Right.
My sister's acting weird?
Yeah, she seemed
really upset earlier.
Actually, I noticed it as well.
I wonder if
something bad happened?
[YOSHIKO]
How naive.
Obviously, she has the smile of
someone possessed by darkness.
[YOU] Well, we can probably
rule out possession.
What do ya think?
We don't really have a choice
but to clue them in
to the situation.
Call her... girlfriend?
[BOTH]
Mm-hm.
The reason she's
been acting strange
is because she's been trying
all day to get closer to you.
[RUBY]
Now it makes sense.
[HANAMARU] So then
that creepy smile was just
Dia tryin' to be friendlier?
[RIKO]
I'm more shocked to find out
that she has such
a cute side to her.
[YOU] She could have just
told us what she wanted.
I know.
Anyway, she's always
been like this.
Even back when we were children
in elementary school.
She's serious, well-behaved, and
has always been very eloquent.
But because of that,
we couldn't help but feel like
she was above us.
[MARI]
Since we all felt that way,
she felt like she
should act that way.
Without meaning to, she
distanced herself from everyone.
[KANAN] Deep down, I think
Dia is just very lonely.
[KINDERGARTENERS giggling]
Wait, children! No running!
Please come back!
Jeez! Listen!
--[SEA LION B barks]
--Stop acting so crazy!
[KINDERGARTENERS giggling]
Whoa! They're outta control!
What do we do?
Don't run, please.
This is terrible!
At this rate,
someone's bound to get hurt!
[gasps]
Stop that!
[KINDERGARTENER D cries]
--[RUBY cries]
--[KINDERGARTENER D cries]
You made them
both cry, big meanie.
[YOSHIKO]
What?!
[MARI]
Such chaos!
[KANAN] Things are
definitely out of hand!
[KINDERGARTENERS giggling]
Why aren't you all listening?
[whistle blows]
Hi-ya! Everyone please
come to the stadium! Ha, ha!
[DIA] Listen, children,
if you run and yell,
you'll scare the animals
and could accidentally
hurt yourselves.
Is that fun?
Boop boop!
That's not fun at all!
So, be on your
best behavior, okay?
[KINDERGARTENERS]
'Kay!
[DIA]
It's no use.
No matter how much I try,
I can't change who I am.
[CHIKA]
What's wrong with that?
[gasps]
For what it counts,
I happen to think you're awesome
just the way you are, Dia.
Look, it's easier to goof-off
with Mari and Kanan
than it is with you.
You've always come off
as a more serious person.
But that's okay.
If we ever run into trouble,
I know you'll be there.
Whether it's
keeping us on track,
or making us
think things through,
you've got our back, always!
That's why
we're depending on you
to keep being the same Dia
that we know and love, right?
[GIRLS giggle]
Please don't ever
change your ways,
because if you did that, then,
we'd be lost without you.
[DIA] I don't care about
the nickname thing, you know!
Dia's fine.
--[KANAN, MARI giggle]
--[OTHERS] Huh?
Okay, Dia.
[GIRLS]
Girlfriend!
[YOSHIKO, RIKO]
Next time, "Taking in a Dog."