[DIA]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[DIA]
Here we go!
Mari turned down the director's
position at the new school.
[MARI]
I declined the position.
I've decided I'm going to
attend a college in Italy.
[DIA]
After their graduation,
the third years will all
go their separate ways.
So, they decided to
find a shooting star together,
like they did as children.
You thought the three of us
could do anything
together, right?
[MARI]
A star that's only for us?
Okay.
[DIA] Because a journey
taken with friends
will always be special.
[YOU]
Okay, a little more to the left.
[RIKO]
Chika, be careful with your end.
[CHIKA]
That should do it.
[RIKO] Now we just
need to secure this side.
[YOU]
Get ready!
[sighs]
All done!
It looks great.
Mm. A festival was
an awesome idea.
Let's get ready to party!
[YOU]
Aye-aye!
[MARI]
Yay, it's finito !
Behold my brand new
culinary masterpiece!
I call it Stewshine Premium!
I would really prefer that
you not use our club room
as a kitchen.
But Dia!
The masses are practically
demanding to eat my food!
Stop me if I'm wrong, but
isn't it typically frowned upon
for school directors to
run a shop during a festival?
Under normal circumstances, yes.
But since we're closing down,
there's no real harm in
the director jumping in
for a little fun!
I just wanna contribute
something special!
[sighs]
I'm worried about
the timing, you know?
The third term
is already so busy.
It's fine!
Besides,
this is what the students
at this school requested!
They wanna honor
Uranohoshi High.
Do what now?
We felt like we
had to do something!
So we talked it over
and came up with this idea.
It didn't seem right to combine
it with the graduation ceremony.
Exactly! If we're gonna go out,
why not go out with a bang?
Know what I mean?
Like boom!
Oh, and we can even invite
the whole community to come!
[MUTSU] Look, we know this is
a busy time for the third years
with college and all,
but this is our last chance.
Shiny.
Approved!
[ALL]
Huh?
[MARI]
You know,
it really is touching how much
the girls here love this school.
[door opens]
[CHIKA]
Heya, Mari!
All done!
The arch is set up
and ready to go!
Grazie!
For now, you can go back
to your normal preparations
until we need you again--
Actually, I think we need
to speed the prep up a bit.
At the rate we're going,
we'll never finish
before the end of the day.
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am, leave it to us!
[MARI]
Ciao for now!
They seem really happy.
Sì , they're excited
for the festival.
I'm so proud of
our fellow students
for coming up with this event.
[DIA]
So basically,
we'll take everything
we've felt for this school,
all of our hopes and dreams,
and channel them into tomorrow.
Is that the idea?
Uh, yeah.
In that case, then I've decided.
I shall put aside my position as
the student council president,
and focus my energy
on this festival!
[RUBY]
Hey, sis!
Everything looks
great over here!
If it's okay with you.
[MARI laughs]
[DIA]
Mm?
Oh jeez, we'll never
finish at this rate!
Where is Ruby?
Well, when you're
as popular as she is,
you're in high demand, zura.
So I guess it's up to the
unpopular girls to work here.
What the heck does that mean?
Are those walruses?
I feel like we've seen those
somewhere before.
Whoa!
Oh, this is coming along nicely!
Oh! Hey, welcome back!
Cool, I didn't realize you were
helping out our class, Ruby.
[RUBY] Mm-hm. I've always wanted
to make this kind of costume.
See?
It's so cute!
You're very talented!
I think that might've been You.
Who's in the other suit?
You, wait up!
[CHIKA]
Weird.
Where'd they run off to?
Yeah, I'm almost positive
they came this way.
They disappeared?
[gasps]
Um, what was that?
Looked like a ghost.
[RUBY, YOSHIKO, RIKO gasp]
[RIKO] Did you really see
the ghost come in here?
Yeah, at least I think I did.
Are you sure? It's dark.
Is the fallen angel
afraid of the dark?
Uh, absolutely not!
If anything, I thrive from
the peaceful emanation
the dark provides!
--[YOSHIKO yells]
--[RUBY squeaks]
Don't worry, I shall
construct a barrier
to protect you from out here!
Scaredy angel.
Be quiet, mortal!
[RIKO]
Uh, Chika, look!
It's the ghost.
That thing?
Well, yeah. Although I suppose
it could just be a sheet?
There's only one way
to find out.
[RIKO]
Be careful.
[CHIKA yells]
Are you okay?
Hm?
[SHIITAKE panting]
[HANAMARU, CHIKA, RIKO]
Huh?
Oh wow.
It's just Shiitake.
Uh...
I can't believe they
thought it was a ghost.
[RUBY]
Mm-hm!
[BOTH]
Huh? Hm?
[RUBY, YOSHIKO scream]
[SHIITAKE barks]
[CHIKA]
Come back, Shiitake!
--[STUDENTS shrieking]
--[SHIITAKE barking]
--[thud]
--[SHIITAKE whines]
[CHIKA gasps]
[DIA] That incident caused
quite a bit of damage.
To repair the arch alone
is going to take four hours
and who knows how many people.
[CHIKA]
Sorry.
[RIKO] Why the heck was Shiitake
at school in the first place?
It turns out that Mito was
taking a walk around here
when she accidentally
let go of the leash.
[DIA]
I don't want your excuses.
What I want is an answer
to how we're going to
clean up this mess before
the closing festival tomorrow!
I'll try and fix it.
Do you really think
that will be enough?
And how will you do that
when it's almost time
for everyone to go?
She's right, the last bus
is running soon.
How will we finish in time?
Good question.
You can stay.
The Ohara family will help out.
We'll be responsible for
getting everyone home safely.
Deal?
Really, zura?
Hold on, "everyone"?
All the girls who wanna stay
and help with the preparations.
Of course, you'll need to
call and let your parents know.
Thanks, Mari!
Come on, let's go
tell the others!
[door opens, closes]
Are you serious?
It's the last event.
Let me do my thing.
What on earth makes you think
I intend to stop you?
I actually expected you
to make this offer.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[CHIKA]
Here! Thanks for waiting!
[RIKO]
Oh, what is it?
[CHIKA] My family's specialty,
mandarin orange hot pot!
Mito brought it by
to apologize for Shiitake.
If dropping that leash results
in free delicious hot pot,
she can let go of Shiitake
whenever she wants!
I'd prefer she not.
Seconds, please, zura!
So you never did explain to us
why you're wearing that costume.
Ah.
It's for the school
closing festival tomorrow.
You and I wanted to dress up
for the ocean themed classroom,
so we decided to borrow these.
Does that mean...
This walrus is You?
[groans] You could
say something you know!
[HANAMARU] Guess we made
a huge fuss over nothin'.
It's probably best if you
refrained from wearing those
until the event actually starts.
[KANAN]
Okay, fine.
Seriously, just say something.
[thud]
[YOSHIKO gasps]
[HANAMARU]
Pop goes the walrus.
[YOSHIKO screams]
--[hammer thuds]
--[YOU grunts]
[YOU]
That should do it.
[footsteps]
Come join the school idol club!
Sign up today and don't delay!
How 'bout you? Or maybe you?
It's gonna be cool!
Embrace your inner idol!
[CHIKA]
Hey!
I wanna be a school idol!
[BOTH giggle]
It's kinda quiet out here, huh?
Even though it's so busy inside.
[CHIKA] Yeah, it's sort of
nice, you know?
[CHIKA] Outside,
everything's super normal,
but the inside of that building
is filled with everyone's dreams
and excitement for tomorrow.
It's like we all
lost track of time.
It's sweet.
I like it.
I wish this moment
could last forever.
Tomorrow, the next day,
for infinity!
And then, maybe...
[YOU]
Know something?
I've always admired you, Chika.
I really wish I could
see things the way you do.
To see the world through
your eyes, for all eternity.
Or at least, until we're
all old ladies together.
[giggles]
[YOU, CHIKA laughing]
[CROWD chattering]
[RIKO, CHIKA] Thanks for
visiting, please come back soon!
You look so cute in that, Riko!
So did you request the design?
Yes. I'm excited
to finally wear it.
You look cute, too, by the way!
Aww, why thank you!
Oh, here, Riko.
Thanks for lending us this.
We were able to use it as a
reference when we were sewing.
[RIKO yells]
What, that old thing?!
I just happened to have a copy
lying around the house!
Yeah, I'll bet.
Chika! Riko!
It's about time
to change shifts, right?
Go check out the rest
of the festival!
Okay!
Hey, do you wanna go
walk around together?
Uh, I'm sorry.
I actually have something else
I need to do right now.
[YOU]
Hello kids!
Welcome to the
Uranohoshi High Aquarium.
How's everyone doing?
[KINDERGARTENERS]
Fine!
[YOU]
Yay!
[KANAN]
This is the deep see of Uchiura!
--[KINDERGARTENERS] Wow!
--Here we go!
[CROWD chattering]
[CHIKA]
Wow!
What a huge crowd!
[DIA] Okay, who's ready
for the next question?
[CHIKA]
Hm?
[RUBY] This next one will
earn you twice as many points.
[CHIKA gasps]
[RUBY]
Try to pick the correct answer.
Do your Rubesty!
Here's the question.
What is the name of the
school idol duo from Fukuoka,
who performed in the
second Love Live
and advanced to the final round?
Mentaifo!
Hakattana!
Tenjintwo!
[DIA sighs]
Boop! Boop! Boop!
Sorry! The correct
answer is "Dream"!
You have a long way to go
if you want to be a real
Love Live expert.
My sis knows everything!
[giggles]
Oh, Dia. I totally forgot!
You're such a Love Live buff.
Huh?
[HANAMARU] Would you like to
have your fortune told, zura?
[CHIKA]
Hanamaru?
Please tell me you want to
have your fortune told, zura.
Well, uh...
[chuckles]
Welcome, my poor,
lost, little demon.
This is what you've
been doing in here?
Confess your troubles
to me and I, Yohane,
will make them disappear.
Ah, I see it now.
Trouble with
a relationship, yes?
Nah, not really.
We're the ones having
relationship issues
since we can't get
any new customers, zura.
Well, okay, then you've
gained some weight recently
and you're worried that you're--
Nope. No changes there.
Isn't that you, Yoshiko?
[YOSHIKO]
Silence, Zuramaru!
And the name is Yohane!
Wouldn't it be faster
if you just asked her
what she wants to
know about, zura?
Enough!
I need not ask,
for the fallen angel within me
knows all and imparts
that valuable wisdom!
Now behold, as I proceed
to reveal your fortune!
And music!
[organ music plays]
[CHIKA]
Whoa!
You girls went all out! Huh?
[RIKO] I can't believe
I'm doing this.
[CHIKA]
Riko?
Isn't she great?
Riko agreed to
help us out, zura!
Just what you'd expect
from the little demon, Lili.
[RIKO]
You agreed, too!
Weren't you the one
saying you wanted
to help Yoshiko's wish
come true for once?
[HANAMARU]
Uh, I didn't say that exactly.
Zuramaru.
Lili.
[CHIKA]
Ah!
Okay, I finally know
what I wanna ask you.
Please tell me.
What is the future of Aqours?
[gasps]
I don't need special
powers to know that.
All of my little demons
are whispering.
And the future of Aqours is...
Hey! Come one, come all
for my famous Premium Stewshine!
[CROWD chattering]
Wow. That's a huge line. Uh?
Shima and Mito!
[SHIMA]
Hi Chika!
Hi, whatcha doin'?
Do you want one?
Oh! Grilled mandarin oranges?
These are so yummy!
They taste so awesome
this time of year, huh?
You've always been
a fan of oranges.
Isn't that right?
[CHIKA]
Mm! I love 'em!
Whenever I eat an orange,
I can't help but think,
"Ah, I'm so glad
I was born here."
I'm so happy!
It's kind of funny.
This old place hasn't changed,
know what I mean?
[MITO]
Right? It even smells the same.
[CHIKA]
Smells?
[SHIMA] Mm-hm.
Since you go here every day
you probably don't notice it,
but it has a particular smell.
Just a scent.
It's something that
brings back good memories.
[hissing]
You hear that too, don't you?
Where's it coming from?
Hey! Chika!
Can you come over here, please?
See ya!
Yoshimi! What's up?
[YOSHIMI laughs]
It's a surprise!
What is?
See?
[CROWD]
Whoa!
Quick, come here!
What is it?
[ALL]
Yay!
[CROWD chattering]
Chika! You like it?!
Do ya?!
[CHIKA]
Mm! I love it!
[ITSUKO] Well then you're gonna
love this next part, too!
Huh?
[ALL]
One, two!
[CROWD]
Whoa!
[CHIKA]
It's true what people say.
Time flies
when you're having fun.
[KANAN]
Memories made with good friends,
it makes you wish you could
freeze those happy moments
and make them last forever.
[YOU] But, all good things
must come to an end.
[DIA]
We can't turn back time
any more than we can relive
those precious moments.
In a way, it's very sad.
[RUBY]
But at the same time,
we're also kind of
looking forward to tomorrow.
Because who knows
what it will bring.
[HANAMARU] And, maybe
that's the sort of thing
that makes us more aware
of the passage of time.
Life goes on, zura.
[YOSHIKO]
And then, it becomes obvious.
That perhaps it's
precisely because
this time will never come again,
that we can truly enjoy
this moment for what it is.
[YOSHIKO]
When you realize that,
when you know what is happening
now will never happen again,
you learn to cherish it.
[RIKO]
Because we all know...
...things will come
to an end someday.
Because we all know
that tomorrow is
still waiting for us.
[MARI] Together, we will walk
towards a bright new future.
[MARI] Together,
we can do it with a smile.
That concludes the festival
for Uranohoshi High School.
When I see how many people
showed up today,
I realize just how much
this school was loved.
Not only by the students
who have worked
so hard to make it great,
but by the community as well.
It truly is a special school.
So, this school
closing festival,
the whole thing made me...
...it made me happy.
I felt warmth,
stronger than I've
ever felt before.
Oh, Mari.
[MARI whimpers]
[MARI]
I'm sorry.
[MARI sobs]
Mari.
[MARI]
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
If I'd just had a bit more time,
maybe I could've...
[MUTSU] Let's go, Aqours. Let's
go, Aqours. Let's go, Aqours.
[MUTSU, YOSHIMI, ITSUKO] Let's
Let's go, Aqours.
[CROWD] Let's go, Aqours. Let's
go, Aqours. Let's go, Aqours.
Let's go, Aqours. Let's go,
Aqours. Let's go, Aqours.
Let's go, Aqours.
[applause]
Thank you, thank you all!
[MARI]
Are you ready?
Let's finish things
by singing together!
Sing with joy and cheer!
Sing with everything you've got!
We'll sing so loud
it reaches the heavens above!
[singing in Japanese]
[CHIKA]
Next time, "Sea of Light."