So right now, it's me
and the two pacifists.
If the rest of you
change your minds,
you can join at any point.
Well, Sleepyhead get up.
Hey! Bunny Ears!
Your team's over here! C'mon!
[TSUGI coughing]
[MISAKI]
Hey, kid! Follow me!
[YOSHIMI grunts]
[grunts]
[KANAE gasps]
[USAGI]
Uuh.
[USAGI chuckles]
'Kay, let's go.
[TOSHIKO gasps]
--[USAGI] Come on.
--[TOSHIKO gasps]
[TOSHIKO gasps]
[crickets chirping]
Wow, they really did
clear out the entire population
of the city just for
one night, didn't they?
I don't know if everyone
made it out of there in time.
Think they're okay?
[TSUGI]
Seriously?
You're worried about
the guys tryin' to kill us?
Ah. Good point. For now,
let's just try to find a place
where we can lay low.
[MISAKI]
Yeah, that'll do.
[MISAKI] Hah. No one's going
to be looking for us down here.
By the way, thanks for
agreeing to my peace treaty.
[TSUGI] No problem.
I mean, that is the reason
you saved me, isn't it?
[MISAKI]
True.
I just realized we haven't
introduced ourselves yet.
I'm Sharyu. Warrior of
the Monkey. Killing peacefully.
I'm Nezumi. Warrior of
the Rat. Killing all.
[MISAKI] Huh. You're awfully
young, aren't you?
Though if you were chosen to
participate in the Juni Taisen,
I guess you must at least be
a halfway decent warrior.
Well, maybe, but when
it comes to fighters,
I think everyone
has their own standard
for what makes
a "decent" one, right?
[MISAKI] Dealing with children
can be such a pain.
[TSUGI] Hey, you're pretty
powerful, aren't you?
[MISAKI]
Hm? Well, powerful enough
to defend myself, I should hope.
You don't have to be so modest.
I mean, you were the one
who blew up the floor,
weren't you?
Miss Sharyu?
[MISAKI]
Oh? He figured it out, huh?
[TSUGI] See, I'm thinkin'
someone saw you
putting together that alliance
and felt threatened.
They were about to launch a
first strike to try and stop it.
But you sensed
something was up
and protected us
by taking out the floor,
causing enough chaos
for us to slip away.
Am I right?
[MISAKI]
Well, yeah, more or less.
But I didn't just "sense" it,
or anything as vague
and subjective as that.
Someone in that room
was emitting
a palpable urge to kill.
That means one of the
other warriors wanted to end
the Juni Taisen with
a bloodthirsty approach
that was the polar opposite
of my peaceful solution.
And I couldn't have that.
[SUMI]
Ooh... and down we go.
[SUMI] Seems most of 'em used
the commotion as a cover
so they could hide out,
at least for the time being.
There are no strict boundaries
to the Juni Taisen
playing field.
Why, I've heard contestants
can even leave the country,
if they desire.
In fact, the man who won
the last tournament, Boar,
managed to turn the
competition around in his favor
specifically by traveling
to a densely populated area.
But with a ticking clock
dictated by this poison
we've got swimming around
inside our bellies,
I doubt anyone'll stray
too far from this city.
Sooner or later, this old-timer
here will get another chance
to use this "Old-Timer"
that I cobbled together.
Tick, tick, tick,
just a matter of time.
[laughing]
[KANAE] Now where the hell did
that bastard get off to?
Well, hello there!
Hello, hello, hello!
[NAGA] Killed right off the bat,
and then reduced to serving
as somebody else's
sad little puppet.
Heh. Just pathetic.
[clanging]
Yeah, I figured
this place'd be deserted.
[chuckles]
[MICHIO]
The rules of this year's Taisen
state the winner
has to nab each
of the poison jewels
we all swallowed.
That little twelve-hour
time bomb is gonna make it
hard to fall back on
the tried-and-true strategy
of just laying low early on.
Ha, that's not my style.
[sniffs]
If everyone's doing one thing,
I do the opposite.
That's me.
[MICHIO] Over the years,
I've been happy
to let the world believe
that my special power
is the savage
Mad Dog's Vise bite.
But the thing that truly
separates us Dog warriors
from the pack is the venom
secreted from our fangs.
'Course, anyone who gets
a taste of it winds up dead,
which tends to keep
the word from spreading.
I produce the toxins
in my own body,
and then inject 'em into
my enemy's bloodstream.
Side effects may include
death, death,
and horrifically violent death.
Of course, a bite is a bite,
so to say that biting
is my go-to move
isn't technically a lie.
[growls]
[MICHIO]
Given my expertise in the area,
I could tell right away that
the jewel was a type of poison.
And since I knew that, I had
my body prepare an antidote
to neutralize it before
I even popped it in my mouth.
Cheating? Sure,
you could call it that,
but ask me if
I feel guilty about it.
When I see an advantage,
I seize it
and use it to the fullest.
Besides, it seems
we have a pretty
bloodthirsty bunch
this time around.
They'll prob'ly thin out
their own numbers up front,
so for now, I'll just
hang back and wait. Gladly.
Waiting is what a dog does best.
I'll wait till they're down
to the last two or three.
Got the perfect hiding
spot here, so why--
[MICHIO]
Mm?
[coos]
A bird?
[MICHIO sniffs]
[RYOKA]
Oh. There you are!
Um, hi there.
[MISAKI]
There we go.
By the way, about before.
It's not like I was trying
to hide the fact that
I was the one who made
the floor go all kablooey
back at the tower.
But, y'know...
Okay, yeah, maybe I was.
It's just, I knew you'd look at
me that way if I'd told you.
[TSUGI] I'm not sure what way
you're talkin' about.
I mean, this is just how
my face looks all the time.
But more importantly,
do you know who
was comin' after you?
[MISAKI] No, I don't. There
wasn't a whole lot of time
to investigate.
Took all I had just to
make sure everyone could escape.
There ya go, playin' all
modest again.
Bet if you'd wanted to,
you coulda easily ID'd them
and even obliterated 'em
right on the spot.
You're more than capable
of that, aren't you?
[MISAKI] Yeah, that's true.
I could have.
But I choose not to
use my power like that.
You'll learn there are
far more appropriate ways
to exercise great power, Nezumi.
Appropriate, huh?
[yawns]
[TSUGI]
Given the circumstances,
I'd say the mystery
aggressor was the one
acting more appropriately.
[growling]
[RYOKA] Uuh! Please
don't get the wrong idea!
Really, I have no desire
to hurt you--I swear!
[MICHIO] What the hell
is this brat thinking?
She was in the perfect
position for an ambush!
Oh right, where are my manners?
I'm Niwatori, the Chicken.
I came here because I was, uh...
Well, I was hoping
we could team up.
Team up, eh?
[MICHIO] That's right.
She tried to accept
the Monkey's offer, too.
For such a timid little
waif, that's one hell
of a flashy outfit.
Like a costume someone
picked out and made her wear.
Sent in to the Juni Taisen
against her will, maybe?
Team up? With you?
[RYOKA] Uh huh.
Things may have gotten off
to a rocky start
back there, but, but--uh!
In a battle royale, you should
obviously try to form
a solid alliance quickly, right?
[MICHIO] Oh, yeah? If that
was such a brilliant idea,
the Monkey wouldn't have been
the only idiot who suggested it.
Everyone knows there can
only be one winner here.
Doesn't she get that teamwork
and betrayal go hand in hand?
Besides, can't see what
I'd get outta working with
a scrawny, obnoxious
flibbertigibbet like her.
Still, if we go at it now
and somehow I end up wounded,
that's not good for me, either.
I don't want to have
even the slightest chance
of getting eliminated early.
My best move here
might be to pretend like
I'm teaming up with this girl,
and then slay her
before we run into anyone else.
[RYOKA] So, can we go now?
We're kinda in trouble here!
Big trouble!
You know that creepy
half-naked guy
with the bunny ears?
I know this sounds crazy,
but he's a Necromantist!
A Necromantist?
He killed the Boar! And now
with her walking corpse,
he's got a three-person team!
How do you know?
[RYOKA] Well, I have
this secret ability
called Eye of the Cormorant.
It allows me to communicate
with all of the birds
in the sky, and see
everything they see.
And that's how I found
your hiding spot down here.
[MICHIO] That pigeon.
It was her filthy little spy.
This birdbrained chick
is even dumber than she looks!
Blabbing about her
"secret" ability to someone
she's just met.
And a rival, no less!
But that Rabbit warrior
is the real problem right now.
A Necromantist. I thought
they were just a myth.
The more they slaughter,
the more they
expand their ranks.
A killer who
creates more killers.
She'll be a cinch to beat,
so I can always take her out
whenever I want.
I'll get all the use I can outta
the girl, then discard her.
But first things first.
[RYOKA]
So if we just combine our--
--[MICHIO] Niwatori.
--Yes?
[MICHIO] Do you by chance
know where the Rabbit is now?
Yes, of course I do.
I've been tracking him.
I had the birds keep their
distance so he wouldn't notice,
but keeping tabs on him
should be our first priority,
don't you think?
All right, fine.
Given the circumstances,
I've decided I'll go along
with your little plan.
[MICHIO]
But make no mistake about
who's in charge here, girlie.
Wait, do you mean that we are--?
[MICHIO] That's right,
let's go hunt some rabbit.
[RYOKA]
Oh, yay! That's awesome!
With you and I working together,
we can win this thing!
You won't regret this,
I promise!
[MICHIO]
Don't get used to it.
Our partnership ends the second
the Rabbit's zombie squad
is destroyed.
I should formally
introduce myself!
Niwatori. Warrior of the
Chicken, killing by pecking!
Dotsuku. Warrior of the Dog,
killing by biting.
[MICHIO] Now it's time
to figure out how to
best use this girl
to my advantage.
[RYOKA]
You know the song that goes,
♪ "We ran through those
mountains full of rabbit, ♪
♪ we fished in those
rivers full of carp," ♪
and the joke about how it
sounds like it's the people
who are full of rabbit,
not the mountains,
even though clearly
that's not what they meant?
But I was thinking,
since the next line
is about catching fish,
they probably caught and ate
a lot of the rabbits, too,
so maybe they really were
full of rabbits,
just like the mountains were...
[MICHIO] If you wanna gab,
then why don't you start
by telling me everything you
know about the other fighters.
Sure!
The only ones I know
anything about are
Ox, Dragon, Snake,
Monkey, and Boar.
Just those five.
The most dangerous among them
is Ox, without question.
How shall I put this this?
He's simply more powerful
than you could ever imagine.
He crushes every foe
he meets on the battlefield.
People call him
the Natural-Born Slayer.
Well, that sounds horrifying.
I'm sure he's gotta be
one of the favorites
to win this thing. If a fighter
like you runs into him,
my advice would be
to run like hell.
[RYOKA]
Mhmm.
[MICHIO]
Not that it really matters.
Whether you're killed
by the Ox or by me,
you're still gonna end up dead.
Lemme see. Not much to say
'bout the Tatsumi brothers,
Dragon and Snake.
They're a pair of twins
who make a terrifying team.
But since one of em's
already dead,
their threat level's
cut in half.
Haha. Literally.
Got it. So, who else then?
Well, as you saw,
Monkey's a pacifist
and all-around do-gooder.
A disgrace to the warrior name.
She makes a living
running into combat zones,
trying to negotiate
peaceful resolutions.
Her mediation has
resulted in ceasefires,
prematurely ending countless
perfectly good wars.
Sure, that broad may be
a warrior for hire like us,
but she's also a huge threat
to our business.
She's probably only
doin' the Juni Taisen
to bring about an end
to this war, as well.
But would that even be possible?
[MICHIO]
Ordinarily I'd think not,
but knowing Monkey,
she just might pull it off.
[RYOKA]
And the last one?
No need to talk about Boar now.
I mean, she could pull off
a pretty impressive
gun maneuver called
Non-Reload, but...
Well, let's just say
it's probably lucky for us
she got taken out so early,
before we had to
go up against her.
So, Niwatori, which of these
fighters do you got dirt on?
[RYOKA] Well, I don't know much
of anything about anyone.
Aside from just some vague,
unverified rumors
here and there.
Sorry. I've lived
a sheltered life.
[MICHIO]
Hmph. You're helpful.
[MICHIO] But it's
not like I was expecting
all that much
out of her anyway.
[RYOKA]
Oh, but wait. That boy.
I wonder what
his deal is, don't you?
[MICHIO]
Huh? Who?
[RYOKA]
The sleepy one.
You know, the kid who
kept dozing off. Remember?
He didn't really seem
like the warrior type.
[MICHIO] Ha, like you're
one to talk, princess.
[MICHIO]
Hmm.
She's right, though--he did
stand out in that crowd.
Not stand out like
psycho Rabbit stand out,
but like he didn't belong there.
Think he's worth
keepin' an eye on?
No. I mean,
it's not like he seems
all that impressive,
exactly, but.
It's just, I don't know.
I can't shake this feeling
like I've seen him
somewhere before.
Did you get that feeling?
[MICHIO]
Hmm.
[RYOKA]
Huh? Wait up.
[MICHIO]
Now that she mentions it,
there was something
familiar about his face.
But I don't know why.
Did I fight with him?
Against him?
--On a battlefield somewhere?
--[RYOKA gasps]
--What's the problem?
--[RYOKA] Bad news, Dotsuku!
Rabbit's gang has split up
into two groups now!
[TOSHIKO gasping]
[EIJI]
Hm. Walking dead, huh?
If there's someone here
who can create those things,
then the first thing
I need to do is...
[YOSHIMI] The most dangerous
person in that room was Ox,
the famous Natural-Born Slayer.
Then again, he was the
first one to raise his hand
in response to the Monkey's
peace proposal.
[YOSHIMI]
Ow!
That alliance fell through
once the Rabbit joined in.
But perhaps we
could still find a way
to work together
as fellow moderates.
[RYOKA] I'm sorry, but I've lost
sight of Rabbit and Snake.
They might have realized
I was watching them
with my eyes in the sky.
[MICHIO]
I'm not surprised she lost 'em.
Given how green she is.
Although...
If they know we're watching,
this could be a decoy.
Rabbit and Snake send that
zombie Boar out as bait,
while they lurk in
the shadows ready to pounce.
Maybe that Rabbit
isn't as crazy as his
severely messed up
appearance might suggest.
Naw, he is. Anyone who
uses one of his own allies
as a pawn is definitely
not right between the ears.
In that case, I'll just have to
beat him at his own game.
Out-crazy the crazy.
And become a mad dog.
Niwatori.
[RYOKA]
Uh, yes? What is it?
[MICHIO]
Lemme see your arm.
[RYOKA]
Uh? Okay.
Aah!
[MICHIO]
Don't move!
How's that feel?
[RYOKA]
Why? Why would you do that?
Hey, wait. What'd you do to me?
[MICHIO] I drugged you.
And you're welcome.
I call it the One-Man Army.
It unlocks the full potential
of your combat abilities.
[MICHIO] My poison can do
more than just kill.
There is such a thing
as non-lethal poison.
I temporarily power her up
with that venom,
then I'll send her out there
to deal with that decoy Boar.
I don't even care if she wins,
just put up a decent fight.
That should be more than enough
to lure out Rabbit and Snake.
Then I'll sneak up on 'em
and wipe out Rabbit.
Course, even with
the power boost,
Rabbit or Snake
could still kill the girl,
but that just saves me
the trouble later.
Once that's done, I'll make
my way back underground.
A hunter and a killer.
That's the Warrior
of the Dog, Dotsuku.
[MICHIO] Calm down!
Everything you're feelin',
that's still your own power.
I just gave ya a little push.
So just relax and
let it happen-- get a grip.
[RYOKA]
Okay.
Okay. Get a grip.
You mean like this?
[MICHIO groans]
[YOSHIMI]
There must be some way
for all of the reasonable
moderates to meet up.
[YOSHIMI]
Huh?
[YOSHIMI sighs]
Uh?
Ushii. Killing systematically.
Warrior of the Ox.
Uuma. Warrior of the Horse.
Killing silently.
[EIJI grunts]
[YOSHIMI grunts]
[yells]
[birds chirping, cawing]
--[TOSHIKO gasps]
--[birds cawing]
--[TOSHIKO gasping]
--[birds cawing, cooing]
[DUO] They say,
"better to be a chicken's beak
than a bull's tail."
A chicken may peck deeply,
but what it finds
may not necessarily be food.
Next time: "Cutting a Chicken
with a Beef Cleaver."
Everyone!
Give yourselves a hand!