[DUO] The Juni Taisen is
held once every 12 years.
The winner of this battle
royale is granted one wish.
Anything they desire.
[TSUGI]
Now presenting the champion
of the 12th competition.
Congratulations... me.
[TSUGI] I get one wish.
So, what should it be?
[STUDENT A] You guys see
that show last night?
Mornin', uh-- Oh.
It's just Nezumi.
[STUDENT A]
Jeez, get my hopes up.
For a second...
Every one of you, just die.
What a weirdo.
So you guys wanna come over...?
[TSUGI]
Just kidding.
I didn't go into the Juni Taisen
with any particular
wish in mind.
But after going
through hell to win,
I'm not gonna waste it on
something so pointless.
I mean, in a hundred years,
they'll all be worm food anyway.
[STUDENT AA] Well, you
look as gloomy as ever.
[TSUGI]
Hm?
[STUDENT AA] So do you just
come to school to sleep?
C'mon, don't you have like,
hopes or dreams?
[TSUGI]
Flip up her skirt.
[gasps]
[screams]
[STUDENT AA]
Hello?
Earth to Nezumi,
ya in there somewhere?
Where you zone out
to all of a sudden?
Something on your mind?
No, nothing really. Just stuff.
[TSUGI]
Dumbass.
Actually, if you could
have one wish granted
in the whole world,
what would it be?
Aww. Only get one?
Yeah. But whatever it was,
it would for sure come true.
Ooh, that's tough. Lemme think.
Uh, how 'bout...
"Let everyone be happy."
That's my wish!
That way I could grant lots of
other people's wishes, too,
all at the same time!
Huh, interesting.
That's not a bad idea.
[TSUGI]
Yeah, right.
Let's just make the worst
people in the world happy.
Take for example the
most terrifying competitor
in the Juni Taisen.
If he had his wish granted,
it'd be a nightmare.
He could wipe out all
life in the universe.
But the more I think about it,
granting the wish of somebody
nice sounds pretty good to me.
And not to be all arrogant,
but if I can't come up
with one on my own,
it'd be a real slap in
the face to those who died.
I could never face 'em again.
But you, I hope you
truly believe
this is the right
end for you, too.
[ANNOUNCEMENT A] Now
arriving. Please stand clear--
[TSUGI]
I didn't really do what I did
'cause I thought it was
"the right thing to do."
It was just the only choice
that would allow me to survive.
The right thing...
What is the right thing?
It's full of trash people,
all of 'em numbed by peace.
When I think about
risking my life
to protect the
anesthetized lifestyle
of those ungrateful brats,
I get sick to my stomach.
[TSUGI]
Don't you ever get tired of it?
I bet no one in the
world has saved
as many people as you have.
But that means, according to
the law of averages anyway,
that you've saved a
lot of garbage, too.
Doin' the right thing, that's
more her field than mine.
[MISAKI]
I carry it with me. Forever.
I choose to stop wars with
the power of my words.
And yeah, I've been through some
terrible things myself, too.
But I won't let that stop me
from getting along with people.
Ideally, I'd like
to be at peace
with everyone in
the whole world.
So don't sell
platitudes short, okay?
[TSUGI] To be honest, I found
that whole speech pretty lame.
But still, I kinda dug
your commitment
to those platitudes
of yours, Sharyu.
I know.
What if I bring the
most righteous person
in the world back to life?
After all, I couldn't've
won without her.
Yeah, that's good.
No problems there.
I'll go with that. It's decided.
The wish I want granted
more than any other is...
Wait a minute.
Should someone be brought back
just 'cause they're righteous?
Is it righteous for only the
most righteous to get to live?
Would she even accept that?
Okay, so what about, "Bring
back everyone who died"?
But then, that would
include some people
who don't wanna come back.
Besides, that'd just lead
to a rehash of the Taisen.
And who am I to be making
decisions about life and death?
And would they still be
the same people they were
before their lives ended?
Or would they be more like
clones of themselves?
And if so, does that mean I'd
just be doing it for myself?
Then again, it is my wish,
so maybe that's okay.
[TSUGI] But what's the point
of bringing them back anyway?
Do I expect them to thank me?
Honestly, I don't wanna
see them again.
Any of them. Ever.
Okay, so if I'm gonna use
this wish for myself...
Let's see. How 'bout
wishing for... good health?
Yeah, come to think of it,
the old man said
something like that.
Huh? What would I wish for?
Eternal life and youth.
When you get to my age,
you discover that youth is the
greatest treasure of 'em all.
[TSUGI] But immortality would
kinda suck though, right?
And staying this age
forever sounds rough, too.
Wasn't just him.
Along my different paths,
I asked all the fighters
about their wishes.
Don't know if they were
telling me the truth,
but their answers
came so easily.
Huh? You wanna know
what I'm wishing for?
Yeah.
I suppose... confidence?
Yeah, confidence.
Confidence? Really?
Confidence in what?
Uh, well, I guess I'd probably
say confidence in myself.
Yeah, but you're
a badass warrior.
I'm sure you've been through
some hard core battles
in your day, right?
Well, yeah, I guess
so, but still.
I don't really have a
solid sense of who I am.
I sorta fell into
this line of work.
I do what I'm told, when
I'm told, the way I'm told.
And even if I make
it out of here alive,
I'll have to keep
doin' this job, right?
So I'd at least like to have
some pride, maybe?
A sense of accomplishment.
Some meaning in what I do.
Or something like that.
Okay then,
why wouldn't your wish be to
just stop being a warrior?
Oh, yeah. Huh. I guess that
is an option, isn't it?
[TSUGI]
I don't get it.
You seem so strong and yet
you'd still ask for talent?
Truth is... I'm more afraid
of losing than dying.
[TSUGI] Afraid? I mean,
nobody likes to lose.
And sure, a genius like Ox,
bet he doesn't have
much to fear.
But it sounds to me like
you just have an
inferiority complex.
[YOSHIMI] It's not a
complex. It's a disease.
[TSUGI]
If I had more power or talent,
my odds of survival
would seriously increase.
But in that case, wouldn't
I just get sent off
to more and more battlefields
to fight more and more
dangerous enemies?
[TOSHIKO] I want a harem
of men, of course!
A harem, harem, harem!
As the heiress to a
historic household,
I want a life surrounded by
three billion gorgeous boy-toys!
To love and be loved
by every single one!
[TSUGI] Maybe it's 'cause
I'm still a teenager,
but I don't wanna
wish for anything
I'd be embarrassed to
tell people about.
This sucks.
Having infinite options only
makes it harder to decide.
Ah, it's just Nezumi. That
kid's such a waste of space.
Like, sometimes I
forget he even exists,
and then I'm like...
Vanish, all you.
So what say we head
out to the mall...?
[TSUGI]
Just kidding.
[TSUGI] This power to
experience the results
of a hundred different actions,
the Hundred Paths of Nezumi
maybe I should upgrade
it to a thousand paths.
While it's true this ability
is what allowed me
to win the Juni Taisen,
without it, I never
would've had to participate
in that horror show
in the first place.
Plus, I still remember
the fear and pain I felt
every one of those 99
times I was murdered.
[TSUGI]
Hey, wait! Don't do this!
[RYOKA]
I really am sorry, Nezumi.
[TSUGI screams]
[TSUGI]
The others retained no memories
of the alternate
paths, obviously.
[TOSHIKO] I regret to inform
you there's no escape.
So just sit back and relax
while I pump your adorable
body full of lead.
[TSUGI] Occasionally
they did recognize me,
but only as a vague
feeling of déjà vu.
Hello there. You
wanna be my friend?
Don't be afraid.
I'll make it quick.
[TSUGI]
But it's burned into my memory,
as though it all
really happened.
Not the kinda thing
you can forget.
[ANNOUNCEMENT A]
For your own safety...
[TSUGI] Still, I was lucky
there was at least one path
where I managed to survive.
There are plenty of
situations where,
even with a hundred options,
I can't catch a break.
For example, there was no
choice I could've made
to avoid the Juni
Taisen altogether.
I doubt anyone can
understand the despair
of trying a hundred
different paths
and having none of 'em pan out.
It was middle school.
I fell in love with the most
popular girl in school.
Well, her third best friend.
A plain girl, but I was smitten.
So I tried a hundred different
ways to ask her out.
[TSUGI] Being shot down
a hundred times at once
hurt at least a
hundred times more.
I found out later that
she was totally obsessed
with this one kid in our class
and wouldn't even
look at another boy.
Guess there are some things
that won't work out,
no matter what you try.
Ever since then, I've written
my power off as something
that's only good for winning
at rock-paper-scissors.
So yeah, I think I'll pass
on the hellish experience
of trying a thousand options
and having them all fail.
I'm a teacher.
At a preschool.
I'm good. The kids and
parents all seem to like me.
Yeah, it's great. My
daughter goes there, too.
Ya think I'm lyin'?
[TSUGI] No, it's just surprising
on pretty much every level.
Well, a long time ago, I made
a mistake on this one job,
and this kid wound up
getting sold to a real sicko.
I managed to get her back,
but she had nowhere to go.
I couldn't live with that,
so I took the little girl in.
[MICHIO]
Now I gotta keep workin',
so I can earn enough
to support her.
[giggles]
[TSUGI]
That must be hard on you.
Not really. And thanks
to her, I have...
I wouldn't call it a purpose,
but it's a less crappy life
than I used to have.
[TSUGI]
A purpose. That reminds me.
Ha. Our wish? Can
you believe this guy?
Oh, c'mon, like you
even have to ask.
[BOTH]
Money, money, money!
It's all about
makin' that scratch!
Ain't nothin' in this
world you can't do
if you got da big moolah!
[TAKE] I know that's what
my big brother said,
but deep down he doesn't really
believe in the value of money.
Hell, I don't think he believes
in much of anything these days.
Except himself, of course.
[NAGA] I know that's what
my baby brother said,
but for him, money's
just one more thing
out there to be stolen.
It's all one giant game to him.
[TSUGI] Those guys,
who acted like money
was their sole purpose in life,
when I really talked to them,
and got to know them,
they weren't as shallow or
simplistic as I thought.
Even a seemingly
irredeemable creep like--
So if what you're
telling me is true,
I should be patient and
wait till the very end
to make you my friend?
Yeah, that's right!
I can't tell you what
my ability is,
but I don't think it'll do you
much good after I'm dead.
So...
[USAGI]
Okay.
Then will you help me track
down the other warriors?
Sure, anything you say.
[USAGI] Let's start with
the Warrior of the Ox.
I'd really, really like
him to be my friend.
[TSUGI]
With each warrior,
once we were able to
have a conversation,
they turned out
to be so different
from my first
impression of them.
Huh? What would my wish be?
Yeah.
My deepest desire is...
To be friends with everyone.
Everyone in the whole world.
[TSUGI]
It was a chilling thing to hear,
but at least he was honest about
what he genuinely wanted.
What a joke.
What cosmic irony for me,
the one person who went into
this without a wish, to win!
[KANAE] So after that, I ended
up thinkin' to myself,
"How the hell does
this guy always know
the right thing to do?"
Ya know? Like, come on!
I thought about,
how "bu" and "michi,"
those things don't mean
nothin' on a battlefield.
Nothing good about war.
But Ushii, he was truly good.
So I guess my wish'd be to
see him again, and finally...
Hey, you listenin'
to me, pipsqueak?
Uh, yeah.
'Kay, then take a swig! Boom!
Um, no thanks. I'm underage.
Wha'd you say? You think...
[TSUGI]
Miss Tiger.
The one warrior
in the Juni Taisen
who actually got her wish.
[KANAE]
You sayin' I'm old?
[TSUGI] I started to think
that having hopes and dreams
was a recipe for misery.
If you make achieving them
your purpose in life,
you'll only wind up feeling
empty if you don't get 'em.
On the other hand,
if you do get them,
what's the point of
living after that?
Doing the right thing
is the same way.
Is that the reason I
fought in the Juni Taisen?
Maybe I just got swept
along in the moment.
Not everyone can see the world
the way Monkey and Ox did.
To finish off the rest of
the Necromantist's allies,
I believe I'll need this.
[yells]
Stop hiding and reveal yourself.
Or must I come to you,
Warrior of the Rat?
[sighs]
[USAGI]
Hey.
Can I ask you something
before you kill me?
What is it?
C'mon, don't you have any,
like, hopes or dreams?
[TSUGI] Do I need to
have hopes or dreams?
I haven't crawled my
way up out of anything!
I've never faced adversity!
Perhaps I could
ask you a question.
Tell me, what would your
wish be, young man?
What matters to you that
you're fighting for?
Living for?
[TSUGI]
Oh, gimme a break.
I've never thought about
a reason for fighting,
let alone a reason for living!
What's my wish?
I have 99 of 'em!
Rule the world? But the ruling
itself is the hard part.
I want a girlfriend.
But would that really be love?
I want wisdom. But
foolishness makes you...
I want to be a pro baseball
player. But you'd have to...
Telekinesis. But then...
I want to fly.
But then why have feet?
I want to speak all languages...
I want X-ray vision...
To never stub my toe again...
I want a cool supercar...
I wanna not feel pain...
I wish every day
could be Sunday...
The ability to wake up early...
--I want that rare book...
--Just to go back to sleep...
...but it would be
harder than it sounds...
I wanna play all instruments...
I wanna live in a mansion...
I wanna enter a manga...
The power to stop time...
It's like you're saying you want
the power to commit crimes.
...be a manga artist...
...one of Young Jump's
rectruiting posters...
I want a time machine...
--I wanna be free of stress...
--I wanna hire a maid...
But you need stress
in order to grow...
I wanna be on the front
page of the newspaper...
I wanna eat the world's
most delicious food...
...but you'd just want
to be shorter again.
--I want courage...
--I want prestige...
I wanna be the strongest
in the world...
I wanna invent
something amazing...
I wanna become a
master swordsman...
I wanna be a cyborg...
I wanna learn the
truth of the world...
No, you really don't.
I wanna wish misfortune
on people I hate.
But wishing misfortune on
others is a crappy thing to do.
[TSUGI] If I do this,
then that'll happen.
But if I do that instead,
it'll lead to this,
so I'd better just...
Hold on, wait.
If that doesn't work,
then what about...?
No, no, that'll ruin this,
so I can't do that.
Okay, if this happens, it'll
result in maybe, possibly...
[DUO] So, have you chosen
your wish yet, Mr. Nezumi?
Turing your one wish into a
hundred is also an option,
if you so desire.
Although, in my experience...
[chuckles]
[DUO] ...even a hundred
wishes are not enough
to satisfy a person's ambition.
[TSUGI]
I've decided.
My one wish...
The wish granted to the
winner of the Juni Taisen...
What I want more
than anything is...
I wanna forget!
I just wanna forget I ever
had this decision to make!
[TSUGI]
Please.
Very well. What a
wonderful wish.
One made sincerely from
the bottom of your heart.
[STUDENT A]
'Mornin!
Oh. Look it's Mr. Popular.
Hey, would you just cut
it out? That isn't nice.
[STUDENT F]
What?
The kid comes to school
just to go back to sleep.
I mean, come on, is there
anything he wants outta life?
What a loser.
Wait a minute. He looks
really content today.
Like he doesn't want for
anything in the world.