[police sirens wail]
[RYOKA] The apartment.
The oldest memory I have.
A dirty building in
an even dirtier neighborhood.
A room crawling
with the remains of life.
People had lived there
for a long time.
Trash piled high,
the air thick with rot.
And the pain shooting
through my body.
But most vividly,
I remember the cold steel
of the egg topper in my hand
and the warm liquid
on the floor.
By then, you couldn't recognize
their faces if you tried.
But I'm pretty sure those bodies
were once my parents.
I couldn't remember how
I got there, or why I did it.
I couldn't remember anything
from before that day.
[RYOKA sighs] Well, I had
to spend more time with him
than I wanted,
but it all worked out.
I got him to give me the drug.
--[squelch]
--[gasps]
[RYOKA]
And we're done!
Dotsuku. I lied when I said
I didn't know anything
about anyone. Because I did
know all about you.
I knew you were a Poisoner.
And I knew I wanted your
special power up, One-Man Army.
When I use my
Eye of the Cormorant,
none of the warriors
can hide anything from me!
[bird cooing]
[RYOKA grunts]
[gasps]
That's awesome! It's like I'm
all maxed out in a video game!
Thanks again for
the power up, Dotsuku.
Now that I've got One-Man Army
pumping through my veins,
I might win
the whole tournament!
And when I do,
I'll have 'em build a statue
thanking you for all your help.
Hold on. I don't really
remember what you looked like.
Well, looks don't matter
so much with a guy.
So long as it has fangs,
they'll know who it is.
[TOSHIKO gasping]
Okay! Next one!
I can win this!
[MEDIC 3A]
She's unharmed, but in shock.
[thud]
[RYOKA] I have a vague memory
of a hospital and doctors
doing lots of tests on me.
No memory, huh?
No, not of the incident itself.
And certainly not of
the years of physical abuse
that led up to her killing them.
Severe amnesia is my diagnosis.
Is her memory back?
[DOCTOR 3B]
No. The psychological shock of
what she's gone through is still
causing her to block it out.
[OLD NIWA WOMAN 3A]
Hm. That may make things easier.
Any change in her abilities?
[DOCTOR 3B] None. Not only
can she control any type
of bird, she's able to exchange
visual information with them.
Then I've made
my decision on her fate.
The Niwa family
will take her in.
She's mine.
[DOCTOR 3B]
Yes, ma'am.
[birds chirping]
[RYOKA] Everything that
happened after I moved in
with the Niwa family,
I remember clearly.
They adopted me as
their daughter and began
training me as a warrior.
I learned everything
there is to know about
espionage and killing.
The Niwa family business is war.
They involve themselves
in conflicts around the world.
They wasted no time
putting me to work.
They gave me jobs
and I always delivered.
[RYOKA] Because I had
no memory of the past,
I had no dreams for the future.
No idea of what
a normal life should be.
I went where they told me to go.
Killed who they told me to kill.
What? Are you serious?
Ryoka, bring a car to the front.
Sir. Right away.
[MAN 3B grunts]
[RYOKA] Hey. They're onto us.
Better make your move now.
[MALE SWAT 3A]
Roger. Strike Team is "go."
Damn. How did they know?
There's a car waiting outside
to take you to
the safe house, sir.
[glass crashes]
[MALE SWAT 3A]
Go, go, go!
Come on. Can't this
thing go any faster?!
[MALE SWAT 3B]
Damn. We just missed 'im.
Secret tunnel
through the basement.
Y'mean, we spent months setting
up this sting for nothing?
[grunts]
How come your recon didn't
turn up that tunnel, Ryoka!
Oh, yeah. Sorry about that guys.
--[MALE SWAT 3B] Mm?
--What the hell are you doing?
[RYOKA] And we're done!
Big Crime Boss Guy
didn't matter to me.
My mission was all about this.
[MALE SWAT 3B]
What's that?
[RYOKA] Clients, weapons
purchases, financial records.
All the good stuff!
--[MALE SWAT 3B] For real?
--[MALE SWAT 3A] Wait, if that's
true, this is our
biggest takedown yet!
Now why would I lie to you?!
--[two gunshots]
--[MALE SWAT 3A, 3B groan]
I know that may have
seemed harsh,
but you know how it is.
What the--? Shit, are you okay!
One of them was hiding
and came out, and--
and I think they're both dead!
[RYOKA]
Hm.
[MAN 3B] You tell me!
How did they know?
How the hell did the cops know
about today's exchange?
We'll find that rat,
don't worry, sir.
[phone ringing]
Who is this?
[RYOKA] Oh. You really
did get away, safely.
I'll be honest, I didn't
think you'd make it.
I'm surprised!
Hold on. It's you?
If you survive this next thing,
I'll be really impressed.
Ryoka. I swear to god,
when I get my hands on you,
it won't be a
quick death, sweetheart.
Oh, my god, no don't!
I get so scared when you
threaten me and stuff.
Seriously though, you won't
ever be see me again.
No one talks to me that way.
When I get my hand around
you scrawny little ne--
[reorder tone]
[RYOKA] Everyone is just a
product of their environment.
Good people can
fall prey to darkness.
Bad people can be
reformed by the light.
But when you do what I do,
the lines get blurred.
I've tricked, betrayed,
and killed so many people
I can't tell who're the bad guys
and who're my friends.
[RYOKA]
Now that that's over with,
I'm gonna hit up a hot spring!
[bird chirping]
[RYOKA giggles]
[RYOKA] I've been around
long enough to know that
the strongest warrior
can have a bad day,
and the opposite's also true.
The weakest warrior
can have a good one.
I don't have to
beat 'em all to win.
I just have to be
the last one standing.
[gasps]
[RYOKA] Okay, my little birdies!
It's go time!
[TOSHIKO gasping]
Killing by pecking.
Sky Burial!
[TOSHIKO gasping]
[birds cawing]
[RYOKA sighs] I hate to lose
so many of my friends.
Wow! Your Non-Reload move
is one dangerous power.
I didn't know you could
still use it as a corpse.
[sighs] I'm glad I had
the birds do the dirty work
instead of going at you
myself with One-Man Army.
It looks like the survivors
had their fill of Boar.
Go work up an appetite so
you're ready for the next one!
[distant clanging]
[YOSHIMI]
Ah!
[thud]
[EIJI] Ah, Ironclad.
Is that your ability?
Heh. Well, if you don't mind,
I'd like to test
the limits of that ability.
[YOSHIMI grunting]
[yells]
[RYOKA groans] Y'know,
if we weren't in the city,
I'd have a lot more birds
helping me out here.
--[gasps]
--[door bell ringing]
--[TSUGI] Hello, miss.
You don't have to point
your pitch fork at me.
I'm not here to fight you.
Wait. Of all the stores in town,
how'd you know
I was in this one?
[TSUGI] I didn't.
I came here for one reason
and one reason only.
Snacks.
Though I suppose I owe you
a proper greeting.
I'm Nezumi. Warrior of
the Rat, killing all.
Your turn.
[RYOKA] Uh, Niwatori. Ch--
Warrior of the Chicken.
[TSUGI]
Huh. Oh, yeah. I 'member.
You raised your hand
for the Monkey.
I did what?
Oh. You're right,
I certainly did.
[RYOKA] Of course my plan
was just to play along,
then kill you later.
What about it?
[gasps]
[TSUGI] Why don't you come
with me, Miss Chicken?
[RYOKA]
Huh?
Don't be scared. I'm just
taking you to see her.
[RYOKA] Is this a set up?
Maybe I should I kill him.
My birds can't see down here.
I don't know if I should be
going along with this.
It's a perfect hide out.
[MISAKI]
Huh? Oh, good you're back!
And with a new friend?
[TSUGI]
Hm. I found her in the store.
[RYOKA]
He left his back wide open.
Has he forgotten why we're here?
Hey, there's no time to sleep!
I'm the one who hiked up there.
You got this. Night, Monkey.
Kid, you might be the weirdest
fighter in this thing.
Anyway. I'm sorry if
the Rat made you nervous.
No, he didn't at all.
I wasn't nervous. It's fine.
[RYOKA]
He looks so familiar.
I could swear I've
met him somewhere before.
Or maybe the poison's
got me imagining things.
[MISAKI] After my
little speech back there,
you raised your hand.
How much do you know about me?
About what I try to do?
Well, all I really know
is that you're the Monkey.
[MISAKI] Then allow me
to introduce myself.
I'm Sharyu. Killing
peacefully, the Monkey.
I'm Niwatori. Killing
by pecking. The Chicken.
[RYOKA] Got the whole
thing out that time.
That's great!
So nice to meet you.
And thanks for accepting
my proposal back there.
I really believe we can make
this peaceful alliance work.
Uh, yeah.
[RYOKA] Wait, she was serious
about the cease fire thing?
I thought she was playing nice
to get teammates
for a typical
back-stabby alliance.
Naw, this pacifist thing
has to be fake.
No one invited to
the Juni Taisen
would ever seriously try it.
After nearly dying up there,
he just wants to hide down here.
I'd rather we
catch our breaths...
[RYOKA] Not surprised that
he's hiding in the sewers.
He is the Rat.
[MISAKI] I think the longer
we stay down here,
the lesser our chance
of finding the others
who raised their hands.
Although, I am
getting to meet you.
Oh, yeah, sure. That makes me
really happy, too. Yep!
[MISAKI] But just 'cause
we met up doesn't mean
we're sittin' tight.
I wanna find the others, ASAP.
[RYOKA]
Yeah, the others.
It's hard keeping
all these animals straight.
I know Rat and I
raised our hands.
Then so did Ox, Horse,
and Rabbit, I think.
But Rabbit seemed more
like he just wanted to
mess with her. She can't be
serious about finding him.
Heck, I wasn't really agreeing
to her proposal, either.
And I bet Horse and Ox were
doing exactly the same thing.
Even Rat boy's probably
working his own angle.
I could kill
both of them right now
without batting an eye. But.
[MISAKI] Niwatori. Have you
run into anyone else?
If so, what's it like
up there right now?
[RYOKA] Uh, well. A few
of them have been killed.
I know for a fact
that Boar and Dog are gone.
Oh, and Snake died
before the tournament began.
So that's at least...
[RYOKA] Why am I telling her
the truth about any of this!
[MISAKI] I see. Just like that,
two more warriors dead.
Such a shame.
[RYOKA] "A shame"?
Are you kidding me?
It's not just that Monkey's
too trusting, she's a fool!
It's impossible to win the Juni
Taisen without using violence.
To think otherwise
you'd have to be
completely detached
from reality!
[MISAKI] Zombies?
He does sound like trouble.
Have some.
--Oh, thank you.
--[MISAKI] Careful, it's hot.
Three warriors gone
out of twelve. That's 25%.
Can you still pull off your plan
with a big chunk
of us already dead?
Yeah, I think so.
I can't share all
the details just yet,
but it shouldn't be a problem.
Pretty sweet.
Oh, did I use
too much sugar?
I always crave it
when I'm tired.
[RYOKA] What's wrong
with you, Niwatori?
What've we got here?
Japanese egg and rice? Uh huh.
After all that sugar in the tea,
this might be too many carbs.
Sorry, but I can't be
a part of your plan.
I think it's better
if I work alone.
Oh. Sorry to hear that.
But hey!
If you change your mind,
you're always welcome here.
You know where to find me.
Promise you won't give up.
Fight to the end.
Hold on, before you go,
why don't you eat with us?
I can't. But thanks
for the offer!
[RYOKA]
You stupid, dumb chicken!
Would it have killed you
to just play along?
What happened to all my
strength and cunning?
My ruthless trickery?
Damn. It's the Dog's poison!
One-Man Army. Yeah,
it's boosted my strength,
but it's also messed
with my emotions.
I've trained myself
to ignore things
like compassion and sincerity,
but now her kindness
is tearing me apart!
So stupid. Why be strong
if you can't control
your emotions anymore!
--[EIJI] All alone?
--[gasps]
[RYOKA]
Ox! Oh god, just my luck!
Answer the question:
Are you alone?
If you have any allies
hiding in the area,
I'd like to see them.
Though to be honest,
it doesn't really matter to me
how many of you there are.
[RYOKA]
He's already fought someone.
No. He's already killed someone.
Wait. Didn't you claim
to be a pacifist earlier?
No. You have me
confused with the Monkey.
[RYOKA] But when she proposed
a non-violent alliance,
you raised your hand.
[EIJI]
I did raise my hand.
Because I wanted
to be a part of a team.
As soon as the explosion
and our dispersal, however,
her peace proposal
was rendered moot.
[RYOKA] What do I do?
Even if I was ready for him,
facing the Natural-Born Slayer
in a straight-up fight
would be suicide.
My birds should
be hungry again soon.
If I run it will give me time
to come up with a plan.
Or I could play dumb,
earn his trust,
and get Ox to drop his guard.
Yeah, I like that.
One-Man Army is still
giving me incredible power.
He has no idea how strong I am.
[EIJI] Hm. The fact that
you bring up the Monkey
means she's on your mind.
In turn, that could mean
that the Monkey
is hiding very close by.
[RYOKA gasps]
[RYOKA]
What? No!
[EIJI]
Oh, my. Judging from that,
the Monkey's your new friend
and you're going to defend her.
Are we playing the
"If you want to get past me,
you'll have to kill me" routine?
Never pegged you
as the heroic type.
[RYOKA] He's right.
This is not who I am!
It's that damned drug.
One-Man Army is changing
my whole approach to battle.
I'd advise against this--
trying to defend her.
It won't make you stronger.
And the honor you're defending
isn't even your own.
It belongs to a person
you barely know.
When you fight, it should
be only for yourself.
[RYOKA]
You don't think I know that?
I know better than anyone!
I gotta get outta here.
I'll make like I'm gonna strike,
then I'll turn and run
as fast as I can.
Niwatori. Warrior of the
Chicken, killing by pecking!
Killing systematically.
Ushii. The Ox.
[RYOKA gasps]
I can win this!
[squelching]
[RYOKA] I spent years
mastering strategy, deception,
and my own special power.
Then someone comes along who's
immune to all those things
and wins in a second.
[EIJI]
Hm.
[birds cawing]
[RYOKA] Well, I guess
this is the end of me.
Could've been worse. At least
I died in a stand-up fight.
Heh. That's pretty good!
My friends. Thank you for
your help all those years.
By now, I bet
you must be starving.
Go ahead. Eat your fill.
[DUO] They say, "Even a monkey
can fall from a tree."
We can also say
that too much talent
can make a sage fall to earth.
Next time:
"The Enemy, a Noble Primate!"
Everyone!
Give yourselves a hand!