[footsteps]
[TOSHIKO]
How about that.
A brand new building
and not a soul inside.
[footsteps]
[TOSHIKO]
An entire city of 500,000
relocated in a single night.
There's no better
example of the power
of the Juni Taisen's
organizers than that.
Of course, the city's
not completely empty.
I assume the other participants
have already gone inside.
Which is fine.
As the Boar, I take
my role very seriously.
And it's tradition that
the Boar always arrive last.
[elevator dings]
[TOSHIKO] Hm. How could I
choose a mode of transport
with no escape and still
call myself a warrior?
[gunshot]
[door creaks]
[TOSHIKO'S FATHER]
When you're on the battlefield,
always have an escape
route planned.
I know this
is training, Toshiko,
but those mercenaries
are still trying to kill you.
[TOSHIKO]
Okay, Father.
--[distant pop]
--[TOSHIKO gasps]
[MERC 1A groans]
--[thud]
--[TOSHIKO gasps]
[MERC 1B groaning]
Uh!
[TOSHIKO'S FATHER]
Excellent. So long as you keep
both hands free,
you can dispatch enemies
coming from any direction
at any time.
Okay, Father. I understand.
[TOSHIKO] Now I've learned
it's even easier to simply
carry weapons all the time.
Right, Father?
[MERC 1D groans]
[MERC 1F groans]
[MERC 1G groans]
[gunfire]
[MERC 1G]
Aah!
[MERC 1G] Wait!
Please, don't. Don't kill me!
[panting]
[TOSHIKO'S FATHER]
What's wrong with you?
I--uh!
[TOSHIKO'S FATHER]
You didn't listen to me!
[MERC 1G groans]
[TOSHIKO'S FATHER]
When you have a chance to kill,
you always take it.
Showing mercy is pointless.
[TOSHIKO]
My father's "discipline"
others would call abuse.
[TOSHIKO'S MOTHER] Honey,
this color's gorgeous on you.
Look how it pops!
It's important to look good.
You'll be head of
the Ino family someday.
[TOSHIKO] My mother's entire
world revolved around me
and my sister. She was obsessed.
Two very different sets
of expectations growing up.
And I met them both. However.
[KIYOKO]
Toshiko!
Kiyoko.
[KIYOKO] Check this out.
I killed three already today!
Actually, if you count
the newborn cubs,
and I think we should,
it's eight!
After the first,
I picked 'em off one-by-one
as they came out of their den!
My beloved little sister
was obsessed with killing.
[TOSHIKO]
Welcome home, Father!
Congratulations on
winning the Juni Taisen--
Enough! I didn't
ask for your praise.
Pay attention.
I've chosen the entrant
for the next Juni Taisen.
--[KIYOKO gasps]
--That's in twelve years!
[TOSHIKO'S FATHER]
Yes. This family's next
Taisen competitor will be...
[TOSHIKO]
Don't worry, Father.
You taught me
everything I know.
The family's honor
demands that I win,
and I plan to do just that.
In a way, my entry's simply
a continuation of your work
in that last tournament.
And I'll win with
grace and nobility.
Traits befitting our title of
"Defending Champion."
[TOSHIKO] Sorry, everyone,
I didn't mean to be this late.
A warm hello to you all!
In case you didn't know,
I am the Boar.
[TOSHIKO] My, my.
So many familiar faces.
The Ox.
The Sheep.
The Chicken.
The Dog.
Looks like she's
waiting to pounce.
That would be our
old friend, the Tiger.
The big guy's a mystery.
Never seen him before.
Oh, look. The Monkey.
[MISAKI giggles]
[TOSHIKO] I suppose I shouldn't
be surprised to find that
repulsive young woman here.
[TOSHIKO gasps]
[TOSHIKO] I definitely don't
recognize Mr. Sleepyhead.
[TOSHIKO]
Huh. What a pathetic warrior!
Who gets himself killed before
the fighting even starts?
Uuh. It wasn't me--
don't you dare say it was me!
You can't just accuse people
of murder with no evidence!
[TOSHIKO] Sorry, but when
I see a headless body
and a bloody sword,
it's not hard to do the math.
[DUO]
Warriors, welcome!
It is my great pleasure
to announce that
with the final entrant arriving,
we can at last begin
the 12th Juni Taisen!
Everyone!
Give yourselves a hand!
[USAGI]
Uh? Uh. Uh?!
I will be the referee for
the duration of the Juni Taisen.
You may call me Duodecuple.
Please try not to forget that.
Since time is always
of the essence,
I will familiarize you with
the rules of our tournament.
First, allow me to direct you
to the center of the table.
Twelve jewels. Twelve of you.
Would you each be
so kind as to take one?
[TOSHIKO] As black as a
starless night sky. Beautiful.
[TOSHIKO] If we just leave
Mr. Sleepyhead there,
does that mean he
forfeits the tournament?
[MISAKI]
Hey. C'mon, wake up!
Tch!
[MISAKI] You gotta
take one of those...
[TOSHIKO]
Stupid, meddling monkey.
[TSUGI]
What?
[TOSHIKO]
It's been a while since we
last shared a battlefield.
And unfortunately for me,
the Monkey remains
as annoyingly nosy as ever.
"When next we meet,
one of us will die."
I promised that before
and I intend to keep it.
--[NAGA] Yo, ref!
--[TOSHIKO gasps]
Since my little brother's
not gonna need it,
do you mind if I
take his jewel for myself?
I mean, it's only fair it...
[TOSHIKO]
Warrior twins?
[DUO] Of course, young man!
Consider it yours!
[NAGA chuckles]
This should fetch
a pretty penny.
However, for the sake of
this being a fair tournament,
I request that you only
swallow one of them.
Wait. What'd you just say?
Yes. And that goes for
the rest of you as well.
I want you all
to swallow your jewels.
I can't be the only one
here who's thinking
this is too big to swallow.
[DUO] I can get you a glass of
water, but that's about all.
I can handle it.
[DUO] Good. Then I take it
you've all finished?
The black jewel
you just swallowed
is a piece of
slow-acting poison.
--It's called "Juseki."
--[TOSHIKO] I should have known.
[DUO] A crystalized version
of a powerful drug that
once ingested, chemically reacts
with your stomach acid.
After twelve hours,
you'll all be dead.
Now that you're ready,
allow me to explain the rules--
I urge you all
to listen closely.
I will only explain this once.
These Juseki jewels are
also called "beast jewels,"
and the one who collects
all twelve will be the winner.
What does the winner recieve?
Whatever they want.
Because the grand prize
is the granting of one wish
of their choosing.
Huh? Wait, me? Yes! All right!
--Father, I will work so hard!
--[TOSHIKO] What?
[KIYOKO] I'm gonna win
just like you did.
I'll keep the title
in the family!
[giggles]
Wow.
Twelve years, though, huh?
[TOSHIKO]
Father. Why?
[KIYOKO] That's a long time
to wait. But hey! No problem!
[glass crashing]
[TOSHIKO panting]
You won't take this from me.
[KIYOKO panting]
--Toshiko?
--[TOSHIKO] Kiyoko.
I've got everything
under control.
You just need to
dispose of these men.
Dispose?
That's right.
Okay.
--[squelch]
--[MALE MERC 1H groans]
--[MALE MERC 1I groans]
[TOSHIKO]
Not enough.
[bird chirping]
And my mom's like,
"That doesn't even fit"--
[MALE STUDENT 1A]
Kiyoko! Hey!
Remember that favor I asked for?
I kinda need it
sooner rather than later.
Mhmm. Say no more.
[MALE STUDENT 1A]
Awesome! I owe you!
[MALE STUDENT 1B]
C'mon, man!
[FEMALE STUDENT 1A] Kiyoko,
what's this favor he wants?
Ooh. Sorry, it's a secret.
--Ah, you're bad.
--[BOTH laughing]
[KIYOKO gasps]
[whispers]
Don't tell anyone.
[TOSHIKO]
You were late, so I decided
to come get you in person.
Ready? It's time
for you to train, Kiyoko.
[MERC 1J groaning]
[MERC 1K groaning]
--[gunfire]
--[MERC 1L groaning]
--[bullet shells clinking]
You're learning!
Mercy is pointless.
[TOSHIKO]
Not enough.
Oh, my.
[gasps]
Toshiko. Um, did I...
...kill them?
[TOSHIKO]
Don't let it bother you.
Killing people is no different
from killing small animals.
You understand me, don't you?
[KIYOKO]
Mm.
[TOSHIKO] You have so much
more killing to do.
--[KIYOKO] Mm.
--More strength to find.
--Much more.
[KIYOKO]
Mm-hmm.
So much more.
[TOSHIKO]
She's almost there.
[KIYOKO panting]
--[TOSHIKO] More.
--[KIYOKO gasps]
--[KIYOKO] Heh.
--[TOSHIKO] More!
--[KIYOKO chuckles]
[KIYOKO laughing]
--[KIYOKO] More. More.
--[door creaks]
[KIYOKO]
More. I need more.
Must kill more!
--[KIYOKO] More. More.
--[TOSHIKO] Kiyoko.
[TOSHIKO] There's a hunger
inside you now, isn't there?
It says, "More." More!
So many more.
Hundreds more. Thousands more!
More for you to stab,
shoot, slice, chop,
choke, burn, shred, break.
[KIYOKO]
More?
So many people to kill!
Lucky for you, you're the
Ino family's chosen one.
Killing people
is your sacred duty.
The taking of lives.
Killing is what we desire most.
Mother, Father, and I.
The more you kill,
the happier we are!
[KIYOKO]
Uh!
[TOSHIKO] Wait, I thought you'd
be so excited to hear that.
Is this not the life
you want for yourself?
Oh, well. Then do
what your heart tells you to do.
[KIYOKO panting]
[door creaks]
[door thuds]
[EIJI]
Excuse me. May I?
--[TOSHIKO] Ox.
--[DUO] Yes. Of course!
[TOSHIKO] He has to be
considered one of the favorites.
Since you've already forced
every warrior to swallow poison,
does it even matter
who wins the Juni Taisen
if we're all going
to be dead anyway?
Your concerns
are understandable,
so I'm more than happy
to put your mind at ease.
Rest assured that as a bonus
prize, the winner will also
receive an antidote
to the Juseki poison.
[MISAKI]
So, basically, if we don't win,
we're for sure dead, right?
[DUO] Yes. The poison's
effects differ by individual,
but the process is the same.
The crystal slowly
dissolves over the course
of the tournament
until the person dies.
So, it sounds like
some of us might bite it,
even before the entire
twelve hours have passed.
[DUO]
That is a safe assumption, yes.
[MICHIO]
Hm.
If you don't mind,
this old man would like
to pipe in with
a question of my own.
[TOSHIKO]
The legendary Sheep.
The way people talk about him,
I assumed he was
either dead or retired.
Over the course
of the Juni Taisen,
I'm planing on using
various high explosives.
My question, referee sir,
is what happens if
in killing the others,
my 'splosions also blow up
the jewels
I'm supposed to collect?
[TOSHIKO]
This talk of explosives
is just him trying
to intimidate us.
Such a disagreeable trait
from a gross, old man.
[DUO] There's no chance
of damaging the crystals
by physical force,
no matter how powerful
your weapons may be.
In fact, you may try it
right now if you like.
Nah, that's fine. I don't
wanna make a mess for nothing.
[laughs]
I trust ya!
I do have one other
question for you.
How are we supposed
to retrieve these jewels
from our victims if
they've all been swallowed?
There's more than just one way--
each warrior may use
his own method.
But if I may offer
my own opinion,
I'd say slitting open
the victim's stomach
is the most efficient way
to recover the jewel.
Since there appear to be
no more questions,
I will declare
the tournament open
and wish you twelve
warriors good luck!
[MISAKI]
'Scuse me! Can I have a moment?
I have an idea.
Under the rules he gave,
I don't think any
of us have to die.
[TOSHIKO] Well, aren't you the
brave, selfless one.
Foolish Monkey.
Let me guess:
You want to rig the battle,
then have the ultimate winner
wish everyone back to life?
Hell, it's probably even
more ridiculous than that!
[TOSHIKO]
Don't waste our time.
Why would any of us ever
use something so powerful
on a bunch of people
we don't even know?!
Raise your hand if you're
interested in hearing my plan?
[TOSHIKO] There's no way any of
them want to join some scheme
to become "super best friends"--
--[TSUGI clears throat]
--[TOSHIKO] Who was that?
[TSUGI] So, yeah, if...
if no one has to die,
then I think that's kinda
for the best. Yeah.
We let you kill us...
[TOSHIKO]
His voice. It's very familiar.
[TSUGI] ...you use
your wish to bring us back.
That's you're big idea...
[TOSHIKO]
No. I'm just hearing things.
[MISAKI] If I suggested that,
I'm guessing most of you
would have concerns
about whether
I'd go through
with reviving you.
My plan offers something more
secure than just a promise.
[TOSHIKO]
Uh. Good lord.
She's really going
for the soft sell.
But they'll see it through it.
It's nothing more than
a monkey's trick.
[TOSHIKO gasps]
No. You've got to be kidding.
I underestimated her.
Right out of the gates,
there's an alliance.
And they've got
the Ox on their side.
I better put an end
to this before it ends me.
I'm in.
[YOSHIMI]
Mmm.
--[TOSHIKO chuckles] Hilarious.
--[MISAKI] Okay. That's fine.
So right now, it's me
and the two pacifists.
[TOSHIKO] What exactly
makes you think a creep
holding a bloody knife
is a pacifist?
[MISAKI]
Well, Sleepyhead get up.
Hey! Bunny Ears!
Your team's over here! C'mon!
[TOSHIKO]
What the hell?
I'm impressed.
You guys are smarter
than you look.
I'd hide in a giant
dust cloud, too,
if I was about to face me.
I haven't yet decided
who's responsible for
collapsing the floor,
but I do know
I'll have to tread
carefully around them.
[TOSHIKO]
Was it the Sheep?
Was it even
caused by explosives?
Or did they bring down the floor
with some kind of special power?
Well, whomever did it, I'll
have to thank before I kill.
It was positively
delightful seeing
Team Monkey cut off
at the knees.
[TOSHIKO]
Mm.
I know you're there!
Be a good sport
and come out and face me!
[USAGI] Aw, man. I would've
been happy fighting anyone,
but you know what they say.
Nothing good ever happens
when you start a fight
with unfinished business
weighing you down.
Oh, jeez!
[TOSHIKO]
Even the stupid Monkey gang
would have been
preferable to this creep.
Hopefully I can squeeze
some fun out of him
before fillin' him with holes.
[USAGI] State-of-mind is so
important when you're a warrior.
I've been bothered ever since
you suspected me
of killing that guy.
Without any proof!
You're an awful person!
[TOSHIKO]
I'd say his state-of-mind's
been in question from the start.
Still, he does seem like one
of the more capable ones.
He could probably dominate
every one of the twelve,
except Ox and myself.
I'll begin with
an opening volley
from Aishu and Inochigoi.
I'll keep my distance
to maintain the advantage.
[USAGI laughing]
[TOSHIKO]
Dodge.
Then pretend
I'm out of ammo...
...to draw him in close.
And then use the
Infinite Fire of Non-Reload
to finish him off.
All that's left will be
to carve the jewel
out of his belly and
move onto the next one.
Regrettable that you'll
die first, but maybe order
doesn't matter
when I'll kill you all!
Killing bountifully.
Inonoshishi. I'm the Boar!
Killing psychotically.
I'm the Rabbit Usagi.
[TOSHIKO]
You're a brave little bunny,
but bravery still
isn't enough to beat--
[TOSHIKO groans]
[TOSHIKO]
Someone's... helping him?
[gasps]
[TOSHIKO]
Who?
[TOSHIKO gasps]
You're a... Necromancer?
Technically, "Necromantist."
That means I have the power
to make the people I kill
into my personal zombies.
I'm sorry I lied about
killing the snake warrior--
really, I am!
[TOSHIKO]
I wasn't fooled by your lie.
You were holding
the murder weapon!
I can't believe I'm dying here.
At the hands of this freak!
I thought you might have had
my special power figured out,
so I had to be careful.
But, hey, listen to me, okay?
You're gonna forgive me
for all this lying and killing,
because I'm making you
my new friend.
[DUO] They say that when
a barking dog catches you,
he won't bite. But what
does the biting dog do?
He doesn't bark. He laughs.
Next time:
"Tricks Both Mongrel and Fowl."
Everyone!
Give yourselves a hand!