[JUDGE A]
Court is in now session!
This is a
Warrior Misconduct Hearing
for the Tatsumi Brothers.
Accused are present.
Counselor.
The prosecution may begin.
Thank you, Your Honor,
guests of the court.
The Tatsumi Brothers
defy warrior standards.
Their actions are routinely
selfish and anti-social.
And given the
most recent incident,
the prosecution hereby
requests that Nagayuki
and Takeyasu Tsumita
be formally censured.
[NAGA]
He already fried Horse.
And now he's strangling Ox
and Tiger at the same time.
Even when he was alive
and in one piece,
there's no way he
could've killed like that.
[NAGA] But maybe I'm
getting ahead of myself.
I don't think Ox and
Tiger'll go down that easily.
So let's see...
If that's the state of the game,
then what's my next move?
[LAWYER] Let the record show,
that the defendants,
Takeyasu Tsumita
and Nagayuki Tsumita,
each worked for rival clients
in a foreign conflict.
This "playing of both sides"
was nothing short of disastrous.
Resulting in an
immense loss of life.
These craven actions have
damaged the prestige
of the Twelve Houses
and their standing in the
international community.
I see.
We will now begin
the question phase.
The defendant originally stated
he'd serve as his own counsel,
is that still true?
Yep.
Before we start, if both
Tatusmi brothers are on trial,
then why is only one
Tatsumi brother
standing in my courtroom?
Uh... My little brother's
stomach is acting up bad.
He didn't want
to be a distraction,
so he thought
it best to stay home.
Don't lie to me.
[NAGA] Your Honor, this is
a chronic condition for him.
He humbly asks the
court's understanding.
And because he can't be here,
I'll also be serving as
his defense attorney.
Very well.
The elder Tatsumi will serve as
proxy for his younger brother.
This will be in conjunction
with his duties as defense
counsel for both.
[NAGA]
'Can't believe he bailed on me.
[JUDGE A]
Prosecutor, you may proceed.
Yes, sir.
Your Honors,
the incident in question
began one year ago.
[screaming]
[MAN B]
Sir, watch out!
[CHIEF] Side effects
from our newest drug.
All part of the process.
Is zat right?
You said we were done
with this kinda thing!
Hmph! We are.
But drug testing can
be a tricky business.
Yeah.
Let me show you
our long-term care.
[BOY A]
Doctor!
Is my little brother ever
gonna get better, sir?
[DOCTOR]
Don't worry.
Your brother will
be taken care of.
But this remains a very
complicated ailment,
so it'll take time and money.
[BOY A]
I'll get the money!
I swear!
I'll do whatever it takes.
Just give it time,
I'll get better on my own.
If you keep running...
Unfortunate side effect.
Drug-induced
temporary blindness.
Of course, they don't
need to know about that.
How interesting.
[MAN C]
Chief.
Your visitors have arrived, sir.
Right on time.
Have them wait
in my office for now.
I'll join them, shortly.
So yesterday,
I was in this back alley.
Stay here, I don't
need you for this one.
Sure.
[phone ringing]
Hey, question.
[NAGA]
Yeah.
What's the status on the money?
Do the pharma guys
have it ready?
[NAGA]
Yeah, enough to show.
But, here.
Look.
The bulk of it's just biding
its time in that vault.
[TAKE]
Biometric entry.
[NAGA]
We'll figure that out.
[CHIEF]
Excellent.
We're still on for tomorrow,
as scheduled
[BOSS]
As scheduled.
Though, I heard something
that's got me wondering.
[CHIEF]
What's that?
A little birdie tells me
you might wanna get out
of our little arrangement.
Your birdie is lying.
[TAKE]
I'll be honest:
Neither of these guys'
actions make much sense to me.
Why do they even
need two guys like us?
This seems to be
just your average
run-of-the-mill
business deal, right?
[NAGA]
Well, it's a lot of money,
and neither side
trusts the other.
Happens all the time.
[TAKE] Nah, there's gotta
be more to it than that.
Then lemme lay it out for ya.
The pharma boys test their
drugs on orphans supplied
by the organization
you currently work for.
[TAKE]
Disgusting.
On the surface,
they're a kids' charity.
They run shelters,
clinics, stuff like that.
But they make their real
money in human trafficking.
Too bad for them,
the pharma company's almost
done testing their latest drug.
So your guys won't need
what my guys are selling
for much longer, huh?
But what happened
to all those side effects?
They've almost got
em all ironed out.
And once they say it's
good enough for market,
they're gonna terminate their
relationship with your guys.
In turn, your client wants
mine to keep paying,
or they'll leak the
testing to the press.
Hah!
One more thing.
If our transaction
was made public,
it's your company
that suffers most.
Try not to forget that.
Threaten all you like, friend.
You're not the only one
with leverage here.
[TAKE] So, tomorrow's
the final exchange
between our two employers.
Yeah.
Then we make our move.
[BOSS] Whaddaya mean you're
ending our partnership?!
It's just what it sounds like!
We got what we wanted from
you and now we're finished!
[BOSS]
Oh, you got that right!
And here's the one to finish it.
[CHIEF]
Call in our guy!
Hey!
Hello!
What? Your guy and my guy are...
Wait, are you two brothers?
Crazy, am I right?
Let's get it on, brother!
Hey. Hey. No, not yet!
[CHIEF]
Hey, I didn't say attack!
Yeah! Yeah!
What? Afraid of fire?
[chuckles]
Hey! Don't follow me!
Who does that?
You tell me.
Who hires a psycho?
[CHIEF]
Apparently, you do!
The power's out!
Hi!
You can take him!
[CHIEF]
Close it!
[BOSS]
You close it!
[NAGA]
End of the line, boys.
Wait, please, don't hurt us!
[BOSS]
You lousy punks, you set us up!
[NAGA chuckles]
Of course!
I-I'll pay you!
How much?
Just name your price!
Whatever he says,
I'll double it!
No, wait, I'll...
I'll quintuple it!
Sound good?
That's four times more!
[laughter]
Naw.
I think we'll
just take all of it.
[TAKE]
Yes!
[laughs]
[NAGA]
What can we do next?
[LAWYER] The Tatsumi
brothers burned down
the pharmaceutical company's
research building.
They slaughtered dozens
of innocent people.
But not before
stealing millions.
Would counsel for the defense
like to make a rebuttal
for the record?
Nothing to say,
'cause warriors accept
that innocents will die
on the battlefield.
[LAWYER] Then do you also
accept the outrageous cost
of cleaning up after
your wanton destruction?!
Hey, now wait.
That was collateral damage!
Collateral damage?
Is that what you call
your dead clients?
Your Honors, they're murderers!
Not true.
I killed my brother's client
and he killed mine.
That's exactly what
we were hired for
and an example of
meeting warrior standards
No!
You are a team.
But this time you falsely
presented yourselves!
You were hired separately
under individual contracts.
The brothers clearly should have
executed separate missions!
Which wouldn't have
changed the result at all.
That's a lie!
[JUDGE A]
Order! Order!
The purpose of this hearing
is to evaluate whether
the Tatsumi brothers adhere
to normal warrior standards.
I've looked at these
materials submitted
by the brothers' family,
on their behalf.
The defendants in this case
have a complex record, indeed.
They once stole
treasure that had been
hoarded by a
brutal dictatorship
and redistributed them
to the oppressed citizens.
[NAGA] Though,
it ended up sparking a riot.
[JUDGE A] On another occasion,
they stole the entire take
from an high-end
underground casino,
and gave it to the children
of a nearby orphanage.
[NAGA]
And the orphanage director
ended up stealing it all.
[JUDGE A] And they once stole
millions from a corporation,
then spread it around to
the poorest areas of the city.
[NAGA] Though the company
killed most of those people
when they came
back to retrieve it.
And then there was
our latest job, at the docks.
What should
we do with this stuff?
It'd be a real waste if it
ends up back in crates.
Honestly, we just did our heists
to have fun and kill time.
[JUDGE B] The younger boy was
one of their guinea pigs.
The testing devastated his life.
Side effects from the drug
blinded him in both eyes.
The Tatsumi Brothers learned
of this boy's misfortune,
and thought long and hard
about the best way to help.
So they gave the boy a large
sum of the money they took
from the pharmaceutical
company operation.
Thank you.
[BOY A]
Huh?
[MAN E]
What's that?
What's...?
[MAN E]
Look!
[BOY A]
Money?
[BOY B]
What's goin on?
[BOY A]
It's raining money!
You're a sucky pilot,
ya know that?
[NAGA] Hey, I don't see
you flying, wise-ass!
I wonder if it's them.
I've heard stories about
a pair of brother thieves
who're like modern
day Robin Hoods.
They steal from the rich, and
then give it back to the poor.
Wow.
[JUDGE B] Any impartial hearing
of the Tatsumi brothers' conduct
must also take these
incidents into account.
[NAGA]
That one backfired, too.
[CLIENT]
We've been ordered to take out
anyone connected to the
incident with the pharma group.
You guys in or out?
Erase any remaining evidence of
their human guinea pig program?
Depends on the pay.
Take a look in
the case beside you.
We're in!
[BOY B]
I see you!
I'm glad.
You both worked hard for this.
Thank you, Doctor.
It's so bright.
Still blurry.
It worked.
Welcome back.
Fire!
It's blocked!
Move!
[BOY B]
Hold on!
Help! Somebody!
My leg's trapped! Go!
Get outta here!
No way, I'm not leaving you!
[BOY A]
If you stay, we'll both die!
Go on! Go!
Go!
[BOY B]
No!
[TAKE laughs]
[MAN F]
Found one alive!
Huh?
What?
[TAKE]
Hey. Hey kid!
What are you doin out here?
You could get hurt!
I could ask you the exact
same question, mister.
I'm just out here
takin' a few pictures.
My brother died here.
We were both in the hospital,
and it burned to the ground
before he could get out.
Ah. Well, I hate to
pop your bubble kid,
but prayin's not
gonna bring him back.
That's a rude thing to say.
I know he's not coming back, but
praying makes me feel connected.
[TAKE]
Connected.
Ok, so you believe in God,
heaven, all that fun stuff?
Because if ya don't you're
just wasting a lot of energy.
Maybe.
I don't really know.
[TAKE] Heh. So, you're just
out here talking to yourself
like a crazy person?
If coming here makes me
feel better, why's it matter?
You're a pretty bad
man ya know that?
[laughs]
The world's full of bad men
with money who're
a lot worse than me!
That's where
you're wrong, mister.
I know for a fact there
are some rich men out there
who give their money away
to the people who need it most.
[NAGA]
Yeah.
That my young friend is
truer you could ever know.
Here, this is for you.
Please accept our apologies
for killing your big brother.
[NAGA] But hey, you got your
vision back so that's something.
I'm sorry, but the good deeds
from those noble thieves
you believe in.
They mean nothing and
aren't worth one thin dime.
[LAWYER]
The whole thing's a con!
Giving to the poor.
They don't do it out of the
goodness of their hearts!
Objection!
Hurtful statement!
Defendant!
You will raise your hand
before you address this court!
Prosecutor, please continue.
They're amoral warriors
and follow no code at all!
It's a joke to them!
They steal, then give
away their ill-gotten gains
for their own amusement!
[JUDGE A]
Go ahead.
Look.
We're part of one of
the Twelve Zodiac Houses.
The jobs we take involve us
in all sorts of criminal acts.
Are you really gonna judge us
by a typical standard?
Or just by your
personal standards?
I've seen kids kill their own
parents for food scraps.
This moral standard you
wanna apply to the two of us.
You can't apply it
to anyone out there.
Honey, I'm home!
[sniffs]
What's cooking?
Hey, you're back
sooner than I thought.
What are you doing?
Oh. Yeah, he died.
So, I'm havin myself
a little memorial.
What a nice way
to remember a friend.
I can't believe you blew off
our hearing for this.
You owe me an attorney's fee!
So, are you gonna blog that?
[TAKE]
What are you an idiot?
I'd freak out my fans.
A toast!
A fond farewell
to that little blind kid!
Is that thing any good?
Yeah, it's awesome.
What do ya think?
[NAGA] My little
brother is even weirder
than I gave him credit for.
When he's not killin for money,
he's blogging about reptiles.
And when he's not doing that,
he's eatin' 'em!
Oh, look what the
mailman brought today.
[TAKE]
Yep, we're going to "the show."
Nice.
[NAGA] I never thought
the day would come.
Now, our whole lives
lead to this,
and you're dead
before it even starts.
Stupid fool.
Still, even in death,
you've given me a chance
to win the whole thing.
[KANAE screams]
So fire will kill it.
And that answers
my other question as well.
I had wondered why we're
not fighting Horse, too.
Being burned to death
must've prevented Rabbit
from turning him into
one of his puppets.
That's how I'll defeat him.
Fire.
It's the only permanent way
to be rid of his
re-animated friends.
[KANAE]
You stupid, son-of-a-bitch!
You're a dead man!
I'll kill you!
Bastard!
All you did was
piss me off more!
Right here! You and me!
Right now!
I'm glad you're
back on your feet
and with that chip on
your shoulder still intact.
I expect our duel later
to be quite lively.
But first...
Our mutual enemy is
proving troublesome.
Setting him on fire
wont be easy now
that we've burned up the fuel,
and chopping him up
will just put us right back into
the bind we were in before.
[NAGA] Those two are making this
way harder than it needs to be.
If they had all the information,
they'd know that my dead
brother's first priority
is following that rat brat.
He's only fighting Ox and Tiger
because Ox and Tiger
are fighting him.
Run away, guys,
and this fight's over!
Assuming Ox's honor
would even let him run away.
Man, would I love to see that
Oh, well.
It's time I made my move.
[chuckles]
I had given up on winning.
But now, with my reanimated bro
we'll have that Tatsumi Brother
teamwork, once more!
Not even death can sever
the bond between us.
How sweet.
Just looking out for
my little brother, that's all.
Why do you make it
so hard to love you?
[NAGA] I'm countin on you,
little brother.
Just keep em distracted for me.
And I will get you the
memorial that you deserve.
[DUO]
They say,
"only a fool hopes a stump
will kill a rabbit twice."
Though, if stumps
could hunt rabbits,
the fool's hope
would be rewarded.
Next time: "The Man Who Chases
Two Rabbits Catches Neither."
Everyone!
Give yourselves a hand!