To the dignitaries gathered
here this evening,
the Juni Taisen is an
encapsulation of all wars.
Wars, with their enormous
economic, humanitarian,
and environmental costs are,
once every 12 years,
distilled into a
single tournament
of 12 special warriors.
A proxy war.
A peaceful way to settle
territorial disputes
between our lands,
represented by each of you.
A high-minded gamble for
control of the world!
When we reach the point
in the tournament
where half the participants
have been eliminated,
we shall begin the
formal betting.
Allow me to now update
you on the performance
of each remaining warrior.
The Warrior of the Ox
took an early lead
and currently holds
three Juseki jewels.
The Rabbit and Dragon Warriors
are tied for second place,
with two jewels each.
Everyone else is in fourth,
with only the jewels
they swallowed
at the tournament's start.
[VIP A]
Under the Juni Taisen rules,
I assumed they would all
divide into teams early on.
But so far only the Rabbit
appears to've formed one.
[VIP AA]
You said we can place bets
when half of them remain.
I assume the headless
corpse doesn't count
as an active fighter.
[DUO]
Yes, madam, that is correct.
[VIP B] I wonder if any
one fighter will be able
to defeat the Rabbit's
team by themselves.
[VIP BB]
The Ox.
[VIP C] The Natural-Born Slayer
would only be held back
by any others.
I guarantee that any
team he encounters,
he'll dispense with quickly.
[VIP AA]
We talk about Rabbit's team,
but Monkey and Rat
are also allied.
[VIP D] I don't know what
to think about them.
The Monkey's certainly
a known quantity,
but there's so little
info on the Rat,
I have no clue how
well he'll perform.
[VIP E]
In the Juni Taisen,
I don't see a scenario where
the Monkey's pacifism
is anything other than
a huge disadvantage.
[VIP A]
I disagree.
I say, Rabbit, Ox, and Monkey
are the clear favorites.
[VIP AA]
Ugh. Where's the fun in that?
Only three favorites means the
winning bet won't pay much.
There must be something we
could do to shake things up.
[VIP B] We have yet to
talk about the Sheep.
[VIP AA]
The Sheep.
[VIP BB] As the winner
of the Ninth Tournament,
he does possess a pedigree
the other's lack.
[VIP F]
Not only that,
he won decisively
and single-handedly.
[VIP D] Three decades ago!
He's well past his prime.
[VIP C] Ha! He's the most
experienced warrior of the 12!
There's no way the old man
entered the Juni Taisen
without a plan.
Dismiss him at your own peril.
[VIP AA]
I tend to agree.
Whatever the Sheep
ultimately does
will undoubtedly
affect the outcome
of the entire tournament.
[VIP E]
So is he one of the favorites?
Or is he a dark horse?
A black sheep?
[VIP F]
Excellent.
Now it's showtime, everyone!
We don't want to
miss any moment!
The outcome of the Juni Taisen
will ultimately re-draw the
maps of the entire world!
After three more warriors die,
wagering will commence.
In the meantime,
watch them fight carefully.
Their performance now
will help you determine
whom you think will
survive to the end.
Distinguished guests,
we are about to enter
an exciting new phase.
From what I know and've seen
of the remaining warriors,
there are three who'll not only
be trouble for me in a fight,
but have gotta be
clear favorites
to win the whole she-bang.
Sharyu, Warrior of the Monkey.
Usagi, Warrior of the Rabbit.
And Ushii, Warrior of the Ox.
Anytime you bring 12
folks together for a fight,
of course some are gonna
have more talent than others.
But the imbalance in favor
of these three warriors
is far too great.
It'd be smart to avoid
direct conflict with them
for as long as possible.
At my age, all that's
left is skin and bones.
I'd crumple from a single blow!
So while everyone else is
zigging, I'm gonna zag. Ha-ha!
I'll trick those three
into killing each other
before they can even
get close to me.
That way, this weak old
man stands a chance.
[MISAKI]
Your raised your hand. Remember?
When I asked people
to join my team?
[USAGI]
Uh?
[YOSHIMI]
Stupid. Stupid!
[SUMI] It's true, I won
the Juni Taisen once before,
but that was ages ago.
All I did in the past makes
no difference in the present.
If my own mother ranked
the warriors in this Taisen,
even she wouldn't put
me higher than tenth.
The older I get,
the more I realize
that a young body in
itself gives great power.
[SUMI]
Little Taro took his bear,
curled up with the blanket,
and fell fast--
[SUMI yawns]
How is it this book's
putting me to sleep,
while you're more
awake than before?
Wanna hear a story about
your Papa when he was young?
A long time ago, before
things were as peaceful
as they are now, there was
a wily weapons merchant,
who peddled his goods
in a far-away land.
[MAN A] You're right.
It is a good product.
That's why I want you
to put it on my tab.
Now, wait. That wasn't
part of our deal.
Thought I made it
clear when I got these
that I only trade 'em for cash.
Well, me and the
boys have been
pretty strapped for cash
ourselves, lately.
So put it on my tab
and we'll be good.
[SUMI]
Oh, I see.
It either goes on the tab,
or you pay in lead.
Well, you don't leave
me much of a choice.
Okay. It's been a pleasure
doin' business with ya.
[PIRATES scream]
[MAN B] So you took out a
whole cell, just like that?
[SUMI]
Eh, no biggie.
Things had run their
course with 'em.
I gotta say, it's a little weird
that you'd try to sell
us the same goods.
[SUMI]
It's not weird at all!
I'll sell to anyone
so long as he respects the
value of what I'm sellin'.
When you're in the sales game,
you find that making
new customers
helps make more new customers.
In honor of our new friendship,
this one's on the house.
Please shop with us again soon.
[SUMI]
As that young man waded through
the worst battlefields
in the world,
he wasn't just selling weapons.
He made quite a name for
himself as a warrior, too.
[SUMI]
It wasn't long after that
one of the man's most powerful
clients, the Tsujiie family,
welcomed him into their house
as their new son-in-law.
During the Juni Taisen,
that young man had his
greatest accomplishment,
representing the family as
the Warrior of the Sheep.
[SUMI] He won the Juni Taisen
and his wish was granted.
To grow peacefully
into the old man
who is here with you now,
watching you sleep.
[SUMI'S GRANDCHILD]
Hey, Grandpa.
What's this thing?
I was wondering
when you'd find that.
It's my birthday present to you.
Don't be afraid. Push it.
[SUMI]
As a young man,
I lived on the battlefield
and I expected to die there.
I never thought
I'd reach the age
where I'd get to play
with my grandchild.
"The best laid plans
of mice and men."
Or, in my case, sheep.
Grandpa, that's five
games in a row now!
Why are you no good at battles?
I'm just a little lost.
This game is nothing
like any battle
I've ever been in,
that's for sure.
If you went on one of the
battlefields these days,
you probably wouldn't
last a second!
What're ya talkin' about?
I'd kick their butts!
Father, are you sure
you want to do this?
At the next Juni Taisen, I will
go in my grandchild's place.
My mind is made up.
[SUMI] Unlike other warriors,
I've had a long and happy life.
My family. My grandchild.
They have made it that way.
I refuse to let them bear the
burden of the Juni Taisen.
Maybe I can take this
burden with me to nirvana,
and bring the other Taisen
warriors along with me.
[TSUGI] I didn't come
here to chase corpses.
[TSUGI]
What the hell?
Well, this took a turn!
You don't have to
do this, Usagi!
it's not too late to join us!
Remember what I said?
I have a plan where
we can all survive!
Just put down your weapons
and listen to what
I have to say!
We're all here because we
want to have a wish granted,
so just stop fighting
and tell me yours!
If we're on the same team,
I promise I'll work with
you to make it a reality!
All right, then. Tell
me what your wish is.
[gasps]
[SUMI] If all the other warriors
are stronger than me,
how do I make up the difference?
What can I do that they can't?
What do I have that they don't?
The easy answer is experience
and the wisdom that
comes with it,
but if there's a more
tangible advantage...
...I suppose it's this!
As you get older,
you learn to approach
things with due caution.
Taking unnecessary risks
can be the difference
between life and death.
As soon as I saw this gemstone,
something about it
seemed unnatural.
Sure, the color was beautiful,
but its cut was too unusual
for normal jewelry.
[DUO] However, for the sake of
this being a fair tournament,
I request that you only
swallow one of them.
[SUMI]
The moment he gave that order,
I knew this jewel was
dangerous with a capital "D."
[DUO]
...the rest of you, as well.
I want you all to
swallow your jewels.
[SUMI] Now, which Warrior shall
I deceive with this beauty.
[YOSHIMI] I can't believe I
thought I could partner with Ox
and dominate the tournament.
[YOSHIMI]
What's wrong with me?
Why do I get my hopes up?
[YOSHIMI]
Why?
Sorry, but given the current
state of the tournament,
the window for any
teamwork has now closed.
But I will say that I've
never fought someone
who's survived as many
of my attacks as you.
Your Ironclad defense is a
very special power, indeed.
[YOSHIMI]
He's a fighting savant.
Without surprising me,
distracting me,
or fighting dirty,
he reduced me to a panicked
mess in a straight-up duel.
[SUMI] Ranked fourth would
have to be the Boar,
daughter of a previous
Taisen winner.
Let's say Horse and Dog
are fifth and sixth.
Both look like they're
straightforward brawlers,
but good luck to the poor sap
who underestimates
Horse on defense!
In seventh and eighth place are
the twins, Dragon and Snake.
'Course, they'd rank higher
if they came as a set.
But Snake's early elimination
lowered Dragon's position.
And finally, let's put
the Chicken in ninth.
I need to go after the ones in
the middle of the ranking.
The top three are
far too powerful
for them to hope to face.
And while I'm sure that
hasn't stopped them
from making their own plans,
I bet they'd love to get
their hands on something
they think can put
them over the top.
I am more than happy to
offer that something.
[SUMI] The tournament
is stressful enough,
but throw in the poison?
Now you're talkin'
about a situation
that'll rattle even the
most stoic of warriors.
I'll exploit their unease
to my advantage.
In a way befitting a kindly
old man, of course.
[SUMI]
Hm?
Phew. That was too close for me.
Doubtful that little bomb'll
take out the Ox,
but it should slow
him down a bit.
Now, where was I?
[MISAKI]
Damn, he's left me no choice.
The Rabbit was only
pretending to listen
so he could buy more time
for his reinforcements
to get here.
[MISAKI]
This is awful.
I hate having to kill animals,
even if they are already dead.
[chuckling]
[SUMI]
Before you kill me,
at least hear about
my special power.
Would you believe I can
use quantum tunneling
to move objects through matter?
[SUMI] Not a complete lie, but
that's what'll I'll tell 'em.
[SUMI] How 'bout this,
my warrior friend?
As a show of good faith,
I'll use my power to pull that
Juseki jewel from your belly,
with no ill effects.
Now, I won't actually
be removing anything.
And to be honest,
I doubt they'll take me up
on the offer at first.
They'll think it's better
just to keep the jewel
for the time being,
rather than risk some old
man runnin' off with it.
So that's when I'll say,
"You can tell me later if you
want your jewel gone.
For now, why don't we team up?"
"These old bones ain't makin'
it to the end, no matter what,
so you know I'm not
gonna get in your way."
[SUMI]
If I can offer 'em a partnership
they see as all favorable,
I can hold off on runnin'
my "jewel removal" scheme
till I really need
a favor from 'em.
The longer they have
to think about it,
the better the chance
they pick my story apart.
They'll say, "Why don't
you just use your power
to steal the jewels
from everyone?"
Anyway, that's how
I'll form a team
that levels the playing
field in my favor.
[SUMI] I won't offer
myself to all of 'em,
even if forming a larger team
would be more to my advantage.
I'll only approach
one of the warriors.
People have a hard
time realizing
when they're being deceived,
but they can always see it
when it's happening to others.
I admit, a team of only
two seems rather weak.
But with Dragon and Snake broke
up before we even started,
the only other team we're
likely to tango with'll be
whatever the Monkey's
cobbled together,
and judgin' from the
pitch she made,
they're all gonna be
pacifists anyway!
In all my years,
enemy numbers alone
have never scared me.
And if worse comes to worse,
then I'll wipe them all out
with the ultimate weapon.
I've created a work of art.
The grenade I call, "Old Timer."
Had I not been interrupted
at the skyscraper,
I coulda finished 'em
all off in one blast.
By my count, about
three hours have passed
since the Juni Taisen began.
Plenty of time for the
remaining warriors
to settle into position.
Tch. It's just a
headless corpse.
How has it been able to
follow me this far?
[TSUGI]
It can't see, how does it know?
Ah, his other senses.
Well, in that case.
[alarm beeping]
[SUMI] Partnering with a weaker
warrior does me no good,
no matter how friendly they are.
It's essential I find someone
I ranked in the
middle of the pack.
Fourth, fifth, sixth.
I'll bet my horns that the
only two weaker than me
are that lazy Tiger
and the Rat boy.
In fact, lumpin' 'em together
is a disservice to Rat!
Tiger's so damn weak, I don't
even know why she's here!
There must be
something I'm missin'.
Some skill or power that
made her good enough
to enter the Juni Taisen.
[SUMI]
Speak of the Tiger.
Looks like she already found
the liquor store, too.
I can't imagine any scenario
where I'd ever partner with her.
I mean, look at her!
She's not trying to find the
others, let alone fight 'em!
She's just out
here gettin' wasted.
Nothin' about her's even
remotely threatening.
I'd wondered why she
was in this tournament,
but now I don't even care.
She's just pathetic.
Hardly worth wastin'
a grenade on.
[KANAE] I know you're hidin' in
those bushes, dirty old man.
Quit peepin' on me
and get out here!
C'mon! Let's go!
[DUO] "You can't judge a
horse you haven't ridden,
or a person you
haven't lived with."
To ride demands courage,
to share a home demands more.
Next time: "Even a Champion
Racehorse May Stumble."
Everyone!
Give yourselves a hand!