[EIJI]
Hmph. Very well.
Consider our alliance
officially dissolved.
I challenge you to a duel.
[gunfire]
[KANAE]
Jeez.
What a pain in the ass.
[gasps]
[SOLDIER G]
Where'd he go?
[EIJI]
Are you injured, miss?
Can you hear me?
Do I smell...?
They forced you to drink.
Those animals.
They are a disgrace.
They don't even deserve
to be called warriors.
You can rest easy now.
There's no need to worry.
The men who did
this to you are gone.
Allow me to escort
you to safety, miss.
[KANAE]
"Miss"?
What, does this guy think
I'm a civilian or somethin.
Where's Mr Matador
get off callin me "miss"?
What's the matter, miss?
Uh... Uh, hey, listen.
If you got a sec, can I
ask you a quick question?
[EIJI]
Of course.
Okay, okay, so you're
clearly somebody
who does the right thing,
but like, how do you do it?
Without hesitation.
Without fear.
Without making mistakes.
Is that possible?
Just do the right thing?
[EIJI]
Hmph. You know,
I've never really given
it much consideration before.
Why do you ask?
Do you desire to do
the right thing, is that it?
Well, then for your sake, I'll
give it some thought right now.
It can be beneficial to express
one's motivation verbally,
from time to time, at least.
First, step one, I want
to do the right thing.
Then, I do the right thing.
That's it.
[KANAE] What kinda circular
mumbo jumbo is that?
Is he tryin to
dumb it down for me
'cause he thinks
that I'm just a child?
Well, screw him.
I mean, if it were that simple,
I wouldn't be suffering so much.
Wait.
Am I still suffering?
oh... Here, I thought I'd
left the pain behind, but...
Does this mean
I haven't drowned it all out?
That I've actually been
suffering this whole damn time?
[EIJI]
What I mean by that is,
it's impossible for you
to do the right thing--
unless you make
a conscious effort.
People do wrong in
the most offhanded ways.
Just swept along,
they fall into evil.
Without purpose,
without deliberation,
without any thought at all.
Then just like that,
they're on the wrong path
as if there were no choice.
" Michi ."
[EIJI] By contrast no one
ever says something like,
"Without realizing it, I was
just doing the right thing."
Or how about,
"The next thing I knew
I was doing good deeds."
Or perhaps,
"I helped someone
by mistake. Oopsie."
You never hear that.
And you never will.
Without intent,
there's no righteousness.
There can't be,
because righteous action
requires righteous intent.
You can't do the right thing
unless you set
your mind to do it.
If your inability
to do the right thing
is causing you
to suffer right now,
that's likely because
you're aware of the fact
that you're not trying to do it.
There are many reasons why
one may not try to do good.
A myriad of fears which
might inspire hesitation.
You can blame it on another
person or on society as a whole.
You can blame the age we live
in, or the cards you were dealt.
But hear me, those who are
not doing the right thing,
must admit to themselves,
it's not that they cannot do it,
but that they will not do it.
And you...
You need not force yourself
to do what is right,
but don't fool yourself into
thinking your failure to do so
is because you're unable
but because you've made
the choice not to even try.
All righteous people
decide to do right.
And then, they do it.
[EIJI] The steps must be
taken in that order.
Worrying about the second step
while you're still on the first,
is the height of calamity.
[KANAE]
Though we were both warriors,
the difference between us
was like the difference
between an adult and a child.
Wish I could say I followed his
advice, did what he said to do.
I wanted to.
I wanted to become the kinda
person who could do good.
I wanted it so badly.
[EIJI]
Miss, take care of yourself.
[KANAE]
Hey, wait.
Could you stay here
just a little bit longer?
I'm still not feeling too well.
I'm afraid I can't
oblige your request.
There are many more
children just like you
who I have to save.
I must go.
[EIJI]
But in the future,
be sure to stay far
away from battlefields.
I pray you never have to witness
killing or witness a slaughter.
Like the sort I've
inflicted, ever again.
[KANAE] The two of
us were both warriors,
and yet, we were so different.
I started to think that
maybe only people like him
had the right to be called that.
A warrior.
But weirdly,
it didn't bother me that much.
Instead, for the
first time in my life,
I felt like I had a goal.
It wasn't like when I had
blindly tried to follow my path
or when I had strayed from it
I wanted to become the
kinda person that warrior
would acknowledge as a peer
the next time he and I met.
He said,"Be sure to stay
far away from battlefields."
Yeah. I ignored that part.
[KANAE]
Step one, want to do it.
Step two, do it.
I might never really
know the right thing to do
or figure out a
good reason to fight.
But what mattered was that
I decided to open my eyes.
I decided to try
and find myself again.
I decided to reexamine things
I had stopped thinking about.
All my life nothing
could stop me.
But now, a towering
wall was in my way.
A teacher I wanted to impress.
Wasn't long before I learned
that the one who'd pushed me
was none other than
the Natural-Born Slayer,
the Warrior of the Ox.
After that,
it didn't take much effort
for me to find out that
his name was Ushii.
But it's a wide world out there,
and there are
countless battlefields.
For a long time, I clung to the
belief that if I kept fighting,
our paths would
cross again someday.
And then, just when I was about
to give up hope of
that ever happening.
[GIRL]
Kanae?
Long time no see!
[KANAE]
The Juni Taisen?
Yeah. You didn't hear about it?
Oh, right,
that is coming up, huh?
So, who's the
Aira family sendin'?
Actually, Sensei hasn't
chosen anyone as of yet,
but I'm sure if you
came back he would--
[laughs]
You're kidding me, right?
Like I really care
about that stuff now.
I got no interest in
some make-believe war
between the twelve families.
Twelve families?
Huh?
[KANAE]
The Ox.
What is it?
[KANAE] I went crawling
back to my estranged father,
got down on my hands
and knees and begged.
By some miracle, I got the
old man to nominate me.
I got to that observation deck,
and there he was.
Looking just like
he had back then.
I was thrilled beyond belief.
[KANAE]
But the warrior of the Ox.
That callous idiot...
...didn't evn recognize me!
He didn't remember me at all!
[gasps]
[EIJI]
Tora!
[KANAE]
Damn.
After everything
I did to get this far.
After I'd gotten the man
who'd inspired me
to challenge me to a duel.
[coughs]
Guess I'm just cursed.
Nothing in my life ever
goes the right way, does it?
A brilliant fighter like him
coulda easily handled
that attack himself
without a pathetic fool
like me getting in the way.
[EIJI]
Tora.
[KANAE]
But still, I...
I made the decision to do it.
Tora!
[EIJI]
This won't end.
I'm sorry, but you'll have
to hold on a little longer.
Don't worry,
I won't let you die.
[KANAE]
Look.
He's carrying me
on his back again.
In all my years, I've never
been saved by anyone before.
I swear, I will repay
this debt I now owe you!
[KANAE]
You blabbering fool.
I'm the one who
was repaying a debt.
You're so dense.
I see. That explains it.
[KANAE]
Explains what?
[EIJI]
It was clearly the Rabbit
who was controlling the
Dragon and Snake earlier.
He must have been
trying to ambush us,
so he could add us
to his ranks as well.
[KANAE] But we chopped
him up into little pieces.
[EIJI]
Yes.
Though there's still one
thing I don't understand.
He wouldn't show up in front
of us without any kind of plan.
Did you happen to notice
he did something right
before we sliced him apart?
My theory is that he
bit off his own tongue,
thus turning
himself into a corpse
that he could
control after death.
[KANAE]
No more.
[EIJI]
Huh?
[KANAE]
Please, no more talking
about that mangled,
freaky-ass bunny.
[KANAE]
Lemme down.
[EIJI] But the Warrior of the
Rabbit is still pursuing us.
Stopping now to face him in your
condition would be too risky.
[KANAE]
Just do it, okay.
The bleeding ain't gonna stop
if you keep bouncin me
around like this.
[EIJI]
All right.
We'll stop the bleeding first.
We should be
far enough away now.
It'll take him some
time to catch up.
[KANAE]
Not usually a big fan
of havin' someone gawking
at my open wounds like this.
You're bleeding out, Tora.
You were stabbed
through the abdomen.
That requires significant
medical care.
Fortunately, I believe there
are numerous hospitals
in this particular ghost town.
So I guess you're gonna
find one, then carry me there,
and fix me up,
all before I croak?
You really believe
I got time for that?
No way, man.
No way. No chance.
You mustn't give up!
If you surrender now,
then what will become
of the duel I've already
challenged you to?
[KANAE] It's easy for
a saint like him to spew
that kinda nonsense when he's
never suffered pain like this
in his whole perfect life.
Besides, even if he could
miraculously do
all that in time.
I'd still be in no
condition to fight.
We couldn't have our duel.
So...
What's the point?
Hey.
Mr. Warrior of the Ox.
I'm callin off our duel. OK?
[EIJI]
Tora.
[KANAE] But in exchange
for that I wanna ask you
for kind of a favor.
[EIJI]
A favor?
[KANAE] Or you could call
it more of a dying wish.
I guess.
Yeah, that's better.
I have one wish to ask of you.
[KANAE] A more girly-girl
type'd probably be asking him
for a romantic kiss
at a moment like this.
But that's never really
been my style, so...
I want you to be
the one to kill me.
Cuz if I... just bleed
to death like this,
it'll mean that...
...I was killed
by that demented little
Rabbit creepazoid, won't it?
It'll have been his
blade that killed me.
So then, what?
I become another one of
his walking dead marionettes?
Huh?
I don't know exactly how
all that Necromantist
mumbo-jumbo works, but...
...I know I want no part of it,
and I know I don't
wanna keep fighting you
even after I'm dead.
[KANAE] The moment you
challenged me to a duel,
made all the fighting I had
to do to get here worth it.
[KANAE]
So I want you to be the one
who brings an
end to all of this.
And hey, isn't it better
for you if I don't come back
as a merciless zombie,
hell-bent on slaughtering you?
I wanna leave no regrets behind.
I want you to use
your incredible power
to kill me systematically,
Natural-Born Slayer.
[EIJI]
Very well.
However, let this be
a duel to the death.
You shall die with dignity.
Now let's do this right.
State your name.
[KANAE] Wow, asking a lot
of a dying woman, aren't ya?
And so formal.
Or it's just the
right thing to do.
Man, this is perfect.
Getting to die in
a duel with the Slayer.
Maybe a little too perfect
for a good-for-nothing
like me.
Yeah, that's for sure.
I slipped up
somewhere along the way,
and things got really
muddled there for a while.
But in the end, I'd say my
life wrapped up pretty nicely.
[KANAE] Think I'm gettin'
drunk on the moment here.
[EIJI]
Tora.
Before this is ended,
would you please tell me
why you were holding a
grudge against me?
Did we perhaps meet on some
battlefield once upon a time?
I don't have any grudge against
you, not at all, how could I?
This is the first time
we've ever met.
You just reminded me of someone.
Don't worry about it.
That's all that it was.
Killin' in a drunken rage.
The Warrior of the Tiger.
Tora.
And the Ox.
Killing systematically.
Ushii.
[DUO] They say,
"Only a fool plays a harp
to stop a raging bull."
But might there be a song
that plucks at the heartstrings
of a music-loving bull?
Next time: "To Treat a Man
to Beef From His Own Cow."
Everyone!
Give yourselves a hand!