[EIJI]
Why is this affecting me so?
This isn't something new for me.
I've put down
many a dying soldier.
It's the humane thing to do.
The honorable thing to do.
Maybe... it's because she
reminds me of a young girl
I once met in a
war zone, long ago.
Of course, comparing someone
as incredible as Tiger
to a lost little girl is
affront to her as a warrior.
I don't partake in alcohol,
but if I had a drink in hand,
I'd raise it you,
"Warrior of the Tiger."
[EIJI]
Now then.
Usagi, Warrior of the Rabbit.
He's so desperate to fight,
he continues even as
a dismembered corpse.
For the traditional warrior,
death at least brings with
it a promise of peace.
There's nothing traditional
about this Necromantist.
To enslave his own
body as he has?
It defies the very
definition of sanity.
And while such actions
are phychotic,
the motivation behind
them may be rational.
It seems even in death,
he's still trying to win.
I doubt even the tournament
organizers expected him
to go to such lengths.
On the other hand, they knew
he possessed this power.
They may have accounted for it
as his advantage from the start.
When I think of what I've
experienced in the Juni Taisen,
every warrior possessed at least
some kind of power or skill
they could use to bend the
tournament in their favor.
I have no such advantage.
Only my skills with the sword.
But perhaps I should
consider meeting the Tiger
to be my advantage.
If not for our alliance
of necessity...
If not for her taking
that stab wound,
I would currently be among
the living dead myself.
Although, I can't help but
think he wasn't going for me.
The way he stabbed
her didn't look like
he'd missed his primary target.
It was a precision strike,
aimed at the poison
jewel in her abdomen.
Once again, there appears to
be a logic to his actions.
And so long as I look at
the situation unemotionally,
I should be able to see it.
He's not doing this simply
to show off his powers
or his fighting style.
It's all about winning
the tournament.
But why?
Why enslave your own corpse
and try to steal the jewel?
Yes, if you win the Juni Taisen,
you get to have
one wish granted.
But such a prize is
only worth something
if you're around to enjoy it.
Can a person have a wish
that's so important
they still desire it
even in death?
But if it is so important,
why gamble your life
fighting in the first place?
Why not just hide and
wait everyone out?
What is the Rabbit doing?
And why is he doing it?
These mysteries will remain
frustratingly unsolved.
I must put my mind toward
what I can accomplish:
Holding a proper
memorial for him.
And when I use
the word memorial,
I mean I shall burn his
corpse down to ashes.
[EIJI] But it may prove
difficult to find
the necessary
flammable materials.
Maybe I can get to a gas
station before he gets to me.
There's fuel in those cars,
though siphoning it
may take even longer.
[EIJI]
He's already here?
I chopped that corpse
into a dozen pieces.
I assumed it would take longer
for him to reassemble.
[EIJI] "Walking corpse" is
too tame a word for him now.
He's become a monster.
[EIJI]
My God. Now what?
I could slice him into even
smaller bits with my saber,
but he'll simply re-form
into a new grotesquerie.
One thing is certain:
I cannot waste any more
time on this wretch.
I need to destroy the
Rabbit, definitively.
I shall use both sword
and fire in concert!
First, I'll dice him up again.
And then with the
time that affords me,
I'll prepare the gasoline
for his ultimate demise.
[EIJI] There are no vital
spots on the undead.
Heart, brain, throat--
they mean nothing now.
[EIJI]
He's already killed the Monkey?
How could I be so... careless?
Even though I didn't know
Monkey had been killed,
I should have been
able to predict
that a monster assembled
from the parts of corpses
could have someone
hiding inside.
It did seem strange
that once re-assembled,
he became larger
rather than smaller.
He used the parts of his
old body to bind together
an even more monstrous form.
The only time he
could have done this
was while I was running
away with Tiger.
And he couldn't
have done it alone.
He must have summoned Monkey
and had her reassemble him.
Like pieces from a model kit.
Even for a haphazard assembly,
his re-formed body was
especially gruesome.
He had her put
himself back together
so she could fit inside.
And then kill me.
[EIJI]
Damn! What a fool I am!
If only I hadn't averted my eyes
and kept my wits about me!
No.
Even if I had figured out that
she was hiding inside him,
that the corpse belonged
to someone of her skill
means I'd still have
ended up in this spot.
I'm completely at
the mercy of a corpse.
If she wanted to, she could
crush my limbs into powder.
The only reason she's not
is because her master
doesn't want her to.
That pulsating ghoul wants
to finish me off himself!
That way, he's assured
of keeping my body
as intact as possible,
thus making me a more
effective servant.
No consciousness. No
desires. No principles.
I'll be fighting constantly,
forever following orders.
In a way, it won't be
so different from now.
But there will be one difference
I very much dislike.
I won't be able to
act righteously.
First, step one: I want
to do the right thing.
Then, I do the right thing.
[EIJI] So what's the
right thing to do now?
I fear my only remaining option
is to kill myself
before he does.
I just have to work up the
nerve to actually do it.
I never imagined killing myself.
And certainly not like this.
[EIJI groans]
[EIJI] Makes sense that
they wouldn't care
about knocking out
my teeth, either.
As a corpse, I'll be mute
and won't need to eat.
One day, they may look back
and say the outcome of this
Juni Taisen was decided
the moment Rabbit killed Monkey
and turned her into
his deadliest friend.
I don't know how many
warriors remain.
I'm fairly certain that
neither Sheep nor Dog
possessed the power to
resist Rabbit on their own.
So who else may yet survive me?
There is one of whom I haven't
seen or heard anything.
[TSUGI]
Nezumi.
Warrior of the Rat.
Looks like you're in trouble.
[EIJI]
Yes. That boy.
But why is he only emerging
at this late moment?
Up to now, he's been a complete
non-factor in the Juni Taisen.
If he was smart,
he'd go back into hiding.
He can't expect to kill
Rabbit or Monkey on his own.
Did he simply wander
here by mistake?
[TSUGI]
Glad I made it in time.
Sorry, it took me a lot longer
than I was expecting
to find the Sheep's body.
[EIJI]
Sheep? That old fossil?
Why were you looking for him?
[TSUGI] I wasn't looking for
him. I was looking for this.
[EIJI]
He made it "in time"?
Yes. In time to use that bomb.
I chopped Rabbit to pieces
a moment ago, which means
his energy is currently
going toward reforming.
And until then, he's unable
to take any action.
Monkey's role is to
pin me to the ground.
But that also means she can't do
anything else right now either.
The Rat didn't arrive
"just in time."
He arrived at the exact moment
where he can destroy
Rabbit and Monkey
and win the entire Juni Taisen.
His timing is so perfect.
It's almost superhuman,
Of course.
Killing Rabbit and
Monkey with that bomb
ensures that he'll
take me out, too.
The Warrior of the Rat could
be the most evil villain ever,
or he could simply be a cheater.
It doesn't matter.
I'll still take this
result over the one
where the Rabbit hops away.
[TSUGI] I don't know if
what I'm about to say
will bring you any
comfort before you die.
But the only reason I'm here
now is because your friend,
Miss Tiger, killed
the Sheep earlier.
If it wasn't for her kill,
I wouldn't be holding the bomb
that's about to end
this tournament.
So any credit for
what's about to happen
really belongs to her.
As for you, Mr. Ox,
do you have any last words?
No. Just do it.
This is the right end.
It's my time to go.
But you, I hope
you truly believe
this is the right
end for you, too.
Killing systematically.
Warrior of the Ox. Ushii.
[EIJI]
He wins.
Legend says the Rat
got to be the first
in the Zodiac by
riding the Ox's horns.
In a way, that's just
what he did--
rode me right to victory.
And that's all right.
What he told me about
Tiger and the bomb
has actually put
my mind at ease.
But now, having talked to him,
I can't shake the feeling
I've met him once before.
I think it was at--
[DUO]
Congratulations, Warrior Nezumi!
Well done and bravo!
You, my boy, are the winner
of the 12th Juni Taisen!
Everyone, give
yourselves a hand!
[DUO claps]
[DUO] The antidote should
be in full effect by now,
so rest easy, young warrior.
[TSUGI]
Okay, got it. So can I go?
[DUO] Not yet. Just a little
bit longer if you will.
Your win was a dazzling
accomplishment, by all measures.
I'd like to interview you
for the official record
so that future Taisen warriors
may understand how you did it.
[TSUGI]
Great. Interrogation time.
What do you say?
It's more of a
formality, really,
it shouldn't take very long.
I'll pass.
Very well then.
It's been a pleasure and
congratulations again.
[gasps]
[TSUGI screams]
What do you say?
It's more of a
formality, really,
it shouldn't take very long.
[DUO]
Very well then.
It's been a pleasure and
congratulations again.
[yells]
[DUO]
What do you say?
It's more of a formality,
really, it-- Uh.
What's wrong? Nezumi, wait.
What do you say?
[TSUGI]
That didn't work.
[DUO] What do you say?
It's more of a formality.
[gasps]
[screaming]
What do you say?
It's more of a
formality, really,
it shouldn't take very long.
I'll pass.
[TSUGI]
In less than an instant,
I refused him a hundred
different ways.
They all failed.
And 40 of those times,
I ended up dead.
Although if you compare
that to my dying
99 out of the 100 times I ran
through the Juni Taisen,
60% survival odds
with our host master
is actually pretty good.
[DUO]
What do you say?
It's more of a
formality, really,
it shouldn't take very long.
Sure. Ask me
anything you want.
[TSUGI]
Okay, lock it in!
[DUO]
I suppose my main question is,
would you explain to us
your over all approach
to the Juni Taisen?
While it's obviously clear
how you won in the end,
many of your actions leading up
to that point were rather,
shall we say, difficult for us
outside observers to understand,
let alone analyze accurately.
You're kidding. I don't think
I did anything that strange.
You're a pain in the ass!
[TSUGI] It seems resisting
is pointless. Lock it in.
You're kidding. I don't think
I did anything that strange.
Ah. What do you mean by that?
I mean, I just did
what I always do.
I ran through a hundred
different strategies
at the same time.
I call it "The Power
of Intervention."
I found the one path, one
strategy out of a hundred,
that allowed me to survive.
Very impressive indeed, my boy!
No matter how
skilled the warrior.
brave or brilliant.
No matter if he's a
re-animated corpse!
He still only gets one
try at any given action.
In other words,
if he looks right,
he can't look left
at the same time.
But it sounds as if you can.
Yep, that's pretty much it.
Now that the Taisen's over
and we understand your approach,
it's clear you dominated
it from start to finish.
[TSUGI]
You make it sound so easy.
It'd be nice if you also
understood how hard it is
to try a hundred different
scenarios at once.
I could really use some sleep.
[DUO]
Your power reminds me
of the paradox of
"Schrodinger's Cat."
The cat in the box exists
simultaneously in two states:
Alive and dead.
Perhaps we should call you
"Schrodinger's Rat."
[TSUGI]
I do kinda feel like a lab rat.
[DUO] ...Zodiac because the
rat tricked it out of its spot.
But this time,
the cat's not alone.
You put one over on
every single warrior.
[tSUGI] Ya know,
that's not exactly true.
There's a cat in the Zodiac.
I mean, a Tiger is a kind
of cat, don't ya think?
[DUO]
Heh. Good point.
[TSUGI]
On one of the paths I tried,
Tiger and I actually
formed an alliance.
[TSUGI] Of the hundred different
paths I dreamt up and tested,
this was the only one
where I survived
the whole way through,
and won the Taisen.
You are a fascinating
young man, indeed
[TSUGI] And I wouldn't have
even stumbled on this path
if it wasn't for
Sharyu, the Monkey.
Oh?
While we were
hiding in the sewer,
she asked me for a favor if
things went south for her.
[MISAKI] Hey, Nezumi.
I wanna ask a favor.
If I get killed up there,
and the Necromantist
ends up controlling me,
please destroy my body.
So, yeah.
But I refused to do it.
She was also the
one who reminded me
of the explosives the Sheep
had mentioned at the start,
and said they would be
effective against the zombies.
[TSUGI] So the one who deserves
credit for taking out Monkey
and the other zombies...
is Monkey.
[TSUGI] All the routes I
cooked up were failures.
I guess I'm just lucky.
[DUO]
You are also humble.
I find it most
impressive how nimbly
you changed your
combat priorities
depending on the circumstances.
Juggling so many different
realities has had
the beneficial effect of making
you a most flexible fighter.
Oh, and if anyone is curious,
of the hundred paths I tried,
I never learned what
Monkey's peace plan was.
It was probably
all just a bluff.
[DUO laughs]
I disagree.
I'm going to give her
the benefit of the doubt
and assume she did have a plan.
For example, it's quite possible
that a warrior of her renown
has friendships...
[TSUGI] There are only three
paths of the hundred
where I can get him
to explain this.
...a large enough alliance,
she intended to
negotiate with them.
The people of the countries
Monkey has saved
revere her as a hero.
She has ties across the world.
In fact, if she wanted to, she
could have sat at the same table
as the Taisen's organizers,
betting and swapping entire
countries, just as they do.
[TSUGI]
They bet countries? Like money?
Unfortunately, we can never
really know the exact truth.
[TSUGI]
Every time I died,
my last thoughts would be
about finding the one path
with the sequence of events
where her peace treaty worked.
If Sharyu is the warrior
who's saved the most people,
I'm probably the one who's
destroyed the most worlds.
[DUO laughs]
Putting aside her peace treaty,
I can't help but wonder
who won in each of
the other 99 routes.
I imagine it ran the gamut
of the whole line-up.
I can't answer that.
Since I died half-way through
all the other scenarios,
I was never around to
see the eventual winner.
But considering the
state of the tournament
whenever I would die,
I bet Rabbit took
the crown most times.
In fact, among those
hundred outcomes,
there was actually one
where we really hit it off
and formed a weird
sorta friendship.
Oh? You and Rabbit, partners?
[TSUGI]
Tch. Oh, crap.
I said way too much
about deleted paths.
Should I erase this one, too?
No.
No matter what I do, he'll
get it outta me in the end.
Lock it in.
[DUO]
Thank you for your time, Nezumi.
This concludes the
winner's interview.
You're free to go home and
get some much-needed rest.
Really?
Okay. Thanks.
And don't forget,
you have yet to pick the
wish you want granted
for winning the Taisen.
Once you do, feel free to
contact me at any time.
[TSUGI]
Right. Got it.
If I had to pick right now,
I'd just wish for a
good night's sleep.
[TSUGI] I'm gonna run through
a hundred different wishes
and make sure I ask for the one
that works out best for me.
[DUO] They say
"a mountain's great labor
may yield only a mouse."
Whatever you think of it,
know that it will at
least be resolved.
Next time: "The One Wish
That Must Be Granted,
and the Ninety-Nine That
Can Be Done Without."