I'm countin on you, bro.
Just keep them distracted
for a little bit longer.
And I will get you,
the memorial you deserve!
[gasps]
Huh?
[USAGI] Warrior of the Rabbit:
Killing psychotically.
Usagi!
Haven't you heard the
old tale, Mr. Dragon?
'Bout the rabbit who could
jump as high as the moon?
Now go down there and
help your little brother for me.
Tiger. Rat. Ox.
Those are the
last three to kill!
[EIJI]
Hmm?
[KANAE]
Huh?
It's two against two now.
Wait.
[EIJI]
If we count Snake's armless,
walking trunk,
his decapitated head,
and Dragon's newly
bifurcated body.
It's actually four against two.
[KANAE]
See ya!
Bye!
Later!
[GIRL A] So you know
Kanae's story, right?
About her family?
[GIRL B]
Kinda.
Don't they don't run
a big dojo, or something?
[KANAE]
Are you guys ready for this?
[DOJO MEMBERS]
Yeah!
Great!
[INSTRUCTOR]
That's enough!
The Aira dojo, hundred-man
sparring exercise
is now complete!
Yes, sir, master.
Thank you.
[KANAE'S FATHER] You were
magnificent out there, Kanae.
In light of your mastery,
I will recommend you
as a candidate for
head of the Aira dojo.
[KANAE]
Thank you, Father.
I must say, there is not
a soul left at this dojo
who's able to best you.
Any critics you had,
have fallen silent.
[KANAE]
Yes, sir.
My daughter.
Can you tell me
the meaning of bu ?
The meaning of michi ?
[KANAE]
Okay.
" Bu " is the power's form.
What we practice and refine.
Michi is how we
use it, for good.
Correct.
And can I trust you'll continue
using your skills for good?
You can.
I am proud.
Now, Kanae.
Those blessed with the name
"Aira" must go and fight
on real battlefields.
You mean in wars?
[KANAE'S FATHER]
Yes.
There are things a warrior can
learn only in actual combat.
This is your next test.
[KANAE]
Yes, Father.
I'll take what I've learned into
the world to do great things!
[KANAE]
So this is what war looks like.
Where is the michi ?
Where is the righteousness
in all this destruction?
[gunfire]
[KANAE]
I don't understand.
What is it in human nature
that makes us kill each other?
[KANAE] We say life is sacred,
but we don't act that way.
[KANAE] All I learned
is lost in the chaos of war.
[KANAE]
If we all disappeared tomorrow,
maybe the Earth
would be better off.
All right. That's your last one.
[KANAE]
You're not my dad.
This stupid world doesn't
make sense anyway.
Hypocrites.
People talk about doing
good and being good.
Ya know what makes
the world go 'round?
It ain't good, it's "evil."
Spend your life
fighting for peace.
Just to find you
changed nuthin'.
We free some country
from tyranny,
and the new leaders are
worse than the old ones.
If ya ask me,
I'm not getting sent out
there to bring peace,
but to create
even more chaos
for the big fish to
take advantage of.
They say fish won't swim
in water that's too
clean, don't they?
[BARTENDER]
It's healthier for them
if the water still has a
little bit of the wild in it.
Ours isn't an easy world
for the honest person
to build a life in, is it?
[KANAE laughs]
I love alcohol!
As long as I'm drunk.
I don't gotta worry 'bout
nothing except not throwing up!
Ya know.
Maybe the bartender was right.
I'm fast!
This kicks ass!
If you can't walk on two legs,
try running on four!
Ow-wee!
[laughs]
[KANAE] I gave myself
to the booze and the blood,
and it was only when
I was swimming in the two,
that I could forget
everything else.
[KANAE] They kept showering me
with more praise and honors.
I'm pretty sure I won more
awards fighting drunk
than I ever did sober.
[KANAE]
What was that for?
Is this how you have honored
your commitment to michi ?
[KANAE]
" Michi "?
I mean, really,
what's that even mean?
Yeah.
I said bu -bye
that stuff's too deep.
Emptyin' out my head made
everything way easier for me.
And all the brass
are getting their wins
and they're happy, so...
The fighting you're
doing is no longer " bu "!
You've become nothing
but a drunken beast!
[KANAE laughs]
Dad.
Man's the most savage
beast of 'em all.
Go away.
Never darken my doorway again.
[KANAE]
Yeah, fine!
I was done with
your stupid dojo anyway!
[KANAE] I don't wanna see
the bottom of that glass again!
I'm sorry to say,
you don't seem like
the girl I remember.
You got that right.
Whoda thought my life was
gonna turn out the way it has.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
[KANAE] I forget what
it means to show effort.
To be diligent.
Perseverance?
I can't even spell it for ya.
[laughs]
But none of that matters,
'cause the way I am now...
Nothing's gonna stop me.
[KANAE]
[KANAE] I couldn't read
people's expressions, anymore.
So I stopped looking
at their faces.
I couldn't remember
my allies' names, anymore.
So, I started fighting alone.
I forgot how to read a map.
But nothing could stop me.
Nothing could stop me.
That was just the start.
Soon, I could barely
read big words.
And outside of some basic crap,
math became a blur.
But still,
nothing could stop me.
I couldn't tell ya what day
of the week it was.
Remembering my own birthday was
enough to give me a headache.
All I could do was
keep moving forward.
And still...
Nothing could stop me.
[KANAE]
Finally, it got to the point...
...where I didn't even care
if I was alive or dead anymore.
There was nothing, and no one...
who could stop me.
[EIJI]
Hmm...
If the Necromantist brings
all his forces against us.
Then I suspect
our remaining time
in this Juni Taisen
is very limited.
Therefore, we have
to move against him now,
before the rest of his
reinforcements have assembled.
If you have an attack plan,
Tiger, I'm all ears.
Failing that, any as of yet
unseen special power of yours
would be quite welcome
right about now.
Perhaps something
like the ability to fly
or tunnel underground
at superspeed.
Sorry, Oxy Boy,
all I gots is my Drunken Fist.
I didn't come into this thing
expecting to fight zombies.
Let alone zombie body parts.
[EIJI]
Hmph. Fair point.
I can't blame you
for thinking that.
Never expected zombies either.
We need to approach
this, strategically.
I'd prefer a head-on fight,
but some kind of gambit
might just even the odds.
Tiger, look at the torso
hovering in the air.
Do you know what chemical is
inside that tank on its back?
Aww, jeez, I don't know.
You tryna say that it's not
the same flamethrower juice
that his dopey
brother was wearing?
[EIJI]
Indeed.
The Snake's backpack
was the fire.
I think this one is the ice.
I'd lay a wager,
it's liquid hydrogen.
[KANAE]
Oh.
Uh, liquid-what-now?
Wait. Are you serious? It's--
Even a small snake
can eat a man.
The Dragon!
The Elder Tatsumi Brother.
Killing for money.
And I'm the Snake.
The younger Tatsumi brother,
also killing for money.
A lot!
[EIJI] That's what we'd
be hearing, if they'd lived.
Ushii.
Killing systematically. The Ox.
[KANAE]
Hmm?
Tiger warrior!
Killing in a drunken rage!
Tora!
[KANAE]
Aww, jeez, I don't know.
You tryin to say that it's not
the same flamethrower juice
that his dopey
brother was wearing?
[EIJI]
Indeed.
The Snake's backpack
was the fire.
I think this one is the ice.
I'd lay a wager,
it's liquid hydrogen.
I got it. That's what he
wants me to do with the tank!
A hell of a fine weapon
you're wearin' pal!
Gotta wonder.
What's the big reason
ya got fur not usin' it?!
[EIJI]
I see you got my message.
Although, I'd prefer
you'd've warned me
before opening that
tank above my head.
You gotta communicate
better, ya'know that?!
It took all of my brains to
figure out what you wanted me
to do with that tank.
[EIJI]
Despite being corpses,
their eyes still display
a flicker of awareness.
Had I explained how
I wanted to use that tank,
they may have overheard
and reacted accordingly.
This kind of gambit's
not my forte.
Trying new things
isn't always easy.
But it all worked out.
[KANAE] Let's not slap each
other's asses just yet,
Fancy Pants.
If things had really ended well,
you'd be crushed ice
right there along with 'em!
[EIJI]
Oh, my.
You seem so certain of that.
Still, I am a man of my word.
I shall honor
my promise to a duel.
However, it would appear
our alliance-of-necessity
will have to continue
just a bit longer.
You know why, don't you?
[KANAE]
No, duh.
I know Rabbit's here.
That old sheep geezer did a
better job sneakin' up on me!
Hey.
Get out here and fight!
Jack ass!
[EIJI]
The tables have turned
and now it's you
who is outnumbered.
But it's only fair,
considering how many you
and your "team"
have disposed of.
Warrior of the Rabbit.
Killing psychotically.
Usagi.
Killing systematically.
Ushii.
The Ox.
Warrior of the Tiger!
Killing in a drunken rage!
Tora!
[EIJI]
Now, then.
Would you like to rest
before we do this?
Or shall we start?
[KANAE] Spare me the "chivalrous
gentleman" routine, Ox.
I got a good buzz goin from
all the blood I been drinkin.
So...
I'm ready when you are, stud!
Just know nothing's
gonna stop me.
[EIJI]
Hmph.
Very well.
Consider our alliance
officially dissolved.
I challenge you to a duel.
[DUO]
They say,
"One can't catch a tiger
without entering its den."
You may still end up eaten,
but you won't know
for sure 'til you're inside.
Next time: "A Tiger May Die,
but It Leaves Its Skin."
Everyone!
Give yourselves a hand!