[BOSS] I'm impressed how fast
you made this country girl
into a household name.
[MICHIKO] That's what the
Marketing Division does, sir.
We're already looking
for the next hot sound
that'll replace her.
I admire that.
Always staying two steps
ahead of the game, I see.
[MICHIKO] Just following
my predecessor's rules.
"Choose the hardest task first."
[BOSS] There's something else
I'd like you to sell for us.
This assignment comes directly
from Advisor Satomi himself.
Must be big then, right?
Satomi's been with us
since before the war.
[KIKKO] Born of a space-man
and an Earth woman,
Master Ultima is a
superhuman genius scientist
who travels the solar
system in his rocketship.
The kaiju he captured on Mars
was mass produced,
turned into a weapon,
and is now used
by the US military
all over the world.
Some are saying
kaiju have changed.
From being humanity's
nemeses to its protectors.
[FUUROUTA] Doesn't matter
how many times I dive.
There's nothing down there.
Well, we're definitely
at the coordinates
published by the US military.
Now, our top story.
The US Defense
Department announced
that the kaiju assigned
to its Okinawa base
has died.
The carcass was
reportedly discarded
off the coast
of Kikaijima Island.
[HYOUMA]
A "Broken Lance." Jeez.
That's what they're calling
these types of incidents.
Kaiju from places like
Greenland and Spain
have supposedly been
disposed of, too.
Meaning they're
killing them all.
Well there's nothin' here.
Who knows,
maybe the fish ate it.
Ooh! And speaking of eating!
Yeah, thanks.
Maybe it was never
here to begin with.
[MICHIKO] If it wasn't
thrown in the ocean,
where was it really taken?
It'll be in Tokyo soon.
You'll be in charge of
directing its public debut.
The campaign'll include
magazines, television, radio.
Hell, even word-of-mouth.
Aren't you going to ask me why?
In my business,
I've found it's best
not to ask why.
But I can venture a guess.
[SATOMI]
Is that so?
Enlighten me.
[MICHIKO] Okinawa gets
returned in a few years.
The Japanese public
needs to outgrow its fear
of kaiju before then.
My guess is,
this job came down
from the government in Roppongi?
Have you heard of
the Superhuman Bureau?
I haven't, Advisor.
Please, enlighten me.
[SATOMI]
Remember their name.
The Superhuman Bureau
is our enemy.
"Enemy."
[MALE TV]
So what I think is,
we should be listening to them.
Actually trying to
start a dialogue.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
What do you mean?
Listening to kaiju ?
[MALE TV] Well, they were on the
Earth since we were primates.
And now we want to
use them for our wars?
Kill them in our struggles?
Since we're on
the subject of war,
how about the
U.S. military working
with these superhumans?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Uh, we c--
[KIKKO] Beastly Radio Wave
Japan was shut down,
and the number of
kaiju decreased.
We were still searching
for its founder, Matsumoto,
as well as Hiroyuki and GaGon,
who'd somehow managed to escape.
Are you still having trouble
remembering what happened?
Kikko.
I'm here.
The kaiju I fought
disappeared, and I'm worried.
You don't think I ate it?
That'd make me
one too, wouldn't it?
[KIKKO chuckles]
You know, it's funny,
you seem to have an extra
special hatred of kaiju .
Care to tell me why?
[door opens]
The Professor is
worried about you.
Why don't we head home?
[EMI]
Lock the door when you leave.
Oh, and toss those
out for me, if you could.
Um, sure!
[door closes]
[ULLR] Star Child, how long
do you intend to stay here?
Your goal is to--
[KIKKO] Hey, Ullr,
what are kaiju anyway?
[KIKKO] At the time,
a nationwide debate
was raging about kaiju .
Were they evil?
Victims of human intrusion?
Everyone had an opinion.
The younger generation
were sympathetic to them,
in particular.
It was as though
the debate was fueling
some kind of agenda.
[ULLR] To me, they're no
different than elephants
or lions.
Just quite a bit larger.
I wish everyone
thought like you.
Humans always want to make
everything so complicated.
[ULLR] Possibly because
within each kaiju --
[KIKKO]
Were these cut out?
What is this?
[ULLR]
I feel an energy here.
[ULLR] A force associated
with the ones we call monsters.
Today's peace march will
depart from the campus
at seventeen hundred hours!
Ichigaya, the Parliament,
and American embassy
will be on our route.
They won't forget
us anytime soon!
[music playing]
[KIKKO]
Do ya think he'll come?
I mean, would Matsumoto show up
with all these people?
Good point.
He'll really stick out
if GaGon's with him.
Pardon me.
Um... Yeah?
We heard a rumor there
might be something special
planned for the
peace rally today.
Is that true?
You must be from
a different university.
To tell you the truth--
[MALE ACTIVIST 5A]
Hey, where are you from?
Where do you belong to?
Oh, you mean which
sect do we belong to?
None of them.
We're looking for someone:
Mr. Shoji Matsumoto.
How did you hear
about that name?
Then he is here!
Idiot!
[HYOUMA] I showed the photo
to a refrigerator truck driver
in Kagoshima.
Matsumoto stole a freezer unit.
Definitely
transporting something.
It's the kaiju the Americans
supposedly discarded.
But could he negotiate
with the U.S. by himself?
What we do know is
the truck disappeared
somewhere near the campus.
I knew Emi posing as a student
was too much of a stretch.
Way too old.
We'll come back later.
Let's go for now.
[HIROYUKI] You guys're
the real monsters here.
[JIRO grunting]
Jiro, no! Stop that kid!
[HIROYUKI]
You recognize this, right?
You gave it to me!
You told me to
go make more kaiju !
So that's what I'm doing!
What is he on about?
Hiroyuki!
[FUUROUTA yelling]
Unlock one.
[JIRO]
Unlock two.
[HYOUMA]
Emi!
Everyone! Run!
It's too late to stop this!
[JIRO yelling]
[JIRO yells]
Jiro! You have to stop!
[STUDENT 5A] The government
is attacking the protest!
[STUDENT 5B]
Hurry! Run!
[STUDENT 5C] Oh, man!
They're over here too!
[SHOJI]
Excellent work.
He's the enemy in the
eyes of everyone here.
And now our kaiju
will take him down
and save all the students.
[MALE ACTIVIST 5A]
Perfect.
So you'll join in
our rally today?
Yeah.
It's still early,
but... let's begin.
[MALE ACTIVIST 5A]
Ugh. It must have died.
One of America's kaiju .
I hope you know some way
to revive this thing.
We'll use GaGon's cells.
Their regenerative
powers are unequaled.
After I inject
this into its body,
it'll grow double its size.
I've tested it many times.
[UKYO]
This is a cellular invigorator.
It enhances the biological
structure of any kaiju .
Just a single injection,
and you can create a
dragon out of a lizard's tail.
[SHOJI]
It's enormous!
[UKYO]
Just as I promised.
GaGon's cells regenerate
at an incredible rate.
[HIROYUKI] What are we
going to do with it?
[SHOJI]
Uh...
[UKYO] First off, we're going
to make some money.
And then?
Those fools who celebrate
"Shinka prosperity"
are in for a big surprise!
Next up, we add GaGon's cells.
[ALL gasp]
[GAGON 4B whimpers]
[MEGAGON roars]
[JIRO yells]
[STUDENT 5B] Our peaceful
march won't be stopped!
Freeze time, Hyouma!
I'll do what I can
to calm Jiro down!
[MEGAGON, JIRO roaring]
I knew it! The Beastly
Radio Wave guys're here!
And they somehow merged GaGon
with the American kaiju !
[MICHIKO]
Don't be afraid!
This beast is the weapon
the American imperialists
tried to place in Okinawa.
It's not anyone's weapon.
It's a soldier who rejected war.
He escaped the
carrier in protest.
He's a conscientious objector!
[CROWD gasps]
We have to protect him
from the American warmongers
and the Japanese government!
We demand he's
given a peaceful life
free of servitude!
That's the true
goal of our rally.
This isn't about us!
Comrades, unite and
help me protect MegaGon!
[JIRO yelling]
If a student gets killed,
the Bureau's finished.
Fuurouta!
Make him abandon Equus!
You got it!
[JIRO yells]
[MEGAGON roars]
Meteortail!
[MEGAGON roaring]
[MALE ACTIVIST 5A]
MegaGon is you and me.
Together our fury is the kaiju !
[JIRO]
We are all-- Kaiju .
[MICHIKO]
Now. Let the peace march begin!
[FEMALE REPORTER 2A] At first,
the rally was only comprised
of students from the
Japan Peace University.
But several other
civilians have joined in.
The protest now numbers
over a thousand.
Are you positive it's safe?
There won't be a sudden rampage?
No, it's safe.
MegaGon will ensure
the safety of Tokyo
and all its citizens.
He'll take out any threat
that might come our way.
[MALE ACTIVIST 5A]
Megagon is just like us!
A victim of a corrupt society!
Help us stop the oppression!
[MICHIKO]
Impressive kaiju . Is he yours?
[HIROYUKI] He's not a kaiju .
He's my little brother.
[MICHIKO]
Huh?
He's leading us.
I just don't know where to.
[MAGOTAKE] That kaiju is in
the hands of a bunch of kids.
[AKITA]
We've taken out too many kaiju .
If we intervene now,
we'll be branded
as enemies of peace,
and the students will
side against us.
But the way they made
Jiro lose control like that--
it's an attack against
the Superhuman Bureau.
There is another way.
Say an accident happens.
Tonight at exactly 1:40 AM,
at the Shinjuku West bridge,
a cargo train and tanker
carrying American jet fuel
will be crossing paths.
A series of small mistakes
results in a collision.
Then a fire.
[AKITA] An explosion large
enough to destroy a kaiju
of that size.
Civilian casualties
would be minimal
due to the hour of the crash.
And all the newspapers
will say the driver
missed a signal.
Human error.
Yoshimura.
I was told you were
a brilliant physicist.
But you seem more like a person
who can see into the future.
With the right formula,
anything can be calculated.
[KIKKO]
Miss Emi!
I asked you to get rid of that.
[KIKKO] Ukyo Yamato
from Beastly Radio Wave.
That was you, wasn't it?
I did what's called
Figure Duplication.
Like shapeshifting.
Except I need to
borrow from an image.
I took this face too.
Kaiju would cause trouble.
Then superhumans
would take them out.
You were trying to
change the public view
of superhumans.
People got hurt--
It was necessary.
And the chief agrees.
But what about Jiro?
[EMI exhales]
Of course he doesn't know.
He loves superhumans,
and would never have
gone along with it.
Such a sweetheart.
If he doesn't know the truth,
then what's the point
of letting him
stay on this job?
He's seriously injured.
And he's only a normal human.
Do you really believe that?
You saw it.
His power.
[EMI]
Jiro is no ordinary human.
He's far stronger
and far more dangerous
than you could possibly imagine.
That's why I love him.
And just for the record--
The only people
qualified to love him...
...are those strong enough
to endure this kind of pain
in order to stop him.
To put it simply,
Jiro has a kaiju
living inside of him.
There's one inside every
human, the way I see it.
So, does that also include you?
Of course not. I'm a yokai.
[door opens, closes]
[KIKKO gasps]
You shouldn't get out of bed!
You need to lay still.
Even Emi said so!
Emi? Where--?
[KIKKO] She went on
a mission with the others.
To defeat MegaGon.
You asked why I hate kaiju .
I'll tell you.
[JIRO] Eight years ago, Tokyo
was attacked, by Giganto Gon.
--[horns, sirens blaring]
--[CROWD chattering]
[CROWD yelling]
[JIRO] It was the first time
I saw a kaiju up close.
And my blood boiled.
Honestly...
I don't know my parents,
or my real name.
I was locked in
a lab for as long
as I can remember.
Seeing his rage
was like he set me free.
Destroy! Destroy it all!
[JIRO]
He was defeated.
Killed by Rainbow Knight.
Kikko.
I know there's a kaiju
living inside of me.
And the only thing
it wants is for this world
to come to an end.
Even though I hate
kaiju more than anyone.
The one I hate
most I can't defeat.
'Cause I can never reach it.
[JIRO]
Kikko?
Rawr...?
[JIRO]
What are you doing?
Nothing, nothing!
It was nothing, I swear!
I have one too!
A monster inside me!
Inside you? No way.
No really, I'm just hiding it.
I'm actually fighting
it off pretty well.
[door closes]
[ULLR] You should have just
shown him the magazines,
Star Child.
Not even a kaiju would
have been that cruel.
[crunching]
Can he just crouch
under the bridge?
Or jump?
He's been able to
get around everything
but a few obstructions.
Just the ones that
couldn't be moved.
It'll show the public
he's safe to be around.
Something needs to blow up!
That'd make for a great shot.
MegaGon is going to be
turned into a national idol.
But he does love fighting evil.
In case you know anyone.
Beastie here is more reliable
than those superhuman freaks.
Let's get some light
on the situation.
[MEGAGON growling]
[roars]
I guess he doesn't
like bright lights.
I'd shine that somewhere
else if I were you.
Uh, yeah.
[MEGAGON roaring]
[MEGAGON growls]
What's wrong, GaGon?
[gasps]
He's trapped in something!
[roaring]
[FUUROUTA yells]
Whoa, what was that?
That's the ghost, Fuurouta.
A friend to every kid.
I know you're sleeping.
But I need you to rise.
[whistles]
[BIRD MONSTERS cawing]
[BIRD MONSTER 5A]
Our princess! She summons us!
[BIRD MONSTERS cawing]
[MEGAGON growling]
There shouldn't be any
birds at this hour!
[STUDENT 5D]
Fight them!
[STUDENT 5E]
Take them out, MegaGon!
[STUDENT 5F]
Swat them down!
[MEGAGON growling]
[EMI]
Three more minutes.
It won't be enough.
[FUUROUTA]
That the train?
Yeah, it is.
And it should be leaving soon.
We just gotta buy
a little more time.
I wish Jiro was
here to help us.
What do we do?
[KIKKO]
Meteortail!
Wait, that's--magic?
Go, Miss Kikko! You got him!
[KIKKO grunts]
I can't.
An American fuel transport.
That must be headed
to a war zone.
All right,
I turned the light green.
Incoming.
We did it!
[CROWD chattering]
[MEGAGON growls]
This can't get worse.
Dammit. It didn't reach.
[AKITA] It's been a while since
I took on a non-human form.
[AKITA (TRAIN)]
Chugga chugga, chugga chugga!
--[STUDENT 5G] Look out!
--[STUDENT 5H] Run!
[STUDENT 5I]
It's gonna fall!
[HIROYUKI]
GaGon!
[MEGAGON growling]
GaGon.
[growling continues]
What are you doing?
Wow.
--[STUDENT 5J] So amazing!
--[STUDENT 5K] Beastly!
[STUDENT 5L]
Attack!
[STUDENT 5M]
Cool!
[STUDENT 5N]
Destroy!
Stop this!
MegaGon is on our side!
Why are you making him rampage?
[SHOJI]
I know now.
I truly do love kaiju .
I know you do!
But we wanted
everyone to love him!
There's no logic to them.
Kaiju can't be
understood by humans.
That's why I love them.
[MEGAGON growling]
[SHOJI]
MegaGon!
[MICHIKO gasps]
We're in trouble.
There's no way we'll
get through this
without a superhuman's help!
[gasps]
[MEGAGON growling]
So what are you,
nature's emissary?
Some ancient deity?
A victim of mankind?
Or just a manifestation
of our wishes and ambitions?
Kikko!
He needs me!
Meteortail!
Doesn't really matter
to me what you are.
Come on!
For every fire you started.
For every child you made cry.
[MEGAGON growling]
[growling continues]
[HIROYUKI]
MegaGon!
[crying]
[JIRO] I swear to fight.
And to keep fighting.
Every kaiju .
Till they're all dead!
We recovered the
remaining samples.
It's been too long
since my last experiment.
Let's just be extra
careful with these.
[KIKKO] A year and
a half after it began,
the kaiju craze came
to an abrupt end.
It was soon followed by
the so-called monster craze.
A different story.
For another time.
[DON] Prepare yourself,
my fellow viewers:
It's time for Mountain Horse!
Haru, Freeze, Dee,
and yours truly,
Don, their leader.
It's all fun-and-games
when we get together.
No one ever died from laughter,
so do it to your
heart's content!
Uh, I'm gonna excuse myself now.