[MALE REPORTER]
Here comes the plane now.
He's almost home.
His feelings seeing
Mount Fuji for the first time
in 28 years are
almost unimaginable.
But that's the story for
this man who didn't know
the war had ended,
so he kept fighting.
But now, he has
finally returned home.
[MEN yelling]
[explosion]
[FEMALE REPORTER] A bomb was
detonated in a Haneda Airport
restroom earlier,
leaving the area
in complete and utter turmoil.
The Metropolitan Police
Department has been called...
They also discovered
bombs on bullet trains
in a Tokyo station, too.
They're trying to
cover a wide area.
[static]
Damn thing's
always on the fritz.
As of this moment, there have
been no threats made public.
Likewise, the bomber's
motive and objectives
remain unknown.
[RAITO]
Excuse me?
You're saying that explosion
left zero evidence?
I said we recovered machinery.
A lot of it, actually.
Great. But you didn't
find the bomb?
No.
And everything we did
have was taken
by executive orders.
[RAITO growls]
[KIKKO]
Here it is.
All the evidence
from the explosion.
[AKITA] Just a bunch of
scraps from a security robot.
Yatsuka Heavy Industries.
This marks the fourth
attack against them now.
Why did the Superhuman
Bureau get it all?!
We have the right to
investigate criminal cases!
Or have you forgotten?
[RAITO] If the explosions
weren't random acts of violence,
the intended targets
must've been
departing passengers.
[WORKER 3A] I'm sorry,
but there isn't a company here
by that name.
[RAITO]
Impossible!
I got written testimony
from one of the blast victims
before he left the
hospital that he worked at
Yatsuka's Kamata Lab.
But he's been
missing ever since!
[growls]
[WORKER 3A]
Wait! You can't go in there!
[EMI] We thought it would
be best to move the lab
to the country as a precaution.
[AKITA]
Good thinking.
Yatsuka is the
cornerstone of Japan's
large machinery manufacturing.
It seems like the
employees are the target.
But why would someone
attack this company?
Because according to rumor,
Yatsuka also develops
robot weapons
for other countries.
[EMI] That's still legal
if it's pure research.
But what if they
actually have physically
built a robot weapon?
Whoever's behind this
could be trying to stop Yatsuka
from using it in a war.
When you put it like that,
this person sounds like a hero!
Sure, if you ignore
that the person's
a serial bomber
causing casualties.
[speaking Russian]
To try and write off what
happened as a simple bombing.
It was terrorism!
[RAITO gasps] You're saying
you saw someone carry out
the attack on the
Yatsuka scientists?
Be specific.
The Japanese person's suitcase
transformed all of a sudden,
then boom! Man.
I'd show you if I
still had that camera.
[RAITO gasps]
[HYOUMA]
Got this from the witness.
Gave him the latest
German model in trade;
he couldn't resist.
Casper, show 'em.
On it!
One! Two! Three!
And four.
This shadowy figure is
the one who attacked
the Yatsuka employees that
were headed for America.
He got the jump on them,
so they hastily activated
their security robot,
but kapow! One hit wonder!
Guy's dangerous if you ask me.
I'm sure he has a reason.
We should try talking to him.
You haven't forgotten the
purpose of our organization.
It's to "protect and manage
superhumans," not--
[FUUROUTA gasps]
Huh?
[RAITO]
Let's make this easy.
I'm here for the evidence
from the Yatsuka attacks.
I'm just surprised there
aren't radio fees anymore.
You got an invitation?
Detective Shiba, hi!
"Detective"?
Whatever it was, I didn't do it!
I should have known
you would have picked up
more stray weirdos since
the last time I saw you.
Fuurouta the ghost?
And why's a random young girl
wasting her time in
a place like this?
Why don't you take a
small break and join us?
I imagine your police
work is exhausting!
[AKITA] Especially with
the recent protests.
I would never lower
myself to join up
with such a filthy operation.
He thinks we're filthy.
[KIKKO gasps]
Not all of us!
[FUUROUTA] Hey, I keep
my tentacles to myself.
Back up a sec.
You said "attacks," plural.
Was Haneda not
an isolated incident?
The official report says it was,
despite that being a lie.
No doubt thanks
to your influence.
The attacker was superhuman,
so you covered it up.
Have you considered
Yatsuka might be evil?
Maybe Kikko's right,
the superhuman's a hero.
It's naïve of you
to think that way.
Well, wishful thinking, at best.
You're living in a fantasy!
Heroic supers don't exist.
All they do is make
trouble for the rest of us.
They're monsters that
have no place in our world.
We are going to
find the attacker.
[RAITO] I'll defeat it
before you have the chance.
It's well within my authority.
[AKITA] There was a time
when he was considered
a brilliant young detective.
Until he was killed by
an evil organization.
And then some genius scientist
thought it would be fun
to implant his memories
and personality
into a new artificial body.
[KIKKO] Whoa, you're
saying he's a robot?
[AKITA]
Yes, and for some reason,
he wanted to continue
being a detective,
serving as the only cop
dedicated to superhuman cases.
[RAITO]
Superhuman Bureau.
All those monsters do is
fulfill their selfish desires
with illegal destructive powers.
What justice is there in that?
[RAITO (SONG)] ♪ Now to say
goodbye, to the one I love. ♪
♪ I'll remember you. ♪
[MIEKO chuckles]
Sorry. I thought
I was alone out here.
I don't mind.
I like that song, too, actually.
[RAITO] I release excess
heat from my electric brain
by converting it to sound waves.
I wonder what she'd say
if I told her that.
[MIEKO] Are you with
Yatsuka Heavy Industry?
They just put in a
new factory nearby.
Uh, no.
It's not safe here. Run away.
Oh, wow.
What happened?
What did--?
We have to hurry!
[MIEKO]
He's here. I've found him!
[RAITO gasps]
This can't be. How?
Mr. Jaguar. Is it her?
Only one way to find out!
Hey! I'm not the bad guy!
You need to stop!
What in the world are you?
Should I stop time, or...?
Ugh, no, there are too
many variables!
--They're here!
--Get the load.
Let go of me!
I have to know!
Are you responsible for
what happened at Haneda?
Forgive me.
[RAITO grunts]
[KIKKO gasps]
[DRIVER 3A gasps]
[MIEKO] It's not him.
But I could have sworn it was.
I won't let this go to war!
[gasps]
Oh, no!
Please, stop!
--Go!
--Okay!
Meteortail!
[RAITO]
Wha--?
[RAITO grunting]
Go! Take the car! After them!
Jiro?
[JIRO]
Hey! Are you all right?
[HYOUMA] The guy's a robot!
He'll be fine!
He's also a superhuman.
This is our job.
[GUARD 3C]
You! Stay where you are!
Identify yourselves!
I--No. I'm not--
[SOLDIER 3A] I was only ever
concerned with getting him
back to Japan.
The record officially states
that only one person
was found in Guam,
which means you never existed.
Why come home
after all this time?
[OFFICER 3A gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
Who the hell is this guy?
[RAITO]
I've been waiting for you.
[HANTA]
That's surprising. Who are you?
Raito Shiba.
Formerly a Metro
Police detective.
Currently, a wanted man.
[MAGOTAKE] I saw that
eight-millimeter footage.
I'm amazed it survived.
It's definitely the
Type A that Ikuta Laboratory
made back during the war.
[AKITA]
Type A, huh? I see.
So it's the female from
that pair of androids.
There's a male, too?
[MAGOTAKE] I was under
the impression both androids
went missing amidst
the post-war chaos.
Can't believe
one's re-activated.
[MAGOTAKE] You know,
there was an airliner accident
at Matsu-shiro the other day.
It's possible this is related.
Regardless of its actions,
it's a valuable superhuman.
We will secure it.
[knocking]
[MAGOTAKE]
Comin' in.
I didn't put you in
the Superhuman Bureau
so you could pull
these kinds of stunts.
I know, Dad. I'm sorry.
[RAITO] Is it true she was
created during the war?
Don't lie to me now, Professor.
You heard?
Ah, I guess you can't
help but snoop
with those ears of yours.
According to rumor, Hitoyoshi,
you were in the Ikuta Laboratory
during that time, yourself.
[MAGOTAKE]
You've done your homework.
But that lab no longer exists.
I, of course, heard
whispers that secret weapons
were in development there.
[MAGOTAKE] But my own
involvement was limited
to research on
strategic superhuman uses.
But why bother making one robot
look like a man and
the other a lady?
Robots can be customized
to look like any nationality,
and programmed to
speak any language,
making them ideal soldiers
for infiltration missions.
They made a male and a female
so they'd look like a couple.
[RAITO] She kept mentioning
a "him" at the Yatsuka lab.
So, that must be it.
She's looking for
the male counterpart
she was separated
from twenty years ago.
Machines in love.
Please don't romanticize
the situation.
[JIRO]
Yeah, but--
They're just androids.
If she's really seeking
the Type B,
it's because it's in
her programming.
There's nothing more
extravagant happening here.
[MAGOTAKE]
You're a special case.
Your mind and personality
are replications
of the original Shiba.
And because of that,
your decisions are your own.
But in the instance
of Type A Mieko Kohrogi
and Type B Kaoru Hanta,
everything about them
is artificial.
Every thought they have
or moral they hold
was decided by a programmer.
That includes their
desire to merge,
which is the driving
force behind their search
for one another.
[JIRO]
Hold on.
What do you mean by "merge"?
"Combining" is their
most unique feature,
and by doing so, they would
become the ultimate weapon.
But I don't know what
that means specifically,
as I wasn't directly involved.
"Become a weapon?"
So first they both
infiltrate a city
by looking like normal humans.
And once they come together,
they detonate like a bomb.
[RAITO]
The ultimate weapon.
Doesn't sound worth it.
[RAITO grunts]
Your repairs aren't complete.
Take it easy.
I don't remember
saying you could tamper
with my body.
My research at Ikuta
laid the groundwork
for robotics engineering.
So don't worry, it's not
like I voided your warranty.
What he means
is that was the basis
for your body as well.
Which is why my
father could fix you.
[ASSISTANT 3A]
Roll camera!
[RAITO] So, this is
where she was "born."
[JIRO] It's my understanding
the Type B, the male,
was sent south at
the end of the war.
[RAITO] And because she
hasn't been able to find him,
she's taking her
anger out on any man
who reminds her of him.
[RAITO] If you protect her,
you'll prevent justice
from being served.
[JIRO] And you think destroying
her is the only way
justice can be served?
[EMI]
I've got this.
[SINGERS] ♪ As the
night turns to morning ♪
♪ And the sun brings
colors of the dawn ♪
Hey, you okay?
Or are you just
not into politics?
♪ He says goodbye
to his hometown ♪
♪ Rivers of his past
and all familiar ground ♪
♪ Left behind, Mmmm ♪
Strange. I didn't think
we'd meet again.
Actually, it's not.
You sought me
out unintentionally.
Oh.
I'm sorry, but you're
not the person
I've been looking for.
I know that. But that
man's not here anymore.
He's gone.
[MIEKO gasps]
[JIRO]
A robot that thought for itself
and decided to rebel
against its maker.
That's how I
imagined it, anyway.
Like a ninja, disappearing
to find justice.
Justice?
But that's not what
Miss Mieko is after.
She's just searching
for a loved one.
It's not love.
The only reason
they look for each other
is 'cause they're made to.
So? I think
people are the same way.
We seek out love,
no matter what the cost.
It's a simple fact of life!
And in a way, finding love
is its own kind of justice.
Shiba thinks justice
can only be served
by destroying her.
But why?
Isn't there a way we can
both be right about this?
[MIEKO]
You're wrong.
I am going to find him,
and I won't give up
my search until I do.
Things just need to stop
getting in my way first.
Everything that's happened
has been a byproduct
of the way you were designed.
You were built with
an artificial love.
And it draws you to robots
that were manufactured
with the same
Yatsuka technology.
[MIEKO]
Is that why I'm drawn to you?
[RAITO]
Mieko!
[HYOUMA]
All right, Jiro.
Time's frozen in a
hundred-meter radius.
But I can only hold it
for the equivalent
of thirty seconds.
You know what to do.
I'm on it.
Now Equus, rear your head!
[HYOUMA panting]
[KIKKO]
Oh, gosh!
Hope it was enough,
and that no one noticed.
[MIEKO]
What the--? How did--?
[JIRO] Sorry about this.
I followed the detective.
I knew if I stayed close to him,
you'd show up eventually.
[MIEKO]
But why?
[RAITO]
It's simple.
I have the same basic design
as the male Type B
that was built alongside you.
That's why I reacted so much
when we came in contact.
Same as you.
So that's it?
None of it's real?
[JIRO]
Enough chatter.
We'll finish this later.
I'm shutting her down
till we're somewhere safe.
I think not!
I'll finish this
by destroying her!
Shiba!
I refuse to let
your bureau take her!
[MIEKO yelps]
[RAITO grunts]
[JIRO, RAITO grunting]
[MIEKO]
I have to know! Please!
Why won't you let me find him?
Tell me!
It's your purpose.
Your prime directive is to
merge with the male Type B.
Together, you will form
a bomb and detonate.
That's not true.
[RAITO] If you choose
to stay with me, however,
you can avoid that.
[RAITO gasps]
[HANTA] This is where
the water plant was?
[RAITO]
Right.
Construction was
behind schedule,
so the land
hadn't dried up yet.
Pretty soon, though,
tons of those
will be built here.
It's hard to believe.
Half a decade ago,
I assumed Miss Mieko
had self-destructed.
In reality,
she had merely sunk
to the bottom of the reservoir.
And that's where she rested.
An acquaintance of mine
happened to work there.
He called me when
they found her.
It's starting
to feel like fate,
you coming home when you did.
[HANTA]
I could have done something.
But instead I just stayed
hidden in the south.
Because that was my given order.
[RAITO] And in that time,
the country has rotted away.
The justice I fought
to protect was lost
alongside many young lives.
That's why I brought you here.
So you can merge.
The love and sense
of justice you two felt
were manufactured.
But I'll teach you
the real meaning of justice
here and now, Hanta.
We'll open Japan's eyes.
They'll--!
Why are you here?
No!
You can't. Not yet.
Detonating it here
means nothing!
The Water Sports Grand Prix!
If we do it there,
the government
will have no choice
but to--[gasps]
Begin Cross-Megassing.
No! Don't let them!
That's not... a bomb.
[JIRO] My father never
said they would be,
only that they'd become
the "ultimate weapon."
And this is it.
The Android Megasshin.
No one else knows about
this superhuman yet.
If they infiltrate the venue,
they can still cause enough
damage to suit my goals!
[HANTA, MIEKO]
Detective Shiba.
I cannot fulfill your command.
Why not?
I'm the only reason
you two have been reunited
after all these years!
[HANTA, MIEKO]
And I'm grateful for that.
However, what you're
asking me to do is evil.
You're nothing but a machine!
[JIRO]
That's where you're wrong.
They're justice.
How can they possibly
know what that means?
Because it was programmed
into them from the start.
To protect the country.
To save the people.
To be truly righteous.
Humans interpret these things
based on their own values,
and thus make mistakes.
But machines perform flawlessly.
If they're "justice,"
are you saying I'm evil?
[JIRO]
I'm not.
That's how they judged you.
[JIRO]
Detective Shiba!
"Shiba" is dead.
I'm Iron Detective Raito!
This is pointless.
Neither of us
represent justice anymore.
[RAITO] No, but we're
gonna fight it out anyway!
[JIRO yelling]
[MAGOTAKE] An untouched
subterranean realm.
An uncharted southern island.
A mystical world ruled
by inhuman beings.
Behold: Explorer
of uninhabited areas
and pride of Japan's
brain trust.
His name: Magotake Hitoyoshi.