[BOSS 10A] The 100 yen
is still in circulation.
However, it's scheduled
for decommission.
Be careful.
[HYOUMA A]
How does a public phone work?
I know going to a
new era for the first time
can be incredibly stressful.
But don't worry.
I have complete
faith you can do this.
Super Jaguar.
Ma'am.
I'll destroy the
Advocates of Free History.
I won't fail you.
Whether or not you succeed,
your body will return
here automatically
after one week's time.
Of course,
from my point of view,
five seconds from now.
[POLICE 10A]
Release the hostages first!
We promise no
harm will come to you!
Whoa!
He's seriously going to kill us!
I can hear it in his voice!
And I can see it.... [gasps]
Around his waist.
He has a belt made of dynamite!
[EMI]
Of course they know.
One of them is a
mind-reading superhuman,
and the other one's clairvoyant.
I don't understand why
they use their powers
for scams.
Because they have power.
More and more superhumans
are joining organized crime.
[JIRO]
And it's our job to save them.
Despite their history.
[EMI] That's right.
They're still superhumans.
And hostages to boot.
[SOGA] Listen to me! These two
conned me out of my shop,
all my money!
Everything I own!
Superhumans saved
me during the war,
but these are just
common thieves.
They use their gifts
to mock normal humans!
I'm not a criminal. They are!
That old man.
He should remain unharmed.
You're not responsible
for his safety.
Isn't that--?
[FUUROUTA] Equus!
Lift your head and do stuff!
You can try all you want.
It only works for Jiro.
Ghost discrimination!
I'll protest!
[HYOUMA chuckles]
[HYOUMA] So, uh, what's he
over there brooding about?
[FUUROUTA] He's sympathizing
with the old guy.
[HYOUMA]
How childish.
You don't really like him,
do you, Mr. Jaguar?
Heh! I dislike all kids.
It's nothing personal.
But still...
You did build Equus
especially for him.
[EMI] Kind of childish,
don't you think?
[HYOUMA]
Not at all.
It looks like it can fight
the Grosse Augen-types,
but why did you
give it arms and legs?
The kid will be more
comfortable fighting this way.
He's both part of the Kikai
and is the Kikai itself.
Boys age, but never grow up.
Meaning?
You try and act mature.
But deep down you
still love your toys.
Thank you, Mr. Jaguar!
It's perfect!
[KIKKO]
Excuse me. Mr. Jaguar?
Hoshino?
Uh...
[explosion]
What's happening?
[AKIRA]
Mari. Nana. Move out.
[NANA]
Roger.
Are the police
trying to negotiate?
So pathetic.
Evil shall be eliminated.
Human or not.
There's no difference.
[AKIRA]
IQ! Go!
[EMI] I didn't know the
Japanese police had an airship.
[HYOUMA]
The IQ.
[FUUROUTA]
IQ?
They call themselves
the Infernal Queen.
And this is the group
that's been carrying out
assassinations all
over the world, right?
[HYOUMA] Politicians.
Guerrillas. Criminals.
To the IQ, anyone they perceive
as evil they eliminate.
There's no shade of gray.
[POLICE yell]
If you did your jobs, none of
this would have happened.
We have to do the dirty work,
'cause you let your
criminals run amok.
[MARI]
You took hostages.
The reason doesn't matter.
You're evil and have
to be destroyed.
So die!
[SOGA yells]
[ECHO, EYES grunt]
Who said you're allowed to move?
They're going to kill us too?
I didn't see that coming!
[JIRO gasps]
[FUUROUTA]
Oh, wow!
They vaporized the criminal
and the superhuman con artists.
We look kind of dumb
for dwelling on it, huh? [yelps]
[HYOUMA] Until now they've
mainly been causing trouble
in the Americas.
The legislature
won't be done in time
for the Self Defense Force
to deal with them.
[SATOMI]
Crew of the IQ, we receive you.
[GROUP]
Another successful mission.
Congratulations.
Yeah, whatever. So what gives?
I thought we were
doing Japan later.
[GROUP] There's a new
enemy standing between us
and global freedom of history.
They are called
the Superhuman Bureau.
Interesting.
You've heard of them, Akira?
[AKIRA]  Under the
Health and Welfare Ministry.
Our next target.
Morning.
Yoshimura.
Chief and Hoshino?
Well, that's out
of the ordinary.
About yesterday.
You mean in regards
to the Infernal Queen?
--I want to--
--Yoshimura Hyouma.
You're a member of the IQ,
and I'm here to question you.
The IQ?
Jiro?
There's nowhere to run.
[HYOUMA]
Heh.
Is that the best you've got?
[HYOUMA grunting]
[growls]
[AKITA] You're aware of the
Public Security Force, yes?
The Cabinet-run
anti-superhuman group?
Yeah!
They were useless against
the Tartaros Bugmen.
[SHAKKOU]
I am the commander, Shakkou.
Word has it, you hate
the Superhuman Bureau.
Sorry. We still won't
share our records with you.
That is why you're here?
[SHAKKOU]
Not today.
I'm working with superhuman
groups around the world.
We're investigating the IQ.
The IQ.
So can you tell us
who they really are?
[SHAKKOU] A band of
well-equipped murderers.
Anyone they deem as evil,
they execute without a trial.
Typically, they target
violent criminals
and anyone beyond
the reach of the law.
Like heads of state,
and military cliques.
Didn't they kill an
American congressman?
[SHAKKOU]
That's correct.
The IQ has a new
technology called
the Meteor Particle Contact.
They can use it to
communicate across the world
instantly and hide
their identity.
That's U.S. Navy
technology, isn't it?
Ah!
The congressman must
have been trying to stop it
from getting out.
[SHAKKOU] The IQ determined
concealing it was evil,
so he had to be destroyed.
Almost like Earth- chan .
[JIRO]
A military version.
[SHAKKOU]
After a lot of legwork,
we've tracked down a
few members of their group.
[EMI]
Wait a second.
This is Mr. Jaguar.
[FUUROUTA]
But that's impossible.
He was with us during
the attack yesterday.
This is stupid.
It's obviously a fake.
I won't hide it from you.
[GROUP gasps]
[HYOUMA]
I am the man in that photo.
There's no way!
What are you saying here?
You're working undercover?
Hyouma has control over
certain aspects of time.
Using that power--
[SHAKKOU] I was expecting
you to make that excuse.
But if he was part
of the assassinations,
the past can't be erased.
Unfortunately,
you're right about that.
[KIKKO]
Meteortail!
[FUUROUTA gasps]
[KIKKO gasps]
Hoshino? What do you
think you're doing?
Hey! You're the
one that ran off!
What do you think you're doing?
The past can't be forgotten.
Shakkou was right.
So you're part of the IQ?
[KIKKO]
Is he related to you?
Hey! This girl is a witch!
You must be me from the future!
Help untie me!
Where did you find him?
Yesterday. By the river.
[HYOUMA C] So, how'd you
know it wasn't me?
[KIKKO]
Because...
[ULLR]
I've never seen this before.
[KIKKO]
Oh! This is my friend Ullr.
--He's um, uh--
--[HYOUMA C] I know.
You talk to him sometimes.
I'm sure they taught you
this in the police academy,
but portable ashtrays
aren't used yet in this era.
But I get it.
Littering's uncomfortable.
I was the same way.
Or rather, I am the same way.
The police academy?
History Police.
They're also known
as the Time Patrol.
[KIKKO]
Huh?
Why are you pretending
to be Mr. Jaguar?
My name is Super Jaguar!
I'm a Historical
Revision Officer
from the 25th century!
Super?
[HYOUMA A] I'm looking for
a man from the future
who's trying to change history!
Hold on.
Is there already another me
running around in this era?
[HYOUMA C] During my tenure
at the History Police,
I felt I could
better the future.
By going back
and changing history.
As a result, I escaped the
Patrol, and formed the IQ.
You're the leader of the IQ?
Where I'm from, there
are no superhumans left.
The potential to become
superhuman was taken
from us entirely.
My choice was clear.
I had to repair history.
But as I made changes,
another copy of myself,
who was still in the
Time Patrol, found me.
I couldn't kill him, or else
I'd disappear as well.
The grandfather paradox.
I decided to travel
further back in time.
To change my methods entirely.
I'd protect and manage.
Not destroy.
[ULLR]
The Superhuman Bureau.
So, in other words,
you've lived through this
era three separate times:
As a Time Patrol officer,
as a member of the IQ--
And at this moment.
The past can never
truly be erased.
We layer paper on top
to draw a new picture.
But the picture underneath
remains the same.
Our mistakes
we live with forever.
[KIKKO] According to the
IQ version of yourself,
is the Superhuman Bureau evil?
We take freedom
from superhumans.
That's how they view it, anyway.
I created the IQ, who wants
to destroy the Bureau,
which I also made.
He can only stay
in this era for one week
before he disappears.
He should be gone
sometime tomorrow.
Just ignore him.
Listen, you... I mean, me!
We're trying to kill
the copy of us in the IQ!
[KIKKO]
Huh?
[ULLR]
The past version of himself.
The one that hasn't created
the Superhuman Bureau. Yet.
Wait. I'm confused
about what would happen
to this current Mr. Jaguar.
What if someone
goes back to prehistory
and kills all the monkeys
that would eventually
evolve into humans?
You'd think that would
cause the eradication
of all humankind, right?
But the future person
evolved from the monkey
as well.
Which created humanity
in the first place.
So, um...
The answer is no.
When forced with
an unsolvable paradox,
time just leaves it alone.
But me, I'm not important
enough to trigger that safety.
Does that mean you're
going to disappear?
Since I first created
the Superhuman Bureau,
I knew this day
would eventually arrive.
Take care of the future.
I hope it's better now.
[KIKKO]
Mr. Jaguar!
All this time I've
been with the Bureau,
I never realized you cared
so much about superhumans.
Which do you think
results in the more
obedient creature?
A human being imbued
with animal traits,
or vice versa: an animal
engineered to appear human?
I already told you,
there are no superhumans
where I'm from.
In other words, we're--
[KIKKO yelps]
What's wrong?
[ULLR]
What is it, Star Child?
[HYOUMA A]
Whoa! What are you--?
Only the Time Patrol
can use that!
[ULLR] Star Child?
What are you thinking?
[HYOUMA B]
Attention.
You are harboring
delinquent superhumans
and hiding their crimes.
During the war,
you performed...
[FUUROUTA]
Well. He's telling the truth.
[AKITA]
I wish it weren't so.
[FUUROUTA gasps]
Hey! Isn't that
Mr. Jaguar's voice?
I thought it was
just an undercover job.
[HYOUMA B] We are here to punish
you in the name of justice.
[NANA]
Who are those guys?
Dogs of the government.
Protecting the Superhuman
Bureau criminals.
[SHAKKOU] I agree that
the Bureau is a hotbed
for criminal superhumans.
But you'll be taken out first.
[FIGHTER 10A gasps]
[FIGHTER 10A grunts]
[JIRO]
Do you think it's actually him?
[EMI]
I hope not.
If it is, I can't tell
what he's thinking.
Lift up your head. Equus!
Where was that?
[EMI yells]
Jaguar! Is that
really you in there?
Jaguar?
Who are you, and how
do you know my old name?
[JIRO]
You are part of IQ.
I'm not surprised.
Evil is wrong.
Superhuman or not,
but this-- killing people?
Does that really work?
Does that make the
world a better place?
You're just a kid.
I can tell from your machine.
A true weapon doesn't
need limbs or a head.
It's a waste of fuel,
and messes with the balance.
All you need is to destroy
enemies from a distance.
Efficiency is the only
thing that matters.
As you can see,
this airship's far superior
to throwing a punch.
If that's your
idea of effective,
you still have growing up to do.
Foolish child.
Jaguar...
You were the one who
constructed the Equus for me.
That means--
[JIRO]
Emi!
[EMI whistles]
Even if it is
childish, it works!
[GROUP yells]
Mari! Nana!
I'll send a Meteor
Particle for reinforcements.
[HYOUMA B yells]
Is this--?
[HYOUMA B]
Time Patrol.
You're from the past?
I'm a version of you
from the future, actually.
So I knew all of
this would happen.
You're responsible?
I made Equus.
After I left the IQ.
That's why you
couldn't defeat it.
It's a better design. Stronger.
[HYOUMA B gasps]
Idiot. Don't you realize?
If I die here, then you'll--
Disappear? Yeah.
But I've made my peace
with that choice.
I was close.
So close to changing
history for the better,
till you showed up
and killed us.
Changing history
by eliminating anyone
who you view as evil?
It's an effective,
but cold and emotionless way
of handling things.
Execution before the crime.
Does that really make
the world any better?
Once you think about it,
it's embarrassing.
A childish idea.
So you wanted to erase me.
Your embarrassing past?
[HYOUMA C] I'm sorry.
That's the mature decision.
I'm alive?
But I killed my past self,
I shouldn't be here.
What is this?
Vanish!
[HYOUMA C panting]
[KIKKO] You're still here!
Do you have all your parts?
You didn't vanish!
I knew my idea would work.
Hoshino. You did this?
Remember the Time Patrol watch?
I showed it to Dr. Hitoyoshi.
He believed me when I told
him it was from the future.
Also, he said it
might take a while,
but he could reverse
engineer it and figure out
how time travel works.
[HYOUMA C] So, my own watch
begins time travel research.
But then that research,
results in the creation
of the Time Patrol watch itself.
Yep. A paradox.
Like what came first?
The chicken or the egg?
Mr. Jaguar, you are now
an unsolvable paradox.
I don't have a choice.
For the sake of time,
I have to keep existing.
Actually, I'm not sure
I even had to do all that.
You probably wouldn't
have disappeared anyway.
[HYOUMA C]
Huh?
It's like you said.
You can't erase history.
Things just get written
over on top of it. Right?
The past.
It can never really be undone.
I'm just talking to myself.
Super Jaguar. Welcome home.
[HYOUMA A]
I have a question.
Now that I'm back, does it
make me a superhuman?
[JACKY]
This is Jacky, singer for the
government-endorsed
band Angel Stars.
Having to hide the fact
that we're superhumans
isn't cool.
We carry the voice of
your entire generation
on our electric tunes.
If it moves you,
you're superhuman too.
Love and Peace!