[JIRO]
Is that it?
It can't be.
[HYOUMA]
I didn't want you to see this.
Gimme a break.
You can't outrun time.
[EARTH-CHAN]
Please stop.
I know deep down you don't
really wanna fight us.
Grown-ups do a lot of
things they don't wanna.
Sorry. That's life.
[EARTH-CHAN yelps]
[YUMIHIKO]
Well done, Rex FE.
So strong! I can't move!
Let go! Daitetsu!
[RAITO] What do you
think you're doing here?
[JIRO]
Don't worry about that.
Just stand back and
let us handle this.
[RAITO] I can't. They're
illegally occupying the campus.
[JIRO]
I know, we're here to negotiate
with the superhumans.
[DETECTIVE 8A]
The times sure have changed.
A few years back, things
were going the other way.
The protestors wanted harsher
control of superhumans.
Really? I didn't know that.
It was around the time
of the Daitetsu thing.
Five years?
You would have been
just a little girl back then.
Oh, yeah.
I wasn't even on Earth
at the ti--[yelps]
--[EMI laughs]
--[KIKKO] Owie.
Anyways, you were
saying Daitetsu?
[YUMIHIKO]
Testing: check, check!
Excuse me, do you realize
you're worrying your mother?
Talkin' to you,
student 1653004.
Or as most people would
call you, Masaki Iga.
Wait a sec.
Are those kids the BB,
or the DL,
or whatever the
heck they're called?
Juvi Investigators BL Club.
Yumihiko there's the leader.
They're superhumans, right?
Yes, but despite our attempts,
they've refused registration.
So protecting them
isn't our priority.
[DETECTIVE 8A]
There goes my day.
So, your headache now?
Nope, we just turn
a blind eye and pretend
they don't exist when
they're not around.
Which, is exactly what you do.
Yeah, but--
[YUMIHIKO]
Come on!
I can't believe you're doing
this to your poor mother.
I'm done. Lin. Saki.
Hey, Hideaki. Whatcha think?
That it can't be helped.
Shouldn't you do something?
[RAITO] No, we have an
understanding with them.
[JIRO] How about you let us
handle this, Otonashi?
Nah, that's all right.
You know how we kids are.
We don't get the
political mumbo-jumbo,
but we'll still
get mixed up in it!
Gigander!
Where the heck did
that even come from?
I'm not sure.
It always shows up
out of nowhere.
[STUDENT 8A]
Uh...!
Sorry, but mama's boy
is our only concern.
We'll leave the rest to you.
[YUMIHIKO] So what can the
Junior Investigators BL Club
do for you?
For the record,
we don't take normal cases.
But we're good for
finding missing people
or spying on spouses
you think are cheating.
I wouldn't blame this
guy's wife for cheating.
Look at him.
Well, I can't go to
the police with this.
You're my last hope.
It's probably from
before your time, but--
Have you ever heard
of the Eye of Lucifer?
[FUUROUTA] Is that what
it's called when your eyes
are all red? [yells]
The Eye of Lucifer!
Rainbow Knight's foe!
I hope you're
proud of yourself.
You should know this is
a touchy subject for Jiro.
[HYOUMA] What do ya expect
when you idolize someone
who turns out to be a criminal?
Rainbow Knight was--
What's the deal with
the Eye of Lucifer?
He's back?
Apparently, and with
a vengeance, too.
A threat claiming
to have been written
by his organization, the Gaze,
was sent to a collector
specializing in items
relating to the Rainbow Knight.
[JIRO]
The Eye of Lucifer.
He was an evil superhuman
who nearly destroyed Japan.
His origin is a mystery,
and his true identity
has never been discovered.
[AKITA]
Hold on. Where are you off to?
[JIRO]
To try and stop him.
[AKITA]
We decided not to get involved.
After all, this is
probably only a hoax.
But chief!
Calm down. They asked the
BL Club kids for protection,
so they're covered.
[EMI]
Have you reached a conclusion?
No. I keep trying,
but it's weird.
I just can't figure out
how something that size
can move the way it does
without some sort of engine
or other energy source.
[EMI]
Would it be possible with magic?
Well, I asked around,
but there aren't
any mages like that.
What do you mean? Asked who?
Oh!
Jiro's Equus is a big robot.
Couldn't it function like that?
[KIKKO] Considering that one
was built by Mr. Jaguar,
it's not likely.
But the real mystery
is this Yumihiko kid.
Seems suspicious I can't
find anything on his past.
That's tough.
Did Jiro put you onto this?
Not really.
He seems overwhelmed,
and I thought I could help.
He gets like that.
The Rainbow Knight was
a big influence on him.
[KIKKO] Why's he so attached to
one of the older superhumans?
I'm gonna do another sweep.
[RAITO]
Birdwatching?
Or are you hoping to get the
Rainbow Knight's autograph?
I'm no worse than a cop
who has to sneak around.
Yeah, so I got kicked out.
That collector's a nut.
He doesn't trust the
police because of some
conspiracy theory.
About the government
killing Rainbow Knight.
[KIKKO gasps]
Killing him?
[FUUROUTA]
Heh...
What are you two doing here?
We thought you might
do something stupid
if we didn't keep an eye on you.
Anyway...
I did some digging
on Rainbow Knight,
but couldn't find anything
on his secret identity.
But what I did find is
he was a big influence
in post-war.
And as a result,
a lot of kids became his fans.
But the truth came out
about him five years ago,
when he died.
He brought it on himself
when he made that ransom.
It's not like
anyone's gonna forget
when you kidnap somebody.
In the end, he was
just another criminal.
Prior to that,
the secrecy law
had almost been forgotten,
and superhumans maintained
relatively public presences.
But that event prompted
the government
to start cracking down.
Which is why the conspiracy
must have emerged.
I was right there when he died.
Maybe he was a criminal.
But he still defended justice.
I know this is tough for you.
Especially because he
saved you from that beast
a long time ago.
But after everything
that happened,
you can't honestly--
Thought we heard trouble,
but it's just you old guys.
[KIKKO]
I'm not old or a guy!
Whatcha think? They could be
working for the Eye of Lucifer.
[RAITO]
Would you stop screwin' around?
[COLLECTOR 8A yells]
--[yelling continues]
--[JIRO] What's wrong?
[COLLECTOR 8A] My precious
Crescent Gun has been stolen!
[EYE OF LUCIFER laughs]
[RAITO]
It's really him!
What are you looking for?
I kind of thought
if he was here,
maybe the Rainbow Knight
would show up as well.
[FUUROUTA] Sounds like
Jiro's not the only fan-boy
with some personal
interest in this case.
Back off!
I grew out of that phase!
[LIN] Where do you think
you're going, old man?
[JIRO]
Eye of Lucifer!
Why have you come back now?
Did you think you were
gonna catch the bad guy
like Rainbow Knight?
Gimme a break.
Doesn't look like
you did any better.
But at least we're not trying
to emulate a criminal.
Get with the times.
C'mon, let's get
out of here, Kikko.
I could go for some ramen.
[door opens]
[JIRO]
Please, Miss Emi!
With your power,
it should be really easy!
You can find the
kidnapped children!
Even with the monsters,
there's no guarantee.
[JIRO]
I don't care.
We have to prove
Rainbow Knight is innocent!
Fine, as long as you uphold
your end of the bargain.
Where are they? Show me.
No, don't!
[OFFICER 8A]
We found Daitetsu!
[MAID screams]
What happened?
[EMI] She was on her way to
the kitchen when she found this.
Wait a minute. The what?
[RAITO]
So, what brings you here today?
I thought that your
group handled things
more discretely.
[DOOR KNOB laughs]
That's cute.
Yeah.
Well, I have some questions
that need answering.
Ask away, then.
Thanks, I will.
I wanna know about the
boy that was kidnapped
five years ago, Daitetsu Maki.
I should've known it had
something to do with that.
When the police surrounded
the Rainbow Knight,
he suddenly lost
control of his powers
and exploded on the spot.
After that, there's
no record of what happened
to the boy he abducted.
It's my understanding
that the authorities
gave the kid a new identity
in order to protect him
from being mobbed by the media.
But you don't know for sure.
What's your point?
[KIKKO] There's a rumor that
Daitetsu never existed,
and the whole thing
was set up by the cops
in order to make the Rainbow
Knight look like a criminal.
Why in the world would they
do something like that?
I don't know. They could?
It's just, when I think
about the people
who still believe
he's innocent--
I want to give
them peace of mind.
You mean "him." Fine.
Here's the truth on Daitetsu.
[crunching]
[MOLLY]
This stuff's great.
Refill!
I don't remember inviting you,
so why are you here?
Because the Eye of Lucifer
sent you a challenge,
--isn't that right?
--[HIDEAKI] Yeah, well.
We thought you could use
our help protecting the mask.
I can defend my house on my own!
Let me show you to the door.
Sorry, but no.
We're staying right here.
After all, we were
hired to stop that creep.
I understand.
But still.
The Rainbow Knight's
mask is more than safe.
We have it locked up
underground in the vault.
There isn't anyone who'd
be able to get to it.
Can't believe you've
had it in your possession
this whole time.
Well, the Rainbow
Knight's powers
were one of the
targets of my study.
[JIRO] But how did the Eye
of Lucifer know it was here?
Not even I knew.
It must have been
in the police records.
Someone let it slip.
[JIRO] Detective Shiba
told you this?
Yeah. There's no denying
Daitetsu existed.
But now I'm more confused
than I was before.
I hate to say it,
but I think we need to accept
that the Rainbow Knight
really was just a kidnapper.
It's all starting to make sense.
Remember what
Detective Shiba said?
[RAITO] I kind of thought,
if he was here,
maybe the Rainbow Knight
would show up as well.
Hey, ghost. You seen Jiro?
[FUUROUTA laughs]
Oh, uh...
[KIKKO]
What's all this?
Are you in here?
[crash]
What's going on?
I bet it was the Eye of Lucifer!
He probably tried to steal
Equus to break into the vault.
[EMI]
That's impossible.
Jiro's the only person
who can activate Equus.
[AKITA]
No point in leaving it out.
Shut it down.
[JIRO]
Right.
Chill out.
It's not even the time
of the challenge yet.
[EYE OF LUCIFER laughs]
[MOLLY]
Looks like he's early!
[LIN] Guess he wouldn't
be a supervillain
if he stuck to a schedule.
The mask he's holding is a fake.
He wants us to panic
and rush down
to open the vault so he
can steal the real thing
once we do.
Oldest trick in the book.
No obvious signs
of forced entry.
What're your thoughts?
Emi and I are the only
ones who know the code.
Then it must be one of you two
who's responsible for this.
He managed to get away
with that balloon stunt again.
--Damn it!
--[LIN] Don't blame yourself.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
I know.
To think he's come back...
[MOLLY] So much for
"no one getting it."
[HIDEAKI]
With screw-ups like that,
I'm glad we never
registered with the bureau.
Yeah, and living in
hiding would totally suck.
[JIRO]
Good work out there.
[YUMIHIKO gasps]
[MOLLY]
Isn't that--?
[SAKI]
It can't be.
Rainbow Knight.
[JIRO]
Now tell me,
where are you keeping
my spare mask?
Excuse me, what?
I think you're confused.
The Eye of Lucifer has it.
You'll have to go after him.
This can't be happening.
[HIDEAKI] I didn't think
he'd ever come back.
Let's see if it's really him!
[LIN, MOLLY, HIDEAKI]
Yeah!
[ALL scream]
You okay?
Just call Gigander!
But he--
It's him! He's the real deal!
Gigander!
Seven!
[JIRO]
It's just as I thought.
You make metals
bend to your will.
And now that I know
your superhuman power,
Yumihiko Otonashi.
I've confirmed that you have
been disguising yourself
as the Eye of Lucifer.
As if!
[JIRO]
Well then,
why didn't you summon Gigander
during either of
his recent attacks?
It's because doing so would
have blown your cover.
You couldn't afford
to reveal yourself yet.
But with that power of yours,
you could open the vault,
as well as make it appear
as if someone tried
to activate Equus.
Oh, wow.
There's no fooling you.
You're right,
I do have your mask.
And his, too.
[CLIENT 8A] The super-criminal
known as "The Eye of Lucifer"
was me.
I retired a long time ago,
but it seems like
my family has become
suspicious of my
former identity.
Oh, I see.
That's easy enough to fix.
I'll don your mask.
But at the time,
you'll be out with your family
enjoying the day.
Bam. Flawless alibi.
After that,
no one'll have reason
to suspect you again.
[JIRO] You acted as
if you were interested
in helping him, but in reality,
you just wanted to draw me out.
So you were alive.
Now that you're here,
there's something
I have to ask you!
[BOTH gasp]
[ROCK MONSTER 8A growls]
Damn. Let's go!
[JIRO]
Kikko?
It's not me!
Magic has nothing
to do with this!
Pretty sure it's
after the BL Club.
After all, we've made
some enemies of our own!
Hey! What gives?
[YUMIHIKO grunts]
Ow.
I made this suit ages ago.
You gotta be kidding!
You can't be the Rainbow Knight!
You're right. I'm not.
He's been dead for
the last five years.
Daitetsu Maki.
[YUMIHIKO gasps]
Why are you doing this?
We've done nothing to you!
[KIDS muffled yelling]
[RAINBOW KNIGHT]
I'm so sorry.
This is because you all
have superhuman powers.
You have the ability
to manipulate metals,
isn't that right?
Do you plan on defending
justice when you grow up?
[YUMIHIKO] Yeah, that's why
I go to the labs so much!
[RAINBOW KNIGHT]
Well, as an ally of justice,
I believe it's my
responsibility to protect you.
[YUMIHIKO] Not long after,
I was rescued by the police.
And they're the
ones who told me.
That the Rainbow Knight
had demanded a ransom
for our safety.
[ROCK MONSTER 8A growls]
Ah! Help them!
I would. But all I can
do is... Crescent Gun!
[laughing]
Just great.
Meteortail!
I'm not registered,
so you shouldn't protect me.
Let me fight!
First, tell me.
Were you looking for
the Rainbow Knight
because you wanted revenge?
I dunno.
I wanna make things
clear for myself.
Back when I met him,
he seemed so warm and gentle.
Like an uncle or someone
I'd known my whole life.
[YUMIHIKO]
I have to know for sure
that the Rainbow Knight
was evil!
And if so, I'll defeat him!
I'll be better than he ever was!
Because I won't betray anyone!
There should never
be any question
to what's wrong or right!
[JIRO]
You're strong.
[YUMIHIKO]
What?
[JIRO] You have a clear
distinction of what you believe
is good or bad.
But me?
I've never been certain.
That's why I can only
call myself an ally of justice.
That's kinda pathetic.
Like you can't commit.
olitical, too?
You non
[JIRO]
Have you heard of GigantoGon?
[GIGANTOGON roaring]
[JIRO]
Nearly a decade ago,
the beast was
rampaging in Tokyo.
They later discovered it
was created from stolen cells
in a secret lab,
so it wasn't something
that developed naturally.
[GIGANTOGON roars]
[JIRO] The Rainbow Knight was
the one who fought against it.
It's you,
the superhuman of justice.
[RAINBOW KNIGHT]
You're wrong.
The best I can hope to be
is an ally of justice.
[JIRO] I can't bring
myself to judge him.
Who am I to say if
he's good or evil?
You see?
Not everyone can
view the world in terms
of black and white.
There's a lot of gray.
But if a person
stands for justice,
then I will stand beside them.
Meteortail!
C'mon, guys!
Gigander!
[YUMIHIKO]
Time for a team-up!
[JIRO]
Kikko!
Uh, right.
You ready, Mr. Jaguar?
Launching now!
[SAKI] So what exactly
was that monster?
[LIN] You think it was the
ghost of the Rainbow Knight?
Not black or white, but
somewhere in between. Right.
[EMI]
Hey.
If you return what you stole,
we'll keep your secret.
Yeah.
Wait! Where'd they go?
Sorry for all the trouble.
You owe me one.
But you can make
it up to me easily.
Stop opposing the
Defense Force of Earth issue.
[AKITA sighs]
I guess I have no choice.
You've become
quite the man, Daitetsu.
Meanwhile, you've
become nothing but garbage.
If you're the great
"ally of justice,"
am I evil?
No.
Because good and
bad don't change
whenever it suits
your selfish desires.
[YUMIHIKO]
Here I come!
[SANAE] Hi, my name
is Sanae Hatakeyama.
We're what you'd call a very
ordinary Japanese family.
It just so happens
that we've been alive
for a little longer than others.
Actually, the
famous Masaki Tsuji
even wrote a story
about us once!
Please don't miss us
on the next episode!