[SOLDIER 9A]
Fire!
Cease fire!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
He's still alive!
[gunfire]
[TEACHER 9A] In regards
to the origin of life,
the most popular theory is that
it started simply by chance.
Over several thousand years,
elements in the ocean
formed a protein.
And a gradual chemical
evolution took place.
This resulted in creating
the Primordial soup.
Without this
miraculous occurrence,
the Earth would be
completely devoid of life.
Even after 4.5 billion years.
[TEACHER 9A]
Morino.
[SHIGERU gasps]
Oh, so you think you're
smarter than your teacher?
No, sir. I'm the stupid one.
[FUUROUTA]
Excuse me?
How many years ago
do you think life began?
Well...
That's still being
researched, but--
What's your name?
My name?
That's um,
still being researched.
--Whoa! What the--?
--He disappeared!
He's a ghost!
[FUUROUTA]
Correct answer!
[STUDENT 9A screams]
A cockroach!
[FUUROUTA]
Hey! Wait a minute! Stop it!
--I oppose violence!
--Die!
[SHIGERU]
Thanks for waiting, Wakaba.
[FUUROUTA]
Wakaba?
She's my type.
[WAKABA] Huh? Did you get
in trouble at school again?
Whenever you screw up,
you make the same expression.
Yeah, well...
I couldn't stand
listening to that dunce.
Life started as soon
as the Earth was formed.
It wasn't just
some random event.
Well, it's like
Father always said.
There's no point arguing
with ignorant people.
Hold still for just a second.
Why?
You've got a stowaway on you.
[FUUROUTA yelps]
A little early in
the season to see these.
Help me! Miss Kikko!
You're there, aren't you?
Officially, I'm not really here.
Traitor!
[SHIGERU, WAKABA]
We're home!
Huh? Learn a lot?
[SHIGERU]
Hey, Mr. Hitoyoshi.
How are you doing, kids?
[WAKABA]
Losing at Shogi again?
Young lady!
Watch your mouth, or you'll
never find yourself a husband.
Yeah, okay.
Boys are swarming me in droves.
I envy you two.
Wakaba's going to be
the cutest kid in town.
No. The entire city.
You're gonna have your
hands full in a few years.
[SHIGERU]
We're home.
[SANAE]
How was school?
We didn't learn anything.
Hey, Megumi.
Look.
Her hands are so soft.
I could stay here forever.
Sister, have you heard
anything from him yet?
[SANAE]
Mm-mm.
I'm sure they're
still keeping brother
locked away somewhere.
I hope he's safe.
[FUUROUTA]
Too tight!
You're right.
He would have called us.
There's no way he would
have missed our signal
from two years ago.
[REPORTER 2A]
Today at 4 PM,
there was an explosion at
an ether factory in Kawasaki.
A piece of the vat in
operation pierced the roof,
hitting a nearby house,
and burning it
completely to the ground.
What a way to
lose a neighborhood.
It happened right
after the kids
came home from school.
It's unlikely anyone survived.
This could be an experiment
by a criminal organization.
We can't rule that out.
I sent Jiro to investigate.
[JIRO]
Jiro Hitoyoshi. Evening.
I'm from the ministry
of Health and Welfare.
You're here about the survivors.
The survivors?
How many are there?
All six family
members from the house
closest to the factory.
They're being checked out now.
[JIRO]
They can walk without help?
[MEGUMI laughing]
[JIRO]
Laughter?
[MEDIC 9A gasps]
[DRIVER 9A grunts]
[DRIVER 9A]
Hey! Where are you going?
[MEDIC 9A]
Come back!
[KIKKO] Then who was
driving the ambulance?
There wasn't anyone in the
vehicle besides the family.
Ah. I see.
So, you suspect the
survivors were all superhuman.
[HYOUMA] Oh.
Time for the morning news.
[REPORTER 2A] The ambulance
that ran off with the survivors
of the ether factory fire
yesterday has been located.
Submerged in Tanzawa Canyon.
There were no
signs of passengers.
Still missing are
the six family members.
All miraculously lived
through the explosion,
but their whereabouts
remain unknown.
Your suspicion's confirmed.
Burnt to a crisp in a fire.
And they're still healthy?
They have to be superhuman.
It doesn't make sense.
Wait.
You don't agree with
the rest of them, Jiro?
Not that.
If they're really superhuman,
why would they bring
so much attention
to themselves?
Don't you think
it's strange, chief?
I concur.
It does seem peculiar.
Putting on a show
like that would attract
national attention
and let people know they
were superhuman.
They should have known it
would have that effect.
They knew, but they
still wanted to advertise.
For what reason?
Either way it's
pretty horrifying.
An entire family of six,
including a child.
That number's wrong.
Hyouma? You've met
these people before?
It's just, um...
I don't want to
jump to conclusions,
but the folks I knew
always traveled together
in a group of seven.
[HYOUMA]
For quite a while now,
I've ventured through
the flow of time
and witnessed the same
family on many occasions.
But, I can't mention
that info to the Bureau.
[AKITA] So then,
one of them is missing.
If we assume it really
is the same family
that Mr. Jaguar knows.
It's been a few years.
So I can't say for sure.
[KIKKO] Of course
one of them is missing!
I mean, just think about it.
What happened
to the baby's father?
Well done.
So you know that making
children requires both
a mother and a father.
[ULLR] I don't remember
teaching you that.
So they sent out a message to
the one remaining superhuman?
Maybe they were
separated by some disaster,
or the war.
I remember hearing a rumor
that came from the U.S.
some time ago.
Now, where did I put it?
[HYOUMA]
The Americans.
They have their own
Superhuman Bureau, right?
We were supposed to
have a tight information
trading agreement,
but they always keep
the important details
to themselves.
Here it is.
They wanted to know
if there were any
immortal superhumans in Japan.
Immortal?
[HYOUMA]
That all happened two years ago.
I remember.
[KIKKO] That family is
still considered missing.
[FUUROUTA]
Huh?
Wait a sec,
I don't remember any of this.
Autumn, two years ago.
That was when
you were undercover
in the novelty band, wasn't it?
Sure took their time.
I mean, waiting so
long to give a reply?
The Americans seem
very easygoing.
Well, the issue with Chief
Akita held up the paperwork.
But Master Ultima
has finally admitted.
The U.S. is holding an
immortal Japanese captive.
Held captive? For how long?
[MAGOTAKE]
It'll be 28 years in December.
[HYOUMA whistles]
He's been a prisoner
since the war?
The very first Japanese
POW the Americans took.
How awful.
A human test subject.
They stopped after an
experiment using army ants.
What are army ants?
A species that's known
for their ferocity.
A row of ants traveling
at 1 kilometer per hour
can extend 20 meters.
They wanted to
control the insects
using a special pheromone.
A sort of antipersonnel weapon.
He was the test subject.
Still, they couldn't
figure out the secret
of immortality.
I guess they can't decide
what to do with him anymore.
Well, after we gave
them the information
about the family,
they confessed that
they were holding him.
Now they're more than
eager to cooperate with us.
I told them that the
family is still missing.
But in reality,
we've known their location
for quite some time and
have been spying on them.
Since they travel together,
it wasn't difficult.
Easy, really.
Just because they can't die,
Japan and the US won't
stop going after them.
Their entire life spent running.
Poor kids.
[MAGOTAKE] Course,
who knows how many hundreds
of years old those
children really are...
[HYOUMA] So, the Americans
want to do shared research
with us now?
I have their word
they're setting him loose
with that intention.
Megumi's going to
see her dad, that's great!
[MAGOTAKE]
The moment they meet,
we register them
with the Bureau,
then, we get them
to help us with research.
I still feel sorry for them.
Something about
this isn't right.
What are you thinking?
Why would they just let go
of an immortal superhuman?
Let alone one who
they've kept locked away
for thirty years?
All right.
Begin surveillance
on the family.
Don't let them know who you are.
[GROUP]
Yes, sir.
--[MAGOTAKE] And, check.
--[KOUSAKU] What? Not again!
Look at that, Megumi.
Grandpa's a
professional at losing.
I'm not a weak player.
Mr. Magotake's just too strong.
Hey, would you mind
if I hold Megumi?
Of course not.
Hi, there!
Oh, my. Who's a cutie pie?
[KIKKO]
Here's Fuurouta, finally.
Wow. He's a mess.
That "I'm the only
one for the job"
talk totally tricked me!
Anyway, nothing to report.
[KOUSAKU]
What?
[BUNA]
Sanae! Come quick!
Darling? Is that really you?
Let me hear your voice.
[MINORU]
It's Minoru. I'm finally home.
[SANAE]
Oh, Minoru.
How are you?
Of course. Yes. Yes.
I know.
He'd probably tell us
to leave them alone.
The census was next year.
You almost missed us.
We were so close to leaving.
Who knows when you
would have found us again?
You can talk more
when he comes home.
We need to hurry.
Where are you now, Minoru?
[FUUROUTA gasps]
Tight squeeze!
Sentimental moments
aren't really my scene.
Let me borrow this.
Hello?
[EMI] So we should apprehend
them after they're reunited?
[MAGOTAKE]
Yes.
Have the Americans contacted us?
[EMI]
They haven't heard from them.
Are they just letting
us handle everything?
[MAGOTAKE] I'd be surprised.
So keep an eye on the bases.
[EMI]
Understood.
Are you here to get
in our way again?
Tell me what the
Bureau is planning to do
with the family.
Don't tell me you've already
forgotten your old job.
We capture and register.
It used to be
about defending them.
Now you just exploit!
And if I say yes, what are
you gonna do about it?
Whatever I have to
do to protect them!
[POST OFFICE GIRL]
Excuse me...
My boss wanted me
to tell you that
we're not a cafe.
What time do you close today?
We're open for about
thirty more minutes.
I'll stay then.
But um, you aren't even--
You're right.
I'll buy ten postcards.
I'll take twenty,
and spend the next half hour
filling 'em out right here.
[POST OFFICE BOSS growls]
[EMI]
No American arrivals.
And no superhumans.
Yokota or Tachikawa
seem pretty quiet.
[MAGOTAKE] I thought they
might be letting Minoru free
so they could follow him back,
and find the rest of his family.
They could be using
a large weapon, or a robot.
[EMI] No large-sized cargo
was sighted either.
[MAGOTAKE] I see.
Well, keep your guard up.
[EMI]
Got it.
[HYOUMA]
Admit it.
You want to come
back to the Bureau.
[JIRO]
No. I'm through.
[HYOUMA] Without the
government on your side,
what good can you do?
Superhumans need us.
You can't save them
all by yourself.
[POST OFFICE GIRL 9A]
I'm sorry...
But the post office
is closed now.
He's back!
Megumi's father is home!
Jiro? You're here?
I'm going in.
[KIKKO]
Jiro?
You going to rejoin the Bureau?
[HYOUMA]
Hitoyoshi!
Don't get in our way.
[FUUROUTA]
We got trouble!
Something's coming!
What are you doing here?
[HYOUMA]
What are you talking about?
I don't know! I think
it followed Megumi's dad!
[HYOUMA]
What did?
Um, sir, we're closing for the--
[HYOUMA]
Jiro!
[POST OFFICE BOSS]
I said it's time!
Stop your clock then!
Thank you for your business.
Hey. Jiro or the mission.
Which is more important?
How should I know?!
Hurry! Get out of--
The Superhuman Bureau.
Are you that
completely heartless?
They've been
separated thirty years.
Minoru volunteered for war.
It was the only way
we could be exempt
from census investigations.
The couple, the family
that was separated.
And all because
of some government.
Don't you people have
any compassion?
That has nothing to do with it.
The point is
you're superhumans.
You need to be managed
by the government.
You mean so you can
use them as weapons
in another war?
[KOUSAKU] What good would
we be in one of your wars?
[BUNA gasps]
What is it? An earthquake?
[CROWD screams]
It's a robot!
[HYOUMA]
The Americans?
How did they bring that here?
They had no intention of
collaborating on research!
They must be trying to
abduct the entire family!
I'm going to launch
a formal complaint.
[EMI]
Jiro! Is he really there?
Let's deal with
the Americans first!
They're the major problem!
[EMI]
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
[phone clicks, beeps]
[KIKKO]
Meteortail!
[KIKKO screams]
[ULLR]
Zero points.
Now it's my turn!
[FUUROUTA grunts]
[FUUROUTA yells]
Lucky shot.
You might be a ghost,
but you're no match
for that machine.
Stop hurting yourself.
Don't worry about me.
I'll handle this!
[KIKKO groans]
Thank you for helping.
But it's okay.
[JIRO growls]
If I only had Equus!
[KOUSAKU]
You should run.
That's impossible!
We're here to protect you!
We're not going anywhere.
Hyouma.
You need to take these
people somewhere safe!
But of course.
Kikko! Buy me some time!
Distract him!
He just said my name!
Fuurouta, go!
[KIKKO yells]
Aim for the eyes!
We'll blind him!
All right! Classic move!
Wakaba! Watch me!
This one's for you!
[FUUROUTA, KIKKO yell]
[BIG MONSTER 9A growls]
Emi's here?
[EMI]
Spirit. Will you help?
[BIG MONSTER 9A]
My pleasure.
At your service, princess!
[BIG MONSTER 9A growling]
What happened?
How could it defeat him?
[MINORU] It's a weapon
developed by America.
Capable of separating
every molecule
in a living being.
A Bio Destroyer.
Even monsters are
living spiritual entities.
They are no exception.
But why would
they even use that?
What do they want?
Their government never
intended to take us away.
They want us together.
[EMI] It can't have
that much fluid stored.
They'll run out soon.
Unfortunately, the
Bio Destroyer is limitless.
As long as there's
a water source nearby.
That robot?
It's self-sustaining.
A moving chemical plant.
[MINORU]
It fights and produces acid.
Simultaneously. Without end.
It has to have a weakness.
Just one.
Only we can defeat it.
[KOUSAKU] The machine is set to
self-destruct once its mission
is completed.
The U.S would never
let it run free otherwise.
[FUUROUTA]
Its mission?
[WAKABA] Isn't it obvious?
To kill our entire family.
[SHIGERU]
If you can't solve the puzzle,
the only option
is to destroy it.
[SANAE]
They think we're divisible.
That immortality won't
work if they destroy us
at a molecular level.
Thank you for everything.
But this is goodbye.
Wait! Wakaba!
Don't blush, Fuurouta.
It wouldn't have worked
between us anyway.
I'm way too old for you.
Well, we're all here.
You can complete
your mission to kill us.
Something about molecules.
I don't pretend to understand
the science behind it.
But to come all the way
to Japan to destroy us?
We aren't worth the trouble.
[JIRO grunts]
What good are we?
We were supposed
to protect them.
[EMI] The news would will
probably just say it was
a tanker that lost control.
Jiro. I'm not mad at you.
You can come back.
[KIKKO]
Jiro! Look!
[JIRO gasps]
Incredible. I can't
believe what I'm seeing.
Are they really superhumans,
or something else?
They are beyond
our comprehension.
No classification.
[JIRO] You still think the
Bureau is needed in this world?
Protecting?
Managing superhumans?
How arrogant can you be?
[MAGOTAKE]
That's enough!
You think a nation
can't control them?
They're beyond the
reach of humankind?
That they've even
surpassed superhumans?
[JIRO] They're incapable
of harming anyone.
And no one is capable
of ever harming them.
They've surpassed us all.
They will live on.
From the beginning of
this planet to its end.
[HYOUMA]
I come from the future.
My name is justice.
A chaser of Free
History Criminals.
And anyone who abuses
the Time Watch.
I will revise history.
Change it back
to its correct form.
Yes! It's me.
The Time Patrol!