[music playing]
I didn't know you were into
the Shonen comics, Kikko.
No, I was just killing time.
[WAITER 1A]
Here's that espresso con panna.
[KIKKO]
Okay. Thanks.
Your espresso con panna, sir.
I hope you enjoy it.
[KIKKO gasps]
[JIRO]
Sorry. One more thing.
[KIKKO]
Um... Yes?
Your name's Kikko Hoshino?
Um, yes.
My name's Jiro Hitoyoshi.
And I need your help.
Jiro! Jiro, wait!
[FUUROUTA growls]
[JIRO] Fuurouta.
Don't bother playing tough.
Watch your mouth, Hitoyoshi.
[TRAIN CONDUCTOR grunts]
[KIKKO grunts]
Kikko!
[KIKKO gasps]
Listen to me! Jiro!
I am twenty years old now!
--[KIKKO] Let go!
--[FUUROUTA] No! Kikko! Don't!
[COMMUTER 1A]
Oh, great. Superhumans.
Why don't you fight
somewhere else?!
[COMMUTER 1C]
Keep us out of it!
I swear I won't lose him again.
[EMI] In addition to
the Summer Triangle,
one of the other most
famous summer star groups
is the Zodiac
constellation Scorpio,
which is now coming into view.
Recently, a new
x-ray-emitting body
has been discovered nearby.
Scientists have
named it "Star-X".
While scholars around
the world continue
to pursue its location,
Japan's Professor Onda
claims to have already
succeeded in determining
the star's precise coordinates.
[HYOUMA] And a certain
group has taken an interest
in his research these
last few days.
[MAN IN SUIT] Professor Onda.
How are you?
Shh! Not so loud, please.
Do you have what
you promised me?
[JIRO] Do you know what
an industrial spy is?
Well, I'm not exactly sure.
But don't they steal things
like corporate secrets
and stuff?
And guess what?
There's one in this very café.
One of our leading
scientists is trying to sell
information to a third party.
[gulps]
What happens if the spy
gets hold of it?
Japan--no--the whole
world loses ten years
of scientific progress.
Damn these spy bastards.
They're quite literally
stealing our future.
[ULLR] Are you sure you
want to help him, Star Child?
[ULLR] Why do a favor
for a complete strang--?
[laughing]
You heard him. It's for the
good of the whole planet.
[KIKKO] Let's see. This guy
is Japan's leading scientist.
And he's a bad guy
stealing secrets.
All right, Kikko. Play it cool.
[KIKKO]
There you are. Please, enjoy.
Well then?
[MAN IN SUIT] Brought it.
Just like I promised.
Ah! Perfect! Thank you!
So this is the latest
collimator model?
I can't believe it!
How did you ever get
your hands on one?
[KIKKO] Wait a minute.
That seems backwards.
I thought the
professor was selling
and the other guy was buying.
We had it all wrong.
Our intel said Onda
had already discovered
the x-ray source coordinates.
Blast. What now?
Whoever you are,
you're a savior to Japan's
astronomical studies.
I have to go to the lab
right away and test it.
So long.
What?
Stop! Thief!
Oh, waitress! I'm paying
for his coffee, it's fine!
Kikko?
Huh? What's going on out here?
What's gotten into you, Kikko?
Please forgive her, sir.
Grab it, Kikko, now!
[KIKKO gasps]
[ONDA]
N-No!
Now sleep!
[KIKKO yelps]
So, a spy from
another planet, huh?
Um... No! I'm just, uh...
A superhuman?
Nope, nope, just
a normal girl! See?
[MAN IN SUIT growls]
[WINDOW SHOPPER gasps]
[ULLR]
Star Child.
We have to set the
witch power's channel.
Huh? Are you sure?
[ULLR] You can't be caught
using magic in public
without your disguise.
Who knows what layer
you'd be sent to next.
Meteor-tail!
[MAN IN SUIT grunts]
Lookit, Mommy!
She's a witch girl, huh?
[KIKKO laughing]
Hey. Where is it?
Oh. Here.
[CROWD yelling]
Is that--?
[ULLR]
An "S" Planetarian.
[GUIDE] Umm...
I'd like to let people in now
if you're finished.
[EMI] Sorry, not yet.
Just a bit longer.
[GUIDE sighs] You say you're
with the Super Population
Research Laboratory?
Who are you guys?
[HYOUMA] Part of the Health
and Welfare Ministry.
I can give you the number
for the main office
if you want to ask
them yourself.
[AKITA] Oh. Here it comes.
Just as we planned.
[BOY 1A]
It's Grosse Augen!
Don't be scared.
He's on our side!
Did he come here
to help fight the evil alien?
They're gone.
What the--?
I think I'll go this way.
He vanished.
Like he always does.
I'm counting on you to find him.
[JIRO]
I know.
[horn beeping]
I need your help
one more time, Kikko.
Wait a minute!
You knew that spy
was an alien all along!
I did.
Just like I knew you
were the new witch girl
on the scene.
[KIKKO]
What? No!
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about!
[JIRO]
Tell me something, Kikko.
Would you stop saying my name?
What for?
Well, the whole point of
having a secret identity
is that it's secret.
I don't normally
use magic at work.
I guess I just panicked.
Sorry. I'll never do it again.
It's not that big
a deal, really!
[JIRO]
Look ahead.
It's the alien and Grosse Augen
fighting each other.
Grosse Augen.
You know about him?
I saw it in a comic.
The heroic superhuman.
I guess he's real!
Our friend and ally,
Grosse Augen. Yeah.
All right. Give me a read
on their position.
What? They're right there!
[JIRO] When Grosse Augen
goes giant-size,
he shifts the surrounding
Temporal Phase,
basically becoming invisible
to normal humans like me.
Tempura-what now?
The Fred &amp; Hoyle effect.
Let me try and
explain it another way.
Imagine a film reel.
As it plays, we perceive the
image as seamless motion.
But in reality,
there are blank spaces
between the frames.
Gaps in time,
invisible to the human eye,
but every bit as real
as the images we see.
That's where Grosse Augen goes,
phasing into the
"gaps" between time.
I bet it's because he
doesn't wanna hurt people
or destroy any buildings
while he's beating up
the bad guys.
Who knows?
This Kikai does have an
observation mechanism
in it, but--
I honestly haven't the
first clue how to read it!
And besides, I really
ought to keep my eyes
on the road.
[KIKKO chuckles]
So um, just who are you?
[JIRO] Superhumans
protect human peace, right?
Well, who do you think
protects all the superhumans?
[KIKKO]
Huh?
[JIRO] They're forced
to hide their identities
just to live among
normal humans.
We're the ones who're
tasked with protecting them.
Nowadays, they don't have
to keep switching jobs,
or be forced to move
from place to place.
[KIKKO]
You can do it, Grosse Augen!
The evil alien's
straight up ahead!
Right this way!
All right.
Equus! Rear your head!
Whoa! What is that?
A literal iron horse?
Where is he?
Right, got it!
Hey, wait! Wrong direction!
Follow my arrow!
[JIRO]
Outta the way, witch girl!
[KIKKO]
Really?!
[MAN IN SUIT]
Earthling!
I will not allow you to
interfere with our plan!
You can take your
stupid invasion plan
and get bent!
[KIKKO]
Watch out! A heat ray!
I could protect Jiro
with an air shield.
Or would that act like
a lens and make it worse?
[ULLR] You really should
know these things.
You don't want to fail
another test, do you?
Do you have to
rub that in right now?!
I got it! Water!
Mr. Cloud!
[CLOUD]
Hello!
[MAN IN SUIT gasps]
[CLOUD]
Bye-bye!
[MAN IN SUIT]
Controlling the atmosphere?
What technology is this?
[KIKKO] Just plain,
old-fashioned magic!
[JIRO]
Sorry, pal.
I can see you so clearly now,
I can't let you go.
--[JIRO yells]
--[MAN IN SUIT yells]
[MAN IN SUIT grunting]
[MAN IN SUIT]
Damn it!
Gah!
[KIKKO giggles]
[GROSSE AUGEN]
Huh?
Hey, what was that for?!
I told you already,
he's not a bad guy!
He's on our side!
Earth's greatest hero!
Hey there. Going somewhere?
--[KIKKO] Why?!
--[JIRO] Huh?
Tell me, Jiro! Why'd you
hurt Grosse Augen like that?
Why, Jiro?
Why do you insist on
making me your enemy?
[SHIROTA]
Tracked me down again, huh?
[EMI] You've been injected
with fluids from a monster
called Nuppepoo.
Don't feel anything, do you?
But to me--
Well, it smells so sweet,
you can never hide.
No matter how far you run,
I'll always be able
to track you...
Grosse Augen.
Grosse Augen?
[EMI] You've forcibly possessed
and are living inside a human.
Because of this,
both of your bodies
are reaching their limits.
You must separate.
Maruya's back door.
You think this guy's
really Grosse Augen?
Grosse Augen. Separate
from this human at once.
--This is your only--
--[SHIROTA] Listen!
I can't separate from him.
We are one.
We share a life now.
[SHIROTA gasps]
[SHIROTA]
When I found him,
I could tell he
was close to death.
His soul spoke to me,
and I answered.
There was only
one way to save him.
I knew what I had to do.
I agreed.
"I will give you my life
so you might live."
"But in exchange,
to save this planet,
you must fight alongside me."
[JIRO] The way I see it, Grosse
Augen took over your body,
and is in fact controlling you.
Your existences are
unstable. Dangerous.
I don't get it.
Nothing bad happened
when Grosse Augen
fought aliens in the past--
why's this time different?
I understand. And thank you.
But no.
I gave my life so
Grosse Augen could live.
I intend to keep that promise.
Just so we're clear,
you'd give up everything?
You can't tell us that
you dying is no big deal!
It's true Grosse Augen's
body has reached its limit.
But it's still possible
for him to return
to his homeworld.
Hey, wait!
--What's gonna hap--?
--[JIRO] Don't interfere!
[ULLR]
Stop, Kikko!
Using your magic
to disrupt human lives
is strictly forbidden!
Yeah, I know!
But I have to do something.
You're free, Grosse Augen.
The world thanks you
for your heroic deeds. Dig?
Where is he?
His fate was sealed
the minute I saw him.
[KIKKO]
But why?
You said you protected
superhumans and kept them safe!
And I dispose of
the dangerous ones.
That's my other job.
[ONDA] Due to the Gemini
Accident in America,
our collimators stopped working
and we couldn't
procure new ones.
He said he could get
me the latest model--
that my research was
too important to stop.
To think, I was
dealing with an alien!
The Gemini Accident
was probably caused
by an "S" Planetarian as well.
Take a look at this.
It does detect x-ray
sources more accurately
than any technology
available here on Earth.
And yet--
Anyone can freely
change the data
with external radio waves,
making the readings
completely worthless.
But why? Why would
someone do all this?
Thanks for your cooperation.
And good luck with your
research in the future.
Just be on the lookout for
any evil aliens next time.
[JIRO] So there never
was any information,
or at least none worth stealing.
[HYOUMA] Well, we did succeed
in locating Grosse Augen
and successfully
confirmed his identity.
Don't complain.
[AKITA]
The "S" Planetarian likely came
from a base of theirs
believed to be on the planet
called Scorpio-X1.
I imagine they're
not too keen on us
confirming its existence.
[knocking]
[EMI]
Hello.
Ah. Welcome!
What... is this?
It's your new gig.
Welcome to the Super
Population Research Lab.
Starting today, you're
an official team member.
[KIKKO]
You're Grosse Augen.
But you--
[SHIROTA] That day,
in exchange for separating me
from Grosse Augen
and freeing him,
he let me merge
with the captured alien.
The "S" Planetarian.
If my heart was dedicated
to order and peace,
I'd be able to control
its body and mind.
And once again become
a superhuman of justice.
[KIKKO]
Come to think of it,
I do remember several
reports of an "S" Planetarian
that was fighting kaiju .
You went against the
Superhuman Bureau that day.
You didn't kill him,
you saved him!
Jiro, you really are the one I--
I'm finished with
the Superhuman Bureau!
[JIRO]
Farewell, Kikko!
[FUUROUTA]
Hey, guys!
You know the skinny
on ghosts, right?
We're not like all those other
monsters, beasts, and spirits!
Ghosts love playing with kids.
It's in our nature.
We're friendly creatures
who love playing pranks
on all the squares out there!
I'm Fuurouta the ghost.
Don't forget it!