[EMI] I have to admit, I'm
honored you asked me out
for drinks.
[ULLR]
I needed a night off.
I have to make that girl
worthy of becoming a princess.
Oh, really?
Jiro and the Chief are
convinced she's just a witch.
Nothing more.
[ULLR]
Far from it.
She's charmed many
people in this world.
And puts them under a contract
without their knowledge.
That's her real power.
[EMI] So she's not so much
a witch, but more of a--
[ULLR] Please don't say "devil."
That's such a human concept.
She's simply tasked
with becoming a ruler
in a different dimension.
It's not her fault.
[EMI] Let's cut to
the chase, shall we?
She's in love with Jiro.
And as her guardian, you can't
let that hinder your plans.
[ULLR] It could jeopardize
our true purpose.
You feel the same way?
[EMI]
I couldn't care less.
I just feel uncomfortable
that she's always
hitting on my
precious boyfriend.
[ULLR]
Hm.
[BAR GUY 7A]
Look! Earth- chan !
[BAR GAL 7A]
Oh! I see her!
[PATRONS gasp]
Always someone in distress.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but your princess--
she receives more human
souls by doing good
in this world?
[ULLR]
Your point?
You mean you don't know?
That machine doll
operates the same way.
[KIKKO]
Are you Mr. Judas?
[HIKARU]
Um... Yes.
[KIKKO]
Sorry I'm late. I'm Kikko.
From the Superhuman Bureau?
[KIKKO]
That's right!
If you follow me,
I'll show you to our office.
I have to thank you.
I've been told it was
your help that allowed us
to defeat the Diamond
Eaters last year.
[HIKARU]
It was nothing. Really.
[KIKKO] What have you
been up to since then?
Were you working
outside the city?
[EARTH-CHAN]
Judas!
[KIKKO]
Earth- chan ?
[EARTH-CHAN]
Released from prison, I see.
And obviously ready
to commit evil again!
But I'm going to
defeat you before you can!
[KIKKO gasps]
Meteortail!
[KIKKO]
Miss Earth- chan !
There's no need for this!
He's about to be registered,
just like you are!
He's helping us!
[KIKKO]
Ullr! Authorize channel set.
Ullr?
[EARTH-CHAN]
Ow!
[HIKARU]
Come on!
[KIKKO]
Yeah! But what about...?
I've got my eye on you, Judas!
[KIKKO] You mean you
really were in prison?
[HYOUMA] He wouldn't joke
about something like that.
A prison for superhumans,
of course.
Why? What did you do, Judas?
Because...
I used to work
for the Diamond Eaters.
This is from July.
Two years ago.
[KIKKO] But this just
says armed robbery.
[AKITA]
Well, you know the law.
Papers can't write
about superhumans.
We aren't all just people
with powers, you know.
There are subcategories.
Some use diabolical inventions
or ancient super weapons.
[LEADER 7A laughing]
No! My diamonds!
Not my precious diamonds!
[yells]
Get 'em, Judas!
[OFFICER 7A]
He's only a kid.
[OFFICER 7B]
And unarmed.
[OFFICER 7C]
It's an evil superhuman!
Call for backup!
[HIKARU laughing]
You're all such weaklings!
[EARTH-CHAN]
You idiot!
Why would you do
such a terrible thing?
Earth- chan ?
What's she doing here?
[LEADER 7A laughs]
You wouldn't understand
our complicated motives.
You're a child.
And a machine to boot!
There's nothing here
to understand!
[HIKARU]
Earth- chan !
When I was in college,
I studied about war,
and I realized something.
The reason we have
them in the first place
is because of humans.
Normal, foolish humans.
[EARTH-CHAN]
You idiot!
Stop, Earth- chan .
You think you're so smart?
Then why can't you
tell the difference
between what's good and bad?
The world isn't
only black and white.
It's not that simple.
Stop your lying!
Don't you know? Lying is bad!
I see, so you
learned your lesson,
and then you became
a good superhuman.
No. There's more to the story.
Nothing important.
He went to prison.
It's in the past.
But now he's wised up
and he's here,
ready to register with us.
Sign here. Fingerprint here.
And wear this.
It lets others know you're
a good superhuman.
Evil organizations
won't hire you.
I'd like to be
assigned to protect
young people like myself.
[EMI] Really?
So now you like Earth- chan ?
I think it's neat that
she can tell the difference
between good and
evil so clearly.
Well, then I happen to
have the perfect job for you.
I need you to get in touch
with Earth- chan for us.
To clear up the
misunderstanding?
About Judas?
[AKITA]
No. We just need to talk to her.
Are you serious?
We're taking that job?
Well, of course we are.
We do still work
for the government.
How about ghost boy?
He's working on
a different mission.
Deep undercover stuff.
[FUUROUTA] Excuse me!
Can you point me to...
[AKITA] So there's no one
else who can get in touch
with Earth- chan , is there?
Yes, Kikko?
[KIKKO] Can't we, you know,
just call her on the telephone?
[KIKKO]
Why is it so hard to fly?
[ULLR]
I told you. There's no air here.
Ride the light. Not the wind.
[KIKKO yelling]
[EARTH-CHAN]
Huh?
Oh! Earth- chan !
Good, I found you!
We haven't officially met yet.
I'm Kikko Hoshino from
the Superhuman Bureau
of Japan's Health
and Welfare Ministry.
We want to be able
to speak with you.
So from now on,
could you hold onto this?
[KIKKO yelling]
You tricked me with investments
that literally cost me an arm,
so now I'm back
with a new power!
[RECEPTIONIST 7A screaming]
[BYSTANDER 7A]
No surprise.
I heard this company's
practices are real dirty.
[BYSTANDER 7B]
Hey! Look!
Let her go right now!
It's you, Earth- chan !
I'm not evil!
I'm not a bad person!
[BYSTANDER 7B] So who
do you think Earth- chan
will beat up this time?
They sold me trash stocks.
Even when they knew I
wasn't good at these things!
I lost everything!
When I hit bottom,
I had to give my body
to research and look what
that scientist did to me!
I'm the victim here!
I'm not the bad one!
I can tell the difference
between what's good and bad!
[MAN 7A grunts]
[BYSTANDER 7A]
Looks like he was the criminal.
[BYSTANDER 7B] If Earth- chan
says so, it's gotta be true.
[KIKKO]
Miss Earth- chan ?
[BYSTANDER 7A]
A witch girl!
[BYSTANDER 7B]
And she's tied up.
[BYSTANDER 7A]
Yeah, she's tied up good!
[KIKKO yelling]
[KIKKO]
Wait for me!
[BIRDS chirping]
[DRIVER 7A yelling]
[KIDS laughing]
[CAT meows]
[KIKKO]
'Scuse me...
[BOY 7C coughing]
[BOY 7C] I was thinking
how great it'd be
if Earth- chan showed up.
That's why I'm here.
Can you help me?
Of course, just tell me
what's causing your pain.
[ULLR]
It's a futile gesture.
The pollution will
come back tomorrow.
[KIKKO] I know, but at least
Earth- chan tried to help.
Maybe someone will notice
and realize we can't
keep going on like this.
[MOTHER 7A]
Seiji!
[KIKKO chuckles]
[ULLR]
Star Child? What's wrong?
Are you done for today?
[EARTH-CHAN]
If someone calls, I will go.
Good work out there!
Here, have some.
My energy comes
from solar power.
I don't require food.
[KIKKO]
This isn't food.
It allows machines
to have dreams
just like humans do.
[EARTH-CHAN]
Dreams?
[KIKKO] Sleep well
tonight, Earth- chan .
[KIKKO sighs]
Oh, wow. I ache all over.
Feels like I flew around
the world three times.
[ULLR] When humans
sincerely yearn for help,
they emit a certain frequency.
That mechanical doll
seems to detect it.
Wow, really?
Where did you learn that from?
[ULLR]
Well, uh...
Anyway, she does seem
to find listening
to their brain waves
quite pleasant.
I have no idea
who made her, but...
A warm-hearted spaceman, I bet.
A machine that hears
anyone call for help?
Designed to save people
any time of day or night?
[JIRO]
You really think so?
[KIKKO]
J-J-Jiro?
Sure, just let yourself in!
He let me in.
Want some tea? Mr. Ullr?
It's no use pretending
you're just a doll.
What are either
of you doing here?
That band assistant
job was really hard.
Lemme tell you about it.
Don't care!
So, for real.
Do you need something?
You forgot to turn
in your report.
Did you talk to Earth- chan ?
Yeah, about that...
We need her.
There's an international
conference.
The Prime Minister's there.
To announce that Japan's
joining the Defense Force
of Earth.
DFE? They're the organization
who defends Earth
from evil spacemen, right?
Yeah, but most
people are against it.
And several superhumans are also
opposing Japan's involvement.
Protests.
The Haneda one should
be the largest.
So you're wanting
to have Earth- chan
protect the Prime
Minister, right?
I'll ask her--I'm pretty
sure she'll go for it.
Huh? You think so?
I thought Earth- chan
supported the students.
What?
[JIRO] Last summer,
Master Ultima tried to bring
his army of kaiju
to visit Japan.
But Earth- chan stood
with the protestors,
and stopped him from entering.
[KIKKO]
How come?
[JIRO]
We don't know.
But the public's views
shifted dramatically
against the use of Kaiju in war.
It was much more
effective than our defeat
of MegaGon.
In short, Earth-
chan needs to defend
the Prime Minister.
Then the public will
view the DFE as "good."
And Japan can join.
But, isn't it supposed
to be the other way around?
Just because Earth- chan
is on the side
of the good guys,
it doesn't mean support from
her makes something good.
Yes, it does.
And it's our job to make it so.
But it just feels wrong, Jiro.
Exploiting Earth- chan
like this.
[phone rings]
[HIKARU] So you won't
give me permission?
To join the protest? Why?
The DFE fights bad
spacemen, isn't that right?
But they can't all be evil.
What if some of them
are actually good?
It's the right thing.
I have to protest.
The Superhuman
Bureau can't help you.
You may be arrested.
Uh, Jiro, you're
saying the "S" word
kinda loud, aren't ya?
[JIRO] You don't have
to worry in this place.
[KIKKO]
No? Why not?
[JIRO]
It's a Free Zone.
Superhumans, and sometimes
members of evil organizations
are allowed to show
their true selves here.
That's the rule.
Let me be clear.
The Superhuman Bureau
supports Japan's joining
of the DFE.
They'll try to use us
in the human's wars again.
What do they think Earth can do?
Let Master Ultima
handle the space-men.
[YUKIHIKO] Earth- chan !
It's rare seeing you here.
I heard you.
You're going to do something
that will get you arrested.
[CUSTOMER 7A]
Nonsense.
He's not a villain
anymore, Earth- chan .
He's on our side now.
[HIKARU]
It's okay.
It's not.
I can't be forgiven.
It's my own fault.
[EARTH-CHAN]
You lied to me, Judas.
Don't you know? Lying is bad!
[EARTH-CHAN]
Stop running!
[HIKARU] Earth- chan !
I'm sorry, I was wrong!
I'll use my powers
for good from now on.
[HIKARU]
I was serious at that time.
And I wanted to be good.
But it didn't last.
I ended up going back
to the Diamond Eaters.
[KIKKO]
Did they threaten you?
No. They treated
me with respect.
They were the only ones.
So I rejoined.
[JIRO]
You were weak.
That all changed.
Someone from the Superhuman
Bureau found me
and asked for information.
Information on my gang.
I was finally able to do right.
That's why I helped destroy
the Diamond Eaters.
So you gave up evil and
became good in the end.
Earth- chan , humans
aren't foolproof like you.
We make mistakes.
He broke his promise.
You said you would
never be bad again.
And lied.
You really don't understand
why people lie, do you?
[HIKARU] I'll walk the path
of good from now on.
This protest isn't just for me.
Protest? You're going
to be violent again?
I have to take a stand;
it's the right thing to do.
I'll make you a promise.
I won't use my
superhuman powers.
[KIKKO, JIRO gasp]
I will join the protest.
As a normal person,
not a superhuman.
Then, will you believe me?
Oh! Earth- chan .
Were you able to dream?
[SUPER MAN 7A]
I advise caution.
The girl from the Bureau--
you know she's a witch?
A witch?
They sell their
souls to the devil.
Oh! How rude of me!
We're the Strange Power
Risk Management Office.
We fight paranormal
activities and occultists.
Nice to meet you.
I won't let a witch
make a fool of me.
[ANNOUNCER 7A]
Here at Haneda Airport,
the police and the protestors
are at a standstill.
This is preventing the
state-of-the-art aircraft
carrying the prime
minister from taking off.
It's unfortunate we
couldn't convince Earth- chan
to run security for us.
Her showing up is good enough.
I'll take what we can get.
[PROTESTORS yelling]
[SUPERHUMAN 7A]
Two! Three! Four!
♪ Got a look with no
expression, ba-bang bang ♪
♪ Bang bang ba-ba-ba-ba
ba-ba-ba-bang ♪
♪ Can't beat a man if
he doesn't have feelings ♪
[POLICE 7A] Superhumans!
They're in the crowd!
March and take 'em down!
[HYOUMA]
It's begun.
I wonder...
Is Earth- chan going
to support the protestors?
[HYOUMA] She only helps
those who emit an SOS
from the bottom of their hearts.
I'm not sure people
who want chaos
and destruction qualify.
They're alone.
So does that mean she's right
and everyone else is wrong?
That's not what we said.
The public will think whichever
side Earth- chan 's on
is right.
And whatever she chooses,
there's no way we can fight her.
[PROTESTORS yelling]
Hey, guys! Stop pushing!
I knew it, Judas!
You lied to me again!
Ullr! Set up
witch power channels!
--Meterotail!
--[JIRO] Kikko! Don't do this!
You won't beat me this time!
Now you can't
make electricity.
You liar!
[KIKKO]
Stop it, Earth- chan !
The witch. Of course!
So you're evil too, I knew it!
Meteortail!
[KIKKO]
Listen to me, Earth- chan !
I think doing bad
things is wrong too.
But we make mistakes!
Humans can't be
right all the time!
[EARTH-CHAN]
You know that isn't true!
[JIRO]
Earth- chan !
Are you certain you're
only doing good?
[KIKKO]
Jiro?
[JIRO]
Think!
You feel good when you
hear people asking for help.
That's what's
fueling your powers!
That's how you were designed.
That's it!
[EARTH-CHAN yelps]
Am I having a dream?
[KIKKO] The more brain waves
there are asking for help,
the better you feel.
Your maker didn't design
you to help humans.
Or to know right from wrong.
You were made to hurt.
[HIKARU]
Enough!
[HIKARU] No, Miss Kikko.
Earth- chan is right.
[KIKKO]
Judas.
[HIKARU] Two years ago,
Earth- chan came to me
when my heart cried out.
It was asking for
someone to save me.
Someone to stop me.
She was the only one who heard.
Who understood
I wanted to be good.
[KIKKO]
That man there?
[HIKARU] He was crushed
under the water truck.
I tried my best to save him.
[KIKKO] And that's why
you used your powers.
Earth- chan , I'm sorry.
I broke my promise again.
At this rate, there's
no way I'll be a superhuman
of justice. Like you.
[EARTH-CHAN]
Let me help him.
[REPORTER 2A]
At last,
the Prime Minister's
aircraft has taken off.
Japan's membership in
the DFE will be confirmed
at the conference.
Now we will hold hands
with the rest of the world
to pursue a unified--
[doorbell rings]
Please cancel the
spell you cast on me.
Spell?
[EARTH-CHAN] I can't sleep.
Not since that day.
[KIKKO]
I gave you some of these? Right?
Yes, that's what I ate.
What did you do to me?
[KIKKO] Earth- chan ...
That was... a lie.
A lie?
[KIKKO] Sometimes,
people need to have lies.
See? Even you.
The taste of lies.
[MOTHER 7A]
Earth- chan !
[BROTHER 7A]
Hey, sister!
[BROTHER 7B]
Come on! We're over here!
[alarm ringing]
[JIRO]
Thanks, Megasshin.
You sure about this, Judas?
Yes.
Earth- chan .
You will be restored.
It's my turn to save you.
[YUMIHIKO] When trouble comes,
you can count on us
to save the day.
Lin, Molly, Saki,
Hideaki, and Yumihiko Otonashi.
We are the Juvenile
Investigator BL Club.
Boys of Light.
The Gigander Seven!