Not again.
So which one of those
boats is the Antares?
Neither of them.
The Antares isn't a ship.
It's supposed to be some
cutting-edge submarine.
Everyone's making a big fuss
'cause it's showing
up in Yokosuka.
[FISHERMAN 11B]
I guess now that Ogasawara
is being returned to Japan,
the Americans can't
park it there anymore.
[FISHERMAN 11A]
Hm?
Hey! Mister!
There's no swimming
allowed here!
A superhuman? Huh.
[phone ringing]
[CHINATSU]
Hello. Hitoyoshi residence.
[KIKKO]
Uh... Chinatsu?
Hey, Kikko! It's been a while.
How are you?
[KIKKO]
Oh. I'm fine.
Jiro's not there
by any chance...
Sorry, He's not.
He left early this morning.
[KIKKO]
Did he say where... he was?
Kikko, where are you?
Um if... you could
have him call work
the next time you talk to him.
[CHINATSU]
Oh. I keep forgetting.
Did I already tell you
Jiro only eats mild curry?
You know, just in case
you end up cooking him any.
[KIKKO grunts]
[ULLR]
Let's wake these people up.
This is nonsense.
Even if they are only students.
[KIKKO]
I know.
But our job is
to provide security
for the Angel Stars.
[NAVY MEN cheering]
[KIKKO] Where did Jiro and
Miss Emi disappear to?
[ULLR]
On a date, perhaps?
[CROWD cheering]
[CHINATSU]
Like I said,
if you were a little
more persistent,
Jiro would pick you
over the ogre Emi.
Hello? Kikko?
Are you still there, Kikko?
[MAGOTAKE]
Hm. You don't like her?
[CHINATSU]
Huh?
I'm talking about Emi.
So, what's wrong with her?
May I be completely
honest with you?
I think she's
a beautiful person.
Well, technically not a person.
Um, right.
But she's also your assistant.
And extremely capable.
Without her, the entire
academic discipline
of superhuman ethnology
wouldn't exist.
However...
However?
It's almost like
she controls Jiro.
And he can't say no to her.
[gasps]
Thank you.
For being so
concerned about Jiro.
[JIRO]
It's a generous amount.
Oh, it'll be one of the
best offers we've made,
on par with the Angel Stars.
But if it's not high enough...
Feel free to add zeroes.
However many.
Thanks. But we have to decline.
Last winter, Imperial Ads
laced chocolate with drugs
to repress superhumans.
A life was lost.
Before that, it was Megagon.
You tried to improve
the public's view of beasts.
Countless lives were lost
because of your publicity stunt.
It's clear.
You're hostile to the Bureau.
And to all superhumans.
You've got us all wrong.
We support the
hypothesis superhumans
are the next evolutionary
step for humans.
[JIRO]
Next step?
[MICHIKO] You're too
liberal with the term.
"Superhuman" should
be used exclusively.
Not thrown around.
Superhumans are a type
of human, after all.
Should you really
count spacemen,
demons, phantoms, and robots?
Next you'll include monsters.
Superhumans are
defenders of justice.
Humanity's path forward.
You should do your homework.
I'm not a superhuman.
I don't have any powers,
but I'll always
fight for justice.
Jiro!
Hey, guys!
We've got trouble in Yokosuka!
They're just a band of freaks.
[SATOMI]
You did well.
Now they won't make it
to the harbor in time.
Satomi?
Do you think we can really
trust him to work with us?
[SATOMI]
Are you referring to Claude?
[SATOMI] He is something we
can call an existential crisis
for the Superhuman Bureau.
[CROWD yelling]
Of course it's you!
We didn't have
anything to do with this!
[RAITO] If more arrive,
this could get bad!
So, help me!
[RAITO]
What is this?
[CROWD laughing]
Shut up!
[singing]
Entertain us, Detective!
♪ I will go alone,
turning my back to happiness. ♪
♪ But I still think
about your kiss ♪
♪ Late at night it
haunts me in my dreams ♪
Listen to me!
Many of you are
superhumans in violation
of the secrecy law.
We want to prevent
tragedies like Haneda.
The police were
the ones that caused
the Haneda death!
You're wrong!
It was because violent
students protested the DFE.
[REIICHI]
Detective!
Do you support Japan's
decision to join the DFE?
They consider all
spacemen enemies!
[music playing]
[RAITO]
Superhuman folksong!
Gah!
[NAVY MEN cheering]
Without further ado,
the latest tech by the US Navy.
The Antares submarine!
[NAVY MEN gasp]
Who is that?
[music playing]
[JACKY (SONG)]
♪ Wait, oh wait, oh wait, oh ♪
♪ Once again ♪
♪ So many words,
I got a lot to say ♪
♪ So I'll go first ♪
♪ Talk with my
vacillating lips ♪
♪ Give a kiss that's
so ballistic, you'll go ♪
♪ Tic tac tic tac BOOM ♪
♪ Embrace me oh so tenderly ♪
Hey, man.
What do you think you're doing?
You should really stop
before there's trouble.
[CLAUDE]
Tell me something.
Beautiful superhumans.
He called us beautiful!
[CLAUDE]
For what reason do you fight?
Is it justice? For peace?
Or to the guarantee
the freedom of mankind?
[CLAUDIA]
Justice. I guess.
[FANNY]
Well, sure.
But peace is important.
[ARACHNE]
So are our paychecks.
[CLAUDE]
Good answer.
Why don't you get to the point?
[CLAUDE]
The name is Claude.
Sword Phantom Claude!
Tell me, villain.
What group do you belong to?
[CLAUDE] Detective Shiba.
I am a superhuman.
That's what they all say.
You're under arrest!
[RAITO yelling]
[RAITO grunts]
[CROWD yelling]
[STUDENT 11A]
Jacky!
[STUDENT 11B]
Angels! Are you okay?
[STUDENT 11C]
Rose!
[RAITO]
What's your real motivation?
[CLAUDE]
The Antares.
Do you know what
it's true nature is?
It's operated by a superhuman
for superior performance.
[CLAUDE] Its superior
ability is for killing.
It's used for war.
[ULLR]
What's wrong, Star Child?
[RAITO gasps]
[CLAUDE] Superhumans are
not meant to be pawns,
used in conflicts
between nations.
Or in petty squabbles
between other superhumans.
We should be focused on
pursuing our own future--
a brighter future.
Based on our own beliefs.
[RAITO laughs]
[CLAUDE]
Think I'm dreaming?
All I see is a
lone man ranting!
[CLAUDE] Changing the
world single-handedly
may be a lofty dream,
but it might be shared
by all superhumans.
I can't be the only one!
[CLAUDE] As you can see,
my body is a factory.
Able to absorb
and transform metal.
You're no match for me.
[RAITO grunts]
You intend to fight
everyone by yourself?
Against thousands who
want to use superhumans
for war?
[CLAUDE]
Freedom.
Peace.
[CLAUDE]
Justice.
[CLAUDE] Superhumans typically
fight for one of these
three reasons.
But it must also
be for the people.
Not for the self.
Ha. He's so cool.
[CLAUDE] Which one do
you choose, Detective?
Superhuman crimes
won't go unpunished.
That's my choice.
The Phantom Sword.
Could he be--?
[ULLR]
What?
Um, nothing.
But, the detective--
we can't just leave
him alone, can we?
Witch power channel set--
Meteortail!
[STUDENT 11A]
It's a witch girl!
[STUDENT 11B]
Hey! Get the camera!
What do you think, Reiichi?
She's with the Bureau.
[CLAUDE]
Kikko Hoshino!
Huh? Who's Kikko?
I have no idea who that is.
I just happened to
be passing through!
[CLAUDE] I have no
intention of fighting you.
You're a good superhuman.
[RAITO yells]
[KIKKO screaming]
[ULLR]
Star Child! Star Child!
[KIKKO]
I've seen this before.
[JIRO]
Kikko. Hey, Kikko.
Wake up.
Jiro. You made it.
You're awake.
Jiro...
[FUUROUTA gasps]
Kikko? What's wrong?
[KIKKO] I'm so embarrassed.
I just want to die.
There's no time for that.
We've got problems. Look.
[SOLDIER 11A]
Don't take pictures!
Give me that!
I was just about
to replace the film.
Guys. We're on camera.
Act distraught.
But I don't want to.
[REPORTER 2A] What you see
here was once the USS Antares.
Destroyed this afternoon
in Yokosuka Harbor.
The identity of the attacker
remains a mystery.
Developed by the US Navy,
the Antares was the first
superhuman-powered submarine.
And part of the
Master Commander plan,
named after Master
Ultima himself.
This footage, acquired
from an anonymous source,
seems to show people stuck
between the machinery.
This broadcast violates
the secrecy laws
but they probably
pulled some strings
to get it through.
Imperial Ads.
Have we learned anything
about the caped man
with the skull mask?
All we know is that
he calls himself Claude.
Sword Phantom Claude.
His goal seemed to be
showing the U.S. military
was using superhumans
inhumanely.
That's our job.
And he's better at it than us.
[phone ringing]
[HYOUMA]
You expecting a call?
[JIRO]
This doctor.
You just need to see him,
and not go to the hospital?
[KIKKO]
It's not serious.
Thanks for driving me.
[JIRO]
Forget it. You were there.
What can you tell
me about Claude?
I remember.
He said his body
was a metal factory.
And after that--
[JIRO]
What is it?
Well, it's hard to explain.
You think I can
beat him with Equus?
Jiro! You're not gonna
fight him, are you?
Of course I will.
He was responsible for more
than seventy deaths today.
Yeah. But you're including
the crew of the submarine,
and they were already dead
before Claude even arrived.
Turned into parts
for that machine.
You're right.
The chief will contact
the US about that,
and we'll get to the
bottom of what's going on.
[KIKKO] The submarine's
crew was superhuman.
Shouldn't we have
been protecting them?
Shouldn't we have saved them?
I would have if I had known.
Really?
It doesn't mean that
I can forgive Claude.
The news crew showed up
at exactly the right time.
He's most likely
connected to Imperial Ads.
Imperial Ads is just a
stupid advertising agency.
Why are you so
hostile towards them?
Because--
Superhumans are a type of human.
Anyway, Claude isn't superhuman.
He's a demon.
And I'm a witch!
It's different! You're--
Please pull over.
You need to see the doctor.
[KIKKO]
I said pull over now!
[AKITA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[AKITA] I thought this
meeting was just between us.
[SHIMAZU]
It's an emergency.
The Superhuman
Bureau is responsible
for letting that freak run amok.
That's not how--
Akita.
Allow me to introduce the
former Minister of Defense.
Mitsuya.
It's a pleasure to
make your acquaintance,
Mr. Akita.
Let's cut to the chase.
The minister is for
the Revised Secrecy Laws.
The Ministry of Health and
Welfare is submitting them
to the legislature.
That's right. In full support.
Please, take a seat.
Pardon my asking,
but you're aware
the Japanese government
secretly employs
superhuman soldiers in the
country's security forces?
This new Superhuman law.
It'll effectively
ban that practice.
Not to worry.
We're covered.
If they register themselves
as a superhuman,
they can volunteer.
It's not a total ban.
Defense.
Foreign affairs. Police.
Mr. Mitsuya will help
pull all the different
disciplines together.
But you see,
in order to do that--
we have to make sure longhaired
kids with electric guitars
aren't inspired by
subversives like this.
Are you proposing
that we make a deal?
[CROWD chattering]
We need to discuss it
with the Americans
before we take action.
But this Claude
villain is an enemy,
and must be dealt with sternly.
[REPORTER 11A] Minister,
what about those who say
he's a superhuman of justice,
who revealed the Antares
was an inhumane weapon?
Really?
If he is right,
and on the side of justice,
wouldn't that make
the U.S. military
and the Japanese
government evil?
[TAKI] You took quite
a beating, Detective.
[KIDS chattering]
I don't approve
of these tools!
There's nothing to worry about.
Advanced technology
is identical to magic.
Our magic is science.
There's no difference.
We're officially commissioned
by the police force.
Please relax.
It'll make things much easier.
Then I'm going
to need your help.
I want to find out
who Claude is.
That's no problem.
There's no mystery
we can't uncover.
That's the motto
of us Sciencers.
We'll get to the truth.
Dreamers and fools.
The Bureau protects them all.
[TAKI, KAEDE]
Huh?
[ULLR] Are you sure you want
to go alone, Star Child?
[CLAUDE] Miss Kikko.
I want to show you something.
Whatever's inside,
maybe it's something
for my eyes only.
[ULLR] Star Child.
If this turns out to be nothing,
you have to buy me
miso butter ramen for dinner.
It's been two months.
And no sign of Claude.
It must be important.
Meteortail.
[KIKKO gasps]
[CLAUDE] Kikko.
What are you doing here?
Why did you... kill them?
Tell me.
[KIKKO screaming]
[ULLR]
Star Child!
[KIKKO]
Hot. Hot!
It's hot! I'm burning up!
[ULLR]
Stop!
Ullr. I think I caught a cold.
--I'm on fire.
--[CLAUDE] No!
[KIKKO screaming]
[ULLR]
Star Child.
Ullr. Your master
commands you.
Bring forth my Comet Tail.
[KIKKO]
Explain yourself, human.
Why this terrible act?
[CLAUDE] Listen to me.
Future queen of the devil realm.
There's a reason I had
to kill these people.
For justice?
[CLAUDE] As a superhuman,
I cannot allow evil to live.
I must destroy it
wherever it thrives.
[KIKKO]
One more question, Claude.
Tell me.
Are you somebody I know?
[CLAUDE]
Yes.
I thought so.
[CLAUDE] Sometimes,
the pursuit of freedom
disturbs the peace.
Justice fights justice
in the name of peace.
Even today, your justice
invades my freedom.
Tell me now.
What reason do you fight for?
I am Claude.
Sword Phantom Claude.