- ( theme music playing )
- ( wind blowing )
- Knives: VASH.
VASH!
- ( groans )
- COME ON, VASH.
STAND UP, ALREADY.
- ( grunts )
- LET'S GO.
HEY!  DON'T BE THAT WAY.
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME HERE.
WE SHOULD AT LEAST TRY
TO ACT LIKE BROTHERS.
- MURDERER!
YOUR WHOLE LIFE IS A LIE!
YOU KILLED REM, THE CREW!
YOU KILLED THEM ALL!
- ( chuckles )
YEAH.  SPECTACULAR, HUH?
THEY ALL DIE,
EXCEPT OF COURSE FOR THE
FRACTION WHO WILL SURVIVE
BECAUSE OF REM'S
INCESSANT MEDDLING.
- Vash: WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- THERE'S NO USE STAYING HERE.
COME ON.
OR WOULD YOU RATHER
JUST LAY THERE
AND CRY YOUR LITTLE EYES OUT?
THIS IS
A TERRIBLE ENVIRONMENT,
JUST AS I PREDICTED
IT WOULD BE.
IT'LL BE IMPOSSIBLE
FOR ANY GARBAGE TO LIVE HERE.
- Vash: IT CAN STILL WORK OUT
IF THEY HAVE THE PLANTS.
- YEAH, PROBABLY.
THEY'LL SURVIVE
BY LEECHING OFF
THE BLOOD OF OUR SIBLINGS,
GORGING THEMSELVES
LIKE PARASITES.
I CAN HEAR THE SCREAMS
OF OUR BRETHREN NOW.
THE ANGUISHED DEATH CRIES
OF OUR FRIENDS.
- IS THAT WHY YOU KILL PEOPLE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I KILL SPIDERS TO SAVE
THE BUTTERFLIES.
IT'S SIMPLE LOGIC.
- ( breathing heavily )
Vash's voice:
DON'T FORGET-- HE KILLED THEM.
THAT'S RIGHT, HE KILLED...
( grunts )
REM, HELP.
- NO ONE EVER HAS THE RIGHT
TO TAKE THE LIFE OF ANOTHER.
- ( crying )
HUH?
- Knives: VASH!
COME ON, HURRY UP!
LET'S GET GOING!
- ( water running )
- ( breathing heavily )
( gulps, yells )
- HEY!
- ( people shouting )
- THAT IS THE TRUE NATURE
OF THESE PATHETIC BEASTS
KNOWN AS HUMANS.
THEY'RE ALL SELFISH,
ARROGANT, INSOLENT,
GROSSLY IMPERFECT ORGANISMS.
THEY MAKE ME SICK
TO MY STOMACH.
- ( humming )
- ( people screaming )
- Vash: WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
- ( grunts )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- WHEN YOU AND I WERE BORN,
WE HAD FREE WILL.
WE'RE NO LONGER MERELY THINGS
TO BE USED BY HUMANS.
- Vash's voice:
WHAT IS HE SAYING?
- ( wind blowing )
- ( Knives laughs )
I FOUND IT.
THE DAMAGE ISN'T ALL THAT BAD.
IT'S USEABLE.
- WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING
TO DO WITH THIS?
- I HAVE TO GO AFTER
SOMETHING I LEFT BEHIND.
I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR IT.
THIS MIGHT TAKE A LITTLE WHILE.
I SUGGEST YOU STAY HERE.
- BUT, KNIVES...
IT'S HARD TO BE ALONE.
I DON'T WANNA BE ALONE.
- ( footsteps )
- SOMEONE-- ( gasps )
KNIVES!
- ALL DONE.
- KNIVES!
( panting )
HEY, NOW WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- ( explosion )
- ( yelps )
- ONLY A 13% OUTPUT.
THAT'S THE BEST WE CAN GET.
- WHA-- WHAT IS THAT?
- THESE ARE OUR NEW SIBLINGS,
AND THIS ONE WILL BE YOURS.
WE WILL USE THESE GUNS
TO DISPOSE OF MANKIND.
- ( gasps ) I--
I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT!
- YES, YOU WILL!
- NEVER!
- THEN WHY DID YOU FOLLOW ME
AND WAIT UNTIL I RETURNED?
BECAUSE YOU'RE HOPELESS ON
YOUR OWN. ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- ( exhales sharply )
- VERY WELL, WATCH ME THEN.
- ( gasps )
DON'T!
- ( both grunting )
- ( gun cocks )
- AFTER 15 YEARS,
ARE YOU STILL SO AFFECTED
BY THAT RIDICULOUS NONSENSE?
THAT FANTASY WORLD
CREATED FOR YOU
BY THE WOMAN WHO LIVED
AND DIED BY CONTRADICTION?
- ( grunts )
I WON'T LET YOU KILL
ANY MORE PEOPLE!
- SORRY, DEAR BROTHER,
I THINK
YOU MISUNDERSTOOD ME.
YOU'RE AIMING
AT THE WRONG PERSON.
- THEY'RE STILL ALIVE.  ALIVE.
I PROMISED REM THAT
WE WOULD MAKE THIS LAND--
- EXACTLY.  WE WILL.
YOU AND I WILL MAKE THIS LAND
INTO OUR VERY OWN EDEN.
JUST FOR US.
- Vash's voice:
IT'S WRONG.
THIS IS WRONG.
IT'S WRONG!
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
MY LEG.
MY LEG, IT HURTS.  WHY?
WHY?
THERE'S SO MUCH PAIN
IN MY LEG!
DID YOU SHOOT ME?
DID YOU ACTUALLY SHOOT ME?
- ( breathing shakily )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
DID YOU REALLY SHOOT ME?!
- ( yells )
( crying )
- NO!  WAIT!
VASH!
( screaming )
- R-- REM.
WHERE AM I?
- ( gunshot )
- ( beeping )
- ( gasps )
THIS MAN IS RELATED TO REM.
HE'S STILL ALIVE.
I HAVE TO TELL HIM ABOUT REM.
( gasps )
- HEY THERE, VASH.
- ( crying )
- NOW EVERYTHING THAT JOINED
YOU AND REM TOGETHER
IS FINALLY GONE.
- IS THAT YOUR EXCUSE
FOR KILLING?
- HAVEN'T YOU LEARNED ANYTHING
OVER THE PAST HUNDRED YEARS?
THE SCARS THEY CARVED
INTO YOUR BODY
WILL NEVER REGENERATE.
SYMBOLIC OF YOUR
FOOLISH WASTE OF ENERGY
ON THIS HUMAN GARBAGE.
- REGARDLESS OF HOW
YOU FEEL ABOUT THEM,
THEY ARE LIVING BEINGS.
THEY DESERVE TO LIVE!
- WHAT'S THE USE OF GROWING UP
IF THE ONLY THING THAT GROWS IS
YOUR USELESS SENTIMENTALISM?
YOU'RE STILL
A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
PATHETIC WIMP!
- ( gun cocks )
- ( grunts )
( whimpering )
- ( snaps )
- ( crackling )
- WHAT-- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- THIS IS OUR GIFT, BROTHER.
NOW IT'S TIME TO TAKE OUT
THIS WORTHLESS HUMAN GARBAGE
FOREVER!
- AAH!
- ARE YOU GOING
TO SHOOT ME AGAIN?
- ( screaming, groaning )
- ARE YOU ACTUALLY
GONNA SHOOT ME AGAIN?!
HUH?!
MAKE VASH SUFFER.
MAKE HIM SUFFER
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
- I WILL, MY MASTER.
I PROMISE THE MAN BELONGING
TO THIS ARM WILL SUFFER.
- NOW'S THE END OF
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
YOU AND THIS TOWN
DIE TOGETHER!
( grunts, groans )
- YOU'RE NAIVE.
HAD I BEEN SO INCLINED,
I COULD HAVE KILLED YOU
AT LEAST THREE TIMES BY NOW.
- DID YOU KILL THEM OR NOT?
- DAMN, YOU ARE A NOISY ONE,
AREN'T YOU?
WHAT IF I DID, CHICKEN SHIT?
( groans )
( groans loudly )
- COME ON.
I THINK YOU'RE DEAD.
READY?
- RUN!
- WHAT IS THAT?!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT THING?!
- RUN!  RUN!
- IT SHOULD NEVER END THIS WAY.
- WHAT OTHER ALTERNATIVE
DO I HAVE
IF WE'RE GOING TO SURVIVE?
OUR LIVES ARE
TOO DIFFERENT, VASH.
AND HE'S NOT ALONE.
- I FAILED.
I FAILED TO SAVE SOMEONE AGAIN.
- JUST BE MORE CAREFUL
THE NEXT TIME.
- COME ON, IT'S TIME TO CHOOSE.
YOU HAVE FREE WILL.
- Meryl and Mllly:
NO!  AAH!
- ( laughing )
( maniacal laughter )
THE HUMANS TREAT YOU WELL?
DID YOU HAVE FUN,
DEAR BROTHER?
- I DID, YEAH.
BEST THING THAT EVER
HAPPENED TO ME.
- ( rock music playing )
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
( panting )
HEH.
- ( grunts )
- ( guns cock )
- ( breathing heavily )
AAH!
( groaning )
- HMM!
HE CANCELLED ME OUT.
I DIDN'T CREATE THESE WEAPONS
TO BE WASTED LIKE THAT.
- USING THEM THIS WAY IS
THE ONLY THING THAT
GIVES THEM ANY MEANING
AT ALL.
- IT'S HOPELESS, ISN'T IT?
- I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
- YOU'RE NOT A HUMAN BEING.
YOU'RE A PLANT.
- I KNOW THAT.
- YOU'RE A SUPERIOR BEING.
- I DISAGREE.
- YOU'RE WRONG
ABOUT THIS, VASH.
- I WON'T MAKE
THE SAME MISTAKE TWICE.
( breathing heavily )
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( gun cocks )
- ( groans )
- HA.
- ( exhales )
- Wolfwood's voice: WHAT ARE
YOU DOING, NEEDLE NOGGIN?!
IT'S RIGHT NEXT TO YOU.
USE IT, DAMN IT!
- AAH.
( screams )
( groans loudly )
AAH!
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( groaning )
- I...
I WILL...
SURVIVE.
- ( rumbling )
- ( townspeople cheering )
- MERYL!
WATER!
WE HIT WATER!
- YEAH.
- ( laughs )
VASH WILL COME BACK,
WON'T HE?
- OF COURSE HE WILL.
HE WOULDN'T DARE KEEP
A GOOD WOMAN LIKE ME WAITING.
RIGHT?
- ( giggles ) RIGHT.
- REM...
I WILL CONTINUE
TO BELIEVE IN YOU.
BUT FROM NOW ON,
I'LL LOOK TO MY OWN WORDS
FOR GUIDANCE.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )