- ( theme music plays )
- ( violin plays )
- ( laughing )
- HEY, BOSS.
HOW LONG ARE YOU GOING
TO KEEP ME HELD UP
IN THIS PLACE, HUH?
HE GOT TWO
OF OUR IDIOTS ALREADY
WHILE WE SAT AROUND
TWIDDLING OUR THUMBS.
YOU SHOULD HAVE
LET ME HANDLE IT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU
SHOULD HAVE DONE.
- ALL RIGHT THEN,
I'LL LET YOU GO NEXT.
I'LL EVEN SET
THE STAGE FOR YOU.
I EXPECT YOU TO ENTERTAIN HIM
WITH A UNIQUE PERFORMANCE
OF TRICKS.
- ( laughs ) YOU CAN
BE REASONED WITH.
LET'S HOPE THE REWARD
IS REASONABLE.
- SO ARE YOU GONNA MAKE HIM
GO AT IT ALONE THIS TIME?
- ( chuckles )
HARDLY.
I'M A FIRM BELIEVER
THAT AN AUDIENCE
ALWAYS GETS MORE PLEASURE
FROM A DRAMA WITH A TWIST.
IT'S A SIMPLE FORMULA.
THE GREATER THE TRAGEDY,
THE GREATER
THE EMOTIONAL EFFECT.
- ( smirks )
- ( clinks )
- ( chatter )
- I'M WORRIED, MERYL.
IT'S BEEN
TWO WHOLE WEEKS NOW.
- Vash: I'M SORRY. THIS IS AS
FAR AS WE CAN TRAVEL TOGETHER.
- Meryl: WHY?
- IT'S YOUR JOB OR YOUR LIFE!
WHICH IS MORE
IMPORTANT TO YOU?
- ( sighs )
- I CAN'T EXPLAIN NOW.
IF I DID,
YOU'D BE PUT IN DANGER.
SO IT'S BEEN A LOT OF FUN, BUT,
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S ALL.
- ( people chatter )
- POOR MR. VASH.
I WONDER HOW HE'S DOING.
- YOU KNOW HIM.
HE'S UNDOUBTEDLY GOOFING AROUND
IN SOME TOWN SOMEWHERE. I'M SURE
HE'S JUST FINE AND DANDY.
- Boy: WAIT FOR ME!
- Man #1: HEY, DID YOU HEAR?
- ( gasps )
- REMEMBER THE GUY
IN THE WHITE SUIT
WHO HAD CAUSED THE SALOON RIOT
THE OTHER DAY?
WELL, HE APPARENTLY TURNED OUT
TO BE ONE OF VASH'S GANG.
- OH, YEAH, THAT
WOULD EXPLAIN A LOT.
INCLUDING WHY HIS METHODS
WERE SO DANG VICIOUS.
- Man #3: ( laughs )
BUT HE TOOK OFF.
- Man #1: YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I GUESS, AT THIS POINT,
WE SHOULD COUNT OUR BLESSINGS
THAT WE GOT OFF SO EASY.
- Man #3: YEAH.
HE'S A DEVIL
IN A RED COAT.
THAT'S WHAT HE IS.
- Man #2: DAMN, I WISH
HE'D JUST DROP DEAD.
- HOW CAN YOU
STAND THERE AND SAY
SUCH AWFUL THINGS ABOUT HIM?
- Men: HUH?
- I MEAN, AFTER ALL,
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT KIND
OF PERSON HE IS.
I THINK YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
- HUH?
- GEE, MERYL.
- ( gasps )
( embarrassed laughter )
- WALK YOUR OWN PATH
WITH YOUR HEAD HELD HIGH.
I JUST HAVE
TO KEEP SAYING IT.
RIGHT.  MILLY.
- YES.
- WE'VE GOT TO GET GOING.
WE HAVE A LOT OF WORK AHEAD.
LET'S STOP WASTING TIME.
- OKAY.
- IF NECESSARY, WE'LL FOLLOW HIM
TO THE ENDS OF THE EARTH.
IT'S NOT ONLY OUR JOB NOW,
IT'S BECOME OUR MISSION
TO TRACK HIM DOWN.
- ( motor whirs )
- ( humming )
HELLO, CHAIR.
HOW YOU BEEN?
- ( gun cocks )
- OH, WHAA!
( whimpers )
- LEGATO, I AM THE ONE
THAT IS HUNTING YOU
THIS TIME.
I WILL FIND YOU
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
YEAH, RIGHT!
- ( relieved sigh )
- IT SOUNDS REAL COOL
IN MY HEAD,
BUT IN REALITY,
I HAVEN'T GOT A CLUE
AS TO HOW I'M GOING TO FIND HIM.
- ( men grumble )
- OH, MAN, WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
- ( driver hums )
- ( sighs )
NOT ONLY THAT,
THE MORE TIME I HAVE
TO THINK ABOUT IT,
THE MORE FRIGHTENING IT BECOMES.
AND NOW MY KNEES ARE STARTING
TO KNOCK TOGETHER.
- ( humming continues )
- OH, MAN! I ACTUALLY
HAVE TO FIGHT THIS GUY!
HOW CAN I POSSIBLY
WIN SUCH A BATTLE
OR EVEN HAVE A CHANCE
TO SURVIVE A FIGHT
WITH A GUY WHO SMILES
WITH THOSE EVIL EYES?!
THE ANSWER IS I CAN'T.
I'M GONNA BE SLAUGHTERED,
THAT'S ALL.
IT'S NOT EVEN FUNNY.
- HMM? HMM? HMM?
- I SHOULD JUST BACK OUT!
THAT'S WHAT I SHOULD DO,
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, YEAH, FOR ONCE,
I'M RIGHT.  YEAH.
- YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT ONE THING.
YOU'RE NOT FUNNY.
YOU CHANGE YOUR TUNE
FASTER THAN RADIO STATIONS.
- YEAH, LIFE OUGHT TO BE FUN,
AFTER ALL, RIGHT?
( chews noisily )
HEY, THAT'S SUPER TASTY, MISTER.
I'LL HAVE ANOTHER SALMON
SANDWICH, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
HMM?
- UH, UH.
AUGUSTA.
- ( gasps )
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU
AT AUGUSTA, VASH THE STAMPEDE.
YOU WILL ACKNOWLEDGE
MY REQUEST IMMEDIATELY.
IF YOU DO NOT
MEET MY REQUEST,
THIS IS A SAMPLE
OF WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
- DON'T!
- ( gunshot )
- Men: ( shouting )
- WHY? WHO DID THIS?
THERE'S NO BLOOD.
- HUH? WHAT? DO YOU
ACTUALLY KNOW HIM?
THIS GUY, YOU KNOW HIM?!
( resumes humming )
- IT MUST BE HIM.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE
CAPABLE OF DOING THIS.
LEGATO.
- YOU CALLED HIM?
HE'S YOUR FRIEND?
HEY, IS HE YOUR FRIEND?
- ( thinking )
DO YOU WANT ME THERE SO BAD
YOU WOULD KILL THE INNOCENT
TO GET ME?!
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL GO THERE, LEGATO.
I'LL FACE YOU
ON YOUR HOME GROUND.
- HEY, WHO ARE YOU?
- HUH?
- Vash:  ME?
WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
- ( messenger panting )
- Bartender:
HEY, EASY THERE, PAL.
WHERE'S THE FIRE?
- LISTEN, IT'S--
IT'S VASH THE STAMPEDE.
HE'S HERE, I'M TELLING YOU.
- ( men mutter )
- ( worried chatter )
- OH MY GOSH,
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- YEAH, HE'S RUNNING RAMPANT
THROUGH AUGUSTA,
BLASTING AWAY WITH THAT
BIG SILVER GUN OF HIS.
- IT'S TRUE.
THAT CRAZY BASTARD'S
GONNA DO TO AUGUSTA
WHAT HE DID TO JULY.
- WELL, IT'S A GOOD THING
WE FOUND HIM.
- HMM.  WHAT IN THE HELL
COULD THAT MAN
POSSIBLY BE THINKING?
- ( gunshots )
- MY NAME IS...
VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- VASH?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
FORGIVE THE LACK OF WARNING,
BUT I'M AFRAID IT'S TIME
FOR MY DAILY MASSACRE.
AND IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE
I'M THE REAL THING,
TAKE A LONG LOOK AT ME
AND START FREAKING OUT.
OBSERVE MY RED COAT,
MY LOVELY BLONDE LOCKS.
AND IF YOU'RE
STILL HAVING DOUBTS,
CHECK OUT MY 100%
ACCURATE GUNMANSHIP.
- ( gunshot )
- OH, HE'S GOING TO KILL US!
- ( meows )
- ( gunfire )
- ( panicked chatter )
- IF YOU PEOPLE
DON'T WANT TO DIE TODAY,
GET AT LEAST 100 ILES
AWAY FROM THIS PLACE
AS FAST AS YOU CAN
AND LIVE
HAPPILY EVER AFTER!
FINALLY, THAT'S
THE LAST OF THEM.
WHY COULDN'T THAT
NIHILISTIC JERK
HAVE PICKED
A BETTER LOCATION?
I USED UP ALL MY ENERGY
JUST CHASING PEOPLE OUT.
I'M POOPED.
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
IT REMINDS ME
OF THE LAST TIME.
( gasps )
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT HERE.
I'M NOT SURE-- HUH?
- ( dripping )
- BLOOD!
( gasps )
- DO YOU LIKE
MY DECORATIONS?
IN THIS GAME, LOSERS
DON'T GET TO GO HOME.
THEY GO TO HELL.
- DID YOU KILL THEM?
- I AM THE FIFTH GUNG-HO-GUN.
MY NAME IS E.G. MINE.
- DID YOU KILL THEM
OR NOT?!
- DAMN, YOU ARE A NOISY ONE,
AREN'T YOU?
WHAT IF I DID,
CHICKEN SHIT?
YOU DON'T SEEM TO
WANT TO KILL ANYONE.
SO SOMEONE HAD TO STEP UP
AND COVER YOUR ASS.
AND BESIDES, BLONDIE,
YOU HAVE FALLEN
INTO MY COURT.
- GEE, AREN'T YOU
THE POETIC ONE?
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT
I ONLY HAVE TWO CHOICES?
TO DIE OR TO LET DIE?!
- WHOA, COWBOY, DON'T BE
SUCH A DRAMA QUEEN.
ONLY ONE MORE HAS TO DIE.
JUST STAND THERE
LIKE A GOOD BOY.
AS SOON AS I TAKE YOU DOWN,
IT'LL ALL BE OVER!
- ( gun cocks )
- WHAT?!
HUH?
- ( grunts )
- WH-- WHAT'S GOING ON?
THAT BASTARD IS TRYING TO
CUT IN ON MY ACTION.
- HAD I NOT CHOSEN TO DISPATCH
MY SABER AT THIS TIME,
THIS SITUATION MAY HAVE
ESCALATED INTO A REAL PROBLEM.
YOU WOULD HAVE AT LEAST
BEEN KNOCKED SENSELESS
BY YOUR HUMANOID TYPHOON,
THERE.
- SAY WHAT?
- WELL, NOW IT'S
GETTING INTERESTING.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
THE FAVORITE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- FORGIVE MY LACK
OF MANNERS.
ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM THE NINTH
GUNG-HO-GUN OF JIGENZAN.
TRAINED BY THE MASTERS
OF THE ITTOU SCHOOL,
I AM RAI-DEI
THE BLADE.
I HOLD NO PERSONAL GRUDGE
AGAINST YOU,
BUT I WISH TO ENGAGE YOU
IN SHI-AI.
- SHI-AI?
I CAN'T READ THAT.
- ( wind whistles )
- HMPH.
IF YOU CANNOT READ JAPANESE,
THEN I'LL GIVE YOU
AN ABBREVIATED EXPLANATION.
IT'S A FIGHT
TO THE DEATH.
- WHAT'S IN IT FOR YOU?
YOU PLAYING ALONG WITH
LEGATO'S LITTLE FARCE AS WELL?
- I WOULD HAPPILY WALK
THE PATH OF CARNAGE
1,000 TIMES
AND 1,000 AGAIN
FOR THE MASTERY OF BUSHIDO.
- WHAT?
- BECAUSE THERE IS SOMETHING
ONLY VISIBLE
WHEN YOU STAND BEFORE
THE DEATH OF THE ABYSS.
I BELIEVE YOU HAVE
SEEN THIS TOO, HAVE YOU NOT?
- I HAVEN'T SEEN
ANYTHING THERE AT ALL,
EXCEPT MY OWN FEAR.
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
I THINK YOU SHOULD EXPERIENCE...
( grunts )
THAT MENTAL STATE.
- ( metal clinks )
- COME ON, NOW.
IT'S MY JOB TO
SLICE AND DICE THIS GUY.
- RIDICULOUS.
IT WOULD APPEAR
YOU SIMPLY DID NOT HEAR
WHAT I TOLD YOU
JUST A FEW MINUTES AGO.
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
I DIDN'T.
HUH? WHAT?
- YOUR MATCH WAS QUITE OVER
BEFORE MY ARRIVAL.
THAT FAST GUNMANSHIP,
WORDS FAIL
TO DESCRIBE
ITS GREATNESS.
THAT MAN WAS NEVER AN OPPONENT
TO BE HUMBLED BY YOU.
YOU WERE COMPLETELY
OUT OF YOUR LEAGUE.
YOUR TURN IS OVER.
- NO!
- TAKE HEART IN THE FACT
THAT YOU MAY HAVE SERVED
TO AMUSE HIM
FOR A MOMENT.
- ( grunts )
- YOU SLIME!
- YES, LET IT BURN WITHIN YOU.
I FEEL IT
BUILD AND FESTER.
THE ANGRY AURA RELEASED
THROUGH YOUR EVERY PORE,
MY KNEES ARE SHAKING.
THAT ALONE MAKES MY TRIP
TO THIS PLACE WORTHWHILE.
IT IS THE SOURCE
OF MY GREATEST PLEASURE.
- COME ON.
- I'M IN YOUR DEBT.
READY?
- ( metal scratches )
- ( grunts )
- ( gunshots )
- H'YAH!
IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
CAUSE ME REAL HARM!
- YOU NEVER HEARD OF
WARRIOR'S COMPASSION?
I CAN'T HIT YOU IN ANY WAY
IF IT'D KILL YOU.
- QUITE THE ARROGANCE.
A REAL EYESORE.
IT BLURS MY PATH
TO SPIRITUAL AWARENESS.
- MY FRIEND, PEOPLE DON'T CHANGE
THEIR WAYS THAT EASILY.
- HA HA! YOU ACTUALLY
THINK WE'RE PEOPLE?
ABSURD!
- HUH?
- YOU AND I ARE MEN,
YET NOT OF MEN.
WE ARE DARK,
DIABOLICAL PUPPETS.
WHAT WE ARE
ARE DEMONS!
( screams )
- ( metal scratching )
- ( rumbling )
- WOW, WHAT IS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT'S DEFINITELY
NOT A GOOD THING.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
DO YOU THINK IT'S VASH?
WE'VE GOT TO HELP HIM.
LET'S GO!
- WAIT, MERYL!
- HUH?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- WE CAN'T THIS TIME.
MR. VASH SAID IT'S TOO BIG
FOR US TO HANDLE.
THIS IS SERIOUSLY DANGEROUS.
- I'M WELL AWARE
OF THE DANGER, MILLY.
- MERYL!
- ( pants )
WHY DON'T YOU STOP
WASTING TIME HERE
AND FIGHT ME
LIKE YOU MEAN IT?!
AH! FIGHT ME!
- ( metal scratches )
- ( groans )
NOW, THAT WAS
A HUGE SHOCKWAVE.
WELL, NO BIG DEAL.
NOTHING I CAN'T DODGE.
- H'YAH!
- ( bullets clink )
- CAN'T YOU MAKE
THOSE BULLETS HIT ME, HUH?!
- ( metal scratches )
- HUH?
COME ON, MAMA'S BOY!
- ( gasps )
- COMPASSION IN
THE HEAT OF BATTLE?!
- ( groans )
- THIS IS A GROSS
DISAPPOINTMENT.
- ( coughs )
- AH!
( groans )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
VASH THE STAMPEDE,
IS THIS ALL YOU AMOUNT TO?
- I SEE ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
TELL ME! AT LEAST
GIVE ME AN ANSWER,
TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE SEEING
RIGHT NOW, AT THIS MOMENT!
TELL ME!
- ( groans )
- Legato: DO YOU INTEND TO DIE,
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- ( gasps )
- THE TIME HAS COME
FOR YOU TO USE IT.
- ( straining )
- GO AHEAD, USE IT.
- ( strains )
- USE IT.
IT'S SOMETHING
ONLY YOU CAN DO.
USE IT! QUICKLY!
- STOP IT, STOP IT!
STOP IT, STOP IT,
STOP IT!
STOP!
- COWARD.  I CANNOT BELIEVE
HE'S BEGGING FOR HIS LIFE.
( gasps )
WHAT? WHAT IS THAT?
- NO, PLEASE DON'T DO THAT.
NOT THE LIGHT!
- OH MY GOD.
- MR. VASH MEANT WHAT HE SAID.
JUST LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
- WHERE IS HE?
WE'VE GOT TO FIND HIM.
( gasping )
- MERYL, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- LET GO OF ME! LET GO OF ME
RIGHT NOW, MILLY!
- ( gasping )
- PUT ME DOWN.
MILLY, I WANT TO GO BACK.
WAIT, I HAVE
TO GO BACK THERE.
- ( static )
- WHAT IS THIS
STRANGE PHENOMENON?
IS THIS SOME SORT OF
TWISTED CHRISTIAN SCIENCE?
( gasps )
- ( screams )
( strains )
STOP, STOP IT NOW!
AH! STOP IT!
- WHAT IS THIS
INDESCRIBABLE HORROR
COURSING THROUGH
MY ENTIRE BODY?
IS THIS IT?
IS THIS THE MOMENT
I'VE BEEN SEEKING?
WILL I REALLY REACH
SPIRITUAL AWARENESS?
NO! THIS THING BEFORE ME--
- RUN! RUN AWAY NOW!
- ( pants )
( screams )
- RUN!
- WHAT? WHAT IS THAT?!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT THING!
- STOP IT! STOP IT!
- ( charge builds )
PLEASE, STOP IT!
- ( gunfire )
- ( screaming )
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( screams echo )
- WHAT THE--
- ( high-pitched whistle )
- ( silence )
( silence continues )
- ( rumbling )
- WHAT IS THAT
HORRIFIC LIGHT?
IS HE THE ONE CREATING THAT?
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- YES, THIS IS
THE SECOND TIME.
THE FIRST WAS A GREAT EXPLOSION
WHICH TOOK JULY 23 YEARS AGO.
( chuckles )
( slurps )
- MILLY, PLEASE LET ME GO.
I HAVE TO GO BACK.
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
BESIDES, IF YOU DIE,
YOU'LL NEVER SEE HIM AGAIN.
- ( gasps )
- ( both scream )
- ( wind rushes )
- MERYL, LOOK!
- ( gasps )
A HOLE IN THE MOON.
- ( ragged breathing )
I FELT THE TERROR.
- Wolfwood: ONLY YOU CAN
SURVIVE SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- ( grunts )
WHO-- WHO ARE YOU?
- WHAT HAPPENED TO
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- DAMN.
- IF WE ACT QUICKLY,
WE MAY BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT THAT MAN,
THAT HORRIBLE
DEVIL OF A MAN.
VASH THE STAMPEDE
IS TOO DANGEROUS
TO BE LEFT ALIVE.
IF YOU HELP ME,
WE CAN DO THIS TOGETHER.
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
- ( gun cocks )
- HUH? ARE YOU INSANE?
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
YOU AND I ARE-- WE COULD--
- I'M SORRY.
SURE, NOBODY DIED
FROM THE BLAST,
BUT JUST LOOK AT THIS.
( blows smoke )
ANOTHER TOWN IN RUBBLE.
IS THIS THE PATH
YOU HAVE CHOSEN?
IS THIS IT,
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- Man #4: HEY, DID YOU
HEAR THE RUMOR?
ABOUT HOW THE HUMANOID TYPHOON
SHOWED UP IN AUGUSTA?
- Man #5: I SURE DID.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY
HE MANAGED TO DESTROY
THE ENTIRE CITY
ALL BY HIMSELF.
FIRST JULY AND NOW AUGUSTA.
WHAT IN THE HELL
CAN THAT MANIAC BE THINKING?
HE'S COMPLETELY
OUT OF CONTROL.
IT'S JUST GETTING
OUT OF HAND.
THE BOUNTY ON HIS HEAD
WILL ONLY GET BIGGER NOW.
AND WHO'S TO SAY HE WON'T
DESTROY OUR TOWN
AND ANY OTHERS?
- Man #4: I'M STARTING
TO BELIEVE IT'S ALL HIS FAULT
THAT WE'RE STUCK
ON THIS PLANET.
NOT TO MENTION ALL OF THE
OTHER CRAP I'VE HEARD ABOUT HIM.
BUT THERE'S MORE.
THEY'RE SAYING NOW
THAT HE'S ALSO
SOLELY RESPONSIBLE
FOR THAT BIG
HOLE IN THE MOON.
IT MAKES ME SICK
JUST TO THINK ABOUT IT.
- Man #6: WHAT ARE YOU NUTS?
THERE ISN'T A MAN ALIVE
WHO CAN PULL OFF
A STUNT LIKE THAT.
- Man #4: COOL YOUR JETS,
WILL YOU?
I'M JUST TELLING YOU
WHAT I HEARD.
I'M NOT MAKING IT UP.
- Man #6: HEY, AT THIS POINT,
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST
BE THANKFUL
THAT WE'RE ALL STILL ALIVE.
- Man #5: YEAH,
YOU SAID IT.
- ( cries )
- ( door opens )
- UM, MERYL,
WE RECEIVED A LETTER
FROM THE MAIN OFFICE.
- IT'S ABOUT TIME.
WELL, THEIR CORRESPONDENCE
CERTAINLY IS SLOW.
WE'VE BEEN SITTING HERE
WAITING FOR TWO WEEKS.
"MERYL STRYFE
AND MILLY THOMPSON
ARE TO RETURN TO
THE MAIN OFFICE IMMEDIATELY.
FURTHERMORE, IN A CONFERENCE
HELD THE OTHER DAY,
IT WAS DECIDED THAT
VASH THE STAMPEDE
WILL BE DESIGNATED AS
MANKIND'S FIRST OFFICIAL
HUMAN DISASTER.
FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
NO MATTER WHAT KIND
OF DAMAGE HE CAUSES,
THE BERNADELLI
INSURANCE SOCIETY
WILL BE--"
"WILL BE--"
"WILL BE...
UNINVOLVED."
THIS CAN'T BE.
( cries )
WHAT DO THEY THINK WILL CHANGE
BY MAKING THIS DECISION NOW?
( cries )
- OH, MERYL.
- ( sobbing wails )
- MR. VASH, YOU'RE A JERK.
YOU MADE MERYL CRY.
I'LL NEVER
EVER FORGIVE YOU FOR THIS.
- ( wind rushes )
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Young Vash:
REM TOLD ME
THAT SOMEONE SHE LOVED
DIED ON EARTH.
SHE TOLD ME
SHE BOARDED THIS SHIP
SO SHE COULD START OVER.
WHAT DOES IT FEEL LIKE
TO HAVE SOMEONE YOU LOVE
DIE?
I TRIED THINKING OF
WHAT IT WOULD BE LIKE
IF REM DIED.
WHEN I DID, HOT WATER
CAME OUT OF MY EYES
AND IT WOULDN'T STOP
FOR A LONG TIME.
REM, I'LL ALWAYS
BE THERE FOR YOU.
I WON'T LEAVE YOU ALONE.