- ( theme music playing )
♪ OH! ♪
- ( wind blowing )
- ( gunfire )
- ( coughing )
- Wolfwood: DON'T
DRINK THIS STUFF.
YOU HAVE NO TOLERANCE FOR IT.
IT'S DISRESPECTFUL TO THE BOOZE
TO DRINK IT LIKE THAT.
( gulps ) AH!
I'M IMPRESSED.
HOOCH IS BRAND NAME.
HMM.
( sighs ) LOOK.
WE DID EVERYTHING WE COULD.
YOU'VE GOTTA STOP
BEATING YOURSELF UP.
IF YOU HAVE TO CALL
IT SOMETHING, CALL IT DESTINY.
- DON'T TRY TO JUSTIFY IT
BY LABELING IT
WITH A SIMPLE WORD.
SO MANY DIED
AND THEY WON'T BE COMING BACK.
I CAN'T STAND IT.
IT'S MORE THAN I CAN BEAR.
- ( rapid gunfire )
- Vash: I KILLED HIM.
I KILLED BRAD.
- VASH, IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
I'M SURE THERE WAS NOTHING
YOU COULD'VE DONE TO SAVE HIM.
( crying )
I'M SORRY.
- EVERYONE WHO TOUCHES ME
ENDS UP DYING.
- THAT VERY WELL MAY BE,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT
AT THIS POINT.
YOU'VE STILL GOT
SOMEWHERE ELSE YOU HAVE TO GO.
DON'T YOU AGREE?
- I AGREE.
I'M NOT DONE YET.
WHATEVER IT TAKES,
I HAVE TO FACE HIM.
- Wolfwood: AH, THERE IT IS!
WE'RE HERE.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
- YAY, TEAM!
I'LL HAVE A PUDDING A LA MODE
AND A MOCHA FROSTY CREAM!
- AM I CORRECT IN ASSUMING
THAT MEANS YOU'RE HUNGRY?
- AMAZING. HOW COULD
YOU TELL, MR. WOLFWOOD?
- I KNOW ABSOLUTELY
EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU, HONEY.
- WELL, FORGET IT, DEAR.
I'M AFRAID SEXTUPLETS ARE
OUT OF THE QUESTION.
- ( laughs )
NICE COMEBACK.
- ( both laugh )
- Meryl: VASH?
- YEAH, MERYL?  WHAT'S UP?
- UH, UMM... NOTHING.
- Wolfwood: HELLO!
IS ANYBODY IN THERE?
HELLO?
- WHO'S THERE?
- ( gun rattles )
- WE'RE POOR, UNFORTUNATE,
HUNGRY TRAVELERS
AIMLESSLY WANDERING
THE DESERT.
- EXCUSE ME, WOULD IT BE
ALL RIGHT IF WE CAME INSIDE?
- I'LL LET YOU IN...
FOR 300,000 DOUBLE DOLLARS.
- OOH!
- 300,000?!
- EXACTLY. I SAID IT 'CAUSE
I KNOW YOU DON'T HAVE IT.
IT'S MY LITTLE WAY OF SAYING
YOU'RE NOT WELCOME HERE.
- ( guns cock )
- WHY THE SUDDEN HOSTILITY?
WE DON'T MEAN YOU ANY HARM.
- YEAH, IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE DANGEROUS OR ANYTHING.
I'M MERYL STRYFE
FROM THE BERNARDELLI--
- ( gunshot )
- OH!
- I DON'T CARE IF YOU'RE
FROM BERNARDELLI OR THE FEDS!
MY ANSWER IS FINAL!
YOU'RE NOT COMING IN,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
- HEY, YOU'RE NOT BEING
VERY FAIR ABOUT THIS.
- LET'S GO.
- HUH?  HOW COME?
- THEY DON'T WANT US
AND WE HAVE TO RESPECT THEM.
THE PEOPLE OF THIS TOWN
PROBABLY HAVE A GOOD REASON.
IT'S NOT JUST A WHIM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'S JUST LEAVING.
ISN'T HE OVER IT YET?
- WHAT?
HI, CAN I HELP YOU?
- ( gasps )
- Vash:
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- NOW NOW, AREN'T YOU GOING TO
SAY THANK YOU TO THE NICE MAN?
- ( grunts )
- SAY, "THANK YOU."
COME ON, NOW.
- THANK YOU, SIR.
- NOW THAT WAS EASY,
WASN'T IT? HUH?
- HEY!  THERE'S ONLY
DESERT THAT WAY!
- LET'S GO. I THINK WE NEED
TO TAKE A LITTLE SIDE TRIP.
- QUIT STANDING AROUND,
WASTING TIME.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- COME ON, HURRY UP.
- ( Wolfwood knocks on door )
ANYBODY HOME?
- ( yelps ) WHAT?
- GET HIM! GET THE
HELL OUT OF HERE!
- ( grunts )
HEY, WAIT! STOP IT!
WE'RE NOT MAD
AT YOU!  HEY!
WE JUST TURNED AWAY
FROM THAT TOWN LIKE YOU!
NOW WE JUST WANNA STAY HERE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
COME ON, WE WON'T HURT YOU.
I PROMISE.
PLEASE, JUST LISTEN TO ME.
I'M NOT ASKING FOR A FAVOR.
HERE, YOU WANNA TRADE?
- ( kids gasp, cheering )
- Wolfwood: HMM.
- Girl: MOVE OUT OF THE WAY!
- WELL, I GUESS
THIS MEANS WE HAVE A DEAL.
- Girl:
GO AWAY.  GIMME!
- MR. WOLFWOOD, THOSE ARE
OUR EMERGENCY RATIONS.
- THIS IS AN EMERGENCY,
ISN'T IT?
- EH... HUH?
- ( Vash laughs )
- I WOULD AGREE WITH THAT.
THIS IS DEFINITELY AN EMERGENCY.
- ( kids chattering )
- REALLY?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
APPARENTLY, I SEEM TO BE
OUTNUMBERED THIS TIME.
- Child: MMM!
- ( laughs ) YAY!
- MILLY?
- HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- OH, I'M SORRY.
YOU WANT SOME TOO, MERYL?
THEY'RE REALLY TASTY.
- ( laughs )
- GIMME SOME OF THAT!
- NO, I WANT IT, I WANT IT!
- Wolfwood: I SEE. SO THESE
KIDS ARE ALL ORPHANS, HUH?
- Boy: YEAH,
IT'S REALLY JUST A COINCIDENCE.
IT HAPPENED BY CHANCE WE ALL
ENDED UP GATHERING HERE
IN THE SAME PLACE
- IT'S UNUSUAL, BUT THAT SORT OF
THING HAS BEEN KNOWN TO HAPPEN.
- YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN
A GREAT HELP, ACTUALLY.
WE DIDN'T HAVE MUCH TO EAT AND
YOU CAME AT A REALLY GOOD TIME.
- NO BIG DEAL.
JUST LENDING A HELPING HAND.
- SO I WAS JUST WONDERING:
WHY IS IT THEY WON'T
LET YOU INTO THE TOWN?
- THEY WON'T LET
ANY OUTSIDERS IN,
EVEN IF THEY'RE ONLY CHILDREN.
THE TOWNSFOLK ARE FRIGHTENED.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
- Wolfwood: WHY?
- I'M NOT SURE.
BUT I DO KNOW
THAT EVERY TOWN IN THIS REGION
HAS BEEN ABANDONED.
WELL, EXCEPT FOR KEYBAS
OVER THERE.
MY TOWN WAS ABANDONED, TOO,
THE SAME WAY.
ONE DAY WITHOUT WARNING,
EVERYONE JUST STOPPED
WHAT THEY WERE DOING
AND THEY BEGAN TO WALK.
THEY DIDN'T TAKE
A THING WITH THEM
AND THEY DIDN'T SAY
A WORD AS THEY LEFT.
- ( clatters )
- HUH?
DAD!  DAD, WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
SAY SOMETHING!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?  HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU ALL DOING?
DAD!  HUH?
MOM!  MOM!
DAD!
THEY ALL JUST LEFT HOME,
WALKED OUT OF TOWN LIKE
THEY WERE BLIND AND DUMB.
THEY LOOKED LIKE ZOMBIES,
LIKE SOMETHING WAS
CONTROLLING THEM.
ALL OF THE OTHERS WENT
THROUGH THE SAME THING
WITH THEIR PARENTS.
THEY ALL LEFT
AT THE SAME TIME.
- Vash:
TELL ME ONE THING:
DURING THE TIME
THIS WAS HAPPENING,
DID YOU SEE ANYONE OTHER
THAN THE TOWNSFOLK THERE?
- NO.  NUH-UH.
BUT ACTUALLY,
I DID HEAR A STRANGE VOICE.
- WHAT DID IT SAY?
- I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT HAD TO DO
WITH THEM LEAVING HOME.
IT SAID, "THIS IS WHAT YOU GET
FOR TAKING SO LONG."
- Vash's voice: IT'S HIM.
- Wolfwood's voice: BOY, HE
NEVER DOES GET A BREAK, DOES HE?
POOR SAP.
- SO WHAT ARE
YOU GONNA DO NOW, VASH?
YOU GOING IN OR WHAT?
- ( kids grunting )
- Both: HUH?
- Kids: HUH?
- ( Vash chuckles )
- ( both sigh )
- WHAT I SAY?
- NO KID IS EVER GONNA WARM UP
TO A GUY THAT WALKS AROUND
WITH AN EMPTY SMILE.
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS
HAND THAT UP TO ME?
I'LL BE HAPPY
TO CARRY IT FOR YOU.
- Boy: LET'S GO.
- HUH?
- DID YOU SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT KIDS WARMING UP?
- ALL RIGHT, SHUT UP.
IT'S JUST THAT THESE GUYS
ARE A LITTLE BIT SHY,
THAT'S ALL.
- ( claps )
- Both: HUH?
- YOU TWO ARE SO GOOD!
YOU'RE GREAT AT HELPING OUT.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- ( kids giggling )
- Both: HUH.
- Meryl: SO IF YOU CUT IT
WITH A KNIFE ALONG THE TENDON
AT A RIGHT ANGLE LIKE THIS
AND SPRINKLE ON A LOT OF PEPPER,
IT'LL ACTUALLY LAST
A LOT LONGER THAN YOU THINK
AND GUESS WHAT--
IT'LL TASTE BETTER TOO.
- Kids: REALLY?
- HUH?
WOMEN ARE A MARVEL,
AREN'T THEY?
- THAT'S FOR SURE.
HEY THERE!
WHAT YOU COOKING, GUYS?
- Meryl: THAT'S OUR SECRET
UNTIL SUPPERTIME.
- Kids: YEAH!
- Vash: OH JEEZ, HOW COULD
YOU BE SO COLD?
- THAT GUY,
HE IS NOTHING BUT TROUBLE.
DIG IN, EVERYONE.
- ( laughter )
- Meryl: HELP YOURSELF.
- ( chattering)
- THIS IS YUMMY!
- DELICIOUS.  THANK YOU.
- HEY, DON'T SPILL IT.
- ( laughter )
- WELL, THEY'RE ALL
FAST ASLEEP AT LAST.
- I'M GUESSING IT'S A LONG TIME
SINCE THEY WERE ABLE TO RELAX.
- JUST LOOK
AT THOSE HAPPY FACES.
- ( boy crying )
MOMMY.  DADDY.
- ( door creaks, closes )
Vash's voice: IF I TAKE TOO
LONG, THEY'LL MAKE ANOTHER MOVE.
STILL...
WE CAN'T JUST
LEAVE THESE KIDS.
HMM?
- QUIT BEING SO
SERIOUS AND CHEER UP.
COME ON, LET'S HAVE A DRINK.
- HUH?
HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?!
- ( cocks )
- HUH? ( screams )
- what was that?
- ( people murmuring )
- HEARD A GUN GO OFF!
- WHERE'D IT COME FROM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
LET'S GO CHECK IT OUT.
- HUH?
- ( rock music playing )
- ( snoring )
- ( ground rumbling )
- ( gun rattles, cocks )
- ( gunfire )
- ( screaming )
- EVERYONE, GET AWAY
FROM THE WINDOWS?
- MERYL, WHY ARE
THEY SHOOTING AT US?
- I SAID GET AWAY
FROM THE WINDOWS!
- EVERYONE ALL RIGHT IN HERE?
- GET DOWN!
- ( kids crying )
- WHOA!
- COME ON OUT!
WE KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE!
IF YOU AREN'T OUT HERE
BY THE TIME I COUNT TO 10,
WE'RE COMING IN AFTER YOU
AND WE WILL SHOOT TO KILL!
- WELL, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
- 10, NINE...
- ONLY WAY OUT
OF THIS MISUNDERSTANDING
IS TO REASON WITH THEM.
- REASON WITH THOSE HOTHEADS?
ARE YOU NUTS?
CAN'T YOU COME UP WITH
ANYTHING BETTER THAN THAT?
- ...FIVE, FOUR...
- NEVER MIND, I'LL GO ALONE.
- THREE...
- ( groans )
- ...TWO, ONE!
TIME'S UP!  HUH?
( humphs )
- HI. WE'RE NOT EXACTLY SURE
WHAT WE DID TO UPSET YOU FELLAS.
WE MEANT NO HARM. WOULD YOU MIND
FILLING US IN A LITTLE BIT?
- YOU'RE JUST PRETENDING
TO BE NICE TO THESE KIDS
FOR CAMOUFLAGE,
YOU PIECE OF TRASH.
I DON'T BUY YOUR CRAP
FOR A MINUTE!
( grunts )
- I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- ( both grunt )
- DON'T PLAY DUMB
WITH US, SPIKY BOY.
YOU AND YOUR PALS
ARE THE ONLY OUTSIDERS
ANYWHERE NEAR TOWN.
- WAIT, THIS IS A FALSE ALARM.
( grunts )
- WE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
THIS IS ALL SOME KIND
OF TERRIBLE MISTAKE.
- Man: OH YEAH, YOU'RE A REAL
MR. NICE GUY, AREN'T YOU?
JEFFREY WAS KILLED
AND HE WAS MY BEST FRIEND!
- ( both gasp )
- Wolfwood: WHY YOU
STUPID BUNCH
OF BLUNDERING IGNORAMUSES.
- WAIT, STOP.
- ( groans )
GIVE THE GOODY-GOODY ROUTINE
A REST, WILL YOU, VASH?
- ( both groaning )
- PLEASE, JUST LISTEN
TO WHAT WE HAVE TO SAY.
- YOU WORTHLESS PIECE OF SHIT!
- ( both gasp )
- YOU HAVE TO HEAR ME OUT.
- ( ground rumbling )
- ( all shouting )
- WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
- WHOA!
- WHOA, HOLD ON!
EASY EASY EASY!
- ( men scream )
- ( gasps )
- ( both gasp )
- Man: OH MY GOD!
WHAT ARE WORMS DOING HERE?
- ( screeches )
- ( screams )
- BUT WHY WOULD THEY--
- ( whimpering )
- WAIT A MINUTE!
ISN'T THIS ENTIRE AREA
MADE UP OF SOLID BEDROCK?
- IT WOULD HAVE TO BE.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY THEY
CAN BUILD A HOUSE ON IT.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE?
- BEATS THE HECK OUT OF ME.
THERE'S ONE THING
FOR SURE, THOUGH:
WE'RE NOT SAFE HERE.
WE'LL DIVERT THEIR ATTENTION.
YOU TWO GET THE KIDS OUT.
- OKAY, UNDERSTOOD.
YOU WILL LET US
INTO YOUR TOWN, WON'T YOU?
- YEAH.
- ( cocks )
- NOW THAT TAKES CARE OF THEM.
- IT'S TIME FOR US TO GET GOING.
- ( clicks )
- HEY, GOOD LUCK.
- THANKS.
- ( laughing )
- Vash: OVER HERE!
COME AND GET IT, BOYS!
- ( screaming )
- ( screeches )
- NICE WORMIE!
- THEY'RE CATCHING UP,
YOU IDIOT!
- ( grunts )
- ( gun fires )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
CAN'T I KILL THOSE EITHER?
- YOU CAN'T KILL THOSE, NO!
- ( screeches )
- WHY DO WE ALWAYS HAVE
TO DO EVERYTHING YOUR WAY?
- ( both screaming )
- WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
PRETTY WELL ORGANIZED
FOR ORDINARY SANDWORMS.
- YEAH, I AGREE.
HE'S OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
- SOME ROTTEN LOWLIFE
MUST BE SITTING BACK,
WATCHING AS THEY DO
HIS DIRTY WORK FOR HIM.
- DO YOU SUPPOSE...
- ( screeching )
- HOW DID THE WORMS
GET INSIDE THE TOWN?
- ( all screaming )
- Vash:
CLIMB THE BUILDINGS, HURRY!
- Women: HUH?
- IF YOU CLIMB HIGH ENOUGH,
THE WORMS WON'T BE ABLE
TO GET TO YOU!
- Meryl: RIGHT, LET'S GO!
- ( kids crying )
- OH!  WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU HURT?
- ( crying )
- OH.  HEY, MIKE, COME BACK.
- I'M SORRY!
- I'M ON IT.
- ( gun cocks )
- ( fires crackling )
- THIS IS SO HORRIBLE.
- OUR WHOLE TOWN'S
DESTROYED NOW.
- ( sighs )
WHERE'S MILLY AND THE BOY?
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
THEY'RE OVER WITH WOLFWOOD.
- YEAH, THEY'LL BE
ALL RIGHT THEN.
- Vash's voice:
BUT WHAT IS THIS FEELING?
I KEEP HAVING
THE STRANGEST SENSATION,
LIKE SOMETHING IS
OUT OF PLACE.
- ( rumbling )
( screeching )
- ( men screaming )
- DAMN. THERE ARE
TOO MANY OF THEM HERE.
- ( rumbling )
- ( Vash gasps )
- ( man screams )
- Milly: WAIT! ( laughs )
I CAUGHT YOU
FAIR AND SQUARE, HUH?
- ( crying )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, THERE'S
NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF.
- ( humphs )
- ( worm screeching )
- Wolfwood: RUN!
- ( grunts )
- ( screeching )
- ( kids scream )
- ( clicks )
- DAMN BULLETS.
- ( high-pitched whine )
- THAT'S IT.
- ( screeches )
- ( gunshot echoes )
- ( both whimper )
- HUH?
- ( both gasp )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- ( screeches )
- YOU WERE USING A
HIGH-FREQUENCY DEVICE
TO CONTROL THEM.
I WANT TO KNOW WHY.
THEY'RE YOUR OWN PEOPLE.
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO HURT THEM?
- ( laughs )
'CAUSE THEY'RE NOT MY PEOPLE.
- ( gun cocks )
- BECAUSE I AM A GUNG-HO GUN!
- ( gasps )
- I'M THE FOURTH
OF THE GUNG-HO GUNS.
I'M ZAZIE THE BEAST.
- YOU'RE KIDDING.
- ( crying )
- ( gun cocks )
- Zazie: DON'T CRY!
GOD, THAT IS SO ANNOYING.
THIS CONFIRMS
WHY I HATE CHILDREN.
THEY WHINE,
THEY GET DEPRESSED
AND THEY'LL ONLY BRUSH
THEIR TEETH WHEN THEY'RE TOLD
BECAUSE THEY'RE
TOO STUPID TO DO OTHERWISE.
THEY COMPLETELY LACK
ANY CONCEPT OF FREE WILL!
- ( gunshot )
- ( clatters )
- Zazie: YOU PROBABLY AREN'T
EVEN CAPABLE OF COMPREHENDING
WHY I WOULD CHOOSE TO DO
SOMETHING THIS INTRICATE.
- ( gasps )
- STOP IT!  NO!
- Boy:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BETE?
- MY NAME IS ZAZIE.
IT'S ZAZIE THE BEAST.
- YOU KNOW, THIS ISN'T
WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
- HUH?
- IT'S TRUE. I SAW YOU
CRYING THE OTHER NIGHT.
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
THE DEMON HASN'T WON.
AT ONE POINT, YOU EVEN TRIED
TO CHEER ME ON IN SPITE OF HIM.
- WELL, THAT'S WHERE
YOU'RE WRONG.
DEMONS CAN BLOCK
THE CONSCIOUSNESS
AND MEMORY ON DEMAND.
- Vash: I DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
- ( growls )
- YOU WANT IT THIS WAY?
YOU'RE FORCING YOURSELF.
- GOODY TWO-SHOES IDIOT!
YOU DON'T KNOW WHO I AM!
- THAT'S FINE. BELIEVE
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU CAN JUST DIE, THINKING
YOUR PLEASANT LITTLE THOUGHTS.
- STOP THIS, BETE, RIGHT NOW!
- HUH?
( growling )
- ( gunshot )
- ( screams )
- ( gasps )
- ( breathing shakily )
-  HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?!
- WHY, WOLFWOOD?
IT DIDN'T HAVE
TO END LIKE THIS!
- KIDS ARE KIDS
AND THAT'S ONE THING.
THIS WAS NO KID.
HE WAS NOTHING BUT A DAMN DEMON.
AND IF I HADN'T SHOT HIM,
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN
YOU LYING THERE.
- BUT YOU'RE WRONG.
HE WASN'T GOING TO SHOOT ME.
- I SAVED YOUR ASS
YET ONE MORE TIME,
AND YOU COME AFTER ME
WITH YOUR CHILDISH BULLSHIT?!
- YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE KILLED HIM.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE WRONG.
- ( both grunt )
- WHAT OTHER ALTERNATIVE DO I
HAVE IF WE'RE GOING TO SURVIVE?
( gasps )
- Vash:
WE'RE SEARCHING FOR A PLACE
WHERE WE CAN LIVE
OUR LIVES IN PEACEFUL DAYS,
WITH NO WARS
AND NO STEALING.
A PLACE
THAT ISN'T RUN BY FEAR.
A PLACE WHERE
PEOPLE CAN LIVE
AND ACTUALLY TRUST
OTHER HUMAN BEINGS.
- ( scoffs )
I DON'T WANNA HEAR IT!
I DON'T NEED TO HEAR YOUR
IDEALISTIC DREAMS RIGHT NOW!
- OH.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: TO REALIZE
A MISTAKE, TO NOT LIE,
TO LOVE ONE ANOTHER,
TO NOT KILL.
THOSE ARE VERY SIMPLE THINGS,
BUT THESE TIMES
WON'T ALLOW FOR THEM.
THERE IS NO GREEN
ON THIS PLANET,
EVEN THOUGH WE WANT IT,
AND WANT IT SO BADLY.
A PLACE WHERE WE CAN LIVE
PEACEFUL DAYS WITH NO WARS,
NOR STEALING.
A SACRED PLACE
WHERE PEOPLE CAN LIVE
AS PEOPLE.
YES, THERE.
THAT PLACE IS CALLED...