- ( theme music playing )
♪ OH! ♪
- ( gunshot )
- Wolfwood:
I PICKED UP MY FIRST GUN
AT THE AGE OF SEVEN,
AND I SHOT.
I REMEMBER HOW
STRANGELY EASY IT WAS
TO PULL THE TRIGGER.
I ACTUALLY LAUGHED.
BECAUSE THAT ONE SHOT
WAS ALL IT TOOK
TO FINALLY SILENCE
THAT SICKENING
PIECE OF GARBAGE
WHO HAD THE NERVE
TO CALL HIMSELF MY GUARDIAN.
( chuckles )
IT WAS THAT SIMPLE.
AND SO,
I WAS FREE.
YES, TOMORROW THINGS
WOULD BE DIFFERENT.
( chuckles )
TOMORROW.
AS MUCH I WANTED
TO BELIEVE,
IT ONLY WENT FROM
BAD TO WORSE.
A VICIOUS CYCLE.
- Chapel: LIFE IS LIKE AN
INCESSANT SERIES OF PROBLEMS.
ALL SO DIFFICULT
WITH BRUTAL CHOICES
AND A TIME LIMIT.
THE SINGLE WORST THING
WE CAN DO
IS TO MAKE NO CHOICE
WHEN WE'RE WAITING FOR
THE ANSWER TO COME TO US.
YOU MUST MAKE THE BEST DECISION
IN A SPLIT SECOND.
WE ARE NOTHING LIKE GOD.
NOT ONLY ARE
OUR POWERS LIMITED,
WE SOMETIMES ARE DRIVEN
TO BECOME THE DEVIL HIMSELF.
- Wolfwood: I DIDN'T WANT
OTHER KIDS TO GROW UP LIKE ME,
SO I STARTED
MY OWN ORPHANAGE.
IT WAS GRATIFYING WORK.
I WAS ACTUALLY DOING SOMETHING
FOR THE GOOD OF OTHERS.
IT WAS MY PLACE OF
PEACE AND HAPPINESS.
YET SOMETIMES,
I STILL THINK TO MYSELF:
THERE'S NO PLACE WORSE
THAN THIS PLANET.
IT'S HORRIBLE HERE.
- ( wind blowing )
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
- Vash:
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU, KNIVES.
HOW CAN YOU ENJOY THIS?
- AW, SHIT.
THIS THING'S FILTHY.
( exhales )
- Vash: YOU'RE WRONG.
HE WASN'T GONNA SHOOT ME.
- Wolfwood: PLEASE. PLEASE
DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
THERE ARE EXTENUATING
CIRCUMSTANCES
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
( gasps )
( groans )
( sighs )
( grunts )
- YOU STILL NEED SOME WORK.
IT'S NOT HEALTHY
TO HESITATE,
BECAUSE EVERY TIME YOU DO,
YOU WEAR DOWN
A LITTLE MORE OF YOUR LIFE.
I'M SURE I TOLD YOU
THAT BEFORE, HAVEN'T I?
- WHY HAVE YOU COME HERE?
- APPARENTLY,
YOU'VE LOST SOME WEIGHT.
WHY, NICHOLAS?
- I'VE BEEN TRAVELING
WITH A REAL TROUBLEMAKER.
- IT'S NOT WISE TO DROWN
IN EACH OTHER'S PAIN.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO KILL THIS MAN NOW.
- BUT KNIVES SPECIFICALLY
TOLD ME TO BRING HIM BACK ALIVE.
THE ORDER WAS NOT
TO DESTROY HIM.
- I'M AFRAID THAT ORDER
HAS BEEN RETRACTED.
- WHAT ABOUT THE MONEY?
- DON'T WORRY.
IT WILL BE PAID AS PROMISED.
FOLLOW THROUGH
WITH YOUR MISSION,
AND I GUARANTEE THE LIVES
OF YOUR PRECIOUS
DECEMBER ORPHAN CHILDREN
UPON THE HOLY NAME OF
THE CHAPEL OF THE GUNG-HO GUNS.
AND AS OF NOW,
YOU TOO, MY FRIEND,
ARE ALSO A GUNG-HO GUN.
Chapel: DEAL WITH
THE SITUATION AS INSTRUCTED
AND YOU WILL INHERIT
MY TITLE.
- ( gasps )
- ( sighs )
- THE WAY HE LOOKED AT ME,
IT WAS AS THOUGH HE WAS
THE ONE WHO KILLED THE KID.
DAMN IT,
I'LL TAKE THE BLAME.
HIT ME IF YOU NEED TO.
THEN MAYBE AT LEAST I CAN--
- Milly: MR. PRIEST?
OH, GOOD.  I WAS HOPING
I'D FIND YOU HERE.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
BE HUNGRY,
SO MERYL AND I
MADE YOU SANDWICHES,
AND I'D BE VERY HAPPY
IF YOU'D EAT THEM.
OH, YEAH.  AND YOU TAKE
YOUR COFFEE BLACK, RIGHT?
- WHY HAVEN'T YOU
SAID ANYTHING?
- ANYTHING?
- ABOUT THE KID I
KILLED THE OTHER DAY.
- OHH.
OH, I JUST DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I'M SO CONFUSED.
BECAUSE WHAT
YOU SAID WAS RIGHT,
AND WHAT MR. VASH
SAID WAS TRUE TOO.
I DON'T LIKE IT WHEN
PEOPLE HAVE TO DIE.
- Wolfwood:
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE?
- I DON'T KNOW, REALLY.
- THAT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HIM.
EVEN IN SUCH AN
IMPOSSIBLE SITUATION,
HE KEEPS SAYING
THAT NOBODY HAD TO DIE.
HOW CAN HE BELIEVE THAT?
( sighs )
- THAT'S THE WAY
MR. VASH HAS ALWAYS BEEN.
I KNOW BECAUSE I'VE
WATCHED HIM FOR A LONG TIME.
HE'S LIVED BY THAT RULE
HIS WHOLE LIFE.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT TO HIM.
- "THOU SHALT NOT KILL,"
REMEMBER?
WHAT THE HELL KIND OF
CHURCH MAN ARE YOU ANYWAY?
COME ON.
- I'VE LIVED MY LIFE
VERY DIFFERENTLY FROM HIM,
AND I GUESS I HAVE TO
ACCEPT THAT.
I WAS SUPPOSED
TO GUIDE HIM.
I WAS ORDERED
TO PROTECT HIM.
IT WAS MY JOB
TO BE THERE FOR HIM.
BUT THE MISSION,
THE OBLIGATION...
IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYMORE.
I HONESTLY WANTED
TO SAVE HIM,
EVEN IF IT MEANT
KILLING A CHILD.
I ACTUALLY WANTED
TO SAVE HIM.
I HAD NO ALTERNATIVE.
I HAD TO CHOOSE
ONE OR THE OTHER.
( crying )
IT'S SO STRANGE.
WHERE DID I GO WRONG?
I'VE ALWAYS CHOSEN
THE RIGHT PATH...
HAVEN'T I?
( crying )
( sighs )
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE SO KIND.
- Milly:
YOU NEED YOUR STRENGTH.
PLEASE EAT THE SANDWICHES.
- Wolfwood: WILL YOU PLEASE
EAT THEM WITH ME?
- MILLY'S SO LATE
GETTING BACK TO HER ROOM.
- I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
WHAT SHOULD I SAY TO HIM?
REM...
- Wolfwood: ARE YOU LEAVING
WITHOUT SAYING GOOD-BYE?
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
HIT YOU THE OTHER DAY.
YOU DIDN'T DESERVE IT.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
MAYBE THERE WAS A WAY OUT
OF THAT PROBLEM.
MAYBE WHAT WE SHOULD HAVE DONE
WOULD HAVE BEEN SOMETHING LIKE--
- SHUT UP!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
- ( gasps )
- OUR LIVES ARE
TOO DIFFERENT, VASH.
YOU AND I WERE
DESTINED TO COME TO THIS.
IT'S PART OF WHO I AM.
LONG AGO, WE STARTED
A QUICKDRAW TOURNAMENT.
WE'RE GOING TO
SETTLE IT AT LAST.
RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
- WHY AT THIS TIME?
- IF I TELL YOU,
WILL YOU AGREE TO DIE?
DRAW.
DRAW!
- OKAY,
I'LL DO THAT FOR YOU.
BUT IN RETURN,
WILL YOU DO SOMETHING FOR ME?
- YEAH, WHAT?
- WHEN THIS IS ALL OVER
AND I'M DEAD,
YOU WON'T EVER SHOOT
ANYONE AGAIN.
- ( rock music playing )
- WHEN THIS IS OVER
AND I'M DEAD,
YOU DON'T EVER
SHOOT ANYONE AGAIN.
- YOU ACTUALLY EXPECT ME
TO BECOME A LIVING TARGET
LIKE YOU ARE?
ALL RIGHT, SO HOW DO
YOU PLAN TO GET OUT OF
THIS PREDICAMENT, HUH?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- THEN ANSWER ME ONE THING,
YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY
GOING AFTER KNIVES.
WHAT DO YOU INTEND
TO DO ONCE YOU FIND HIM?
- MANY YEARS AGO,
HE STOLE SOMEONE
WHO WAS VERY
IMPORTANT TO ME.
- SO YOU WANT REVENGE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
- I SEE.
SO THAT'S HOW YOU LIVE.
THAT'S HOW YOU
CHOOSE TO LIVE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE AN EXPERT
AT PISSING ME OFF.
AMAZING.
- HEY, WOLFWOOD.
- ( grunts )
- ( gunshots )
- TAKE COVER!
- WHO FIRED THAT?
- IT MUST BE CAINE.
HE'S PROBABLY SNIPING
FROM THE OUTSKIRTS OF TOWN.
IF WE DON'T DO
SOMETHING NOW,
HE WILL HIT HIS TARGET.
AND HE'S NOT ALONE.
- WHAT?
- WHY DON'T YOU
GO AFTER CAINE?
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
ANY PROBLEM FINDING HIM.
THE OTHER ONE'S MINE.
BY THE WAY,
I ONLY KNOW YOU
AS THE STAMPEDE.
I THINK YOU CAN AT LEAST
TELL ME YOUR REAL NAME.
- NO WAY.
I'M NOT GONNA TELL YOU
JUST SO YOU CAN GO OUT
AND GET KILLED TODAY.
- NOW DON'T BE STUPID.
TELL ME.
- BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
MY NAME'S IRRELEVANT.
- ( chuckles )
- ( grunts )
- TIME TO GET
BACK TO BUSINESS, VASH.
HMM?
- WOLFWOOD, WHY?
NO, DOESN'T MATTER.
- Meryl: MR. WOLFWOOD?
I HEARD GUNFIRE.
( gasps )
MILLY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- ( murmurs )
I'M STAYING HERE, MERYL.
HE TOLD ME TO STAY HERE.
HE MADE ME PROMISE,
SO I'M NOT MOVING
UNTIL HE COMES BACK.
- GOT IT.
- ( grunts )
( grunts )
( gasps )
ALCOHOL?
HE LED ME IN HERE!
- THE ONLY CLUES I HAD
WERE THE LAG TIME
BETWEEN RIFLE REPORTS
AND MY ROUGH CALCULATIONS
OF THE ANGLES ON IMPACT.
I HAD A HARD TIME
FINDING YOU.
WELL, GEE NOW,
SINCE YOUR GUN'S
GONE TO PIECES,
WHY DON'T YOU HEAD ON HOME?
IT'S TOO HOT OUT HERE.
GREAT, I'M GLAD
YOU'RE SEEING IT MY WAY.
( gasps )
- WHERE?
WHERE WILL HE
ATTACK FROM?
( gasps )
OH, SHIT!
( grunts )
( groans )
- ( gunfire )
- ( sighs )
( groans )
( breathes heavily )
- SO NOW WHAT'S
THE BEST CHOICE?
TELL ME.
IS THIS GOOD ENOUGH?
IS IT?
- ( exhales )
- I'M DONE.
THAT'S GONNA BE IT FOR ME.
HMM.
NOW THAT'S TASTY!
- ( grunts )
THIS IS A HUGE
DISAPPOINTMENT TO ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D SO EASILY WASTE
THE 10 YEARS OF TRAINING
I GAVE YOU--
- ACTUALLY, IT WASN'T
WASTED AT ALL.
I'VE USED EVERYTHING
YOU'VE TAUGHT ME.
I JUST DECIDED TO DO
THINGS A LITTLE DIFFERENTLY.
MAY YOU GO WITH
GOD'S PROTECTION.
OH, YEAH.
AND THANKS FOR THE APPLE.
- ( grunts )
AAH!
( groans )
AAH.
( shouts )
- HMM?
- ( gunfire )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I FAILED.
I FAILED TO SAVE
SOMEONE AGAIN.
- MAN IS BORN
A MORTAL BEING,
AND WE ALL MAKE MISTAKES.
IT'S PART OF THE GAME.
JUST BE MORE CAREFUL
THE NEXT TIME.
- IT'S HARD FOR ME TO ACCEPT
MAKING MISTAKES LIKE THIS.
- THEN YOU CAN
CHOOSE TO SUFFER.
THAT'S ALSO A PART OF
THE EXPERIENCE OF MORTAL LIFE.
- OH, YEAH.  MORTAL.
- BY THE WAY,
KNIVES IS IN DMITRI.
- ( gasps )
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I NEVER TOLD YOU
ANYTHING ABOUT KNIVES.
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
- I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND ME
BARGING IN LIKE THIS.
( grunts )
( gasps )
IN SPITE OF
THE PROFESSION I'VE CHOSEN,
I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY
MADE A CONFESSION BEFORE.
IT'S THESE TIMES
WE LIVE IN.
I DID WHAT IT TOOK TO PROTECT
THE CHILDREN AT ANY COST.
THAT'S HOW I ALWAYS
JUSTIFIED MY ACTIONS.
I TOOK MANY PEOPLE'S LIVES.
ALL THAT TIME BELIEVING
THERE WAS NO OTHER WAY.
( sighs )
MY SINS ARE SO HEAVY.
TOO HEAVY.
TOO HEAVY TO EVER
ATONE FOR.
( grunts )
AND YET...
SOMEHOW I FEEL HAPPY,
AT PEACE WITH
MYSELF TODAY.
IT REALLY CAN BE DONE.
ONCE YOU STOP
TO THINK ABOUT IT,
THERE ARE PLENTY OF WAYS
TO SAVE EVERYONE.
WHY DIDN'T I EVER
LISTEN TO HIM?
WHY DIDN'T I SEE THAT
BEFORE IT WAS TOO LATE?
( inhales, exhales )
THAT TASTES GOOD.
- YOU KNOW, CIGARETTES ARE
BAD FOR THE BABY, DARLING.
- Wolfwood:
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
IF I AM REINCARNATED,
I'D LIKE TO LIVE SOMEWHERE
WHERE LIFE IS EASIER.
SOMEWHERE WITH NOTHING
BUT PEACEFUL DAYS.
SOMEWHERE WITH NO STEALING,
NO KILLING.
EDEN.
IN EDEN...
I COULD LIVE HAPPILY
WITH HIM
AND THE GIRLS.
( groans )
I'M NOT READY YET.
THERE'S STILL SO MUCH
LEFT TO BE DONE.
I WANT TO STAY WITH THEM.
I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
( gasps )
I'M A MAN.
WAS EVERYTHING I DID
IN MY LIFE A MISTAKE?
WOULD I BE WRONG NOW
TO ASK FOR YOUR FORGIVENESS?
I DID NOT WANT TO
DIE THIS WAY!
- ( birds chirping )
- ( sobbing )
- ( crying )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: REPEATED TRAGEDIES,
REPEATED PAIN.
THE WISHES OF A MAN
ARE SO STRONG
AND YET SO FRAIL AND WEAK.
TO LIVE,
TO STAY ALIVE.
WHO WOULD HAVE KNOWN THAT
SURVIVAL WAS THIS HARD?
THIS PAINFUL?
I MUST CHOOSE.
I MUST MAKE THE CHOICE.
IN THE MOMENT THAT
INTERTWINES LIFE AND DEATH,
CAN I CHOOSE TO
REMAIN A HUMAN?