- ( theme music playing )
- ( distant music playing )
- ( sloshes )
- THAT SURE PAID OFF, HUH?
- YES SIR, I'D SAY THAT
LADY LUCK IS ON OUR SIDE!
- ( laughing )
- ( slurring ) YO, BROTHER.
- HMMM?
- YOU SURE SEEM LIKE A
MIGHTY PROSPEROUS FELLA.
HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?!
- I AIN'T GOT NO CASH.
HOW ABOUT BUYING ME
A DRINK, HUH?
I'LL TAKE ANYTHING
THAT'S GOT ALCOHOL IN IT.
ETHYL, METHYL,
COUGH SYRUP, WHATEVER.
- HUH.
SCREW OFF,
YOU STUPID DRUNK!
- DON'T BE BRINGING YOUR REEKING
CORPSE IN HERE EVER AGAIN!
- I WON'T GIVE YOU ALCOHOL,
BUT I'D BE HAPPY TO GIVE
YOU A NICE HOT LEAD BULLET
BETWEEN THE EYES.
SO WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU TOO SCARED
TO TALK NOW, MISTER?
- ( both laugh )
- ( yelps )
- AND DON'T SHOW YOUR UGLY FACE
AROUND HERE EITHER.
- ( laughs, door closes )
- ( laughing )
THE STUPID IDIOTS.
- Milly: SO, MERYL, WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO SEARCH FOR TODAY?
A GIANT MAN?
A RED COAT?
BLONDE HAIR
OR A GUY WITH A MOHAWK?
LET'S SEE NOW, AFTER THAT,
WHAT WAS NEXT?
- I'VE HAD IT WITH RUMORS.
FROM NOW ON, I'LL ONLY BELIEVE
WHAT I SEE FOR MYSELF.
THERE'S A GUNMAN OUT THERE
THAT'S SO AMAZING,
THEY PUT $$60 BILLION
ON HIS HEAD.
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE GOING
TO BEGIN OUR SEARCH TODAY.
- THAT'S AWFULLY VAGUE, MERYL.
CAN YOU BE MORE SPECIFIC?
- ( sighs )
ALL I'M SAYING
IS THAT WE NEED TO
PAY SPECIAL ATTENTION
TO ANYONE THAT
MIGHT BE LIKE THAT!
- BUT THIS SEEMS TO BE SUCH
A PEACEFUL, QUIET TOWN.
- YOU'VE GOT TO ALWAYS
BE ALERT, MILLY.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN
VASH THE STAMPEDE
IS GOING TO SHOW UP
AND THEN KABOOM.
- Milly: OH WOW! HI, VASH!
- HMMM?
HUH?
- ( gulps )
- WELL, HEY THERE!
IT'S THE INSURANCE GIRLS.
ARE YOU WORKING?
- OH YES, WORKING HARD.
- ( growls )
- HMMM, WELL, YOUR COMPANY
MUST BE VERY PROUD OF YOU.
KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK.
- OKAY, MR. VASH, WE WILL.
- SEE YOU AROUND, LADIES.
- ( giggles )
GEE, MERYL,
HE MATCHES
THE DESCRIPTION PERFECTLY.
- WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
HE'S VASH?
- WELL, BECAUSE HE
RAISED HIS HAND
WHEN I CALLED HIS NAME.
- HE ONLY RAISED HIS HAND
BECAUSE YOU CALLED OUT TO HIM.
IT'S A NATURAL RESPONSE
WHEN SOMEONE CALLS OUT TO YOU.
LISTEN, WE'RE LOOKING
FOR A HORRIBLE FIEND
WITH A PRICE ON HIS HEAD.
NOT A OBNOXIOUS IDIOT
LIKE THAT MAN.
- ( sneezes )
I THINK I HAVE A COLD.
- ( slurring )
I'M GOING!
- ( both yelp )
- DAMN, THAT REALLY HURT.
HUH?
- ( muffled shouts )
- ( animal groans )
- OVER HERE, BUDDY!
- HUH? HMM HMM?
- TALKING TO YOU, PAL.
YOU BUMP INTO SOMEONE,
THEN YOU AIN'T GOT NOTHING
TO SAY FOR YOURSELF?
- HUH?
- ( stammering )
HI.
CATCH YOU LATER.
- HOLD IT-- OW OW!
MY FRIGGING SHOULDER HURTS
'CAUSE YOU SLAMMED
INTO ME BACK THERE.
( moaning )
HOW ABOUT BUYING ME A DRINK?
- HUH?!
- I DON'T EXPECT ANY MONEY.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO BUY ME A DRINK.
- NO NO NO NO NO.
- HEY, DON'T BE SHY!
- ( shrieking )
- HEY, WE'RE PALS, AREN'T WE?
- BUT I DON'T EVEN KNOW YOU!
- AW, COME ON, BUDDY!
GIVE IT UP.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO ME?
- Vash: STOP! STOP IT!
- WHAT THE--?
- JUST ONE DRINK, BRO!
YOU OWE ME.
SHOW A LITTLE GENEROSITY HERE.
- HUH?
- Drunk: COME ON.
- DISGUSTING.
JUST IGNORE THEM.
- Vash: INSURANCE GIRLS!
- BUT, MERYL, WAIT.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
I NEED YOUR HELP!
HOW COULD YOU JUST
LEAVE ME LIKE THIS?!
- HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
MAKE-UP KISS, BROTHER!
- Vash: AAH! HELP!
- HEY, BARTENDER,
BRING ME THE BEST IN THE HOUSE!
- YOU GOT MONEY, FRANK?
- ( grunts ) MY BOY HERE IS
THE SON OF A MILLIONAIRE!
- BRING IT ON! NOTHING
BUT THE FINEST!
- HE'S LYING, PLEASE JUST
BRING US THE CHEAPEST
IN THE HOUSE, ALL RIGHT?
( sighs )
HMMM?
- I DON'T WANT NOBODY
MAKING TROUBLE IN HERE,
SO, MISTER, YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO LET ME
HOLD YOUR GUN UNTIL YOU LEAVE.
- HUH? ALL RIGHT.
- THIS IS A STRANGE GUN.
- IT WAS GIVEN TO ME.
I THINK
IT'S A PRETTY GOOD GUN.
- Frank: NO, IT ISN'T.
- YEAH, YOU'RE PRETTY SHARP.
YOU MUST KNOW GUNS.
IT'S THREE INCHES OFF
FROM ONLY 10 YARZ.
- ( cork pops )
- IT WOULDN'T KILL HER TO BE
MORE FRIENDLY, NOW WOULD IT?
I PROPOSE A TOAST
TO NEW FRIENDS!
- OH, YEAH!
- AHH, SWEET!
OUT OF ALL THE
GREATEST INVENTIONS
MAN CREATED IN HISTORY,
ALCOHOL IS HIS GREATEST!
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE, MY PAL?
- UH, BY THE WAY,
I WASN'T REALLY INTENDING
ON BUYING YOU DRINKS,
BUT SINCE I AM, COULD YOU
LISTEN TO MY REQUEST?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- FRANK MARLON, DO YOU KNOW HIM?
- NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
- HEY, GRANDMA!
OH, I MEAN, MISS?
HE IS FAMOUS, ISN'T HE?
- YEAH, HE'S FAMOUS, ALL RIGHT.
HE'S THE HERO
OF THIS HERE TOWN.
A LONG TIME AGO, THIS TOWN
WAS ATTACKED BY VICIOUS BANDITS.
SO MARLON THE GUNSMITH
WENT AROUND TOWN
HANDING OUT GUNS
HE MADE HIMSELF,
TEACHING FOLKS HOW TO USE
THEM AGAINST THE BANDITS.
- HUH.
- NOW YOU KNOW THE STORY.
SO WHAT'S YOUR BUSINESS
WITH FRANK MARLON?
- I JUST WANTED HIM TO FIX
MY OLD HEAP, THAT'S ALL.
- YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
HE'D JUST PAWN IT FOR BOOZE
AND YOU'D HAVE TO BUY
YOURSELF A NEW G--
- HEH.
( laughs )
YOU REALLY WANNA GIVE YOUR GUN
TO A COMPLETE STRANGER, MISTER?
YOU'LL ONLY HAVE YOURSELF
TO BLAME
IF YOU GET SHOT IN THE BACK.
YOU'D HAVE TO BE
A DAMNED IDIOT.
THAT'S RIGHT, NOTHING BUT
A HOPELESS OLD FOOL.
HUH?
- WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THERE'S REALLY NO SHERIFF
IN THIS TOWN?
- THAT'S RIGHT, MISS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
THAT'S RIGHT?
- MY DEAR, THIS IS
A VERY QUIET TOWN.
NOTHING SERIOUS
EVER HAPPENS HERE.
I'M PROUD TO SAY
THAT WARREN CITY
IS A SAFE PLACE FULL
OF HAPPY PEOPLE.
- THE WORST IT EVER GETS
ARE A FEW CRAZY DRUNKS.
- MR. MAYOR, I DON'T MEAN
TO ALARM YOU, SIR,
BUT THERE IS SOMETHING
VERY IMPORTANT
I HAVE TO TELL YOU NOW.
- ( mayor laughing )
- ( meow )
- THE LEGENDARY CRIMINAL
HERE IN MY TOWN?
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
- I ASSURE YOU IT'S NO
LAUGHING MATTER!
- WELL, IF HE'S REALLY
THAT GREAT,
I THINK IT WOULD BE KINDA FUN
TO HAVE HIM ATTACK
AND SPICE THINGS UP
AROUND HERE.
- I'M SORRY, MR. MAYOR, BUT I
DON'T FIND THIS FUNNY AT ALL.
- ( cackling )
- Man: HEY, BIG BRO!
- HUH?
- THEY WAS RIGHT.
IT'S JUST LIKE WE HEARD!
A BIG ARMORED TRUCK'S
GONNA BE COMING
TO THAT TOWN'S BANK AT NOON.
- EXCELLENT, DEAR BROTHER.
- IT'S 4,000 YARZ
TO THE NEXT TOWN.
THEY HAVE NO SHERIFF.
WE COULDN'T ASK FOR
A BETTER LOCATION!
- AND LISTEN TO THIS,
I HEARD A RUMOR GOING AROUND.
THEY SAY VASH THE STAMPEDE
SHOWED UP AND HE'S REAL CLOSE.
DO YOU MEAN VASH
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON?
- YEAH.
- ( cackles )
- Both: HUH?
- ( grunts )
ALL RIGHT.
( cackles )
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
( laughs )
I HAVE A PLAN.
WE WILL HAVE THE HUMANOID
TYPHOON, VASH THE STAMPEDE,
ATTACK THE ARMORED CAR.
I CAN SEE IT NOW.
THIS IS PERFECT.
( cackling )
- ( meows )
- GET THE HELL OUT!
- HEY, WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?
WE WERE JUST ENJOYING A DRINK,
YOU SELFISH WITCH.
- GIMME-GIMME BACK
MY GUN, GRANDMA.
- HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED, BROTHER?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MY HEAD JUST STARTED TO HURT.
- OH, THAT'S NOT GOOD.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
- YOU HAVE AN IDEA?
- LET'S GO TO MY PLACE
AND DRINK IT BETTER.
- Meryl: WHAT ARE
YOU TWO DOING THERE?
- HUH?
- UH-OH.
- Vash: OH,
IT'S THE INSURANCE GIRLS!
- YOU SURE LOOK HAPPY,
MR. VASH!
- ( laugh )
HAVING A HECK OF A GOOD TIME.
BY THE WAY, WHAT ARE THE
TWO OF YOU DOING OUT SO LATE?
- WE'RE HERE ON NIGHT PATROL!
MY PARTNER IS CONVINCED
THAT VASH THE STAMPEDE
IS GONNA SHOW UP
IN TOWN TONIGHT!
- HE DOES NOT NEED TO KNOW
WHY WE ARE OUT SO LATE, MILLY.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT, MERYL.
- NIGHT PATROL?!
WOW, THAT'S REALLY GREAT.
AREN'T THESE GIRLS
WONDERFUL?
- HERE'S TO
THE WONDERFUL WOMEN!
- ( both laugh )
CHEERIO!
( drunken singing )
- GEE, MERYL, THEY LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE HAVING A BLAST.
- I DON'T THINK SO. PEOPLE ONLY
DROWN THEMSELVES IN ALCOHOL
WHEN THEY HAVE SOMETHING
THEY WANT TO FORGET!
IT'S AN ESCAPE
FROM REALITY.
- Frank: ARE YOU STILL
DRINKING, BROTHER?
- YEAH, TONS.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
GONNA BE IN ANY SHAPE
TO GO TO WORK TOMORROW.
- I GOT IT COVERED.
I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT IT.
I ONLY DO CHARITY WORK.
DON'T GET PAID,
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHETHER I'M COHERENT OR NOT.
- HUH?
- MY FRIEND, THE WORLD IS FULL
OF THE WEAK AND THE SUFFERING.
I'VE ALWAYS MADE IT MY BUSINESS
TO HELP OUT THOSE
IN TIME OF NEED.
- AHH.
- ( gulps )
BUT THEN I FOUND A WAY TO HELP
THOSE WHO AREN'T
SUFFERING AT ALL.
- WHAT? WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THEY SAY IT'S WRONG
TO DISCRIMINATE, RIGHT?
YOU HELP SOMEONE,
AND THEN SOMEONE ELSE SUFFERS.
THAT IS HOW
THIS WORLD WORKS.
- OH.
- THAT IS WHY
I'VE DECIDED TO DO NOTHING.
THAT'S ALL I DO,
NOTHING BUT DRINK.
THERE YOU HAVE EQUALITY.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- ( Frank snoring )
- Man: YOU WANT TO SEE
FRANK MARLON? ( laughs )
MIGHT AS WELL
GIVE IT UP, PAL.
HE JUST AIN'T THE MAN
HE WAS 10 YEARS AGO.
NOW HE'S JUST DAMNED DRUNK.
AS A GUNSMITH, HE WAS
SOMETHING OF A GENIUS.
BUT THEN IN ONE DAY
HIS WHOLE LIFE CHANGED
WHEN HIS WIFE AND KID
WERE KILLED IN A BANK ROBBERY.
- HUH?
- ( gunshots )
- Tailor: THEY HAPPENED TO BE
IN THE BANK AT THE WRONG TIME.
THEY JUST GOT CAUGHT
IN THE CROSSFIRE.
BUT TO FRANK,
THE REAL TRAGEDY WAS...
HE HAD MADE THE GUNS
THAT THE ROBBERS USED.
IN FACT, HE HAD GIVEN THEM
THE GUNS PERSONALLY.
- ( gags )
( running footsteps,
retches )
- ( moans )
HUH?
WHAT THE...
WHERE'D HE GO?
- Man: OH MY GOD!
- HUH?
- VASH THE STAMPEDE IS HERE!
HE'S ATTACKING
THE ARMORED CAR!
- EH, VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- ( gunshots, laughter )
- YOU'D BE REAL SMART
TO KEEP YOUR DISTANCE!
'CAUSE THIS GENTLEMAN HERE
IS NONE OTHER THAN
THE $$60 BILLION MAN...
VASH THE STAMPEDE,
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON!
- LEAVE HIM ALONE!
IF YOU GET HIM REAL MAD,
HE MAY JUST DECIDE TO BLOW
THIS TOWN TO SMITHEREENS.
- HMMM, HOW PLEASANT.
SURE WOULD BE NICE
IF ALL THE TOWNSFOLK
WERE THIS HELPFUL.
- UH, EXCUSE ME, MR. VASH?
MY NAME IS MERYL STRYFE
AND I'M HERE WITH MY PARTNER
REPRESENTING THE BERNARDELLI
INSURANCE SOCIETY.
AND WE WERE SENT HERE TO--
- HEY, SHUT UP AND
JUST LOAD THE BAGS!
- Both: YES SIR!
- I FEEL HORRIBLE, MERYL.
- IF ONLY I WOULD HAVE
BOUGHT HIM A BOX OF DONUTS.
- YOU'D BETTER GET
THE LEAD OUT, LADIES.
- Both:
YES SIR, WE WILL.
- COUNTERMEASURE #1:
TAKE THE PLACE OF A HOSTAGE.
( muffled groan )
- WON'T WORK.
- #2 THEN:
SEND EVERYBODY INTO A MAD PANIC
BY SHOUTING "EARTHQUAKE!"
YEOW!
- EVEN WORSE.
- ( growls ) WELL THEN,
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
- I HAVE TO GO WITH #3:
YOU KNOW, JUST STAND BACK HERE
WHERE IT'S SAFE,
LET 'EM TAKE THE MONEY
AND SHUT UP.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- WHY THE HELL ARE YOU
STICKING YOUR NECK OUT?
JUST KEEP QUIET,
YOU JUST MIGHT STAY ALIVE.
AND THERE'LL BE A LOT LESS
DAMAGE AROUND HERE TOO.
- LOOK, DO YOU SEE
THAT LITTLE GIRL?
- YEAH.
- HER MOTHER PROMISED TO BUY
HER SOMETHING WITH HER MONEY
THAT USED TO BE IN THE BANK
BEFORE THIS HAPPENED.
- YOU KNOW HER?
- NAH, JUST MADE IT UP.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING WORRYING
ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE'S MONEY?
I MEAN, WHAT GOOD'S
IT GONNA DO YOU?
- NOTHING AT ALL.
EXCEPT THAT THIS
SITUATION IS NOT EQUAL.
- Both: HUH?
- HUH?
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
- ( whispers ) BIG BRO.
- HMM?
- ( gunshot )
- WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
TRYING TO PLAY THE HERO, COWBOY?
- NO, NOT REALLY. I'M NOT AS
GREAT AS YOU MIGHT THINK I AM.
AW, GEE, THAT'S TOO BAD.
YOU'VE GOT A FLAT TIRE!
WELL, I GUESS YOU WON'T BE
ESCAPING IN THIS.
- ( screaming )
- YOU LITTLE--
- ( screams, gasps )
- ( laughs )
HUH? LET--
SON OF A--
WHOA, LET GO, YOU--
( moaning )
- HOW'D HE DO THAT?
- ARE YOU CRAZY?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING YOURSELF INTO, MISTER?
THIS GENTLEMAN HERE
IS THE ONE AND ONLY
INFAMOUS HUMANOID TYPHOON.
HE'S VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- NOW THAT'S FUNNY.
PARDON ME.
- ( bones crack )
- BUT I UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THAT HE WAS A LOT MORE HANDSOME.
- ARE YOU IMPLYING THAT
I AM NOT VASH THE STAMPEDE?!
- MAYBE WE SHOULD FIND OUT.
- HUH? UHH.
( thinking )
WHY?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- WE CAN USE FORCE
IF WE HAVE TO.
- RIGHT!
- WHY?!
- Bartender:
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
- HUH?
- ( groans )
- ( wind blowing )
- ( both gasp )
- THIS GUN IS AN ORIGINAL
FRANK MARLON SPECIAL!
AND DON'T THINK I'LL MISS
JUST 'CAUSE I'M A WOMAN!
- AM I SUPPOSED TO BE AFRAID
OF THIS FRANK MARLON?
IT'S A RUSTED PIECE OF CRAP!
YOU ACTUALLY BELIEVE YOU'LL
HIT ME WITH THAT THING?
- ( sloshes )
WHY?
WHY ARE THEY DOING THAT?
AND WHY AM I JUST
STANDING HERE?!
- THAT THIS SITUATION
IS NOT EQUAL.
- HUH? HMM?
WHAT THE--?
- UH?
- ( laughs ) APPARENTLY
YOU THINK THAT YOU HAVE WON.
YOU THINK WRONG!
- ( cocking )
- A PIECE OF PARTING ADVICE:
YOU SHOULD ALWAYS SAVE
YOUR ACES FOR LAST!
( cackles )
( gulps )
- CHECKMATE, MISTER.
- ( gulps )
- SHOOTING FROM BEHIND'S
JUST NOT MY STYLE.
- YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS!
- ( screaming )
- YOU WILL PAY!
- ( all grunt )
- WOW, THEY REALLY
STICK TOGETHER.
HUH?
- HMPH, WASN'T EVEN LOADED.
- HUH, SURE WASN'T.
- ( all cheering )
- HE'S ACTUALLY DUMBER
THAN I THOUGHT.
THAT GUY IS UNBELIEVABLE.
- ( excited chatter )
- HERE'S TO ALL THE GREAT FOLKS
WHO SAVED THE TOWN!
IN YOUR EYE!
AHA HA HA!
GRANDMA, WHAT YOU WAITING FOR?
FILL 'ER UP!
I MEAN, PLEASE FILL 'ER UP,
MISS, IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND?
- THAT'S BETTER!
- ( laughs )
I WILL NEVER UNDERSTAND HIM.
- THINGS TURNED OUT WELL
AFTER ALL.
THERE'S NO DAMAGE
TO THE TOWN.
THE CHIEF WILL PROBABLY
GIVE US BOTH PROMOTIONS!
- BUT THE BANDIT WAS A FAKE.
IT WASN'T REALLY HIM.
AND WE STILL HAVEN'T
GOTTEN OUR CHANCE
TO MEET VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- Milly: BUT SOMEONE
MATCHES HIS DESCRIPTION!
- HUH?
- OH MAN, I'VE GOTTA
FIND THE CAN.
- Frank: STICK 'EM UP.
- ( laughing )
- I WOULDN'T EXACTLY COUNT
ON THIS FOR EVERYDAY USE
IF I WERE YOU.
- HUH?
- BUT HERE, TAKE IT.
I'VE CHANGED THE CYLINDER
AND HAMMER PARTS FOR YOU,
AND I GAVE IT
A FULL TUNE-UP.
- HEY, THANKS.
- AW HECK, YOU DON'T
NEED TO THANK ME.
BUT THERE IS ONE THING
I WANT TO KNOW.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WITH THAT GUN?
- I INTEND TO USE IT
TO CREATE EQUALITY
AND PEACE THROUGHOUT THE WORLD!
- HUH?
WELL, IF YOU EVER
WEAR IT OUT AGAIN,
BRING IT BACK,
I'LL FIX IT AS GOOD AS NEW!
- GREAT. AND WHEN I DO, I'LL
BRING THE BOURBON NEXT TIME.
- NO THANKS,
I'VE GIVEN UP ALCOHOL.
I'VE GOT BETTER THINGS TO DO
INSTEAD OF DRINKING.
- Milly: WHAT DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT?
- SHH!
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST REALIZED, PAL,
I NEVER DID GET YOUR NAME.
- WELL-- I'M--
( gags )
( retching )
- YOU DRINK TOO MUCH!
- Vash: I'M SORRY!
- Frank: DISGUSTING.
- ( animals groaning )
- YOU JUST DON'T WANT TO ADMIT
THAT YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT HIM, DO YOU, MERYL?
- NO, AND I AM NOT FOLLOWING
HIM, FOR YOUR INFORMATION.
WE JUST HAPPEN TO BE GOING
IN THE SAME DIRECTION.
- BANG BANG.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: A PAST THAT
CAN'T BE FORGOTTEN
AND CAN'T BE BURIED.
A PAST THAT CAN'T EVEN BE SHAKEN
FOR JUST A LITTLE TIME.
THE SENTIMENT DEEP INSIDE
EACH OF THEIR HEARTS
IS STRONG AND EQUAL.
FOR BELOVED PARENTS,
AND FOR A BELOVED DAUGHTER.
TWO MEN CAN ONLY FIND THE ANSWER
FROM BEHIND THEIR TRIGGERS.
THE MOMENT THE SENTIMENTAL
BULLETS FLEW TOWARDS EACH OTHER,
THE MEN STOOD SILENT,
YET WERE WEEPING.
THE PAST ENSLAVES.