- ( theme music playing )
♪ OH! ♪
- Milly: WE REALLY DO APPRECIATE
YOU LENDING US BUS FARE!
- HMM?
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- IF WE DON'T COME WITH YOU,
WE CAN'T DO OUR JOB!
I'LL HATE YOU!
I'LL HAUNT YOU
AND YOUR CHILDREN AND YOUR
CHILDREN'S CHILDREN TOO.
- OH YEAH, I KNEW
IT WAS A MISTAKE,
BUT I COULDN'T TAKE THE WHINING!
- I APPRECIATE IT!
- Vash: OKAY OKAY.
YOU CAN SHOWER ME WITH ALL
THE APPRECIATION YOU WANT.
- ( whimpering )
- JUST MAKE SURE YOU PAY
ME BACK WHEN WE HIT TOWN.
MY WALLET'S ALMOST EMPTY.
- YOU'VE GOT A POINT THERE.
- AM I REALLY GETTING
THROUGH TO THIS GIRL?
- I'M A LITTLE BIT THIRSTY.
- ( door opens )
- DO YOU THINK THAT I COULD
HAVE SOME OF YOUR WATER?
- FINALLY!
- I'M NOT GETTING THROUGH
TO HER AT ALL!
- WILL YOU KEEP IT DOWN?
- GUH!
- HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED THAT
EVERYONE HERE IS EXHAUSTED
FROM THEIR TERRIBLE ORDEAL
IN THE SAND STEAMER?
DON'T WORRY,
I'VE SHUT HIM UP FOR YOU.
HE WON'T BE CAUSING
ANY MORE TROUBLE.
- ( laughing )
- I REALLY DON'T THINK
YOU HAD TO HIT ME.
HUH?
WA-HAAA!
- WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
- THAT.
- HUH?
- THAT IS ONE HECK
OF A WELL-PREPARED DEAD GUY.
HEY, YOU.
- HA!
AHEM.
WELL, PRAISE THE LORD.
HELLO!
- Milly: ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- Meryl: HERE, HAVE SOME WATER.
- Man: OH, THANK YOU!
AHHH!
AH, I'M ALIVE AGAIN!
I'M MUCH OBLIGED!
- YOU'RE WELCOME!
- BUT THAT WAS MY--
- Meryl :WHAT WERE YOU DOING
OUT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DESERT?
- HEH, WELL, MY BIKE DECIDED
TO BREAK DOWN ON ME
ABOUT 100 ILES OR SO
DOWN THE ROAD FROM HERE,
SO I THOUGHT
I'D JUST HOOF IT.
- Meryl: ARE YOU SAYING
YOU ACTUALLY WALKED 100 ILES?!
- THAT'S RIGHT!
IT WAS PRETTY HORRIBLE.
- UH...
- Milly: GEE, IT MUST HAVE
BEEN AWFULLY TIRING
TO WALK CARRYING THAT HUGE THING
ON YOUR BACK.
- ( man laughs )
I COULDN'T LEAVE IT BEHIND.
I DO HAVE MY PRIDE
AS A TRADESMAN, YOU KNOW.
- Meryl: UH, TRADESMAN?
- I'M A MAN OF THE CLOTH.
- YOU? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- ( laughs ) DO YOU, LIKE,
MAKE PRETTY DRESSES?
- HARDLY! I'M A PRIEST!
SAVING THE LAMBS WHO HAVE
STRAYED OFF THEIR PATH,
A SOLDIER OF LOVE!
YOU GIRLS ARE THE ONES WHO
SPOTTED ME, AREN'T YOU?
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
- WELL, ACTUALLY THE
ONE THAT SPOTTED YOU
WHEN YOU NOTHING BUT A TINY
LITTLE SPECK ON THE HORIZON
WAS THAT PATHETIC GUY.
- ( moaning )
- OH. HEY,
I'M ALIVE BECAUSE
OF WHAT YOU DID.
HOW COULD I EVER THANK YOU?
UH, MISTER...
I AM KNOWN AS
VALENTINEZ ALKALINELLA
XIFAX SICIDABOHERTZ.
...GUMBIGOBILLA BLUE
STRADIVARI TALENTRENT PIERRE
ANDRE CHARTON-HAYMOSS
IVANOVICCI BALDEUS GEORGE
DOITZEL KAISER III.
DON'T HESITATE TO CALL.
- ( Milly laughs )
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
MR. VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- HMMM?!
- I HATE IT WHEN YOU CALL
ME BY MY FULL NAME!
- THE VASH?! YOU MEAN TO SAY
HE'S THE VASH THE STAMPEDE?!
- ( groaning )
- HUH?
CAN THIS MAN REALLY BE HIM?
HE'S ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
AT ALL LIKE I ENVISIONED!
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?!
- YEAH, I KNOW.
I HAVE TROUBLE BELIEVING IT TOO.
- YOU MEAN...?
OH, HEY!
GEE, SORRY ABOUT THAT!
I'M WOLFWOOD.
AT YOUR SERVICE!
- HMM.
( grunting )
- Wolfwood: LIFE SURE CAN
BE FUNNY SOMETIMES.
IMAGINE RUNNING
INTO THE LEGENDARY OUTLAW
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS!
( laughing )
- Vash: DON'T BROADCAST IT
TO THE WHOLE WORLD, OKAY?
- IF I SHOT YOU DEAD RIGHT NOW
AND COLLECTED THE $$60 BILLION
I'D HAVE A REALLY
FUN JOURNEY, WOULDN'T I?
( laughs )
- YOU WEREN'T
LISTENING, WERE YOU?
- GOT ANY MORE WATER?
- I WOULD, BUT YOU DRANK IT ALL.
- YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT!
- ( fake laughter )
- Milly: HEY, THEY SEEM TO BE
GETTING ALONG REALLY WELL.
- ( cackling )
- Meryl: THE BIRDS OF A FEATHER
HAVE FLOCKED TOGETHER.
- ( passengers grumbling )
I'M TIRED. THAT WAS A LONG TRIP.
- I'M SO STIFF!
- I COULD GO TO SLEEP.
- I'VE GOTTA STRETCH!
- MOMMY, I'M TIRED.
- LOOK, MISTER, DO ME A FAVOR,
PLEASE COUNT IT ONE MORE TIME.
- OKAY, READY?
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
RECOUNT IT ALL YOU WANT,
IT'S STILL NOT ENOUGH.
LIKE I TOLD YOU,
THE FARE IS $$100.
- IF I GIVE YOU ANY MORE,
I'LL DIE OF STARVATION.
COME ON, DRIVER.
PLEASE GIVE ME A BREAK.
- ( groans )
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
I'LL LET YOU RIDE FOR $$80.
TAKE IT OR LEAVE IT.
- REALLY?! THAT'D BE GREAT!
THANKS A LOT!
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT!
- WHAT?
W-WHAT-- WHOA.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?!
- IT'S A CONFESSIONAL.
YOU KNOW, THOSE PRIVATE ROOMS
THEY USED TO HAVE IN THE
CHURCHES BACK HOME?
THIS ONE IS PORTABLE!
YOU MUST HAVE
SOMETHING TO CONFESS?
SOME BLASPHEMOUS ACT,
AN INDISCRETION MAYBE?
IT'S ON THE HOUSE!
GO AHEAD, DON'T BE SHY!
( gasps )
- NO THANKS, PADRE.
- WELL NOW, HE'S NOT MUCH FUN.
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
A PRETTY TOUGH JOB.
- HMM?
- IS THAT THING
PART OF YOUR GOSPEL?
- OF COURSE NOT.
IT'S ALL BUSINESS--
UNFORTUNATELY.
OUR CHURCH KIND OF DOUBLES
AS AN ORPHANAGE.
WE SCRAPE OUT A LIVING
DOING WHAT WE CAN.
WE TAKE IN ALL THESE KIDS
WITH NO LIVING FAMILY,
NO PLACE TO GO.
( inhales, exhales )
GUESS IT WAS TIME
I LEFT THE CHURCH ANYWAY.
I DECIDED IT WAS
A HOPELESS EFFORT
UNLESS I MADE SOME
MONEY FOR THEM.
- ARE YOU SAYING
YOU MAKE MONEY AS A PRIEST?
- WELL, I WOULDN'T EXACTLY
PUT IT LIKE THAT.
BUT... OH.
- MAMA, I'M REALLY HUNGRY.
- AND I'M TIRED.
- WE'LL BE IN THE CITY SOONER
THAN YOU THINK, GIRLS.
ONCE WE GET THERE,
I'LL GIVE YOU PLENTY TO EAT.
BE PATIENT FOR MOMMY, OKAY?
- BUT, MOM...
- DON'T BE THAT WAY, HONEY.
IT'S ONLY GONNA BE
A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
- ( groans )
- I WANT FOOD NOW, PLEASE, MAMA?
- MAMA, I'M THIRSTY!
- Wolfwood: ARE YOU GUYS HUNGRY?
- HUH?
- UH-HUH.
- I SEE.
WELL, I HAVE THESE.
THEY'RE LITTLE,
BUT THEY TASTE PRETTY GOOD.
- UH.
- OH.
- OKAY? WELL, THIS...
IS YOURS.
AND THIS ONE...
AND THEN THIS ONE...
UH...
IS MINE.
SORRY IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT YOU THINK IT WILL
BE ENOUGH FOR NOW?
HMM?
- AHHH.
( laughs )
- THANK YOU.
- ( girls laugh )
- COME ON, YOU TWO.
WASN'T THAT NICE?
- YEAH!
- I WON'T DROP A CRUMB.
- WELL, I'LL BE.
I'M ACTUALLY SURPRISED THAT
YOU CAN SMILE LIKE THAT.
- HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU HAD ME KIND OF WORRIED.
I NOTICED THAT YOU ALWAYS
SMILE AND SEEM REALLY FRIENDLY,
BUT THE WAY YOU SMILED WAS
SO EMPTY, IT HURT TO WATCH YOU!
YOU'RE HURTING LIKE CRAZY
ON THE INSIDE,
YET YOU GRIN AND BEAR IT.
AT LEAST THAT'S THIS MAN'S
OPINION ANYWAY.
THAT'S WHY I HAVE
THIS CONFESSIONAL!
- GAH!
- NO MATTER WHAT THE WORRY,
I'LL LISTEN TO IT.
JUST PUT A COIN IN HERE.
- YOU'RE REALLY
GOOD AT YOUR TRADE.
- I'VE GOTTA BE
TO MAKE A LIVING!
IT'S NOT EASY, YOU KNOW.
- SOMEBODY COME QUICK!
- Both: HUH?
- ERIK IS COMPLETELY CRAZY!
- Wolfwood: I GUESS
IT WAS BOUND TO HAPPEN.
THE SUN IS GETTING WORSE.
- HEY, ERIK, BUDDY,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HANG ON OKAY!
- IT-- IT WAS...
- DON'T TALK. HEY, GET THE
STRETCHER OVER HERE!
- HE'S JUST FALLEN DOWN.
HE DOESN'T REALLY LOOK THAT BAD.
HMMM?
- ( moans )
- WHO'S RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS?
- THERE ISN'T ANYONE HERE
BUT THE PASSENGERS.
- ( murmuring )
- ALL RIGHT, ALL
RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WHOEVER DID IT, COME OUT WITH
YOUR HANDS UP RIGHT NOW!
- WHY YOU POINTING
THAT THING AT ME?
- IT WAS YOU, WASN'T IT?
- IT WAS NO MORTAL
THAT DID THIS.
- Girls: HUH? HMM?
- COME AGAIN?
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
THAT THING IS HUGE!
- ( zooming )
- ( screaming )
- WELL, IT'S--
- IT'S STILL ALIVE!
- WHAT IS IT?!
- Wolfwood:
HEY, NOT BAD, GIRL.
- ( laughs )
- ( all scream )
- Meryl: RUN!
WHY DOESN'T ANYTHING
NICE EVER FOLLOW YOU?!
- Vash: I KNOW!
IT'S A REAL DRAG, ISN'T IT?
- WHAT THE HELL ARE
THOSE UGLY THINGS?
HUNKS OF LOST TECHNOLOGY?!
DAMN! IT'S ALL BECAUSE
I CHANGED MY ROUTE
TO SAVE THAT STUPID
CHEAP PRIEST!
- I'M TOO NICE. I SHOULD'VE
CHARGED HIM FULL PRICE!
- NOW NOW.
( thinking ) HOW CAN THEY
STILL BE OPERATIONAL?
THEIR EXPIRATION DATE
WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
- ( moaning )
- THIS IS HORRIBLE.
- Vash: CAN YOU HELP HIM?
- I MAY NOT LOOK IT,
BUT I AM A PRIEST.
LEAVE IT TO ME!
UH, I'M SURE I HAVE
A BOOK ON IT.
- ( Vash sighs )
- MEOW.
- NEVER MIND, I'LL DO IT.
- OH OKAY. THANKS.
- MEOW.
- ( moaning )
- HELEN?
HAS ANYONE SEEN MY DAUGHTER?
OH MY GOD, NO.
- ( Vash gasps )
- HUH?
- ( unison )
TAKE CARE OF THE WOUNDED MAN!
- Meryl: OH GREAT.
- OH DEAR.
- HUH?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- DON'T ASK
RIDICULOUS QUESTIONS.
I'M GOING TO SAVE THE CHILD!
- WITH YOUR BARE HANDS?
- OH, SHIT!
HUH?
- YOU WOULD HAVE
GONE ANYWAY, HUH?
- OF COURSE I WOULD.
- I SEE 'EM, I SEE 'EM!
THERE'S LOTS OF THOSE BIG GUYS!
HEY, BUT THOSE ARE
NOTHING FOR THE LIKES
OF VASH THE STAMPEDE, RIGHT?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- MY STOMACH KINDA HURTS.
- OH, COME ON NOW, TOUGH GUY.
GET OVER IT. YOU'RE NOT
THAT FRAGILE, ARE YOU?
- I GOT SHOT BY THE
LEADER OF THE BAD LADS
ABOUT THREE DAYS AGO.
- YOU GOT SHOT BY
BRILLIANT DYNAMITES NEON?
( laughs )
NOW THAT IS IMPRESSIVE.
YOU DO LEAD AN EXCITING LIFE,
JUST LIKE THEY SAY.
WE GOTTA GO.
- YOU LISTEN TO PEOPLE AND
THEN AGAIN YOU DON'T!
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
- A CHILD'S LIFE IS ON THE LINE.
SHE NEEDS HELP.
- JUST LOOK FOR A
SECOND, WILL YOU?
THEY USE THAT THING ON THE END
TO DETECT OBJECTS
WHICH RADIATE HEAT.
- ( clattering )
- HEY, LISTEN TO ME!
- I DON'T HAVE TIME TO JUST
SIT AROUND AND CHITCHAT!
( groans )
OH, THIS IS BAD.
THIS IS GONNA BE TOUGH.
I'M IN TROUBLE!
- Warning. Your I.D.
has not been registered,
therefore you may
not enter this area.
- HUH?
- You will now be
removed by force.
- ( screaming )
- GET DOWN!
- FIRE!
- THAT'S HIM ALL RIGHT.
HEY, NICE SUPPORT!
- AND YOU WERE A NICE DECOY.
OH!
- AND THAT'S WHAT'S KNOWN
AS A NICE COVER.
YOU WERE THE DECOY
THAT TIME!
- HUH, GUESS SO.
NICE SUPPORT!
- ( grunts )
- WHAT IS IT?!
- OVER THERE!
- ( crying )
- SHE'S STILL ALIVE AND SHE
LOOKS OKAY. PRAISE THE LORD!
- Both: HUH?
- MAMA!
- ( thinking )
HE'S FAST, UNBELIEVABLY FAST!
THAT SOUNDED LIKE
A SINGLE GUNSHOT!
- ( gunshots )
- THANKS A LOT, VASH.
BEHIND YOU!
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE JUST ABOUT DONE.
- ( girl screaming )
- HUH? NUTS!
- ( girl screams )
- ( men scream )
OH NO, IT'S QUICKSAND!
( both screaming )
- WHAT AN EMBARRASSING WAY
TO GO.
- Wolfwood:
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- WE REALLY FELL INTO IT NOW.
WE'RE SMACK IN THE MIDDLE
OF THEIR TERRITORY.
- WHAT?
- THIS IS THE INSIDE
OF AN ALIEN SHIP.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME
WE DISCOVERED SOME KIND
OF SPACESHIP THAT
CRASHED HERE A LONG TIME AGO?
- I'M CURIOUS TO KNOW
WHAT'S INSIDE THE BELLY
OF THIS MONSTER WHALE.
- ( whirring )
- HUH?
- ( shrieks )
- NOW I KNOW WHY THE
SHORT-HAIRED GIRL
IS ALWAYS SO PISSED OFF
AT YOU ALL THE TIME!
WHEN YOU'RE AROUND
THINGS ALWAYS SEEM
TO GET MUCH WORSE.
MY BRAIN'S ABOUT
TO EXPLODE INTO PIECES!
IT'S YOUR FAULT,
DO SOMETHING!
- YOU FELL IN ALL BY YOURSELF.
- YOU'RE THE OUTLAW!
- WHAT'S THAT GOT
TO DO WITH ANYTHING?
( shrieking )
- ( both panting )
- I THINK WE SHOULD
TAKE FIVE HERE.
- ALL THIS IS
MAKING ME HUNGRY.
THERE!
HERE.
- THAT'S FUNNY.
WITH THE CHILDREN
YOU SEEMED TO BE
A BIT MORE GENEROUS.
- I GUESS YOU DON'T WANT IT.
- AHHH!
I AM ETERNALLY GRATEFUL
FOR YOUR HUMANITY
IN THIS MOST EXTREME
SITUATION.
- OKAY, THAT WAS FUN.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO NOW?
- I LOST $$80 BILLION AT POKER,
BUT THERE'S A LITTLE LEFT.
- A REAL MAN WOULD LAY IT
ALL ON THE TABLE.
- ALL RIGHT THEN,
LET'S FIND OURSELVES A CASINO.
- Wolfwood:
THE PLANT'S FULLY OPERATIONAL.
THIS IS AN AWFULLY BIG CASINO!
WELL THEN,
WHERE ARE THE CARDS?
- RIGHT HERE.
- HUH?
- I'LL GO.
YOU COVER ME.
- HEY, I HAVE TO TELL YOU,
I'VE NEVER FIRED A GUN BEFORE!
BESIDES IF I GO AHEAD
AND TAKE THIS ONE,
DOESN'T THAT MEAN YOU'RE GOING
IN THERE COMPLETELY UNARMED?
YOU'RE REALLY CRAZY!
- WHY DON'T YOU GO THEN?
I'LL WAIT HERE.
- I'LL SHOOT THE GUN.
- OKAY, SHUFFLE THE DECK.
IT'S TIME FOR A GAME.
- JUST ONE MOMENT.
- WHAT IS IT?
- MAY YOU GO WITH THE PROTECTION
AND LOVE OF ALMIGHTY GOD.
IT'S THE USUAL MANTRA
FOR THE BIG GUY.
- DOES IT WORK?
- THAT'S ENTIRELY UP TO YOU.
- WONDERFUL MANTRA
YOU'VE GOT THERE.
- BELIEVERS WILL BE
REDEEMED IN THE END.
- OKEY-DOKEY THEN.
SHALL WE BEGIN?
- OKAY, LET'S GET IN THE GAME.
- ( thinking ) HE'S GOOD.
THAT'S PRECISE SHOOTING.
I KNEW HE WAS
NO ORDINARY PRIEST.
- ( whirrs )
- I'LL GET IT!
( clicks )
HUH?!
DAMN!
- ( laser blast )
- ( grunts, gasps )
- Please show
your I.D. number.
- LEAVE ME ALONE ALREADY!
- Unable to confirm identity.
Conclusion: intruder.
- ( growls ) WOULD YOU
JUST GET OUT OF MY WAY?!
( groans )
THIS IS BAD!
- ( laser blasts )
- ( mutters )
NO NO NO--
HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
HEY, VASH?
HE'S ALIVE.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS GUY!
- ( thinking )
YOU CAN STOP NOW.
THERE'S NO ONE LEFT
TO PROTECT.
- ( beeping )
- GOOD NIGHT.
( footsteps )
- WHAT HAPPENED BACK THERE?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- DON'T PLAY DUMB WITH ME.
I'M ASKING WHAT YOU
DID BACK THERE.
- IT MUST HAVE BEEN GOD.
IT'S THE ONLY EXPLANATION.
- ( banging )
- WHAT'S THAT?!
- OH NO, THERE'S MORE!
- HELLO? ARE THE TWO OF YOU
DOWN THERE SOMEWHERE?
CAN YOU HEAR US?
- IT'S US, MILLY AND MERYL.
WE'RE HERE TO SAVE YOU!
- Meryl: IF YOU'RE THERE,
GIVE US A SIGN.
- ( groaning )
- I THINK THEY'RE MAYBE...
- ...A LITTLE LATE, I'D SAY.
- ( yelps )
- ( snoring )
- Wolfwood: YOU CAN GET
OUT OF THE WORST
PREDICAMENTS IMAGINABLE,
JUST LIKE THEY SAY,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- I'D MUCH RATHER LEAD
AN UNEVENTFUL LIFE
IF IT WAS UP TO ME.
- YOU COULDN'T IF YOU TRIED.
- HUH?
- CAN I SIT HERE?
UH, YEAH, GO AHEAD.
- ( yawns )
- HUH?
- HEY, YOU'RE REALLY
COMFORTABLE.
- ( door shuts )
- UGH!
BOY, THAT GUY
SURE HAS A LOT OF NERVE.
ACTUALLY, HE REMINDS ME
OF SOMEONE I KNOW.
- YEAH, ISN'T HE HORRIBLE?
I THINK WE SHOULD TELL HIM OFF!
YEAH, LET'S DO THAT.
- ( sighs )
- ( passengers grumbling )
- MM, MY BACK HURTS.
- THANKS A LOT FOR
ALL THE SUPPORT, VASH.
IT WAS A FUN
AND INTERESTING TRIP.
- YOU'RE LEAVING NOW?
- I GOTTA GET BACK
TO WORK, YOU KNOW.
- HEY, PREACHER MAN!
- ( all groaning )
- HERE!
- HEY, THANKS A LOT!
- DAMN, THAT THING'S HEAVY!
- THAT, MY FRIENDS, IS BECAUSE
IT'S SO FULL OF MERCY.
SEE YOU LATER!
TRY TO STAY OUT
OF TROUBLE, VASH.
EVERYONE AROUND YOU WILL BE
A WHOLE LOT HEALTHIER FOR IT.
AND WITH ANY LUCK,
WE'LL MEET AGAIN SOON.
MAY YOU ALL GO
WITH GOD, MY FRIENDS.
- HE WAS A STRANGE
AND UNUSUAL MAN.
- YEAH.
- AND THERE WENT WOLFWOOD.
OKAY, I THINK I'LL GO GET
SOMETHING YUMMY TO EAT!
- Milly: MMM,
THAT SOUNDS GOOD!
- Vash: BUT FIRST, I NEED YOU
TO RETURN THE MONEY I LENT YOU.
- Meryl: ALL RIGHT, ALREADY!
WE'LL GIVE IT BACK!
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE TO FIND US OR ANYTHING.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: I THINK I'D LIKE TO DO
SOMETHING NICE FOR SOMEBODY.
I THINK IT'S GOOD
IF YOU SMILE AT SOMEONE
AND THEY SMILE IN RETURN.
VOLUNTARY LOVE
ENCOURAGES PEOPLE
TO CREATE A SENSE
OF FRIENDLINESS.
LOVE THAT IS UNCONDITIONAL
GIVES US RESPECT AS PEOPLE.
HOWEVER, IT'S WRONG
TO FORCE LOVE
TO TRY TO KEEP IT ALIVE.
IT THE STRAIN GOES ON,
EVENTUALLY IT'LL BLOOM
INTO THE FLOWER CALLED LIE,
THE DECEPTIVELY THORNY FLOWER
THAT HURTS PEOPLE.