- ( theme music playing )
♪ OH! ♪
- ( rumbling )
- Milly: MERYL, LOOK!
- OH.
- Woman:
MERYL? MERYL?
MERYL, WAKE UP!
- OH, HI KAREN.
- INTERESTING MAKEUP JOB.
DID YOU ENJOY YOUR REST?
- ( laughs )
I'VE BEEN TRAVELING
AROUND FOR SO LONG,
I GUESS I HAVEN'T QUITE
REGAINED MY LAND LEGS YET.
- IT MUST BE STRANGE
TO BE HOME.
AFTER ALL, MISS STRYFE,
YOU WITNESSED THE HOLE
BEING BURNED
INTO THE FIFTH MOON.
HOW DID IT MAKE YOU FEEL
WHEN YOU LOOKED UP?
- THIS IS NOT SOME TOURIST
INTERVIEW, MARK. STOP IT!
YOU'RE TALKING TO SOMEONE
WHO SPENT FIVE MONTHS
ON THE OUTSIDE, WORKING
WITH THE ULTRA DANGEROUS
MAN WHO'S BEEN LABELED
A HUMAN DISASTER.
CONSIDERING EVERYTHING THAT'S
HAPPENED TO HER OUT THERE,
IT'S A MIRACLE THAT
SHE CAME BACK ALIVE.
- Meryl: YES, BUT...
- Both: HMMM?
- ACTUALLY IT WASN'T
AS BAD AS ALL THAT.
SURE, IT GOT A LITTLE BIT
SCARY AT TIMES,
AND THERE WAS
SOME DANGER INVOLVED,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
DESPITE HIS FRIGHTENING
AND AWFUL REPUTATION,
VASH TURNED OUT TO BE
MORE OF A REGULAR GUY
THAN YOU WOULD HAVE THOUGHT.
- REALITY CHECK, MERYL.
THAT ATTITUDE OF YOURS
GETS ALL OF THE ODDBALL JOBS,
WORKING WITH DANGEROUS SLIME.
IT'S GREAT THAT YOU'RE
SO COMPETENT AND WILLING,
BUT IF YOU KEEP RISKING
YOUR LIFE OUT THERE,
I'M AFRAID THERE'S NO WAY YOU'LL
EVER ACHIEVE WOMANLY HAPPINESS!
- EXCUSE ME, IS THIS SOCIAL
TIME, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN?
- ( gulps )
- UH, GOOD MORNING.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU, CHIEF!
- MERYL, WILL YOU PLEASE
STEP INTO MY OFFICE?
- UM, SIR?
- Both: HMM.
- Meryl: I HAVE TO WHAT?!
- HUH?
- MILLY?
MILLY, WHERE ARE YOU?
- I'M OUT HERE.
GOOD MORNING, MERYL.
- ( groans ) WHAT HAVE YOU
GOTTEN YOURSELF INTO NOW?
- I'M BEING PUNISHED
FOR COMING IN LATE
FOR WORK 20 TIMES IN A ROW.
- WHY DO I EXPECT HER
TO CHANGE? I'M DREAMING.
GUESS WHAT?
WE GOT ANOTHER ASSIGNMENT TODAY.
VASH THE STAMPEDE SHOWED
UP IN LITTLE JERSEY
AND WE'RE THE ONLY
ONES QUALIFIED.
WE LEAVE RIGHT AWAY.
- YAY, THEN IT'S REALLY TRUE?
VASH IS STILL ALIVE? DOESN'T
THAT MAKE YOU INCREDIBLY HAPPY?
- HMMM-- OOOH!
THERE IS NOTHING
TO BE HAPPY ABOUT.
OUR JOBS ARE
ON THE LINE HERE, MILLY.
WE HAVE TO STOP HIM THIS TIME
BEFORE HE STIRS UP
TROUBLE AGAIN.
NOW COME ON, YOU'RE WASTING
TIME. LET'S GET GOING.
- WAIT. HOLD ON A
SECOND, MERYL.
AREN'T YOU BEING A LITTLE HASTY?
- FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
IF HE'S ALIVE, HE COULD HAVE
AT LEAST MENTIONED IT.
HE PROBABLY GETS A KICK OUT
OF MAKING PEOPLE BITE HIS DUST.
THAT BUM.
- Karen: MERYL!
- I'LL BRING YOU BACK AN
A.A.P. BAG AS A SOUVENIR!
SEE YOU LATER, KAREN!
- OH WELL.
IT'S NO USE.
THERE SHE GOES AGAIN.
I SUPPOSED THERE'S
JUST SOME GIRLS
WHO NEED TO RISK THEIR LIVES.
- IF YOU'RE DEAD, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO SAY ANYTHING.
BUT IF YOU'RE ALIVE,
I WOULD APPRECIATE IF YOU
FELLOWS WOULD SAY SOMETHING.
I'LL GIVE YOU A LIFT.
- ( unison )
UH, GEE, BLESS YOU, MISTER.
- YEAH, I AM PRETTY DAMN
HAPPY TO BE ALIVE!
OH.
- ( gulping )
- WHY IS IT THAT I ALWAYS
RUN INTO SO MUCH TROUBLE
WHEN YOU'RE AROUND?
- ( laughs ) YOU'RE NOT A VERY
METHODICAL PERSON, ARE YOU?
NORMALLY WHEN
YOU BUY A USED BIKE,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
REPAIR IT, YOU KNOW?
MAKE SURE IT'S IN DECENT
CONDITION BEFORE YOU DECIDE
TO TAKE IT OUT AND RIDE IT.
- ARE YOU DISSING MY BEAUTIFUL
SHINY ANGELINA II, VASH?
- ACTUALLY I'M DISSING YOU, NOT
YOUR STUPID BROKEN MOTORCYCLE.
- COME AGAIN, NEEDLE-NOGGIN?
- HEY, WHO YOU CALLIN'
NEEDLE-NOGGIN?
- I'D SAY IT'S
PRETTY DARN OBVIOUS.
- ( both shout )
( screaming )
- Wolfwood: NOW LOOK
WHAT YOU'VE DONE, YOU IDIOT!
- OH, SO NOW IT'S MY FAULT, HUH?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT!
- SHUT UP BACK THERE
OR I'LL HAVE TO THROW YOU OUT!
- OH!
( both laugh )
YES SIR. WE'RE REALLY SORRY.
- ( groans )
ALL RIGHT, NOW WHERE
ARE YOU GUYS HEADED?
- KANSAS!
- NEW OREGON!
- Both: HUH?
- ( growls ) NEW OREGON?
WE'RE GOING TO THE TOWN
WITH ALL THE DISAPPEARANCES
IN SOUTHERN CORNELIA.
- NO, I WANNA GO TO NEW OREGON!
IF YOU WANNA GO TO KANSAS,
GO THERE BY YOURSELF!
- WHAT DID YOU SAY? -
Driver: I SAID SHUT UP, YOU TWO!
- OH, WE'RE SORRY.
- Meryl: THIS PLACE IS
REALLY FALLING APART.
- Man: THE LOCAL RIFFRAFF
WERE MAKING TROUBLE AS USUAL.
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN THIS GUY
STEPPED IN TO HELP.
SEEMED LIKE A PRETTY
WELL-MEANING FELLA.
UNFORTUNATELY THIS IS
WHAT HAPPENED AS A RESULT.
- ONCE AGAIN HE'S POKED
HIS NOSE INTO MORE TROUBLE.
HONESTLY, THAT MAN NEVER LEARNS.
- Milly: MERYL!
I JUST FOUND OUT WHERE VASH IS
AND THEY SAID HE'S OKAY.
- VASH?!
- YEP, THE ONE AND ONLY
HUMANOID TYPHOON.
- HUH?
- HE CARRIES THE DUBIOUS TITLE
OF MANKIND'S FIRST
LOCALIZED HUMAN DISASTER.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
WHEN I SAW HIM
HE WAS WEEPING AND EATING PILES
OF DONUTS AT THE SAME TIME!
JUST LIKE THIS!
- DONUTS ARE HIS FAVORITE FOOD.
- IT'S REALLY HIM?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS NUTCASE IS ACTUALLY
THE LEGENDARY GUNMAN?
- SO WHERE DID YOU GET
YOUR INFORMATION, MILLY?
- OVER THE SATELLITE.
EVERYONE'S TALKING ABOUT IT.
THE REPORT SAID THAT HE'S
HEADED FOR NEW OREGON
AT A SPEED OF 3,000
YARZ AN HOUR!
ISN'T THAT INCREDIBLE?
HE CAN MOVE REALLY FAST.
- THAT'S A LITTLE MORE
INFORMATION THAN I NEEDED.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
AND ONE OF THE LOCALS
WAS EVEN RUNNING AROUND,
TELLING EVERYONE TO BE CAREFUL!
- Man:
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS?
- Man #2: THE DAY
BEFORE YESTERDAY
MOST OF THE POLO FAMILY
WENT OUT OF TOWN,
LEAVING NO ONE THERE
BUT THE FOURTH SON SLATER.
ALSO I FOUND THERE'S A SHUTTLE
THAT GOES TO NEW OREGON.
IT'S IDEAL. A CHANCE LIKE
THIS DOESN'T COME TWICE.
- I-- I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
- Others: HUH?
- I THINK WE ALL AGREE
THE POLO FAMILY
CAN'T BE ALLOWED TO HAVE
THEIR WAY ANY MORE.
HUH? AREN'T I RIGHT?
- RIGHT. WELL, SORT OF.
AT LEAST THIS TIME
WE'LL HAVE MR. LURALD
WITH US TO BACK US UP.
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
- THAT SETTLES IT THEN.
ALL RIGHT, GENTLEMEN,
THIS IS IT.
WE'LL MEET HERE AGAIN
AT SUNUP TOMORROW.
- Man on P.A.:
Shut up and listen up!
Today, I'm going
to school you people.
Today's lesson is
about typhoons.
Since you probably
don't know, here I go.
A typhoon is a little phenomenon
where the wind blows like crazy
and carries your houses
and kids off into the sky.
Her name is Jacqueline!
And this lovely young lady
has come to wipe you out!
- WHAT'S ALL THIS
ABOUT, MR. TYPHOON?
ARE YOU EXPECTING A RELATIVE
OF YOURS SOMETIME SOON?
- SO IS THAT
WHAT A TYPHOON IS?
A FURIOUS BEAUTY
WHO LEVELS ENTIRE CITIES
WITHOUT EVEN A WARNING?
HUH.
- HMM, A BEAUTY?
SOUNDS PRETTY TOUGH.
HUH?
HEY, BY THE WAY,
WHO'S PICKING UP THE TAB
FOR THIS LITTLE FOOD?
- YOU, OF COURSE.
- ME? WHY ME?
I WAS THE ONE
GRACIOUS ENOUGH
TO GIVE IN TO YOUR
STUPID WHINING
AND COME ALL THE WAY
OUT HERE TO NEW OREGON!
- I DIDN'T ASK YOU
TO DO THAT!
- ( growls ) NOW LISTEN UP,
THIS TOWN MAY LOOK PEACEFUL,
BUT THINGS ARE LIKELY TO GET
BLOODY AROUND HERE AT ANY TIME.
- UH?
- I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU'RE AWARE OF THIS,
BUT THE POLO AND FRIS FAMILIES
ARE STILL QUARRELLING
OVER THE RIGHTS
TO THE SATELLITE.
A GIRL WHO WAS A DISTANT
COUSIN OF THE FRIS FAMILY
WAS MURDERED IN COLD BLOOD.
IT'S A HIGH-STAKES FEUD.
- ( sighs )
- MMM.
THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT,
I DON'T WANT THIS TOWN TO TURN
INTO ANOTHER LITTLE JERSEY.
LET'S TAKE OFF
BEFORE IT'S DESTROYED.
- ( whimpering )
- HMM?
KNOCK IT OFF!
- BUT DOESN'T THAT
STORY GET YOU UPSET?
WHY DO THINGS LIKE
THAT HAVE TO HAPPEN?
- IT'S NOT LIKE
IT'S ANYTHING NEW.
THIS KIND OF THING
HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
EVEN THE MOST PEACEFUL FOLK
WILL TAKE UP ARMS
IF SOMEONE HAPPENS TO THREATEN
OR KILL A FAMILY MEMBER.
BOTTOM LINE IS WE SHOULD GO
BEFORE WE GET INVOLVED IN THIS.
- MEOW MEOW.
- I ALWAYS HAD MY SUSPICIONS
THAT YOU WERE NO MERE MORTAL,
BUT I NEVER IMAGINED
YOU WERE ACTUALLY A CAT.
WAIT, WHAT THE HELL AM I SAYING?
WHERE IS THAT IDIOT?
- SIR?
- ( chokes )
- ALTOGETHER YOUR MEAL
COMES TO EXACTLY $$30.
- PUT IT ON MY TAB?
- NO DICE.
- ( Wolfwood growls )
ROTTEN NEEDLE-NOGGIN!
- ( door opens )
- UH, MR. SLATER!
THERE'S A HICK OUTSIDE
ASKING TO BE LET IN, SIR.
SIR?
- I'M NOT INTERESTED IN ANY
BEGGARS OR JOB HUNTERS.
JUST SEND HIM AWAY.
- Vash: A FRIEND OF
MINE WORKS HERE
AND I WAS IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
I JUST THOUGHT I'D DROP
BY TO SAY HI TO HIM.
- HEY! I DIDN'T SAY YOU COULD
COME IN HERE, STREET WORM.
- WHO ARE YOU HERE TO SEE?
- HIS NAME IS MAX SIMON!
- THAT OLD CODGER
ACTUALLY HAS FRIENDS?
GO AHEAD, ENTERTAIN HIM.
- ALL RIGHT, THANKS A LOT.
I APPRECIATE IT. BYE.
- ( sighs )
SURE ABOUT THIS, BOSS?
- DO I REALLY HAVE A CHOICE?
HE'S A FRIEND OF MAX'S
AND I'M NOT ABOUT TO
START ANY TROUBLE NOW.
- Meryl:
THIS WAS A GOOD IDEA.
WE DID THE RIGHT
THING TO SPLURGE
ON A ROOM IN SECOND-CLASS!
- YEAH, THE LAST TIME
WE RODE ONE OF THESE,
IT WAS FULL OF BANDITS.
THE WHOLE
EXPERIENCE WAS RUINED!
- IF WE RUN INTO HIM
IN NEW OREGON,
THINGS ARE GOING
TO GET REAL BUSY.
LET'S ENJOY THE PEACE
WHILE IT LASTS.
- I GUESS THAT MEANS
WE'RE GONNA GET DRAGGED
INTO TROUBLE AGAIN, HUH?
- ( both gargling )
- ( gunshots )
- ( both yelp )
- Man: BANDITS!
- HANDS IN THE AIR
AND MOUTHS SHUT!
YOU'D BETTER NOT
TRY ANYTHING FUNNY,
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
- ( both whimper )
NOT AGAIN!
- ( laughs )
I SUGGEST YOU ALL BEHAVE,
IF YOU VALUE YOUR LIVES!
- ( grunts )
- MAKE THIS EASY ON
YOURSELF AND DON'T MOVE.
I PROMISE, YOU WON'T BE HARMED
IF YOU JUST COOPERATE.
- YOU HAVE A CHANCE
TO STOP THIS RIGHT NOW
AND THE LAW WILL
BE MORE LENIENT.
- I GAVE UP MY LIFE
A LONG TIME AGO.
BESIDES, THERE'S A DAMN
GOOD REASON I'M DOING THIS
AND I DON'T CARE
WHAT THE COST IS.
- ( gasps )
- WE'VE ALMOST
REACHED OUR DESTINATION!
- MAKE SURE YOU
KEEP AN EYE ON THEM.
- GOT IT!
- IF SHE WERE ALIVE, SHE'D BE
ABOUT YOUR AGE NOW, YOU KNOW?
- ( girls sigh )
- ( knocks )
- I'M NOT FINISHED
WITH THE FORECAST.
BEAT IT! LEAVE ME ALONE.
- I CAN SEE YOU HAVEN'T
CHANGED A BIT, OLD MAN.
- VASH! IT'S BEEN
A VERY LONG TIME!
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE OLD SNAPPY OUTFIT?
- I GUESS I KIND OF WORE
IT OUT ON MY LAST JOB.
- ( laughs )
WELL, WELCOME BACK.
YOU ARE HERE ON BUSINESS
OR JUST COME TO PEEK
UP JACQUELINE'S DRESS?
HMM? HAS IT REALLY BEEN 10 YEARS
SINCE YOUR LAST VISIT, VASH?
- ( chuckles ) WHOA!
- ( crashing )
- OH!
WHAT WAS THAT?
- ( robbers yelling )
FIND THAT POLO SON!
- NO MERCY,
KILL ANYONE WHO RESISTS!
- ( panting )
WHERE IS HE?!
I WANT HIM!
- HOLY COW!
A MONSTER IDIOT
JUST CRASHED A SAND STEAMER
INTO MY EXALTED PLACE OF WORK!
I'VE HEARD OF PEOPLE
FALLING ASLEEP AT THE WHEEL,
BUT THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
- ( panting )
- HUH? MR. S?
- ( gunshots )
- ( screams )
- Wolfwood: PARDON ME,
COMING THROUGH.
EXCUSE ME, LADIES,
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- ( shrieks )
- OOH, THIS IS BAD.
LOOKS LIKE A RAID!
- P.A.: Citizens of New Oregon,
listen carefully.
The Fris family has seized
this satellite facility!
The injustice we have
suffered at the hands of the
greedy vicious Polos has
left us with no choice.
We have but one demand:
bring us the head
of the Polo family!
WE HAVE A GUEST WE THINK WILL
BE OF GREAT INTEREST TO HIM.
- Slater: Help me.
Somebody help me!
- ( thinks )
SO THAT'S HOW IT IS.
- P.A.: If our demands are
not met within three days,
I will not be able
to guarantee his safety.
- THE HEAD OF THE FAMILY
IS IN NEO COLORADO.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE. HE'LL NEVER
MAKE IT BACK WITHIN THREE DAYS.
ARE YOU GOING IN?
- YOU KNOW ME, MAX. IT'S JUST
MY NATURE. I HAVE TO DO IT.
- ALL RIGHT!
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS KILL POLO, USE JACQUELINE
FOR COVER, AND MAKE TRACKS.
PIECE OF CAKE.
- WHO'S JACQUELINE?
- IT'S THE NAME OF THE TYPHOON
WHICH IS HEADING FOR THIS TOWN,
AND IT'S COMING SOON,
LITTLE LADY.
- HE'S TALKING ABOUT THE REAL
STORM KIND OF TYPHOON.
HOW IN THE WORLD DID
YOU MIX THAT UP, MILLY?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
- I FEEL SO SILLY.
IT SLIPPED MY MIND.
DARN IT!
I HATE BEING WRONG.
- Meryl: THAT'S NOT
WHAT I WANT TO HEAR.
- ( clangs )
- ( moaning )
- ( Milly laughs )
- COME ON, LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE, MILLY!
- ALL RIGHT.
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
- I DON'T THINK SO!
- HUH?
( groans )
I... I SAW WHITE ANGELS.
( moans )
- THEY SEEM TO HAVE
THE HOSTAGES UNDER CONTROL.
HE SAYS WE CAN DO WHATEVER
WE WANT WITH THE OTHERS.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- SOUNDS GOOD. I SAY
WE GO HAVE SOME FUN.
I JUST LOVE PARTY TIME.
- Vash: YOU TWO SHOULD BE
ASHAMED OF YOURSELVES.
- Both: HUH? OOOH!
- VASH, AMAZING. ARE YOU
STILL DOING THINGS THIS WAY?
- UH, YEAH.
( gunshot )
- WHAT THE HELL?
- ARE YOU A POLO BODYGUARD?
- NO, I'M NOT.
- IF YOU HAVE A DEATH WISH,
GENTLEMEN, TRY TO TAKE US DOWN!
BUT BEFORE YOU DO, YOU
SHOULD KNOW THAT THIS MAN IS
VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?!
- AW, COME ON, MAX.
- CAN YOU AT LEAST ACT THE PART?
THEY'LL CHICKEN OUT AND RUN AWAY
AND WE WON'T HAVE TO FIGHT THEM.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK SO?
( clicks )
- ( whimpering )
( footsteps )
- HUH?
- ( panting )
- ( man yawns )
- ( whimpering )
- EASE UP THERE, BENSON.
THERE'S NO ONE
TO SHOOT HERE.
NOW TAKE YOUR FINGER
OFF THE TRIGGER.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
- Man: LISTEN UP!
- Both: HUH?
- Lurald: WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S THE GUNMAN.
IT'S VASH THE STAMPEDE!
HE'S COMING OUR WAY.
HE'S COMING!
- YOU SAW HIM?
- BUT WHY?
WHAT WOULD VASH THE STAMPEDE
BE DOING HERE?
- THIS IS LIKE A BAD DREAM.
- ENOUGH, CALM DOWN!
- HUH?
- ( growls )
RUMORS LIKE THIS
ARE ALWAYS EXAGGERATED.
AND EVEN IF HE IS
THE REAL THING...
HE STILL HAS TO TAKE
THAT PASSAGE TO GET HERE.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY IN.
REMEMBER IT'S THE REASON
WE CHOSE THIS LOCATION.
- HUH. OH YEAH.
- ( footsteps )
- HUH?
- H-HE'S HERE!
- ( slow footsteps )
Vash:
♪ TOTAL SLAUGHTER ♪
♪ TOTAL SLAUGHTER... ♪
- ( whimpering )
- ♪ I WON'T LEAVE ♪
♪ A single man alive ♪
( footsteps continue )
♪ La-dee-da-di die... ♪
- HUH?
- ♪ Genocide ♪
♪ La-dee-da-di dud,
an ocean of blood ♪
♪ LET'S BEGIN ♪
♪ THE KILLING TIME. ♪
( footsteps )
- Thug: HE'S... SINGING?
- GOD, WHAT HORRIBLE LYRICS!
- STAY RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
- HUH?
- HE'S JUST TRYING
TO SCARE YOU.
- ( Vash sighs )
I KNEW IT WOULDN'T WORK.
- HUH?
- HEY, CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING?
- Lurald:
YEAH, WHAT?
- WOULD YOU PREFER TO
CALL OFF OUR LITTLE GAME
LIKE A SENSIBLE ADULT,
OR WOULD YOU RATHER GET INJURED
AND BE OUT OF THE GAME FOR GOOD?
- HOW ABOUT A NEW GAME?
I'LL ANSWER YOUR QUESTION
WITH ANOTHER QUESTION:
NOW THAT I'LL PLAY, DO YOU
WANT A BELLY FULL OF LEAD?
- OH, WHAT A SHAME!
A NEGOTIATIONS BREAKDOWN.
( footsteps )
- GET OUT OF MY WAY!
( grunts )
- WHAT? SHIT, THIS GUY
CAN'T BE FOR REAL!
- ( all gasp )
- ( yelping )
- HEY, MR. LURALD.
HE'S GONE.
( moans )
- HAH.
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
THE FIGHT IS OVER.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO LET
GO OF THE HOSTAGE NOW.
- NEVER!
ACTUALLY
I'M GRATEFUL TO YOU.
NOW THAT THAT'S OUT OF THE WAY,
I'M GONNA GET TO KILL HIM!
- I'LL WHACK YOU, MISTER.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY
GIVE YOU THE RIGHT
TO DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- ( growls )
- NOW COME ON. GIVE
THE GUY A BREAK.
- FORGET IT!
- AHH, WOULD YOU KNOCK IT OFF?!
- HE KILLED HER!
- UH.
- ( whimpering )
- THIS BASTARD KILLED HER.
HE KILLED MY DAUGHTER
AND HE'S GONNA DIE.
( over P.A. ) He's going to pay
for her death with his life!
- ( murmuring )
- ( thinking )
WE'RE NOTHING LIKE GOD.
NOT ONLY DO WE HAVE
LIMITED POWERS,
WE SOMETIMES ARE DRIVEN
TO BECOME THE DEVIL HIMSELF.
- ( whimpering )
- Wolfwood: WHAT'S YOUR
ANSWER THIS TIME?
- ( grunts )
- THAT WAS MY DAUGHTER.
MY DAUGHTER...
- Man: THIS IS HORRIBLE.
DEAR GOD, NOT AGAIN.
I KNOW SHE'S RELATED
TO THE FRIS,
BUT SHE HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH IT!
- EH, I'LL MAKE IT FAST.
- UH--
- ( cocks )
ONCE I'M FINISHED HERE, YOU CAN
HAND ME OVER TO THE SHERIFF
OR EVEN THE CAVALRY
FOR ALL I CARE!
- Slater: DON'T DO IT! PLEASE!
I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
( sobs ) FORGIVE ME.
FORGIVE ME, PLEASE!
I'M SORRY.
- HOW DARE YOU BEG
FOR YOUR LIFE?
WHAT ABOUT MY DAUGHTER
BEGGING FOR HERS?
WHEN I SAW WHAT YOU DID
TO MY LITTLE AILEEN,
MY AILEEN... NO HUMAN BEING
COULD DO SUCH AN EVIL THING!
YOU PEOPLE...
YOU PEOPLE AREN'T HUMAN
AND YOU ALL NEED TO DIE!
- DON'T LET ME DIE!
STOP! STOP!
OH, STOP PLEASE.
- JUSTICE AT LAST.
- ( whimpering )
- DON'T, IT'S WRONG!
- I MUST AVENGE HER.
- ( wailing )
- GET OFF! WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS?
YOU COULD NEVER
UNDERSTAND HOW I FEEL!
( blows thud )
I DON'T WANT YOUR HELP!
( grunting )
LET GO OF ME!
( grunts )
- ( whimpering )
- ( cocks )
- DADDY! DADDY!
- ( sighs )
- ( Slater sobbing )
DADDY! DADDY!
- ( growls )
HOW MANY TIMES DID MY
DAUGHTER SCREAM FOR HER DADDY?
- ( sobbing )
- HOW MANY TIMES?!
- DON'T TAKE
THIS MAN'S LIFE!
DON'T KILL HIM, PLEASE!
PLEASE DON'T SHOOT HIM!
DON'T DO IT, I'M BEGGING YOU!
- ( sobbing over P.A. )
- THIS IS SO STRANGE, AILEEN.
I-I CAN'T SHOOT HIM.
WHY CAN'T I DO IT?
I WANT TO AVENGE YOU...
HE SHOULD DIE!
( sobbing )
- OH, THANK GOODNESS.
- HUH?
- IT'S NOTHING. I'M JUST
GLAD IT'S OVER NOW.
I THINK IT WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA
TO GET BOTH OF THEM
AS FAR AWAY FROM HERE AS WE CAN
BEFORE THE CAVALRY ARRIVES.
- Man: GET A STRETCHER
OVER HERE!
- The shootout which began
late this afternoon
was brought to a
safe conclusion with
one swift charge of the cavalry!
The 12 idiots who were
held hostage, myself included,
were freed. For an incident
involving the humanoid typhoon,
the damage wasn't that bad!
But the day after tomorrow,
a real typhoon is
coming to town.
Be very very careful,
boys and girls.
- Wolfwood: GO EASY ON
THE NICE-GUY STUFF, OKAY?
YOU'VE GOTTA START
TAKING CARE OF YOURSELF.
LUCK AND PERSISTENCE
WON'T WORK FOREVER.
SO LONG.
- UH?
- ( giggles )
- Vash:
LONG TIME NO SEE.
- YEAH.
- I HAVE NOW FOUND HIM.
I WILL TOTAL EVERYTHING
SO MY CONCLUSION
WILL THEN BE FINAL.
THERE IS NO DOUBT.
VASH THE STAMPEDE
HAS BEGUN TO MOVE,
MR. LEGATO.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: IN TIMES OF HARDSHIP,
IN TIMES OF SADNESS,
THERE IS A PLACE THE TRAVELER
CAN LET HIS MIND RETURN TO...
HOME.
I STILL DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF A PAST THE TRAVELER ABANDONED
WHEN HE LEFT
HIS HOME BEHIND.
I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT KIND OF SORROW HE BEARS.
BUT THE TRAVELER CAN
KEEP WALKING FORWARD
BECAUSE HE HAS SOMETHING
WHICH SUSTAINS HIM,
A PLACE WHICH ACCEPTS HIM.
HE CAN WALK FORWARD
STEP BY CAREFUL STEP.