- ( theme music playing )
- HEY, VASH.
- ( breathing heavily )
- NOW EVERYTHING THAT BROUGHT
YOU AND REM TOGETHER IS GONE.
- IS THAT YOUR EXCUSE
FOR KILLING?!
- HAVEN'T YOU LEARNED ANYTHING
OVER THE PAST 100 YEARS?
YOU CAN'T EVEN
REGENERATE THE SCARS
THEY CARVED
INTO YOUR BODY.
IT'S SYMBOLIC OF YOUR
FOOLISH WASTE OF ENERGY
ON THIS GARBAGE.
- IT'S NOT YOUR RIGHT TO DECIDE
WHETHER THEY LIVE OR DIE.
THEY DESERVE A CHANCE!
- WHAT'S THE USE IN GROWING UP
IF THE ONLY THING THAT GROWS
IS YOUR SENTIMENTALISM?!
YOU'RE STILL A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
PATHETIC WIMP!
- ( grunts )
AAH!
WHAT-- WHAT IS THAT?
- THIS IS WHAT WE'RE CAPABLE OF.
IT'S TIME TO TAKE THIS GARBAGE
AND GET RID OF IT FOREVER!
- ( screaming )
- ARE YOU AIMING AT ME AGAIN?
- ( pained groaning )
- ARE YOU ACTUALLY
AIMING AT ME AGAIN?
AAH!
- Lina:
ERICS!  ERICS!
- ( door opens )
- HOW LONG ARE YOU PLANNING
ON STAYING IN BED, ERICS?
COME ON NOW, GET UP.
ERICS!
- THERE HE IS!
- ( people clamoring )
- COME ON, YOU GOTTA LET US
ON THIS BUS.
- HE MIGHT TRY
AND TAKE THIS TOWN.
- I HAVE MONEY,
LET ME ON THIS BUS.
WHILE WE'RE STANDING HERE
ARGUING, IT COULD BE TOO LATE.
- YOU NEED A TICKET TO RIDE,
MISTER, AND I DON'T GIVE A DAMN.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?!
DON'T YOU GET IT YET?
JUST NAME YOUR PRICE.
I'LL PAY ANYTHING!
- ( guns cock )
- ( grunts )
- ( people clamoring )
- THERE SURE SEEMS TO BE
AN AWFUL LOT OF TENSION
IN THIS TOWN.
- HAVEN'T SEEN YOU BEFORE.
I TAKE IT YOU JUST ARRIVED.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- WELL, YOU HAVE MY SYMPATHY,
'CAUSE YOU'RE NEVER
GONNA LEAVE THIS TOWN.
- ( all scream )
- WHAT HAPPENED OVER THERE?
- THIS TOWN HAS BEEN COMPLETELY
TAKEN OVER BY BANDITS.
- HMM?
- AND TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE,
THEY SAY THAT CRAZY FELLA,
VASH THE STAMPEDE,
IS RUNNING THE SHOW.
THE SHERIFF WENT OUT
TO NEGOTIATE WITH THE VARMINTS,
BUT WHEN HE CAME BACK, HE HAD
DOUBLED HIS WEIGHT IN LEAD.
WALKING INTO THIS TOWN
IS LIKE WALKING INTO A
GIANT SPIDER'S WEB.
- THE LEGENDARY GUNMAN'S
BEHIND THIS?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DO YOU BELIEVE IT?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK.
HE IS THE MAN WHO TURNED TWO
OF THE SEVEN CITIES INTO ASHES
AND WAS CALLED "MANKIND'S
FIRST LOCALIZED DISASTER."
SOME FOLKS SAY HE PUT
THAT HUGE CRATER IN THE MOON.
I GUESS YOU'D HAVE TO BE NUTS
TO BELIEVE THAT.
- ANYWAY, WHETHER THE LEGEND
IS TRUE OR NOT,
THE ONE THING I DO KNOW IS THIS
TOWN IS IN SOME BIG TROUBLE.
- BY THE WAY, FRIEND,
WHAT IS THAT THING?
- I'M A TRAVELING PRIEST.
- WELL, THAT'S GOOD TIMING.
YOU'LL BE USEFUL HERE.
DON'T NEED ANYTHING FORMAL,
JUST SOME HELP
WITH THE FUNERALS.
THEY TOOK OUT THE CHAPLAIN
A WHILE BACK.
- ( guns cock )
- HMM?
- UH-OH.  UM...
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA,
YOU GUYS?!
- OH, IT'S ONLY LINA.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"ONLY LINA"?
LET GO OF ME, ERICS.
( humphs )
- LINA, WHAT'S THE BIG HURRY?
- I WAS WONDERING IF
YOU COULD HIDE ME SOMEWHERE.
- WHAT'D YOU DO THIS TIME?
- SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WHEN TO QUIT.
SHE WAS JUST HAVING SOME
HARMLESS FUN, THAT'S ALL.
- THE GUY'S A PEDOPHILE.
HE DESERVED A GOOD THUMP.
- NOT REALLY.  ALL HE DID WAS
GRAB HER REAR-END.
- ( grunts )
- ( yelps )
- WILL YOU KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT?
- WHAT ARE YOU TELLING ME?
OH, MY DEAR.
- YEAH, I'M AFRAID SO.
AND THEY WEREN'T REAL HAPPY
ABOUT IT.
BUT AT LEAST I DON'T THINK
THEY SAW ME COMING IN HERE.
- HEY, THAT'S NOT FUNNY, KID.
- OHH!
- IF WHAT SHE SAYS IS TRUE...
- ( wind blowing )
- ( all scream )
- HEY, I WASN'T DONE
EATING YET.
- ALL RIGHT,
WHERE'S THE LITTLE GIRL
WHO STRUCK MY FACE
WITH HER HEEL?!
SHE'S GOT A PRICE TO PAY
AND I'M HERE TO COLLECT!
- THAT HEEL LOOKS MORE
LIKE A WHOLE FOOTPRINT.
- AH, QUIET, YOU!
- I COULD SEE WHY HE'S UPSET.
IT DOES RUIN
HIS BOYISH GOOD LOOKS.
- THIS GUY SAYS
HE SAW HER ENTER THAT BAR.
IF HE'S WRONG, HE'S DEAD.
WHY?  BECAUSE I LIKE TO KILL
SCUM WHO WASTE MY PRECIOUS TIME.
IN ANY EVENT,
THIS PROBLEM WILL BE SETTLED
IN APPROXIMATELY
THREE MINUTES, TWO SECONDS.
THREE...
- ( all gasp )
- ...TWO...
ONE!  HE DIES!
HMM?
- ERICS, WAIT A SECOND!
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?!
- OH, HEY.
HI THERE, MR. BANDIT MAN.
WE'RE SORRY YOU DIDN'T
FIND IT THAT FUNNY.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY THAT
SHE'S ONLY A LITTLE 12-YEAR-OLD.
COME ON NOW.
HAVE A HEART, WON'T YOU?
( screams )
- SEND OUT THE KID NOW,
OR ELSE.
- I'M AFRAID
THAT'S NOT AN OPTION.
LOOKS LIKE YOU WANNA KILL HER
OR CAUSE HER SOME KIND OF HARM.
I WON'T EVEN ASK
FOR A FREE FAVOR.
HOW ABOUT IF I DO THIS?
- ( gasps )
- WILL YOU LET HER
OFF THE HOOK?
- ERICS...
- SORRY, BUT THAT'S NOT
GOOD ENOUGH, BLONDIE.
IF YOU'RE GONNA GO DOWN
ON ALL FOURS,
THE LEAST YOU COULD DO IS
ACT LIKE A DOG,
AND I EXPECT
SOME REAL COMMITMENT.
NATURALLY THAT MEANS
GETTING NAKED.
- ( gasps )
- All: UH...
- ALL RIGHT, IT'S A DEAL.
YOU'VE GOTTA KEEP YOUR WORD.
- All: OH...
- I CAN'T LET YOU
DO THIS, ERICS!
PLEASE, STOP!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO IT!
ERICS!
- ( buckles jingle )
- ( gasps, murmurs )
- ERICS...
- ( chuckling )
HUH?
- OH, MY GOD.
- ( cries )
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT, KID.
HE'S GOT HIS REASONS.
WE'VE GOTTA TRUST THAT
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
- BUT WHY?
- THAT'S JUST THE WAY HE IS.
- ( howling )
( barking )
- I'M GONNA THANK YOU
FOR THE CANINE TRICKS.
I'VE DECIDED TO YOU GIVE YOU
A NICE, BIG TIP.
OH?
( groans )
LET'S GO.
- ( chuckles )
- ( crying )
- SHOOT HIM.
- ( gun cocks )
- ( gunfire )
- ERICS!
- OH.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO THIS MAN?
- HE'S BEEN SHOT.
YOU GOTTA HELP HIM!
- ERICS AGAIN.
WHAT'S HAPPENED THIS TIME?
- I CAN'T TELL IF THE BULLET'S
STILL INSIDE HIM, DOC.
- IF YOU HAD TO CHOOSE BETWEEN
YOUR LIFE AND YOUR PRIDE,
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'D DO?
- I DON'T KNOW, BUT I WOULD
NEVER STRIP BUCK-NAKED
AND BARK LIKE A DOG.
- TALENT LIKE THAT COMES EASY
FOR A WIMP LIKE ERICS.
- ( both grunt )
- IF IT WEREN'T FOR THAT WIMP,
YOU TWO WOULD BE DEAD.
- OH, ERICS!
- Lina: GRANDMA!
- HUH?
- MY POOR ERICS.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, GRANDMA.
THEY WERE ABLE TO GET
THE BULLET OUT IF HIM SAFELY.
- I'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND HIM.
HE'S ONE LUCKY DEVIL.
- I DON'T KNOW WHO THIS
LEGENDARY GUNMAN THINKS HE IS,
BUT WHAT IN THE HELL
GIVES HIM THE RIGHT
TO STEAL WHAT PRECIOUS
LITTLE FAMILY I HAVE LEFT?
DAMN HIM, ANYWAY!
- HEY HEY, EASY THERE.
NOW DON'T GO DOING THAT.
- YOU WON'T LAST TWO SECONDS
AGAINST HIM.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
- Grandma:
OH, LET ME GO!
ALL RIGHT, HOW ABOUT YOU
GOING IN MY PLACE?!
( laughs )
SEE?
YOU'RE ALL A BUNCH OF COWARDS.
YOU WEAK,
YOUNG WHIPPERSNAPPERS
HAVE NO RIGHT
TO ORDER ME AROUND!
- YOU'RE GONNA GET YOURSELF
KILLED, YOU STUPID OLD BAT!
- OH, SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
- GRANDMA, DON'T SAY THAT.
- I CAN'T, LINA.
- ALL OF THIS IS MY FAULT.
IF I HAD JUST STAYED AWAY
FROM THEM,
HE WOULDN'T HAVE--
( crying )
I'M SO SORRY, ERICS.
- IF YOU'RE QUITE FINISHED HERE,
COULD YOU PLEASE KEEP
THE NOISE DOWN?
THERE ARE OTHER PATIENTS HERE.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME, DOCTOR.
- I UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL.
YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY.
I'LL HAVE ERICS MOVED
TO THE WARD RIGHT AWAY.
- THANK YOU, DOCTOR.
LINA, LET'S FETCH HIM
A CHANGE OF CLOTHES.
- OKAY.
( sniffles )
- LET'S MOVE HIM
AND GET THIS PLACE CLEANED UP.
HMM?
OH, HELLO.
SORRY, I DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT NOW,
I ASSURE YOU.
- I KNOW THAT.
NO PROBLEM.
I JUST STOPPED BY
TO SEE IF I COULD HELP OUT.
( sighs )
YOU JUST GONNA SLEEP?
SNAP OUT OF IT!
- WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU DOING TO HIM?!
- HE NEEDED IT!
- DOCTOR, LOOK AT THAT!
OH, MY GOSH!
- HUH?
- HEY!
- WHAT AN AMAZING RECOVERY.
YOU'VE REGAINED CONSCIOUSNESS
SO QUICKLY.
- EXCUSE ME, DOCTOR?
BUT COULD YOU LEAVE THE ROOM
FOR A LITTLE WHILE?
- WELL, YES, I SUPPOSE.
DON'T LET HIM STRAIN HIMSELF,
YOU UNDERSTAND?
- ( door opens, closes )
- WELL, IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- ( rock music playing )
- I FINALLY FOUND YOU,
YOU DUMB JERK.
WHAT'S A LEGENDARY GUY LIKE YOU
DOING IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH.
I COULD HAVE DESTROYED
THIS ENTIRE PLANET
WITH THAT ANGEL ARM
OF MINE.
IT GETS WORSE.
THERE'S A LOSS OF MEMORY.
I DON'T REMEMBER
WHAT I DID.
- THAT MAY BE TRUE.
BUT YOU DO KNOW
YOU DID IT, RIGHT?
- OH, YEAH, I KNOW.
I HAVE FRAGMENTED VISIONS.
BUT MORE THAN ANYTHING...
THERE'S AN ACHE IN MY HEART
THAT TELLS ME I DID IT.
I KNOW I'M THE ONE WHO PUT
THE HOLE IN THE FIFTH MOON.
IT WAS ME.
- OKAY, SO YOU DID
THIS TERRIBLE THING.
NOW WHAT? ARE YOU SO AFRAID
OF WHAT YOU CAN DO,
YOU'RE LIVING
IN EASY RETIREMENT?
- NO.
IT'S JUST THAT I WANNA
LIVE QUIETLY FOR ONCE.
SO I DECIDED TO CHANGE MY NAME
AND MY WAY OF LIFE.
( softly groans )
WHY ARE YOU HERE, WOLFWOOD?
WHAT BRINGS YOU TO THIS TOWN?
ARE YOU HANGING AROUND
FOR A GOOD LAUGH?
- ACTUALLY, I CAME TO
TAKE YOU AWAY.
- AWAY WHERE?
- WELL, IF YOU'RE ASKING ME
FOR A FINAL DESTINATION,
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA.
HOWEVER, THE ONE THING
I DO KNOW IS I NEED YOUR HELP.
I SPENT A LOT OF TIME
COMBING THROUGH AUGUSTA,
TRYING TO FIND YOU.
DOES THE NAME FRANK MARLON
HAPPEN TO RING A BELL?
ALL I DID WAS MENTION YOUR NAME,
AND HE FIXED THE GUN FOR FREE.
- MAYBE.
WHY GIVE IT TO ME?  HUH?
- I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT NEED IT.
- WHAT I NEED?
WHAT I WANT IS TO LIVE
MY LIFE HERE...
WITH THEM.
- WHY WAS HE HOSPITALIZED
THE LAST TIME, LINA?
- HE TRIED TO STOP
A VIOLENT DRUNK AT THE BAR,
AND ENDED UP
GETTING PUNCHED HIMSELF.
- AND WHAT ABOUT
THE TIME BEFORE THAT?
- HE FELL OFF A THOMAS.
- ( clicks tongue )
AWW.
BE SURE YOU REMEMBER
TO THANK HIM.
- I KNOW.
I'LL REMEMBER, GRANDMA.
OH.
( echoing )
HELLO THERE.
UH, ARE YOU OKAY?
OH...
- YOU'RE IN HORRIBLE SHAPE.
YOU POOR THING.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
THROUGH AN AWFUL LOT.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE.
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOU.
- SO YOU'RE STAYING HERE, HUH?
- WHENEVER I DO ANYTHING,
PEOPLE DIE.
- ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU WANT THIS PATHETIC
LITTLE EXISTENCE SO BAD
THAT YOU'D GIVE UP
EVERYTHING ELSE...
THEN GO FOR IT.
BY THE WAY,
ARE YOU FAMILIAR WITH
A TOWN CALLED CARCASSES?
IT'S A TINY TOWN
ON THE SOUTHERN CORNELIA REGION.
SOMETHING REALLY
STRANGE HAPPENED THERE
ABOUT SIX MONTHS AGO.
SEEMS THE ENTIRE POPULATION
SUDDENLY DISAPPEARED
WITHOUT A TRACE.
THERE WAS NO SIGN
OF EVEN THE SLIGHTEST STRUGGLE.
EVERYTHING IN TOWN
LOOKED COMPLETELY NORMAL,
EXCEPT THAT ALL THE PEOPLE
HAD VANISHED,
LIKE A MIRAGE.
THEY SENT IN THE CAVALRY
AND SEARCHED THE PLACE OVER,
BUT DIDN'T FIND A SOUL.
ONE CAVALRYMAN DID DISCOVER
SOMETHING ODD, THOUGH.
THERE WAS A MAN'S NAME
PAINTED ON THE MONUMENT
IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE TOWN SQUARE.
IT WAS ONE WORD,
CAREFULLY WRITTEN IN RED.
KNIVES.
- DAMN YOU, KNIVES.
IT DOESN'T SEEM TO MATTER
HOW FAR I TRAVEL,
MY DESTINY IS ALWAYS FOLLOWED
BY BLOOD AND GUN SMOKE.
THE RESULT IS THE SAME
EVERY TIME--
MOUNTAINS OF DEATH
AND DEBRIS.
- YOU GOT TO COME WITH US, VASH!
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE US!
- Rem:
VASH, TAKE CARE OF KNIVES.
- ( inaudible )
- NO, REM, COME BACK!
- ( crying )
WHAT--?
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- Grandma: YOUR GUN.
GIVE ME YOUR GUN, HURRY!
- GRANDMA SHERYL,
WHAT-- WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S LINA-- THEY GOT HER!
- WHAT?  HOW?
- JUST GIVE IT TO ME, NOW!
- STOP!  YOU'LL THROW
YOUR LIFE AWAY!
BESIDES, THEY'VE PROBABLY
ALREADY KILLED HER.
- OH, SHUT UP!
DON'T ARGUE WITH ME!
JUST GIVE ME THE GUN.
- SHERYL SHERYL, WAIT!
- ( door opens )
- HMM...
- YOU KNOW,
I WAS KINDA FOND
OF MY NEW LIFE HERE.
I REALLY HATE TO LEAVE.
- SORRY, THEM'S THE BREAKS.
SOMEONE'S GOTTA GET TOUGH
AROUND HERE,
OR THOSE MANIACS ARE
GONNA DESTROY THIS TOWN.
- ( running footsteps
approaching )
- THEY'RE BOTH GONE.
"PLEASE DON'T FOLLOW US.
TELL EVERYONE TO STAY
WHERE THEY ARE.
WE'VE GONE TO GET LINA."
BY THEMSELVES?
- HOW MANY ARE THERE?
- ABOUT 200.
- 100 FOR EACH OF US, HUH?
- YEP.
- WELL, THAT'S NOT
EXACTLY FAIR TO THEM.
- UH-- HEY!  I DON'T WANT YOU
KILLING ANYONE, ALL RIGHT?
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST ASK ME
NOT TO BREATHE?
- "THOU SHALT NOT KILL,"
REMEMBER?
WHAT KIND OF CHURCH MAN
ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
- HMM?
( chuckles )
WHOA, DEJA VU.
I'VE HEARD THAT BEFORE.
NOW YOU'RE STARTING TO SOUND
LIKE YOUR OLD SELF.
- ( cackling )
- ERICS!
- OH.
- ( men laughing )
- TIME TO KILL!
- Both: SHOWTIME.
- WHY DID I HAVE TO GO AND TALK
TO SOMEONE THIS FILTHY, ANYWAY?
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
I GUESS I MUST BE CRAZY.
( softly chuckles )
- Man #1: WHAT A MESS!
HOW THE HELL
DID THOSE TWO MANAGE
TO TAKE CARE OF ALL THEM
THUGS BY THEMSELVES?
- Man #2: I HAVE NO IDEA.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
SO HORRIFYINGLY STRONG.
- Grandma:
SO YOUR MIND IS MADE UP THEN?
- YES, I'M SORRY.
IT'S TIME I GO.
EVEN THOUGH I HATE TO DO THIS
TO YOU AND LINA.
- ISN'T THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO, ERICS?
MAYBE IF YOU TELL ME ABOUT IT,
I COULD HELP SOMEHOW.
- THANK YOU, BUT I CAN'T.
BECAUSE, YOU SEE, IF I DID...
I'D ONLY BE PUTTING
YOU AND LINA IN DANGER.
- HERE YOU HAVE A HOME.
YOU COULD END UP ALONE AGAIN,
WITH NO ONE THERE TO HELP.
THAT'S WHAT WORRIES US
THE MOST ABOUT YOUR LEAVING.
- I'M SORRY.
- WHO WOULD HAVE GUESSED THAT
ERICS WAS VASH THE STAMPEDE.
UNBELIEVABLE.
- YEAH, TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- AND TO THINK
THAT ALL THIS TIME
WE WERE CONVINCED
THAT THIS PIG MAN WAS VASH.
SO, YOU THINK THE
LEGENDARY GUNMAN'S
GONNA STICK AROUND THESE PARTS?
- SHOOT, DON'T EVEN GO THERE.
HAVEN'T WE SUFFERED ENOUGH?
- YEAH!  WE OUGHTA
RUN HIM OUT RIGHT NOW.
- SHE CRIED, HUH?
THAT'S A SHAME.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
GEE, NOW I FEEL BAD.
I GUESS MAYBE I WAS ACTING
JUST A LITTLE BIT TOO PUSHY.
- YOU DON'T NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
MR. PREACHER...
PLEASE TAKE GOOD CARE OF ERICS.
UNLIKE YOU, HE'S A BUMBLING FOOL
OF A GOODY-GOODY
AND A SWEET GENTLE SOUL.
LINA AND I HAVE ALWAYS KNOWN
SOMEWHERE DEEP IN OUR HEARTS,
IT WAS TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
WE KNEW ERICS WOULD PROBABLY
HAVE TO LEAVE US SOMEDAY.
YET WE CHOSE NOT TO BELIEVE IT.
BLESS HIM.
IT DOESN'T CHANGE THE
FACT THAT WE'RE LOSING
A MEMBER OF THE FAMILY.
PLEASE, MR. WOLFWOOD,
DON'T FORGET THAT.
- I'M TRULY SORRY.
I REALLY AM.
I'M-- I'M SORRY, GRANDMA.
- THERE.
IT'S ALL DONE.
( crying )
- LINA.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
- I ONLY WANTED
TO KEEP YOU SAFE.
BUT SOMEHOW...
IT TURNED OUT
THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
I WAS TOO WEAK.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
- THANK YOU.
I'M SORRY.
- NO, LINA.
IT'S ME WHO SHOULD BE
SAYING THAT.
- ( crying continues )
- LINA...
THANK YOU.
AND GOOD-BYE FOR NOW.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash:
STRONG WILL CAN STIR THE HEART.
BUT A WILL TOO STRONG CAN CUT
OFF THE HEART'S VISIBILITY.
THE SORROW OF A MAN
BEREAVED OF HIS FAMILY
TURNS INTO HATE,
WHICH EVENTUALLY
METAMORPHOSES INTO
THE INTENT TO KILL.
THE MAN'S FINGER
REACHES FOR THE TRIGGER.
SINS CHANGE PEOPLE.
SIN BEGETS SIN.
BUT I, I STILL WANT TO BELIEVE.
I WANNA BELIEVE IN THE HEART,
THE HEART THAT FEELS THE SIN.