- ( theme music playing )
♪ OH! ♪
- SPEED: 85 MILES PER HOUR.
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT--
88 "ILES."
12 MINUTES REMAINING.
WE'LL BE CROSSING THE DEADLINE
IN 10 MINUTES, SIR.
- WE ONLY HAVE 12 MINUTES.
GIVE IT SPECTACULAR WINGS.
- YOU AND YOUR MEN ARE ALL
GOING TO DIE ALONG WITH US!
- YOU THINK SO, HUH?
- ( clicking )
- YOU'RE WRONG THERE.
WE'RE PERFECTLY PREPARED
FOR THIS.
HERE'S TO AN ABSOLUTELY
BEAUTIFUL RENDEZVOUS.
HUH! ( laughing )
- LISTEN UP!
HE'S A BLOND MAN IN A RED COAT.
FIND HIM OR ELSE!
- Men: YES SIR!
- LET'S GO! LET'S FIND HIM!
- LET'S GO! EVERYONE GO!
- ( chattering )
- JEEZ! THIS PLACE IS CRAWLING
WITH THOSE BAD LADS.
MAN, THIS JUST ISN'T MY DAY.
I'M STUCK.
NOW WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
- HEY, YOU.
- HUH?
- TELL ME SOMETHING:
WHY'D YOU SAVE ME?
OW!  OOH, THAT HURT.
WHAT YOU REALLY MEAN TO SAY IS,
"THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME"!
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?!
- UH, YEAH, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
( chuckles nervously )
- OKAY, MR. KNOW-IT-ALL,
WHAT ARE THE BADDY LADDIES
GONNA DO NOW?
- WELL, ITS NOT GOOD.
- YOU MEAN INTO THE CANYON?!
THEY'RE GONNA DROP THE STEAMER?!
OH MAN, WHY CAN'T
I JUST GET A BREAK?
DEATH AND POVERTY
LIKE ME SO MUCH,
THEY'VE BROUGHT FRIENDS!
OH YEAH, AND THEN
THERE'S THE INSURANCE GIRLS!
IT NEVER ENDS! OW.
- WHY? WHY DID I SAY THAT?
WHY DID I SAY
IT WAS MY DAD'S SHIP?
SHIT.  WHY DO I EVEN CARE
ABOUT THIS STUPID RIG?
MY DAD WAS JUST
A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING WORKAHOLIC.
- ALL RIGHT!
- ( groans )
- OKAY, TIME TO GET GOING.
- WELL, CAN I AT LEAST
ASK WHERE WE'RE GOING?
- THIS IS NOT THE TIME TO BE
WORRYING ABOUT THINGS LIKE THAT.
IT'S MUCH MORE IMPORTANT
THAT YOU KEEP SOME ROOM
IN YOUR BRAIN OPEN.
- HMM?
- I'M STOPPING THIS SHIP.
AND YOU, MY FRIEND,
ARE GOING TO HELP.
- OKAY.
- HEY, ISN'T THIS THE--
- YEAH, THE BLUEPRINT
OF THE FLOURISH,
THIS STEAMER.
- BUT HOW?
HOW ARE YOU ABLE TO GET THAT?
IT'S NOT THE ORIGINAL.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING I COPIED
FROM MY DAD'S WORKPLACE
- WHEN I WAS A LITTLE KID.
- BUT THIS IS REALLY AMAZING.
IT'S REPRODUCED ALL THE WAY DOWN
TO THE TINIEST SCRIBBLES
YOU MUST'VE HAD
A LOT OF RESPECT FOR YOUR DAD.
- Man: KAITE?
KAITE!
KAITE, YOU MUST BECOME
THE KIND OF PERSON
WHO DOES THINGS FOR OTHERS.
AS FOR ME,
I WAS ABLE TO DO IT
WITH THE SAND STEAMER.
I WONDER WHAT YOU'LL DEVOTE
YOUR LIFE TO, MY SON.
- ( crying )
I DON'T HAVE A DAD.
WHAT THE HELL IS
SOMEONE LIKE ME SUPPOSED TO DO
FOR A LIVING
WHERE I CAN HELP PEOPLE?
HUH?
- ( emphatically )
WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
ALL SENTIMENTAL ON ME FOR,
YOU LITTLE SQUIRT?
FEELING BETTER NOW?
- ( groans )
- WE'RE GOING TO SURVIVE!
GOT THAT?!
- UH, YEAH.
- ( wheels rattling )
- HUH?
( men whimpering )
- ( gunshot )
- ( men scream )
- WHY DIDN'T IT EXPLODE?
- IS IT A DUD?
- THAT WAS FREAKY.
- ( gasps )
- ( gunfire )
- ( grunting )
- ( whimpering )
- ( gun clicks )
- ( squeals )
- ( sighs )
- ( thuds )
- WHAT A HAUL! NOW WE'VE GOT
SOME GUNS TO PLAY WITH!
- WHEN WE GET TO THE END,
MAKE A RIGHT.
- ( door opens )
- OH, I UNDERSTAND.
THESE ARE ALL VOICE TUBES.
- YEAH, BUT...
- HMM?
- ...DO YOU REALLY THINK
THIS'LL WORK?
- HMM.
WELL, THE BALL'S IN MOTION,
WE JUST HAVE TO SEE
IF THEY PICK IT UP.
- HMM?
- ( panting )
HE-- HE GOT US, BOSS.
HE'S NOT HUMAN.
( groans )
- HMM.
( laughing )
THIS IS GREAT.
EVEN BETTER THAN A DIME NOVEL.
AT LAST, WE'RE ACTUALLY
GONNA HAVE SOME FUN.
LET'S SEE IF OUR LITTLE FRIEND
REALLY SPARKLES.
Attention, scumbags:
If you slack off till time out,
I will kill you.
Drag that blond bastard
up here or else.
- IT'S MY TIME.
I'M AT THE STARBOARD
PASSENGER CABINS!
IT'S HIM!
IT'S THE BLOND GUY!
- Good.
Hold him right there.
I'll send you some help.
- IT'S NO GOOD!
I CAN'T STOP HIM!
HE'S HITTING HIMSELF!
HIS SPEED IS INCREDIBLE!
( choking )
- JEEZ. WHAT A SHOW-OFF.
- ALL RIGHT! GOT HIM!
- NOW I'LL BE ABLE
TO FIGURE OUT WHERE THEY ARE.
BUT HOW WILL I CONTACT YOU
TO LET YOU KNOW WHERE
THEY'RE GONNA BE?
HUH?
WAIT, ISN'T THIS--
IT'S SIMPLE. ALL YOU HAVE
TO DO IS TALK INTO IT
AND I'LL HEAR YOU.
I DON'T WANT TO BE CAUGHT
IN SOME SHOOTOUT
IN A NARROW PASSAGEWAY,
SO I'M GONNA BE
COUNTING ON YOUR HELP.
DON'T LET ME DOWN, OKAY?
- HMM.
HOLD ON JUST A MINUTE!
WHERE DID YOU GET THIS?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH
THIS LOST TECHNOLOGY?
JUST WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
- I'D EXPLAIN IT TO YOU,
BUT YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE ME.
BESIDES, THERE'S NO TIME.
DON'T WORRY SO MUCH
ABOUT THE LITTLE DETAILS.
SEE YA!
- ( cocks )
- ( gasps )
- ( rapid gunfire )
VASH, YOU OKAY?
- NO, KAITE. IT WASN'T
SUPPOSED TO START LIKE THIS.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- I SCREWED UP.
THEY'RE BLEEDING BADLY.
I HAVE TO HELP THEM.
- HELP THEM?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
ARE YOU ACTUALLY SAYING
THAT YOU PURPOSEFULLY AVOIDED
KILLING THEM THE ENTIRE TIME?
HUH?  WHAT--
WHAT THE HELL?!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU!
NO MATTER HOW GOOD
A SHOT YOU ARE,
UNLESS YOU SHOOT TO KILL,
YOU'RE GONNA GET
YOURSELF KILLED!
( gasps )
HUH?
- ( grunts )
WELL, I GUESS IT IS KIND OF
A STUPID APPROACH, ISN'T IT?
I KNOW THAT.
- ( gasps )
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS TRUE.
IT IS VERY SLOPPY OF ME.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I MADE A PROMISE.
IF I PUT OUT
EVEN ONE FLAME OF LIFE,
IT WOULD MAKE HER SAD.
( grunting )
- HUH?
- ( clicks )
- ( grunting )
- Man on voice tube:
There's something happening
in the central stairway,
third floor!
- GOOD!
PORT PASSENGER CABIN TEAM,
HEAD AROUND BEHIND
THE CENTRAL STAIRWAY QUICKLY!
EVERYBODY ON FLOORS
ONE THROUGH FIVE,
POSITION YOURSELVES AROUND
EACH STAIRWAY AND CLOSE IN NOW.
- WHAT'S OUR TIME?
- SEVEN MINUTES LEFT.
- WHEN YOU GET THERE,
YOU SHOULD SPEED RIGHT ACROSS.
THEY'RE GATHERING ABOVE
AND BELOW YOU RIGHT NOW.
- Vash: Roger.
- ( both grunt )
- THAT'S STUPID.
YOU GOTTA STOP BEING
SO SOFT WITH THOSE BAD LADS!
NO, IT'S MORE THAN THAT!
STOP BEING SO DAMN SOFT
WITH THE ENTIRE HUMAN RACE!
( growls )
I HAVE BETRAYED,
THEY HAVE BETRAYED,
AND WE ALL LET A LOT
OF INNOCENT PEOPLE DIE!
IT'S TOO LATE
FOR US TO GO BACK NOW!
AND-- AND YOU'RE
TOO DAMN CLEAN!
( pants )
- ( footsteps )
- HUH?
- THEN YOU SHOULD START OVER.
- WHAT?
- THE TICKET TO THE FUTURE...
IS ALWAYS OPEN.
- Man on voice tube:
He's broken past the central
engineer's cabin. He is good,
a real tough bastard,
but he's also got
the Devil's luck!
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO, BOSS?
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT LUCK
HAS ANYTHING TO DO WITH THIS.
- ( grunting )
- Good, keep going straight.
There should be a stairway
on your right.
Take it all the way down.
Don't go anywhere else.
That's the only unmanned place.
- WELCOME TO THE PARTY.
OH, YOU ARRIVED JUST IN TIME.
I TRUST THAT MY BRILLIANT
DIRECTIONS WERE CLEAR ENOUGH.
- OH, KAITE, YOU'VE GOT TO GET
OUT OF THAT ROOM IMMEDIATELY.
- ( guitar music playing )
- ( gunfire stops )
- I LIKE THE WAY YOU SPARKLE.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
I'M GLAD
YOU'RE A WORTHY OPPONENT.
ARE YOU NO LONGER
AFRAID OF DYING?
- Man on voice tube: We found
him, Boss! It was the kid.
- ( grunts )
- Get up, you pain in the ass.
You gave us
a lot of trouble.
- ( blows thudding )
- ( Kaite grunting )
- LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE ALL OUT OF TRICKS.
OH WELL.
IT'S A REAL ACCOMPLISHMENT
THAT YOUR RAG TEAM
MADE IT THIS FAR.
HOWEVER, THE SIMPLE
FACT IS REALITY IS
ALMOST NEVER THAT BEAUTIFUL.
I ACTUALLY DO FEEL FOR YOU.
- ( beeps )
- VAYA CON DIOS.
HMM?
- ( gun cocks )
- THAT'S FAR ENOUGH.
- WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO PULL?
- I'VE NEVER BEEN PARTICULARLY
FOND OF THIS METHOD,
BUT IT SEEMED TO BE THE
QUICKEST AND EASIEST WAY
TO GET PAST YOU.
I AM MERYL STRYFE FROM THE
BERNARDELLI INSURANCE SOCIETY.
HOWEVER IN SOME PLACES
I HAPPEN TO BE BETTER KNOWN
AS DERRINGER MERYL.
- DON'T MESS WITH US,
LITTLE GIRL.
- ( gunshots )
- ( men grunt, crash )
- UMM, HI.
MY NAME IS MILLY THOMPSON.
LET'S SEE NOW.
I SUPPOSE FOR THE TIME BEING
YOU CAN JUST CALL ME STUN
GUN MILLY. HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
- WE'RE GONNA
LET YOU OFF EASY THIS TIME.
ONLY BECAUSE WE DON'T SEEM
TO HAVE A LOT OF TIME LEFT.
NOW I EXPECT YOU'LL ACT
LIKE A REASONABLE ADULT
AND TAKE CARE OF THEM QUICKLY
WITHOUT SCREWING AROUND,
MR. VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- Men: VASH THE STAMPEDE?!
- VASH THE STAMPEDE?
( chuckles )
- ( rumbling )
- ( yelps )
- ( screaming )
- WELL, MY FRIEND.
IT LOOKS LIKE OUR TIME
TOGETHER IS RUNNING SHORT.
THIS SHIP'S TAKING
A REAL BEATING.
I DOUBT
IT'LL LAST VERY LONG.
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
HOW ABOUT YOU AND YOUR GUYS
GO DOWN WITH ME?
- I'LL DROP YOU
RIGHT NOW, BLONDIE.
HMM?
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S FIND OUT JUST WHO SPARKLES
THE MOST BETWEEN US.
YOU IDIOTS STAY OUT OF IT.
WE'LL SETTLE IT
WITH AN OLD-FASHIONED DUEL.
- I'M IN.
AND IF I WIN THIS SHOWDOWN,
WILL YOU STOP THE SHIP?
- IF YOU WON.
- ( grunts )
- ENGINE TEMPERATURE
IS AT NORMAL, SIR.
THE HULL IS SCREAMING.
- ALL WE CAN DO AT THIS POINT
IS BET ON HIM.
HE'S OUR ONLY HOPE.
- ( chuckles ) I KNOW IT'S
RATHER TRITE AND OLD-FASHIONED,
BUT WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE START RIGHT WHEN
THIS COIN HITS THE DECK?
- ( screaming )
- ( clinks )
- ( yelling )
( grunts, thuds )
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- OH NO! VASH!
- ARE THEY BOTH HIT?
- ( cocks )
- ( gasps )
- ( beeping )
- ( both whimper )
- ( gunshot )
- YOU STUPID IDIOT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR JUMPING AROUND
LIKE AN ACROBAT IN
THE SHAPE YOU'RE IN.
- AREN'T YOU GONNA FINISH HIM?
- ( footsteps )
- HEY. BOSS?
- BEREMY, JUST SHUT UP.
I DIDN'T EVEN SHOOT HIM.
HE TORE HIS OWN WOUNDS OPEN.
- YOU SHOULD FINISH HIM,
ANYWAY, BOSS.
YOU'RE TOO SOFT-HEARTED.
HEY, USE THOSE
HUGE DYNAMOS OF YOURS.
- ( chuckles ) LIKE I'VE
MENTIONED SO MANY TIMES BEFORE.
A NAME DEFENDED TO THE DEATH
IS A NAME WORTHY OF RESPECT.
- EVERYBODY, VASH WON THE DUEL!
- ( cheers )
- EMERGENCY BRAKES!
HIT THEM NOW!
- AYE, CAPTAIN.
- ( clanking )
- ( grunts )
IT'S NO GOOD.
THEY WON'T ENGAGE.
- SIR!
- DID THE IMPACT DAMAGE
THE HYDRAULIC SYSTEM?
- UNCONFIRMED, SIR,
BUT I'M GETTING
ABNORMAL PRESSURE READINGS
IN THE BOILER.
IF IT GETS MUCH
HIGHER THAN THIS,
THE ENTIRE HULL WILL EXPLODE.
- FORCE THE ENGINES
TO A FULL STOP IMMEDIATELY.
- ( groaning )
-  I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU WERE
FIGHTING IN THAT CONDITION.
- ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?!
- WE HAVE TO GET THAT
LOOKED AFTER QUICK.
- WE'VE GOT AN EMERGENCY!
- All: HUH?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- THERE'S-- THERE'S BEEN
A SYSTEM MALFUNCTION.
WE'VE LOST THE STEERING!
- ( gasps )
- WHAT?
- WE NEED KAITE.
- IS THERE A WAY
TO SHUT THE ENGINES DOWN?
- WE'D HAVE TO POWER DOWN
THE SYSTEM MANUALLY.
- WHERE CAN WE EVEN DO THAT?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
THIS SHIP IS SO OLD.
- IT'S IN ENGINE ROOM TWO.
- Men: HMM?
- THERE'S AN EMERGENCY STOP
LEVER INSIDE THE CONTROL SYSTEM,
BUT ACCESS IS LIMITED.
- WHAT THE HELL DO
YOU KNOW, YOU LITTLE BRAT?
GIMME THAT.
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
- SO THIS IS HOW YOU DID IT.
DAMN DAMN DAMN!
- DAMN DAMN!
- OW!
- OH!
I'LL NEVER FORGET
WATCHING MY FELLOW CREWMATE
AS HE WAS KILLED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
I WILL NOT
ACCEPT HELP FROM YOU.
WE WILL STOP
THE SHIP OURSELVES.
- Vash on radio: Kaite.
Kaite.
What are
you gonna do, Kaite?
- QUIT BUGGING ME. I KNOW.
THE TIME HAS COME FOR ME TO PAY
THE PRICE FOR WHAT I'VE DONE.
- Man on voice tube: Only 4,500
yards left till the deadline.
- ( grunting )
- 4,000 yards remaining.
- OKAY, THAT'S IT!
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET IT OPEN!
- ( grunting )
- 3,500 yards.
3,000!
- WHERE'S THE DAMN LEVER?
WHAT'S WITH THIS PLACE?
IT'S LIKE A CELLAR IN HERE.
- 2,500!
- LOOK!
IT'S WAY OVER THERE!
- ( chattering, crying )
- IT ISN'T WORKING, DAMN IT!
IT WON'T BUDGE!
THERE JUST ISN'T ANY WAY
WE CAN GET THROUGH
THIS MESS OF PIPES!
- 1,800!
- COME ON.
- IT'S HOPELESS! THERE'S
NOTHING WE CAN DO!
WE'RE NOT GONNA MAKE IT!
- CALM DOWN.
THERE'S A WAY.
THERE'S GOTTA BE.
- ( men grunt )
- MOVE IT!
( yells )
- ( hissing )
- ( screams )
( grunts )
- ( sizzling )
- ( screams )
- EMERGENCY STOP SYSTEM
HAS BEEN ACTIVATED, SIR.
- HOW MANY YARDS
DO WE HAVE LEFT?
- 800.
- WE'RE JUST GOING TOO FAST!
IT'S TOO LATE!
- ( yelling )
- ( engine revving )
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
THANKS TO MR. NASTY'S
SELFLESS ACT OF HEROISM,
WE WERE ALL SAVED.
- NEON DID THAT?
- NOW DON'T GET THE WRONG IDEA.
I JUST PAID OFF MY WAGER.
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET,
IT'S NO HOLDS BARRED.
I'LL TAKE THAT LIFE OF YOURS.
COUNT ON IT.
- ( chuckles )
- THAT SMUG JERK LAID IT ON US
REAL THICK ALL THE WAY HOME.
( chuckles )
- ♪ SO... ♪
♪ ON THE FIRST EVENING
A PEBBLE ♪
♪ FROM SOMEWHERE
OUT OF NOWHERE ♪
♪ DROPS UPON
THE DREAMING WORLD ♪
♪ SO... ♪
- THAT SONG.
- YEAH, I KNOW IT'S
AN OLD SONG, BUT I LIKE IT.
IT'S A GOOD SONG,
SO SHUT UP!
- OH. YEAH.
RIGHT, IT'S A GOOD SONG.
- ( vocalizing tune )
- ( Rem vocalizing tune )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
- ♪ FROM SOMEWHERE
OUT OF NOWHERE ♪
♪ DROPS UPON
THE DREAMING WORLD... ♪
- IT'S THE SAME SONG
THAT SHE LOVED.
- ♪ SOUND LIFE ♪
♪ SO, ON THE THIRD
CELESTIAL EVENING ♪
♪ ALL THE CHILDREN
OF THE WALTZ ♪
♪ MAKE WAVES UPON
THE DREAMING WORLD... ♪
- WILL YOU STOP IT?
YOU'RE MAKING ME CRY!
- ( growls ) QUIT MAKING FUN
OF ME, YOU BIG BUTTHEAD!
- Vash: OW!
I'M INJURED HERE, YOU KNOW?
- Kaite: SHUT UP,
YOU FLAKEY SHOW-OFF!
- Vash: WHAT?
I'M A FLAKY SHOW-OFF?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A BIG HAM.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"A BIG HAM"?
- Rem: ♪ MAKE WAVES UPON
THE DREAMING WORLD. ♪
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
I MET A LONE MAN
IN THE DESERT.
A TRAVELING PRIEST,
NICHOLAS D. WOLFWOOD.
HE SMILED AND THEN HE TOLD ME
THAT I'M A TROUBLED MAN.
FACED WITH
HIS ALL-SEEING SMILE,
THERE WAS NOTHING
I COULD SAY IN MY DEFENSE.
DID I MEET THIS MAN
BECAUSE I WAS DESTINED TO?
OR WAS IT SIMPLY
BY A SMALL JEST OF GOD?
THE MAN'S NAME IS
NICHOLAS D. WOLFWOOD,
A TRAVELING PRIEST
I MET IN THE DESERT.