- ( theme music playing )
- WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
A FORTUITOUS OCCASION INDEED.
JUST WHO I WANTED TO SEE.
YOU'RE ANGRY WITH ME,
AREN'T YOU?
APPARENTLY YOU'RE
UNHAPPY THAT I FORCED YOU
TO KILL NICHOLAS
D. WOLFWOOD.
- ( grunts )
AAH!
( pained groaning )
- YOUR SCENE IS OVER NOW,
CHAPEL.
NOW THE CURTAIN'LL RISE
FOR THE FINAL ACT.
- ( groans )
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasps )
- ( whimpering )
- I'M CURIOUS.
WHY DID YOU COME HERE?
- I-- I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO LIVE
WITHOUT BEING ABLE
TO PAY OFF A DEBT.
- THAT'S NONSENSE.
ANIMALS RUN INSTINCTIVELY
WHEN THEY SENSE DANGER.
BUT YOUR BEHAVIOR IS
COMPLETELY IRRATIONAL.
( laughs )
YOUR SACRIFICE IS MEANINGLESS.
YOU DON'T EVEN DESERVE
TO BE CALLED A FOOL.
THE ONLY REASON THE HUMAN RACE
CAME TO POSSESS THE CAPABILITY
OF COMPASSION IN THE SENSE
OF MORALS
WAS BECAUSE THEY SOMEHOW
MISTAKENLY BELIEVED THEMSELVES
TO BE A SUPERIOR BREED OF BEAST.
THE MOMENT THEY TASTE
THE FEAR OF KNOWING
THERE'S A SUPERIOR BREED,
SOMETHING SEEMS TO TAKE CONTROL
OVER THEM EVERY TIME.
AND FOR SOME REASON,
HUMANS ACT MERELY BY INSTINCT
FROM THAT POINT ON.
- THE CORNERED MOUSE
ATTACKS THE CAT,
EVEN KNOWING THE CAT
HAS THE UPPER HAND.
- BUT THE CAT IS WISE
TO THE MOUSE'S GAME.
THE MOUSE SEEKS DEATH
IN ORDER TO AVOID THE PAIN.
- ( whirring, zapping )
- ( groans )
- IMAGINE THE PLACE
BETWEEN LIFE AND DEATH.
- AAH!
- YES, THE PAIN YOU FEEL IS
YOUR VERY ESSENCE,
THE ESSENCE OF THE CRUDE ANIMAL
KNOWN AS HOMO SAPIEN.
- ( screams )
- GARBAGE-- ONLY GOOD FOR
CONSUMING RESOURCES.
( softly chuckles )
- I UNDERSTAND.
MASTER?
VASH THE STAMPEDE
WILL EXPERIENCE ETERNAL PAIN
AND SUFFERING.
- ( townspeople chattering )
- HEY, LADY.
- HMM.
- OH, MISS, MAY I HAVE
SOME DOUGHNUTS, PLEASE?
- OH, YEAH?
HOW MANY DO YOU WANT?
- 30 DOUBLE DOLLARS WORTH.
OH, AND COULD YOU PLEASE
MAKE THEM FRESH ONES?
I DON'T WANT ANY DAY-OLDS, OKAY?
- FINE, YEAH.
WHATEVER.  DON'T WORRY.
- ( Vash humming )
( exhales )
A POPULATED CITY AT LAST.
SURE FEELS GOOD TO SEE
HAPPY PEOPLE AROUND AGAIN.
IT'S A LUCKY LUCKY DAY.
BONJOUR!  JE T'AIME!
MM.  THAT SMELLS GREAT.
WHAT A HEAVENLY AROMA.
SMELLS LIKE LITTLE CAKES
MADE FROM HONEY.
AND WITHOUT FURTHER ADO...
( laughs maniacally )
( chomping )
THIS IS INCREDIBLE!
SUPER TASTY!
IT'S SO GOOD TO BE ALIVE!
- Boy #1: COME BACK!
- Boy #2: MOM SAYS SHE'S GONNA
BUY US SOME NEW TOYS!
HURRY UP!
- I'M RUNNING AS FAST AS I CAN!
- Man: HAVE YOU BEEN
TO MAGGIE'S STORE?
SHE HAS NEW BULKS OF THAT NICE
FABRIC YOU LIKE SO MUCH.
- Woman: I HAD NO IDEA.
SHE DIDN'T TELL ME.
- Woman #2: THANKS A LOT!
- I HAD THE OUTLAW.
WHICH GIRL IS SHE?
- NEVER MIND.
I'LL GO TELL HER MYSELF.
- AT LEAST TELL ME HER NAME.
- Man #2: IT TAKES THREE DAYS
TO GET THERE BY SAND STEAMER.
FORGET IT!
- TRUST ME, YOU GOT ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IT'LL BE FINE.
- ALL RIGHT, IF YOU SAY SO.
- ( chatter continues )
- Man #3: HA, I'M GONNA
GET YOU FOR THAT.
- WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
LINDA.
- ( crying )
( voice breaking )
THESE ARE GOOD...
THESE ARE REALLY GOOD.
WHY ARE THEY SO...
- ( echoing )
VASH!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
WHY DO ALL THESE TERRIBLE THINGS
ALWAYS HAVE TO HAPPEN
WHENEVER YOU'RE AROUND?
WHY DID MR. WOLFWOOD
HAVE TO DIE?
( normal voice ) WHO IS HE?
YOU MUST TELL ME NOW.
- YOU HEARD ABOUT IT.
- YOU HAVE TO TELL ME.
- I AM TO BLAME.
IT'S BECAUSE OF ME
THAT FRIENDS DIE.
THEY ALL GOT INVOLVED
BECAUSE OF ME.
I'M SORRY.
BUT THAT'S WHY
YOU CAN'T STAY WITH ME.
- ( exhales )
I ASKED YOU
AN IMPORTANT QUESTION,
AND I EXPECT A DECENT ANSWER.
I NEED TO UNDERSTAND.
PLEASE, FOR ONCE,
I NEED YOU
TO BE HONEST WITH ME.
- AS LONG AS HE LIVES,
I COULD NEVER DIE HONORABLY,
AS LONG AS KNIVES IS ALIVE.
- WHO'S KNIVES?
- MY BROTHER,
I'M SORRY TO SAY.
- ( gasps )
- ( soft rock music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- WELL, THAT'S IT.
NOW I NEED TO SPEND
A LITTLE TIME ALONE, OKAY?
- ( door opens )
- AND BESIDES,
THERE'S A GIRL IN PAIN
WHO COULD REALLY USE
YOUR SUPPORT RIGHT NOW.
- ALL THIS TIME.
- Milly:
ARE YOU SURE?
- HUH?
- I MEAN, DON'T YOU WANNA
FOLLOW HIM?
- FRANKLY, I'M GLAD THAT NO-GOOD
TROUBLEMAKER IS GONE.
LET'S GET THE REPORT IN QUICK,
AND GET THEM TO TAKE US OFF
THIS DETAIL ONCE AND FOR ALL.
THERE'S SO MANY BETTER THINGS
OUT THERE.
BESIDES, WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH LIVES--
- I CAN HANDLE IT, MERYL.
- BUT YOU--
- UNLESS WE GO AFTER HIM NOW,
THERE'S A GOOD POSSIBILITY THAT
WE MAY NEVER SEE HIM AGAIN
IN THIS LIFETIME.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT WITH YOU,
MERYL?  HMM?
( giggles ) I'M COMPLETELY,
TOTALLY, PERFECTLY FINE NOW.
IN FACT, I NEED TO
GET UP AND GO.
AND BESIDES,
AS WE BOTH KNOW,
IF WE DON'T WORK,
WE DON'T GET PAID.
- MILLY.
- ( sniffles )
ALL RIGHT,
FIRST THING'S FIRST--
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHICH WAY HE WENT?
- YES.
- GREAT, THEN WE HAVE
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
I'LL BE READY
IN A FEW MINUTES.
GATHER ALL OF YOUR THINGS
TOGETHER TOO, MERYL.
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
LEAVE A THING BEHIND,
BECAUSE WE WON'T
HAVE TIME TO COME BACK.
- ( crying )
YES.
OF COURSE.
- Boy #1:
HEY, THIS GUY'S CRYING.
- YEAH, AND HE'S A GROWN-UP.
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THAT?
EVERYONE FEELS LIKE CRYING
SOMETIMES.
- WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
- A FRIEND OF MINE
WENT AWAY, AND I'M SAD.
- WHY?
- BECAUSE--
- HE DIED BECAUSE OF YOU,
DIDN'T HE?
- ( gasps )
- IT WAS YOUR FAULT. YOU'RE THE
ONE KILLED WOLFWOOD, AREN'T YOU?
- YEAH, IF YOU HADN'T SWAYED HIM
WITH YOUR STUPID IDEAS,
HE MIGHT HAVE HAD A CHANCE.
YOU KNOW THAT'S TRUE.
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO DIE.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- Both: UH...
- ( gasps )
- I DECIDED TO DO THIS
AS MY HUMBLE WAY
OF EXHIBITING GRIEF
AT THE LOSS OF A GOOD FRIEND.
HOW'D I DO?
- YOU AGAIN.
DAMN YOU!
- ARE YOU GOING TO DRAW?
- PLEASE STOP.
DON'T DO IT.
SOMEONE ELSE WILL DIE
IF YOU DO THIS.
ANOTHER ONE WILL DIE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY DRAW.
YOU SEEM TO THINK
YOU'VE NEVER KILLED ANYONE,
BUT I'M AFRAID YOU'RE
VERY SADLY MISTAKEN.
YOU'VE MANAGED TO FOOL
NO ONE BUT YOURSELF.
YOU WANT TO BELIEVE THAT
BECAUSE YOUR HANDS AREN'T DIRTY,
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T PERSONALLY
PULL THE TRIGGER,
THAT YOU ARE INNOCENT.
WHEN IN ACTUALITY,
YOU'VE KILLED COUNTLESS PEOPLE.
INCLUDING THE GUNG-HO GUNS
AND YOUR FRIEND...
NICHOLAS D. WOLFWOOD.
- I WAS FORCED TO DO THAT!
I HAD NO CHOICE!
- EVERY TIME YOU MAKE THAT FACE,
IT'S STRANGE.
MY LEFT ARM BEGINS
TO SHAKE UNCONTROLLABLY,
BECAUSE IT HAPPENS TO BE
THE VERY ARM
THAT ATTACHED YOUR ARM
TO YOUR BODY.
- ( gasps )
- I WILL BE WAITING
FOR YOU ON THAT HILL.
IF YOU WISH TO SHOOT ME NOW,
GO AHEAD.
- ( Boy #1 groans )
- ( gasps )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
MY HEAD FEELS FUNNY.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- ( townspeople murmuring )
- ( groans )
- HOW DARE YOU.
HOW DARE YOU BE SO DAMN CASUAL
TO TOY WITH PEOPLE'S LIVES.
- YOU'D DO THE SAME THING.
- ( gasps )
- YOU ALONE TURNED JULY
AND AUGUSTA TO RUBBLE
AND PUT A HUGE HOLE
IN THE FIFTH MOON AS WELL.
YOU CAN DENY IT,
BUT YOU'RE A MONSTER.
- Child:
MOM, WHERE ARE YOU?!
- YOU AND HE ARE EXACTLY
THE SAME BREED.
- WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
- I'M THE 11th GUNG-HO GUN,
MIDVALLEY THE HORNFREAK.
THE MAN WHO PLAYS
THE GREATEST MUSIC
ON THE GREATEST STAGE
OF ALL.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY.
JOIN ME ON A NUMBER.
WON'T YOU, VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- VASH?  THE STAMPEDE?
- OH, NO.
NO WAY, IT CAN'T BE!
- ( townspeople screaming )
- ( rock music playing )
- ( saxophone playing )
- AAH!
WHAT THE--?
SOMEHOW HE'S ABLE
TO SYNCHRONIZE THE SOUND WAVES
FROM HIS HORN WITH THE PHYSICAL
SENSATION OF PAIN.
AAH!
- HMM.
SYLVIA IS RESPONDING
RATHER WELL TODAY.
HEY, YOU WOULDN'T KNOW,
BUT UP CLOSE,
THE SOUND THAT'S PRODUCED
BY EVEN A FAMOUS
TOP-QUALITY INSTRUMENT
CAN ACTUALLY SOUND
RATHER FLAT SOMETIMES.
OF COURSE THERE ARE
VARYING DEGREES,
BUT YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
ABLE TO BRING OUT
THE GREATEST SOUND.
A BEAUTIFUL MELODY IS
GREETED WITH APPLAUSE.
THE AUDIENCE SHOUTS
WITH APPRECIATION.
THE ACKNOWLEDGMENT
OF A SPLENDID PERFORMANCE.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU FINISH ME OFF?
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
IT'S OBVIOUS YOU COULD HAVE
TAKEN ME OUT BY NOW.
- THE ANSWER'S SIMPLE.
I'M UNDER HIS ORDERS.
THE CHOICE IS NOT MINE.
- KNIVES...
- CAN'T DEFY HIM.
ANYONE WORKING FOR KNIVES IS
AT HIS BECK AND CALL.
YOU RELINQUISH ALL RIGHTS
AND FREE THOUGHT.
END OF DISCUSSION.
- YOU'RE WRONG!
YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT!
- A SUPERIOR BEING
TRYING TO SHOW MERCY?
- HELP ME, I--
I CAN'T STOP MYSELF!
OH, NO!
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?!
- LEGATO AGAIN.
- HMM!
- ( saxophone playing )
- NO!
- NO, PLEASE!
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME.
- AAH!
- SOMEBODY HELP STOP ME!
PLEASE!
HELP ME!
- ( panting )
AAH!
WELL, THAT'S IT. NOW I NEED TO
SPEND A LITTLE TIME ALONE, OKAY?
- ( animal bellows )
- DON'T START BROODING, MERYL.
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME AND ENERGY.
AND BESIDES,
YOU'LL REGRET IT LATER,
SO JUST STOP.
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
THIS IS NO TIME
TO LOSE MY NERVE.
GOTTA KEEP GOING, RIGHT?
MERYL?
LET'S GO!
- ( grunts, groans )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HERE, DRINK SOME WATER.
( gasps )
- ( all groaning )
- TALK ABOUT IRON WILL.
- ( groans )
- YOUR DEDICATION IS
COMMENDABLE.
IT'S NOT OVER YET.
THE SHOW MUST GO ON.
- ( gasping )
- STOP IT!
- YOU GOTTA BE COOL.
- AAH.
- ( air hisses )
- DAMN!
MY "B"-FLAT!
MY "B"-FLAT'S GONE!
- SORRY, THE SHOW'S OVER.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU BEEN TRYING
FOR A RICOCHET SHOT?
( chuckles )
MAYBE, BUT IT'S NOT QUITE TIME
FOR THE CURTAIN CALL YET.
HA.
I HAVE TO ACCEPT THIS
AS MY FATE.
THE DESTINY
OF THE DYING.
- DON'T, STOP IT!
IF YOU SHOOT NOW...
DON'T!  NO!
- HEH.
- LEGATO...
- WE SHOULD HAVE DIED A VERY
LONG TIME AGO, YOU AND I.
THE INSTANT WE FELL UPON
THIS SANDY LAND WITHOUT PAIN
AND WITHOUT SORROW.
NOW THE SCHEDULE HAS
MERELY BEEN SET BACK.
THE END IS NEAR.
IT IS TIME TO EMBRACE IT.
THAT IS WHY I MUST...
I MUST END IT.
END IT NOW.
THIS IS THE CLIMAX,
VASH THE STAMP--
- ( gunshot )
- ( breathing heavily )
- SO DO YOU HATE ME?
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
IF YOU DO,
I WOULDN'T BLAME YOU.
SO MANY SAD THINGS
HAPPENED TO YOU.
WHETHER THEY ARE FRIEND
OR ENEMY,
THE PEOPLE YOU MEET DIE.
IT'S ENOUGH
TO SAP ONE'S TEARS.
- SHUT UP!
- YOU KNOW, THIS IS NOT
FINISHED YET.
DID YOU REALLY EXPECT THE END
TO COME SO EASILY?
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND
YOU'RE NOT HUMAN?
IT IS TIME TO REALIZE
EXACTLY WHO YOU ARE.
- NO.
PLEASE, IT CAN'T BE.
- THERE'S POWER IN THAT LIGHT.
POWER THAT YOU HAVE
ALWAYS POSSESSED.
EVEN MORE, THIS REPRESENTS
WHAT YOU ARE.
- AAH.
( grunts )
AAH!
I-- I CAN'T--
NOT AGAIN.
NOT AGAIN!
( breathing heavily )
- HAVEN'T YOU GIVEN UP
YET, VASH?
IT'S REALLY QUITE ANNOYING.
- ( gunshot )
- AAH.
( groans )
BASTARD.
- YOU'RE OUT OF OPTIONS.
FIGHT BACK OR YOU'LL DIE.
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans )
- ( softly chuckles )
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD?
I WOULD WELCOME THIS
TO BE MY TIME.
AFTER ALL, THERE'S NO REASON
FOR SUCH AN EGOCENTRIC,
INCOMPLETE LIFE
LIKE MINE TO BE ALLOWED
TO CONTINUE ANYWAY.
GIVE ME THE GIFT OF NOTHINGNESS.
GIVE ME DEATH.
MY MASTER IS WAITING FOR YOU.
HE'S LOOKING FORWARD
TO YOUR VISIT.
I WAS COMPELLED
TO ATTACH THIS ARM TO MYSELF.
I HAD TO, BECAUSE YOU
REFUSED TO BE BY HIS SIDE.
- ( grunts )
- KILL ME.
- I CAN'T.
- GO AHEAD.
- I CAN'T!
- ( woman panting )
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- MILLY!
- ( thuds )
- ( both groaning )
- STOP THEM.
NO MORE!
- Both:
AAH!
- I SAID STOP IT NOW!
- THEN SHOOT ME!
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
KILL ME.
IT'S SIMPLE.
ALL YOU NEED DO IS
PULL THE TRIGGER.
ONCE YOU HAVE KILLED ME,
THIS WILL ALL BE OVER.
COME ON,
TIME TO CHOOSE.
YOU HAVE FREE WILL.
- STOP IT.
DON'T MAKE ME SHOOT.
- Milly and Meryl:
NO!
- Milly:
NO, PLEASE!
( whimpering )
- YOUR FAITH IS
HOPELESSLY OBSTINATE.
TO ACTUALLY BELIEVE
THE PRATTLINGS OF A WOMAN
WHO SPEAKS IN IDEALISTIC TERMS
THAT ARE WORTHLESS.
- ( gasps )
- I GUESS THAT KIND OF THINKING
IS REASONABLE FOR
SOMEONE WHO'S LIVED
FOR MORE THAN A CENTURY.
BUT THAT--
THAT WAY OF LIFE IS PATHETIC.
EVEN COMICAL.
REM SAVEREM.
( chuckles )
A WASTED EXISTENCE
WHO ONLY SPOKE
IN AGGRAVATING LOGIC.
A WORTHLESS HUMAN BEING...
JUST LIKE ME.
BUT UNLIKE YOU.
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
- Wolfwood's voice:
LUCK AND PERSISTENCE
WON'T WORK FOREVER.
- ( gunshot )
- Rem's voice: AS WE JOURNEY
THROUGH OUR LIVES,
WE MUST ALWAYS SEARCH FOR WAYS
TO MAKE EVERYONE HAPPY.
- ( girls groaning )
- Wolfwood's voice: DON'T FORCE
YOUR WAY OF LIFE UPON OTHERS.
- Rem's voice:
NO ONE HAS THE RIGHT
TO TAKE THE LIFE OF ANOTHER.
- Wolfwood's voice:
DON'T TELL ME YOUR DREAMS
IN A WORLD LIKE THIS.
- IF YOU KEEP YOUR VISION CLEAR,
YOU WILL ALWAYS FIND THE FUTURE.
- Girls:
PLEASE, NO!
- ( gasps )
- Legato:
I UNDERSTAND...
MASTER.
VASH THE STAMPEDE
WILL EXPERIENCE
ETERNAL PAIN AND SUFFERING.
- ( laughing )
( maniacal laughter )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash:
I WAS DREAMING, REM.
EVERYTHING WAS SO HORRIBLY DRY.
THEY'RE ON THAT PLANET.
EVEN PEOPLE'S HEARTS.
AS I WATCHED THE PEOPLE
WHO LIVED THERE FROM FAR AWAY,
I KEPT WONDERING
WHY THEY WENT ON LIVING...
HOW THEY KEPT ON LIVING.
REM, LISTEN TO ME, REM...
I DID A BAD THING.
TELL ME,
WHAT SHOULD I DO?