- ( theme music playing )
♪ OH! ♪
- Milly: DEAR MOM, DAD,
BIG BIG SISTER,
MIDDLE BIG SISTER,
LITTLE BIG SISTER,
BIG BIG BROTHER,
MIDDLE BIG BROTHER,
LITTLE BIG BROTHER,
DOUGIE, ANRI,
RODNEY, MIKEY
AND LITTLE SANDRA.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M DOING JUST FINE.
( yawns )
GOOD MORNING. I'M SLEEPY.
- MILLY, YOU STAYED
UP ALL NIGHT...
- ...WRITING HOME TO YOUR
FAMILY AGAIN, DIDN'T YOU?
- ( nervous chuckle )
- THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU WRITE
TO EACH OF THEM SEPARATELY,
DOWN TO THE LAST
LITTLE NIECE AND NEPHEW.
- TADAH!
AT LEAST IT PAYS OFF.
I'M GETTING RAVE REVIEWS.
THEY CALL MY LETTERS
"THE MILLY MONTHLY."
- QUALITY ASIDE, YOU COULD'VE
WRITTEN SEVERAL BOOKS BY NOW.
- WHAT'S SO WEIRD ABOUT THAT?
DON'T YOU WRITE HOME?
- UH...
YEAH, WELL,
I USED TO WRITE AT FIRST,
BUT IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
BUT I THINK FOR MOST PEOPLE,
THAT'S NORMAL.
BESIDES, WHAT WOULD
THEY SAY IF I TOLD THEM
I WAS HANGING OUT
WITH VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- SO YOU JUST DON'T WANT
TO WRITE, MERYL?
IT'S NOT THAT I DON'T WANT
TO WRITE TO THEM.
I GUESS
IT SOUNDS PRETTY LAME
TO SAY THAT
I JUST DON'T HAVE THE TIME.
- ( gunfire )
- ( both gasp )
( both yell )
- ( people gasp,
chattering )
- OH GEE, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I MUST'VE ACCIDENTALLY
PULLED THE TRIGGER.
- HOW DARE YOU!
YOU HAVE A LOT OF NERVE,
YOU IMPUDENT SCOUNDREL!
- WE'RE NOT DUMB ENOUGH
TO BE SCARED BY YOU
AND YOUR ROTTEN FRIENDS!
- OH YES, IT'S BECOME
CLEAR TO ME NOW.
THERE'S A LOT OF MEANING
BEHIND THOSE WORDS, FRIENDS.
SO STAND UP WITH
YOUR HEADS HELD HIGH
AND SAY WHAT YOU WANT TO SAY!
- WE WON'T GIVE UP OUR LAND
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO TO US!
- YEAH, WE'RE NOT GONNA
TAKE THIS ANYMORE,
AND YOU CAN GO BACK
AND TELL THAT TO MORGAN!
- DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID,
YOU OLD GEEZERS?
- HEY, COME ON NOW.
MY GUN WENT OFF BY MISTAKE.
YOU KNOW THAT.
- Old man: A MISTAKE MY ASS,
YOU FAT-LIPPED GOLEM!
- WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
A GOLEM?  HA!
I'M LAUGHING SO HARD,
MY PISTOL'S TWITCHING.
- ( both yell, grunt )
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW DANGEROUS THAT WAS!
( humphs )
IF YOU MAKE THIS BROOM HEAD MAD,
I GUARANTEE HE'LL LEAVE YOU
WITH A LOT MORE
THAN INJURIES
AND PROPERTY DAMAGE.
GOOD GOD!
- YOU'RE THE ONES
WHO ARE DANGEROUS,
CLOTHESLINING HIM
FROM BEHIND LIKE THAT!
- ( chattering continues )
- ( clatters )
- HUH?
- ( creaking )
- ( screams, whimpers )
- MERYL,
THAT'S A SMALL SACRIFICE
FOR A GREAT CAUSE.
- I KNOW!  THAT'S RIGHT!
- WAY TO GO, MILLY!
- THAT'S ALL YOU'VE GOT TO SAY?
- DID YOU SAY BODYGUARDS?
- EXACTLY.
IF YOU TWO WERE HERE
TO PROTECT US,
WE'D FEEL A WHOLE LOT SAFER.
- I'M SORRY.
THANKS, ANYWAY,
BUT COMPANY REGULATIONS
STRICTLY FORBID US
FROM TAKING ANY PART-TIME JOBS.
- I UNDERSTAND. HOW ABOUT
YOU, SON? ARE YOU INTERESTED?
- WHY THE HELL
ARE YOU ASKING HIM?!
- THE WAY THAT HE MOVED
WHEN HE PROTECTED US BACK THERE,
HE WAS EXCEPTIONALLY BRAVE.
- YOU DON'T SAY!
WELL, IT'S NOTHING.
I DO THE BEST I CAN.
( laughs )
- ABSOLUTELY NO WAY!
( growls )
HOW COULD YOU ASK HIM?!
DON'T YOU KNOW WHO
THIS BROOM HEAD IS, MISTER?
- WHAT IS IT, LITTLE LADY?
YOU WANT THE JOB NOW?
- ( whimpering )
- WOW, THAT'S GREAT.
ONLY YOU WOULD THINK
OF USING YOUR POSITION
TO HELP OUT PEOPLE
WHO ARE TRULY IN NEED.
- UH, WELL,
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
I THINK THE
SITUATION REPRESENTS
THE CATEGORY OF
RISK-PREVENTION TO THE "T."
WHY HAVE YOU DECIDED
TO COME WITH US, MR. VASH?
- ( chuckling )
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS SOMETHING WAS
BOTHERING ME, THAT'S ALL.
- Meryl: KEEP OUT OF THIS ONE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
- Vash: YES, MA'AM.
- YOU SEE THAT?
THAT'S OUR LAND THERE.
- ( Meryl gasps )
- ( birds chirping )
- Meryl:
THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
HOW IS ALL OF THIS HERE
IF THERE'S NO ACCESS TO A SHIP?
- AMAZING.
IT'S JUST LIKE A GEO PLANT.
- NO, IT'S NOT JUST LIKE IT.
THIS IS A GEO PLANT.
- YES, WE BELIEVE
THAT A GEO PLANT
RAN ALONG A MINERAL VEIN
TO FORM THIS OFFSHOOT.
THE LAND VALUE HAS
SKYROCKETED SO HIGH,
IT'S WORTH AS MUCH
AS A SHIP 300 YARDS WIDE.
- THAT MAY BE,
BUT IT COULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN
THIS FAR
WITHOUT A LOT OF HELP.
IT WOULD'VE TAKEN
A MASSIVE AMOUNT OF EFFORT.
- I REMEMBER IT CLEARLY,
20 YEARS AGO IT WAS A TINY BUD.
BUT I COULDN'T
BELIEVE MY EYES.
JUST IMAGINING
HOW WE COULD RAISE
SUCH LUSH, BEAUTIFUL LAND
ON AN ARID PLANET LIKE THIS--
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW THAT KEPT US GOING.
THAT'S RIGHT.
OUR LIVES, OUR DREAMS
AND OUR HOPES
ARE ALL HERE.
- IT IS AMAZING
WHAT YOU'VE DONE HERE,
BUT WHAT DOES THIS HAVE TO DO
WITH YOUR HIRING BODYGUARDS?
- YOU SAW WHAT HAPPENED
BACK THERE IN TOWN.
THAT WAS NOT
THE FIRST TIME.
THE LANDOWNER MORGAN
HAS BEEN THREATENING
US TIME AND AGAIN
TO HAND OVER
THE DEED OR ELSE.
BUT THAT IS
ALL GOING TO END TOMORROW.
ONCE WE GET THIS DEED
OVER TO CITY HALL,
THERE'S NOTHING HE CAN DO.
Man: HEY, GUYS,
IT'S TIME TO CHANGE SHIFTS.
- ( door opens )
- OH, IT'S FREEZING OUT THERE.
- IT GETS COLD AT NIGHT.
- I APPRECIATE
ALL OF YOUR HELP.
- HEY, IT'S NO PROBLEM.
SINCE WE WERE LITTLE KIDS,
THIS PLACE HAS ALWAYS BEEN
OUR PLAYGROUND, HUH?
- YEAH, AND WE'RE
NEVER GONNA GIVE IT UP.
- BESIDES, WE GOT THESE
TWO GORGEOUS GIRLS TONIGHT
TO KEEP US COMPANY.
- ( women laugh nervously )
- YEAH, I ALMOST WISH THAT
MORNING DIDN'T HAVE TO COME.
- ( all laugh )
- THAT REMINDS ME:
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT BROOM BOY?
- I THOUGHT THAT FOR NOW WE
SHOULD HANDLE THIS WITHOUT HIM.
I TOLD HIM TO GO BACK
TO TOWN IN THE MEANTIME.
- WHAT'S THIS?  A LITTLE FIGHT
WITH THE BOYFRIEND?
- ( coughs )
HE'S NOT MY BOYFRIEND!
- ( both laugh )
- STOP IT. I DON'T
EVEN LIKE HIM.
LET'S GO, MILLY.  WE HAVE
TO GO DO THE ROUNDS NOW.
- COMING!
- HUH?
OH.
- ( shivers )
IT SURE IS COLD.
HEY, MERYL,
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- IT'S NOTHING, REALLY.
IT'S JUST THAT
I KNOW I'VE SEEN THE FACE
IN THAT PICTURE
SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
THE ONLY THING IS
I CAN'T SEEM TO PLACE IT.
- OH, YOU MEAN LIKE
A PASSING FANCY?
- A PASSING LIKENESS.
I'M ABSOLUTELY SURE
I'VE SEEN THAT FACE BEFORE.
- ( rustling )
- ( guns cock )
Women:
WHO GOES THERE?
OOH.  WAIT.
DON'T SHOOT!
- ( both gasp )
- OH NO, IT'S THAT MAN.
- WELL,
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE--
THE TWO OF YOU ONCE AGAIN.
YOU CAN PUT
YOUR GUNS AWAY, LADIES,
OBVIOUSLY
I'VE COME HERE UNARMED.
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I CAME TO TRY
AND TALK DAD OUT OF THIS.
MORGAN MEANS
BUSINESS THIS TIME.
- "TALK DAD OU--" OH?
AH!  THE PICTURE!
- ( chuckles )
YUP, THAT'S ME, ALL RIGHT.
THE UNWORTHY SON.
NOW WHERE IS HE?
- ( both grunt )
- WHAT REASON
COULD YOU POSSIBLY HAVE
TO POINT A GUN
AT YOUR PARENTS?
- OH.
- IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS,
BUT IF YOU MUST KNOW,
IT'S THEIR OWN FAULT FOR
NOT LISTENING TO REASON.
I HAD TO DO IT OR THEY'D
NEVER GET THE HINT.
- ( grunts )
YOU... FAT-HEADED JERK!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CUT IT OUT!
- STOP IT!  MILLY!
MILLY!
- YOU ROTTEN INGRATE!
EVIL AND STUPID GOOD
FOR NOTHING, AWFUL SON!
- WHAT?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
- ( door opens )
- Old man: WHAT'S ALL
THE COMMOTION?
- HUH?
- WHO'S FIGHTING OUT THERE?
OH.  BADWICK.
- YOU MIND TELLING ME WHAT THE
HELL YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
LOOK AT YOU GUYS
STANDING THERE.
YOU HAVEN'T TAKEN CARE
OF A DAMN THING!
- UH, WELL, BADWICK WANTED
JUST ONE MORE CHANCE
TO PERSUADE HIS PARENTS,
SO WE DIDN'T REALLY
SEE ANY HARM IN THAT,
SO WE JUST--
- ( growling )
- ( men whimpering )
- HE DID, DID HE?
I HIRED HIM
FOR HIS DILIGENCE,
BUT WHAT'S THE POINT IF HE CAN'T
EVEN KILL HIS OWN PARENTS?
EVIDENTLY, I MADE
AN ERROR IN JUDGMENT,
HAVING ANY FAITH IN HIM.
- ( thundering footsteps )
- HMM?
- ( men yelp )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- HEY!
- ( mumbling )
- ( men yelp )
- ( crying )
- ( men scream )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
THAT'S MY CAR
YOU JUST DESTROYED!
- ( crying continues )
- OH, WELL, EXCUSE ME!
YOU PROBABLY DID SOMETHING
CROOKED TO GET IT, ANYWAY.
LISTEN, MR. MORGAN,
MY FATHER
AND LITTLE BROTHER'S BAIL MONEY
IS RIDING ON THE SUCCESS
OF THIS LITTLE SCENARIO.
IF YOU TRY TO TAKE IT
OUT OF OUR PAY,
YOU'RE GONNA
GET YOURSELF FLATTENED.
- UH, UH... YOU'RE
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I CAN APPRECIATE
THE VALUE OF FAMILY.
I DIDN'T LIKE THAT CAR ANYHOW.
- Men: HUH?
- GREAT!
NOW THAT THAT'S SETTLED,
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE STRENGTH OF
OUR STEEL-PLATED FAMILY BONDS!
- ( shouts )
- LOOK OUT BELOW!
- Badwick: SO YOU DECIDED
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LISTEN TO ME
NO MATTER WHAT.
- WE WILL NOT GIVE HIM THE DEED.
- YOUR LITTLE BAND OF
VIGILANTES ISN'T GONNA BE ABLE
TO HELP YOU IF YOU DO THIS.
YOU'LL ALL BE SLAUGHTERED.
- I THINK OF MORGAN
AS A CHILD WHO WANTS
A PRICELESS TREASURE
HE KNOWS NOTHING ABOUT!
- ( growling )
- IF NOT CARED FOR PROPERLY,
THIS LAND WOULD QUICKLY
DRY UP AND DIE.
BADWICK MY SON,
THIS LAND LIVES AND BREATHES.
- YOU THINK LAND IS MORE
IMPORTANT THAN YOUR OWN LIFE?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
YOU CAN SO WILLINGLY CONTINUE
TO KEEP SACRIFICING
EVERYTHING FOR THIS LAND!
DAMN YOU!
MAX WAS RIGHT.
HE CHOSE TO DIE INSTEAD OF BEING
RAISED BY WORTHLESS PARENTS!
- ( both gasp )
- ( gasps )
- ( whistling )
- HUH?
- Both: HUH?
- ( whistling louder )
- HUH?
- ( rock music playing )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- RAIN?
- ( yells )
- Both: HUH?
- ( men gasp )
- ( laughing )
- ( whimpers )
- HUH?  WHERE'S HE GOING?
- ( yells )
- WHERE'S HE GOING?
- ( squeals ) YEAH,
THAT WAS REALLY SMOOTH, MOM.
NOW PLACE THE NEXT SHOT
ABOUT FIVE YARDS OVER THERE.
- PLEASE DON'T HIT THE TREES.
THAT WOULDN'T BE RIGHT.
- HUH?
- I SEE NO POINT IN IT.
- JEEZ, YOU'RE RUINING
ALL MY FUN.
WAIT, HOLD ON A MINUTE!
DO YOU HAVE
ANY IDEA WHO WE ARE?
PATRICIA, TONCHIKI,
CHINPEI AND THE ONE
HEADING HOME IS KANTA.
ALL TOGETHER WE ARE,
THE TOTALLY INVINCIBLE TEAM
OF MARILYN NEBRASKA
AND FRIENDS!
- ( moans )
- ( laughs )
- WHAT? "YOU HAVEN'T
DONE ANYTHING,
SO DON'T HOG THE LIMELIGHT"?
OH MOM, YOU'RE FUNNY.
DON'T BE SUCH
A STICK IN THE MUD.
- I SURE HOPE THAT THEY'RE
WORTH ALL THE MONEY
WE'RE PAYING THEM.
- ALL RIGHT, MOM!
COME ON!
NOW LET'S GIVE CHINPEI A WHIRL!
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- ( moaning )
- READY... TAKE AIM...
AND FIRE!  WHOO-HOO!
- ( grunts )
- ( men shouting, laughing )
- HEY, THEY'RE COMING!
- WE GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE!
- WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
THEY'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE YET.
WHAT DO THEY EXPECT ME
TO DO NOW?
- COME ON,
IT'S JUST ABOUT SHOWTIME.
- UM, YEAH, RIGHT, BUT--
- ( crashes )
- ( women groan )
- ( Badwick laughs )
IT FIGURES.
- Women: HUH?
- ANYONE IN THEIR RIGHT MIND
WOULD JUST RUN FROM THEM.
- Old man: THAT MAY BE SO.
- All: HMM?
- ( gasps )
- MOM?  DAD?
- GO AHEAD AND RUN IF YOU WANT.
I DON'T EXPECT YOU
TO STAY HERE AND DIE WITH US.
- Badwick: WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- ( explosions )
- ( screaming )
- THOSE GUYS ARE REALLY SERIOUS,
AND THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT THEY'RE GONNA DO.
- ( Patricia moaning )
- ( laughs )
- Man: WE NEED MORE BULLETS!
- ( gunfire )
- ( panting )
- THIS WHOLE THING HAS
TURNED INTO A REAL MESS!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO, MERYL?
MERYL?
- ( explosions )
- ( screaming )
- DARN!
WE JUST CAN'T STOP 'EM!  HUH?
- I AM SORRY THIS HAPPENED.
YOU CAN LEAVE NOW
AND THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
- OH, I'M SO SORRY.
( crying )
- HEY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- WELL, HAVE WE COME
TO AN UNDERSTANDING, OLD MAN?
- SURE, I UNDERSTAND
WHAT A SCOUNDREL
AND A PIG YOU REALLY ARE.
- DAD, STOP THAT!
- DON'T WORRY.
THERE'S NO WAY MORGAN'S
GOING TO SHOOT HIM.
AT LEAST NOT YET, ANYWAY,
BECAUSE THE LAND WOULD
NEVER BE HIS WITHOUT THE DEED.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT CRAZY OLD MAN.
WHY'S HE DOING THAT?  OW!
- ARE YOU REALLY
THAT MUCH OF AN IDIOT?  HMM?
HE'S DOING IT TO SAVE
THE LAND, ME AND YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DON'T SEE THAT.
- HUH?
- I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU FELT
ABOUT YOUR FATHER
ALL THESE YEARS,
BUT I'M SURE HE LOVES YOU
AND IS WILLING TO RISK
HIS LIFE FOR YOU.
- I'M AFRAID IT'S A LITTLE LATE
FOR THIS LOVEY-DOVEY CRAP.
UNLESS WE GIVE IN, MA,
WE'RE ALL GONNA DIE HERE.
- THIS LAND JUST EATS MONEY.
I'M NOT SURE WHY
IT'S SO IMPORTANT TO YOU,
BUT IT'S A BURDEN
I'M WILLING TO TAKE ON.
HERE IS A NEW CLAIM,
A WAY OUT OF THIS MESS THAT
IS ACTUALLY WORTH SOMETHING.
I'LL FILL IN
THE AMOUNT RIGHT NOW,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TELL ME
HOW MANY ZEROES YOU WANT.
- ( gunshot )
- HMM?
- I THINK
MY ANSWER'S PRETTY CLEAR.
NOW BEAT IT!
- SO YOU WANT AN
EARLY DEATH, DO YOU?
VERY WELL,
I'LL ACCOMMODATE YOU.
- Meryl's voice:
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- GO AHEAD AND KILL ME.
BUT THE MOMENT YOU DO,
YOU LOSE EVERYTHING.
CAN'T YOU SEE ALL THE
WITNESSES STANDING HERE?
- ( laughing )
- ( guns cocking )
- DID YOU SAY "WITNESSES"?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
I WON'T LEAVE A SOUL STANDING.
MY JOB WON'T BE FINISHED HERE
UNTIL THE LAST MAN IS DEAD,
I ASSURE YOU.
- ( both gasp )
- Milly: YOU CAN'T!
( pants )
- ( clangs )
- HUH?
- NO, MILLY!
- EXCUSE ME,
BUT DIDN'T YOUR FATHER
EVER TEACH YOU THAT IT'S WRONG
TO TAKE THINGS
THAT BELONG TO SOMEONE ELSE?!
- BE CAREFUL, LITTLE LADY.
- ( laughs )
ARE YOU THE TOUGH LITTLE HELPER?
- YES, I AM.
NOW YOU BE QUIET.
- MILLY.
- Morgan: YOU'RE WASTING
YOUR TIME, LITTLE LADY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU'RE ALL DESTINED TO
BECOME CORPSES, ANYWAY.
- ( whimpers )
- ( breathing hard )
- ( Morgan humphs ) CHARMING AS
THIS IS, I'M GETTING TIRED.
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
- Meryl: I DON'T THINK
SO, MR. MORGAN.
- All: HUH?
- NOW THAT I'VE HEARD
YOUR GRUESOME PLAN,
I'M AFRAID I CAN'T
LET YOU OFF THAT EASILY.
MAKE EVEN THE SLIGHTEST TWITCH
AND I'LL BE ALL OVER YOU AND
YOUR SICK LITTLE BAND OF THUGS.
- OH, MERYL,
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
I WOULD SUGGEST
THAT NEXT TIME
YOU THINK A LITTLE BIT MORE
BEFORE YOU ACT, MILLY.
YOU MIGHT LIVE A LOT LONGER.
- RIGHT.
- ( groaning )
- ( running footsteps )
- Old woman: BADWICK.
- ( grunts )
- BADWICK!
- FREEZE.  I JUST
DON'T UNDERSTAND ANY OF YOU.
WHY DID IT
HAVE TO COME TO THIS?
IF YOU HAD ONLY TAKEN
THE MONEY AND SOLD THE LAND,
WE WOULDN'T HAVE A PROBLEM.
NO ONE WOULD HAVE TO DIE
AND WE'D ALL BE SAFE FROM HARM.
I SAID FREEZE!
- ( cocks )
YOU KNOW, MILLY,
WHEN YOU GOT ANGRY BEFORE
YOU WERE RIGHT
IN CONFRONTING THEM.
WE SHOULD BE OUTRAGED
WHEN SOMEONE THREATENS
THEIR OWN PARENTS AND DO
WHATEVER WE CAN TO STOP THEM.
IT'S EXTREMELY IMPORTANT.
- ( Morgan laughing )
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
DO YOU HONESTLY BELIEVE
THAT YOU CAN TURN THE TIDE
WITH THOSE TINY DERRINGERS?
- UHH...
YEAH. WANNA FIND OUT
WHAT I CAN DO WITH THEM?
THAT IS IF YOU
HAVE THE GUTS
AND WANT TO RISK TAKING
A CHANCE ON THE ODDS.
- GO ON.
( humphs )
- ( Patricia grunts )
- ( motorcycle revving )
- WHAT?
- HUH?
- ALL RIGHT, MORGAN, ENOUGH!
I'VE GOT THE DOCUMENT!
I'VE GOT WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN ASKING FOR!
- SON, DON'T DO IT!
- AH.  WELL DONE.
HUH?
- ( all gasp )
- ( growls )
GET HIM NOW!
- ( yelling )
- ( gasps )
- ( both gasp )
- ( grunts )
- ( gun clicks )
IT CAN'T-- NO!
I'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
Meryl's voice:
BUT I HAVE TO TRY.
- ( yells )
- ( screams )
( groaning )
- ( Patricia and Morgan gasp )
- THAT WAS
REALLY AMAZING, MERYL!
- I DID THAT?
- THAT MAKES US EVEN NOW FOR
YOUR HELP ON THE SANDSTEAMER.
HUH?  HEY!
IS THAT ALL THE TIME I GET?!
- WELL THEN,
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
DON'T SAY SHE DIDN'T WARN YOU.
NO ONE CAN ESCAPE THE WRATH
OF MERYL'S DERRINGERS!
CONSIDER YOURSELF FORTUNATE
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE!
HER NEXT TARGETS ARE GOING
TO BE YOUR HEARTS AND BRAINS
AND THEN YOU'RE THROUGH.
- ARE YOU INSANE?
THAT WAS NOTHING MORE
THAN A LUCKY SHOT.
THAT GUN COULDN'T POSSIBLY
HAVE DONE THIS.
HUH?  COULD IT HAVE?
- ( whimpering )
-  Marilyn: NO!
- ( Patricia crying )
- ( crying ) HOW COULD THIS BE?
OUR SUPER COOL TECHNIQUE
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
TOTALLY INVINCIBLE!
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
STOP THAT THIS INSTANT,
YOU BLITHERING COWARD.
THAT ADVANCED PAYMENT
I MADE YOU WASN'T CHEAP,
AND I EXPECT RESULTS!
SO GET YOUR ACT TOGETHER RIGHT
NOW! DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
( screams )
- ( crying continues )
- Morgan: OH!  OH!
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, MOTHER.
I'M SURE CHINPEI IS FINE.
EVERYTHING WILL BE OKAY.
- Man: SO GO HELP HIM.
OF COURSE, IF YOUR SON
MEANS THAT MUCH TO YOU,
WHY DON'T YOU STOP
THROWING HIM AROUND?
- GET OFF.  GET OFF!
- Man: I CAN'T HANDLE
ANY MORE OF THIS.
LET'S BEAT IT.
- Man #2: RIGHT.
- ( crying continues )
- ( old man groans )
- Old woman: WHAT'S
WRONG, MY DEAR?
- I THINK I MIGHT'VE
PULLED SOMETHING.
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT, DEAR.
- YES, I'M SURE IT WILL.
AND NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
WE HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
IT'S WHAT HE WANTS.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO TRUST HIM.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO FIND
THE WORDS TO THANK YOU BOTH
FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
- ( both laugh )
- ESPECIALLY YOU, MS. MERYL.
I WANT TO SHARE
SOMETHING WITH YOU...
FROM AN OLD MAN
WHO RAISED AN IDIOT SON.
EVERYONE MAKES
THEIR OWN CHOICES.
NOTHING COULD
COMPARE TO THE LOVE
BETWEEN A PARENT AND A CHILD.
LOVE FOR THEM DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE A BURDEN.
INSTEAD OF WORRYING
ABOUT IT,
DO SOMETHING MORE SIMPLE,
YET VERY IMPORTANT.
WALK YOUR OWN PATH
WITH YOUR HEAD HELD HIGH.
YOUR LIFE IS THEIR LIFE.
THE FACT THAT
YOU ARE WHO YOU ARE
HELPS THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE
TO LIVE THROUGH YOU.
- Badwick's voice:
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS SO GREAT
ABOUT THIS STUPID DEED.
( groaning )
- THIS IS THE REAL DEED?
- Badwick: YEAH.
NOW IT'S IN YOUR HANDS.
- HEY!  HOLD ON A MOMENT, SIR.
- HUH?
- THERE SEEMS TO BE ONE MORE
CLAIM TRANSFER IN THE ENVELOPE.
YOU NEED TO LOOK AT IT.
THE BENEFICIARY,
AS WRITTEN HERE,
IS BADWICK.
ISN'T THAT YOU?
- ( gasps )
( breathes shakily )
YES.  THAT'S ME.
- Milly: YIKES!
MERYL, WE'RE NEVER
GONNA MAKE IT!
- I'M SORRY, MILLY! THIS TIME
IT WAS ACTUALLY MY FAULT
FOR STAYING UP
ALL NIGHT WRITING.  AH!
- ( meowing )
- Milly: MERYL!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
VASH'S BUS IS
GETTING READY TO GO!
THEY'RE GONNA LEAVE
WITHOUT US!
- I'M COMING, I'M COMING!
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- PEOPLE JUDGE PEOPLE.
LIVES ARE BEING CUT SHORT
BECAUSE OF SOMEONE'S
PERSONAL LOGIC--
MOTHERS, FATHERS, FRIENDS--
THEIR ENTIRE PAST INSTANTLY
VANISHES INTO THIN AIR.
THE QUESTION IS:
SHOULD THIS TAKE PLACE
ON THE WHIM
OF ONE INDIVIDUAL?
A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
STOOD BEFORE THE CORPSES
OF THE RODERICK THIEVES.
SHE TOLD ME THAT
SHE WAS MERELY DISCARDING
SOME USELESS GARBAGE.
DOMINIQUE THE CYCLOPS
TOLD ME TO JUST THINK OF IT
AS SPRING CLEANING.