- ( theme music plays )
- ( bird chirping )
- ( yawns )
HELLO THERE,
LITTLE FRIENDS.
MY NAME IS
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
I HAVE BEEN
A HUNTER OF PEACE,
CHASING THE ELUSIVE MAYFLY
KNOWN AS LOVE
FOR MANY,
MANY MOONS NOW.
THERE IS NO REST FOR ME
IN MY SEARCH OF PEACE.
I MEDITATE DILIGENTLY
EVERY MORNING.
THE SUBJECTS
ARE LIFE AND LOVE.
I QUIT AFTER
THREE SECONDS.
IN MY SEARCH FOR PEACE,
I ALSO TRAIN DILIGENTLY.
OOPS.
- ( egg cracks )
- ( sizzles )
- THANKS, FRIEND,
AND FAREWELL.
- Boy #1: HEY, VASH!
- HMM?
- COME ON!
- HURRY UP, WOULD YOU?
LET'S GO!
- WE'RE WAITING FOR YOU.
- RIGHT.
- ( kids laugh )
- I'VE ALSO MADE IT MY MISSION
TO TEACH THE PRECIOUS
VALUE OF PEACE
TO THE CHILDREN WHO
WILL ONE DAY OWN THE WORLD.
- ( bones cracking )
- ( straining )
- THAT'S CUTE.
MR. VASH IS BEING
PUT IN STRANGLEHOLDS
BY THE CHILDREN AGAIN.
- ( typing )
- THAT'S NICE.
- ( boys roughhousing )
- Vash: I WILL SAY IT AGAIN.
MY NAME IS VASH
THE STAMPEDE.
I AM A HUNTER OF PEACE,
CHASING THE MAYFLY
KNOWN AS LOVE.
- HUH?
OH!
( screams )
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, MISTER?
- EILEEN?!
- HUH?
- I-- I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT YOU LOOK
SO MUCH LIKE
MY POOR,
DEAD GIRLFRIEND.
PLEASE TELL ME YOUR NAME.
- I'M MICHELLE.
- LOVELY NAME.
MY NAME IS VASH,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE...
( gasps ) THE NAME
OF THE OUTLAW
WITH 60,000,000,000$$
ON HIS HEAD.
- I GET THAT A LOT.
SO, ANYWAY, WHAT WOULD YOU SAY
TO HAVING LUNCH WITH ME?
- NOT A CHANCE.
- ( grunts )
- ( wind whistles )
- Boy #2: ( grunts ) THAT
MAKES TEN LOSSES OUT OF TEN.
- YOU KNOW, VASH, WE DID
ALL THIS FOR YOU.
- YEAH, YOU COULD
TRY HARDER.
- ( whining )
BUT, CAPTAIN,
THIS STRATEGY DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE WORKING.
CAN'T WE TRY SOMETHING ELSE?
- HEY, IT'S NEIL.
- HEY, NEIL!
WANT TO JOIN IN?
- HE'S BEEN A REAL QUIET
LONER LATELY.
- WE INVITE HIM,
BUT HE NEVER COMES.
- ( footsteps approach )
- HMM?
- MR. VASH, JUST HOW LONG
DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN PERPETUATE THIS
SELF-INDULGENT LIFESTYLE
OF DOING NOTHING BUT
PLAYING WITH CHILDREN
AND EATING
AND SLEEPING
WITHOUT DOING ANY WORK
WHATSOEVER?
- OH, A LECTURE.
- YOU GOT TO BE PRETTY LAME
TO TAKE THAT KIND OF ABUSE.
- Neil:
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HUH?
- COME ON.
- WAIT, DAD.
- ( chuckles )
- ( giggles )
- Vash: NEIL.
- HUH?
- HI.
- OH, GREAT.
IT'S JUST VASH.
- NOW, THAT WASN'T
A VERY WARM HELLO.
ARE YOU HELPING OUT?
THAT'S REALLY GOOD, NEIL.
- THAT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- HEY, NOW DON'T
BE LIKE THAT.
WAIT, DOES YOUR FAMILY
RUN A RESTAURANT?
I'M STARVED.  THINK YOU CAN
GET ME SOMETHING TO EAT?
- YOU'RE NOT GETTING
ANY HANDOUTS.
- I KNOW THAT.
- AND...
MY MOM'S OFF-LIMITS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- HEY, MOM, CUSTOMER.
- ( food sizzles in pan )
- HELLO AND WELCOME!
- HEY!
- ( chuckles )
COME ON IN.
- ( exasperated sigh )
- DON'T WRECK THE PLACE,
STUPID.
- ( sizzles )
- AND WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, PREACHER-MAN?
- CAN'T YOU TELL?
I'M LENDING A HELPING HAND.
- MM-HMM.
- IT'S ONLY NATURAL
TO HELP OUT THOSE IN NEED.
HERE YOU GO.
ALL DONE.
- THANK YOU.
BUT I FEEL LIKE I'M
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF YOU.
- THINK NOTHING OF IT.
I'M DOING IT BECAUSE
I WANT TO HELP.
NOW, COME ON,
GET IT WHILE IT'S WARM.
- ALL RIGHT.
HERE YOU ARE.  ENJOY.
- DID SOMETHING BAD HAPPEN?
- UH...
THANK HEAVEN YOU ASKED!
IT'S A LONG STORY, ALTHOUGH
IT'S KIND OF A SHORT ONE.
ANYWAY, THIS IS
HOW IT HAPPENED.
BY CHANCE, I HAD JUST
STOPPED BY HERE
TO GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
- ( woman screams )
OH, NO!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO MY MOM?!
- HELP!
- ( in falsetto )
"I'M BEGGING YOU, PLEASE,
JUST WAIT A BIT LONGER
AND I'LL PAY YOU
THE MONEY I OWE YOU.
I PROMISE!"
- ( mimics gangster )
"LADY, YOU'RE WAY PAST
YOUR DEADLINE.
UNLESS YOU PAY OFF YOUR DEBT
IN FULL,
WE CAN'T MAKE
ANY MONEY EITHER.
AND I DON'T LIKE THAT.
HEH HEH!"
( normal voice )
SO AFTER THAT,
I DECIDED YOU USE
A LITTLE OF HIS GOSPEL
TO TALK THEM OUT OF IT.
I ASKED THE LADY,
"WHAT HAPPENED?"
SHE SAID THAT HER HUSBAND
DISAPPEARED
LEAVING HIS DEBT BEHIND,
BUT SHE DECIDED TO KEEP
THIS PLACE RUNNING.
EVEN THE CHILD IS DESPERATE
TO HELP HIS MOTHER IN NEED.
IT SHOT ME THROUGH THE HEART.
COULD YOU JUST SIT THERE?
COULD YOU JUST IGNORE THAT?
- THAT'S JUST AWFUL!
- YES, JUST AWFUL.
- AWFUL! ( cries )
- ( dramatically ) OH, YES!
MOST DEFINITELY.
- YES, DEFINITELY.
IT'S THE MOST
TERRIBLE THING.
- YOU'VE SAVED ME TIME.
I WAS GOING TO GO LOOK FOR YOU
ONCE WE CLOSED SHOP.
- FOR ME?
- YUP.
- THE THIRD ANNUAL
QUICK DRAW TOURNAMENT.
GRAND PRIZE, 50,000$$.
WHAT'S THIS?
- TO HELP OUT A POOR FAMILY,
YOU'RE GOING TO COMPETE.
- I WILL?!
- THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS SHOW UP THERE
ON TIME TOMORROW.
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE REGISTRATION
AND PAPERWORK FOR YOU.
- WHY ME ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- WE'RE HELPING THESE
GOOD PEOPLE OUT HERE!
OR WOULD YOU PREFER
IF I TURNED YOU IN
AND GET
THE 60,000,000,000$$ INSTEAD?
- THAT'S NOT
VERY FUNNY, PAL.
- JUST LOOK AT HER.
ISN'T THAT A SAD FACE?
- YEAH.
- NOT TO MENTION BEAUTIFUL.
FOR LOVE!
- FOR LOVE AND FOR PEACE.
- Meryl:
A QUICK DRAW TOURNAMENT?!
- HM-HMM.
- WHAT IS GOING ON
INSIDE THAT PEA-BRAINED
SPIKY HEAD?
ANY NORMAL PERSON
WOULD BE ABLE
TO SEE THE DANGER
OF PARTICIPATING
IN SUCH A STUPID CONTEST.
- I DIDN'T EVEN ENTER
THE CONTEST MYSELF.
I WAS KIND OF
TALKED INTO IT.
- Meryl: BY WHOM?
- THE PRIEST WE MET ON THE BUS.
- HEY, MR. VASH,
IF YOU WIN THE CONTEST,
WILL YOU TREAT ME
TO SOMETHING?
- ( chuckles )
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
- ( groans ) NOT AGAIN!
I'M HAVING
UNHAPPY VISIONS HERE!
- Meryl: I SEE THIS
SCENE IN MY HEAD
OF DOZENS OF HOTSHOT GUNMEN
AFTER THE 60,000,000,000$$
HAVING A MACHO-SHOOTOUT WAR.
- I'M JUST TAKING PART
IN A FUN CONTEST, THAT'S ALL.
IT'LL BE OKAY.
- YOU HAVEN'T GOT
A SINGLE CLUE, HAVE YOU?
- AND YOU ALWAYS SAY
THE STRANGEST THINGS.
- FUNNY, THE CHIEF SAYS
THE SAME THING.
- IT'LL BE OKAY, OKAY?
I'LL BE OKAY.
- ( growls )
- I GUESS IT WILL.
- Butler: SIR, I JUST THOUGHT
I SHOULD LET YOU KNOW
THAT WHEN WE WERE GOING
THROUGH TODAY'S ENTRIES,
THIS NAME CAME UP.
- Organizer: VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- THIS IS A MOST TROUBLING
TURN OF EVENTS.
SHALL I HAVE
HIS ENTRY WITHDRAWN?
- I HIGHLY DOUBT THAT
THE LEGENDARY GUNMAN
WOULD COME OUT OF HIDING
FOR A MERE 50,000$$ PRIZE.
IT'S JUST A WANNABE PUNK
USING THE NAME FOR KICKS.
- BUT, SIR...
- WE'LL JUST LET HIM TRY IT.
THEN WE'LL KNOW
IF HE'S THE REAL THING.
WE WILL HOLD THE TOURNAMENT
AS PLANNED.
THAT IS ALL.  GO.
- VERY GOOD, SIR.
- ( door opens )
( door closes )
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WILL THIS DO?
- ( knocks on door )
- WHO IS IT?
- Wolfwood: IT'S ME.
- DOOR'S OPEN.
- ( door opens )
- HEY, YOU STILL AWAKE?
LADY GAVE US A PRESENT.
CARE FOR A SWIG?
( sighs )
SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS.
I DIDN'T REALLY MEAN
TO FORCE YOU INTO IT.
- COME ON, YOU PLANNED IT
FROM THE START.
- WELL, YEAH,
BUT I APOLOGIZED.
- Vash: THE CHURCH.
- HUH?
- YOU SAID EARLIER
THAT YOU CAME FROM A CHURCH.
WHERE IS THIS PLACE?
- IT'S 300 ILES FROM
THE CITY OF DECEMBER.
- YOU BRING ORPHANS
THAT FAR OUT INTO THE BOONIES?
- IT'S THE ONLY PLACE
I'VE GOT.
KIDS I'VE MET ON THE WAY
WITH NOWHERE ELSE TO GO--
EITHER THEIR PARENTS ARE DEAD
OR THEY ABANDONED THEM.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S KIDS LIKE NEIL.
I REALLY DON'T
WANT TO TAKE HIM.
- ( gulps, gasps )
( hisses )
THEY'RE YOU GO
SMILING AGAIN.
IT LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
HEY, GIRLS!
- Both: HMM?!
- Wolfwood: YOU DON'T HAVE TO
LISTEN THROUGH THE DOOR.
COME ON IN.
- ( nervous laughing )
- WELL, HELLO.
- I APOLOGIZE
FOR EAVESDROPPING,
BUT AT LEAST NOW
I UNDERSTAND A LITTLE BETTER,
MR. VASH.
- WHAT?
- SINCE IT APPEARS THAT
YOU WERE FORCED THIS TIME,
I WISH YOU G--
- SHE MEANS,
"GOOD LUCK, MR. VASH.
GIVE 'EM HECK, ALL RIGHT."
- THANKS, GUYS.
- WHO'S DRINKING?
- I AM! OH YEAH!
- UH...
HEY, DON'T LET HER
HAVE TOO MUCH, ALL RIGHT?
- Wolfwood: HEY, LIGHTEN UP.
- ( meows )
- Milly:
OH, I FEEL SO HOT.  WOW.
- Meryl: HEY,
DON'T DO THAT HERE.
- Milly: WHOO!
- Meryl: MILLY!
- Wolfwood: YOU GO, BIG GIRL!
- GET YOUR CLOTHES BACK ON
RIGHT NOW.
- ( Milly laughs )
- Vash: OH YEAH!
- Meryl: MILLY!
- ( all laughing )
- ( chatter )
- ( gunfire )
- Old Man: OH, WE GOT IN
SOME AMAZING GUNMEN THIS YEAR.
- Younger Man:
GET A LOAD OF THAT GUN.
THIS IS GONNA BE GREAT.
- Milly: ( muffled )
MR. VASH AND MR. WOLFWOOD
HAVEN'T ARRIVED YET.
- WELL, YOU SAW HOW
THEY WERE LAST NIGHT.
THEY'LL TAKE
THEIR OWN SWEET TIME.
BESIDES, IT'S PROBABLY BETTER
IF THEY DON'T DRAW
TOO MUCH ATTENTION ANYWAY.
- Wolfwood:
SO, SHALL WE GO?
- PLEASE KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN.
WILL YOU?
MY HEAD REALLY HURTS.
- YOU'RE REALLY A WUSS, VASH.
CAN'T YOU HANDLE
A FEW DRINKS?
- THAT WASN'T A FEW DRINKS.
THAT WAS MORE LIKE
A FEW GALLONS.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- Neil: HEY, VASH!
- HEY, THERE.
- IS IT REALLY TRUE?
ARE YOU GONNA
HELP MY MOM?
- NEIL, STOP. I CAN'T
ASK YOU TO DO THIS.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO YOU ARE.
- HEY, WE'RE ALL FRIENDS NOW.
AND BESIDES, I'M NOT TOO BAD
AT THIS SORT OF THING, ACTUALLY.
( shaky laughs )
- ( gunfire )
- ( crowd shouts )
- Man #1: WHAT WAS THAT?
HE COULDN'T HIT
A SINGLE ONE.
- Shooter: ( mutters )
- ( jeering )
- ( gunshots )
- VASH IS IN THE TOURNAMENT.
- HE IS?
YOU THINK
HE CAN HANDLE IT?
- LOOK, THERE HE IS.
OVER THERE.
- ( gags )
( moans )
- Boy #2: HE LOOKS LIKE
A LOST CAUSE TO ME.
- ( crowd taunts )
- Man #2: COME ON,
JUST SHOOT IT.
- ( gunshots )
- Boys: WHOA!
- IS THAT THE MAN
YOU SPOKE OF?
HE'S NOT BAD.
- OOPS.  OH NO,
I HIT THEM ALL.
( sighs )
- YOU ARE VASH THE STAMPEDE,
ALL RIGHT.
- I'M STANDING OUT
TOO MUCH.
- EH, IT'LL MAKE THE GOING
THAT MUCH EASIER, VASH.
KEEP KNOCKING
'EM DEAD OUT THERE.
- THAT GOES FOR YOU TOO.
- HUH? ME TOO?
- IF THE THIRD ROUND CONTESTANT,
MR. NICHOLAS D. WOLFWOOD,
IS PRESENT AND
READY TO COMPETE,
STEP FORWARD NOW...
- AAH!
- OR BE DISQUALIFIED.
- WHAT THE HELL DID YOU
SIGN ME UP FOR?!
- WELL, IF WE BOTH COMPETE,
IT'LL IMPROVE OUR CHANCES.
- WHAT?!
- GOOD LUCK OUT THERE,
MR. PRIEST-MAN.
- OH, GREAT.  HMM?
- Vash: FOR LOVE...
- Wolfwood: AND PEACE.
- ( gunshots )
- ( excited hooting )
- WOW, THAT WAS SO AMAZING.
HOW COME YOU'RE GOOD?
- UNFORTUNATELY,
WE HAVE TO LIVE
IN A DANGEROUS WORLD.
IT'S FOR SELF-PROTECTION.
- MAYBE YOU'RE AN EX-GUNMAN.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
WHAT IS IT?!
- NOTHING.
- YOU GUYS ARE PRETTY GOOD.
I'M IMPRESSED.
- Both: HUH?
- BUT I'M AFRAID THIS
IS THE END OF YOUR SPREE.
THIS TIME, YOU AIN'T SHOOTING
NO LIQUOR BOTTLES.
THIS TIME, IT'S LIVE
ONE-ON-ONE COMBAT.
- ( gasps )
- YOU MEAN, YOU DIDN'T KNOW?!
- ( gunfire )
- ( chuckles )
- CAN I DROP OUT NOW?
- YOU DRAGGED ME INTO THIS
WITH YOU
AND NOW IT'S
TOO DAMN LATE!
- ( hawk screeches )
- ( ragged breathing )
- ( hissing breaths )
- ( swipes )
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans )
- ( Doctor laughs )
YOU'RE VERY LUCKY, MISTER.
IT'S ONLY YOUR SHOULDER.
- YOU'RE GOOD AT
CHANGING TRAJECTORIES.
YOU DON'T LIKE SEEING
PEOPLE KILL EACH OTHER, HUH?
- REMEMBER, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO DRAGGED ME INTO THIS.
- NO NEED TO THANK ME.
- Announcer:
WE WILL NOW COMMENCE
THE FIRST
QUARTERFINAL MATCH.
- IT'S YOU AND ME,
SPINELESS COWARD.
- PLEASE GO EASY ON ME.
I'M REALLY SCARED.
- Announcer: READY, GO!
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshot )
- ( screams )
- ( groans )
( chuckles )
NOT BAD.
( forced )
NICE... SHOT.
- HE WAS FACING BACKWARDS
THE WHOLE TIME.
- SNAKE!
- ( gunfire )
- ( gunshots )
- ( strangled scream )
- ( gunshot )
- ( men moan )
- Shooter: BUT I SHOT HIM FIRST.
- ( moaning continues )
- THIS IS UNUSUAL.
SO FAR, WE HAVEN'T HAD
A SINGLE FATALITY
IN THIS YEAR'S CONTEST.
- HELL, HE'S ACTUALLY
THE REAL THING.
HE'S VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- VASH, YOU'RE INCREDIBLE.
- NOW YOU'RE COOL ENOUGH
TO JOIN OUR CLUB.
- MR. WOLFWOOD
JUST TOLD ME
THAT HE'S GONNA STEP OUT
OF THE COMPETITION.
SO I GUESS THAT MEANS
NOW YOU'VE WON
THIS CONTEST FOR SURE.
- ISN'T THAT WONDERFUL?
- ( people chatter )
- I'M NICHOLAS D. WOLFWOOD.
I'M WITHDRAWING
FROM THE FINAL ROUND.
- REALLY?
BUT YOU WERE DOING
SO WELL FOR YOURSELF.
MAY I ASK WHY?
- AH, IT'S TOO MUCH
OF A BOTHER, THAT'S ALL.
THEN JUST GIVE THE PRIZE
TO THE OTHER GUY, ALL RIGHT?
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
- WHAT?
- LOOK.
- HUH?
WELL, NOW,
THAT'S HOW IT IS.
- NICHOLAS,
YOU REALLY ARE VERY GOOD.
WOULD YOU CONSIDER ELIMINATING
VASH THE STAMPEDE
WITH YOUR SUPERB
GUNMANSHIP?
IF YOU DO AS I ASK,
I WILL GUARANTEE YOU THE SAFETY
OF THAT FAMILY.
AND I'D EVEN BE WILLING
TO RAISE THE PRICE
TO 30,000,000,000$$.
- YOU MEAN, 50/50?
- ( chuckles ) I LIKE A MAN
WITH A HEAD ON HIS SHOULDERS.
- Announcer: GENTLEMEN,
THE FINAL ROUND WILL NOW BEGIN.
- HUH?!
- BUT WHY?
- NO, VASH.
- DIDN'T YOU GO OVER THERE
TO WITHDRAW?
- HERE'S THE BIG MONEY QUESTION.
TELL ME, WHAT DO YOU SEE
IN THE WINDOW
OF THAT BUILDING
OVER THERE?
AND THAT JUST ABOUT
SUMS IT UP.
- READY, GO!
- ( gasp )
- ( gunfire )
- RUN, VASH!
- IT'S FOR THE GOOD
OF THAT FAMILY.
JUST RESIGN YOURSELF
AND DIE.
- ( gunshots )
- COME ON, GET SERIOUS!
- I'M SAYING THAT WE ALL
HAVE TO MAKE A FEW SACRIFICES.
- CAN I MAKE
A DIFFERENT ONE?
- UGH!
NOW, YOU'VE DONE IT!
- SO THIS IS
WHAT YOU GOT ME
SO PLASTERED FOR
YESTERDAY.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK
I'D TRY SOMETHING THAT CHEAP?!
- YEAH, I DO.
AFTER YOU WENT AND SIGNED ME UP
WITHOUT ASKING.
- YOU DID
THE SAME TO ME.
- ( gunshots )
- HMM.
HMPH.
- ( gasps )
- OH!
- ( laughing )
NOW THE 60,000,000,000$$
IS ALL MINE!
HOW FORTUNATE.
NOW FINISH THEM OFF!
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshot )
- HUH?
( gasps )
- ( laughs )
- ( gunfire )
- ( groaning )
- WHAT?!
- ( laughing )
- WHAT? WHAT?
WHY DON'T YOU KILL THEM?!
- ( gunfire )
- ( shouting )
- MILLY, MERYL,
THROW ME MY LUGGAGE.
- Both: HUH?
- BUT IT'S TOO BIG.
- Milly: COME ON,
WE CAN DO IT.
( stun gun contracts )
OOH, STEP ASIDE.
I'M GONNA GIVE IT A PUSH.
H'YA!
- THANKS.
- HEY, DON'T KILL THEM.
- ( gunfire )
- ( screams )
- I'M AMAZED YOU CAN SAY THAT
AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
- HEY, WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO THOU SHALT NOT KILL?
- ( screams )
- GLORIA!
- ( screaming )
- ( gunfire continues )
I WON'T LET
ANY MORE CHILDREN SUFFER!
NEVER AGAIN!
- ( moaning )
- OH, NOT AGAIN.
- ( groans continue )
- MY LEG, IT HURTS!
- WOW, THIS IS HORRIBLE.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO GO
AND INJURE
SO MANY OF THESE PEOPLE?
WHAT KIND OF A CHURCHMAN
ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
- HEY, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
NOBODY'S DEAD.
I KEPT MY WORD.
- NOW THEN.
MISTER...
MAY THE LORD
HAVE MERCY ON YOUR SOUL.
OR DO YOU INTEND TO PAY ME
THE PRIZE MONEY AFTER ALL?
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I'LL PAY IT.  I'LL PAY IT.
- MUCH OBLIGED.
- ( kids straining )
- OUCH! ( groaning )
OWW! STOP IT!
GO AWAY! IT HURTS!
- HE SURE HAS BECOME AWFULLY
POPULAR ALL OF A SUDDEN,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- I KNEW HE WAS NO
ORDINARY PRIEST,
BUT I HAD NO IDEA
HOW UNUSUAL HE WAS.
- STOP, IT HURTS!
- ( kids straining )
- Boy #2: GOTCHA NOW!
- ( groans ) HUH?
- ( sizzling )
- THERE YOU ARE.
- ( giggles )
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- AH, HECK.
THINK NOTHING OF IT.
- ( running footsteps )
- Both: HUH?
- M-- M-- MA!
- WHAT'S WRONG NEIL?
- D-- D-- D--
D-- D...
DAD!
- ( Clair gasps )
DEAR!
- ( sighs )
I GUESS MY JOB IS DONE.
- YUP, SURE LOOKS LIKE IT.
FOR LOVE...
- AND PEACE.
HUH?
- ( sinister chuckling )
- Boy #2: GET 'EM!
- ( Vash screams )
NO, CAPTAIN,
ANYTHING BUT THAT!
NO!
- ( thudding )
- ( meows )
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: A CHOICE
BETWEEN TWO THINGS,
THE FORKED ROAD,
A CROSSED ROAD
WHERE MEN GIVEN LIFE
MUST TAKE
IN ORDER TO STAY ALIVE.
WHICHEVER END
THEY LIVE ON,
THEY LOSE SOMETHING.
WHICHEVER END THEY LIVE ON,
THEY ARE UNABLE
TO FIND HAPPINESS.
BUT ARE THERE REALLY ONLY
TWO PATHS TO A FORKED ROAD?
NO, THERE ARE INFINITE
PATHS WE MUST TAKE.
THERE IS MORE THAN ONE PATH.
THERE'S MORE THAN ONE
PATH TO THE FUTURE.