- ( theme music plays )
- Boy: COME ON, MOM.
PLEASE BUY ME A GUN.
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU CALL THAT
THING IN YOUR HAND?
- I MEAN, A REAL ONE.
- YOU'RE NOT OLD ENOUGH,
TONIS.
- YES, I AM.
I'LL CLEAN OUT
THE THOMAS STABLE EVERY DAY.
COME ON, MOM, PLEASE.
- ( footsteps )
- Tonis: I'LL BE CAREFUL.
I PROMISE.
PLEASE!
- ( silent )
- ( gunfire )
( gunfire continues )
- ( rounds clink )
- ( chuckling )
- ( gasps )
- ( Tonis cries )
( wails )
- ( snickers )
"VASH THE STAMPEDE,
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON
TAKEN DOWN AT INEPRIL CITY."
NICE HEADLINE.
- ( men laughing )
- THE 60,000,000,000$$ IS OURS!
- ( gasping )
- ( laughing )
- I'M SO EXCITED I COULD...
- NOT ONLY ARE WE
DISGUSTINGLY RICH,
WE'RE GONNA BE FAMOUS
ACROSS THE ENTIRE GALAXY.
- HMM.
- HA HA HA! HUH?
YOU'RE ACTING
AWFULLY CAUTIOUS.
IT'S OKAY.
HE'S DEAD.
- I CAN'T HELP IT.
IT'S HIM LYING THERE.
- ( shivers )
- HEY, CHEER UP.
YOU LOOK SO DEPRESSED.
THIS IS A GREAT DAY FOR US.
WITH WHAT WE JUST EARNED,
WE CAN HAVE THIS RESTAURANT
REBUILT IF YOU WANT.
- Vash: DO YOU MEAN IT?
- DAMN STRAIGHT, SWEET CHEEKS.
- ( men gasp and shiver )
- ME AND MY ESTEEMED PARTNERS
HERE ARE
MULTI-BILLIONAIRES NOW.
HUH?!
- OH, I'M SO RELIEVED.
I WAS VERY
WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
- ( sniffs )
YOU REEK OF TOMATOES.
- I KNOW.  WHEN I WAS
TRYING TO RUN AWAY,
IT GOT DUMPED ALL OVER ME.
HEY, WOULD YOU MIND REIMBURSING
ME FOR MY DRY CLEANING?
- I'LL REIMBURSE YOU,
ALL RIGHT!
- ( gun clicks )
- WITH A ONE-WAY TICKET
TO THE PEARLY GATES!
- ( gasps )
- ( popping )
- ( screams )
- ( sighs )
THEY ARE SO IMPATIENT.
HEY, WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO BE IN SUCH A RUSH?
COME ON, LET'S JUST
TALK IT OVER.
- WHO THE HECK ARE YOU, MISTER?
- OH, I GET SO EMBARRASSED
WHEN I HAVE INTRODUCE MYSELF.
BUT SINCE YOU ASKED,
I'M LIKE A HUNTER OF PEACE,
ONE WHO CHASES THE ELUSIVE
MAYFLY OF LOVE--
OR, WELL, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- ( gasping )
- I'LL KILL HIM MYSELF!
- ARE YOU INSANE?
DO YOU WANT TO DIE, STUPID?
HE JUST SHOT US ALL.
NEXT TIME, HE MIGHT
USE REAL BULLETS.
- IT'S OKAY.  SHOOT IF YOU WANT.
TRY YOUR LUCK.
- ( screaming )
- NO, WAIT! DON'T PROVOKE HIM!
- I'M GONNA CLAW YOUR
FRICKIN' HEAD OFF--
- ( both scream )
- ( gun clicks )
- HUH?
- GIVE IT UP.
WITH THE EXCEPTION
OF THIS GUY,
I'M AFRAID YOU'VE USED UP
ALL YOUR BULLETS ALREADY.
- ( gasps )
- ( wind rushes )
- Robber: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW COULD YOU TELL?
- Vash: I COUNTED.
GEE, I REALLY HOPE
IT'S NOT COLD OUTSIDE FOR THEM.
- HMM? ( laughs )
- HERE'S YOUR GUN, PARTNER.
IT REALLY HELPED.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- AHH.
( sighs )
- Old Man: THAT WAS
QUITE IMPRESSIVE, YOUNG MAN.
A DANGEROUS SITUATION,
HAVE YOU ALWAYS
SURVIVED LIKE THAT
WITHOUT SHOOTING ANYONE?
- 'CAUSE IT'S TOO WASTEFUL.
AFTER ALL, I CAN COME INTO
A RESTAURANT LIKE THIS
AND ORDER AN ENTIRE
STACK OF PANCAKES
FOR THE PRICE
OF ONE SILLY BULLET.
- YOU ARE A STRANGE ONE.
IT SEEMS VERY ODD THAT YOU
CONSIDER YOURSELF A GUNMAN.
- ( muffled )
YOU GOT A POINT THERE.
( laughs )
- ( laughs )
- ( gun clicks )
- ( Vash laughs )
- I'M VERY SORRY.
- HUH?
- ( clicks )
- I REALLY HATE TO DO THIS, SON.
BUT YOU ARE MR. VASH
THE STAMPEDE, AREN'T YOU?
- UH...
- I AM SORRY.
PLEASE DIE
WITHOUT A FUSS, OKAY?
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS,
MR. VASH, SIR.
- HEY, NO BIGGIE.
- ( wind rushes )
- Milly: OH MY GOSH.
HALF THE CITY
IS BURIED IN SAND.
- Meryl: THEIR PLANT
PROBABLY BROKE DOWN
AND STOPPED WORKING.
- WELL, THEN,
THEY SHOULD FIX IT.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH REPAIRS TO
A PLANT THAT SIZE CAN COST?
- WHY? IS IT EXPENSIVE?
- ( sighs )
- ( both gasp )
- ( explosions )
- ( sirens wail )
- Milly: THIS TIME, IT LOOKS
LIKE THE RUMORS ARE TRUE.
- ( sighs )
- YOU'RE SMILING.
- HUH? I AM NOT SMILING.
NOW WE HAVE TO GO RUN
RISK PREVENTION
AND GET THIS DOCUMENTED.
THIS TIME, WE WILL FIND
THE REAL VASH THE STAMPEDE
AND BRING ABOUT
HIS DOWNFALL.
- ( screams )
AAH!
CAN THIS BE THE END?!
( grunts )
- Man: THERE HE IS!
IN HERE!
GET HIM!  SHOOT HIM!
- OH CRAP!
- ( gunfire )
- THERE HE GOES.
- DON'T LET HIM GET AWAY.
- THAT'S HIM!
WE'VE GOT YOU NOW.
- OH, REALLY?  DO YOU MEAN ME?
- ( gunfire )
- ( screams )
NOT AGAIN! WOAHHH!
OWW! OOH! AH!
- Man #2: WHERE'D HE GO?
THAT BASTARD!
- Man #3: SHOOT HIM!
- ( gunfire continues )
- EVERYONE'S SO BUSY TODAY.
- ( meows )
- MAMAN, WHY DOES THIS
KEEP HAPPENING TO ME?
I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING WRONG,
BUT I'M ALWAYS IN TROUBLE
AND EVERYBODY'S ALWAYS
PICKING ON ME.
WHAT DO I DO, MAMAN?
( blows )
WHY AM I CRYING IN FRENCH?
HMM?
( screams )
- ( bell rings )
- IT'S HIM!
HE'S UP THERE.
- HE'S ALL MINE!
- GET ME OUT OF HERE!
- ( banging )
- Milly: UH-OH.
LOOKS LIKE THINGS ARE GETTING
PRETTY HEATED UP DOWN THERE.
- WE HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING
BEFORE THE ENTIRE CITY
AND EVERYONE IN IT
IS BLOWN AWAY.
BUT IF THEY'RE
THIS AGITATED,
I WONDER IF...
IT REALLY MIGHT BE HIM.
LET'S STOP THIS NOW.
COME ON.
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE, MERYL.
COME BACK.
MERYL!
- ( shouts )
- ( rumbling )
- ( man screams )
MY ARM HURTS SO BAD!
- ( girls scream )
- I CAN'T STAND IT!
- ( gunfire )
- WHOSE IDEA WAS IT
TO USE THE GRENADE?
HE CAN'T BE IDENTIFIED
FOR THE REWARD
IF HE'S A PILE OF PULP,
YOU DUMB ASS!
- THIS IS BAD.
PEOPLE OUT OF CONTROL,
COMPLETE MAYHEM...
- ( growls )
- ATTENTION! EXCUSE ME!
- IF YOU'D JUST
LISTEN FOR A MOMENT!
I'M VERY SORRY
TO DISTURB YOU.
MY NAME IS MERYL STRYFE
FROM THE BERNADELLI
INSURANCE SOCIETY.
AND I AM HERE TO SAY--
- ( rumbling )
- ( screams )
THE MAN YOU'RE ALL AFTER,
THE ONE WHOSE NAME
IS VASH THE STAMPEDE,
IS A VERY DANGEROUS MAN.
IN ORDER TO PROTECT
YOUR PRECIOUS LIVES
AND ALL OF YOUR VALUABLE
POSSESSIONS
FROM ANY FURTHER HARM...
- ( chimes play )
- ( Man through P.A. ):
THIS IS A MESSAGE FROM
MISSION CONTROL.
TEMPORARILY SUSPEND ALL PURSUIT
OF VASH THE STAMPEDE.
EVERYBODY PROCEED
TO BASE AT ONCE.
- UH, TEMPORARILY?!
WHAT THE HELL'S
THE MATTER WITH THEM?
STOP ALL PURSUIT NOW!
- ( chattering )
- WELL, WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO NOW, CHAIRMAN?
THE DAMAGE AND CASUALTIES
ARE JUST GETTING WORSE
BY THE MOMENT.
- ( groans )
I CANNOT BELIEVE
WE STILL HAVEN'T
CAUGHT THIS GUY
AFTER FOUR HOURS
OF FIGHTING.
- CAUGHT HIM?
THE GUY'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HE'S MANAGED TO RUN AWAY WITHOUT
RETURNING A SINGLE BULLET.
- HE'S JUST TOO GOOD FOR US.
IF WE MAKE HIM MAD,
THERE'S NO TELLING...
- CHAIRMAN, PERHAPS
WE SHOULD STOP THIS
WHILE THE CITY
IS STILL STANDING.
- Meryl: THAT GOES
WITHOUT SAYING.
- HUH?
- WHERE CAN I FIND
THE MAN IN CHARGE?
I NEED TO SPEAK TO HIM.
- AND JUST WHO ARE
YOU PEOPLE?
- LET ME SEE
THE MAN IN CHARGE!
- ( rumbling )
- ( meows )
- Meryl: HOW CAN YOU ALLOW
THIS TO HAPPEN?
THIS IS AN OUTRAGE!
YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY TAKE OUT
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON
NO MATTER HOW MANY THOUSANDS
OF PEOPLE YOU SET ON HIM.
- UH, YES, I KNOW THAT
THE RISK IS VERY HIGH.
BUT, MISS,
YOU MUST UNDERSTAND
THAT WE REALLY NEED
THAT 60,000,000,000$$.
- IT'S FOR THE PLANT.
ISN'T IT?
- Chairman: THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE OF A SUPPORT SYSTEM BUG,
OVER HALF OF THE PLANT
IS COMPLETELY UNUSABLE.
- BUT IF YOU MESS
WITH MR. VASH
AND THE ENTIRE CITY
GETS WRECKED,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE A LOT MORE
THAN JUST THE PLANT
TO WORRY ABOUT.
- Chairman: OH NO.
- HUH?
- IT MAY ALREADY
BE TOO LATE.
I THOUGHT WE SHOULD
FIGHT FIRE WITH FIRE.
SO THAT'S WHEN I CALLED IN
OUR LAST RESORT.
- AND, SIR, JUST WHAT IS
OUR LAST RESORT?
- ( sighs )
THAT.
- Girls: "THAT"?
- ( rumbling )
- ( deep grunting )
( sputters )
( whistles )
- ( gasps )
- IT'S OVER.
IT'S ALL OVER.
- ( screaming )
- ( cries )
- CAN SOMEBODY TELL ME
WHO OR WHAT THAT IS?
- IT'S THE NEBRASKA FAMILY.
- ( cries )
- ALL RIGHT, WHO'S THE IDIOT
THAT PARKED THIS CAR HERE?
ARE YOU TRYING TO MAKE
MY SON TRIP, OR WHAT?
LOOK, YOU HURT HIM!
MOVE IT NOW, YOU DUMB,
IGNORANT DRIVERS.
- LET ME BORROW THAT THING
RIGHT NOW!
- NEBRASKA FAMILY,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
BOTH OF YOU ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE SERVING
A JAIL TERM
OF 700 YEARS.
- SHUT YOUR STINKING TRAP!
WE RELEASED OURSELVES YESTERDAY
AT OUR OWN DISCRETION.
- THAT-- THAT IS CALLED
A JAILBREAK!
- ( snickers )
GEE, THAT'S TOO BAD.
AND I WAS GETTING QUITE
FOND OF THE QUIET LIFE.
BUT THEN AGAIN,
WHO CAN LIE IDLE
KNOWING THAT 60,000,000,000$$
IS THERE FOR THE TAKING?
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, GOFSEF?
- ( sputters, whistles )
- THE INFAMOUS
NEBRASKA FAMILY,
CONVICTED FELONS OF OVER
150 CLASS-A OFFENSES AND...
( gasps )
TELL ME YOU'RE NOT
GONNA SICK THAT BIG OAF
ON VASH THE STAMPEDE NOW?
- WELL, IT SEEMED LIKE
A GOOD IDEA AT THE TIME.
- OH! I'M SICK OF THIS!
WHY DOES EVERY SITUATION
WE RUN INTO
TAKE THE WORST POSSIBLE TURN?
I CAN'T STAND IT...
ANYMORE!
- Girl: WE CAUGHT
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- HUH?
- DOWN HERE.
I SAID WE CAUGHT
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- EH?
-  LIKE I SAID BEFORE,
WE CAUGHT
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- DO YOU MEAN
YOU REALLY CAUGHT HIM?
- ( running footsteps )
( panting )
WELL, MAYBE THEY'VE DECIDED
TO GIVE UP, AFTER ALL.
HUH?
( extravagant sigh )
I'M ALIVE!
- ( gun clicks )
- OH?
- DON'T MOVE, MR. VASH.
- HUH? UH-OH.
- ( guns click )
- HEY, SANDY, GO TELL CONTROL
THAT WE'VE CAUGHT HIM.
WE'VE CAUGHT VASH THE STAMPEDE.
TELL THEM TO HURRY.
- RIGHT.
- BE QUICK NOW.
- ( door closes )
- BOUNTY HUNTERS IN APRONS?
- HUH?
- WOULDN'T WANT CHILDREN
TO SEE THIS.
- ( gasping )
- THAT'S RIGHT. WE DON'T
WANT THEM TO SEE THIS!
BUT WE HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE.
WE DESPERATELY NEED MONEY.
I HAVE A SON
LYING SICK AT HOME,
BUT THE TOWN DOCTOR
DECIDED TO TAKE OFF
AND ABANDON
THIS DYING CITY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S WRONG WITH MY BOY.
I CAN'T JUST STAND BACK
AND WAIT.
THERE'S NO ONE LEFT
TO HELP HIM HERE.
THAT'S WHY-- THAT'S WHY I--
- THE PEOPLE, THE LAND,
EVERYTHING WENT WRONG
AFTER THE PLANT MALFUNCTIONED.
- BUT NOT EVERYONE
IS RICH ENOUGH
TO LEAVE THIS DAMNED CITY.
- WE NEED MONEY TO CALL
THE ENGINEERS TO FIX THE PLANT.
UNLESS IT'S REPAIRED,
THIS CITY IS FINISHED!
ALONG WITH EVERYONE IN IT.
- ONLY ONE PERSON HAS TO DIE
TO SAVE THIS CITY.
SO PLEASE, MR. VASH,
GIVE YOURSELF UP.
HUH? PLEASE DON'T MOVE.
- I UNDERSTAND YOUR SITUATION
BETTER THAN YOU KNOW.
HOWEVER...
- NO, PLEASE, SIR.
DON'T DO THAT.
( gasps )
- UNTIL I SEE THIS
MAN YOU'RE AFTER,
I HAVE NO CHOICE,
BUT TO KEEP MOVING.
- ( ragged breathing )
- NOW PLEASE,
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD,
DON'T SHOOT THAT GUN.
- ( rumbling )
- ( rattling )
- ( women gasp )
- EVERYBODY GET DOWN!
- ( gasping )
- ( screaming )
- OVER THERE.
- RIGHT, I SEE IT.
- VASH THE STAMPEDE
IS RIGHT OVER THERE.
- BINGO!
THAT WAS SO EASY,
ALMOST TOO EASY.
ARE YOU DONE
AFTER ONLY ONE SHOT?
- ( laughs )
- THAT'S FUNNY.
THAT IS SO FUNNY.
( laughs )
- ( whirring )
- ( townspeople gasp )
- ( grunts )
- ( people mutter )
- BUT WHERE'S VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- UGH!
- HA! HUH?
WHAT THE HELL?!
OH?
- ( gasps )
( gasping )
- THAT'S HIM,
THE DEVIL'S HELPER
WHO SINGLE-HANDEDLY REDUCED
A CITY OF 1,000,000 PEOPLE
TO ASHES.
THE LEGENDARY OUTLAW
VASH THE STAMPEDE
IS JUST OVER THAT HILL.
( gasps )
THAT--
THAT CAN'T--
NO WAY!
- ( snickers )
MY MY, THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
ISN'T THERE SOMETHING
WRONG WITH THIS PICTURE?
THEY MUST KNOW
THAT MAN CAN'T BE HIM.
VASH THE STAMPEDE
IS A HORRIBLE FIEND.
IF YOU GET IN HIS WAY,
HE CAN DESTROY CITIES.
AND HE CAN GET OUT OF
THE WORST SITUATIONS IMAGINABLE.
EVEN IF HE'S UP AGAINST
1,000 MEN,
HE'D FIND A WAY TO EMERGE
WITHOUT A SCRATCH.
THAT-- THAT'S WHO--
- Nebraska: WHAT NOW,
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- ( gasps )
THAT'S HIM.
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
BUDDY BOY?
ARE YOU CHICKENING OUT? HUH?!
HMM?
HMM, WELL, AREN'T YOU
A NICE GUY?
HEY, TIME'S UP,
WONDER BOY.
THROW THE FEAR OF DEATH
INTO HIM, GOFSEF,
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( Gofsef roars )
- ( loud bang )
- MOMMY!
- CHAIRMAN, THAT DAMN
NEBRASKA'S A LOOSE CANNON.
- ( frightened muttering )
- I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T WANT ANYONE
TO GET HURT.
- HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?
- ( laughs )
HUH?
- ( sighing )
- WHOA.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU BOTH
ARE STILL ALIVE AND WELL!
I WAS KIND OF HOPING
YOU'D DITCH THE WOMAN
AND SAVE YOUR OWN SKIN.
- VASH, WOULDN'T DO THAT.
HE ISN'T THAT KIND OF PERSON.
- ( gasps )
COME TO THINK OF IT...
- Nebraska: SO YOU WON'T KILL
NO MATTER WHAT, HUH?
YOU ARE DISGUSTING!
YOU KNOW WHAT, VASH?
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT
A DAMN HYPOCRITE!
THERE'S NO WAY YOU
HAVEN'T HAD TO KILL
TROUBLEMAKERS
SOMEWHERE ALONG THE LINE.
HOW DO I KNOW?
BECAUSE NOBODY COULD SURVIVE
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
WITHOUT HURTING SOMEBODY.
THE 60,000,000,000$$
BOUNTY ON YOUR HEAD
IS PROOF OF THAT.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU HAVE
TO SAY FOR YOURSELF,
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- WHY WON'T HE SAY ANYTHING?
- WHY IS HE JUST
STANDING THERE,
TAKING THAT KIND OF ABUSE?
- HMM.
HMM?
YOU'RE FINALLY READY
TO FIGHT, ARE YOU?
OH, SO YOU WANT TO DRAW?
IT'S POINTLESS NO MATTER
WHAT CALIBER PISTOL YOU USE,
LIKE TRYING TO STOP A CAR
FROM RAMMING AT
120 ILES AN HOUR.
YOU FELT IT TWICE ALREADY.
EVEN YOUR PUNY BRAIN
CAN REALIZE
MY SON'S FIST IS A FORCE
TO BE RECKONED WITH
OR DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
YOU'LL SURVIVE ANOTHER ONE?
THIS IS YOUR
LAST CHANCE TO RUN.
ALTHOUGH, NO MATTER
HOW FAST YOU ARE,
WITHIN THE NEXT FEW MINUTES,
YOU'LL BE SMASHED
INTO TINY PIECES.
( laughs )
NOW PAY ATTENTION
BECAUSE AS A COURTESY,
I'M GOING TO LECTURE YOU
ON JUST
WHAT A STUPID FOOL
YOU REALLY ARE,
USING THIS TECHNIQUE.
MY HUMAN MINCEMEAT
SPECIAL COURSE!
( laughs )
- ( gasps )
- GO HELP THEM, QUICK.
ENJOY BEING A HERO
FOR A MOMENT.
THEN DIE IN A MOST
HUMILIATING WAY.
- ( grunts )
- ( heartbeats )
- ( silent )
( silent )
- ( heartbeats continue )
- ( heartbeats increase )
- ( Gofsef grunts )
- ( gunshots )
- ( Gofsef screams )
- OH.
- HE DID IT.
- AH.
- IT CHANGED COURSE.
- THAT WAS GREAT.
- ( blubbers )
- ( strangled scream )
HE CAUSED MY SON'S FIST
TO VEER OFF COURSE
WITH SIX LITTLE BULLETS!
- NOT QUITE, DOC.
I HAVE ONE LEFT.
COULD BE MY SPECIAL ONE.
- ( screams )
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans )
( blubbers )
- MY BABY! ( cries )
- ( shouting )
- Woman: GET OUT OF THE WAY!
- ( muttering )
- WHOA.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
DID YOU SEE WHAT HE DID?
HE REALLY BEAT HIM.
AND HE DID IT WITH
ONLY SIX BULLETS.
UNBELIEVABLE.
- Meryl: SUDDENLY,
IT'S BECOME VERY CLEAR TO ME
WHY HE IS CALLED
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON.
IT'S ACTUALLY HIM.
HE'S FOR REAL.
THE LEGENDARY OUTLAW,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- Tonis: YOU'RE AMAZING.
- ( both laughs )
- THAT'S NICE OF YOU GUYS
TO SAY THAT,
BUT I'M NO MORE AMAZING
THAN YOU ARE.
- IT AIN'T OVER YET!
- ( gun cocks )
- ( popping )
- WHAT?
WHAT THE--
- THAT'S TWICE
YOU'VE SAVED ME TODAY.
- ( chuckles )
- Nebraska: DIE!
DON'T--
DON'T IGNORE ME, YOU!
DON'T-- DON'T THINK--
DON'T THINK YOU WON
EVEN FOR A SECOND.
- LET'S CALL IT QUITS ALREADY.
- HUH?
- AFTER ALL NOW,
THIS LAND IS MADE OF
LOVE AND PEACE!
- HUH?
- LOVE AND PEACE.
LOVE AND PEACE.
- All three:
LOVE AND PEACE!
- ( whimpers )
- LOVE AND PEACE!
- WHAT IS HE DOING?
- COME ON, MERYL.
YOU GOT TO WRITE
THE COMPANY REPORT,
HURRY UP.
- HUH?
- LOVE AND PEACE!
- "M. STRYFE COMPANY REPORT:
FOUR MONTHS AND TWELVE DAYS
AFTER RECEIVING OUR ORDERS
FOR THE INSURANCE
INVESTIGATION,
WE ACHIEVED CONTACT
WITH OUR TARGET,
THE MAN CALLED VASH--"
- LOVE AND PEACE!
- "CONTACT WITH OUR TARGET,
THE MAN SIMPLY KNOWN
AS VASH THE--"
- LOVE AND PEACE!
- NO, MAKE IT GO AWAY!
I CAN'T STAND ANY MORE!
- Vash: NOW, EVERYBODY,
JOIN ALONG!
LOVE AND PEACE!
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: THE LONGER ONE
HOLDS ONTO A MEMORY,
THE LONGER ONE LIVES
IN THE PAST.
THE DEEPER THE MEMORY
THEY HOLD ONTO,
THE MORE BEAUTIFUL
THE PAST WILL BECOME.
THE BEAUTIFUL MEMORIES
WILL EVENTUALLY TURN INTO HATE.
EVEN IF THEY LOOK AHEAD,
THEY LOSE THE ABILITY TO WALK.
AS LONG AS THE HEAVY CHAIN
CALLED "REVENGE"
CONTINUES TO BIND THE HEART,
THE TEARS OF SADNESS
WILL CONTINUE TO FLOW.