- ( theme music playing )
( theme music continues )
- ( saxophone playing )
- YES, MASTER,
I'M IMMINENTLY AWARE OF THAT.
LET ME TEACH HIM
THAT TO STAY ALIVE
IS TRUE SUFFERING.
FOR ALL ETERNITY
HE WILL PAY FOR
THE GRIEVOUS SIN
OF INJURING YOU.
HE WILL SUFFER
UNCEASING DESPAIR,
ANGUISH,
WOUNDS WHICH CAN
NEVER BE HEALED.
A WONDERFUL SHOW
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN,
AND YOU WILL PERFORM
AS THE STAR ATTRACTION,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- THREE DEMONS?
THREE DEMONS ARE HERE?
- Leonof: YES. THIS IS YOUR
COMEBACK CELEBRATION,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- OH, MAN.
WHAT IS THAT THING?
- HEY!  HELLO THERE.
APPARENTLY YOU'RE FROM
THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
WE'RE A PEACEFUL PEOPLE. WE
DON'T WANT ANY TROUBLE WITH YOU,
SO IF YOU'D PLEASE--
- ( all gasp )
( all gasp )
( screaming )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HE'S JUST LYING THERE.
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
- HEY, YOU!
GET OUT OF HERE.
- ( all gasp )
( screaming )
- ( laughing )
- ( Leonof laughs )
YOU SEEM SURPRISED.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THIS SHIP
IS EASY PREY FOR US.
THE NEXT FEW MOMENTS
ARE LIKELY TO BE
THE MOST FULFILLING
YOU HAVE EVE EXPERIENCED.
TEMPER, TEMPER.
- ( gasps )
- Leonof: YOUR EXCITABLE NATURE
WILL WORK NICELY FOR OUR GAME.
( laughs )
- WHAT NOW?
- ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'S THE SITUATION, DOC?
- Doc: Oh, Vash...
INTRUDERS ARE APPROACHING
FROM BOTH SIDES OF THE SHIP.
I'M AFRAID THE ONES
WHO WENT TO CHECK IT OUT
have stopped reporting in.
- I'M GONNA DO THIS MY WAY.
OH, YEAH.
A WORD TO THE WISE,
WE'RE NOT DEALING WITH
TYPICAL HUMAN BEINGS HERE.
IF YOU TRY PULLING
THE SAME STUNT AS BEFORE,
I GUARANTEE YOU
THEY WILL DESTROY YOU
THIS TIME.
- UHH.
- HUH?
- GO STAY WITH THE DOCTOR
UNTIL THIS IS OVER.
- WAIT A SECOND.
YOU MIND TELLING ME
WHAT THE HELL
THESE THINGS ARE?
'CAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE
WE SHOULD BLAME FOR THIS.
- GET MOVING!
- ( both gasp )
- ( sighs )
HUH?
- DAMN!  HOW MANY OF THESE
THINGS DO I HAVE TO SHOOT?
I'M WASTING BULLETS.
- Vash: WHERE IS HE?
WHERE'S THE MAN
BEHIND THE CURTAIN?
- ( screaming )
( screams )
- ( gunfire )
- ( gasps )
- ( whimpers )
- ( grunts )
AAH!
( grunts )
THE KICK FROM THIS THING
IS TOO STRONG.
- ( screaming )
- CONCENTRATE.
- I'M NOT ABOUT
TO TRUST YOU
TO DO EVERYTHING
AROUND THIS PLACE.
- THIS IS DEFINITELY
NOT GOOD.
THEY'RE GOING AFTER
THE POWER PLANT.
- ( all gasp )
- WHY ARE THEY DOING THAT?
- ARE THEY TRYING
TO MAKE US CRASH THE SHIP?
- VASH IS NOW OUR
ONLY HOPE AGAINST THEM.
EVERYTHING NOW DEPENDS
UPON HIS SUCCESS
ALONG WITH THE HELP AND STRENGTH
OF THE PREACHER IN BLACK.
- I'M AMAZED THAT
A GUY AS BIG AS YOU ARE
ACTUALLY MANAGED
TO GET THIS FAR.
HA.
WELL, NICE OF YOU TO POP IN.
I BELIEVE YOU'LL BE
A WORTHY OPPONENT.
HELLO THERE.
DO YOU EVEN UNDERSTAND
A WORD I'M SAYING?
ALL RIGHT,
YOU CAN TAKE OFF RIGHT NOW.
IT'S YOUR LAST CHANCE.
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
I WILL SHOW NO MERCY.
WHAT THE--?
( shouts )
WELL NOW, THAT WAS
AN INTERESTING DISPLAY.
OKAY, TRY THIS.
SAY GOODNIGHT.
- I THINK THAT'S
MOST OF THEM.
- YEAH.
- Doc: Vash!
- HMM?
- Doc: One of the demons is
heading for power room #2.
They're going to try
to bring down the ship.
- THAT POWER ROOM
IS SIX FLOORS BELOW US.
WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT ALL THE
WAY DOWN IN TIME TO STOP HIM.
HEY, WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- I'M MAKING MYSELF
A LITTLE SHORTCUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? NOW THAT I
ACTUALLY STOP TO THINK ABOUT IT,
THIS IS REALLY KIND OF...
SCARY!
- THAT IDIOT.
- ( screams )
( whimpers )
AHH.
THIS IS A NEW MODEL,
ALL RIGHT.
PACKS A PRETTY
POWERFUL PUNCH.
HUH?
( gasps )
NO.
MY FRIENDS...
IT CAN'T BE.
VAL.
JONES.
UMERA.
FARINA.
I REMEMBER YOU.
I REMEMBER ALL OF YOU.
I'VE NEVER FORGOTTEN YOU.
I'M SORRY I DIDN'T
COME HOME SOONER.
I--
I'M SO...
( crying )
( gasps )
( grunts )
- DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
WHAT ARE YOU
CRYING FOR?
THIS ONLY HAPPENED BECAUSE
YOU'RE HERE, REMEMBER?
I AM THE THIRD
GUNG-HO-GUN,
HOPPARD THE GAUNTLET.
- TELL ME WHY!
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO KILL THEM?!
WHY WOULD YOU EVEN WANT TO
DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- THAT'S SIMPLE.
BECAUSE YOU ARE
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- ( gasps )
- COMPARED TO WHAT
YOU DID TO JULY
AND AUGUSTA,
THIS IS A STROLL
THROUGH THE TULIPS.
YOU SHOULDN'T EVEN
BE ON THIS PLANET.
- ( sighs )
- IN FACT,
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
I'M GOING TO CRUSH YOU
WITH MY GUTTERRIER.
- ( gasps )
- HMM?
WELL, HOW'D THAT FEEL?
( gasps )
IT DIDN'T MAKE A DENT.
I GET IT.
YOU MUST BE
GRAY THE NINELIVES.
CAN'T EXACTLY SAY
I'M HAPPY TO MEET YOU.
I GUESS THE RUMOR OF THE MAN
WITH THE NINE EXTRA LIVES
ACTUALLY HAD SOME
TRUTH TO IT.
( gasps )
AAH!
( grunts )
SHIT.
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO DO THAT,
YOU BIG DUMB?
HUH?
GREAT.
CAN THIS GET ANY WORSE?
- ( grunts )
AAH.
- IN ANOTHER LANGUAGE,
THE WORD "CONTRADICT"
IS DERIVED FROM
A BATTLEFIELD SITUATION
WHEN A GREAT SPEAR
AND A GREAT SHIELD
WERE PITTED AGAINST
EACH OTHER AND BOTH BROKE.
THE DIFFERENCE HERE IS THAT
MY SHIELD IS INVINCIBLE.
IT WILL REPEL
ANY KIND OF ATTACK.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GIVE IT A TRY.
( gasps )
- THAT IS WHAT'S KNOWN
AS A WASTE OF TIME.
NOTHING CAN CONTRADICT
MY GUTTERRIER.
- ( grunts )
( groans )
- I HAVE ONLY THREE
IMPORTANT WORDS
IN MY VOCABULARY.
"ATTACK,"
"TRAMPLE,"
AND "DESTROY."
THESE DESCRIBE WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN DOING ALL THIS TIME,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- AAH!
( grunts )
( groans )
UH-OH.
( grunts )
NOW I UNDERSTAND.
THAT EXPLAINS YOUR
INVULNERABILITY.
THIS SIMPLIFIES MATTERS.
- HUH?
- ( cackles )
- ( sighs )
HEY, STOP SHOOTING!
- YES, THAT'S IT.
KEEP ON HOLLERING
AND MAKING THOSE STUPID FACES.
I CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF IT.
- IS IT SO MUCH TO ASK?
YOU'VE CAUSED ENOUGH DAMAGE.
CAN'T YOU LEAVE THEM ALONE?
- ( giggles )
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT I
HAD THIS DONE TO MY BODY
JUST SO I COULD LISTEN
TO YOUR PATHETIC
BLEEDING-HEART NONSENSE?
( laughing )
YOU'RE CRAZIER THAN
THEY TOLD ME YOU WERE.
I'M GOING TO
PULVERIZE YOU
AND THIS SHIP INTO
TINY LITTLE PIECES!
- Vash:
MUST KEEP MOVING.
I PROMISED HER.
I MUST KEEP MOVING.
- HUH?
HE'S GOT LEONOF'S WIRE!
( shouts )
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
( screams )
- HEY, SNAP OUT OF IT.
- ( grunts )
THE PLANT.
- OH, NO.
WHAT DO WE DO?
- WELL, I'M OUT OF HERE.
HUH?
DAMN,
YOU'RE A PERSISTENT BUGGER.
- ( gun clicks )
- I'M OUT OF AMMO?!
NOT GOOD.
THAT THING'S
WAY TOO CLOSE TO THE PLANT.
DON'T!
NO!
- ( both grunting )
- HEY, MERYL,
I THINK IT FINALLY STOPPED.
- YEAH.
- ( both gasp )
- ( meows )
- WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THAT?
IT'S A--
- PLANT NUMBER ONE IS DOWN!
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
- ( crowd shouting )
- THE POWER LEVELS
OF PLANT NUMBER TWO
ARE ALSO DROPPING.
I CAN'T STOP IT.
- THE PLANT IS SHUTTING DOWN?
IS OUR CITY GONNA FALL?
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR.
WHY NOW?  WHY IN THE HELL
IS ALL OF THIS HAPPENING?
IT'S NUTS.
UNTIL YESTERDAY,
MY BIGGEST PROBLEM
WAS FIGURING OUT
HOW TO GET THE GIRL I LOVE
TO LOOK MY WAY.
- Vash:
ARE YOU GIVING UP ALREADY?
- HUH?
- IT'S TOO SOON
TO JUST GIVE UP.
THERE'S ALWAYS A SOLUTION IF
YOU'RE WILLING TO LOOK FOR IT.
WE HAVEN'T TRIED
EVERYTHING YET.
ARE YOU JUST GONNA
ROLL OVER AND DIE?
'CAUSE IF YOU WANT TO LIVE,
THINK!
THINK OF WHAT
YOU SHOULD BE DOING.
YOU CAN OPERATE THE CONTROLLER,
CAN'T YOU?
WELL, CAN'T YOU?
- YES.
- GOOD.
THEN THERE'S STILL--
STILL TIME.
- ( typing at console )
- I'M IN.
CAN YOU DO IT?
ANSWER ME!
- ( gasps )
COME ON NOW, FRIEND.
IT'S NOT OVER JUST YET.
HOLD ON JUST
A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
I CAN HELP YOU IF YOU'RE
WILLING TO GIVE IT A TRY.
I KNOW WE CAN DO THIS.
PLEASE.
- ( exhales )
- ( heartbeat )
- ( sighs )
WHAT?  WHAT IS THAT?
HMM.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
- THE PLANT!
IT'S COMING BACK TO LIFE.
- CHECK IT OUT.
THE POWER LEVELS ARE RISING.
- WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT
AFTER ALL.
- ( cheering )
- THAT'S THE WAY.
TAKE IT NICE AND EASY.
- IT'S THE ONES THAT LIVE
OUTSIDE OF TIME.
- ( clanging )
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- NO!
( grunts )
- ( all screaming )
- ( screaming, grunts )
- Wolfwood: DAMN IT.
EVERYTHING HAPPENED
EXACTLY THE WAY THEY PLANNED IT.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU SAY,
IT'S NOT GONNA CHANGE ANYTHING.
YOU'D BETTER GET USED
TO THE IDEA THAT SOME DAY
YOU'RE GONNA ALL LIVE
ON THAT DESERT PLANET!
( groans )
I KNEW THAT IT WAS
INEVITABLE,
BUT I NEVER THOUGHT
I WOULD BE THE ONE
TO TRIGGER IT.
- ( gasps, murmurs )
- HMM?
MY GOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
OH, NO.
YOU MEAN THE GIRL WE SAVED IS--
- THE SHIP.
- WE'RE DONE FOR.
WE'RE STUCK ON THIS PLANET.
- OUR WAY OF LIFE,
OUR PEACEFUL DAYS,
THEY'RE OVER.
- DAMN.
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
- IT'S VASH.
- HMM?
- THIS IS ALL HIS FAULT!
- THAT'S RIGHT,
IT'S HIS FAULT!
- YEAH.
EVERYTHING WAS FINE
BEFORE HE CAME BACK!
- FORGIVE ME.
- YOU THINK THAT'LL
MAKE IT BETTER?!
- Brad:
ALL OF YOU, SHUT UP!
- ( crowd silences )
- THIS WASN'T BECAUSE OF HIM.
IT'S OUR FAULT.
WE ALL CHOSE TO
IGNORE REALITY
WHEN WE KNEW WHAT WOULD
HAPPEN SOME DAY.
WE NEVER LIFTED
A FINGER TO HELP,
SO WE HAVE NO RIGHT
TO POINT ONE NOW.
WE'VE JUST HUDDLED TOGETHER,
SHAKING IN FEAR
LIKE SCARED ANIMALS.
WE'RE STILL ALIVE,
AND THAT'S WHAT MATTERS.
IF WE CAN WORK TOGETHER,
WE CAN BUILD A DECENT LIFE
ON THIS BALL OF SAND.
- BRAD.
- Jessica: VASH!
- HUH?
- VASH!
- JESSICA.
- YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
WHAT A RELIEF.
- THAT REMINDS ME,
I NEVER THANKED YOU
FOR THE NEW COAT, DID I?
SO THANKS.
IT FITS ME LIKE A GLOVE.
- GREAT.  IT LOOKS
REALLY GOOD ON YOU, VASH.
- SHE DOESN'T SEEM
UPSET ABOUT THE SHIP AT ALL.
GEE, SHE'S A TOUGH COOKIE.
- ( both chuckle )
- Wolfwood: NEEDLE-NOGGIN!
- Both: HUH?
- ( gasps )
- ( gasping )
- GAHH...
- ( gasps )
- ( gasping )
- BRAD!
- ( groans )
- ( gun clicks )
- BRAD, NO.
BRAD!
- I HAVE FAILED.
BUT I DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
IT WAS A PERFECT PLAN.
HMM?
- YOU DEPRAVED LUNATIC!
THIS DAMN JOB'S
KILLING ME.
- ARE YOU ACTUALLY CRYING,
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
THAT IS WONDERFUL.
TRULY WONDERFUL.
- Vash: BRAD!
BRAD!  HANG ON, BRAD.
- ( groans )
- OH, BRAD.
- ( sighs )
THE ONES WHO LIVE
OUTSIDE OF TIME.
IT REALLY IS AMAZING.
MY HANDS GREW THIS BIG
IN 13 YEARS,
BUT YOU HAVEN'T
CHANGED A BIT.
YOU'RE EXACTLY
AS I REMEMBER.
( gasping )
- ( crying )
- ( grunts )
( exhales )
- ( gasps )
- BRAD!  BRAD!
- ( Vash and Jessica crying )
- ETERNAL PAIN.
- ( sobbing )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: SELF-PROTECTION,
THE MEANS OF PROTECTING
ONESELF.
PEOPLE EXPOSE THE WEAKNESSES
WHICH PAIN THEM,
AND THUS FORM A GROUP.
BEFORE THEY KNOW IT,
THEY BEGIN TO EXCLUDE THOSE
WHO ARE NOT ONE OF THEM.
BUT WHAT BECOMES OF THOSE
WHO HAVE BEEN EXCLUDED?
I SMILED AT THE CHILDREN
WHO LIVED IN A TIGHT GROUP
IN THEIR RICKETY HOUSE.
SURE, LET'S LIVE TODAY,
LET'S LIVE TOMORROW,
AND LET'S LIVE
THE DAY AFTER THAT,
EVEN IF IT MEANS
LIVING IN ETERNAL PAIN.