- ( theme music playing )
♪ OH! ♪
- A $$700,000 REWARD
FOR THE ESCAPED CONVICTS,
THE NEBRASKA FAMILY.
THAT IS HUGE!
- DON'T WASTE YOUR TIME.
TAKE THAT ONE DOWN.
- BUT WHY?
- BECAUSE THEY WERE CAUGHT.
- HUH? WOW, IT'S ONLY
BEEN FIVE HOURS
SINCE THE WARRANT
WAS ISSUED!
THAT HAS TO BE THE RECORD!
- YOU'LL BE EVEN MORE SURPRISED
WHEN YOU SEE WHO CAUGHT THEM.
- "THE ENTIRE CITY OF INEPRIL"?
WHAT IS THIS?!
- IT'S TRUE, JUST LIKE IT SAYS.
THE ENTIRE CITY
PROBABLY JUMPED 'EM.
- THAT IS A WHOLE LOT
OF DIVVYING.
MUST BE POPULATED
BY A BUNCH OF MACHO TYPES.
- Man: ARE YOU REALLY
SURE ABOUT THIS?
AFTER ALL, THE ENTIRE TOWN
DID TRY TO KILL YOU.
- AND YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SINGLE-HANDEDLY
DEFEATED THE NEBRASKA FAMILY.
SO WHY DID YOU PASS UP
THE $$700,000?
- WELL, WHY NOT?
( chomps )
A BIG PILE OF MONEY LIKE THAT
WOULD JUST BE A NUISANCE
TO A CARELESS DRIFTER LIKE ME.
AND BESIDES, NOW I GET TO HAVE
ALL THE SALMON SANDWICHES
I COULD POSSIBLY EAT.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, GRAMS?
- OH YEAH, DARN TOOTIN'!
- I'M KINDA JEALOUS.
- ( moans )
HE COULD HAVE BOUGHT
ALL THE SANDWICH FACTORIES
WITH MONEY LIKE THAT.
- OH.
- WELL THEN,
ARE YOU GENTLEMEN
FINISHED WITH YOUR TALK?
- WHY, YES.
- THEN I WOULD SUGGEST
THAT YOU GET AWAY FROM HIM
AS SOON AS YOU CAN.
AFTER ALL, THIS MAN IS
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
HE'S DANGEROUS YOU KNOW?
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- UH, WELL, YEAH.
- HMMM.
WHY DID IT HAVE TO BE HIM?
- ( chattering )
- MAKE WAY, MAKE WAY!
STEP ASIDE PLEASE.
THE INFAMOUS OUTLAW VASH THE
STAMPEDE IS COMING THROUGH!
HE'S A WANTED MAN
WITH A BOUNTY ON HIS HEAD
FOR $$60 BILLION,
FEARED EVERYWHERE AS
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON.
- ( whimpers )
- Meryl: WATCH OUT,
HE'S THE LEGENDARY
ACE GUNMAN, FOLKS!
IF YOU COME NEAR HIM
AND HE BITES YOU,
DON'T EXPECT YOUR INSURANCE
TO COVER IT.
- HEY, MR. VASH,
STOP BY THE SALOON LATER!
IT'LL BE MY TREAT!
WE GOT SOME OF THE GOOD STUFF!
- ( laughs )
- ( growls )
- HI, VASH HONEY!
- ( laughs )
- ( growls )
- ( grunting )
YOU KNOW,
I WAS JUST WONDERING,
HOW LONG ARE YOU GUYS PLANNING
ON HANGING AROUND ME?
- WELL, ALWAYS, MR. VASH.
YOU SEE, AS INSURANCE SOCIETY
REPRESENTATIVES,
IT'S OUR ASSIGNMENT
TO CURB THE DAMAGES
IN THE CASES WHERE
YOU'RE INVOLVED.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, MERYL?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( moaning )
- JUST WHAT IN THE HELL DO YOU
HAVE TO BE UPSET ABOUT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
MUCH MONEY THE SOCIETY LOST
'CAUSE OF THE CRAP
YOU'VE PULLED?
- NOW NOW, STOP THAT.
- Boy: I'VE FOUND YOU,
VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- IT'S A BOUNTY HUNTER!
- ( popping )
- ( moaning )
- YOU'LL HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
- RATS! I THOUGHT WE WERE
GONNA GET YOU, VASH!
- I GUESS I'M JUST LUCKY THAT
THESE GIRLS AREN'T TOO SWIFT,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
- ( both cackling )
- ( guns cock )
- I UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL,
BUT THIS IS NOT THE ANSWER.
YOU HAVE TO TRY
TO CALM DOWN.
- ( rumbling )
- HUH?
- ( kids laughing )
- IT'S THE SAND STEAMER!
- ( horn blowing )
- ( people cheering )
- Man: YAHOO, TIME TO
MAKE SOME MONEY!
- Man #2: HURRY!
- WOW, IT'S A
HUMPBACK-CLASS STEAMER.
- OH MY GOSH, THAT THING
IS GIGANTIC.
I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH
A HUGE SAND STEAMER!
- ALL RIGHT!
- IT'S REALLY INCREDIBLE.
- I KNOW. MILLY?
- HMM?
- WHERE DID VASH GO?
- HE'S GONE.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- Boy: HEY HEY HEY,
LOOK AT THIS!
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
- Man #3: CHECK THIS OUT.
IT'S THE LATEST TASSELED BEAGLE!
- Man #4: HOLY MOLEY!
HOW ABOUT THIS MUCH?
- Man #5: ARE YOU NUTS?
THEY'RE WORTH WAY
MORE THAN THAT!
- HEY, MISTER, DO YOU NEED
AN EXTRA-HARD WORKER TODAY?
- I COULD USE AN EXTRA PAIR
OF HANDS, BUT NOT A KID'S.
- SHIT.
- THIS IS LIKE A BIG ANNUAL
COMMUNITY FESTIVAL.
- THE TIMING COULDN'T BE BETTER!
ALL OF THE PLANT ENGINEERS
THAT WE CONTACTED ARRIVED
ON THE STEAMER
AND WE HAVE MORE
THAN ENOUGH TO PAY THEM.
- LOOKS LIKE MY IDEA OF
CALLING IN THE NEBRASKA FAMILY
SAVED THE DAY AFTER ALL.
- YEAH RIGHT, BUT ONE FALSE MOVE
WOULD HAVE MEANT UTTER DISASTER.
- YOU'RE NO FUN.
- Both: HUH?
- Man: WHOA, THERE'S A
TOTAL BABE ON THAT SHIP.
- Man #2: SHE IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
- ( brakes squeal )
- ( shouts )
- HEY, GODDESS GIRL, WOULD YOU
LIKE TO GO ON A DATE?
HEY, I'M THE GUY WHO'S
IN CHARGE OF THIS FINE CITY.
( laughs ) HEY, DON'T BE
LIKE THAT! WHOA!
HEY, COME ON, BABE,
GIVE ME A CHANCE.
HEY, DON'T YOU KNOW
I'M SUPERSONIC SODUM THE GREAT?
HUH?
- ( rasping breathing )
- PERHAPS IT'S BETTER IF YOU'RE
NOT TOO FAMILIAR WITH ME.
- OH MY GOODNESS.
- ( laughs )
- YOU WERE JUST TIRED.
- ( footsteps )
- HMM?
- Woman: VASH THE STAMPEDE...
AGE UNKNOWN,
ORIGIN UNKNOWN,
NO PERMANENT ADDRESS,
WANTED FOR THE MURDER
OF COUNT LEBNANT VASQUES
AND UNDER SUSPICION
OF CLASS-G WEAPON DAMAGE.
THEY WILL PAY $$60 BILLION
FOR YOU, DEAD OR ALIVE.
- ( cheers )
- ( laughs )
I EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU,
MR. VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- THAT MAKES IT SO MUCH EASIER!
LET'S GET MARRIED RIGHT NOW,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
OH...
- WONDERFUL PROPOSAL.
- YOU LIKE THAT, HUH?
- BUT I HAVE YOU AT
A DISADVANTAGE.
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME.
AREN'T YOU CURIOUS A LITTLE?
- HMM, I ALREADY CAN
TELL A LOT ABOUT YOU.
YOU HAPPEN TO BE A WOMAN
WHO, BY CHANCE,
HAD HER HEART STOLEN
BY A STOIC PEACE-LOVING GUNMAN.
IN A WORD,
A PRETTY FAIRY.
- MY NAME IS ELIZABETH.
- HUH.
- I HAPPEN TO BE THE
CHIEF ENGINEER OF
THE MARIUS BRESKEN KANTACLE
TECHNICAL INDUSTRIAL UNION
WORK DISPATCH TEAM.
- SO IN SHORT YOU'RE A
FAIRYLIKE PLANT ENGINEER THEN?
- DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT PLANTS, MR. VASH?
- HUH?
AREN'T THEY, LIKE,
LOST TECHNOLOGY
FROM OVER 100 YEARS
AGO OR SOMETHING?
- THAT'S RIGHT. THEY ARE
SYSTEMS WHICH CAN ACHIEVE
PRODUCTION BEYOND ALL
THEORETICAL LAW.
THEY ARE THE LEFTOVERS FROM
THE PANDORA'S BOX GOD GAVE US
THAT ALLOW YOU AND I TO EXIST
IN THIS POOR ENVIRONMENT.
I CAME TO THIS PLACE
TO REPAIR THE PLANT
AND TO KEEP THAT HOPE ALIVE
FOR THESE PEOPLE.
- THEN WILL YOU MARRY ME?
- FIRST I HAVE A SPECIAL JOB
I WANT YOU TO DO FOR ME.
- IS THERE SOME KIND OF REWARD?
( whimpers )
- DON'T WORRY,
I WILL GIVE YOU WHAT YOU WANT.
- WHAT I WANT?
REALLY REALLY?
I'LL DO IT, I'LL DO IT!
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU WANT!
- OVER HERE!
EVERYTHING IS DIRT CHEAP!
- HERE'S A PIPING HOT ONE,
FRESH OUT OF THE OVEN.
- OOH, THANKS!
SMELLS DEE-LICIOUS!
- FOR CRYING OUT LOUD,
WHERE THE HELL DID THAT
MAN RUN OFF TO NOW?
- MEOW.
- ALL OF THESE EXTRA PEOPLE HERE
MAKES IT HARD TO FIND HIM.
- THAT DOESN'T MEAN
HE'D BE IN THERE.
KEEP LOOKING, MILLY.
- WELL, HELLO THERE, CUTIE PIE!
I'M READY AND WILLING TO BE
YOUR OBEDIENT LITTLE DOGGY!
I RESPOND WELL TO DISCIPLINE.
- NICE TRY, PUNK, BUT YOU'RE
JUST A CHILD.
- THAT'S RIGHT! SHE MAY NOT
LOOK IT, BUT SHE'S 20--
- MILLY, HE DOESN'T
NEED TO KNOW THAT!
- Vash: YEAH, I'D ADVISE
AGAINST IT ANYWAY, PAL.
SHE'S REALLY BITCHY.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
- Milly: MR. VASH!
- WHAT? VASH?!
( screams )
- WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?
WHAT HAVE YOU-- HUH?
WHO, MAY I ASK, IS THAT?
- Vash: A TOTAL BABE!
- THAT IS NOT WHAT I MEAN.
- I ASKED HIM TO SERVE AS
MY PERSONAL BODYGUARD
WHILE I'M HERE TO REVISE
THE PLANT SYSTEM PROGRAM.
- Both: OH.
- COME ALONG, SPOT!
- ( barks, pants )
- Both: WHAT? SPOT?
- WHERE'S THE HOTEL?
- IT'S JUST UP AHEAD. WE'RE
ALMOST THERE, MASTER!
- THANK YOU, SPOT.
- ( growls )
- WELL, WE DID FIND HIM.
THAT IS GOOD, ISN'T IT?
- AREN'T WE GOING
TO GO FOLLOW HIM?
- I'D RATHER DO A MOUNTAIN
OF PAPERWORK
THAN WATCH OVER THAT IDIOT
FOR ONE MORE SECOND!
- Elizabeth: I'M BEGINNING
THE RESTORATION WORK
AT 6:00 A.M. SHARP,
SO, SPOT, DON'T BE LATE.
- NOT TO WORRY, MA'AM.
IN SOME PLACES I'M KNOWN AS
ROOSTER BOY OR EARLY BIRD
OR EVEN
MR. UP-AND-AT-'EM.
( groans )
HEY, AREN'T WE
IN THE SAME ROOM?
- AS SOON AS MY WORK
IS DONE, SPOT.
UNTIL THEN, YOU ARE GOING
TO SLEEP IN THE INNERMOST ROOM.
GOOD NIGHT NOW.
- ( sighs )
IT NEVER SEEMS
TO GO MY WAY.
HMMM?
SOMETHING'S COMING.
( shrieks ) STOP!
HEY, YOU'RE NOT PLAYING FAIR.
( gulps )
OHHH!
STOP THERE.
I DON'T LIKE SLEEPING WITH MEN,
ESPECIALLY UGLY ONES.
WOULD YOU PLEASE BE
GOOD ENOUGH TO GO NOW?
HEY, HE ACTUALLY DID
WHAT I ASKED HIM.
- ( beeping )
- HMM?
( panting )
- HUH? WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
THIS IS HORRIBLE!
- OH HI, NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
GO BACK TO SLEEP!
- OH MY GOD, IT'S VASH
THE STAMPEDE!
( screams )
- I'M GLAD THAT I TOOK THE TIME
TO SWITCH OUR ROOM NUMBERS
IN THE HOTEL REGISTRY.
- THAT'S NO FAIR!
- AREN'T YOU PROTECTING ME?
- I'D AT LEAST LIKE
TO HEAR AN EXPLANATION.
- TOMORROW WILL DO.
- I LOST MY ROOM
SO CAN I SHARE YOURS?
- BUT YOU HAVE
A BED RIGHT OUT THERE.
- ( sobs )
- ( wind gusting )
- THAT'S SO COLD.
- Owner: I SURE AM GLAD YOU
BERNARDELLI PEOPLE ARE HERE.
HERE'S MY INSURANCE POLICY.
- Meryl: BY THE WAY,
FOR OUR RECORDS, WHO WAS
STAYING IN THIS ROOM?
- CAN'T YOU TELL
BY LOOKING AT THE DAMAGE?
IT WAS VASH THE
STAMPEDE OF COURSE.
- OH.
UH YEAH, THAT GUY.
- Elizabeth: THERE CAN
ONLY BE ONE REASON WHY
SOMEONE IS
TRYING TO KILL ME.
MOST OF WHAT CREATED THE PLANT
WAS LOST TECHNOLOGY.
AND I HAVE THE KNOWLEDGE
TO USE IT,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
NECESSARILY MEAN
THAT I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND
WHAT THE PLANT REALLY IS.
- WELL, HOW HAVE YOU MANAGED
UP TO THIS POINT?
- THE UNION HAS ALWAYS
PROVIDED AN ESCORT FOR ME
IN CASE THERE WAS
ANY TROUBLE, BUT THIS TIME,
ISN'T IT WONDERFUL
YOU WERE HERE FOR ME?
- I'LL DO MY BEST TO LIVE
UP TO YOUR EXPECTATIONS!
- Man: HEY, YOU!
- Man #2: YOU CAN'T
COME IN HERE!
THIS AREA'S RESTRICTED!
- I FOUND OUT YOU'RE
THE ONE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE HOTEL EXPLOSION.
- WELL, YOU FOUND OUT WRONG.
- IT WAS YOUR FAULT, WASN'T IT?
- THE CHIEF IS
GONNA GET MAD AT US
FOR NOT DOING OUR JOB AGAIN!
- BUT I WAS THE VICTIM
IN ALL THIS!
BESIDES, YOU'RE NOT
REALLY CRYING, ARE YOU?
- ANYWAY, THIS PLANT IS
AN IMPORTANT PLACE
AND YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED
TO BE IN HERE.
- BUT I REALLY NEED HIM HERE.
AFTER ALL, SPOT IS
GUARDING ME.
- HUH?
HE MAY APPEAR
TO BE HARMLESS,
BUT HE'S VASH THE STAMPEDE,
YOU KNOW.
- THAT'S EXACTLY
WHY I NEED HIM.
- BUT DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
WHEREVER THIS MAN GOES,
HE ALWAYS LEAVES TROUBLE
BEHIND HIM.
- CHIEF! THERE'S A MALFUNCTION
IN SECTION NUMBER THREE!
- GEE, WHAT AMAZING TIMING!
- NO-OOO!
- ( whirring )
- I DON'T GET IT.
THE PRODUCTION SYSTEM
IN PLANT NUMBER FOUR
SUDDENLY STARTED OPERATING.
- SHUT DOWN THE MAIN CONTROL.
- YES, MA'AM!
IT'S NO GOOD.
IT'S NOT SHUTTING DOWN!
- THIS IS REALLY BAD.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO SEND THE
PLANT ALL THE NEW DATA DIRECTLY.
SPOT?
- YES?
- COME.
- HUH?
- COMING!
- WAIT A MINUTE! WHERE
ARE YOU GOING?
- TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
EVEN IF I HAVE TO SHAKE YOU
FROM ME, I'VE GOTTA GO!
- THERE'S DEFINITELY
SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THE DYNAMICS
OF THE SITUATION HERE!
- I THINK
WE BETTER TAKE SHELTER!
THERE'S TROUBLE ALREADY
SWARMING AFTER HIM!
- ( panting )
- Elizabeth: FLIP THE SWITCH.
- RIGHT!
- GET IN.
- RIGHT AWAY! I'M ON IT.
( gasps )
GET BACK!
- ( evil laughter )
- RUN.
CAN'T YOU RUN?
NICE WARM-UP.
NOW LET'S PLAY.
- ( groans )
- ( both yelling )
- ( gurgling )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU GOT IN HERE,
MY VICIOUS LITTLE FRIEND.
IT'S A MYSTERY TO ME.
- ( bangs )
- ( moans )
- YOU'RE ACTUALLY
KIND OF CUTE!
- Elizabeth: I GUESS I'LL HAVE
TO GET SOMEONE BETTER
TO BEAT YOU.
IT LOOKS LIKE
I'LL HAVE TO DO IT MYSELF.
- ( footsteps, screams )
HEY, WHAT DID
YOU DO THAT FOR?
AM I BEING PUNISHED
FOR SOMETHING?
- I WANT YOU TO DEAD.
- HUH?
- OH, ARE YOU AFTER
THAT STUPID REWARD?
- NO. I WANT YOU TO DIE FOR
WHAT YOU DID ON STAR DATE 0104,
JULY 21st, 2:06 P.M.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
I'D THINK THAT YOU WOULD,
BECAUSE THAT WAS THE DAY
THAT YOU EARNED FIRST
CRIMINAL RECORD.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT DAY YOU TRANSFORMED THE
THIRD CITY OF JULY, MY HOMETOWN,
INTO NOTHING LESS
THAN HELL ITSELF.
( Elizabeth chuckles )
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF WITCHCRAFT YOU USED--
THE CITY WAS
SO BADLY DESTROYED,
AND YET NO ONE WAS KILLED.
BUT DO YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED AFTER?
1,400,000 PEOPLE BECAME
HOMELESS AND DESTITUTE,
THEIR BODIES AND SOULS
PARCHED TO THE BONE.
THEY ABUSED EACH OTHER,
STOLE FROM EACH OTHER
AND DESPISED ONE ANOTHER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE OF YOU
I WAS THROWN INTO HELL,
BUT I STILL HAD
TO GO ON LIVING!
- MOMMY, DADDY!
WHY AREN'T YOU MOVING?
( cries )
- Elizabeth: I REMEMBER IT
LIKE IT WAS YESTERDAY,
WANDERING THROUGH THE RUBBLE
OF WHAT USED TO BE A CITY
AT THE AGE OF THREE.
- ( gasps )
( whimpering )
- I WANT YOU TO EXPERIENCE
THE SAME PAIN
AND SADNESS I FELT.
IT'S YOUR TURN.
NOW IS THE TIME...
TO AVENGE
MY MOTHER AND FATHER!
REPENT...
REPENT AND DIE!
VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN DO?
- IT'S NO GOOD. THE POWER
LEVELS AREN'T DROPPING!
- IF WE DON'T CONTROL IT,
IN A FEW HOURS IT WILL
TRIGGER AN OVERFLOW!
THEN MELTDOWN TIME.
- FIRE HAS ERUPTED AND SPREAD
INTO THE ENOMES GLASS.
- IF IT EXPLODES, IT'LL LEAVE
A CRATER 200 YARZ WIDE!
- Elizabeth:
I INPUT THE NEW DATA.
HOW ARE THE POWER LEVELS?
- Man: IT'S NO GOOD!
THEY'RE NOT DROPPING!
- EVERYONE EVACUATE
THE FACILITY. QUICKLY!
- YES MA'AM!
- MOVE IT PEOPLE, LET'S
MOVE, LET'S MOVE!
- EXCUSE ME,
WHERE'S MR. VASH?
- HE DECIDED TO STAY BEHIND.
- WHAT?
- THAT'S RIGHT, HE'S DECIDED
TO STAY OUT OF IT.
- BUT IT'S NOT NECESSARY
FOR HIM TO STAY BEHIND!
I'M GOING TO GO GET HIM BACK!
- WAIT, MERYL,
DON'T GO IN THERE.
IT'S TOO LATE.
- BETTER GET OUT QUICKLY
OR YOU'LL BE KILLED.
- UH?
- ( grunts )
THE PLANT IS ACTIVATED.
DAMN! DID THAT WOMAN
LEAVE ME HERE TO DIE
WITH THAT IDIOT
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
THAT WASN'T OUR DEAL!
( groans )
WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING!
- AND IT WAS SO HARD
TO GET THE FUNDS TO REPAIR IT.
- WE HAVE TO LEAVE.
- BUT VASH IS STILL
IN THERE, MOM!
- Man: GET BACK!
- COME ON,
WE'D BETTER LEAVE.
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
- Meryl: THE PLANT!
- ( gasps ) WHAT?
- Man: THE LEVELS
ARE DROPPING!
- Man #2: BUT HOW
DID THAT HAPPEN?
- Man: HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
- IT CAN'T BE!
- IT COULDN'T BE!
- ( all gasp )
- ( townspeople clamoring )
- Both: ALL RIGHT, YES!
- VASH DID IT!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
MR. VASH IS ALIVE!
HE STOPPED THE PLANT FROM
EXPLODING AND HE SAVED US ALL!
- UH, YEAH.
- THANKS, MR. VASH!
- NICE GOING, VASH!
- THAT WAS INCREDIBLE, VASH!
- YOU SAVED OUR BUTTS!
- HUH?
- AREN'T YOU GONNA GO SEE HIM?
- OH, UH...
HE JUST LIKES TO
SCARE PEOPLE. HE'S SO BAD.
COME ON, MILLY, LET'S GO
ORGANIZE OUR PAPERWORK.
- HUH?
HEY, MERYL, WAIT UP!
- Man: HEY, THANKS, VASH!
- Woman: THANK YOU, VASH!
- THANKS AGAIN!
- THANKS A LOT, VASH!
- Elizabeth:
YOU... HOW?!
- I'M VERY SORRY
THAT I DIDN'T DIE.
I JUST COULDN'T ALLOW EVERYONE
IN THE CITY TO BE DESTROYED.
- ( sighs )
HOW DARE YOU.
HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT
AFTER WHAT YOU DID!
- ( clicks )
- IF YOU HAD SUCCEEDED
IN DESTROYING THE PLANT,
THEN YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
THE SAME AS ME.
- I KNOW THAT,
BUT YOU'RE THE LAST PERSON
I WANT TO HEAR THAT FROM.
YOU DESTROYED JULY!
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A HYPOCRITE!
- I HAVE NO MEMORY
OF ANY OF IT.
- ( gasps )
- Vash: THAT RUINED CITY
WITH ALL THE PILES OF DEBRIS
WERE THE FIRST AND LAST THINGS
I SAW OF THAT PLACE.
IT'S STRANGE-- I CAN'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING BEFORE THAT...
EXCEPT FOR MEMORIES
OF MY EARLY CHILDHOOD.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME
IT WASN'T YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- DON'T KNOW?
THEN JUST LET ME
BLAME YOU FOR IT!
LET ME HAVE MY REVENGE!
- Man: WAY TO GO, MR. VASH!
THE CITY IS SAVED!
- ( Elizabeth shuddering )
WHY DID IT HAVE
TO BE YOU?!
WHY DID SOMEONE LIKE YOU
HAVE TO TURN OUT TO BE
VASH THE STAMPEDE?!
( sobbing )
- I'M SORRY.
- ( gasps )
IT COULDN'T BE THE SAME MAN.
( ragged breathing )
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
IT WAS YOU ALL THE TIME.
( sobbing )
THAT CAN'T BE.
THAT CAN'T BE...
( sobbing continues )
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: THE TRAGEDY
ENDLESSLY REPEATED
IN ORDER TO FULFILL DESIRES,
THE LUST FOR CONQUEST,
MAKING PEOPLE BEND TO YOUR WILL,
A THRILL INTENSE ENOUGH
TO MAKE YOU SHUDDER--
THERE'S A MAN WHO WAS
A SLAVE TO THAT ECSTASY.
THE LEADER OF THE BAD LADS,
A MAN WHO SHINES--
BRILLIANT DYNAMITES NEON.
THE SAND STEAMER WILL SHAKE
THE MOMENT THE HUGE DYNAMOS
ON EACH OF HIS SHOULDERS
START TO SPARK.
IN THE PITCH BLACK DARKNESS,
THE GRUESOME PARTY BEGINS.