- ( theme music playing )
♪ OH! ♪
- ( alarm blaring )
- Woman: TARGET PLANET
ON MAXIMUM TELEFINDER RANGE
IN FIVE, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE.
HERE IT COMES!
- ( cheering )
- HEY, GUYS,
THIS COULD BE IT.
SURE LOOKS PROMISING THIS TIME,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- I HAVE A GOOD
FEELING ABOUT THIS.
I THINK THAT PLANET IS
GOING TO BE OUR NEW HOME!
- ACCORDING TO OUR PRELIMINARY
OBSERVATIONAL DATA,
IT SEEMS TO BE
REASONABLY SIMILAR TO HOME.
- ENOUGH WITH
THE SCIENTIFIC CRAP ALREADY.
I SAY WE TAKE A CHANCE.
LET'S LAND THIS PUPPY.
WE'VE DONE THE COLD SLEEP
FIVE TIMES.
IF WE GET FROZEN ONE MORE TIME,
WE'LL SHRIVEL UP! ( laughing )
- ( grunts ) KNOCK IT OFF.
YOU'RE SUCH A PIG, STEVE.
- IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO SETTLE HERE.
AND BESIDES, WHETHER
WE LAND OR NOT,
THAT'S NOT A DECISION
FOR US TO MAKE.
IT DEFINITELY HAS
A HABITABLE ENVIRONMENT,
BUT IT HAS NO EXISTING OCEANS
AND ITS STRATUM CONSISTS
MOSTLY OF QUARTZ.
IT'S NOT WORTH
WAKING UP THE OLD MAN.
- Rem: HEY, JOEY,
JUST OUT OF CURIOSITY,
WHAT KIND OF FLOWERS
ARE ON THAT PLANET?
- HUH? UH... WELL--
- WEREN'T YOU LISTENING TO
WHAT I SAID BEFORE, REM?
THAT PLANET DOESN'T HAVE--
- HOLD ON, WHY NOT?
WE DON'T KNOW THAT YET.
WE'LL DECIDE ONCE THE RESULTS
OF THE MINUTE ANALYSIS ARE IN.
FOR ALL WE KNOW,
IT JUST MIGHT HAVE THE
FLOWERS REM THINKS IT HAS.
- IF IT DOES, I SURE HOPE
THEY'LL BE RED FLOWERS!
♪ SUNLIGHT! ♪
- YOU'RE STILL IN HERE.
WHERE'S KNIVES?
- I WAS WONDERING...
WHY DON'T THEY EVER WAKE UP?
THE SHIP IS TOO QUIET.
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME
AND KNIVES.
AND EVEN WITH THE
REST OF THE CREW,
THERE ARE ONLY SEVEN OF US.
- ALL RIGHT, VASH.
THE DAY HAS FINALLY COME
TO TELL YOU WHAT IS WRITTEN
ON THE OUTSIDE OF THIS SHIP.
IT SAYS "PROJECT SEEDS."
- Young Vash: PROJECT SEEDS?
- YES, THESE SHIPS
ARE LIKE SEEDS
THAT ARE FILLED WITH
OUR OWN GENES,
GENES FROM THE HUMAN RACE.
THEY ARE SENT OFF TO DISCOVER
AND POPULATE AN UNKNOWN WORLD.
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD
SAY THAT WE ARE
THE CARETAKERS OF
ALL THOSE SEEDS.
IF THERE'S A GOD
IN DEEP SPACE,
HE MUST BE LAUGHING
AT US RIGHT NOW.
OUR PITIFUL STRUGGLE
FOR IMMORTALITY
MUST LOOK LIKE AN
IMPOSSIBLE QUEST TO HIM.
EVEN THOUGH IT MAY
LOOK SHAMEFUL TO OTHERS,
IT REPRESENTS,
FOR ALL OF US,
THE DESPERATE HUMAN WILL
TO SURVIVE,
TO CARRY ON OUR SPECIES.
WHEN THEY ARRIVE,
A FIGHT ON A NEW LAND
AWAITS THEM.
THIS SHIP IS THEIR HOME
AND UNTIL IT'S TIME,
IT'S OUR JOB TO LET THEM
SLEEP IN PEACE.
- REM, IS THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO TO HELP YOU?
- ( laughs )
- OH, THAT'S WHERE YOU ARE!
SO DO YOU WANT TO HAVE LUNCH
IN THE USUAL PLACE
IN THE REC ROOM?
- ( birds chirping )
- ( Rem humming )
- YOU REALLY LIKE
THAT SONG.
- IT SEEMS TO POP INTO MY HEAD
WHENEVER I'M HAPPY.
DO YOU THINK
IT'S STRANGE?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
IT'S A NICE SONG.
- THAT'S SWEET.
THANKS, KNIVES.
- IT'S WEIRD. NOTHING'S
ACTUALLY BEEN MOVED AROUND,
BUT EVERY TIME WE COME HERE
THIS PLACE SEEMS DIFFERENT
FOR SOME REASON.
- Rem: THAT'S BECAUSE
IT'S ALIVE.
- HMM?
- CAN'T YOU FEEL IT?
IT HAS ITS OWN RHYTHM.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY FEEL THE LIVING
HEARTBEAT OF THE PLANTS.
THERE SHE GOES AGAIN,
THINKING ABOUT HOME.
- Knives: SO THIS LOOKS
LIKE THE WORLD YOU
AND THE OTHERS KEEP
TALKING ABOUT.
- Rem: SORT OF. BUT THE
SCENERY AT HOME WAS
ACTUALLY MUCH MORE EXPANSIVE,
WITH A LOT MORE VARIETY
OF PLANTS AND ANIMALS.
- I'D LIKE
TO SEE THAT, REM!
- WE'RE NOT JUST GOING TO SEE
IT, WE'RE GOING TO CREATE IT!
WE'LL FIND A PLACE
TO CREATE OUR NEW HOME.
AND WHEN WE GET THERE...
- Knives: THERE WILL BE
NOTHING BUT PEACEFUL DAYS.
- Vash: WITH NO WAR.
- Knives: AND NO STEALING.
- Vash: AN EDEN WHERE PEOPLE CAN
LIVE IN FREEDOM AND HARMONY.
RIGHT?
- Joey: THE STATE
OF OUR HOME, EARTH,
WAS SO DESPERATE,
WE HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO LEAVE.
MANKIND CAN NO LONGER
SURVIVE THERE.
THE ENTIRE POPULATION
WAS FACING DEATH,
SO PROJECT SEEDS WAS DRAFTED
AS A WAY TO RESOLVE THIS CRISIS.
- REM, THAT'S OUR SHIP.
THE ONE YOU TOLD US ABOUT.
- MM-HMM.
- JUDGING FROM THE
COMPUTER DATA,
IT LOOKS TO ME LIKE
MANKIND IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR DAMAGING THE PLANET.
RIGHT, CAPTAIN?
- I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT IT'S TRUE.
OUR YOUNG RACE BELIEVED THE LAND
AND RESOURCES WERE UNLIMITED,
WHICH LED TO GRADUAL
DESTRUCTION.
BY THE TIME THEY REALIZED WHAT
THEY HAD DONE, IT WAS TOO LATE.
THE PLANET COULD NO LONGER
TAKE THE ABUSE.
- IF THAT'S TRUE, WHY DID
THEY COME UP WITH THE IDEA
TO SET THIS PROJECT IN MOTION?
- THE NEED TO SURVIVE.
- Joey: EXACTLY.
THE BEHAVIOR OF CLINGING TO LIFE
UNTIL THE VERGE OF DEATH
IS INTRINSIC
TO ALL ORGANISMS.
SURVIVAL INSTINCTS TAKE OVER,
DISMISSING SHAME
IN ORDER TO LIVE.
- Knives: BUT IS IT RIGHT
TO LIVE IF IT MEANS
SUCH HUGE SACRIFICES?
- Joey: WE MAKE THE SMALLEST
SACRIFICE WE CAN THINK OF
AT THE TIME. UNLIKE THE OTHER
ORGANISMS ON THE PLANET,
WE POSSESS LOGIC, THE KNOWLEDGE
TO MINIMIZE THE SACRIFICE.
- ALSO AS HUMAN BEINGS, WE HAVE
THE ABILITY TO RIGHT OUR WRONGS.
HOPEFULLY WE'LL LEARN
FROM OUR MISTAKES
AND START OVER IN A NEW HOME.
AS WE JOURNEY, WE NEED
TO TAKE TIME TO SEARCH
AND THINK OF WAYS TO
MAKE EVERYONE HAPPY
WITHOUT ENDANGERING
OUR ENVIRONMENT.
- THIS IS NO GOOD.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- I'M NOT CUT OUT
TO BE AN EDUCATOR.
WHAT WAS I THINKING, REM?
I CAN ONLY TEACH THEM
HOW TO USE THE COMPUTER.
I'VE NEVER BEEN A FATHER.
I DON'T KNOW THE FIRST
THING ABOUT RAISING KIDS.
- THAT GOES DOUBLE FOR ME.
- I'M SERIOUS. YOU'RE TEACHING
THEM ALL SORTS OF THINGS--
LIKE EMOTIONS,
HOW TO BE KIND TO OTHERS
AND THE VALUE OF THE FUTURE.
- I'M NOT THAT GREAT,
JOEY, REALLY.
I JUST PLAY WITH THEM,
THAT'S ALL. IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
- ( chuckles ) YEAH, I GUESS
WE JUST HAVE A DIFFERENT WAY
OF LOOKING AT THINGS.
YOU KNOW, I WAS THINKING,
WHY DO YOU SUPPOSE
THEY CAME HERE ANYWAY?
- BECAUSE THEY'RE ANGELS!
- ANGELS?
- PERHAPS WE SHOULD PAY
MORE ATTENTION TO THEM.
VASH AND KNIVES COULD
BE ANGELS GOD SENT
TO POINT US IN THE
RIGHT DIRECTION!
THEY MAY EVEN GUIDE US
THROUGH OUR DREAM.
- ( groans )
HEY, REM HERE?
- NO, SHE'S WITH THE KIDS
IN THE REC ROOM.
- OH, LIKE THERE ISN'T
A CARE IN THE WORLD.
APPARENTLY SHE DOESN'T REALIZE
WE STILL HAVE THREE
PLANTS LEFT TO ADJUST.
- OH YES,
I MEANT TO TELL YOU.
THE TWO LITTLE GUYS TOOK CARE
OF THOSE WHILE YOU WERE NAPPING.
- WHAT?!
TELL ME YOU'RE KIDDING, ROWAN.
I'M FAST, BUT THAT'S STILL
A TWO-DAY JOB FOR ME!
WHAT'S WITH THEM?
- IT'S NOTHING TO
BE SURPRISED ABOUT.
THEIR I.Q. IS WAY
WAY ABOVE OURS!
DON'T TAKE IT SO PERSONALLY.
YOU SHOULD BE GLAD
THEY'RE WILLING TO HELP.
- MAYBE THEY'RE BETTER SUITED
FOR BRAIN WORK THAN YOU, STEVE.
YOU NEED TO LIGHTEN UP
ON THOSE KIDS A LITTLE.
- CUT THE CRAP!
- ( both wince )
- DO YOU REALLY WANT THE
SHIP LEFT IN THE HANDS
OF THOSE MONSTERS?
- HMM?
- ( gasps )
- JUST LOOK AT HOW BIG
THEY GREW IN ONE YEAR.
IT ISN'T NORMAL. THOSE KIDS
ARE MONSTERS, I TELL YOU!
MONSTERS!
- ( Vash sobbing )
- VASH!
VASH...
HEY, YOU'RE CRYING AGAIN.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S STEVE. HE SAYS
THAT WE'RE NOT HUMAN.
HE HATES ME!
- ( chuckles )
- ( evil laugh )
- Knives: I KNOW
IT'S HARD TO UNDERSTAND,
BUT TO THESE PEOPLE
WE'RE JUST UNINVITED GUESTS.
WE ONLY NEED TO BE
PATIENT FOR A LITTLE WHILE,
UNTIL THEY ACCEPT US.
- BUT REM SAID THAT
WE COULD STAY HERE.
DO YOU THINK SHE FEELS THAT WAY?
- REMEMBER WHAT JOEY SAID?
WE HAVE TO MAKE THE SMALLEST
SACRIFICE WE CAN THINK OF
AT THE TIME.
IF WE CAN DO THAT,
WE CAN GET THROUGH ANYTHING.
HEY, VASH, DO YOU KNOW
WHY PLANTS CAN'T TALK?
- REM SAID IT'S BECAUSE
THEY'RE STRONGER THAN WE ARE.
SHE SAID THEY'RE SO STRONG,
THEY CONCENTRATE ALL
THEIR ENERGY ON LIVING
SO THEY DON'T NEED TO USE WORDS.
- YEAH, THEY'RE STRONG,
BUT WE EAT THEIR FRUIT.
- WE HAVE TO EAT
THEIR FRUIT TO LIVE.
- DO YOU THINK
I'LL BE EATEN SOMEDAY?
- NO, KNIVES,
DEFINITELY NOT.
AT LEAST ACCORDING TO REM.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
SHE SAID THEY'RE MAKING
A DIFFERENT KIND OF EDEN.
- Steve: KNIVES! WHAT THE
HELL ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
- ( blow thuds )
- THIS PLACE IS OFF-LIMITS
TO YOUR KIND, YOU GOT THAT--
MONSTER?
- Knives: SO THEN
WHY AM I HERE?
- ( crying )
- DON'T!
- Knives:
THERE'S GOT TO BE A REASON.
- KNIVES?
IT WON'T BE MUCH LONGER.
- TAKE YOUR TIME.
- THIS IS TURNING INTO
QUITE A TRIM.
I NEVER NOTICED BEFORE,
BUT YOU'RE REALLY HANDSOME.
- REALLY?
DO YOU THINK SO, REM?
- HEY, I HAVE
AN IDEA, HANDSOME!
- IT'S STICKING UP!
- ( chuckles )
- I THINK IT'S GREAT.
IT REALLY SUITS YOU, VASH.
AND IT REMINDS ME OF HIM.
- Vash: WHO?
- SOMEONE I LOVED VERY MUCH
BACK HOME.
- SO WHERE IS HE NOW, REM?
- HE IS IN THE LAND
OF ANGELS...
HEAVEN.
HE WAS MY EMOTIONAL SUPPORT.
THANKS TO HIM, I WAS ABLE
TO FACE MY MISTAKES
WITHOUT JUDGMENT.
I LEARNED TO MAKE
THEM RIGHT AGAIN.
THEN I LOST HIM AND REALIZED
I WOULD HAVE TO DO IT ALONE.
BUT I WASN'T AFRAID
TO MAKE MISTAKES ANYMORE.
I BELIEVED I COULD POINT MYSELF
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION WITHOUT
LOOKING BACK.
THAT IS EXACTLY WHY
I GOT ON THIS SHIP.
SO I COULD ENTER
THE FUTURE AS I AM.
- Vash: REM, ARE YOU SAD?
- HUH?
WELL, JUST A LITTLE.
- YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE ME.
I WON'T LEAVE YOU ALONE!
I PROMISE I WON'T,
BECAUSE I REALLY LOVE YOU, REM!
- ( laughs )
YOU'RE SUCH A BABY.
BUT THANK YOU, VASH.
ANYWAY, WE'RE DONE.
SHALL WE SWITCH NOW?
KNIVES?
- ( scissors snip )
- Knives:
IT'S ALL WRONG!
- ( electricity crackling )
- HEY, SOMEHOW
I KNEW YOU'D BE IN HERE.
( gasps )
WHAT HAPPENED?
- JUST A SMALL CHANGE
OF HEART, THAT'S ALL.
BESIDES,
IF WE STAY THE SAME,
THERE'S NO INDIVIDUALITY.
- Rem: THAT'S A WONDERFUL
HAIRCUT, KNIVES!
- THANK YOU.
AS STRANGE AS IT MAY SOUND,
I ACTUALLY FEEL REFRESHED.
- Woman: YOU KNOW,
YOU LOOK VERY INTELLECTUAL!
- Rowan: WHY, YOU LOOK LIKE
A REGULAR LITTLE PHILOSOPHER.
- Vash: WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE?
- Adults: A MOMMA'S BOY.
- THAT'S MEAN!
- ( all laugh )
- All: HUH?
- I'M AMAZED YOU CAN STOMACH
EATING AT THE SAME TABLE
WITH THOSE LITTLE MONSTERS!
- STEVE, I THINK
YOU'VE HAD ONE TOO MANY.
- NO, I HAVEN'T, BABY.
- HEY, STEVE, COME ON.
DON'T YOU HAVE SOME WORK
YOU STILL HAVE TO DO
SOMEPLACE ELSE?
- SHUT UP, POINDEXTER.
I CAN ALWAYS DO THAT LATER.
- Knives: YOU'RE A DISGRACE.
- GUH?
- NOW IS THAT ANY WAY FOR A
GROWN MAN LIKE YOU TO BEHAVE
IN THE PRESENCE
OF INNOCENT CHILDREN?
- ( growls )
( cackling )
- ( Rem thinking ) HE SURE
HAS BEEN ACTING CRAZY LATELY.
- Knives:
IT'S BECAUSE HE'S AFRAID.
- WHO DOES HE THINK HE IS,
DRAPING HIMSELF ALL
OVER MARY LIKE THAT?
HUH?
- ( Mary sighs )
THOSE TWO ARE SUCH A PAIN!
BUT THEN AGAIN, I SUPPOSE
JUST ONE WOULD BE RATHER BORING.
HUH? OH.
- ( Rem humming )
- OH OH!
- HUH?
- Vash: AH AH!
- THAT WAS THE EASIEST
WAY TO STOP HIM.
YOU WANTED TO SAVE
THE BUTTERFLY, RIGHT?
- I DIDN'T WANT TO
KILL THE SPIDER.
I WANTED TO SAVE THEM BOTH!
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
UNLESS THE SPIDER
CAUGHT THE BUTTERFLY,
IT WOULD DIE OF
STARVATION ANYWAY.
YOU CAN'T SAVE BOTH.
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT?
- Rem: IT'S NOT RIGHT TO MAKE
THAT CHOICE SO EASILY.
BOTH OF THEM ARE
LIVING CREATURES, KNIVES.
SO YOU SHOULD--
- BUT I'M NOT WRONG
ABOUT THIS, REM!
IF YOU JUST KEEP
SAVING THE BUTTERFLIES,
THE SPIDERS WILL DIE!
- YES, BUT--
- WANTING TO SAVE BOTH IS
JUST A NAIVE CONTRADICTION.
AND WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE
RATHER HAD US DO?
JUST STAND
AND THINK ABOUT IT?
IN THE MEANTIME,
WHILE WE DO THAT,
THE SPIDER EATS THE BUTTERF--
- ( growls )
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU, KNIVES?
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
I WANTED TO SAVE
BOTH OF THEM, YOU IDIOT!
( panting )
- Knives: YOU DON'T MAKE
ANY SENSE, VASH.
- I DON'T THINK SO, KNIVES!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- Joey: ACCORDING
TO INTERPLANETARY LAW,
STEVE IS RELIEVED OF DUTY. HE
WILL BE DETAINED IN THE FREEZER.
( through P.A. ) Furthermore,
upon the completion
of our mission,
he will be released from
detention to stand trial.
That is all!
- ALL I DID WAS
GET A LITTLE DRUNK.
WHY CAN'T YOU BELIEVE
WHAT I'M SAYING?
- WE HAVEN'T HEARD HIS SIDE YET.
YOU'RE NOT BEING FAIR TO HIM.
- I SAW HIM GO INTO MARY'S ROOM
AND I FIND THAT UNACCEPTABLE.
- HEY WAIT,
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
- WE STILL HAVE TIME
TO DISCUSS THIS.
- IN ORDER FOR US
TO FUNCTION AS A GROUP,
WE NEED LAW. IT PROTECTS
ALL OF US FROM HARM.
THE ENTIRE TEAM
MUST UNDERSTAND THIS.
- BUT MAYBE IT WOULDN'T
HURT TO HEAR HIS SIDE OF
THE STORY BEFORE WE FREEZE HIM.
- REM, HE RAPED ME.
- NO, I DIDN'T DO IT!
- ( whooshes )
- ( screams )
- Vash: REM, WHY CAN'T EVERYONE
JUST GET ALONG WITH EACH OTHER?
- I SUPPOSE IT'S BECAUSE
PEOPLE HAVE MANY DIFFERENT
WAYS OF THINKING.
BUT EVEN IF WE DO
MAKE MISTAKES,
WE HAVE THE ABILITY TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT
AND MAKE BETTER CHOICES
THE NEXT TIME.
AND IF YOU KEEP YOUR VISION
CLEAR, YOU WILL SEE THE FUTURE.
WHAT HAPPENS IN OUR FUTURE
IS OUR OWN RESPONSIBILITY.
- ( Mary scoffs )
MARRY YOU?
- HERE.
- COME ON, YOU MUST BE TEASING.
- AS SOON AS WE'RE
FINISHED HERE,
I'D LIKE YOU TO COME
TO THE BRIDGE.
THE ANALYSIS SHOULD BE IN
IN JUST A LITTLE WHILE.
- I MADE SURE THAT STEVE
WILL NEVER WAKE UP AGAIN.
I READJUSTED
THE FREEZER.
- I DIDN'T MEAN FOR US
TO KILL HIM!
- I GUESS NOW THAT MEANS
WE'RE PARTNERS.
- ( banging )
- All: HUH?
- Joey!
- WHAT'S WRONG, REM?!
- ( panting )
- THE A-12 MONITORS,
SOMEBODY DISCONNECTED THEM.
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
ROWAN!
- IT'S HER OWN FAULT.
I HAD NO CHOICE.
I HELPED HER
AND THEN SHE BETRAYED ME.
I WAS ONLY TRYING
TO PROTECT HER FROM STEVE.
- ROWAN, PLEASE DON'T.
- SHE EVEN TOLD ME
SHE LOVED ME!
THERE'S SIMPLY NO EXCUSE.
REM, YOU DO UNDERSTAND ME?
( gasps )
- ( gasps )
- Rowan: OH, I SEE NOW.
- HUH?
- IT HAD TO BE HIM.
BECAUSE OF HIM, MARY HAD TO DIE.
IT WAS HIS FAULT.
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, ROWAN?
PLEASE PUT THE GUN DOWN.
- Joey: Rem, what's happening?
REM, REM!
- HE CAN'T GET AWAY
WITH IT, THAT MONSTER.
I HAVE TO SHOOT HIM.
NOW GET OUT OF THE WAY, REM!
- NO ONE HAS THE RIGHT
TO TAKE THE LIFE OF ANOTHER.
YOU DON'T WANT TO KILL HIM.
NOW PUT IT DOWN.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
- STAY-STAY-- STAY BACK!
( gasping )
- Rowan!
What are you doing?!
- SOMETHING'S BROKEN
INSIDE ME. I'M NUMB.
I CAN'T SEEM TO STOP.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, ROWAN.
- Joey: REM, GET OUT OF THERE!
Rem!
- Rem: IT'S NOT TOO LATE
TO START OVER.
- ( moaning )
- Rem: HERE.
- PLEASE STAY BACK, REM.
DON'T MAKE ME SHOOT YOU!
( screams )
- ( growls )
- ( both screaming )
- ROWAN!
NO, ROWAN, NO!
- ( door clanks )
- Rem: WHY DID YOU
DO THAT, JOEY?
- If I hadn't,
he would have shot you.
I'm sorry.
There was no other way.
- I KNEW ROWAN.
HE WOULDN'T SHOOT ME.
- PLEASE UNDERSTAND! I COULDN'T
SEE THAT FROM THE MONITORS.
- I HAD TO DECIDE QUICKLY.
IF I HADN'T...
- ROWAN... MARY...
- JOEY, I AGREE WITH YOU.
I THINK YOU DID
EXACTLY THE RIGHT THING.
ROWAN WENT CRAZY.
THAT'S ALL YOU COULD DO.
- THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT,
BUT WHAT IF REM WAS RIGHT?
PERHAPS HE WASN'T
GOING TO SHOOT HER.
IF THAT'S TRUE, WHAT I DID
WAS A HORRIBLE MISTAKE.
- YOU'RE JUST A HUMAN
LIKE THE REST OF THEM.
I KNOW MY CHOICE
IS THE THE RIGHT ONE.
- ( gunshot )
- ( computer beeping )
- Altering ships'
course program.
- ( gasps )
- Vash: WHAT IS IT?
- Rem: WE'RE CHANGING DIRECTION.
OUR COURSE HAS BEEN RE-ENTERED.
- WHAT?!
- SOMEONE IS SENDING ORDERS
TO ALL OF THE SHIPS.
ALL SYSTEMS ARE NOW
OPERATING ON AUTO-LOCK MODE.
OH MY GOD!
AT THIS RATE,
THE SHIPS ARE GOING TO
CRASH ON THAT PLANET!
- APPARENTLY ROWAN HAD STARTED
UP THE ORBITAL PROGRAM!
WE HAVE TO EVACUATE.
- Rem: WHERE'S JOEY?
- Knives: HE TOLD ME TO GET US
TO THE ESCAPE PODS!
HE SAID HE'D TRY
TO SAVE THE SHIPS!
- Vash: BUT WHAT ABOUT ALL
THE SLEEPING PEOPLE ON BOARD?
- WE CAN'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- REM...
- COME ON!
- WE HAVE TO GO
TO THE PODS.
- ( alarm blaring )
Warning, warning.
The ship is about
to enter the atmosphere.
Please proceed
to the escape pods.
Please proceed to
the escape pods.
- COME ON, WE'VE GOT
TO HURRY, REM!
- ( thinking ) A FIGHT ON
A NEW LAND AWAITS THEM.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO SEE IT,
WE'RE GOING TO CREATE IT.
AND IF YOU KEEP YOUR VISION
CLEAR, YOU WILL SEE THE FUTURE.
WHAT HAPPENS IN OUR FUTURE
IS OUR OWN RESPONSIBILITY.
- REM, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ALEX, HELP ME.
GIVE ME STRENGTH!
YOU TWO, GO ON AHEAD.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU MEAN. WHY?
- I CAN'T LEAVE JOEY
HERE BY HIMSELF
AND I HAVE TO TRY TO FIND
A WAY TO SAVE THE OTHERS.
- Vash: BUT THE PROGRAM
IS ALREADY RUNNING!
- YOU'VE GOT TO COME WITH US,
REM. PLEASE DON'T LEAVE US!
- I'M SORRY, VASH.
IF ALEX WERE STILL ALIVE,
I BELIEVE IN MY HEART
THAT HE WOULD DO THE SAME THING.
VASH, TAKE CARE OF KNIVES!
DON'T WORRY, VASH.
- ( screams )
( sobs )
( screams )
NO, REM!
NO, YOU CAN'T LEAVE!
( sobbing )
PLEASE COME BACK, REM!
- ( laughing )
- REM...
- I'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND HUMANS.
THEY'RE A TOTAL
WASTE OF LIFE.
TO THINK THEY'D ACTUALLY
SACRIFICE THEMSELVES
OUT OF FOOLISH SENTIMENT FOR
OTHERS. IT'S INCOMPREHENSIBLE.
I THOUGHT I'D LET HER LIVE
ONLY BECAUSE YOU WERE
SO ATTACHED TO HER.
BUT NOW I SEE HOW TRULY
IMPERFECT SHE REALLY WAS.
IT'S A GOOD THING SHE DIED.
- DON'T SAY THAT!
- THEIR IMMIGRATION
IS OUT OF THE QUESTION.
THAT WOULD BE LIKE SPREADING
PATHOGENIC ORGANISMS
ACROSS OUR HEALTHY UNIVERSE.
- YOU'RE SAYING
YOU PLANNED THIS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
YOU AND I WILL BE FINE.
I MADE SURE THE PLANT
SHIP WILL SURVIVE.
AFTER ALL WE NEED THAT
TO CREATE OUR NEW HOME,
NOW WON'T WE,
MY DEAREST BROTHER?
ONLY SHIPS CARRYING
THE HUMANS WILL CRASH.
- ( screams )
BRING HER BACK!
BRING REM BACK, YOU BASTARD!
( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- All ships now commencing
orbital correction.
- WHAT?
- ( engines roaring )
- Knives:
REVERSE THRUSTERS?
THAT BITCH ACTUALLY DID IT.
- ( crying )
I'M SORRY, REM.
- ( Rem humming )
- Rem's voice:
VASH, TAKE CARE OF KNIVES!
- ( Vash thinking )
TRUST ME, REM.
I WILL...
( cocks )
...TAKE CARE OF HIM.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: LET US REGARD
THE FIFTH MOON
SHINING DOWN UPON US
FROM THE SKIES,
STAINED RED WITH BLOOD.
AND LET US REMEMBER
HIS NAME, HIS LEGEND.
TO DO SO,
YOU ONLY NEED TO LOOK UP.
LIKE IT OR NOT, HIS LEGEND IS
CHISELED INTO THE FIFTH MOON,
A PERMANENT ETCHING
FROM A TERRIBLE PAST.
THE LEGEND
OF VASH THE STAMPEDE,
CHISELED FOREVER.
AND THEN THE TIME COMES, YOU
ONLY NEED TELL OF THE TRACKS
WHICH LEAD TO THE FUTURE.