- ( theme music plays )
- ( music plays )
- Man: VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
HE'S THE MAN WITH
THE SIXTY BILLION
DOUBLE DOLLARS ON HIS HEAD.
THEY SAY HE SHOWED UP
IN DANKIN TOWN RECENTLY.
MADE QUITE A MESS I HEAR.
- SO WHAT HAPPENED?
- ( chuckles )
THE WHOLE TOWN GOT ZAPPED.
MOUNTAINS OF CORPSES
ALL OVER DANKIN.
THE COFFIN MAKER
GOT SO RICH
HE BUILT HIMSELF
A MANSION OF WOOD.
- ( whistles )
GUY SOUNDS PLAIN CRAZY.
- HE'S MORE THAN CRAZY.
I THINK WE'D BE WISE
TO KEEP A SAFE DISTANCE.
MESSING WITH VASH
IS LIKE DANCING WITH DEATH.
HE LEAVES A TRAIL OF DESTRUCTION
WHEREVER HE GOES.
WOMEN, CHILDREN,
HE DON'T CARE.
HE'LL KILL 'EM ALL.
THEY CALL HIM
"THE HUMANOID TYPHOON."
- HUH?
- ( crash )
- HMM?
- HUH?! OHH, AHHH!
- ( metal swishes )
- HUH?
- ( whirring )
- ( man grunts )
- HMM?
- HUH?
- ( ice clinks )
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( gun cocks )
- both: HUH? AHHH!
- HUH?
- ( chuckles )
I FINALLY FOUND YOU.
- ( gunfire )
- Sherriff: ONE NIGHT AND
JUST LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
I DIDN'T BELIEVE THE RUMORS,
BUT THIS GUY
REALLY IS A TYPHOON.
OVER HALF THE TOWN
AIN'T NOTHING BUT RUBBLE NOW.
- THAT'S A REAL SHAME, BUT
THE UNDERTAKERS MUST BE HAPPY.
SO HOW MANY DID
HE GET THIS TIME?
100, 200?
- ACTUALLY, ZERO.
THERE'S A WHOLE LOT
OF INJURIES,
BUT SOMEHOW
NO FATALITIES AT ALL.
I GUESS WE HAD
A MIRACLE HERE...
WITHOUT GOD'S HELP.
- SO WHAT WAS HE LIKE?
- ( sighs )
WELL, HE WORE RED,
HAD EARRINGS--
A GIANT MAN WITH SHORT LEGS.
I'M AFRAID I DIDN'T GET
A REAL GOOD LOOK AT HIM MYSELF.
- THANKS, SHERIFF.
- WHATEVER YOU DO,
STAY AWAY FROM HIM
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
- RED.  HMPH!
- Radio Host: THE AREA OF DANKIN
IS MOSTLY DEMOLISHED.
ALL RESIDENTS GO TO YOUR
DESIGNATED SHELTER AREAS.
THE NEXT UPDATE
WILL BE AT 1: 30 P.M.
- HUH?
- UNTIL THEN,
PLEASE ENJOY
OUR MUSICAL SELECTION.
- ( leering chuckles )
- WHAT'LL YOU HAVE?
- A BANANA SUNDAE.
- HUH?
- AND I WILL HAVE A GATOE
MILK BOWL WITH SALONG TEA.
- All: HUH?!
- ( growling )
( grunts )
LISTEN, MISSES,
I'M AFRAID YOU'D BETTER
ORDER MILK WITH THAT
OR THAT GAG
AIN'T GONNA WORK.
- YEAH, 'CAUSE IF YOU DID,
WE'D GIVE YOU ALL THE MILK
YOU COULD POSSIBLY WANT.
- ALTHOUGH,
I HATE TO TELL YOU,
BUT IT WOULDN'T
EXACTLY BE FREE.
- ( men laugh )
- BUT I DIDN'T SAY MILK.
I SAID SALONG TEA.
- ( grunts )
- ( men mutter )
- HEY!
- OH, SORRY.
- YOU LITTLE BITCH, YOU!
- AWWW.
- THAT STUPID SLING
BROKE AGAIN.
- YOU HAVE A SPARE, DON'T YOU?
YOU SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- WHAT THE HELL IS SHE?
- SHE'S A MONSTER.
- BY THE WAY, MISTER,
WE HEARD THAT VASH THE STAMPEDE
SHOWED UP IN FELNARL RECENTLY.
IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU CAN TELL US?
- WHAT ABOUT VASH?
AND WHY ARE YOU ASKING?
DON'T TELL ME YOU TWO
INNOCENT-LOOKING THINGS
ARE AFTER THAT SIXTY BILLION
DOUBLE-DOLLAR REWARD.
- OH, NOT AT ALL.
- YEAH, ACTUALLY,
WE'RE JUST PASSING
THROUGH HERE ON BUSINESS.
- BUSINESS? WELL, I DIDN'T
EXACTLY SEE HIM, MYSELF.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL, HE WAS
GONE FROM THE CITY BY DAWN.
LAST I HEARD, HE WAS
HEADED OUT TO THE EAST.
- CAN YOU TELL ME
ANY MORE ABOUT HIM?
- HMM, WELL, HE STANDS ABOUT
12 FIELDS TALL.
AND HE WIELDS A HUGE WEAPON.
- Men: HUH?!
- Chef: HE'S SUPPOSED
TO HAVE A MOHAWK.
AND NERVES OF STEEL.
- ( chuckles )
- APPARENTLY, HE'S GOT
TONS OF HENCHMEN.
AND A REPUTATION AS
THE WORST WOMANIZER
ANYONE'S EVER SEEN.
- WOMANIZER!
- I HEARD WHAT HE SAID,
"A HUGE WEAPON
AND A MOHAWK."
THAT'S OUR MAN,
ALL RIGHT.
- WHERE IS HE?
WHERE THE HELL DID HE GO?
I DON'T CARE IF YOU
HAVE TO DIG UP THE WHOLE AREA--
I WANT YOU TO FIND IT.
- WELL, BOSS, I
DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THAT LITTLE COWARD
COULDN'T BE HIM.
( inhales )
I DON'T SEE ANY POINT
IN STICKING AROUND THIS PLACE.
LET'S JUST MOVE--
WAIT!
- SO YOU THINK YOU'RE BIG ENOUGH
TO GIVE ME ORDERS NOW,
YOU LITTLE WEASEL, HUH?
YOU SAW WHAT HE WAS WEARING.
YOU KNOW THAT IT'S HIM.
FIND HIM NO MATTER WHAT
OR I'LL HAVE TO BREAK YOUR NECK.
OKAY?
- YES, BOSS!
- ( screams )
( grunts )
- ( gasping )
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA
SUFFOCATE A MINUTE THERE.
- IT'S VASH!
( grunts )
UGH!
- HI, THERE.
PARDON ME.
THANKS FOR NOTHING, FELLAS.
- ( empty rounds click )
- ( laughing )
- ( screams )
( pants )
( screaming )
- THAT WAS A PRETTY CLOSE ONE.
ALMOST BOUGHT THE FARM
BACK THERE.
IT'S ACTUALLY A MIRACLE THAT
I GOT AWAY WITH IT THIS TIME.
- I FOUND HIM!
OVER THERE!
- ( screams )
PERFECT SHOT!
- ( gunfire )
- ( screams, pants )
- WELL, HE THINKS
HE'S FUNNY.
HUNT HIM DOWN.
- RIGHT.
- ( panting )
( breathes harshly )
I'M GETTING HUNGRY.
THEY'RE PERSISTENT.
HA HAHAHA!
I'M LIKE A SITTING DUCK
OVER HERE.
I'M DEFENSELESS!
- ( grunts )
( growls )
HUH? UH...
OH, SHIT.
- NOW, STAND REAL STILL.
YOU WOULDN'T WANT THIS GUN
TO GO OFF, WOULD YOU?
- ( gulps )
I FOUND HIM!
HE'S RIGHT
OVER HERE, BOSS!
- UH, WOULD YOU MIND
LOWERING YOUR GUN
LIKE A GOOD BOY?
- FORGET IT.
- YOU DON'T LIKE PAIN, DO YOU?
- I'M USE TO IT.
- WELL, I FEEL SORRY
FOR YOUR WIFE AND KIDS.
YOU'LL MAKE 'EM CRY.
- I AIN'T GOT NO KIDS
AND MOST WOMEN FIND ME
PRETTY OFFENSIVE. SO I'M SINGLE!
- SOUNDS LIKE A PRETTY
LONELY LIFE.
- I'M TELLING YOU...
YOU HAVE TO DIE.
IT WOULD SURE MAKE US
ALL HAPPY IF YOU DO.
- SORRY, I DON'T DO REQUESTS.
- ( metal swishes )
- HUH? GET DOWN!
- ( screams )
- ( rumbling )
- ( groans )
- BOSS! HELP ME!
- HUH, THAT'S GOOD WORK.
MY COMPLIMENTS.
- BOSS, IT HURTS.
- ATTACKING WHILE YOUR PAL
IS IN THE LINE OF FIRE.
- IT HURTS! HELP ME.
- DON'T YOU CARE
ABOUT HIM AT ALL?
- HELP.
- WE'RE NOT PALS.
OUR FATE IS
OUR BEING PARTNERS.
THE ONLY POSSIBLE WAY
HE CAN BE HAPPY
IS WHEN I'M HAPPY.
- THAT'S JUST BEAUTIFUL.
- YOU CAN SHOOT ME IF THAT'LL
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER
THAT IS IF YOUR BIG GUN
OF YOURS
ISN'T JUST FOR SHOW.
- ACTUALLY, I CAN'T STAND BLOOD.
JUST THE VERY SIGHT OF IT
MAKES ME FEEL A LITTLE FAINT.
- FINE THEN.
HOW ABOUT WE FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU GET TO SEE
YOUR OWN BLOOD, HUH?
- ( groans )
- NOW, IT WOULD
MAKE ME REAL HAPPY
IF YOU GO HOLD HIM DOWN.
- UGH!
- ( both grunt )
- ( whimpers )
- THERE NOW. DO YOU
SEE HOW DEVOTED HE IS?
- ( shivers )
HEY, COULDN'T YOU GUYS BE
JUST A LITTLE BIT MORE GENTLE?
- ( animal groans )
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
OUR PRECIOUS LITTLE CARGO
TO THE FEDS RIGHT AWAY.
- HAHAHAHA!
- YEAH! HAHA!
YEAH, WE'RE GONNA
BE FILTHY RICH.
- ( both laugh )
HUH?
- ( animal groans )
- WOMEN.
ARE THEY FRIENDS OF HIS?
- Leader: WELL, ARE THEY GONNA
TRY AND STEAL OUR REWARD?
- WE'RE GOING IN.
- RIGHT.
- ( groans )
- NOW WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I'M VERY PLEASED
TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS MERYL.
I'M-- I'M MERYL STRYFE
AND I'M HERE REPRESENTING
THE BERNARDELLI
INSURANCE SOCIETY.
- AND I'M MILLY THOMPSON.
- THIS, UH, IS A SMALL TOKEN
OF OUR GOOD WILL.
- NICE GOING, MERYL.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU HERE WITH HIM?
- ( laughs )
- ACTUALLY, NOT AT ALL.
WE WERE SENT HERE
BY THE BERNARDELLI
INSURANCE SOCIETY
TO INVESTIGATE A REPORT--
- ( gunfire )
- HUH?!
- ( chuckles )
I FINALLY FOUND YOU.
IT'S THE SIXTY BILLION
DOUBLE-DOLLAR BIG BOUNTY,
MR. VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- ( growls )
- HUH?
- MY NAME IS LOOSE RUTH.
I'M A BOUNTY HUNTER.
AND SOME PEOPLE KNOW ME AS
CONSTANCE RIFLE.
MR. VASH THE STAMPEDE,
TIME YOU KNOW THAT I'M HERE
FOR THE PRICE ON YOUR HEAD.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- WELL, MERYL?
- THIS LOOKS BAD.
- UH, DID I MISS SOMETHING?
- MR. VASH THE STAMPEDE,
IT'S A PRIVILEGE TO MEET YOU.
YOUR FACE IS STARTING TO LOOK
LIKE IT BELONGS ON
THE DOUBLE DOLLAR.
YOU REALLY CAN'T BLAME ME
FOR COMING AFTER YOU NOW,
SINCE YOUR HEAD IS WORTH
60,000,000,000.
- Milly: WHAT DO WE DO, MERYL?
- I THINK IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS.
WE'VE GOT TO STOP THEM.
- SO DID YOU YOU SAY
YOUR NAME WAS RUTH?
- UH, COULD YOU EXCUSE ME?
- WELL, I'M GLAD TO SEE
YOU ENJOY YOUR WORK, MR. RUTH.
BUT I'M AFRAID THAT
YOU'RE JUST A LITTLE BIT LATE.
- PLEASE, LISTEN TO ME.
- ME, LATE?
I DON'T RECKON SO.
- ( gun cocks )
- ( gasps )
YOU ASSHOLE!
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE AIMING AT?
- JUST A SIXTY BILLION
DOUBLE-DOLLAR SKULL.
THAT'S ALL.
- DON'T BE A MORON!
- ( laughs )
- HUH?
- YOU THINK THE BOSS IS VASH?
WHERE THE HELL
DID YOU GET THAT IDEA?
- HUH?
- I AIN'T FOOL ENOUGH
TO LISTEN TO SOME LAME HENCHMAN.
SORRY, JOKE'S OVER
AND I AIN'T LAUGHING.
- HUH, THIS IS JUST STUPID.
QUIT WASTING MY TIME.
GET THE HELL OUT OF--
- Ruth: DON'T MOVE.
YOU'RE DRESSED
IN A RED COAT.
YOU'VE GOT EARRINGS
AND YOUR LEGS ARE SHORT.
I'M CONVINCED YOU ARE
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR MIND!
VASH IS A BLONDE-HAIRED MAN
IN A RED COAT
AND HE CARRIES
A GREAT BIG HANDGUN OKAY.
- NO, HE ISN'T.
VASH THE STAMPEDE
IS A GIANT MAN
WITH A REALLY HUGE WEAPON
AND A MOHAWK!
- Milly:
THAT'S AWFULLY STRANGE.
- Meryl:
YEAH, THE RUMORS DON'T MATCH.
- Milly:
SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
- Meryl: WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO BELIEVE WHAT WE'VE HEARD.
- BUT MERYL.
- HUH?
- YOU'RE ALL CRAZY.
I'M NOT VASH.  HUH?!
- HEY, BOSS, LOOK!
- THE FEDS'LL PAY
SIXTY BILLION DOUBLE DOLLARS
FOR VASH THE STAMPEDE,
DEAD OR ALIVE.
SO IT'S YOUR CHOICE, FRIEND.
I'D BE HAPPY TO KILL YOU NOW
IF YOU LIKE.
- SO HE'S BLONDE,
HAS A RED COAT, A BIG GUN.
( chuckles )
I GET IT.
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET
THE JUMP ON ME, AREN'T YOU...
VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- WHAT'D HE SAY?
- Gang leader: YOU EVEN CAME UP
WITH THAT STUPID FAKE NAME.
NICE TOUCH.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
- HE IS DEFINITELY
THE REAL THING.
LET'S GET HIM!
- HMM, WELL, I'LL BE.
SO THIS IS HOW HE STAYED ALIVE
THIS LONG.
- COME ON, SHOOT!
- ( shouts )
- ( all scream )
- AAAAH! LET ME OUT OF HERE!
- THAT BASTARD!
DON'T PUSH YOUR LUCK!
( growls )
- ( whimpers )
I'M REALLY SCARED.
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON
IS ON THE LOOSE.
WHAT DO WE DO, MERYL?
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
DUH, WE RUN AWAY,
THAT'S WHAT.
- I GUESS IT IS IMPORTANT
TO STAY ALIVE, ISN'T IT?
- ( panting )
- ( shouting )
- ( gunfire )
- WE HAVE TO GIVE THE TOWN
THE EVACUATION ORDER
IMMEDIATELY.
- BUT, MERYL,
ISN'T RUNNING AWAY LIKE THIS
THE SAME AS IF WE WERE
ABANDONING OUR POST?
- IT'S MORE IMPORTANT THAT
WE CONTACT THE TOWN NOW.
- MM-HMM,
THESE ARE REALLY GOOD.
- HUH? WHEN DID
YOU GET HERE?
- THANKS A LOT.
I WAS REALLY GETTING HUNGRY.
THESE DONUTS HIT THE SPOT.
THANK YOU.  THANK YOU.
- GIVE ME THOSE! YOU KNOW,
WE DIDN'T COME OUT HERE
JUST TO SAVE
YOUR SORRY BUTT.
- OH, OKAY, THEN.
WHAT WERE YOU TWO DOING THERE?
ARE UGLY GUYS LIKE THAT
YOUR TYPE OR WHAT?
- SHUT UP, IT'S NOT
LIKE THAT AT ALL.
WE CAME TO THIS PLACE
ON OFFICIAL BUSINESS.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
OFFICIAL REPRESENTATIVES
OF THE BERNARDELLI
INSURANCE SOCIETY.
WE'RE DISASTER INVESTIGATORS.
- SO IF YOU'RE REALLY
INSURANCE PEOPLE,
WHY ARE SO INTERESTED
IN SUCH A DANGEROUS BOUNTY?
- THERE'VE BEEN OVER
300 INCIDENTS
INVOLVING VASH THE STAMPEDE.
IT'S A HUGE LIABILITY
FOR ANY INSURANCE COMPANY.
( sighs )
YOU GOT TO UNDERSTAND RISKS...
( grunts )
AND JUST CUT
WHAT HE TAKES!
- YEAH, THAT MUST BE ROUGH.
( chews loudly )
- ( scoffs )
LIKE YOU CARE.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO FIND
VASH THE STAMPEDE
AND KEEP HIM UNDER
24-HOUR SURVEILLANCE.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO PREVENT
FURTHER DAMAGE.
- 24-HOUR?!
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, NOTHING.
- OH, I GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M PREPARED
TO MAKE YOU A DEAL.
IN EXCHANGE FOR THIS
AND THE DONUTS,
WOULD YOU CONSIDER GOING INTO
TOWN AND WARNING THE PEOPLE?
I'LL EVEN LEND YOU
MY OWN PERSONAL THOMAS.
- ARE YOU ACTUALLY
GOING BACK THERE?
- IT'S THE JOB.
IT'S WHAT I DO.
- ( thomas groans )
- ( silent )
- Meryl: LOOKS LIKE
IT'S ALL OVER.
GOOD, THERE DON'T
SEEM TO BE ANY CASUALTIES.
- BUT, MERYL, DIDN'T THAT
BOUNTY HUNTER GET KILLED?
I'D CALL THAT A CASUALTY.
- THAT'S TRUE.
IT'S VERY SAD.
- WELL, HOW'RE WE GONNA
APPROACH 'EM THIS TIME?
HAVE YOU GOT SOME KIND
OF PLAN?
- ( laughs ) YEAH.
A DELUXE BOX OF 30.
- HEY, WHAT A GREAT IDEA!
- AS LONG AS WE'RE
CLEVER ABOUT THIS
AND TREAT THEM WITH
COURTESY AND RESPECT,
WE HAVE NOTHING TO FEAR.
- ( metal swishes )
- ( screaming )
- YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF NERVE
COMING BACK HERE.
- PLEASE ACCEPT
THIS TOKEN OF GOODWILL.
- I HATE PRESENTS. NOW, WHERE'S
THE GUY YOU RAN AWAY WITH?
- UH, I DON'T KNOW.
WE SPLIT UP HALF WAY.
- AND IT WAS SO DAMN HARD
TO TRACK HIM DOWN.
WHAT THE HELL ARE WE GONNA
DO ABOUT THIS, RUTH?
- YOU'RE ALIVE?
- HOW CAN YOU STILL BE ALIVE?
I THOUGHT YOU TWO WERE
FIGHTING TO THE DEATH.
- IT LOOKS AS THOUGH WE BOTH
MADE A LITTLE ERROR.
- "WE MADE THE ERROR"?
IN MY OPINION,
YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT SCREWED UP.
IT WASN'T ME.
LISTEN HERE.
WE'RE GONNA SPLIT IT.
70-30.
AND DON'T YOU FORGET IT.
- WHAT IS ALL THIS ABOUT?
- TIME TO GO.
- HOLD ON JUST A MINUTE.
- ( whimpers )
OH, MERYL.
- I GUESS, I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
TAKEN THIS JOB, AFTER ALL.
- Gang leader:
WHAT GOOD WILL THIS DO?
THESE TWO ARE USELESS.
- Ruth: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
JUST ENJOY THEM.
- OH, YOU'VE GOT BAD TASTE,
SICK AND TWISTED,
BUT, ACTUALLY,
I KIND OF LIKE IT.
- THEY DID SAY HE WAS
THE WORST KIND OF WOMANIZER.
- NOW IS NOT THE TIME
TO REMIND ME OF THAT.
- ( both shiver )
- ( chuckles )
I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOU PREFER, LADIES.
PLEASURE BEFORE DEATH?
OR JUST DEATH WITHOUT PLEASURE?
- ( squeaks )
- HE HE HE HE HE HE.
HM-HMM.
( breathy exhale )
HUH?
- Minion: BOSS, WE GOT
A BIG PROBLEM!
- I'M BUSY!
- YA-OWW!
WELL, ACTUALLY,
IT'S ME
WITH THE BIG PROBLEM HERE.
- HE'S HERE.  THAT LITTLE--
- ( growls )
- HE CAME BACK.
- ( gunfire )
- GOTCHA.
- ( grunting )
- AH!
- RUN!
- ( gunfire )
- ( whimpers )
- THANKS FOR SAVING ME
THE TROUBLE
OF LOOKING FOR YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT,
VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- VASH?
- ( gang leader grunts )
HUH?
HUH?! WHERE'D HE GO?
- WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- TO THE POTTY, SIR.
- HMM.
- ( yelping )
- HE DID SAVE OUR LIVES.
- PRETTY PATHETIC HERO
IF YOU ASK ME.
- MOMMY!
- ALL RIGHT, CORNER HIM.
- UH-OH.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
WELL, VASH, IT'S TIME
TO CHOOSE YOUR WAY TO DIE.
BY A BOOMERANG OR TO
A SUICIDE DIVE OFF THE CLIFF.
- SUICIDE?
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DISAPPROVE OF SUICIDE
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
- HMM.
ALL RIGHT,
THE BOOMERANG IT IS.
ARGH!
WHAT?
- AYE, AYE, AYE, AYE,
AYE, AYE, AYE, AYE,
DANGEROUS TOYS ARE FUN,
BUT YOU COULD GET HURT.
- YOU BASTARD!
( screams )
( bones crunching )
- WATCH OUT, BOSS!
- HEY, BOSS, LOOK OUT!
- ( gasps )
- HE GOT THE BOSS!
- THAT GUY ISN'T HUMAN!
- ( both screaming )
- ( sighs ) WHAT FRAGILE
BONDS OF LOYALTY.
NOW, YOU THERE!
- HUH?
- YOU BETTER LOOK OUT!
- WHAT FOR? UGH!
- OOPS, JUST
A LITTLE TOO LATE.
- ( gasping )
- WELL, FRIENDS,
I REALLY HOPE YOU FEEL BETTER.
- ( gags )
- THAT'S AMAZING.
HE ACTUALLY GOT BOTH OF THEM
IN A MATTER OF MINUTES.
- IT'S AS IF HE WERE
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- HUH?
- WELL, DID I WORK OFF
THE DONUTS
AND THE TEN DOUBLE DOLLARS?
- HUH?
- ( hysterical laughing  )
( hysterical laughter
continues )
- IT CAN'T BE HIM.
THERE'S JUST NO WAY.
- ( screams )
- ( screaming )
- ( gargled scream )
- ( rumbling )
- ( typing )
- Meryl: "DISASTER REPORT:
WE HAVE DETERMINED
THAT THE LANDSLIDE,
WHICH DESTROYED FELNARL
WAS A DIRECT RESULT OF
THE ILLEGAL USE OF EXPLOSIVES
BY A MAN CALLED LOOSE RUTH.
PLEASE PAY ALL INSURANCE CLAIMS
AS PER REGULATIONS."
( sighs )
AFTER ALL THAT WORK, WE'RE AT
LESS THAN ZERO ON OUR VASH HUNT,
BUT WE CAN'T JUST
IGNORE THE RUMORS.
THIS IS GOING TO BE DIFFICULT.
- WHAT ABOUT THAT CRAZY GUY?
- HMM?
- HE COULDN'T POSSIBLY BE VASH.
I JUST DON'T BUY THAT.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- Man: VASH THE STAMPEDE?
- Man #2: YUP, THAT'S THE ONE.
THE MAN WITH SIXTY BILLION
DOUBLE DOLLARS ON HIS HEAD.
THEY SAY HE SHOWED UP
IN FELNARL.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ABOUT IT?
- NO, SO WHAT HAPPENED?
- THE FUNNY THING IS
THEY SAY NOBODY DIED.
- YOU MEAN LIKE, "YOU DON'T
NEED GOD FOR A MIRACLE"?
- ( both laugh )
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
CANNOT BE EXPRESSED IN WORDS,
HUMAN EMOTION.
EMOTIONS OF THE HEART CAN'T
JUST BE TUCKED AWAY IN A CLOSET.
THERE'S A WAY
TO KNOW THE EMOTIONS.
LOOK INTO THE EYES.
THE GIRL LIED TO ME...
AND I BELIEVED HER.
THE GENTLEMAN LIED TO ME
WHEN I TRUSTED HIM.
BUT THE MOMENT
I LOOKED INTO HIS EYES,
THE ANGEL OF DESTINY
BEGAN TO UNRAVEL THE TRUTH.
JUST LOOK INTO THEIR EYES.
THERE IS ONLY ONE TRUTH.