- ( theme music playing )
- ( panting )
WELL, AREN'T YOU
GONNA SHOOT ME?
- WHERE DO I FIND YOUR BOSS?
- UH...
I WAS BOUGHT.
IT WASN'T MY FAULT.
THE MAN I THOUGHT
TO BE MY FATHER...
TURNED OUT TO BE
NOTHING MORE THAN AN AGENT.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ELSE.
I SWEAR.
( groans )
HEY, IT'S DANGEROUS
TO BE TOO TRUSTING.
WHAT IF I DECIDED TO GET UP
AND SHOOT YOU IN THE BACK?
- I'M NOT THAT TRUSTING.
I KEPT MY FINGER ON THE TRIGGER
THE WHOLE TIME.
- ( murmuring )
- WHAT NOW, VASH?
- ( typewriter keys clacking )
- Meryl:
ROUTINE REPORT, DATE: JULY 20th.
TWO DAYS AFTER THE INCIDENT
CAUSED BY A MAN NAMED MONEV,
TENSION STILL RUNS HIGH
IN THE CITY.
THE EVENTS THAT OCCURRED THERE
MADE ME REALIZE SOMETHING
ALL OVER AGAIN.
IT'S AN AWARENESS
WHICH BECOMES OBSCURED
AS I KEEP REGULAR
CONTACT WITH HIM.
THAT BEING THE REASON
VASH THE STAMPEDE
IS CALLED
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON.
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY IS IT
THAT SO MUCH TROUBLE
FALLS INTO THIS MAN'S LAP?
LAST DECEMBER,
FOUR MONTHS AGO,
WE, MERYL STRYFE
AND MILLY THOMPSON,
EMPLOYEES OF THE BERNARDELLI
INSURANCE SOCIETY MAIN OFFICE,
WERE HANDED DOWN OUR ORDERS.
OUR OBJECTIVE WAS TO MAKE
CONTACT WITH VASH THE STAMPEDE--
A MAN WANTED FOR
60 BILLION DOUBLE DOLLARS
UNDER SUSPICION OF CLASS "G"
PROPERTY DAMAGE.
UPON LOCATING
THIS HUMANOID TYPHOON,
IT WAS OUR MISSION TO MINIMIZE
ANY TROUBLE INVOLVING HIM,
AND BRING A QUICK RESOLUTION
TO SITUATIONS THAT
HAD ALREADY STARTED.
- WHAT ABOUT VASH?
AND WHY ARE YOU ASKING?
DON'T TELL ME YOU TWO
INNOCENT-LOOKING THINGS
ARE AFTER THAT
60 BILLION-DOUBLE DOLLAR REWARD.
- OH, NOT AT ALL.
- YEAH, ACTUALLY, WE'RE JUST
PASSING THROUGH HERE
ON BUSINESS.
- BUSINESS?
WELL, I DIDN'T EXACTLY
SEE HIM MYSELF.
AS FAR AS I COULD TELL, HE WAS
GONE FROM THE CITY BY DAWN.
LAST I HEARD, HE WAS
HEADED OUT TO THE EAST.
- CAN YOU TELL ME
ANY MORE ABOUT HIM?
- HMM, WELL, HE STANDS
ABOUT 12 FIELDS TALL.
AND HE WIELDS A HUGE WEAPON.
- HUH?
- HE'S SUPPOSED TO HAVE
A MOHAWK AND NERVES OF STEEL.
APPARENTLY HE'S GOT
TONS OF HENCHMEN,
AND A REPUTATION AS THE WORST
WOMANIZER ANYONE'S EVER SEEN.
- WOMANIZER!
- I HEARD WHAT HE SAID.
HUGE WEAPON AND A MOHAWK.
THAT'S OUR MAN, ALL RIGHT.
- ( typewriter keys clacking )
- HAVING OBTAINED
INFORMATION OF SOMEONE
MATCHING VASH'S DESCRIPTION,
WE FINALLY ACHIEVED CONTACT
WITH HIM AFTER THREE MONTHS.
- NOW WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I'M VERY PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS MERYL.
I-- I'M MERYL STRYFE,
AND I'M HERE REPRESENTING
THE BERNARDELLI
INSURANCE SOCIETY.
- AND I'M MILLY THOMPSON.
- THIS, UH, IS A SMALL
TOKEN OF OUR GOOD WILL.
- NICE GOING, MERYL!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU HERE WITH HIM?
- ( chuckles )
- Meryl:
IT WAS HIM--
THE OUTLAW,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- THAT'S A LOT DIFFERENT
FROM WHAT ACTUALLY HAPPENED.
- I TOOK A LITTLE BIT OF
LICENSE TO KEEP IT INTERESTING.
COME ON, MILLY,
DO YOU WANNA GET A PROMOTION
OR DON'T YOU?
- ( chuckles nervously )
- AT FIRST GLANCE,
I MUST ADMIT,
IT WAS A BIT DIFFICULT TO TELL
IF IT WAS HIM.
THIS WAS BECAUSE HE
DIDN'T ACT ANYTHING LIKE
THE LEGENDARY GUNMAN
THAT I'D HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT.
IN FACT, THE ONLY THING
LEGENDARY ABOUT HIM
WAS HIS HUGE APPETITE.
- ( screaming )
- JUST ONE DRINK, BRO!
- DISGUSTING.
JUST IGNORE THEM.
- HEY, INSURANCE GIRLS!
- MERYL, WAIT.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I NEED YOUR HELP!
HOW CAN YOU JUST
LEAVE ME LIKE THIS?
- HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
MAKE-UP KISS, BROTHER?
- Meryl:
HE SEEMED TO BE NOTHING BUT
A VULGAR,
HOPELESS TROUBLEMAKER.
- HMM.
- ( giggles )
- HUH?
- ( humming )
- UGH.
AND EVEN WORSE YET,
HIS INCORRIGIBLE LECHERY
MADE HIM AN EXASPERATING IDIOT.
- YOU CAN DEFINITELY
COUNT ON ME, MR. CLIFF.
- UGH.
- I DON'T LET ANYONE
IN MY SIGHTS GET AWAY.
AND I'M KNOWN FOR MY BULLETS
NEVER MISSING THEIR MARK.
- ESPECIALLY IF IT'S THE HEART
OF A BEAUTIFUL LADY.
BANG!
- AAH!
( groans )
- MERYL, YOU OKAY?
- ( groans )
JUST REMEMBERING
WHAT HAPPENED THAT DAY
GIVES ME CHEST PAINS.
I FEEL LIKE MY HEART'S
GOING TO BURST A VESSEL.
- I THOUGHT VASH WAS
REALLY FUNNY BACK THEN.
I LAUGHED ALL THE TIME.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HE WASN'T FUNNY.
HE WAS DOWNRIGHT WEIRD.
MILLY, NOBODY IN
THEIR RIGHT MIND
COULD TELL THAT
GOOFBALL WAS HIM.
HOW COULD YOU EVEN THINK THAT?
- BUT I THOUGHT IT WAS HIM
FROM THE START.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
REFUSED TO BELIEVE IT.
DOES IT BOTHER YOU THAT MUCH
THAT I COULD BE RIGHT ABOUT HIM?
- MILLY, HAVE YOU FINISHED
WRITING THE PAPERS YET?
- NO, BUT I'LL KEEP AT IT.
- AHH.
- ( keys clacking )
- HE TRIED TO FOOL US
WITH HIS PERFECT PORTRAYAL
OF A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING,
DIMWITTED LOSER,
BUT IT SOON BECAME
CLEAR TO ME
THAT HIS ANTICS WERE MERELY
PART OF HIS LITTLE GAME.
I WAS ABLE TO CONFIRM
HIS TRUE IDENTITY
AS I WATCHED HIM RESOLVE
EVERY INCIDENT
HE WAS INVOLVED IN.
- SUICIDE?
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DISAPPROVE OF SUICIDE
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
- HMM!
- ALL RIGHT,
THE BOOMERANG IT IS.
AAH!
WHAT?
- AY-YI-YI-YI-YI!
- ( groans )
- DANGEROUS TOYS ARE FUN,
BUT YOU COULD GET HURT.
- YOU BASTARD!
( screams )
- WATCH OUT!
- BOSS!
- ( metal clinks )
- ( girls gasp )
- HUH?
- ( snorts )
SCARY!
- DAMN YOU!
- AAH!
OH!
( yelping )
- ( gasps )
- JUST NO SKILL.
- OW!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
- I'M YOUR BODYGUARD
AND ACE GUNMAN,
JUST AS ADVERTISED.
- ( gunshot )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
TRYING TO PLAY
THE HERO, COWBOY?
- NO, NOT REALLY. I'M NOT AS
GREAT AS YOU MIGHT THINK I AM.
- ( air hissing )
- AH, GEE, THAT'S TOO BAD.
YOU'VE GOT A FLAT TIRE.
WELL, I GUESS YOU WON'T BE
ESCAPING IN THIS.
- ( all shouting )
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
HUH?
( straining )
SON OF A--
OH, YOU-- AAH.
- HOW'D HE DO THAT?
- ARE YOU CRAZY?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING YOURSELF INTO, MISTER?
THIS GENTLEMAN HERE IS
THE ONE AND ONLY
INFAMOUS HUMANOID TYPHOON.
HE'S VASH THE STAMPEDE!
- ( groaning loudly )
- THAT'S FUNNY.
PARDON ME.
BUT I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THAT HE WAS A LOT MORE HANDSOME.
- ARE YOU IMPLYING THAT
I AM NOT VASH THE STAMPEDE?!
- MAYBE WE SHOULD FIND OUT.
- Meryl: HE WAS A SUPERB GUNMAN
JUST AS THE RUMORS CLAIMED,
AND EVERY INCIDENT HE WAS IN
WAS SWIFTLY, SWIFTLY--
HE DID IT SO HAPHAZARDLY.
HOW COULD THOSE INCIDENTS HAVE
BEEN ANYTHING BUT DUMB LUCK?
ANY OF THEM!
( groans )
DARN IT!
UGH!
- SAFE!
- ( meows )
- HUH?
- STILL...
STILL, IT IS
THE UNMISTAKABLE TRUTH
THE HE SOLVED EACH INCIDENT
WITHOUT THE USE OF HIS GUN.
HE ABSOLUTELY REFUSED
TO HARM ANYONE,
EVEN WHEN CITIZENS
TRIED TO KILL HIM
TO COLLECT THE
BOUNTY ON HIS HEAD.
- AAH!
CAN THIS BE THE END?!
( grunts )
- THERE HE IS.
IN HERE!  GET HIM!
- OH, CRAP!
- ( gunfire )
- AAH!
- GET BACK HERE, YOU!
- THERE HE GOES!
- WE'VE GOT YOU NOW!
- OH, REALLY?
YOU MEAN ME?
- ( gunfire )
- NOT AGAIN!
WHOA!
MAMAN, WHY DOES THIS
KEEP HAPPENING TO ME?
I HAVEN'T ANYTHING WRONG,
BUT I'M ALWAYS IN TROUBLE
AND EVERYBODY'S ALWAYS
PICKING ON ME!
WHAT DO I DO, MAMAN?
( sniffles )
WHY AM I CRYING IN FRENCH?
AAH!
- Meryl: WHY DOES HE
ACT THE WAY HE DOES?
I CAN ONLY SPECULATE,
BUT PERHAPS PART OF THE
REASON CAN BE FOUND
IN THE TESTIMONY OF
MISS MONICA ALLEN
OF INEPRIL CITY.
- GET ME OUT OF HERE!
- ONLY ONE PERSON HAS TO DIE
TO SAVE THE CITY.
SO, PLEASE, MR. VASH,
GIVE YOURSELF UP.
( murmurs )
PLEASE DON'T MOVE.
- I UNDERSTAND YOUR SITUATION
BETTER THAN YOU KNOW.
HOWEVER--
- NO, PLEASE, SIR,
DON'T DO THAT.
( gasps )
- UNTIL I SEE THIS MAN
YOU'RE AFTER,
I HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO KEEP MOVING.
- ( breathes heavily )
- NOW, PLEASE...
- ( yawns )
WHO DO YOU THINK
MR. VASH WAS REFERRING TO
WHEN HE MENTIONED THE MAN
MONICA WAS AFTER?
- ( typewriter keys clacking )
- AND SO, HE FINALLY TOOK
HIS GUN INTO HIS HAND.
HE PULLED THE TRIGGER
FOR THE FIRST TIME
TO SAVE THE VERY PEOPLE
WHO HAD TRIED TO KILL HIM.
- ( rock music playing )
- HEY, TIME'S UP, WONDER BOY.
THROW THE FEAR OF DEATH
INTO HIM, GOFSEF.
- ( grunting )
- ( gasps )
- MOMMY!
- HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?
- ( cackling )
HUH?
- WOW...
( all murmuring )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU BOTH
ARE STILL ALIVE AND WELL.
I WAS KINDA HOPING
YOU'D DITCH THE WOMAN
AND SAVE YOUR OWN SKIN.
- VASH WOULDN'T DO THAT.
HE ISN'T THAT KIND OF PERSON.
- SO YOU WON'T KILL
NO MATTER WHAT, HUH?
YOU ARE DISGUSTING!
YOU KNOW WHAT, VASH?
YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A DAMN HYPOCRITE.
- ( exhales )
- THERE'S NO WAY
YOU HAVEN'T HAD
TO KILL TROUBLEMAKERS
SOMEWHERE ALONG THE LINE.
HOW DO I KNOW?
BECAUSE NOBODY CAN SURVIVE
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
WITHOUT HURTING SOMEBODY.
A 60 BILLION-DOUBLE DOLLAR
BOUNTY ON YOUR HEAD
IS PROOF OF THAT.
WELL?  WHAT DO YOU
HAVE TO SAY FOR YOURSELF,
VASH THE STAMPEDE?
HMM.
HMM?
YOU FINALLY READY
TO FIGHT, ARE YOU?
OH, SO YOU WANNA DRAW?
YOU FELT IT TWICE ALREADY.
EVEN YOUR PUNY BRAIN
CAN REALIZE MY SON'S FIST IS
A FORCE TO BE RECKONED WITH,
OR DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
YOU'LL SURVIVE ANOTHER ONE?
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO RUN.
ALTHOUGH, NO MATTER
HOW FAST YOU ARE,
WITHIN THE NEXT FEW MINUTES,
YOU'LL BE SMASHED
INTO TINY PIECES.
( laughs )
NOW PAY ATTENTION,
BECAUSE AS A COURTESY,
I'M GOING TO LECTURE YOU
ON JUST WHAT
A STUPID FOOL YOU REALLY ARE.
USING THIS TECHNIQUE.
MY HUMAN MINCEMEAT
SPECIAL COURSE.
HA-HA.
- ( slightly gasps )
- GO HELP THEM, QUICK.
ENJOY BEING A HERO
FOR A MOMENT,
THEN DIE IN A MOST
HUMILIATING WAY.
- ( grunts )
- ( heartbeats )
- ( gunshots )
- WHOA!
- HE... DID IT.
- WOW...
- IT CHANGED COURSE.
- THAT WAS GREAT!
- AAH!
- ( blubbering )
- IT CAUSED MY SON'S FIST
TO VEER OFF-COURSE
WITH SIX LITTLE BULLETS.
- NOT QUITE, DOC.
I HAVE ONE LEFT.
COULD BE MY SPECIAL ONE.
- ( screams )
- ( groans )
- MY BABY!
- ( townspeople screaming )
- WHOA.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
DID YOU SEE WHAT HE DID?
HE REALLY BEAT HIM.
AND HE DID IT
WITH ONLY SIX BULLETS.
UNBELIEVABLE.
- Meryl: SUDDENLY,
IT'S BECOME VERY CLEAR TO ME...
WHY HE IS CALLED
THE HUMANOID TYPHOON.
IT'S ACTUALLY HIM.
HE'S FOR REAL--
THE LEGENDARY OUTLAW.
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
OH, YEAH!
- ( keys clacking quickly )
- NO MATTER WHAT,
I THINK THIS MAN...
IS VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- Vash: LOVE AND PEACE!
- HUH?
- LOVE AND PEACE!
LOVE AND PEACE!
- AAH!
- YOU'RE REALLY FUN TO WATCH.
( yawns )
- MEOW.
- MMM. MILLE-FEUILLE...
- VASH THE STAMPEDE...
EVERY TIME I OBSERVE
HIS ACTIONS,
I CAN'T HELP BUT SENSE...
SOMETHING HIDDEN
DEEP WITHIN HIM.
SOMETHING WE CAN'T
BEGIN TO UNDERSTAND.
BUT THIS MUCH IS CERTAIN...
EVERYONE WHO HAS BECOME
INVOLVED WITH HIM
HAS SOMEHOW REGAINED AN EMOTION
WHICH WAS ONCE LOST.
- FATHER!
FATHER, I'M COMING!
- I'M-- I'M ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
- ( gasping )
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
IT WAS YOU ALL THE TIME?
- LIKE I'VE MENTIONED
SO MANY TIMES BEFORE,
NOTHING BEATS HARD-WON FAME.
- ( chuckles )
- MM-MM.
FROM THIS POINT ON,
WE'RE GONNA GO ON LIVING
WITHOUT RELYING ON ANYONE.
IT'LL BE JUST THE TWO OF US.
- ( giggles )
- THAT'S NICE OF YOU GUYS
TO SAY THAT.
- Meryl:
BUT I STILL WONDER...
- HUH?  OH.
MR. VASH.
- STAY BACK!
STAY AWAY FROM ME.
- WHO IS HE?
THAT'S NOT VASH.
THAT IS NOT THE SAME MAN.
WHO IS THAT MAN?
CAN HE POSSIBLY BE
THE REAL VASH THE STAMPEDE?
THE EVIL 60 BILLION-DOUBLE
DOLLAR OUTLAW
WITH THE FIRE OF HELL
BURNING IN HIS EYES?
- ( screams, grunts )
HE'LL PAY.
HE WILL PAY FOR THIS.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- HUH?
- THEY'RE DEAD.
PEOPLE ARE DEAD.
- WHO THE HELL CARES?
( groans )
AAH.
- YOU KILLED ALL THE PEOPLE!
THEY'RE ALL DEAD,
AND YOU KILLED THEM ALL!
- ( groans loudly )
- AND YOU WERE THE ONE
SOLELY RESPONSIBLE.
- AAH, AAH, AAH...
- NOW IT IS YOUR TURN TO DIE!
- ( slightly gasps )
( sighs )
THERE ARE SO MANY SIDES TO HIM.
WHICH IS THE REAL VASH?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- ( snoring )
- Man: WE'RE ALL SCARED.
WE CAN'T SLEEP AT NIGHT.
- Man #2:
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE.
- CAN'T WE GET SOMEONE TO TELL
HIM TO GET OUT OF THIS HOTEL?
- TELL VASH THE STAMPEDE
TO GET OUT?
HA!  ARE YOU INSANE?!
- ( rumbling, crashing )
- HUH?!
- ( Vash yelping )
- HUH?
- ( whimpers )
- VASH, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( both gasp )
- ( exhales )
- MM.  AAH.
- ( girls deeply sigh )
- SO THOSE SCARS
ARE THE PRICE YOU PAID
FOR DEALING WITH
YOUR OPPONENTS
WITHOUT KILLING THEM.
- IT'S NOT EXACTLY
SOMETHING I LIKE GIRLS TO SEE.
I THINK MANY OF THEM
WOULD RUN AWAY.
- I WOULDN'T RUN AWAY.
WHAT I MEAN IS
THEY WOULDN'T RUN AWAY.
UH, VASH?
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO ASK YOU
THIS FOR A WHILE NOW.
YOU HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING WRONG,
YET TERRIBLE THINGS KEEP
HAPPENING TO YOU ALL THE TIME.
THE TOWNSPEOPLE LOOK AT YOU
LIKE YOU'RE SOME
SORT OF CRIMINAL.
DOESN'T THAT BOTHER YOU?
HOW CAN YOU GO ON
LIVING THIS WAY?
IT SEEMS SO AWFUL.
- I CAN'T.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
I HAVEN'T YET
BURIED MY PAST.
THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN LIVE IN PEACE
UNTIL I'VE COME
TO TERMS WITH IT,
AND I'M ABLE TO
FINALLY PUT IT BEHIND ME.
- YOU'RE LEAVING?
- HEY, THANKS, SHERIFF,
FOR LETTING ME GO LIKE THIS.
- I'M ONLY DOING IT 'CAUSE
I DON'T WANT YOU IN MY TOWN.
AND I DON'T WANT YOUR THANKS.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO GET THE HELL OUT.
- ( chuckles )
YEAH, I GUESS I WILL.
- DO YOU PLAN TO
FOLLOW HIM THIS TIME?
- OF COURSE I AM.
I HAVE TO; IT'S MY JOB.
- THAT'S TRUE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I CAN'T VERY WELL LEAVE
THE TWO OF YOU ALONE TOGETHER,
SO I SUPPOSE
I BETTER COME ALONG.
- UGH, ANYONE EVER TELL YOU
YOU'RE JUST SIMPLY ANNOYING?
- OH, REALLY?!
YOUNG LADY,
WHEN YOU TRAVEL ALL ALONE
IN THE DESSERT,
IT CAN BE VERY PERILOUS.
BUT IF YOU ACT NOW, YOU CAN HIRE
YOUR VERY OWN BODYGUARD
FREE OF CHARGE!
AND MY WORK IS GUARANTEED.
- OH, GREAT!
I TAKE MY EYES OFF HIM
FOR A MINUTE,
AND HE'S AT IT AGAIN.
- WAIT!  WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HEY!  DON'T JUST WALK AWAY.
COME ON NOW.
YOUNG LADY!
- Meryl:
VASH THE STAMPEDE...
( chuckles )
- ( chuckles )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash:
IF YOU ONLY FACE FORWARD,
THERE IS SOMETHING
YOU WILL MISS SEEING.
IT IS A VIRTUE
TO DEVOTE ONESELF TO SOMETHING,
FIRMLY BELIEVING
IN ONE'S OWN IDEALS.
BUT THAT DOES NOT MEAN
IT'S ALL RIGHT
TO BELITTLE THE IDEALS
OR FEELINGS OF OTHERS.
IF YOU LEAD SUCH A BUSY LIFE,
AND YOU DON'T REALIZE
HOW YOUR PARENTS FEEL,
IT'S ONLY SELF-SATISFACTION.
IT'S ALL RIGHT TO STOP
EVERY NOW AND AGAIN...
IF YOU WANT A MOMENT'S REST,
IF YOU WANT TO FEEL
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE FEEL.