- ( theme music playing )
( theme music continues )
- Reporter: The typhoon
is currently gaining strength
and will be passing
approximately 30 isles
away from New Oregon.
The gale is expected
to last until 40.
Please be advised
that high wind warnings
are still in effect
until further notice.
- SO THIS IS A TYPHOON.
I'VE HEARD THAT
WIND CAN BE STRONG,
BUT I NEVER DREAMED IT COULD
BLOW WITH THIS KIND OF FORCE.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IN FACT,
THIS ONE IS SO HUFFY
SHE MUST BE RELATED TO--
( chuckles ) MR. VASH!
HER NAME IS JAQUELINE--
- ( both scream )
- ( knocks on door )
- MR. VASH, EXCUSE ME,
BUT MAY WE HAVE A MOMENT
TO SPEAK WITH YOU?
( sighs )
HUH?
- Vash: "PLEASE DON'T
LOOK FOR ME. VASH."
- DAMN, HE GOT US.
EITHER HE'S INCREDIBLY SLIPPERY
OR HE'S JUST GONE
COMPLETELY OUT OF HIS MIND.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'D ACTUALLY
GO OUT IN THESE CONDITIONS.
- NO PROBLEM. WE'LL FIND HIM.
- HUH?
- I SUSPECTED
HE MIGHT TRY THIS,
SO WHEN I BROUGHT HIM
BREAKFAST EARLIER THIS MORNING,
I SLIPPED ONE OF THESE
INTO THE FOOD ON HIS PLATE.
- OH MY GOSH.
THAT'S A TRANSMITTING DEVICE.
I'M AMAZED THE COMPANY LET
YOU HAVE SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- ( chuckles )
SINCE I'M ALWAYS MESSING UP,
THE CHIEF GAVE IT TO ME
AS A GOING AWAY PRESENT.
HE SAYS IT'LL KEEP ANYONE
FROM OUTWITTING ME.
- ( chuckles )
MILLY, I HATE TO TELL YOU,
BUT THAT'S NOTHING
TO BRAG ABOUT.
- ( beeping )
- LOOK, LOOK.
HE'S REALLY CLOSE BY.
WE'RE CATCHING UP ALREADY.
YEAH!
WARMER, WARMER.
WARMER.
- ( beeps )
- ( meowing )
- OH MY GOD.
HE CHANGED INTO
A CAT THIS TIME.
- MILLY!
- Knives: VASH.
VASH!
- ( groans )
- COME ON, VASH.
STAND UP ALREADY.
- ( sighs )
- LET'S GO.
- ( grunts )
- HEY.
DON'T BE THAT WAY.
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME HERE.
WE SHOULD AT LEAST TRY
TO ACT LIKE BROTHERS.
- ( gasps )
MURDERER.
YOUR WHOLE LIFE
IS A LIE.
YOU KILLED REM,
THE CREW.
YOU KILLED THEM ALL!
- YEAH.
SPECTACULAR, HUH?
THEY ALL DIE.
EXCEPT OF COURSE
FOR THE FRACTION
WHO WILL SURVIVE BECAUSE OF
REM'S INCESSANT MEDDLING.
- KNIVES.
YOU--
YOU AREN'T EVEN HUMAN!
( grunts )
- DAMN STRAIGHT I'M NOT.
HOW DARE YOU COMPARE ME
TO THOSE IMPERFECT THINGS.
HOW DARE YOU.
NEVER COMPARE ME TO THEM.
- ( groans )
- YOU'RE NOTHING BUT GARBAGE.
I WILL KILL YOU ALL.
ONLY WE WILL BE
LEFT ON THIS PLANET.
- REM...
- NOW VASH,
TAKE CARE OF KNIVES.
- I KNOW WHAT
I HAVE TO DO, REM.
I CAN'T WAIT ANY LONGER.
IT'S TIME TO FACE HIM.
I HAVE TO BE READY.
- JAQUELINE'S ANGLE SHOULD
PASS NEAR THE CRAGGY BLUFF
BLOWING TO THE SOUTHEAST
AT EXACTLY 1:22 PM.
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU,
OLD CHUM.
( grunts )
IF YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THIS,
YOU CRAZY OLD GEEZER,
I'LL HUNT YOU
TO THE GRAVE!
WHOA!
YEOW!
( groans )
( gasps )
I STILL FEEL LIKE I'M HAVING
A FREAKING HEART ATTACK
EVERY TIME I DO THIS.
THIS THINGS GOING
BADA-BOOM BADA-BOOM.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE
COMMITTING SUICIDE.
- SUICIDE?
I STRONGLY DISAPPROVE
OF SUICIDE.
IT'S JUST A--
HUH?
WOLFWOOD?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- FIRST YOU'RE CRYING
YOUR EYES OUT
LIKE AN ABANDONED BABY,
AND THEN YOU'RE RUNNING AROUND
JUMPING OFF CLIFFS.
WHAT THE HELL'S
THE MATTER WITH YOU ANYWAY?
- I'M VISITING.
- ( grunts )
SAY WHAT?
- I'M VISITING THE FOLKS.
- ( laughs )
YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT DO THEY HAVE,
A SUMMER COTTAGE
IN THE SKY?
I'M REALLY GETTING
SICK OF YOUR LIES.
HUH?  HEY,
WHAT THE HELL'S THAT?
- JUST WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
IT'S A SHIP THAT
DIDN'T QUITE CRASH
130 YEARS AGO.
- THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
WHO'D HAVE KNOWN THAT
THE LOST TECHNOLOGY
WAS STILL PRESERVED
LIKE THIS.
WAIT.  DID YOU SAY
YOU'RE VISITING YOUR FOLKS?
DOES THAT MEAN PEOPLE
ARE ACTUALLY LIVING UP HERE?
- I THINK THAT YOU'LL BE THEIR
FIRST HOUSE GUEST TO VISIT
IN OVER 20 YEARS.
- MISTER LEGATO,
IT HAS HAPPENED
AS EXPECTED.
HE HAS MADE HIS MOVE.
ALSO, VASH THE STAMPEDE
APPEARS TO BE WORKING
WITH A MINISTER
CLAD IN BLACK.
I SUSPECT THIS MAN IS--
- NEVER MIND HIM.
YOUR TASK WILL
REMAIN THE SAME
NO MATTER WHO HE IS.
- YES.
UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
- YOU'RE SUCH A FOOL.
HAD YOU BEHAVED,
YOU MIGHT HAVE LIVED
TO SEE DOOMSDAY.
BUT I MUST SAY,
I AM PLEASED.
FOR NOW I HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY
TO FULFILL ANOTHER
OF MY MASTER'S WISHES.
( chuckles )
- ( typing on computer )
- DOCTOR,
YOU WON'T BELIEVE THIS.
- ARE YOU GOING TO TELL
ME THAT SOMEONE IS HERE
FROM THE OUTSIDE?
- UH, YEAH.
- IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME,
BUT HE'S BACK.
SO, BRAD,
HAVE YOU EVER MET HIM BEFORE?
- WELL, YEAH I HAVE.
BUT I WAS JUST A KID
BACK THEN.
- ( chuckles )
THEN THIS WILL BE THE FIRST TIME
YOU'VE MET A REAL LEGEND.
HE'S CHANGED OVER THE YEARS.
COME WITH ME.
- SO HE REALLY IS BACK.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
- THIS IS AMAZING.
HOW MANY YEARS
HAS IT BEEN
SINCE I LAST
OPENED THIS DOOR?
- ( winces )
IS HE THERE?
IS THAT HIM?
- ( screams )
- ( gasps )
- MERCY, MERCY, MERCY!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU'RE TELLING ME NOW
I CAN'T COME IN?
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE,
YOU NEEDLE-NOGGINED IDIOT?
- OH, HEY, DOC.
- ( grunts )
- ( screaming )
- IS THAT YOUR
GREAT LEGEND?
IS THAT FOOL HIM, HUH?
- ( chuckles )
WHAT A RELIEF.
HE HASN'T CHANGED AT ALL.
- OHH.
- YOUR NAME'S BRAD,
ISN'T IT?
MAN, YOU SURE GOT TALLER.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
BY THE WAY, WHO'S HE?
- ( chuckles )
YOU KNOW,
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
- LOOK, I DON'T MIND
YOU WANDERING AROUND THE PLACE.
BUT OUTSIDERS
ARE NOT WELCOME HERE.
- OH, NOW DON'T BE LIKE THAT,
BIG GUY.
( gasps )
OKAY.
HUH?
- DON'T STARE.
COME ON INSIDE.
- GET USED TO IT.
- YOU WIN.
I'LL BEHAVE.
- VASH!
- All: HUH?
VASH!
- AHH.
- VASH!
- ( sighs )
OHH!
- ( crying )
- GEE, THIS IS ALL
RATHER SUDDEN, YOUNG LADY.
I MAY HAVE A REPUTATION
OF BEING EASY,
BUT EVEN I NEED A BIT
OF ADVANCE WARNING.
- ( giggles )
- JESSICA!
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU REMEMBERED ME.
THIS IS THE BEST DAY EVER.
- ( grumbles )
- ( gasps )
( chuckles )
- WELL, VASH,
THIS MUST BE
YOUR GIRLFRIEND, HUH?
YOU ARE ONE LUCKY DEVIL.
- SHH, SHH!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DID I EMBARRASS YOU?
- ( growls )
- SORRY.
BUT I HAVE TO SPEAK WITH THE
DOCTOR FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- HEY!
NOW THAT'S NOT FAIR.
- JESSICA.
- HMM.
COME SEE ME AFTER,
OKAY,
LIKE RIGHT AFTER?
I'LL HATE YOU
IF YOU DON'T.
- OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE BACK IN A MINUTE.
- SO, VASH, HOW'S MAX?
IS HE WELL?
- OH, YEAH.
HE'S DOING GREAT.
HE HAS STARING CONTESTS
WITH FORECAST CHARTS.
- HUH?
- ( crying )
- HMM.  WELL NOW,
I HAVEN'T INTRODUCED MYSELF.
MY NAME IS WOLFWOO--
- CAN YOU BLAME HER?
THE PEOPLE WHO LIVE
ON THIS SHIP
AREN'T ABOUT TO TRUST
A BUNCH OF OUTSIDERS
BRINGING IN
WAR AND VIOLENCE.
YOU MAKE THIS PLACE
STINK LIKE GUNPOWDER.
STAY PUT UNTIL HE GETS BACK.
I DON'T WANT ANY TROUBLE,
GOT THAT?
- ( sighs )
YOU COULD AT LEAST OFFER ME
A DRINK OR SOMETHING.
- FOR CRYING OUT LOUD,
I AM NOT THE LEAST BIT HAPPY
ABOUT THIS, MILLY.
WE HAD JUST FOUND HIM AGAIN,
AND THEN WE LET HIM SLIP
RIGHT OUT FROM UNDER OUR NOSES.
- I KNOW ALL THAT,
BUT WE CAN'T GO OUT THERE.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
- WE HAVE TO.
AND BESIDES,
DANGER IS PART OF THE JOB.
( gasps )
- ( both scream )
- ( crowd chattering )
- Wolfwood: AN ENTIRE CITY
SURROUNDED BY LOST TECHNOLOGY.
I'M SEEING INTO YOU
LITTLE BY LITTLE, NEEDLE-NOGGIN.
( grunts )
- GET OUT OF HERE, MISTER!
- ( gasps )
I'M SO SORRY.
- IT'S COOL.
- BUT HE'S RIGHT.
I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT I FEEL THE SAME WAY HE DOES.
I'M BEGGING YOU,
FOR THE GOOD OF ALL OF US,
PLEASE LEAVE THIS PLACE.
- ( crowd shouting )
- WHY, SO YOU CAN ALL JUST
CARRY ON WITH YOUR PERFECT
COZY LITTLE SHELTERED LIVES?
- HUH?
- YOU NEED TO REALIZE
YOUR PLANTS ARE NOT
INEXHAUSTIBLE.
THEY COULD VERY EASILY
BREAK DOWN SOME DAY.
YOU CAN'T CLING
ONTO THEM FOREVER.
THIS TECHNOLOGY HAS
A FINITE LIFESPAN.
- WHAT ARE YOU TELLING US?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW HARD IT IS
TO MAINTAIN THESE SYSTEMS.
WE'RE NOT PLANNING ON
ANYTHING SHUTTING DOWN
FOR A LONG TIME NOW.
- AND ANYTHING'S BETTER
THAN LIVING OUT THERE.
- I'VE HEARD THAT PEOPLE'S
LIVES ARE MEANINGLESS TO YOU,
SO WHY SHOULD WE LISTEN TO
ANYTHING YOU HAVE TO SAY?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT!
- ( all gasp )
- NO MATTER WHAT YOU SAY,
IT'S NOT GONNA CHANGE ANYTHING.
YOU BETTER GET
USED TO THE IDEA
THAT SOME DAY YOU'RE GONNA
ALL LIVE ON THAT DESERT PLANET.
- ANYTHING NEW HAPPEN
WHILE I WAS AWAY?
- NO, NOT MUCH.
THEY'RE STILL SLEEPING
IN SUSPENDED ANIMATION.
- REALLY?
- WE WERE ALL
WORRIED SICK.
YOU'VE BEEN OUT OF TOUCH
FOR NEARLY FIVE YEARS.
- I'M SORRY.
- SURE.
LIKE YOU EVEN CARE.
FIVE YEARS IS PROBABLY
NOTHING MORE THAN
THE BLINK OF AN EYE
FOR YOU ANYWAY.
- THAT'S ENOUGH, BRAD.
VASH IS NOT
THAT KIND OF PERSON.
- PERSON?
( scoffs )
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
- SINCE YOU HAVE RETURNED,
I SUPPOSE THAT MEANS
IT'S NOT OVER YET.
DID YOU COME INTO
CONTACT WITH HIM
DURING THE FIFTH MOON
INCIDENT?
- NOT DIRECTLY.
BUT MY GUESS WOULD BE THAT HE
HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
I'VE ABSOLUTELY
NO MEMORY OF IT HAPPENING,
JUST LIKE THE TIME BEFORE
IN JULY.
- TELL ME, VASH,
DID YOU FIRE IT?
- HEY, MISTER LEGEND...
( grunts )
SINCE YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT FIRED OFF THE BIG WEAPON,
DOESN'T THAT MAKE YOU
MORE DESTRUCTIVE THAN KNIVES?
- I SAID ENOUGH, BRAD!
- WELL, DOESN'T IT?!
- BRAD!
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I SUPPOSE IT DOES.
- THAT IS NOT FUNNY.
THAT IS NOT FUNNY!
IT'S THE WHOLE DAMN WORLD
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HERE!
- DON'T YOU THINK
I AM AWARE OF THAT?
HOWEVER, THE ONLY ONE WHO HAS
BEEN ABLE TO OPPOSE KNIVES,
FIGHT OFF HIS DEMONS,
AND SURVIVE THEM
IS THAT GENTLE MAN
YOU'RE HOLDING
BY THE NECK.
- ( groans )
- I'M ASKING YOU TO
PLEASE TRUST ME.
- ( growls )
- PLEASE.
- ( grunts )
- ( door opens )
- I'M SORRY.
- HE'S RIGHT.
I CAN'T BLAME HIM.
TO SIMPLE AND ORDINARY PEOPLE
I MUST SEEM LIKE A MONSTER.
- HA!  WELL, THAT'S
HALF HIS PROBLEM.
HE'S HOPELESSLY
IN LOVE WITH JESSICA,
AND HE JUST TOLD HER
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
- JESSICA.
- I'M SORRY, BRAD,
BUT I'M GONNA MARRY VASH.
- ( gasps )
- I'M GONNA MARRY VASH.
VASH, VASH!
- SO THAT'S THE OTHER HALF
OF BRAD'S PROBLEM.
( laughs )
- WHAT'S IN THERE?
( gasps )
- A LITTLE SOMETHING
YOU MIGHT BE NEEDING.
- ( humming )
HE HASN'T BEEN MUCH FUN,
BUT I'M SURE GLAD HE'S BACK.
AT LEAST HE HASN'T CHANGED.
HE HASN'T CHANGED A BIT.
HEY, VASH!  WAIT.
WAIT FOR ME.
( sighs )
LOOK AT ME, LOOK AT ME,
I'M IN LOVE.
( giggles )
- THIS DAMN SHIP IS FULL
OF NOTHING BUT ROTTEN,
IGNORANT PEOPLE.
DOESN'T ANYONE TRUST
THE WORD OF A PRIEST ANYMORE?
- ( screaming )
- ( gasps )
HEY, OPEN UP IN THERE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( gunshot )
- ( screaming )
- WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON IN THERE?
- ( panting )
- ( men gasp )
- ( crowd shouting )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- IT WASN'T ME.
IT WAS EXACTLY LIKE THIS
WHEN I GOT HERE.
- ( crowd gasps )
- HEY, LISTEN TO ME.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- BRAD, IT'S TERRI AND NATASHA.
- SHOW HIM, BRAD.
SHOW HIM.
- IT WASN'T ME, BRAD.
- ( gasps )
- I'M ASKING YOU,
PLEASE TRUST ME.
- THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN
PROVE YOUR INNOCENCE.
- THIS IS GREAT, DOC.
IT'S BY FAR
THE SMOOTHEST ONE YET.
- I'M GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
NOW WE'D BETTER HURRY.
IT'S GOTTEN VERY LATE.
JESSICA WILL BE
FURIOUS WITH YOU.
STRANGE.
SHE SAID SHE WOULD BE HERE.
HUH?
OH, YES, THAT PRESENT.
SHE WANTED TO
GIVE IT TO YOU.
SHE'S BEEN LOOKING FORWARD
TO YOUR RETURN
FOR QUITE SOME TIME NOW.
- DOC, WHAT IS THIS?
- HMM?
( gasps )
- I'LL SAY IT
ONE MORE TIME.
I DIDN'T KILL THEM.
- SHUT UP. YOU'RE A KILLER
AND A LIAR, OUTSIDER.
- YOU'RE SERIOUS,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU REALLY WANT TO
FIGHT ME, HUH?
- ( groans )
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JOSEPH!
- MOVE IT!
- WHAT?
( pants )
YOU DID THIS,
DIDN'T YOU?
BACK OFF NOW, BRAD.
YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY
SURVIVE A FIGHT
AGAINST THIS BREED
OF BAD GUY.
- WHOA.
- LEONOF, I PRESUME.
- OH?
SO YOU KNOW MY NAME.
WELL, I MUST SAY,
I'M HONORED.
I'M AFRAID WE'VE NEVER MET,
BUT I HAVE HEARD OF YOU.
AN INTERESTING REPUTATION,
YOU ARE THE MAN WHO
RINGS THE BLACK FUNERAL BELL.
CHAPEL--
- DON'T DAY IT!
ENOUGH WITH YOUR PUPPETS.
- HOLY SHIT.
- THIS IS JUST A WARM-UP.
BOTH FOR HIM
AND FOR ME.
- YOU ARE SMART,
PREACHER.
IT WOULD BE EASY
TO DESTROY YOU AT THIS POINT,
BUT THAT WOULD BE BORING.
TO MAKE THE GAME
MORE INTERESTING,
I'VE ADDED A SWEET ELEMENT.
- JESSICA!
- I HAVE BEEN WATCHING YOU
THROUGH HIS EYES
THE ENTIRE TIME.
I KNOW THAT YOU HAVE
VERY STRONG FEELINGS
FOR THIS YOUNG LADY.
VERY TOUCHING.
YOU DO KNOW WHAT
I HAVE IN MIND, DO YOU NOT?
- ( exhales )
- ( gun cocks )
- YOU PACIFISTIC FOOL.
DON'T YOU REALIZE
THIS IS A TRAP?
- I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
- THEN LOWER YOUR PIECE.
- I CAN'T.
I JUST DON'T SEE ANY WAY
OUT OF THIS DAMN SITUATION!
- THERE IS ANOTHER WAY.
IF WE SIMPLY IGNORE
THE GIRL'S PLIGHT,
WE'LL DEFINITELY
MAKE IT THROUGH.
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- I THINK THAT'S THE BEST OPTION
AT THIS POINT IN TIME.
IT'S THE ONLY LOGICAL WAY
ANY OF US WILL
SURVIVE AGAINST THEM.
- NO, YOU CAN'T.
- HOWEVER,
I DO KNOW OF A GUY
OF WHINES, CRIES,
AND THROWS TANTRUMS,
AND HE SOMEHOW MANAGES
TO FIND A WAY
TO SAVE EVERYONE.
- ( gasps )
- HE'S A CRAZY MAN
WHO'S NOT AFRAID OF ANYTHING.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S BEEN
SCARRED FROM HEAD TO TOE,
HE'LL ALWAYS BE THERE.
- ( gunshots )
- AHHH.
- ( gasps )
- JESSICA!
JESS, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
THEY DIDN'T HURT YOU,
DID THEY?
- I GUESS THEY DIDN'T.
- WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
- A FLOWER.
A RED FLOWER.
- ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
THEY CALL THIS ONE
A GERANIUM.
THERE ARE MANY OTHER
TYPES OF FLOWERS ON EARTH
OF ALL DIFFERENT
COLORS AND SHAPES AND SIZES.
THEY HOLD A VERY SPECIAL
PLACE IN PEOPLE'S HEARTS.
- CAN YOU EAT THEM, REM?
- SOME FLOWERS
CAN BE EATEN.
- DO YOU LIKE FLOWERS?
- I LOVE FLOWERS.
ESPECIALLY RED ONES.
YOU KNOW, THEY CAN BE
VERY SYMBOLIC.
EVEN THE TINIEST FLOWERS
WHICH BRAVE THE ELEMENTS
BEHOLD A MAGNIFICENT STRENGTH.
AND VASH,
IN THE LANGUAGE
OF THE FLOWER,
RED GERANIUMS REPRESENT...
DETERMINATION AND COURAGE.
- HEY, WAIT A SEC.
WHERE'D YOU GET
THE RED COAT?
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- ( giggles )
- AAH!
- OH, VASH, VASH, VASH.
I WAS SO SCARED.
I JUST KNEW YOU'D
COME BACK FOR ME.
- KNOCK IT OFF.
COME ON, WILL YOU STOP IT?
YOU'RE NOT UPSET,
ARE YOU?
- ( Leonof laughing )
- ( all gasp )
- Leonof: YOU ACT LIKE
IT'S ALL OVER,
BUT LET ME ASSURE YOU,
SOME OF MY CHILDREN
ARE STILL THERE.
BESIDES,
DID YOU REALLY THINK
THAT THE GUNG-HO-GUNS
ONLY COME TO CALL
ONE AT A TIME?
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THREE OF THEM.
- THAT IS CORRECT.
I HAVE SENT THREE DEMONS.
THEY HAVE ARRIVED,
AND WILL BE VISITING YOU
VERY SOON.
- Leonof: WELCOME.
THIS IS YOUR BIG
COMEBACK CELEBRATION,
VASH THE STAMPEDE.
- ( both screaming )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Vash: THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP.
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO PROTECT.
THERE'S A TIME
YOU MUST TAKE A STAND,
NO MATTER WHAT KIND OF
PAIN AWAITS US.
THE MAN CLAD IN THE RED COAT
TOOK UP HIS GUN
ONCE AGAIN
IN ORDER TO STOP
THE SADNESS.
THE HATE.
I KEEP THE WORD
OF THE RED GERANIUM
WHICH I WAS TAUGHT
SO LONG AGO.
I KEEP THE COURAGE
AND DETERMINATION
DEEP IN MY HEART.