(birds chirping)
(bubbles popping)
- I missed you guys.
(bright music)
My sweet waves.
> Oh oh oh )
> Oh oh )
(singing in foreign language)
- What do you think we should
make for dinner tonight?
Minato?
> That's right )
- She's come back.
- [Kawamura] Do you know her?
- [Minato] That girl is my hero.
(Minato humming)
> Oh oh oh )
> My brand new story )
RIDE YOUR WAVE
(Hinako grunting)
(Hinako groaning)
(Hinako sighing)
- Huh?
(Hinako groaning)
(Hinako panting)
(Hinako gasping)
(phone ringing)
Huh?
(Hinako groaning)
MUKAIMIZU LANDSCAPING
Yeah, hey Mom.
- [Mom] Oh, there you are.
Have you finished unpacking yet?
- What? Yeah,
everything's all unpacked.
- And you're making sure to eat?
- [Hinako] Yeah, I made omurice.
- [Mom] (chuckling) I did too.
It's what your brother
wanted for dinner.
(Hinako grunting)
And how are your classes?
- [Hinako] Don't know,
haven't started yet.
- [Mom] I still don't know
why you chose oceanography.
- (gasps) I like the sea.
- [Mom] Well, that may be,
but isn't it a lot of science?
- Don't worry, I'll be fine.
| need to call you back, okay?
- [Mom] Oh, no problem.
Talk soon.
(Hinako screaming)
- Seriously, I just
want this to work out.
- [Deputy Lieutenant]
Deploy the second hose.
- Yes, sir.
(dramatic music)
Ready.
(water hissing)
- [Deputy Lieutenant] Put
your back into it, Kawamura.
- [Kawamura] Yes, sir.
- [Deputy Lieutenant] Wide fog pattern.
Straight stream.
Increase the water
pressure, maximum pressure.
Wide fog.
Straight stream.
(Kawamura groaning)
What are you doing?
Grab that hose.
Cut it.
Kawamura.
- [Kawamura] I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
- That's it.
Practice is over.
- No worries.
| got my swimsuit on.
(people chattering)
Oh, you can use my towel.
It's clean, I promise.
- Oh, no, don't worry.
- Hmm.
- All right then, thanks a lot.
- You can keep it if you want.
My family gives them out every
year as new year's gifts.
So, I've got tons.
| could use some directions, though.
I'm a bit lost.
- [Kawamura] Where are you headed?
- I'm trying to find my
way back to my apartment.
- [Kawamura] Okay.
- I'm still new around here.
- Well, do you know the address?
- Hmm, all I remember is
Sunrise Katamiya is the
name of the building.
- Oh, the one next to
the construction site?
-That's the one.
How did you even know that?
Super impressive.
- [Deputy Lieutenant] Kawamura,
you wanna be a firefighter
or a tour guide?
- Sorry, I'd show you personally,
but I'm kinda on duty right now.
- Oh, that's okay.
You can just point me
in the right direction.
- [Kawamura] Sure.
You wanna head straight that way.
Take a right at the white apartment,
and then a second left after that.
And when you see the school,
you're gonna wanna
take the next right.
- Right, left, school, then right.
- [Deputy Lieutenant] That hose
isn't gonna put itself away.
- Coming.
- [Hinako] Laters.
- [Kawamura] See ya.
Hope you don't get lost, hero lady.
(Hinako humming)
Right.
And left.
School!
(car horn blaring)
Huh?
Did I miss a turn?
Wait, no, no.
How do I?
(Hinako whimpering)
(Hinako groaning)
(Hinako sighing)
- [Man] Let 'er rip, whooo.
(fireworks popping)
(people cheering)
(fire roaring)
(Hinako snoring)
- [Man] Fire, that building's
gonna go up in flames!
- [Man] Our balcony's on fire!
- Fire!
- Call 911.
- [Man] Get outside.
Evacuate the building.
(Hinako gasps)
(alarm beeping)
- [Fire Center Operator]
Fire reported at 43rd street
in Katamiya.
Spreading to neighboring building.
(Kawamura gasps)
(dramatic music)
- [Minato] Protective gear, check.
Boots, check.
- [Kawamura] It's the
apartment complex
where your hero lives.
- What?
- [Kawamura] Boots, check.
Bunker pants, check.
- Collar, check.
- Coat, check.
Collar, check.
- Safety belt, check.
Good to go.
- Oh?
- [Firefighter] Come on, move it, men.
(horn beeps)
(siren wailing)
- Someone was setting off
a bunch of industrial
strength fireworks.
(fireworks popping)
(alarm blaring)
- Oh no, my phone.
- [Automated Voice] Fire
detected, fire detected.
Fire detected, fire detected.
- Ah, my wallet.
- [Deputy Lieutenant] Turn it on!
(water hissing)
Hot spot on sixth floor staircase.
Connect supply pipes from
the fifth floor hydrant.
Hoses two and three, get up there.
- Yes, sir.
- [Both] One, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two, one, two.
- [Hinako] Ah, wait.
(Hinako panting)
(Hinako gasps)
- [Kawamura] Ready!
(water hissing)
-We're going to be
conducting a roll call
by apartment number.
- (crying) I left teddy upstairs.
-The fire is contained
and residents have evacuated
to the ground floor.
One woman from the eighth
floor is unaccounted for.
Hoses two and three, locate
the eighth floor resident next.
- [Kawamura] Roger.
(fireworks popping)
(Hinako yelps)
(Hinako panting)
- [Hinako] Someone help!
(fireworks rumbling)
- [Lieutenant] Someone's on the roof.
Get up there.
(Kawamura panting)
- [Kawamura] Are you hurt?
(cherry picker whirring)
(dreamy bells tinkling)
(fireworks rumbling)
(Hinako gasps)
(fireworks popping)
- Are you all right?
- Huh?
I, uh...
- You injured?
- No, I'm fine.
- Remain calm.
We'll get you down safely.
- Can I take my board with me, too?
- Of course.
Sorry, it's cramped.
It's best if you squat.
| have a resident on board.
Please take us down.
(cherry picker whirring)
(crowd murmuring)
- Okubo.
- Yes, sir.
- Nice job guys.
-Thank you, sir.
- Trespassing and the
use of illegal fireworks?
- Back it up, let's go.
-You're safe now.
-Thanks so much for rescuing me.
- No, I should thank you.
- Huh?
-You know the rules.
No personal items aboard
the cherry picker.
- [Minato] Sorry, sir.
- That's my fault.
- It must mean a lot, your board.
- I've been using it since
| was a kid, so, guess so.
- I hope to see you again,
riding the waves, I mean.
| can see you out there
from our rooftop,
the station's roof--
- Hinageshi, time to go!
(Minato chuckles)
- [Minato] See you round.
- Wait.
How about next time,
if you'd like, I mean,
| could teach you how to ride
the waves, that is.
Unless you already know how?
(firefighters cheering)
- [Firefighter] Eye on the prize,
eye on the prize.
(Kawamura grunting)
- [Firefighter] Come on,
one more try, you got it.
- [Firefighter] Pull yourself up.
You can still do this.
- [Firefighter] Better
not be giving up, newbie.
- I believe in you.
- You can still do it.
You've come this far.
- Don't be a quitter.
(Kawamura panting)
- [Minato] (sighs) What a day.
- I'm not sure if
I'm cut out for this.
- [Minato] Don't worry about it.
When you're down, just get back up.
- You say that like it's so easy.
| think maybe I've chosen
the wrong career path.
- Driver engineer Koba's map.
Have you ever seen it?
He just transferred
yet already knows all the
water systems and shortcuts.
Getting that good is no easy task.
You've gotta have the
resolve to keep on pushing
if you wanna reach that level.
You're a strong guy.
If I can do it, I know you can.
Later.
- Hang on.
You're in a good mood.
- 'Bout to ride some waves.
(bright music)
Was this too early for you?
- Huh, no.
I'm not sleepy at all. (gasps)
That was weird.
- You can nap until we get there.
Don't blame ya.
Moving can be tiring.
- [Hinako] Well, it was
just the eighth floor
to the second this time,
so it wasn't that bad.
I'm pretty much done.
- [Minato] Those balconies
are made of really flammable material.
The flames from the bottom
ate their way right up to the top.
So, be extra careful
when you're out there.
- [Hinako] For sure.
But seriously, what a pain.
All 'cause people just had
to set off illegal fireworks.
Meanwhile, you have to risk your life
'cause people decide to be morons.
- [Minato] Yeah, |
really wish they'd stop.
| hear they do it
so they can make videos
and share it online.
- My family used to live in this area
when I was a little kid.
But then we had to move
after my dad got a promotion.
| always wanted to come back, though.
So, I applied to the college here.
What about, you, mister...
- [Minato] What?
- Ah, I'm so sorry.
| realized I don't know
how to say your last name.
- It's Hinageshi.
- [Hinako] Huh?
So that's how you say it,
Minato Hinageshi, like that?
- People never know how to
say it, but I don't mind.
- [Hinako] I get it.
My last name is Mukaimizu.
People are always calling
me Mukomizu, though.
- Oh, hey, if a fire breaks out,
get to the ground floor
as quickly as possible.
- [Hinako] Is that a finless porpoise?
- It is.
It's not a beluga.
- Knew it, I thought
you might like them.
You know, your car even
kind of looks like one.
| really love them, too.
Don't they look like that
show "Little Ghost Q-Taro?"
- Wanna listen to something?
What music do you like?
- I'll listen to whatever you want.
- Mm, let's see
> Oh oh oh )
- Ah, this song.
Takes me back.
- Since they used it in that movie,
they've been playing it a lot.
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
> Day grows long, colors
around us change )
> But you're still
sparkling evermore )
(singing in foreign language)
- [Hinako] I see you've
bought yourself a board.
- Well, I'll need a lot of
practice if I wanna get good.
Besides, it's always
been a dream of mine
to have a surfboard attached
to the top of my car.
- Oh, a full wetsuit in
the middle of summer.
That's so cool.
You'll pick this up in no time.
(bright music)
Keep your head up.
Paddle, paddle, paddle.
Paddle, paddle, paddle, paddle.
Now, pop up.
(Minato groans)
Paddle, paddle, paddle.
Now, pop up, hurry.
(Minato groans)
(Minato panting)
Paddle, paddle, paddle.
Good, now stand up.
Keep your balance.
(Minato panting)
Are you sure you okay?
- I'll try again this afternoon.
(Minato coughs)
I'll make us some coffee.
- With that thing?
(Hinako sniffing)
Hmm, that smells good.
- [Minato] I brought a blend
| thought would go well
with the sandwiches.
(Hinako gasps)
Freshly ground beans really
make the coffee bloom.
- [Hinako] Why's that?
- [Minato] Well, when you
use freshly ground beans
with a dripper, it
releases carbon dioxide.
- Sounds complicated.
- [Minato] Time for the egg sandwiches
- [Hinako] Is there anything you can't do?
Are you a superhero in disguise?
(sighs) They're so perfect.
(bird cawing)
| thought this when you
rescued me from the fire,
but you're basically a
hero, Hinageshi, aren't you?
-That's an overstatement.
And you know, just call me Minato.
Is it okay if I call you Hinako?
(car horn blaring)
(Hinako gasps)
WATCH OUT FOR KITES!!
- [Hinako] He stole my sandwich.
Paddle, paddle.
(bright music)
- [Minato] Whoa.
- [Hinako] That's it, now stand.
(Minato grunting)
- [Hinako] Yes, yes, like that.
You got it.
WATER DRIP - PAPER DRIP
NEL DRIP - FRENCH DRIP
(coffee machine hissing)
- I'm sorry.
| was no good even though
you took me all the way out
to the beginner's spot.
- Even if you fall,
you just have to get back
up to ride the next wave.
And if we hadn't have
come all the way out here,
we wouldn't have come to
this lovely little cafe.
- It's great, huh?
I've been meaning to
check it out for a while.
Mm, good to see they've
got a few extinguishers.
(Minato gasps)
(Hinako giggling)
- You know, I've got
this funny feeling that
if something were to
happen, you'd be there for me.
- Mm-hmm, I'll always
be there, definitely.
(car horn blaring)
- Well, we'd better get going, huh?
- Uh, yeah.
Hey, you don't have to do that.
| got it.
- It's fine.
- [Minato] No, wait.
(Hinako yelping)
(objects clattering)
-I am so sorry.
- Don't worry, it's quite all right.
It happens all the time.
- Tokyo?
- I'm from Chiba.
- Oh, really?
- [Grandpa Owner] One
of our former employees
just opened a cafe there.
You should visit it sometime.
- [Grandma Owner] He has
slightly more modern equipment
than we do here.
- It's not a bad life.
| wouldn't mind running
a cafe like this one.
- Sorry for getting so
flustered back there.
- Hey, know what?
I'd like to do this
again with you sometime.
Surfing, if you can call
what I'm doing that.
And even grab another coffee.
I'd also like to check
out other surf spots.
- Wait a second.
You...
Thank you.
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
> Day grows long, colors
around us change )
- What, who's that?
> But you're still
sparkling evermore )
> Sometimes life will
come with its own plan )
> With a quest that
puts you to the test )
> And when you're stuck and
feel like you're frozen )
> Just hold on, you can push
past the pain, and if you do )
» That's right, open up your
eyes and see everything new )
D It's time to start
your brand new story )
> With every little step,
you'll go forward again.
> The path will appear
and your journey clear )
D> To where we both promised we'd be )
2 In all our glory )
(gentle guitar music)
> Now and then, your tears
may drown out your smiles D
> And the undertow of
sadness will pull you down )
> Don't forget that
everything ebbs and flows )
> Like rain, your tears
will one day dry )
> Rest assured no wave
has a true twin )
(Hinako giggling)
> Every one with
its own unique motion )
> So let's just be
and live in the moment )
- [Minato] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
> Take my hand, we'll
be brave here and now )0
D Let's face our fears )
D> That's right )
D Life is even brighter
than what you had dreamed )
> A dazzling, vivid, brand new story )
- [Woman] Why's a cute guy
like you working as a florist?
- [Woman] I know, right?
- I don't work here.
- Are you from around here?
- [Woman] You know,
we're on our way to go
watch the fireworks.
- [Woman] You should join us.
How 'bout it? (giggling)
- I'm so sorry.
I've already got plans.
D All those days we spent alone )
> How could I not
hold on to each moment )
> So don't you fret, my darling.
> They'll shine on
deep in our hearts )
> Always D
> And so, you hold your head up high )
> And look straight out ahead )
> And gather that courage inside you )
D> That's right )
> Open up your eyes and
see everything new )
D It's time to start
your brand new story )
> With every little step,
you'll go forward again.
> The path will appear
and your journey clear )
D> To where we both promised we'd be )
2 In all our glory )
D One, two, my brand new story )
(Hinako laughing)
- [Minato] First you do this.
Then have it like this.
-You're right, it's
sweet but not too sweet.
- [Yoko] You two are
sugary enough as it is.
- Sorry, my sister can be a bit rude.
- [Yoko] Well, I am not sorry, okay?
- She speaks her mind.
- We'll get along just fine.
- Huh?
- [Hinako] My two best
friends are both pretty blunt
and speak their minds.
Jun, the scorpion and Ai, the cobra.
- [Yoko] You actually call them that?
-Then you're the blue-ringed octopus.
- I'm a what?
- It may be small,
but it is one of the most
deadly marine animals
in existence.
- Well, aren't you
a walking encyclopedia?
- I'm leaving.
| only came here
'cause I wanted see what
your girlfriend was like.
And I've seen
everything I need to see.
- [Minato] What's that
supposed to mean?
- Falling in love is
something only idiots do.
This blue-ringed octopus
is so full of venom,
she needs to go home, bye.
- [Hinako] See you later, bye.
- Later?
- Yeah 'cause I'm immune
to octopus venom, see?
- [Yoko] Ugh. (groans)
- Thanks for being so chill just now.
That winning attitude of hers
hasn't exactly
garnered her many friends.
She had been avoiding
school because of that.
But she suddenly started
going again recently.
- Well, that's good.
- She's a handful, but maybe
you guys could be friends.
- Of course.
(gentle music)
(Hinako gasps)
(Hinako giggling)
Look at that.
It's Mount Fuji.
(camera shutter clicking)
It's so pretty.
- [Announcer] This message
goes out to Mai Uchida
from Shota Namikoshi.
Merry Christmas, let's
stay together forever.
Will you marry me?
- So sweet.
- How romantic, I love it.
- [Minato] You think so?
You know, they're
just reading messages
from people who
submitted them in advance.
- [Announcer] I think it's
about time we got married.
I'm waiting for your proposal.
- So, you wanna go up?
- [Announcer] Merry Christmas.
This message goes out
to Yoshiko Kamiichi.
Thank you for everything, Mom.
Merry Christmas.
- [Hinako] What a view.
| wonder if we can see
my house from here.
(people chattering)
Wow.
- [Minato] Wanna do one too?
- Huh?
It's okay, I wouldn't
know what to write.
- Is it because you still don't
know how to write my name?
-That's not true.
- Great.
HINAKO MUKAIMIZU
And?
MINATO HINAGESHI
- Your last name is
just too hard to write.
- What are you gonna do when
it becomes your last name?
- Huh?
What did you say?
(Minato whistling)
Hey.
-The photo line is real long.
- [Photographer] That's it.
Looking good, you two.
What a cute couple.
Perfect, okay, let's take one more.
Hold right there, got it.
- [Minato] Hinako, come over here.
| want you to see something.
- Another cute couple.
Get a little closer, great.
(camera shutter clicking)
Hold her with those big strong arms.
- [Hinako] The key to your heart.
- [Photographer] Smile, one
more big smile for the camera.
- [Minato] Here.
(lock clicks)
- [Hinako] It's snowing.
(Hinako sighing)
- Wish I didn't have
to go to work tomorrow.
Working on Christmas...
You know, after it snows,
you can get these
really great big waves.
They say if you catch one,
whatever you wish for will come true.
I've never done it though.
- So good.
How do you get it to
not slip off each time?
- Okay, the outside needs to be cooked
while the inside's runny.
Getting it to stay is all
about keeping it soft.
See, like that.
You wanna give it a go?
- Mm-hmm.
Ah.
- Don't worry.
You can still save it.
Just calmly lift it, oh.
(chuckle) You sure having
omurice in the middle of nowhere
is how you want to spend Christmas?
-Yep, it's what I'd always
have on special occasions
when I was a kid, thanks.
And I wanted it to be
just two of us tonight.
- Can you eat with
your left hand, though?
- I got this.
I've been practicing.
I wanted to make sure I could eat
without letting go of your hand.
If it were up to me, I'd
never let go of your hand.
- I'm gonna get my own place soon.
Do you wanna move in?
- Don't joke like that.
What if I really said yes?
- Great, when?
- Huh?
| don't know if
I'm ready for that yet.
(gentle piano music)
Not until I can ride my own wave.
| feel like I rely on you
all the time for everything.
But I hope I can find my
footing on dry land too,
and finally find something
I'm good at, like you have.
-You've already got
something you're good at,
so I'm sure you'll
find your path soon.
I've never been particularly
good at anything.
- You're joking, right?
-When I was a kid, |
almost drowned in the ocean.
I can still remember every
detail about that day.
| promised myself
| would become strong,
but instead I failed at
everything I tried to do.
And then, suddenly one day, |
came across a newborn turtle.
- [Hinako] A baby sea turtle?
- [Minato] Yeah, they're
all over the beach.
SEA TURTLES LAY THEIR EGGS HERE.
You've never seen one?
-Whoa, what's that?
Turtles?
Watching them struggle
towards the ocean
with such persistence,
it made me realize how much
determination I needed.
So, I started joining my
grandpa on his beach patrols.
That's when I got a sense
of what I wanted to do with my life.
And it dawned on me that
| wanted some kind of job
where I could help people.
- I love that story.
| have a hard enough time
taking care of myself,
let alone helping others.
I'm always the one needing help.
You seem to be able to just do
anything with ease, though.
-That simply isn't true.
| still can't surf like you can.
Try thinking of the sea and
the shore as no different.
You paddle, and when you get tired,
catch your breath and paddle again.
You can think of me as
your harbor, if you want.
When you need a break, just
call for me and I'll be there.
- How long will you be
there for me, I wonder.
- 10 years, 20?
When every hair has turned gray.
Until you're able to
ride those waves alone.
(jet ski riders cheering)
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
(phone ringing)
Hmm?
What?
GONE SURFING
No way.
- [Jet Ski Rider] Whoohoo!
Oh yeah!
- Coming through!
- All right!
- Yeah!
(dramatic music)
- Hey, where did he go?
- Call 911.
- Somebody help!
- I'll swim
and see if I can find him.
- Ah.
(Hinako groans)
Aw, Minato, who said you
could go surfing without me?
Huh?
(siren wailing)
- Hinako?
(panting) Hinako!
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR SAVING TEDDY,
YUKI YOSHIKAWA
(Kawamura chuckles)
- Uh, hello?
- Huh?
(phone ringing)
- [Voicemail] The number
you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
(voicemail beeps)
- [Mom] Hinako, are you there?
How are you doing?
Please give me a call when
you're feeling up to it, okay?
I'd love to speak to you.
(doorbell ringing)
- [Voicemail] Message recorded
on January 16th at 2:42 p.m.
(doorbell ringing)
(knocking on door)
- [Yoko] Hello?
We know you're in there.
Please, open the door.
- Sorry for stopping by
without giving you a heads up.
The new place is nice,
further inland, I see.
- [Hinako] I figured I wouldn't
have to look at the sea
from out here.
(Kawamura gasps)
- Here, this is some
of my brother's stuff
from the firehouse.
(Hinako gasps)
If you want anything, just take it.
- I'm sorry.
It was insensitive to not call first.
It must very be painful for you.
- Are you seriously
doing this right now?
- [Kawamura] I never
thought I'd be (sniffing)
Sent out on a search and rescue
mission for Minato. (crying)
It's just like him, though.
He sacrificed his own life in
order to save someone else's.
- You're wrong.
It's my fault.
| told him the best waves occur
the morning after it snows.
- Cut it out.
Saying that isn't going to
bring my brother back, you know?
- Sorry.
I'm just (crying) so sorry.
- [Yoko] This is his cell phone.
It's yours if you want it.
Throw it out for all I care.
- Yoko, please don't--
- [Yoko] What?
It'd be better if she did.
- My card, it's got my number.
If you need anything, anything
at all, I'll be there.
Yoko, wait.
- Is that a finless porpoise?
- [Minato] This app
tracks surfing conditions.
- [Hinako] I didn't know that existed.
- |I can download it to
your phone if you want.
(phone line trilling)
(Minato's phone buzzing)
- [Voicemail] The number
you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
(Hinako groaning)
- Even if I left a message,
it's not like you would get it.
You said you'd be by my side forever.
Minato?
(bubbles popping)
Oh.
(Hinako whimpers)
- [Jun] Come on, you've
gotta eat something.
- [Ai] Here, coffee would
do you good, too.
(Hinako whimpering)
There, there.
(Hinako sobbing)
- I know, everything
reminds you of him.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- It's normal.
- [Hinako] You guys are
being so nice to me.
And you were the ones who always said
we were such sappy lovey-dovey idiots
that we'd make all other
couples heads explode.
- Sorry.
- We take it all back.
Is that your boyfriend's?
- [Hinako] Yeah, but |
can't see what's on it
'cause it's locked.
We always went surfing together.
So why'd he go out on his own,
and while it was still dark?
I need to know.
- So, that's a blue-ringed octopus?
- [Hinako] Hey, Yoko,
when's your birthday?
- [Yoko] February 3rd.
Which, by the way, my
brother never remembered.
- When is World Marine Day?
- July 15th.
- Disaster Prevention Day?
- September 1st.
- [Hinako] It's no one
I know's birthday,
the day of the fire, nor our
first date surfing. (sighing)
It's none of the days I can think of.
- You should ask Wasabi.
- Huh?
-You met him.
He brought you the box, Miss Mikomizu.
- Kawamura?
Oh, and it's Mukaimizu.
- I'll ask him to coffee.
He should be off today.
This is the same as the other place.
Their main store is in Chigasaki.
- It's not a bad life.
| wouldn't mind running
a cafe like this one.
There are lots of different
ways to brew coffee.
-That's pretty cool.
| want a strawberry soda.
(Hinako gasps)
Sorry for the, ah!
- What the heck, man?
- Are you okay?
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't touch it.
I'll go get some towels.
- Ah, I am so sorry.
(Hinako whimpers)
- Don't you dare.
It'll make the coffee taste bad.
- Sorry.
I'm not a crybaby, at
least I didn't used to be.
- Oh come on, I've seen
newborns cry less than you.
- Yoko, please.
- I apologize for being so blunt.
- Hey, don't worry about it, okay?
| mean, you've got to be
true who you are, right?
(singing in foreign language)
(Hinako gasps)
Oh, I know this song
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
> Day grows long, colors around us )
Minato?
- Are you okay?
- [Hinako] I just saw Minato.
- Have you lost it?
Come on, get it together.
- Minato.
- Okay, listen up.
My brother is dead and
he is not coming back.
And you just need to accept that.
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
> Day grows long, colors
around us change )
> But you're still
sparkling evermore )
> Sometimes life will
come with its own plan )
> With a quest that puts you to the )
But why?
Why's he in the water?
Is it 'cause of that song?
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
(Hinako gasps)
(Hinako whimpers)
Hey, guys.
- What's up?
- Do I seem weird to you?
- [Ai] Weird looking?
Or weird in the head?
- Like having hallucinations,
that kind of weird.
-You're not taking
weird drugs are you?
- [Ail That would be really bad.
You're weird enough as it is.
- I'm not taking drugs.
But I can see Minato
wherever there's water.
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
> I can see your )
- Hey, wait.
- Minato.
(gentle music)
Look, see?
He's right there doing the Shaka sign.
- [Ai] Maybe you are
weirder than normal.
- [Jun] Why don't you go
back home for a while?
You need to take it
easy, okay, Hinako?
(Hinako humming)
(gentle music)
(Hinako gasps)
(Hinako humming)
HINAKO
(Hinako gasps)
Look, up there, right there.
It was definitely
Minato, I'm sure of it.
Is he a ghost?
Does that mean he's stuck in limbo?
Or is it 'cause he died at sea?
Is that why he's
appearing to me in water?
(Hinako gasps)
Am I really trying to take a
picture of a ghost right now?
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
(bubbles popping)
> Day grows long, colors, oh )
(Hinako gasps)
(gentle music)
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
D I can see your )
> Smiling face reflect back at me )
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
(gentle music)
(Hinako gasps)
Minato.
But why are you?
- I promised to always be there
if you needed my help, didn't I?
- Minato.
- [Minato] Hinako.
-This is a bit weird.
- It sure is.
- So, does this mean
you couldn't pass on?
- Uh, maybe.
- [Hinako] Did you have
any unfinished business?
- Or maybe my wish came true.
Did you move again?
- [Hinako] What?
Uh, yeah.
- [Minato] Are you not surfing?
- It's too sad.
| can't.
- Sorry.
It's my fault, isn't it?
- Ah, I didn't mean to--
Tell you what, let's not be sad, okay?
Talking to you is
like a dream come true
and I don't want to ruin it.
So you appear in water whenever
| sing that song, right?
- I don't quite know how it works.
But if you need my
help, just call, okay?
- Oh, Yoko's doing well.
Wasabi, too.
- [Minato] Yeah, I saw
them for a second.
- Oh, that's right.
It didn't seem like either of
them could see you, though.
Does that mean I'm the
only one who can then?
- Maybe, but I don't really mind,
as long as I can be seen by you.
- [Hinako] I guess.
(gasp) Oh yeah.
Could you tell me your passcode?
- [Minato] Why do you
wanna get into my phone?
- It's because I wanna know
why you went surfing
all by yourself, okay?
- You see, I wanted
to practice in secret
and surprise you
with how good I'd gotten.
- [Hinako] Really?
- It's the truth.
Funny, I don't seem to recall
giving my girlfriend permission
to try to break into my phone, though.
(Hinako groans)
- Huh?
You know what?
| should probably go take a bath.
Don't go anywhere, okay?
What am I doing?
Are Minato and I living together?
Does that mean we'll get married?
Hinako Hinageshi? (giggling)
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
> I can see your smiling
face reflect back
(bubbles popping)
(gentle music)
(Hinako yelps)
You pervert!
- Oh, sorry, but you started singing.
- You're right.
You just scared me.
It's not like I mind.
(firefighters chattering)
-Whoa.
(Hinako gasping)
You okay?
Sorry, I didn't see you.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Where do you come from?
- Oh, well, I'm from Chiba.
- [Man] We're in Chiba.
So who's the big guy?
- [Hinako] Something wrong?
- [Minato] Well, I was just thinking
about how I can't hold
your hand, anymore.
And how I can't help you like
that guy did earlier, either.
- Huh?
Could you be a little jealous?
- You got it wrong.
- I'm not gonna cheat, okay?
I only have eyes for you.
-That's not what I meant at all.
- I think this might
be our first fight.
Please don't be mad.
(Hinako giggles)
- Another, please.
- Ooh, someone's greedy.
Mwah!
Forgive me now?
- Not quite yet.
- What?
- 'Cause I need one
more thing from you.
- 'Kay, what is it?
- Take me to the ocean.
| wanna see you surf again.
That's what I'd like.
(waves whooshing)
- Sorry.
- No, I'm sorry.
| should've realized that
you probably weren't ready.
-You know, I used to live
in this area when I was kid.
All I did was surf.
I could ride the waves
whenever I liked.
But now (sighs) whether it's
in the water or on land,
| just don't know which
direction I should be paddling.
- [Minato] No matter
how small the wave,
it contains the power built up
from traveling thousands of miles.
Right now, you're being
pushed back by that power.
I'm just one of those many waves,
and you have to prepare
yourself for the next one.
- Why do you have to say
depressing stuff like that?
As long as I can be with
you, Minato, I'll be fine.
That's all I want.
- [Minato] I'll be
here for you, Hinako.
I'll support you in any way I can
until one day you can
ride those waves of life.
(gentle music)
- Hi, come on in.
(door bells tinkling)
Oh, hey, what's up?
- Your mom was the one who told me
that you started working here.
| wanted to talk
to you about something.
- Boss, so, I'm going on my break now.
Here, on the house.
What did you wanna talk about?
Stop worrying.
You just have to be true
to yourself, remember?
- [Kawamura] Actually--
- It's what my brother used
to say, so just suck it up.
- [Kawamura] Believe
it or not, I'm not here
to talk about how I screwed
up at work for once.
-You're not?
- [Kawamura] It's about Hinako.
- Oh, you don't say.
- She's acting strange.
- Course she is.
- I mean, I've seen her
talking to her water bottle.
And skipping hand in hand
with Minato's old blow-up porpoise.
It's like she thinks that the
water is Minato or something.
- [Yoko] Are you stalking her?
- Well, I was worried.
- Why?
- I'm not quite sure.
Minato used to always watch her surf
from the roof of the fire station,
so I started watching too, and well,
but she was Minato's
girlfriend, so I never,
ah, I didn't mean to bring that up.
I'm just worried
about Hinako, that's all.
So, I can't help thinking about it.
-You're so dumb.
- Huh?
- If you're really that
worried about Hinako,
then go talk to her.
Don't talk to me.
It's 'cause you're in
love with her, aren't you?
- Uh...
- And for the record,
falling in love is
something idiots do.
Hey, Boss, I'm done with my break now.
(Kawamura sighs)
(Hinako grunting)
- Sorry.
Here, I've been meaning
to return this to you.
Wait, you're that fireman?
- You never realized that was me?
- Oh, I guess not.
| probably won't
need the towel, though.
You here for flowers?
- Uh, right.
(Hinako grunting)
- I really hope that she enjoys these,
whoever the lucky girl is.
- Oh, actually, well,
she likes the sea.
That's why I went with the
white and blue flowers.
Too cheesy?
- No, not at all.
It's so thoughtful.
-Thank goodness.
You don't have it with you today
- Huh?
- [Kawamura] You've been taking
it with you wherever you go.
Your water bottle that is.
(Hinako sighs)
- 'Cause I'm at work.
- [Kawamura] You don't
have that porpoise, either.
- Huh, you saw that?
- I saw you in public with them,
and then again when you
came into the station,
but I didn't say anything.
You were talking to the
bottle, as if it were Minato.
- Ah, no, I was
just talking to myself.
- But--
- Here.
Hurry up and take them.
If you don't, they will wilt.
- But they're for you, Hinako.
- Huh?
It was for someone who liked the sea.
- For a long time I've
been watching you now.
Could I ever replace him?
Do you think one day, I might
be able to make you happy?
Because I just wanna
see you happy again.
'Cause I love you.
- Uh, I can't.
I'm sorry.
(gentle music)
(Kawamura sighs)
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
- What is it, Hinako?
- Just now, Wasabi, he--
- Are you okay?
What happened?
- He tried to tell me he loves me.
- And how do you feel?
- How do I feel?
I'm in love with you, Minato.
- But the reality is,
| can't hold your hand.
I can't hold you or kiss you.
Plus, he's a good guy.
- [Hinako] Minato.
- [Minato] He's an honest
person and has a gentle soul.
- Why do you have to
say stuff like that?
I'm fine with the way things are.
| can see you whenever I want,
even if we can't hold
hands or hug anymore.
You said you'd be there
for me, didn't you?
That's all that I want.
- [Minato] Shh, calm down.
People will hear you, and
you're talking to a toilet.
- [Hinako] Huh?
(Hinako's coworker gasps)
Sorry, I got worked up.
- Hinako, listen.
New waves will always keep coming in.
Not all of them will be good ones,
you'll wanna let those pass.
But if you keep staying
with your head underwater,
you'll never learn to ride any waves.
(Hinako panting)
(dramatic music)
(tires screeching)
(vehicles rumbling)
(Kawamura gasps)
(Kawamura panting)
- [Kawamura] Hinako!
(explosion rumbling)
(tires screeching)
- [Man] Does someone
have a fire extinguisher?
There's been accident.
-The one driver is still inside.
- No, there's nothing
we can do about them.
-They're trapped in the car.
- It's too dangerous.
-We can't let them die.
Minato wouldn't.
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
- Please, Hinako.
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
- [Kawamura] Hinako!
> Day grows long, colors
around us change )
> But you're still »
Minato!
- What's wrong?
- It's Minato.
| can't hear him anymore.
- Calm down.
- Minato!
- It's gonna be okay.
- Minato's disappearing.
- Please, Hinako.
- He's turning into
steam and disappearing.
- [Kawamura] Hinako, you need
to get a hold of yourself.
I don't wanna be harsh,
but Minato is gone.
He's not a ghost.
- You might not be able to
see him, Wasabi, but I can.
And I'm telling you that
Minato is in the water.
He appears whenever I sing to him.
| swear to you, it's really him.
You say he's not there,
but you wouldn't know.
Minato is going to be by
my side forever. (crying)
- I'm sure he loved you enough
that he would have done
everything in his power
to try and appear to you
somehow, but I'm also sure
that he would have never, ever
wanted to see you like this
right now, Hinako.
Minato used to say, "Hinako
inspires me and is my hero."
We all thought it was so cool
how you could ride those waves.
But now...
- I know but,
and I want to, it's just...
(Hinako crying)
- Minato will never
be able to be at peace
if you do not move on.
Hinako!
- Is everyone okay?
- (panting) Minato.
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
- Hinako.
- I'm so sorry, Minato.
This wouldn't have happened
if it weren't for me.
It's 'cause I've been
relying on you too much.
What do I do?
How am I supposed to go
on without you in my life?
I'm so sorry.
D There you )
(door bells tinkling)
- Feel free to sit wherever.
Our specialty is being
able to provide customers
with the best coffee
in a variety of ways.
| recommend our drip coffee.
Whatever you do, please don't
order the strawberry soda.
- Wow, you're really good at that.
- Are you mocking me?
- Course not.
| came because I heard
that you were working here.
- Wasabi?
- Yeah.
- What else did he tell you?
- Huh?
Nothing, really.
- I really wish I was
a blue-ringed octopus
because then I could bite you.
- What?
- Never mind.
- [Hinako] Why are you
working here anyway, Yoko?
- [Yoko] I've decided
| want to open a cafe.
- [Hinako] Huh?
- [Yoko] My brother's dream
was to one day open a cafe,
so, I'm gonna make it come true.
(Hinako gasps)
| took this job so I could
learn more about the business.
Like this, a coffee bloom has to do
with the release of carbon dioxide.
Gas gets released
slowly from the beans
after they're roasted.
Once the beans are ground, though,
it speeds up the release of CO2.
So the fact that it blooms
means that the beans are fresh.
When I finish high school,
I'll go get trained at the
main branch in Chigasaki.
| mean, the couple
that owns this place
will eventually retire, right?
(firefighters cheering)
- [Firefighter] That's it,
you can do it.
- [Firefighter] You got it,
you got it.
- Nice job!
- All right, Kawamura!
- A little late, don't you think?
- Sorry.
| was having a hard time accepting it,
so it's taken me a while
to come pay my respects.
Where are your parents?
- At work.
They've only just managed
to start working again,
so it's not really the best time to...
- Sorry, to have caused
so much trouble.
- My brother's room is how he left it.
Wanna see it?
- [Hinako] Sure.
- My brother always
seemed cool and collected,
so people assumed
everything came easy to him.
But the truth is he worked
hard at everything he did.
Both our parents worked, so he
would have to make us dinner.
It was awful in the beginning.
But he'd read cookbooks
and watch cooking shows,
and he was suddenly a gourmet chef.
Same with studying.
Even after he became a fireman,
he said he had to keep working hard
to make sure to keep
his head above water.
| could never live up to that.
And then, after he died,
so many people came to the
house to pay their respects.
They all said he'd
helped them somehow.
Minato always did whatever
he could to help others.
It was his life's mission.
Started when he was just a kid.
He almost drowned when
he was a little boy,
but someone saved him.
The one who saved
him was a little girl
who was even younger than my brother.
It made him realize that he
could accomplish anything
as long as he worked hard.
His entire life was changed
by that little girl,
So he wanted to become someone
who could do the same for others.
He said that a hero saved his life.
He wanted to make sure
he made good use of it
and save others.
(dramatic music)
(Hinako gasps)
What now?
Man. (sighs)
MUKAIMIZU LANDSCAPING
- So tell me, why the
sudden surprise visit?
- Remember when I saved
a boy from drowning
when I was a kid?
- Didn't they give you an award?
Hmm, I think it's here.
(lid pops)
Oh.
Here it is.
That kid called you his hero.
(singing in foreign language)
(Minato gasping)
(Minato coughing)
(gentle music)
(Hinako gasps)
(Hinako panting)
(bubbles popping)
(Hinako gasps)
(Hinako grunting)
- Way to go.
- Great job, kid.
- Be on the lookout.
Bring the ambulance
here when it arrives.
- Oh.
(Minato coughing)
- Yes, they did it!
- He's gonna be okay.
(singing in foreign language)
(crowd chattering)
-Turn him over.
- Kid, cough up the water.
What a brave little girl.
(Minato coughing)
- You saved his life.
- That's my girl.
(all cheering)
(Hinako laughing)
- [Lifeguard] You did good, kiddo.
- See that little girl over there?
She's the one who saved you.
- [Yoko] He said that
a hero saved his life.
- [Minato] When I was a kid,
| almost drowned in the ocean.
I can still remember every
detail about that day.
And it dawned on me that
| wanted some kind of job
where I could to help people.
Since they used it in that movie,
they've been playing it a lot.
D> That's right )
(singing in foreign language)
- Hinako.
What about the strawberries?
- [Minato] The day that I was reborn
8 AUGUST 2006
was the day I found my reason for living.
(Hinako gasps)
- [Minato] Hinako, I got
to ride the waves
after yesterday's snow and
pulled off an air reverse.
You said my wish would come true
if I could ride those waves, right?
My wish is for you to able
to conquer life's waves.
Well, that and for me to be
able to be by your side forever.
(Hinako whimpers)
(waves whooshing)
Watching them struggle
towards the ocean
with such persistence,
it made me realize how much
determination I needed.
JOBS HELPING OTHERS
TOP 10 JOBS HELPING OTHERS
1. LAWYER, 2. TEACHER, 3. CARE WORKER,
4. POLICE OFFICER, 5. SDF, 6. FIREMAN
(Hinako grunts)
(bright music)
- You interested in saving lives?
We get everything
from surfers to those
can't even doggie paddle
but just wanna help.
Of course we're gonna train you
in how to rescue people at sea,
but our main goal
is to prevent accidents
before they even happen.
You'll have to pass
a qualification test,
but there's plenty of free
time if you like sports.
We've got six males and four females.
Training camp and lifeguard duty
both take place during the summer.
We also run several community events.
(Kawamura panting)
- [Yoko] Yoohoo!
- Huh?
- [Yoko] You run even
on your days off?
- [Kawamura] Well, I need to know
where all the hydrants are,
and they sometimes move them.
And that turned into a daily jog.
It's not really in my
job description, though.
- [Yoko] My brother
always used to go around
making sure everything was safe too.
He said the best firefighters
are the ones who prevent fires.
- Minato really was an amazing guy.
No matter how hard |
try, I don't think I--
- [Yoko] You're right.
You could never fill his boots.
- (chuckles) So true.
Could I ever replace him?
Do you think one day, I might
be able to make you happy?
- Why'd you wanna become
a fireman, Wasabi?
- Huh?
Oh, it's 'cause, well, 'cause
firemen are cool, aren't they?
Plus, you get to
drive the fire engine.
- You say that like it
would be such a no brainer.
- Oh, thank you.
-There's sugar if you want it.
- Hmm.
It probably was naive of me
to choose a career path based on that.
You want some?
(Yoko stutters)
I've always been athletic,
but the job is more physically
demanding that I expected.
No matter how hard I try, though,
I'll never be as good as Minato.
I'm not convinced I'm
cut out to be a fireman.
Actually, saving lives is
probably beyond what I could do.
Whoa, that's sweet.
-That's an understatement.
- Ah, sorry, too much sugar.
Well, guess I don't have
Minato's taste buds, either.
- Minato this, Minato that, enough.
No one is asking you to
be just like my brother.
Just focus on being yourself.
That's all you need.
- Ah, that was actually
really well put, Yoko.
-You dummy, you're the one
who said that to me, remember?
When I stopped going
to school, my mom asked
why couldn't I be
more like my brother.
But you were the one who told me
that I should just be myself.
I'm not like my brother,
who always did his best at everything.
| have trouble fitting in with others.
But because of what you had said,
| thought maybe it was
okay for me to be myself.
Your words were what
put my mind at ease.
And so I managed to go back to school.
So, you see, you were
the one that saved me.
- My words actually did that?
Then maybe I can save people.
Thank you, Yoko.
I'll do it.
I'll do my best.
- Gotta go.
Shift's about to start.
When you're done with the coffee,
just bring the stuff back to the cafe.
- [Kawamura] Uh...
- [Yoko] I've been in love with you
ever since you
said those things to me.
| love you more than anyone I know!
So you'd better
do your best, you idiot!
(Kawamura sighs)
-You'll call for help,
alert emergency services,
and don't forget to
bring the AED with you.
First, check if they're
conscious by talking to them
to see if they respond.
Can you hear me?
If there's no response, check
to see if they're breathing.
Next, compressions.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Place one hand on top of the
other, using your body weight.
Adults need at least 30
five-centimeter-deep compressions.
Remember to wait until the chest rises
before compressing, 29, 30.
Tilt their head, pinch their
nose, and support their chin.
Aim for one breath per second, repeat.
Make sure their chest is
expanding when you're doing this.
After that, start the
chest compressions again.
Five, six, seven, 30,
that's the pattern.
Okay, who wants to give it a go?
Miss Mukaimizu?
(Hinako gasps)
(Hinako inhales deeply)
- One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
-You might be
pressing a bit too hard.
You don't have to press hard.
Five centimeters is fine.
Let's try mouth to mouth next.
(Hinako whimpers)
(Hinako gasping)
Miss Mukaimizu?
Miss Mukaimizu.
(Hinako panting)
> There you J)
(Hinako groaning)
| shouldn't!
(people chattering)
- You shoot 'em off the roof
like they do for New Years
in Taiwan and Shanghai.
- Really?
- Are you serious?
-Things got out of hand last time,
so we're bringing a
fireworks expert with us.
You'll wanna have earplugs.
- Sounds like a blast.
- Minoru got nabbed by the
cops, but this guy ran away.
- [Woman] You guys
just left him there?
- [Man In Green Shirt] Well,
lucky I didn't get caught
or you wouldn't have an
explosive show to see tonight.
In fact, I think you
should be thanking me.
- [Woman] You want a
gold star or something?
- [Man] I know the
perfect abandoned tower.
- [Woman] Do you mean the OST?
It's, like, famous.
It's where they had the
world's biggest Christmas tree.
- [Man] That tree's still
there, you know.
- [Woman] It's super tall.
- [Man In Green Shirt] So the plan
is to launch them from there.
- This is gonna be epic.
- [Man In Green Shirt] You
don't know the half of it.
- [Man] I am so fired up.
- [Woman] That was such a dad joke.
- Yeah, that was pretty bad.
- What are we waiting for?
- [Woman] I can't wait.
- [Woman] It's my first
time, you know.
- [Man In Green Shirt]
It's gonna be real loud.
Don't say I didn't warn ya.
You go kinda deaf afterwards.
- [Woman] Wait, I don't
have any earplugs.
- [Man] No worries, babe.
| got extra.
- Hi, Yoko, what's up.
- Shh.
- Can I have pair now?
- [Man] I think she's
trying to shut you out.
- Ah, don't be mean.
- I'm gonna hold you to that.
(group chattering)
(suspenseful music)
(door bells tinkling)
- Boss, I'm clocking out for the day.
- Where are you going?
- [Yoko] Remember when
about a year ago,
some illegal fireworks set
that construction site on fire?
- [Hinako] Yeah, I was actually
living in the apartments
next to that building.
- What, really?
Well, I think those are
the guys who did it.
They were talking about
launching more fireworks.
And they're planning on
sneaking up to OST to do it.
-The place with the
humongous Christmas tree?
- Damn it, can't reach Wasabi.
They're going to break in
to launch the fireworks
and they're illegal ones too.
- Yoko, this is serious.
We should call the police.
(group chattering)
Listen, I'm gonna go
call the cops, okay?
- We need proof first.
I'm gonna get a photo of these jerks.
(dramatic music)
- Yoko.
Hey, Yoko.
Where'd you go?
Whoa, it's huge.
Looks pretty dead, though.
Yoko, wait.
- [Yoko] Shh!
That was a pool.
- Oh, check it out.
- This is so sick.
- [Man In Green Shirt] I told
you guys it was gonna be awesome.
You can see the whole
town from up here.
- Amazing.
- Look at all the lights.
- [Woman] (giggling) Wow.
We're so high up.
- Nice view.
(woman gasps)
- Oh.
- [Woman] That was so mean.
- We can set the fireworks
off from right here.
- You ready?
- Hold on.
What you think you're doing?
(women yelping)
-That wasn't funny.
- What the hell, you idiot?
- All right, grab one and get ready.
Come and get it.
(group chattering)
- I can't get a clear shot.
Crap, it's just too dark.
- I think you already
have enough proof.
- I wanna catch them
actually doing it.
- Oh.
- [Man] Yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
- Fireworks
- Is that Katsura?
(fireworks popping)
(both gasping)
That's bad.
(fireworks whistling)
(fireworks popping)
(crowd cheering)
(bright music)
(crowd clamoring)
- [Man] Let's get out of here!
- [Yoko] Hey, morons!
That's why you don't set
off illegal fireworks
in abandoned buildings!
- What was that?
I can't hear you.
- [Yoko] I think I got
hit by one of the sparks.
- We have to get out of here.
We can't go back the way we came.
We're going to have to jump, okay?
(both groaning)
- My leg hurts bad.
(fireworks popping)
(dramatic music)
- Oh.
YOKO HINAGESHI: MISSED CALL
YOKO: I'M WITH HINAKO...
(Kawamura gasps)
(alarm beeping)
- [Fire Center Operator]
Fire reported in Nagakawa.
20th Street Number 9, third
block of the Nishikubo District.
- Mr. Yamashiro, it's east of the OST.
And the closest hydrant's been moved
30 meters south of
the new mansion block.
- You sure?
- Yes.
The girl I like is in danger.
- Wait, what?
(siren blaring)
- Our ladders aren't
gonna be tall enough.
And if that tree catches fire,
it'll be a towering inferno.
(fireworks rumbling)
(siren wailing)
Damn, fireworks again?
Grab the hose.
We'll have to use the stairs.
Get up as high as you can.
- Roger.
- [Deputy Lieutenant] Search for 252s
on the 15th and other floors.
- Yes, sir.
- [Firefighter] The steel
door is locked.
We'll have to cut through it.
How did they get in there?
- I think I found
how they gained entry.
We're going in now.
(Kawamura panting)
- [Kawamura] Is anyone in here?
Shout if you can hear us!
(fireworks rumbling)
(fireworks whistling)
- 13th floor, the stairwell's
inaccessible, too many sparks.
We cannot go higher, over.
Shit, put your face guards on!
- [Kawamura] Captain,
we've got no water.
- What?
Wait here, I'll check it out.
- [Commander] We've yet
to rescue any civilians.
The 14th and 15th floor stairwells
are currently engulfed in flames.
No other 252s on any other floors.
Reports indicate there
were 10 people on the roof.
We're still trying to locate them.
(water hissing)
(Kawamura grunting)
(Kawamura screaming)
- It's okay, I made a call.
The fire department's downstairs now.
They'll be here to save us real soon.
(fireworks popping)
(Yoko whimpers)
If I call on Minato now,
he might disappear forever.
- [Minato] If you need
my help, just call, 'kay?
- [Hinako] I can't.
If I do that, you'll--
- [Yoko] (whimpers) Minato.
- [Kawamura] Minato will
never be able to be at peace
if you do not move on.
- [Hinako] Minato said
that what he wanted.
- [Minato] Until you're able
to ride those waves alone,
you can call on me whenever you need.
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
D I can see your smiling
face reflect back at me )
- [Minato] Hinako, did
you need something?
- Minato.
- My wish came true.
I'm still here.
| got to stay.
My wish is and has
always been the same,
that I'll be here for you.
- [Minato and Hinako] Until
you can ride your wave.
(water hissing)
(bright music)
- [Minato] You've really improved.
- [Kawamura] Minato?
- [Minato] I'm proud
to call you my friend.
There are two more on the top
floors, but I'll get them.
- [Kawamura] Minato!
(fireworks popping)
-The fireworks can no longer ignite.
And there's a column of water
traveling up the old tree,
dousing its branches.
But how, I couldn't say.
(fireworks popping)
(fire crackling)
- Listen up.
We're going under the water,
but don't worry, it's safe.
(Yoko inhales)
You'll get to see your brother.
- [Minato] How's my little
blue-ringed octopus?
- [Yoko] Minato? (mumbling)
- [Minato] Say hi to
Mom and Dad for me.
(Yoko mumbling)
(both gasping)
- [Hinako] Come on, Yoko, this way.
(both panting)
Right.
Left.
(bright music)
Right.
Left.
We gotta go under, hold your breath.
- [Minato] When the water
has extinguished the fire,
it'll spill out like a giant wave.
Once you surface, you're
gonna have to ride that wave.
Yoko, hold on to the
board and don't let go.
Get ready, I see the top.
You're almost there, one, two, three.
(both gasping)
(Yoko screaming)
Hinako, paddle, paddle.
(Hinako gasps)
Pop up, ride the wave.
(wave roaring)
(Hinako yelps)
(bright music)
(both groaning)
- [Hinako] Thank you, Yoko.
(both giggling)
- [Minato] Thank you, Hinako.
You're my hero.
- Hinako.
Thank goodness.
- [Hinako] Thanks for
celebrating Christmas with me.
- We couldn't miss celebrating
your lifeguard certification.
But are you sure you
wanna do it with omurice?
- I've always celebrated with omurice
ever since I was a kid.
Even though I've
never really been able
to make it very well.
But I have been practicing,
and recently I've gotten a tad better.
- Wait, really?
- [Kawamura] Lifeguard
and omurice master.
It looks like you've
tackled life's waves.
- That's right.
I'm riding the waves, this
time on and off the shore.
You could say I'm surfing
my way through life.
(Kawamura and Yoko chuckling)
- I'm sure my brother's
smiling down on us.
Oh, reminds me.
4 MEN ARRESTED OVER "OST RUINS" FIRE
They finally caught those bastards.
- [Kawamura] (chuckles)
Okay, enough detective stuff.
- Fine, I got it.
- [Hinako] Thanks for dinner.
- [Kawamura] My pleasure.
Congratulations again.
- Yeah, congrats.
- Hey, you wanna check out Port Tower?
They have a lover's sanctuary inside.
- [Yoko] What's that?
- And they have these heart cards
that you can write messages on.
- Sounds lame.
- Nah, sounds romantic.
- Huh?
- If you wanna go Wasabi,
| don't mind giving you some company.
- [Hinako] (gasps) You
two should go together.
- Oh, you think so?
- Uh, but--
- Don't worry about me.
I'm feeling kinda tired.
- Okay.
- Great, we're gonna check it out.
Come on, Wasabi.
(Kawamura groaning)
- See you later.
Bye, Happy New Year.
- Hinako, Merry Christmas.
Not falling in love is
something only idiots do.
(Kawamura chuckling)
(gentle music)
D> There you are )
> Out on the water )
(Hinako crying)
- [Announcer] This message
is from Minato Hinageshi,
and it goes out to Hinako Mukaimizu.
It was submitted exactly a year ago.
NEXT YEAR'S CHRISTMAS MESSAGE BOX
Merry Christmas, Hinako.
Let's spend every Christmas
together from this day forward
forever and ever and ever.
(Hinako sobbing)
This next message is
for Tatsuya Shibasaki
from his whole family.
(Hinako wailing)
Merry Christmas.
What a year it's been, but
thank you for everything.
And Happy New Year.
I also have a message from Miyu
Watanabe to Koichi Watanabe.
(waves whooshing)
- [Hinako] Hi, guys. (chuckling)
There's a rip current around
here, so be careful, okay?
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Hinako's the best.
- [Surfer] I guess there's
no more waves today.
- Let's bail.
(bright music)
> Oh oh oh )
> Oh oh )
(singing in foreign language)
D> That's right )
> Brand new story )
(singing in foreign language)
> Oh )
D Yeah )
(singing in foreign language)
D> That's right )
> Brand new story )
(singing in foreign language)
D> That's right )
> Brand new story )
(singing in foreign language)
> Oh oh oh )
> My brand new story )