Hey, Yui, see if this will work.
I'm transferring the code.
We're gonna teleport! Daddy, give me your hand!
Daddy.
Daddy!
Yui. Where are we?
I don't know.
There's no mapping data available.
Then do you know where Asuna is?
Yes.
She's close... very close, in fact.
This way!
Is this it?
Is this the top of the world tree?
There's supposed to be a floating city up here.
There was never any grand quest.
The whole damn thing was a lie.
He's gonna pay for this.
Yeah, I know.
We've got to get Asuna out of here first, right?
Mm-hmm.
Mommy!
Yui!
Mommy! Mommy!
Kirito.
Asuna.
Hey. Sorry I took so long.
Mnh-mnh. No, it's okay, really.
I always knew you'd save me.
Well... ready to go home?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Yui, can you log Asuna out from here?
Unh-unh.
Her status is locked by complicated
codes that I don't have access to.
We'll need to find a system console to bypass them.
I found a console in the laboratory.
I can...
what's that?
Yui, what's happening?!
Daddy! Mommy! Be careful!
Something... something bad's coming!
Yui!
Asuna.
What a surprise.
The last thing I expected to find was
a cockroach in my little bird's cage.
You got to be kidding!
It's Sugou!
Mnh-mnh.
I'd prefer it if you didn't
call me that name in this world.
You should address me as his
highness, the fairy king, oberon!
Kirito!
How do you like it?
Want to know why you can't move?
It's a little something called "gravity
magic," coming out in the next update.
You think the players will go for it?
Leave him alone, you coward!
Tell me something, Kirigaya,
or should I call you "Kirito" instead?
How did you manage to get all the way up here?
I saw a strange program running.
Is that how?
I flew up here with my wings.
Ha! Suit yourself.
If you don't want to tell me, that's
fine. I'll just go ask your mind instead.
What?
Oh, please. You don't really think I went to all that
trouble setting this whole thing up just for fun, did you?
I have 300 former players of S.A.O. under my
thumb, and now, thanks to their dedicated cooperation,
the technology I developed for total
control of emotions and thought is 80% complete.
I'm about to achieve what no one else has... the
total control of the human soul, the power of a god!
It's so close, I can almost taste it!
Seriously, thank god for virtual reality, huh?
Sugou!
You're never gonna get away with this, you hear?!
You monster!
Ah, who do you think's going to stop me?
Oh, maybe a god.
But, sadly, there's none in
this world, except for yours truly!
I know... before I start tinkering with your
little souls, why don't we have ourselves a little fun?!
You bastard!
Leave her alone!
Yes!
Ha ha! Great!
That's what I was hoping for! You can't
get NPC girls to make faces like that.
Ahh. You smell lovely. Figuring out how to replicate
the way you smell in real life was a challenge.
And don't even get me started on how hard it was to
get an analyzer into your hospital room undetected.
Get away from her, Sugou!
Give me a break.
Why don't you stay down and
grovel like a good little doggy?
Ohh!
Kirito!
System command, change the pain
absorber from level 10 to level 8.
Aaah!
Hurts, doesn't it?
I'll increase the pain gradually to
give you something to look forward to.
By the way, once it drops below level 3,
it'll start affecting your body in the real world.
As for you...
Stop it, Sugou!
It's okay, Kirito.
Whatever he does, he's not really hurting me.
I was hoping you'd say that,
but I wonder how long your pride's
going to last... 30 minutes, an hour?
Why don't we see how long you can hang on to it?!
Now that that's out of the way, would
you like to know what I'm thinking?
Once we've had our fun here, I'm
going to pay you a visit at the hospital.
I'll set up a big monitor and
play back a recording of this,
and we can enjoy ourselves all over again
but this time, with your real body.
Ah. Yummy. How sweet.
Sugou, you bastard!
You bastard!
Mmm!
I'll kill you!
You hear?!
I'm gonna kill you!
Why is this happening?
Am I being punished for thinking I was some kind of hero,
for thinking I was the only one who could save Asuna,
for thinking I was strong enough, even though I'm not?
Are you giving up?
No.
I'm facing reality.
Then you aregiving up... to the
power of a system you once defied.
What choice do I have?
I'm just a player, and he's the G.M.
Then our battle was, what, a joke?
Do you remember how you showed me the power
of the human will was superior to the system,
how you showed me the possibilities of the future?
You're...
Get up, Kirito.
Get up!
Ahh.
Your attacks are weak.
The blades in S.A.O. hit way harder!
And they hurt way more!
Unbelievable.
I've got a few bugs left to deal with.
Yah!
System log-in.
I.D. Heathcliff.
Wh-what?
Whose I.D. Are you using?!
System command,
enable administrator privileges.
Set I.D. Oberon to level 1.
An I.D. That outranks mine?
That's impossible!
This is my world! I'm the creator!
I'm its ruler, its king, its god!
No, I don't think so.
You stole everything in this world...
everything... including its people.
You're nothing but a king of thieves,
sitting alone on your stolen throne!
You little punk.
You dare... you dare talk to me like that?!
System command, generate object! I.D. Excalibur!
Do as I say, you piece of crap!
System, your god is ordering you to comply!
Think you can wait a little bit
longer? This will only take a sec.
Mm-hmm.
System command, generate object! I.D. Excalibur!
A simple command summons a legendary weapon.
Who knew?
Huh! Uh!
Huh?
It's time to settle the score...
the king of thieves versus the gilded hero!
System command, set pain absorber to zero!
No, not that!
Did you just flinch?
'Cause the other guy never
flinched, no matter how bad things got.
You know him... Akihiko Kayaba!
Oh, my god! Kayaba?!
Oh, I get it.
That was his I.D.
Why?
You're supposed to be dead!
Why are you still getting in my way?!
You are always doing this,
acting all high and mighty, like some big
shot, taking everything that was rightfully mine!
Sugou, in a way, I get where you're coming from.
I lost to him, too, and then I had to go work for him.
But whatever happened, I never
wanted to be him, unlike you.
Damn you!
God damn you!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Aah! Aah!
Hurts, doesn't it?
But it's nothing like the pain you
made Asuna feel... not even close!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
My hand!
My hand! My hand!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
I had faith in you.
I have faith in you.
Always have, always will.
And I know you'll always save me
because you are my hero.
I-I don't have any power.
I'm not a hero.
But, I-I'll do my best to be one.
Mm-hmm.
Come on. Let's go home.
It's got to be nighttime already back there,
but I'll see you at the hospital as soon as I can.
I'll be waiting for you.
I want you to be the first person I see when I wake up.
It's finally over, isn't it?
We're going home... back to the real world.
That's right.
But a lot's changed, so try not to freak out.
Let's go places and do fun things, just the two of us.
Sound good?
Yeah... real good.
That's it.
Game over.
Or is it?
What do you think, Heathcliff?
Good to see you again, Kirito.
So, you arealive.
You could say I'm alive, in a way.
Ultimately, I'm the afterimage of the
mind that was Akihiko Kayaba... an echo.
And, as usual, I have no idea what you're talking about.
I guess I should thank you, though.
That's not necessary.
What do you mean?
We're not exactly friends, so we
shouldn't expect favors from each other.
There's always a price... always.
Okay. What do you want me to do?
What's this?
The beginnings of a new world.
I call it "the seed."
Once it sprouts, you'll know what it is.
What you do with it is up to you.
You can even delete it if you want.
However, if you still have a tiny bit of fondness
left for the virtual world, you'll take care of it.
I should get going now.
I do hope we meet again, Kirito.
Yui! Are you okay?!
Where are you?!
Daddy!
Thank god.
You're safe.
Uh-huh.
I hid myself inside the local
memory of your nervegear rig.
Where's mommy?
Don't worry. She's safe.
She's back home now.
Mommy's back?!
Thank goodness!
I'm so happy...
really!
I promise we'll be back to visit soon, although I
don't know how much longer this world's gonna be around.
It doesn't matter because my core program's inside
your nervegear now, so we'll always be together.
All right.
I'd better head out.
I'm gonna go see mommy.
Okay, daddy.
I-I love you!
Aah!
I-I'm sorry!
When you didn't log out right
away, I got worried, and then I...
sorry I took so long to come back.
Is it really over now?
Yeah, it is.
It's all over.
That's awesome!
Hey, Sugu, thank you for all the help you gave me.
I couldn't have done it on my own.
You're the reason I was able to finish it.
No.
Ugh!
You don't have to thank me for a thing.
I'm just happy I got the chance
to help my big brother in his world.
What happened with Asuna?
Did you get her back?
Uh-huh, finally.
She's back in the real world.
Sugu, I, uh...
Unh-unh. You get going.
She's got to be wondering where you're at by now.
Ohh. It's cold.
Look... snow.
Be careful out there and say Hi to Asuna for me.
You got it.
I can't wait for you guys to meet for real!
Next time: "The World Seed".