There's the exit!
Are you trying to kill me?!
No, just trying to save us some time.
You and your shortcuts.
Uh, wait a sec.
Do you even know where this meeting's happening?
Yeah, I'll check.
Mm...
Northwest... inside that mountain.
How much time we got?
20 minutes.
Then we're not going fast enough.
I wish we could go faster, 'cause at this rate,
we're not gonna make it before the salamanders.
I know.
Even if we can warn them, it doesn't
mean we'll get the commanders out in time.
We just might end up dying with them all in battle.
I've got player readings...
68 of them flying in formation.
From what I can tell, it could
be the salamander attack squad.
There are 14 more players on the plateau.
Most likely, they're the diplomats
from the sylphs and cait siths.
The two groups of players will make contact in 50 seconds.
We didn't make it after all.
Thanks for trying, Kirito, but this is far enough.
I'm gonna try and save Sakuya.
Get out of here and head for the world tree.
We didn't get to hang out for long, but it was fun.
Hope we meet again someday.
Sorry, but running away from
a fight's not really my style.
Why are the salamanders here?
Salamanders, stand down!
Who's that?
Sakuya!
Leafa?
W-What are you doing here?
It's too complicated to get into
now, but you see that guy out there?
Believe it or not, the fates of
our races depend on his next move.
You have got to be kidding.
I want to talk to your commander!
What the hell is a Spriggan like you doing here?
I'm gonna kill you no matter what your answer,
but since you're brave enough to
face me, I might as well hear you out.
My name is Kirito.
I'm an ambassador for the spriggan/undine alliance.
Since you're on the offensive today, I'm assuming
you want to wage a full-on war between all our races.
Huh?
Uh...
Mnh-mnh! Mnh-mnh!
The undines are allied with the spriggans, huh?
And you're supposed to be their ambassador,
but you've come here without a guard?
Yeah, that's right.
So what?
I was sent here to negotiate trade
terms with the sylphs and cait sith,
but if you interrupt our talks, you're
gonna get to feel some serious hurt.
All of our races are gonna team up, and we'll
bring the fight straight to the salamanders.
You're kidding me, right?
You're all alone and you've got crappy gear, so
there's no way you could be anyone's ambassador.
If you can survive my attacks for 30 seconds,
then I'll believe you are who you say you are.
Gee, thanks.
That's mighty generous.
This is bad.
Why?
Do you see that salamander's sword?
It's the demon sword gram.
You need a two-handed sword skill of 950 to equip it.
950?!
Yes.
And there's only one person I know who can use it...
General Eugene.
Have you heard of him?
Yeah, I know the name.
He's the younger brother of
Mortimer, the leader of the salamanders.
They're brothers in real life, too.
Mortimer's a brilliant strategist, but in terms of sheer
power, they say Eugene is the game's strongest player.
Oh, no.
He's the strongest player?
Kirito.
Mngh!
Oh! What was that?!
The ethereal shift... the sword's bonus skill.
Whenever someone tries to block it with a shield or a
sword, the demonic sword gram can phase right through it!
Really?! No way!
Can't believe you're not dead.
What the hell kind of attack was that?!
Damn, he's good.
Hey, big red, I think your 30 seconds are up by now.
I've changed my mind.
I've decided to kill you anyway.
Now you have to survive until I do.
Yeah, that figures.
But I won't go down that easy!
This won't end well.
They both seem like equally skilled
fighters, but Eugene's weapon is far superior.
He can do it.
Kirito can beat him. I know it.
What the...
I need to borrow this for a sec.
K-Kirito?
Aah!
A few seconds... that's all you bought!
Hey, where'd he go?
Do you think he... Ran away?
Of course he didn't!
As long as I'm alive, I'm not
gonna let anyone in my party die.
I won't let that happen again.
Kirito would never run away and leave us.
Huh?
Kirito!
Aaaaaaaaah!
Die!
Yaaaaah!
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Splendid! Marvelous!
That was the most amazing fight ever!
Nicely done, Spriggan!
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
That was good!
Yeah, seriously!
You're an excellent fighter.
In fact, you're the most powerful player I've ever seen.
Well done.
You're not so bad yourself.
I didn't know the spriggans had
someone like you in their ranks.
This world's a bigger place than I thought.
Are we cool, then?
Will you withdraw?
Mm.
Eugene, may I have a word?
Kagemune, what is it?
Him again.
Oh.
The next time, I'll make sure
to bring more friends along.
You might find this interesting.
You know how my party was wiped out yesterday?
So?
Well, this Spriggan... he's the
same guy who took everyone out.
And he was traveling with an undine.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Then I guess I have to believe you.
But just for the record, the last thing our leader and
I want is to go to war with the spriggans and undines.
We'll withdraw for now, but I'm
gonna be looking forward to fighting you again.
Then that makes two of us.
I guess so mesalamanders can be cool after all.
Who knew?
You really are insane, you know that?
Yeah, I get that a lot.
Excuse me, but could either
of you explain what's going on?
I see.
I could tell there was something
off about Sigurd's attitude recently.
He seemed so irritated.
Irritated?
About what?
My guess... he was dissatisfied about the state of things,
that in terms of power, he couldn't
accept we'd fallen behind the salamanders.
Power is very important to a man like Sigurd...
and not just for his abilities and
character stats, but also as a player.
He craves power.
Yeah, but even so, why would
he turn spy for the salamanders?
It must have something to do with the
5.0 update that's going to be released soon.
I heard a rumor that they'll be
putting in a reincarnation system.
No way!
I'm sure Mortimer made him an offer.
"Bring me the head of your leader, and
I'll reincarnate you as a salamander."
So, now what?
What'll you do, Sakuya?
Ru, have you raised your dark-magic skill yet?
Mm-hmm.
Open a moonlight mirror to Sigurd.
Hmm.
Sigurd.
S-Sakuya!
Nice to see you, too.
Unfortunately, I'm still alive.
How... I-I mean... What happened at the meeting?
It went very well.
There's still the matter of signing the treaty, though.
By the way, we had an unexpected guest.
W-What guest?
His name is general Eugene, and he sends his regards.
Leafa.
So that's it.
Oh, those incompetent lizards.
Well, it's your move now, Sakuya.
Are you gonna fine me?
Or maybe you want to take away my command.
If so, remember... without me running
your military, your rule won't last very long.
Actually, I was thinking of
granting the request you made them.
Since you can't stand being a Sylph, you're free to go.
Wait... what?!
Hold on.
Are you crazy?!
Me?! You... you're banishing me?!
I'm letting you live to wander
the neutral territory as a renegade.
With any luck, you'll find something
there that'll occupy your precious time.
You bit...
Sakuya?
Thank you for saving us, Leafa.
You've no idea how grateful I am having you around.
Oh, well... I didn't really do anything.
If you want to thank someone, thank Kirito.
She's right. Whoever you are, you have my thanks.
Hey, handsome, about this Spriggan undine
ambassador business... you aren't ,are you?
Mm...
Uh...
Yeah, that was a big, fat lie.
I was bluffing, conning... you know, negotiating.
Oh, god. You must be insane.
You have to be, to make all
that stuff up at the last minute.
Yeah, but it worked, didn't it?
Whenever I'm dealt a bad hand, I always raise the pot.
You know, for a big, fat liar,
you're pretty freakin' strong, handsome.
You're like the mvp of spriggans.
Are you their secret weapon?
Nah, of course not.
All I am is your friendly neighborhood mercenary.
I like the wandering type.
Have you ever thought about
being a merc for the cait sith?
You get three meals a day, plus snacks and a nap.
So, Kirito, I was thinking... how about
we get to know each other a little better?
I know a cute little pub in Sylvain... my treat.
Wait...
Aw, come on, Sakuya.
That's not fair.
You're totally seducing him with those things.
I'm seducing him? If you were any
closer to him, he'd be wearing you.
Would you guys chill out?!
For your information, he's my...
I mean, he's...
What?
He's my...
Uh... never mind.
Look, I appreciate the offers, really.
But the thing is, she promised to
take me to the world tree, so... sorry.
Really?
Oh, well.
That is a shame.
Are you going there for a little sightseeing, Leafa?
Or... what?
I'm leaving the sylphs.
Or planning on it, anyway.
But I want to return to Sylvain at some point.
I just don't know when that's gonna be.
Not a problem. I understand.
Just make sure you come back, okay?
And bring your friend.
On the way back, stop by my place.
We'll throw you a party.
Thank you so much for coming today, Leafa, Kirito.
If you hadn't been here to stop them, the salamanders
would have become even more powerful than ever.
I'd like to pay you back somehow.
Oh, no. It was nothing.
Hey, Sakuya, Alicia...
Wasn't the point of you guys getting
together to make a tribe for the world tree?
Ultimately, yes, that was our goal.
If you're okay with it and it's no
trouble, we'd like to go with you.
We're kind of in a hurry to get there, though.
Hmm.
Well, I can't see why not. In fact, the
truth is, we'd be grateful to have you along.
But why are you in such a hurry to get there?
She's not in a hurry.
I'm the one who has to get to the top of the tree.
I think someone I know is up there, waiting for me.
Hmm.
Is it oberon, the fairy king?
No. It's not him.
It's someone I can't reach in real life.
But in here, I might be able to.
We want to help, but storming the
tree's gonna take some time to set up.
We got to gear up the raiding party and stuff,
and that'll take us way more than a few days.
I see.
Never mind, then.
I don't want to raid the tree, like you.
I just want to get to the base of it as soon as possible.
So it's cool. We'll figure it out.
Oh, by the way...
Maybe this will help you guys
get some new gear for your raid.
Mm.
Whoa! Sakuya, look!
Check it out!
$100,000 pieces of mithril yuld?!
You don't want it?
You could build a castle on prime land with this.
Nah, it's yours.
I don't need it anymore.
You are so awesome.
With this bag of loot, we've
got just about enough for new gear.
We'll get ready as fast as we can.
When we're set to go, we'll message you, okay?
Yeah. You got it.
Thanks, guys!
We'll be seein' ya!
I don't know about you, but I
can't believe you pulled that off.
Oh, honestly!
I thought I told you... no more flirting, daddy!
I wasn't flirting with anyone.
When those girls were clinging to you,
I noticed that your heartbeat increased.
I'm a guy.
That's what happens when girls get too close.
Seriously.
What about me? I'm a girl.
Isn't that a problem?
No, you seem pretty safe to me, Leafa.
What do you mean, "safe"?!
Mm...
I think what she means is, most of the
time, you don't really seem much like a girl.
Okay, whoa!
Say that again! I dare you!
No, like... like, you're easy to get
along with. I meant it in a goodway.
Yeah.
Come on.
We still got a ways to go before we get to arun.
The sun's starting to go down.
Okay, I'm coming!
Wait up!
8, 1, 1...
3, 2, 3, 2, 9.
Kirito, I promise you...
I won't give up.
Next time: "The Truth about Alfheim".