But now, if this is how it is, I
wish you'd kept on being a jerk to me.
If you had, I wouldn't have realized how I felt about you.
I wouldn't have felt sad and
jealous when I found out about her,
and I wouldn't have tried forgetting about
you and falling in love with Kirito instead!
I'm sorry.
Go on.
Leave me alone.
I remember the day when everything changed...
the day I found out I wasn't really part of this family.
It felt weird, like I didn't fit in with them anymore.
And I found this out when I was 10.
I'd wonder, "who is she?" And
"do I really know anything about her?"
Maybe that feeling I had of not fitting in
was the thing that drove me to online gaming.
I guess I figured in the virtual
world, no one knows anything about anyone,
so I dove right in and thought it was where I belonged.
But those two years I spent
trapped in S.A.O. taught me something.
The difference between a real
and a virtual world is slim at best.
It's a waste of time asking people who they really are.
All you can do is accept them
as is and have faith in them,
'cause, in the end, whoever you think
they are... that's who they really are.
When I got back to the real world and saw
Suguha's face, I was really, truly happy.
Right then and there, I swore I'd do whatever I
could to try to close the gap that had grown between us
over the last couple of years.
But how do I do that?
What can I do for Sugu?
Sugu, I'll wait for you in arun, on the north terrace.
How could I be so horrible to
you, and how could you be so strong?
I wish I could be as strong as you, big brother.
I told you to hang in there, to
not give up on the one you love,
but I can't do that.
And now I can't stop crying.
I guess this is how it is.
Leafa?
Uh, hi.
Y-You know, I've been looking all over for you.
Wait.
What are you doing here?
I thought the salamanders caught you.
Yeah. Well, I sort of poisoned them all and escaped.
No way. You poisoned them?
Big-time, and after I got away, I tracked you here.
Hang on.
What are you doing here alone?
Where's that Spriggan?
Oh, yeah. Well...
I kind of... Said something really mean to him.
It wasn't cool, and I shouldn't have said it.
It was... Pretty stupid of me.
Oh, never mind.
I'm just being weird.
I'm not gonna be seeing him around anymore.
Come on.
Let's go back to Sylvain.
Don't cry like that.
Wait!
You shouldn't be crying like that!
Uh, sorry?
The Leafa I know is always smiling and happy,
and I... well, I'd never leave you like that!
I'd stay with you always, in here and in the real world!
I-I, uh... Leafa... I mean, Suguha... I love you!
You what?
Wait. Don't do that. No! What are you doing?!
Aaah!
Uh... oh.
Uh, are you okay?
Ohh, where did I go wrong?
After everything I've said and done, I thought all I
had to do was find the guts to confess my feelings to you.
You really are a moron, aren't you?
Huh?
Even so, I could learn a thing or two from you.
Hey.
Here I am.
Suguha...
Kazuto, I want a rematch.
Huh?
Let's finish what we started.
And this time, no holding back.
Now I know why he looked so composed.
Here I come!
What are you doing?
What are youdoing?
Mm.
Look...
I wanted to apologize, but I just
didn't know how to go about doing it...
So, I was gonna throw the duel.
You were?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too. I think my problem is I never
really came back to the real world after S.A.O.,
and I can't come back until she wakes in
a way, the game hasn't ended for me yet.
And I guess that's why I still haven't figured out
how I fit in at home or with you... not yet, anyway.
Mm.
And when you do, I'll be there.
It doesn't matter how long it takes. I'll be
waiting for the day you come back to us for real.
Until then... I'll help you in here.
So, uh... Wait.
What's going on again?
Three players are gonna raid the world tree today.
He's player 1, you're player 2, and yours truly makes 3.
Oh. Okay.
Wait. What?!
Yui, you there?
Hi, daddy. What is it?
I need some info on the guardians.
You learn anything?
The stats for one aren't very
high, but that's not the problem.
There's just too many of them.
As I see it, this quest was designed
to be next to impossible to finish.
So, what you're saying is they all
add up to one unbeatable boss, huh?
Yes, but don't forget your skills and xp are really high,
so maybe, with a burst of speed,
you can smash right through them.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, guys...
This isn't your fight.
The only way I'm gonna get through is with your help.
But time's running out,
so we have to go now.
Don't worry. I'll do whatever I can to get you up there.
You ready?
Let's see that game face.
Huh?
Well, I guess I don't have a choice,
since we were destined to be together forever.
Okay! Don't talk stupid.
Ow! Sorry! Geez!
We're in this together.
Thanks, guys. I mean it.
I'll draw the guardians' attention.
While I do, stay back and heal
you shouldn't be in any danger then.
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Let's go.
Soo fillah haydle astaloo prottoh supaal baani!
Aaaaaaaah!
That's awesome!
There's a lot more coming.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
There are so many of them!
Now, Recon!
Right!
Why are the guardians targeting us instead of him?
My guess is they're using a different targeting
algorithm than any of the other bosses in the game.
It looks like we're gonna be
doing some fighting after all.
Wait!
What are you doing?!
Wait a second.
Listen, I'm not sure what's going on
here, but, like, is this raid that important?
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
I don't think it's just a game... not now, anyway.
Then I'm gonna help you help that Spriggan!
Wait! Recon!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Se-ahh mareeta fimm glown vin-doh!
No! You idiot!
Heal!
Recon! That's enough!
Go on! Get outside!
Ekku kalla svalt tu-garli belfa hi-mun!
No way!
He's using a dark magic spell!
Blotoh leggin' garpah! Kneeza fall!
A self-destruct spell!
He used it even though the
penalty's worse than a normal death!
That dummy!
What was he thinking?!
No!
Oh, no.
Now what?! He can't keep this up! It's impossible!
What are the sylphs doing here?
No way! They made it!
Dragons.
It's the cait sith, and they brought the whole ar...
Hello, there!
I hope we're not late.
Yeah, sorry!
It took us a while to get ready, but we're here now!
Sakuya! Alicia!
Okay, dragoons!
Get ready to toast these suckers!
Sylph warriors, prepare to engage the enemy!
Fire breath... Atta-a-a-a-ck!
Fenrir storm... Fire at will!
Ohh.
Thank you!
Thank you so much for coming!
You don't have to thank us.
We can't even begin to repay
that Spriggan for all he's done.
Sakuya's got a point, you know.
I mean, the only reason we're here for this
little raid's 'cause of all the money he gave us.
warriors, forward to battle!
Destroy them all! Keep going!
Sugu!
Yeah?!
Watch my back, okay?!
You got it!
Follow their lead!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Kazuto!
You can do it!
Go, Kazuto!
G-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
We're clearing out!
Everyone, fall back!
Keep going.
Fly!
Keep flying as long as you can...
To the very end.
Damn it!
Now what do I do?
Hey, Yui!
Yes, daddy?
Daddy, something strange is going on.
This door isn't locked by a quest flag.
It's locked by the system administrator.
What's that supposed to mean?
Restricted access.
This door was never intended to be opened by a player!
No. Wait.
That's it!
Hey, Yui, see if this will work.
I'm transferring the code.
We're gonna teleport!
Daddy, give me your hand!
Next time: "Gilded Hero".