It's amazing.
I know. Isn't it?
Welcome to arun.
It's the center of Alfheim.
It's also the biggest city in this world.
Yeah.
We finally got here.
How exciting!
I've never been to a city this big before!
Me, neither.
The ore light's so beautiful,
like a bunch of twinkling stars.
Attention, players.
The server will be down today,
January the 22nd, from 4:00 A.M.
To 3:00 P.M. for scheduled maintenance.
We ask that all players please log out
no later than 10 minutes before shutdown.
Repeat...
I guess that does it for us for today.
Let's go find an inn and log out.
Sure.
Uh... uh...
Well, I hope we can find someplace
good... nothing too pricy, though.
I sort of blew threw all my cash today.
And why is that?
Oh, right... you were showing off
and you gave all your money to Sakuya.
You should have saved a little for the inn, big spender.
Your dad's financially challenged.
Do you know if there's a cheap inn anywhere?
Hmm?
Um... there's one there, and from
what I can tell, it's supercheap!
Great. Supercheap. Yay.
Come on. Let's go.
Hey, wait for me!
An opening.
Hey, Sugu. Good morning.
Morning, Kazuto.
Someone looks sleepy today.
When did you get to bed last night?
I don't know.
Around 4:00, I think.
Whoa.
A kid like you shouldn't be up that late.
What were you doing?
Oh, uh, tooling around online.
Just don't go too overboard, okay?
Right. Like I'm one to talk.
Hey, Suguha, turn around for a sec.
Why?
Go on. Turn around.
Okay.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
How far does this hallway go?
No way.
It's a map.
Where is it?
There's got to be a console where I can log out.
Experiment hangar?
To make up for that water gag you pulled,
you owe me one green tea raspberry parfait.
You cool with that?
All right.
Then we're even.
We could go get them today if you're not too busy.
I can't today.
I have to do something in the afternoon, and
I was also planning on going to the hospital.
Oh, right.
Hey, I was wondering... is it okay
if I go with you to the hospital?
Huh?
Sure. Why not?
I'm sure it'll make Asuna happy.
Hmm.
Come on. Let's eat. I'm starving.
Is that a...
Did you know that by expanding
the brain's control regions,
one could influence a person's
thoughts, emotions, and memories?
It's suffering!
They're all... Players.
Oh, my god.
This is horrible.
He won't get away with this...
not if I can do anything about it.
Don't worry.
You'll be okay. I'm gonna save you.
Time to see what everyone's up to.
Ooh. This guy's dreaming about spica again.
His b-13 and b-14 fields are way off the scale.
Look at 16 getting up there too.
He's really excited.
It's only the third experiment.
Maybe it's a coincidence.
No, it's definitely the induced emotion circuit.
He's over the threshold now because of the
frequency at which the imagery's occurring.
Hmm. Then we have to keep monitoring him.
I'll put him on the list.
Hey, I was wondering...
what's happening with school?
What about it?
It's just that you were supposed to start high
school last year, and it'd suck if you got too far behind.
Yeah, well, I don't know.
They said something about me
having to go to school in the city.
It's kind of a temporary thing
they set up in an old building.
Middle-schoolers, high-schoolers... everyone's from S.A.O.
Now departing.
You can get in without taking the test, and once
you graduate, you can take the college entrance exams.
Really? Huh.
If you ask me, that's a pretty good deal.
But it sucks they're cramming you together like that.
I get why they're doing it.
When you think about it, we were all trapped
inside that death game for more than two years,
so no one knows what that experience did to our minds.
This is how they keep an eye on us.
Seriously?
If I wanted to get into a normal
high school now, it'd be way too hard.
I'd have to spend a whole year in cram school,
but then i'd basically be starting over from scratch.
I could always just take the exams now
and see what happens, but I doubt I'd pass.
What are you saying? You'd totally pass!
You're smart, and you've got good grades.
My grades used to be good.
I haven't studied for two years, remember?
I've got a great idea! I can be your tutor!
Oh, sweet. Then you can help me
with math and information technology.
There it is...
...the system console.
They didn't see me. Good.
Please work.
This is it.
Wow!
That's a big hospital!
The inside's amazing, too...
like a hotel.
"Asuna Yuki."
She used her real-life name for her avatar.
That's not something a lot of people do.
I can't believe you know that.
Asuna's the only person I ever
met who played under her real name.
I'll introduce you.
This is Asuna,
knights of the blood oath, second in command.
They call her "lightning flash."
I could never match her speed in
battle or her accuracy with the sword.
Asuna, this is my sister, Suguha.
Uh... hello, Asuna.
Nice to meet you.
Aaah! Ohh! Ugh! Ohh!
Who are you?
You want to tell us what you're doing here?
Hey, let me go of me.
Sugou's a very good friend of mine.
I have his permission to be here and was
just about to leave when you grabbed me.
No one told me you were gonna be here today.
Did you know about her?
Uh, no.
All I know is that he doesn't
want anyone seeing this stuff ever.
Hmm.
Hang on a sec.
This is the girl... you know, the one Sugou
keeps locked up at the top of the world tree.
Right. Right.
I heard about her.
I don't think it's fair how the boss
gets to have all the fun with this cute girl.
Aah!
Oh, come on.
Stop struggling.
Stop it!
Let me go, you monster!
Oh, don't be so mean.
After all, you interrupted our
deep-sense mapping experiment.
You're supposed to be scientists, right?!
All this... it's wrong!
It's illegal to mess with people's
minds... illegal and unethical!
Well, it's more ethical than sticking electrical
probes into the brain of some poor animal,
wouldn't you say?
Our experiments are just dreams,
that's all.
He's right.
Sometimes we show them the most wonderful
dream... dreams you wish you'd never wake up from.
I wish I could have that.
You're insane.
The boss is out on business,
right?
Log out and go see what he wants us to do with her.
Ah, fine. Whatever.
Listen, though... until I get
back, don't do anything I wouldn't do.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Hurry up and get going.
You can't keep me here!
Put me down right now!
I'm sorry, but I can't.
The boss would kill me if I let you go.
Oh, wait, I have it.
Why don't you and I take electro-drugs?
I'm so bored with dolls, but you
look like someone I can have fun with.
Stop it!
No!
Stop!
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Okay!
I'm putting you down! Here's me putting you down!
Geez!
Next time I'll remember to turn my pain sensors off.
Okay. What happened here?
Hmm? What? Nothing.
Uh, nothing happened. So, what did the boss say?
Oh, he was so pissed.
He said we had to put her back in the cage upstairs,
change the passcode, and keep an eye on her 24/7.
Damn it, damn it, damn it.
I was just about to have some fun.
Okay. I say we walk her back instead of teleporting her.
I want to enjoy this feeling as long as I can.
You know what I think?
You're a perv.
Huh?
Stop struggling. It won't do you any good.
Don't fall off him!
Let me go!
Good one.
She's really pretty.
I feel sorry for her that she hasn't woken up yet.
I don't know if coming here was such a good idea.
I'm so confused.
I don't know how I feel.
I thought if I met her, i'd figure it out.
But now I don't know what I want.
Do I want to be a good sister...
Or... what?
Kazuto.
Don't go anywhere. I hope we
have another chance to hang out.
This won't stop me, Kirito...
No way.
I'll never give up.
I'll find a way to get out of here.
Hey, Leafa.
What's wrong? You okay?
Unh-unh.
I'm not okay at all.
I just... I just... I just got my heart broken!
I...
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I'm telling you this.
We just met. And I know it's not cool for players
to drag their real-life problems into the game.
It's okay to cry.
Doesn't matter if you're here or in the real world.
There's no rule.
Even in a game, you can show your feelings if you want.
Kirito...
I'm in love with my brother.
And that's something I can't tell anyone about... ever.
I have to Bury these feelings deep in my heart.
Maybe then, someday, I can forget.
I'm okay now.
Thanks for the pep talk, Kirito.
You're really sweet. You know that?
Uh, yeah, well, you're probably the
only person who thinks that about me.
You want to log off for today?
I can make it the rest of the way myself.
No.
I mean, I've come this far, so
I might as well go all the way.
Come on. Let's go.
Yui, you here?
Good morning.
I hope you both slept well.
Good morning, Yui.
Hey, I didn't get the chance to ask you
yesterday, but, like, do navi pixies ever sleep?
Oh, no.
See, whenever daddy logs out of the game, I shut down
my input circuits and process the data I've acquired.
You could consider it a little
like human sleep, but it's not.
Then how come you yawned?
Oh. Well, that's what humans
do during their boot-up sequence.
When daddy yawns, it usually lasts for eight seconds.
Please keep the weird trivia to yourself.
You ready to go?
Yep.
There's tons of people here!
I guess it really is the center of Alfheim.
It seems all the fairy races the world over are here.
Look how they're all getting along.
And he flew right off!
Whoa.
There it is... the world tree.
Yeah, and it looks even more amazing up close, doesn't it?
Um... i heard there's supposed
to be a city up there at the top.
What else?
Oberon, the fairy king, lives there,
along with the alf, the fairies of light.
And they say the first race to get to
the top and see the king will become an alf.
Has anyone ever tried climbing up the side of that thing?
They made the whole perimeter of the trunk off
limits so a player can't even get close enough to try.
And if you just fly straight up,
the flight limit of your wings would
expire before you even got halfway.
I heard about some players who tried.
They got more than halfway up
by piggybacking on each other.
Yeah, I heard about them, all right, but they could
only make it up to the lowest branches before bailing.
The g.M.S freaked out and fixed
it so no one could ever do it again.
Know what they did?
They put a barrier up there just above the clouds.
Interesting.
All right, then.
Let's head to the base of the trunk.
Right behind you.
Once we pass through that gate,
we're in the world's heart...
the central district of arun.
What, Yui?
Is something wrong?
Mommy.
It's mommy! She's here!
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm positive!
Hey, I...
I scanned again, and it's mommy's player I.D.!
Her coordinates are above us in the tree!
Kirito!
Wait!
Next time: "The Grand Quest".