I understand the situation.
Now I just have explain it to the rest of the guild.
Also, we'd like a temporary
leave of absence from the guild.
Really?
Why?
We have concerns with the current state
of the guild, and we need time to think.
Hmm.
Very well.
Although...
I'm positive you won't stay
away from the battlefield for long.
Uh...
Wow, this view's amazing!
It ispretty awesome, but don't fall off the balcony.
That would really suck.
We bought the best house.
Andnow we're totally broke.
It's worth it, though, 'cause we can live in peace here.
Uh...
Kirito?
What's wrong?
Well...
I was thinking...
Does our relationship only exist in this world?
I can't believe you'd say that.
Uh...
I don't give a damn if this is a virtual world.
My feelings for you are real.
Huh?
If I learned anything in the last two years, it's this
to keep doing the best we can till the very end.
And if we make it back to the real world,
I promise I'm going to find you again,
no matter what, and fall in love with you again.
Usually, he's brash and impulsive.
But he can be so naive, too,
almost like a little kid.
Oh, my god, is he younger than me?!
Kirito...
I love you.
Let's stay together forever.
Huh?
Unh!
Good morning, Kirito.
Mm.
Morning.
D-Did you...
Hear what I said?
No, I didn't hear a thing.
What'd you say?
Nothing! Not a thing!
Anyway, you want to go have some fun today?
Yeah, you know...
Didn't we have fun yesterday and
the day before, too?
So you're saying you don'twant to go have fun today.
Uh...
Wait, I know a place we can go.
Come on!
Where are we going?
You're just gonna have to wait
till we get there to find out.
Hmm.
Hey, carry me on your shoulders.
Uh, seriously?
Oh, please! It's no fun seeing the
world from the same height all the time.
Besides, with your strength
parameter, you won't break a sweat.
Yeah, I mean...
I guess, but...
... aren't you a little old for that, though?
It doesn't matter how old I am.
Come on, it's not like anyone's gonna see us.
Okay.
Get on.
Uh...
I-If you turn around, I'm gonna slap you.
Are you gonna hop on already, or what?
Giddyup!
Whoa!
This is so cool! You can already see the lake from here!
No, youcan see the lake. I...
Okay, if you want, you can ride on my shoulders later.
Let's get a move on, horsey.
We're heading north-northeast!
Okay.
It almost flew up my nose!
We got people staring at us now.
Our own audience.
Go on.
Wave back, or he'll think you're rude.
Nope, not gonna happen.
Do you want me to get off you now?
Mnh-mnh.
You're fine right where you are.
Whoa!
Aah!
I heard this weird rumor in the village yesterday
about how if you go deep enough
into the forest, you'll see...
Them.
Huh? See who?
Ghosts.
Y-Y-You mean, like,
those in-game, astral-type monsters, right?
No, not those.
Realghosts.
They say the tortured souls of the monsters hunted here
come back to wander the forest at night.
We're almost there.
The place the rumor mentions?
About a week ago, a carpenter hiked into
the forest to get some wood for a project.
He stayed so long that before he knew it, it was night.
As he walked along, he caught a glimpse
of something white standing by a tree.
Aah!
Was it a monster or something else?
The white figure slowly walked toward some trees, and...
Hey, look!
Uh, huh?
Aah!
I want to get down! I want to get down!
Uh?
What's wrong with you?
It's... it's over there!
What are you talking about?
Uh, you got to be kidding!
Hold on.
That's not a ghost!
Oh, wait, K-Kirito!
Oh, geez!
It's another player!
Yeah...
But there's something really strange about her.
What do you mean?
She doesn't have a cursor.
Maybe it's some kind of bug.
Yeah, maybe it is.
What's a little girl like this doing playing s.A.O.?
Uh...
I guess we'll find out when she wakes up.
But we can't just leave her out here till she does.
Let's take her home with us.
Yeah, okay.
Well, one thing's for sure.
She's not an NPC.
We didn't have any trouble moving her here.
Yeah, that's true.
She can't be that.
If she were, she would've given off a
warning when you picked her up, like other NPCs.
You're right, and she's
definitely not a quest giver either.
Our quest log would've been updated
as soon as we interacted with her.
She has to be a player. She'd probably been
out there for a while, wandering around, lost.
That's the most likely scenario.
Yeah, but what was she doing out there?
Your guess is as good as mine, but she has
to have a parent or guardian out there, right?
Mm-hmm.
She had to have logged in with someone from her family.
I just hope they're safe.
Hey, do you think she'll wake up?
Yeah.
If her body hasn't disappeared, that means signals
are still being transmitted to and from her nervegear.
She's in some kind of sleep mode.
I'm sure she'll wake up soon.
And the sooner, the better.
Yeah.
Hey, Kirito?
I wonder, did she log into S.A.O.
By herself or with her family?
Or has she been alone here all this time?
Sleep well.
Please hurry and wake up tomorrow.
Uh...
Huh?
K-Kirito, wake up!
Good morning.
Something wrong?
Hurry! Get over here!
Huh?
You woke up!
Thank goodness!
Do you remember what happened to you?
Mm...
Mnh-mnh.
Okay.
How about your name?
My...
My name is...
I think my name is...
I think...
Yu-i.
Yui.
That's it... Yui.
That's a cute name.
Nice to meet you.
My name's Asuna.
And this is Kirito.
A-una?
Ki-to?
Try to remember.
What were you doing in the forest?
And do you know where your mom and dad are now?
Um...
I-I don't know.
I-I can't remember anything.
Oh, no.
Well, you're awake.
Can I call you "Yui"?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Then I want you to call me "Kirito."
Can you say "Kirito"?
Ki-to.
It's Kirito.
Kirito.
Mm.
Kito.
That's okay. Maybe it's a little hard.
How about you call me whatever's easier for you.
Mm.
Daddy.
M-Me?
Auna is...
Mommy.
Mm...
Okay.
I'm mommy. That works.
Mommy!
Mommy! Daddy!
You must be hungry!
How about breakfast?
Okay!
Hmm?
Here you go, Yui.
This one's yours.
Oh, I don't know, Yui.
This one's super spicy.
Oh.
I want the same one that daddy has.
Okay.
If you think you're ready for it, I won't stop you.
You only live once, right?
Uh...
Ahh...
Mmm.
I like it.
Wow, you've got an iron stomach.
We can do a full course of
extra-spicy food tonight if you want.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let's not get carried away.
I'm not cooking anything nuclear.
You heard the lady.
You heard the lady?
So...
What do you think?
I don't know.
She's a blank slate...
no memories.
It's really weird.
Yeah, I know.
It's like she's a baby again.
I just...
I don't...
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
I get it.
You want to take care of her...
At least until she gets her memory back.
Uh, yeah, but...
But it's a catch-22.
We have to get back and clear the game.
Otherwise, it'll take that much
longer for Yui to be free of it.
I know.
For now, we'll do
what we can.
Judging by the gear she's got in her
storage, she hasn't been out in the field much.
We'll check the town of beginnings.
Maybe there, we can find out if she's got family.
Okay.
Look, I don't want to say goodbye to her either.
Huh?
You really don't?
I don't know what it is.
I mean, we just met her and all.
But having her here, it's made
our little cabin feel like a real home.
Don't you think so?
Mm-hmm.
This doesn't mean we'll never see her again.
But look, if she's got a family out there,
they're probably worried about her right now.
Okay.
When she wakes up, we'll go to the town of beginnings.
That place is army territory.
It might be a good idea if we go in
fully equipped, ready for anything.
Yeah, we better be careful.
Mommy...
Daddy...
It's been forever since I've been back here.
Me too.
What do you think?
Huh?
Do any of these buildings look familiar?
Uh...
I don't know.
Don't get down about the town of
beginnings is a really big place.
So, how about it?
Should we start at the central market?
Hey, Kirito?
Yeah?
Do you know how many players
are here right now in the town?
Hmm.
Good question.
Last I checked, there were 6,000
players still alive in S.A.O.,
and about 30% of those people, including
the army, live in the town of beginnings,
so maybe a little less than 2,000?
Then doesn't it seem a little dead around here?
You're right.
Leave those children alone!
Look, it's that daycare bitch!
We've been waiting for you!
Uh...
Leave them alone, and let them go!
You make it sound like we're
doing something illegal, baby cakes.
We're just teaching 'em how things work
around here, making sure they pay their way.
It's all part of the army's job, ma'am.
That's right.
Everyone's got to pay taxes around here.
Gin, kain, Mina, are you okay?!
Help me, Sasha, please!
Save us!
They just want your money, so
give it to them, and it'll be okay!
We tried, teach, but they said it's not good enough!
You know, you deadbeats owe us
a hell of a lot in back taxes.
You need to drop all the equipment you got right there,
including your armor.
Come on, honey, don't be shy.
No way!
Let me through or else!
Stand aside!
Huh?
Huh?!
You guys are gonna be okay now.
Pick up your stuff.
Uh, okay.
What the...
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey, who the hell are you?!
This is army business, so get the hell out of our way!
Hold on.
Huh?
I got this.
I guess you're all new in town, yeah?
'Cause we're with the liberation
army, and you do not mess with us!
Kirito, take care of Yui.
Uh-huh.
What?
Agh!
Unh!
Ohh!
Oh, don't worry...
it's a safe zone.
Your HP won't deplete, no matter what I do.
There's just a feeling of getting knocked off your feet.
Even so, a fight with me is still
gonna scare the hell out of you.
No! No, don't!
Agh!
Unh!
Don't just stand there, you assholes!
Do something!
Uh...
Awesome!
That was so awesome!
Oh, I've never seen anything like that before!
Yeah, you were so cool!
Yeah, thanks!
Thank you for helping us out!
Please, please?!
You see that?
You're mom's crazy-strong, isn't she?
Huh?
Their hearts...
Everyone's hearts are...
Yui?
Uh, what's wrong, Yui?!
Huh?
Yui, what's the matter?
Their hearts...
Yui!
Yui, did you remember something?
I...
I-I...
I was never here...
In this place.
I was always alone...
In the dark!
No, Yui!
Mommy, I am scared!
Mommy!
My god...
Yui...
What was that?
Next time: "Yui's Heart".