Asuna!
Asuna!!
Oh, Asuna.
I've turned into the biggest crybaby.
Haven't I?
Me and him, we look nothing alike.
I'm off to practice!
I'll see you later, okay?
Hu...
Good morning, Sugu.
U-Uh, g-g-good morning.
Uh... oh, eh, eh, uh!
God, seriously?
Instead of lurking, you should have said something.
Yeah, well, you were practicing,
and I didn't want to bother you.
I wasn't really practicing.
I guess it's just habit, is all.
Oh. Huh.
At least you've been keeping it up.
It's light.
What?!
It's not light.
It's timber bamboo.
Oh. Yeah, right.
I meant, like...
It's lighter than I thought.
It's not as heavy as what I'm used to.
Oh.
What the heck's he comparing it to?
Ahh.
Hey, you think maybe we could give it a go?
What, you mean a match?
Like, seriously?
Yup.
A real match with pads and stuff?
Mm...
Yeah, on second thought, no contact.
I mean, I'd feel like crap if I ended up hurting you.
I still got to dig out grandpa's old gear.
How 'bout we spar in the dojo?
Whoa!
You sound pretty darn confident for
someone who's been asleep for two years.
For your information, I was a
quarterfinalist in the middle-school nationals.
Seriously, though, are you sure you're feeling up to this?
You might want to take it easy.
I've been doing rehab in the gym every
day, so I think I'm gonna be good to go.
Eh... hm.
What kind of stance is that supposed to be?
Don't you worry about
this is my own style. Okay.
Ready?
Uh-huh.
His head's wide open.
That'll be my first strike.
Huh?
It's an odd stance, but he looks composed.
Okay, then.
Oh, my god!
A-A-Are you okay?
Okay, okay. You win.
You sure are strong, Sugu.
You'd mop the floor with Heathcliff.
Maybe you should sit down or something.
I'm good.
Thanks for the match.
Uh... huh.
Uh...
D-Did I hit you too hard?
No, I'm okay!
Just years of habit.
Let's see.
My footwork was okay, but the attack sucked.
I guess I can't use the sword skills I
acquired, unless I got the system helping.
I have to say, I'm really surprised.
I mean, how long have you been practicing behind my back?
Oh, you know...
It iskinda fun, after all.
But you never know... maybe I'll take it up again.
Really?!
Oh, seriously?!
Yeah, sure.
You want to be my teacher?
Are you kidding? Of course!
We'll train together, like we used t...
After I build up some more muscle, okay?
I've been practicing, too.
Want to know what?
Huh?
Nope. I'll keep it a secret.
That is so not cool.
You going anywhere today?
Oh.
I don't know.
I guess... The hospital.
Oh, you are?
That's nice.
Her name's Asuna, right?
You... visit her a lot.
Uh-huh.
As much as I can.
It's the only thing I can do for her.
Anyway, Sugu, it's myturn to make breakfast today.
It'll be ready by the time you finish your shower.
Okay.
It's been two months since I beat Heathcliff.
Two months since I beat the death game.
When I woke up, I talked to someone
from the ministry of internal affairs.
I told them everything I knew
about S.A.O., and in exchange,
they told me where Asuna was.
I found out she was nearby, in Saitama.
Asuna's family admitted her
to to korozawa general hospital.
I also found out that besides her, there's
about 300 other players who haven't woken up yet.
Akihiko Kayaba's still missing.
And people think he's keeping the
players in their comas as part of his plan.
S.A.O. isn't over.
Not by a long shot.
Asuna.
Kazuto.
Sorry... I didn't know you were here.
Thank you for coming.
Hello, Mr. Yuki.
I hope it's okay I'm here.
Please.
You can visit whenever you like.
I know it makes her happy.
Sir.
Oh.
I don't think the two of you have ever met.
This is Sugou.
He's our company's director of R&D.
I'm Nobuyuki Sugou.
It's a pleasure.
I'm Kazuto Kirigaya.
You're the Kirito?
You're a hero. It's an honor!
Oh. I-I'm sorry.
I know we're not supposed to talk about
what happened inside the S.A.O. server.
But he's my partner's son, so it's fine.
Besides, I've always thought of him as part of my family.
Uh, actually, sir...
Speaking of family...
If I may, I'd like to make it
official as soon as possible.
This is sudden.
Are you sure this is really what you want?
I mean, you're still young.
You have your whole life ahead of you.
Thank you for your concern,
but my heart's set on it.
It sounds strange, but even though
she's like this, she's still beautiful.
I'd like to see her in that wedding dress.
You have a point.
The sooner we prepare ourselves
for the inevitable, the better.
Sorry to cut the conversation short.
I have a meeting to get to.
We can talk more about this later.
Kazuto, take care.
I heard you and Asuna were lovers in the game.
Is that true?
Uh-huh.
That is unfortunate.
It's going to make for one complicated
relationship between you and I.
In case you're curious, her father and
I were discussing her marriage... to me.
No way.
You can't do that.
You have a point.
It's true. We can't legally marry.
But if the Yuki family adopts me, it'll
be as if we are... on paper, that is.
Just like we're married.
The truth is, she's always hated
me... ever since we were kids.
Neither my parents nor hers know that.
If I proposed and she could speak,
I'm pretty sure her answer would be "no."
For me, this situation is...
Very favorable.
Stop it!
Who do you think you are?
You can't take advantage of Asuna like this.
"Take advantage"?
Oh, please.
If anything, I have a right to her.
Perhaps I should explain why.
Any idea what happened to argus?
They're the company that developed S.A.O.
I heard they closed it down.
Very good.
The lawsuits and damages they had to pay took their toll.
The company was forced into bankruptcy.
But the maintenance of the S.A.O.
servers was given to another company...
an electronics manufacturer,
where Asuna's father, shouzou Yuki,
is the C.E.O.... Rct progress.
And I work for the company's
full-dive technology R&D division.
In other words... and without getting into specifics...
you could say I'm the one keeping Asuna alive.
Now, I ask you... is it wrong for me to
expect a little compensation for my trouble?
I don't know what kind of promises you made to
each other in the game, and I don't really care.
But I don't ever want to see you here again.
Understood?
And from now on, stay away from the Yuki family.
We're having the ceremony here
on January 26th... a week from now.
Save the date.
Even though you're not welcome here
anymore, you should come to the wedding.
No need to thank me.
Well, Mr. Hero, you've got the room all to yourself now.
Say "goodbye" and get out.
Kazuto!
The bathroom's all yours!
Geez. What's wrong?
Why didn't you say something?
And turn on the heat. It's freezing in here!
Sorry.
I just... Want to be left alone.
Hey, how come you didn't turn the heater on?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's nothing.
Okay, but...
You're freezing.
You're gonna catch a cold.
I could run you a hot bath, if you want.
I'm so hopeless and weak.
I didn't want you to see this.
I swore, no matter what, you'd
never see me being such a crybaby.
Is it Asuna?
Is she okay?
Did something happen to her?
She's leaving...
Somewhere far away.
And I'll never... I'm never gonna see her again.
Hey.
Hang in there, okay?
If you really love someone that much, even
when things look hopeless, you can't give up.
I know I can't.
And I won't lie to myself anymore.
Gosh.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
Kazuto stood there looking at me, and then he
told me he wanted to know who his real parents were.
I was so shocked, I didn't know what to say.
He was only 10, but here's the thing...
somehow, he logged on to the citizen's
registration network and found the file!
That figures.
Sounds just like something he'd
I was so stunned, I couldn't think of a way to deny it.
So what do I do instead?
I tell him how my big sister and
her husband are his real parents.
Wow!
Mom?
I was wondering...
About what?
I guess about the way he's been since middle school.
He'd go into his room and play games online for hours.
You think it's 'cause he found out about his real parents?
No, not at all.
He was always into computers and technology.
By the time he was 6, he'd already
built his own computer out of spare parts.
If anything, he's like that 'cause
he's a huge computer nerd, like me.
Or so he thinks.
Well, I'm heading home and get dinner ready.
Don't stay too long, okay, Suguha?
Don't worry. I won't.
Happy birthday, kiddo.
He's my cousin, not my big brother.
I still have a hard time believing it.
My big brother.
But...
In the end, your heart...
Belongs to her.
Come on.
Wake up, Sugu.
It's morning.
I said you got to wake up now.
Not gonna have time to practice if you don't wake up.
Uh... Wha...?
Oh. Hey.
Morning.
Rise and shine.
Hiya, sleepy.
Um, I...
Oh, my god!
As weird as ever.
Just hang in there, okay?
She's right.
Yeah, she's right.
What the hell?!
Asuna.
Next time: "Land of Fairies".