Lure it to the village.
That's how we get the boss.
W-Wait... you can't be serious.
If we do, the boss'll go after the villagers.
Yes, that's the idea.
And while the boss is busy killing NPCs, we can attack it
and kill it.
But they're not just objects.
NPCs are different than rocks and trees!
L-Look, they're...
You think they're alive?
Really?
Uh...
In this game, they are just objects, and unlike
us, if they are killed, they can always respawn.
Sorry, but I'm not cool with that plan.
I'm running this operation, okay?
In case you forgot, I'm still
second-in-command of the knights of the blood oath.
You'll obey my orders, like it or not.
Hey.
What's with you guys?
Huh?
You and the second-in-command... you're
always getting into it, and not in a good way.
I guess we just don't click, Agil.
You can become powerful here on your own,
but if the day comes when someone you trust
invites you to join a guild, don't turn it down.
Well, she took my advice, but who knew she'd
join the top guild and be a floor-clearing bad-ass?
What are you doing?
Hmm?
Oh, hey. What's up?
Everyone in the assault team's working
their butts off to clear the dungeon,
and where do I find you?
Out here, taking a nap.
Even if you're a solo player,
you should take this more se...
Bet you didn't know this is Aincrad's nicest season.
Today's weather is at its optimal setting.
Huh?
It'd be a waste to have to go to work on a day like this.
Whatever.
I can't believe you.
Do you even understand what's going on?
Every day here is another one lost in the real world.
Yeah, but right now we're not in the
real world, are we're alive in Aincrad.
See?
Doesn't that breeze feel good?
And the sun?
Oh, come on.
The weather is always the same here.
If you laid down on the grass
for a little bit, you'd understand.
Hmm.
Mm.
Damn, would you look at that?
Oh.
Taking a nap in the middle of the day.
Some people sure got it easy.
Couple of lazy losers, man.
I can't believe she fell asleep.
Oh.
Huh?
What? Uh, uh...
Good morning.
You slept like a rock.
You get one meal.
Huh?
One meal... all you can eat, my treat.
Then we'll be even. Deal?
That's Asuna from the knights of the blood oath.
Really?
Yeah, they call her the lightning flash.
Who is the shady-looking guy dressed in black?
Well, anyway...
Mm-hmm.
Thank you for today.
Why?
For keeping an eye on me.
Oh. Sure.
The towns are supposed to be safe zones,
and unless you've agreed to a duel,
a player can't attack or kill you.
But when you're asleep, you're vulnerable.
Yeah.
Now we've got player-killers
who can cheat the duel system.
Duels are normally supposed to be tests
of strength, not a fight to the death.
But even if you duel in a safe zone, your h.P. Is
still gonna go down based on the damage you take.
All a sleep PKer has to do is manipulate a
sleeping player's finger to click the "okay" button...
the duel begins like normal.
But the sleep PKer is doing all of the attacking.
God knows how many times it's happened.
So, anyway, thank you.
Uh, sure. Anytime.
Well, you'd do the same for me.
Hurry! Pull it out!
I'll cut him down. You catch him.
Got it.
Help's on the way!
Damn it.
The only way he could have died in a
safe zone is if he was beaten in a duel.
That means...
Everyone, look for the player with the "winner" icon!
There's no one here! The room's empty!
So, any idea how this could have happened?
Well, there is always the obvious... there was a duel,
and the other guy impaled the victim with that spear.
Then he put a noose around his
neck and pushed him out the window.
Wouldn't you say that's about right?
Yeah, but I couldn't see the "winner" icon on anyone.
It hadto be a duel...
it's a safe zone, and a player died.
A duel is the only thing it could have been.
Or maybe not.
Either way, we can't ignore this.
I know.
As it is, a player takes huge
risks going outside a safe zone,
but if someone's found a way to PK Inside,
no one's going to be safe in the towns, either.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess we won't be going back
to the front lines anytime soon.
Listen, you're going to work
with me until we solve this thing.
Until we do, there won't be any time for napping, okay?
Okay, but you'rethe one who was napping.
Ow!
Listen up... did anyone see what
happened before that player died?
If someone did, please speak up.
Sorry.
I can imagine how frightened you are.
Could you tell us your name?
Sure.
My name is Yoruko.
Oh.
Was that you?
I mean, were you the one who screamed?
Uh, uh-huh. I-I knew him.
His name was Kains, and the two of
us used to belong to the same guild.
Anyway, we came here together today.
We were going to have dinner somewhere in town.
But we got separated in the Plaza.
I looked around for him, and then I
saw him hanging from that balcony, and...
Was there anyone else up there?
For a second there... I'm not sure... but I
think I did see someone standing behind Kains.
Mm.
And this person, had you seen them before?
Mnh-mnh.
Um, I know this is hard for you,
but think back and try to remember...
Could therebe someone, anyone,
with the reason to kill him?
Mnh-mnh.
Thank you for walking me back.
Sorry if it's out of your way.
No worries.
But we'd like to talk to you again
tomorrow if you're feeling up to it.
Okay.
So, what do we do?
Simple... we follow the only solid clue we have.
If we can find out where that spear came
from, it might lead us straight to the killer.
We'll need to find someone with an appraisal skill.
I mean, it's pretty obvious you don't have one.
No, I don't, and neither do you.
Oh, and by the way, try not to be
so rude when you're speaking to me.
Oh.
Uh, okay. Should I call you miss next time?
Mm.
Second-in-command?
Lightning flash?
Oh, never mind.
Call me Asuna.
Okay. Sure.
Back to the appraisal skill,
though... Do you know anyone who has it?
Hmm.
I've got a friend who does.
She's a weapons merchant.
But she's really busy these days, so I
don't think she'll have time to help us.
No worries... I happen to know an item
merchant who might be able to help us out.
Thanks, my man. Come back anytime.
Yeah. Whatever.
Looks like you're still running all the
suckers down with those hard deals of yours.
No way... Kirito!
Buy cheap and sell cheap...
that's my motto. I'm a businessman.
You know that.
That "selling cheap" part's a lie, though.
Don't go slandering my good name, brother.
Uh...
What the hell has gotten into you?!
You're supposed to be a solo player, man!
What are you doing hanging around with Asuna?!
I thought you guys hated each other's guts, straight up!
What's the deal?!
His h.P. Dropped to zero in a safe zone?
You sure it wasn't a duel?
Well, no one saw a "winner" icon.
And we can also rule out the murder being a sleep PK.
He was walking with Yoruko before it happened.
And, besides, his death was too
elaborate to be some random duel.
The PKer who did this had it planned out.
We're pretty sure of that.
And then there's this.
Hmm.
A player made this.
Really?
Who was it?
Can you tell?
"Grimlock."
Never heard that name before.
It's not one of the top blacksmiths. That's for damn sure.
Far as I can tell, there is nothing special about this.
Yeah, but it's something to go on, right?
Mm-hmm.
Is there, like, an item name listed?
You'll love it...
"Guilty Thorn."
There's a name for you. It kind
of fits, though. Don't you think?
Hmm.
Seriously? Guilty Thorn?
Here goes.
Wait! Stop!
What's the matter?
What do you mean, what's the matter?!
Are you out of your mind?!
That thing's already killed one person!
I know.
But we need to find out what
this thing's capable of, don't we?
Would you stop being so reckless?!
Oh.
Agil.
Would you please hold onto this for us?
Uh... yeah.
Mm.
So, uh, Yoruko, we, uh... we were wondering
if you had ever heard the name Grimlock.
Yes. I have.
Actually, until a few months ago,
he was in the guild with me and Kains.
Mm.
Listen, we took the spear that
impaled Kains to an appraiser.
We had him go over it pretty carefully,
and we found out Grimlock made it.
Can you think of any reason why he did?
Yes. I can.
I should have told you everything yesterday.
It's just... I couldn't.
It's something I've been trying very hard to forget.
But now I have no choice.
I should tell you about how my guild was destroyed.
When we formed it, "golden apple" was the name we chose.
Six months ago, we killed a rare monster.
It dropped a powerful ring that
raised a player's agility by twenty.
Some of us wanted to keep it for the guild.
Others wanted to sell it and split the earnings.
We couldn't agree, and in the end, we put it to a vote.
It was five to three in favor of selling it.
Our leader, Griselda, took it to
a large town on the front lines.
She was going to sell it to a
broker and was staying overnight.
We waited and waited, but she never came back.
It wasn't till later we learned
our worst fears had come true...
Griselda was dead.
To this day, I still don't know how she died.
No one's gonna leave a safe
zone with a rare item like that...
Too risky.
You think someone could've pulled a sleep PK On her?
Not if it was six months ago...
that method's still sort of new.
You're right.
But she wasn't a random victim, either.
No, the killer was after the ring.
It has to be someone who knew she had it, which means...
The killer is one of the seven others in our guild.
Yes.
We have our suspects.
Now we just have to figure out
who didn'twant to sell the ring.
I doubt the killer waited till
after Griselda sold the ring.
She was killed before she sold that's my guess.
Probably.
Tell us what you know about Grimlock.
Well, I guess, for starters, he was Griselda's husband...
Oh, but not in real life, just in the game.
Griselda was a powerful swordswoman.
She was beautiful and smart.
Grimlock was kind, and I can't
remember a day when he wasn't smiling.
They made a great couple and
got along as husband and wife.
If Grimlock is really the one
who murdered Kains yesterday, then
he's probably going after the three guild
members who voted against selling the ring.
Kains was one of the three who
wanted to keep the ring for the guild.
I was the other one.
Then who's the third person?
The other's a tank named Schmidt,
and he, the last I heard, is on the front
lines now with the holy dragon alliance.
Schmidt, huh?
I've heard that name before.
He's leader of the defense
unit of the holy dragon alliance.
He's an exceptional lancer.
Oh, yeah. Him.
Wait... do you really know Schmidt?
Well, I've run into him a couple
times while clearing bosses, so...
I need to see him right away.
Could you please take me to him?
If he is on the front lines, he
probably hasn't heard about the murder.
He needs to know before what
happened to Kains happens to him.
We'll help you get in touch with Schmidt.
I know someone in the holy dragon alliance.
He'll help us out. We'll visit their HQ.
Okay.
But first we should make sure she gets back to the inn.
Yoruko, you have to stay there, okay?
Seriously, don't go anywhere until we get back.
All right.
Okay, so, how do you think a murder
like this happened in a safe zone?
I can see three ways it could've.
Right off the bat, it's possible it was a fair duel.
Or maybe someone took advantage of a bug
that combines a bunch of different kill methods.
Yeah, I can see that happening.
And the third?
Used something to bypass the protection of a safe zone...
Some kind of skill, or maybe an item.
No, on second thought, that third idea is impossible.
What do you mean?
Because it's unfair.
I kind of hate to admit it, but it's true...
The rules of SAOare essentially
fair for every player in the game,
so there is no way the game
would allow murders in safe zones.
I see.
So that's what killed Kains. And you're
sure about the spear? Was it really Grimlock's?
There is no doubt.
But then why would he wait six months to kill him?!
Unless... wait... could he have stolen the ring?!
Do you think it's possible he killed Griselda after all?!
Does Grimlock want to kill the three of us
because we didn't want to sell the damn ring?!
Is that why he's after you and me now?!
Maybe Grimlock made the spear
for someone else from our guild,
and maybe they'rethe ones who killed Kains.
Or maybe...
Griselda has come back from the dead to get her revenge.
Huh?
A player can't kill another player inside a safe zone,
but something else, like a ghost, could.
Uh...
Oh.
I couldn't sleep at all last
night, so I stayed up thinking.
It was everyone's fault!
Everyone in the guild is guilty!
Her blood is on all our hands!
Our fate was sealed when that ring dropped!
We shouldn't have voted!
We should have done whatever Griselda told us to do!
Grimlock was the only one...
The only member of the guild who said
we should leave the decision to Griselda.
You see?
He's the only one of us who can avenge Griselda.
He's the only member of our guild
who has the right to avenge her.
You got to be kidding.
You got to be kidding!
Why now? After all this time, why kill us now?
You can't be okay with this, Yoruko! How can
you accept being killed over some stupid vendetta?!
Yoruko!
Next time: "Illusionary Avenger".