I want to see what virtual reality's like.
I wonder when I first thought that.
I used to hate virtual-reality games with a vengeance,
and I blamed them for stealing my brother away from me.
But later on, I got curious.
I didn't know why my brother loved them so much,
so I figured, maybe I should see why for myself.
I didn't know what to expect at first, but after a
while, I was surprised by how much I loved Alfheim Online.
It was amazing...
flying through the sky on my very
own wings, to fly as far as I wanted,
as high as I wanted, as fast as I wanted.
I'd give anything and everything for that.
I think I get it now.
I can see why my brother loves the virtual world.
Hold it, Leafa!
I thought I told you not to
call me that at school, Nagata.
Didn't I?
Yeah, you did.
Sorry, Suguha.
Idiot!
I'm sorry! I meant "Kirigaya"!
What do you want?
Uh...
Wait... why are you even here?
You got a release from taking
the high-school entrance exams.
They're not making you come anyway, are they?
Sugu...
Kirigaya!
I need to talk to you, so I've been waiting all morning.
Wait... you're not here for the exams, are you?
No.
The advisor for the kendo club
asked me to come in, that's all.
Well, what's up?
It's Sigurd and the others.
They all wanted to go hunting again this afternoon.
Sorry.
I won't be going out with those guys for a while.
Wait! What?!
Why not?!
I've got plans to head over to arun.
That's why.
But isn't arun at the base of the world tree?
Wait a second!
You... are you... you're not going with that Spriggan?!
Yeah...
Well... sort of.
I promised I'd show him how to get there.
But... have you thought about what you're doing, Lea...
...K-Kirigaya?
It's just so far away, and you guys
will be... Sleeping together, and...
don't get any weird ideas about it, you jerk!
Look, I've made up my mind, and that's that.
Say "hey" to Sigurd and the others for me.
See ya later!
All I'm doing is showing him the way.
That's all I'm doing.
Link, start!
Hey, there.
Been waiting long?
Not at all. I just walked in.
Actually, I was out shopping for gear.
Oh. That's right.
I should update my equipment, too.
I don't think thisis gonna be enough.
Okay.
I know a good weapon shop in town.
But do you have enough money? 'Cause they're not cheap.
Okay, money.
Wait.
This thing called "yuld"... is that money?
Uh-huh.
Hey, Yui?
Wake up. We're heading out now.
Okay.
Hm?
Why'd we come here?
Well, when flying long distances, it's
better if you start from a higher altitude.
That's what the tower's here for.
Oh. That makes sense.
You're kidding me!!
U-Uh... wait!
Come on! Let's go!
I want to get past the forest before dark.
Uh...
This way, slowpoke!
Leafa!
Oh. Uh, hello, Sigurd.
What's this I hear about you leaving the party?
Is that true?
Well... yeah, it is.
Do you have any idea how much that's
going to upset the other members?
You said it wouldn't be a problem
if I joined only when I had the time.
You also said I could quit whenever I wanted to.
Yes, I know what I said, but
you've been with us for a while now.
Everyone knows you.
If you leave us, it's going to
damage the reputation of the party!
Party members are not items.
What did you say?
Party members aren't items, so don't
expect them to be on call for you.
They're not your armor.
They're not your sword.
They're not your equipment.
You son of a...
I bet that big mouth of yours got
you thrown out of your own territory.
Let's see what you got, you piece of Spriggan trash.
Okay, that's it! Enough!
Kirito's my new partner, so leave him alone!
What?!
Leafa!
You're abandoning us to be a renegade, like him?
Yes.
I am.
And I'm not coming back... ever!
I don't give a damn about you
buzzing around my party members,
but if you think you can steal
them, then that's another story.
If you're stupid enough to waltz
into another race's territory,
then it's your own damn fault if you get killed, Spriggan!
This isn't the time or place, Sigurd.
If we gank this guy in front of all
these people, we're gonna look bad.
Once you cross our border, you better run and hide, Leafa.
I never expected you to betray me like this.
Never.
But you'll regret it soon enough.
I'm really sorry you got dragged into all that drama.
It's cool.
I'm worried about you, though.
Are you sure about this?
Uh...
Hey! Don't!
Wow.
This is an amazing view.
The sky's so close, it's like
I can reach out and touch it.
I know, right?
Whenever I look up at that sky,
everything else feels so small.
The timing couldn't have been any better.
I've been thinking about leaving here for a while now.
Okay, but... I feel
like it's sort of my fault you
left on bad terms with those guys.
Yeah, well, I don't think it
could have happened any other way.
What do you mean by "renegade"?
A renegade's a player who abandons their territory.
If you get branded as one,
everyone's gonna look down on you.
And you're cool with that?
Yeah.
I don't really care.
But I don't understand why everyone's
so quick to tie each other down like that.
I mean, what's the point in having wings, you know?
You humans are so complicated.
Honestly, your psychology is confusing.
Why do you act so horribly to each
other, when all you want is companionship?
What do you mean?
If it were me...
...I'd do that.
It's simple, straightforward, and efficient.
That's an amazing A.I.
Do allprivate pixies act like that, or just yours?
No, just mine, but she's a weirdo.
I guess you would know, huh?
"All we want is companionship."
Huh.
Leafa!
Hey, Recon.
How could you do this?!
You could have at least said somethingbefore you left!
Oh, sorry. I guess I forgot.
Why'd you quit the party all of a sudden like that?
Well... i didn't really think
too hard about it. I just did it.
What are yougonna do, though?
As if, Leafa!
It doesn't matter where you go.
My sword belongs to you and you alone.
I don't need it, but...
Thanks.
W-W-What I mean by that was,
I'm gonna go with you... wherever.
That is, I'd liketo go, but there's
something that's been bugging me.
What is it?
I can't really prove anything yet, but there's a few
things I want to look into some more, so I'm
gonna stay in Sigurd's party a little longer.
Hey, Kirito?
She has a habit of getting herself in trouble.
I'd appreciate it if you keep an eye on her.
Yeah. Sure.
Whatever you say.
And just to make sure we're
absolutely clear, Leafa is my...
we'll be in the neutral zone for a while.
Message me if you need anything.
Let me get this straight. In real life, he's your friend?
Yeah, something like that.
Mm-hmmmm.
Okay, what's that weird noise supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Just a little jealous, is all.
Now, that person's feelings, I can understand.
He must like you a lot, wouldn't you say, Leafa?
Do you feel the same way about him?
I-I don't know!
Geez!
Hurry up, you guys!
Let's try to make it all the
way to the lake without stopping!
Okay!
Unbelievable.
You can be so stubborn... seriously.
No matter what I do, I can't hurt you.
It's not like that body's real.
Why can't you just loosen up and enjoy yourself a little?
I don't expect you to understand, but to me,
it doesn't matter if my body's real or virtual.
You may not think that way, but I do.
Are you afraid you're going to be corrupted somehow?
Because if that's the case, you definitely need to
take things a little less seriously while you're here.
Well, I'm not planning on staying in this cage forever.
You'll see.
He'll come and save me.
Really? Who will?
That hero boyfriend of yours?
Goes by the name of Kirito?
Please.
You think I didn't know?
His real name's Kirigaya.
I met him the other day... in the real world.
I couldn't believe that weak little boy
was the same one who beat sword art online.
It took me a second to collect myself.
By the way, where do you think I met him?
In your hospital room.
As you were lying there, I told
him I'd be marrying you next week.
My god, you should have seen his face.
It was like all the color drained out of it!
I could barely keep myself from laughing!
Do you want to know what I think?
I'll bet you anything that brat won't have
the guts to put on the nervegear ever again!
That reminds me... I promised him I was
going to send along a wedding invitation.
I'm pretty sure he'll come.
He's going to want to see you in your wedding dress.
I know... I'm generous. The least I can
do is leave the little hero a few crumbs!
Well, I have to get going now, Titania.
I hope you don't miss me too much.
He's alive.
Kirito's alive!
8... 1, 1...
3, 2... 3, 2... 9.
Say-ah sleeta fim-glown veendo!
Hm.
Nice job.
Thanks for the awesome backup.
Our wings aren't gonna last much longer.
I think we should land down there for a bit.
Okay.
Hey, you getting tired yet?
Nope.
I'm good to go.
Okay, Mr. Tough guy.
I hate to break it to you, but flying's
out for both of us for a little while.
Huh? How come?
You see that mountain way over there?
It's above the altitude limit, so we can't fly over.
The only way anyone can pass
it is to go through the caves.
It's the toughest part of the trip between
Sylph territory and arum... or so I've heard.
I've never even been this far myself.
Guess we walk.
These caves... are they long?
Pretty long.
There's a mining town about halfway.
It's neutral territory, so we can rest there.
That reminds me... are you good
for time, or do you have to get back?
It's 7:00 at night in the real world.
Yeah, I can keep going for a while.
Cool.
I can, too, so let's keep going.
But since we're here, we should rotate out.
Wait... rotate?
Yeah.
We take turns logging out and
resting while the other keeps watch.
You can't log out when you're in the field, remember?
So we have to take turns logging out.
The person who stays behind guards the other's avatar.
Okay.
Sounds like a plan.
Ladies first.
Okay. Don't mind if I do.
See you in about 20 minutes.
Waaah!
Hey, Kazuto! What do you want to do for dinner?
I wonder if he's asleep.
I can't wait to get back there.
Kirito.
It's not that I'm in love with him or anything,
or that I've got someone to go on adventures with.
No.
I'm just excited I get to go places in a new world.
Hey, I'm back!
Did you see any monsters?
No, I didn't.
It's been pretty quiet this whole time.
What are you eating?
I bought a bunch at a shop before we left Sylvain.
I don't know what they're called, but
an NPC said you can only get them there.
I've never seen them before.
Sorry to leave you like this, but it is my turn.
Keep me safe, okay?
Get out of here before I hurt you!
No way! You can move when your master's logged out?!
Well, of course I can move.
You know, I'm my own person.
And for your information, he's
not my master. He's my daddy!
Yeah, about that...
I was gonna ask you before.
Why do you call him your daddy?
Did he, you know, um, set you that way or something?
He didn't do anything to my settings. He saved me.
He told me I was his daughter.
That makes him my daddy.
You see how that works?
Yeah, I... Guess.
Do you, you know... like him?
I'm sorry.
I don't understand what you mean by "like."
Are you serious?
It means you want to be with him all the time, and when
you're together, you get excited about being near him...
Or... something like that.
What's wrong, Leafa?
Nothing! It's nothing!
What's nothing?
What's going on?
What is it?
Did something happen?
Welcome back, daddy.
Leafa was just explaining to me what
it means when someone says they like s...
N-o-o-o!
I said it's nothing!
It's nothing!
You weren't there for very long.
I hope you got something to eat.
Yeah.
My family left something for me, so I'm good.
Sweet!
Well, come on, then. Let's get going.
Oh. Okay.
All right. Lead the way.
Is something wrong?
I don't know.
It sort of felt like someone was watching us.
Hey, Yui, there any players nearby?
No, I'm not sensing any other players.
Hmm.
It's possible someone put a tracer on us.
What the heck's a tracer?
A kind of tracking magic.
It looks like a small animal or an insect.
It tells the caster a target's position.
Can you dispel it?
Sure... if you can find it.
The thing is, if the caster's magic skill is
high, the tracer can track you from far away.
In a field this size, it'd take forever to find it.
Great.
Eh, maybe it's just my imagination.
Come on. Let's go.
Okay.
Next time: "The Legrue Corridor".