Oas narza Noh-toh raisa auga.
Whoa!
Everything looks way brighter now!
So thisis night-vision magic.
I guess spriggans aregood for something after all.
I don't know if that was a compliment or a diss.
You're practicing the magic you can use.
That'sthe important thing.
And projecting illusions is one of your specialties.
Illusions?
Yeah, to trick people with.
It's cool, but it's not gonna help anyone much in combat.
But you never know.
In a life-or-death situation, your lame
Spriggan magic might actually come in handy.
Now, thatwas a diss.
Se-ah uraaza Noh...
Noh-toh?
No, you're just memorizing the words.
You have to learn what the words of power mean
first, then match them with the effects of the magic.
That's how you memorize spells.
Ugh!
I never thought I'd be in a game and have
to memorize words from a different language.
Oh, and just so you know,
the higher-ranked spells have about 20 words.
Holy crap.
I'll just stick to fighting, then.
Would you quit complaining?
Oh, someone's messaging me.
Sorry... I have to get this.
Sure.
It's Recon again.
It's probably nothing, but I'll check anyway.
It says, "I was right.
Be careful. S."
That's it.
What's that mean?
"S"...
Sa... shi... su...
ohhhh.
What's wrong?
Oh... nothing.
Daddy! I'm picking up movement behind us.
Are they monsters?
Unh-unh.
They're players... a lot.
12 total.
You're kidding.
Ohh.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
We better take cover.
Okay, but where?
Ha!
Just leave everything to me.
Hey! Easy!
Shick shaalu ohbis grown loputoh!
We can talk, but we have to be really quiet about it.
Anything louder than a whisper,
and it's gonna break the spell.
Okay.
They'll be coming into view soon.
What is that?
You see it?
Huh?
No, I can't see anything.
I can tell it's not a player.
It's got red eyes...
kind of like a bat.
Why'd you break our cover?
Because that thing out there's
a high-level tracing searcher!
We have to destroy it!
Ekku skeetoh tutoogue sumahl streeda!
Come on! We got to go!
Can't we just hide behind one of your spells again?
They already know we're here.
That tracer had us pegged.
Hiding's not gonna do us any good.
Besides, that bat was a fire element familiar.
That can only mean the ones who are tracking us are...
The salamanders.
What's a party of salamanders doing way down here?
Whoa!
Check out the lake!
Looks like we're gonna get away!
Watch where you're going, or you'll fall in!
Oh, crap!
Oh, damn it!
Unh!
That won't work.
Why didn't you tell me that before?
Oh, right... like it's my fault you're in a hurry.
It's an earth-magic barrier,
you can bash on it all day, and it won't destroy it.
Can we jump in the lake and swim around it?
Nope.
At least, not unless you want to be lunch.
The water's filled with high-level monsters.
The undines are the only ones who
can take those kinds of things on.
Then I guess the only option left is to fight.
I'm not gonna argue with that, but it won't be easy.
If the salamanders have high-level
earth magic, it can only mean one thing...
they have a powerful mage on their side.
Leafa...
I know you're good with a sword,
so don't take this the wrong way,
but could you back me up from here on in?
I need you to stay behind and focus on healing me.
That way, I can fight harder and not worry about my HP.
They're targeting him with everything they got!
Leeza foruk!
Randol dorotoh!
Kirito!
Soo fillah haydl astaloo prot-to su-paal bhaa-ni!
Uh-oh.
Prottoh supaal baani!
What do we do?
He's gonna run out of HP at some point!
That's enough, Kirito!
If we lose, it'll just mean a
couple extra hours of flying!
Let's give up while we can!
No way.
As long as I'm alive,
I'm not gonna let anyone in my party die.
I won'tlet that happen again!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
What the hell?!
What's he doing?!
Hurry!
This is your only chance!
What do you mean?
You have to use all the mana you have!
Hurry and focus on shielding
him from the next magic attack!
Uh, okay.
But I don't think it's gonna help.
Ekku balpa eh-in brandoh muspeeeek karrah breasta.
Soo shalu lindoh ashee-nya baatoh Aimee oh-gu!
Baa-ni stay-pah.
Sveldoh!
Raahn-dol doro-toh!
Do it now, daddy!
Se-ah uraaza no-toh deeptoh!
He's using illusion magic.
But all that's gonna do is make
him look like a giant monster.
Is that... Kirito?
Idiots!
Don't break formation!
It's not real! Don't be afraid!
He can't hurt us if you stick
to the plan and stay in formation!
Hit him with an explosion spell!
Ecku balpa!
Eh-han!
Yay!
Retreat! Retreat!
Retre-e-e-e-e-at!!
Aah! Aah!
No!
Stop!
Wait, Kirito!
Hold on! Don't kill him!
Isn't my daddy amazing?!
Ow, my...
aah!
Okay, if you want to live, you better
tell me who sent you ass-hats after us.
Never.
Kill me if you want!
You got it.
Oh, man!
Now, that was cool!
That was an awesome fight!
Hehhh?
Your plan wasn't shabby, either.
If I was alone, I wouldn't have
lasted a minute against you dorks.
What are you telling him that for?!
Let me handle this.
Listen up.
I want to see if you and me can make a deal.
Check it out. Those are all the items
and yuld I won after beating your asses.
All you have to do is answer my
questions, and they could be yours.
Sound good?
Seriously?
Totally.
Ugh. Men.
M it's like they forgot we're even here.
Earlier this evening, I got an urgent text from G-Takusu.
He's the leader of the mage squad... or usedto be.
Anyway, I got this text telling us all to meet him here.
And when I showed up, he said he needed
12 of us to go on a hunt for two players.
At first, I thought it was overkill, but,
well, he said you guys took
out Kagemune, so it made sense.
Who's this Kagemune guy?
He's the leader of the lancer squad,
and he's known for hunting sylphs.
Yesterday, he got creamed in a fight and had to retreat.
That was you guys, wasn't it?
Wait.
Why's G-Takusu so interested in getting us out of the way?
The order came from the top.
Something about you "interfering with the plan."
Yeah? Whatplan?
Hey, I'm just a grunt.
They don't tell me anything.
But I'm pretty sure something
really big's about to go down.
When I logged on today, I saw this big-ass
swarm of salamander troops heading up north.
No way.
They're gonna go try to clear the world tree, aren't they?
I doubt that.
Someone figured that to take
the tree, the whole army would need
ancient-weapon-class equipment,
and we can't afford that stuff.
Hmm.
That's everything I know. I promise.
You weren't lying about your end of the deal, were you?
No.
I'm a man of my word, partner.
Hey.
That big, ugly monster that was tearing everything up...
was that you or an illusion?
Yeah...
I don't remember.
Wait... you don't know?
Not really. It just happens sometimes.
In the heat of battle, I'll snap
and can't remember a thing after.
Whoa. Scary.
I think I remember most of what
happened this last time, though.
Like, I know I used that spell Yui suggested.
Do it now!
I also remember getting huge.
That was cool.
I remember losing my sword and then... grabbing people.
And you were chomping down on them. Remember that?
Oh, yeah.
I totally felt like a monster...
all eating people and everything.
So, uh... What did they taste like?
Kinda like grilled meat just before
it gets burnt... all crispy and...
Okay, good! Sorry I asked!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Wow!
So, this is legrue!
Ow! That hurt.
Then you shouldn't be biting people.
I'll say.
Why is everyone ganging up on me?
I was trying to break the
tension with a stupid joke, is all.
Bite me again, and I'll cut you in half.
Yes, ma'am.
Ugh.
Oh, look!
Hey, I just remembered something.
Hmm?
Right before those salamanders attacked
us, you got a message from your friend.
Oh! I totally forgot!
Recon's not online.
Maybe he's asleep.
Okay, well, why don't you log out and give him a call?
Hmm.
Yeah, I think I better check in with him.
I'll only be gone a sec.
Wait for me here, okay?
Yui, would you please keep an eye on my avatar?
Me?
Yeah, I need to make sure your dad
doesn't mess around with it while I'm out.
Copy that, ma'am.
You got to be kidding.
Hey, Nagata.
What's with all the calls?
What do you want?
You picked up! Finally!
Where were you, Suguha?
I was dealing with some in-game stuff.
W-We got trouble! Like... like big trouble!
Sigurd's coming after us!
A-And that's not all!
He betrayed Sakuya, the Sylph commander!
Betrayed her?
How?
Start from the beginning and
tell me everything that happened.
But we're running out of time!
Okay.
Remember when the salamanders
ambushed us in the ancient forest?
Well, didn't that whole setup
seem a little... Weird to you?
I don't know. Not really.
Why do you think it was weird?
Remember how Sigurd said he'd be the
decoy and then he lured three of them away?
Yeah, now that you mention don't
you think it was out of character?
I mean, usually, he'd make someone else do it, right?
Yeah... i guess.
I mean, you're right... it's
weird... but what's your point?
Okay, here it is.
I found out he's been working as a spy for
the salamanders... probably for a while now.
What?!
Do you have proof, or did you just hear about it?
Remember how I said something was bugging me?
Well, I used a transparency spell,
and I've been following Sigurd all day.
I tracked him to a back alley.
And I saw him and a couple
others put on invisibility cloaks.
They were up tosomething.
That's for sure.
I followed them down into the sewers, where
these two sketchy guys were waiting for them.
I couldn't believe it.
They were salamanders!
They were a little ways away from
me, so I couldn't hear everything.
But I heard the salamanders say they put a tracer on you.
Uhhh!
Keep going.
Then what?
The salamanders caught me.
I'm still in the sewers, paralyzed by the poison arrow.
Well, now I know why you kept calling me I.R.L.
There's something else.
Sakuya is supposed to form an
alliance with the cait sith today.
The meeting's in neutral territory, and
she's heading there right now... in secret.
Sigurd knows about it, too.
He's gonna show up at the signing
ceremony with his goons and attack it!
Ahhh...
We have to hurry!
Hey, welcome back, Leafa.
Yeah, welcome back.
Kirito, I have to leave.
Why?
Sorry, but there's something I
have to take care of right away.
If I had time to explain, believe me, I would.
But I can't.
And I don't think I'll be coming back here, either.
Then I guess you'll just have to explain it me on the way.
Huh?
It'll take a while to get out of here 'cause we can't fly.
That's enough time, right?
Yeah, right.
40 minutes from now, in the valley of the butterflies,
the leaders of the sylphs and the
cait siths are gonna have a meeting.
Mind if I ask a couple questions before we get there?
Go ahead.
If the salamanders attack the sylphs and the
cait siths, what are theygonna get out of it?
For one, they'd stop the alliance from happening.
And if the cait siths find out their
leader died because a Sylph turned traitor,
they'd be pretty pissed, wouldn't they?
Superpissed.
It's a good way to start a war between the
cait siths and the sylphs, that's for sure.
It's also a good way to get rich.
If you take out the leader of a
territory, you get 30% of its money.
You can invade its hometown for 10
days and charge whatever tax you want.
No way.
Really?
Seriously!
Would I lie to you?
This isn't your problem, Kirito. It's a Sylph problem.
You don't have any reason to get
involved and risk your life over it.
If we go to the meeting, chances
are we won't make it back alive.
And we'll probably have to start over from Sylvain again.
But... this could work for you.
You want to get to the top of the world tree, so...
You might be better off working with the salamanders.
If they can pull this off, it'll give them the power and
resources they need to make an attempt at the world tree.
And since you're a Spriggan,
they might hire you as a mercenary.
So... if you wanted to kill me, you could.
I wouldn't hold it against you.
It's just a game in the end.
Anything goes, right?
If you want to kill, you kill.
If you want to steal, you steal.
A lot of people think like that.
More than I care to know.
And in a way, I get it.
Even I used to think like that.
But none of it's true.
In a virtual world, there's things you
have to protect becauseit's a virtual world.
Someone special taught me that.
If you give in to your impulses in here,
it's gonna change who you are in the real world.
The player and the character are one and the same.
Leafa... you're a good person.
And I want to be your friend.
So it doesn't matter what the reason is... there's no
way in hell I'd ever attack a friend for my own benefit.
I couldn't live with myself.
Kirito, I...
Thank you.
Oh. Wow. I sounded pretentious, didn't I?
Sorry about that.
Unh-unh.
That was pretty cool.
Oh, crap!
We're wasting time just standing here.
We got to go.
Yui, lead the way.
You got it, daddy!
Here... give me your hand.
Okay, but, uh...
come on!
M-Monsters!
There's the exit!
Next time: "General of the Blazing Flame".