You catch anything?
Sorry, I didn't mean to sneak up on you like that.
My name's Nishida, and I'm a
fisherman... in the game, anyway.
Back in Japan, I was the head of network security
for a company called Toto high-speed Internet.
I'm Kirito.
Wait.
Wasn't Toto the company that... yup.
We were the folks in charge of
network security for this game.
It's a big one!
Yeah!
But I've caught bigger!
Whoa!
Awesome!
Thanks.
I'm good at catching 'em, but cooking 'em?
Yeah, not so good.
I'd love to make sashimi or a nice stew out of 'em.
But what's the point when I don't have any soy sauce?
I could go for fish baked with soy sauce
right now or with radishes and soy sauce, yeah.
Hey, uh, if you want, I just might
be able to help you out with that.
Wait! Say whaaaaaaaaat?!
Ahh!
That was an amazing meal.
I had no idea you could get soy sauce in this world.
Actually, I made it myself.
If you want, you can take some home with you.
Really?
Ma'am, my taste buds bow down before you!
Glad you liked it. By the way,
how high is your fishing skill?
I'm asking because Kirito hasn't
been able to catch anything yet.
Yeah, well, maybe if all the
lakes on this floor weren't so hard.
Well, actually, that's not true.
As far as fishing goes, the only lake that's tough
to catch anything in is the big one you were at today.
What?!
Why would someone design it like that?
Yes! Good question!
That lake is the home of...
The king of all fish.
Seriously?
Yup. We're old pals. I've had him on
the end of my hook quite a few times.
But he's so strong, he yanks the
pole right out of my hands every time.
I was wondering...
Do you have any plans for tomorrow?
I don't mind helping the old guy out, but how am
I supposed to do a switch move with a fishing pole?
You're the only one I know who can figure it out.
What if you catch it?
Will you keep it?
Is that even possible?
He is pretty cool, though, don't you think?
When you both showed up, I was like, "who is this person?"
Isn't it funny how people are
living normal lives in this world?
And since we're the ones on the front lines, their lives
have sort of become our responsibility, haven't they?
For me, I wasn't getting stronger for anyone else.
It was just about me staying alive.
Everyone expects great things from you now.
And guess what. So do I.
Talk about pressure, huh?
Yeah.
I promised I'd save everyone.
Hell of a thing to live up to.
Oh, well.
They'll understand if you take tonight off.
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
Can you believe all the people who showed up?
Well, here we go!
Thanks for your Patience, everyone.
Here comes today's main event!
It's about time!
Kirito, let's catch us a fish.
Yeah. Hmm?
How big's this thing supposed to be, anyway?
Okay, here goes nothin'!
Um, shouldn't you reel it in?
No, not yet.
Uh, Nishida?
Hang on. Not yet.
Now! I got the sucker!
Here!
Uh, switch?
Come here, you bastard!
Look! It's coming up!
I think I tired him out.
W-Where you goin'?! Hey!
Aah!
No! No! No! No!
Kirito!
Look out!
For what?
Aaaaah!
You ran away! You left me there to die!
Here it comes!
Whoa. It can run?
It's like a crazy lungfish.
Kirito! This is serious! That thing's comin' for us!
Hurry! Do something!
Yeah, I'm still thinking.
Guess I'll take care of this.
Run while you still can!
Nah, she'll be fine.
Save your wife, Kirito!
No! Watch out!
Wow.
That was badass!
You're Asuna, right?
What are you doing here?
Man, this is awesome!
I'm a big fan of yours!
Can I shake your hand?
Nice job, honey.
Heathcliff?
Come on, you've moped long enough already.
I know.
But it's only been two weeks.
If he needs us on the front lines,
then something must've happened.
Why else would he interrupt our vacation?
Yeah, but still...
Let's at least hear what he's got to say.
Come on. Time to go.
We'll take care of this, then come back.
You got it.
Thanks for seeing us off.
I know we didn't get to spend
much time together, but it was fun.
Oh, well, it was an honor and a privilege.
Actually, before I met the two of you, I couldn't imagine
what the folks working to clear the game were like.
You might as well have been from another planet.
Being trapped in here for the past two years...
...even if I made it out alive,
I don't know if I can go back to my old job, my old life.
Maybe deep down inside, I've
given up hope of ever gettin' out.
I figured spending my time with a fishing
pole between my mitts was the best thing for me.
Pretty sad, huh?
Unh-unh.
That isn't sad. I get what you mean.
I used to feel the same as you... at first, anyway.
I felt lost and hopeless.
Every night, I'd cry myself to sleep.
It felt like each day that went by in
here was another day lost from my real life.
So I'd cry, and afterwards, I'd
go and fight as hard as I could.
All I cared about was winning, getting
stronger, and getting to the next floor.
But then, I was walking along and I
saw someone taking a nap in the shade.
I was so mad.
I told him he shouldn't waste his time like that.
And then he said... and I'll
never forget it... "this is Aincrad's best season,
and today's weather is at its optimal setting!"
He said it'd be a waste to go into
some dungeon on such a beautiful day.
So I tried lying down, too, and you know what?
I slept like a baby.
When I woke up, it was evening and
he was giving me the weirdest look.
Anyway, we formed our own party.
And that's when I realized something.
Even in a world like this, he
was really living.
He wasn't losing a day in the real world.
He was gaining a day here.
I learned so much from him.
And by "him," I mean Kirito.
When I thought about him before falling
asleep, I noticed I wouldn't have nightmares.
I began looking forward to seeing him again.
It was like, for the first time,
I was glad I was here.
Kirito is everything to me.
He's what the last two years were about.
He's proof I'm alive.
Why'd I put on the nervegear that day?
It's obvious. So I could come here and meet him.
You're still alive, right?
You must have something to live for, too.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
Life isn't so bad here.
No, it's actually pretty damn good.
I wish there was something I could
do to help, but well, there it is.
Good luck and be safe.
Don't worry.
We'll go fishing again.
Take care, okay?
Teleport... Grandzam.
The recon team was wiped out?
They were scouting for the upcoming boss fight.
It was a party of 20 members,
taken from five different guilds.
10 of them reached the center of the room...
Then the boss appeared.
And that's when the entrance closed,
cutting them off from the rest of the party.
They walked into an anti-crystal zone.
Precisely. And it couldn't have been more than
five minutes or so when the door finally opened.
The room was empty.
There wasn't any trace left behind
of the 10 soldiers or the boss.
You're kidding!
Now more than ever, clearing the game
should be everyone's number-one priority.
We're going to launch an attack
with the largest group we can assemble.
You can count on us to fight with you.
But this needs to be clear.
Asuna's safety is my priority.
If things start to get hairy
in there, I'm gonna protect her.
That's not negotiable.
A person with something to
protect is a strong ally to have.
I'm expecting a good fight from you.
Three more hours of waiting.
What should we do?
What's wrong with you?
There's something I have to ask you.
But I don't want you getting mad at me.
Instead of going to the boss
fight, could you please stay here?
Why would you ask that?
We won't be able to use teleport crystals,
so there's no telling what could happen.
I'm scared.
If anything happened to you, I...
So you want to go to someplace dangerous... Alone.
And you expect me to stay here, where it's safe?
You know what would happen if you didn't come back, huh?
I'd kill myself!
I'd never forgive myself for staying
behind, so what would be the point in living?
I'm sorry!
I guess I'm losing my nerve.
All I want to do is run away with you.
I don't care if we never make it back to the real world.
I just want to live with you
in our little house in the woods.
It'd be nice if we could do
that... be together every day forever.
Have you ever thought about
what's happening in the real world?
About what's happening to our bodies while we're in here?
A few weeks after the game was
launched, do you remember what happened?
Most of the players suddenly went
offline and stayed that way for a few hours.
My guess is that's when all the
players' bodies were being moved
to hospitals in the real world.
If that's where we all are right now, in hospitals,
barely being kept alive by machines, it's hard to
believe we're gonna survive like that for much longer.
So that means it doesn't matter
whether we clear the game or not anymore.
Everyone here's on a time limit.
And once that's up...
I-I want to... to stay with you forever!
I want us to go on real dates
and to really get married
and for us to grow old together!
That's why... that's why...
We don't have a choice.
We have to keep fighting.
Whoa.
Hey!
No way.
You guys are coming, too?
That's the best you got, "no way"?
Hey, man, I shut my shop down to
come out here and help get this done.
Brother, you're lookin' at a player
who's about as philanthropic as they come.
Then seeing as how you're so philanthropic, you're
not gonna mind if we take you off the drop list.
Hey, now!
Let's not be too hasty, man!
Hmm?
Corridor... open.
Well, here we go.
Feel that?
There's a bad vibe in here.
Yeah.
Everyone ready?
The knights of the blood oath will be out in front,
distracting the boss and blocking its attacks.
In the meantime, the rest of you have to stay
sharp and try to figure out its attack patterns.
I won't lie.
This battle will be hard.
But I have faith that we can and will prevail.
For our day of liberation!
Everything's gonna be fine.
I won't let anything happen to you... promise.
Make sure you protect me, too, okay?
Yeah.
You know I will.
Don't die, guys.
Same to you, buddy.
I'm gonna make a fortune off today's drops.
No way am I missin' out on that!
Forward to battle!
Nothing's happening.
Where is it?
Up there!
It's the skull...
Reaper!
Stay away from it!
Spread out!
This way!
Hurry! Run!
Ugh!
That was one hit!
Man, we are so dead!
Aah!
We can't even get in close enough to hit the damn thing!
Look out!
It's too strong!
If we block it together, we have a chance.
Come on, we can do this.
Okay.
Me and Asuna will deal with the scythes!
Everyone else, flank it and attack!
You heard the man!
Okay!
Aaah!
Hold still, baby!
Damn you!
Ready, Kirito?
Yeah!
Next time: "The End of the World".