Hmm!
There you go! All done.
You're the best, Liz. Thanks.
Sure! Anytime.
Hey, aren't you supposed to be
out hunting with the guild today?
Yeah. I had to take the day off, 'cause I
sort of have this little meeting with someone.
Oh.
I bet you have a little meeting!
No! It's not like that!
Uh, I have to get going!
I bet he must be pretty special, whoever he is.
Huh?
Did you say something?
Mm. Get going!
It's rude to keep your date waiting!
It's not like that! I... uh, whatever! See you!
I wonder if I'll ever find someone special.
Hmm.
Good enough, I guess.
I better get ready for the customers!
Perfect!
Welcome to Lisbeth's blacksmith shop!
Oh. Hi.
Uh, I was wondering if you do custom orders.
Hmm.
He doesn't look like he has that much money.
I can. The thing is, metal
prices are kind of high these days.
Oh.
Well, I'm not worried about the cost.
I just want the best sword you
can make as soon as possible.
Well, I make a lot of different swords.
But if you have any idea of the
quality of sword you want, I can make it.
Uh, sure. One sec.
Hmm?
So, I'm looking for something either
the same quality or better than this.
Oh.
An Elucidator!
This is the gnarliest magic sword a
person can get from a monster drop!
What do you think?
Mm.
How about this?
It's the best sword I ever forged.
I call it my masterpiece.
I don't know. It's a little light.
It should be.
I used a speed-type metal to forge it.
I'd like to test it, if it's cool.
Test it how?
You know, its durability.
What the heck are you doing?!
If you break your sword, I'm not responsible!
If it breaks, then that's too bad!
Uh...
You broke my masterpiece.
What the hell were you thinking?!
I'm sorry! I didn't think yours
was gonna break so easy, honest!
Are you saying my sword, my masterpiece
of a sword, was lamer than you thought?!
Yeah... something like that.
For your information, if I had the
right materials, I could make a butt-load
of swords that would shatter yours
into a million tiny, little pieces!
You got that?
Oh, yeah?
That sounds like the kind of sword I'm looking
for, as long as it can shatter mine, though.
Okay, smarty pants! But you have to
help me make it every step of the way!
Seriously?
Absolutely.
And we'll start by getting the metal for it.
I think I can handle that myself.
I'd rather not have you slowing me down.
Don't you dare insult me!
Believe it or not, I'm an expert mace-user.
Suit yourself. So, where do we find the metal?
Floor 55 on the western mountain.
There's a dragon there that eats crystals.
According to the legends, it's supposed
to store a rare metal in its body.
Floor 55, huh?
Yeah, I should go alone.
And they say that in order to get the
metal, you need to bring a master Smith along.
Still think going alone's a good idea?
I...
fine. Just keep quiet and stay out of the way.
Wha... keep quiet and...
by the way, my name's Kirito.
Looks like we're a party until we make that sword.
Yeah, whatever, Kirito!
Well, if you're gonna be like that, I can roll with it...
Lis-s-s-s-Beth!
It's cold!
Well, you should've brought a coat or something.
I didn't know floor 55 was going to be this freaking cold!
Huh?
Are you going to be okay without this?
You don't feel cold if you're disciplined.
If you're trying to piss me off, it's working.
It's warm, though.
I can't believe I'm out here all alone with this guy.
This is getting weird. What's wrong, Lisbeth?
Giving up already?
Not on your life!
And if you're gonna be a jerk about
it, you might as well call me Liz.
Okay, okay!
Got it, Liz.
Yeah, well, don't wear it out!
It's beautiful!
What's your problem?!
You should get your teleport crystal ready.
I know, I know. I'm doing it.
And I'm handling this part on my own.
Once the dragon appears, you're gonna
hide under one of those crystals over there.
Don't come out no matter what.
Oh, come on!
I'm not a noob!
If I want help you, I'll darn well...
Do what I say!
Mm-hmm.
Good.
Okay. Let's get going.
Hurry up and take cover!
Okay!
Watch out! It's a breath attack!
Wow.
And with that skinny sword!
Who is he?
Come on! Stop playing with it and finish it off already!
Damn it!
Don't come out yet!
What's the big deal? You've got it right where you...
Liz!
Hang on to me, Liz!
Are we still alive?
Yeah. Looks like it.
Drink one of these just in case.
Mm.
Thank you, you know, for... for saving me.
It's a little early to be thanking anyone.
We have to find a way to get out of here first.
Huh?
Can't we just teleport out?
Teleport... lindas!
No way!
Well, if we can't use crystals, that
means there should be another way out.
How can you be so sure there is?!
I mean, maybe this is some kind of trap
rigged to kill anyone who falls into it!
Good point.
Maybe it is.
Would it kill you to at least try to cheer me up?!
I think I have an idea.
Really?
Yeah.
We could try running up the wall.
Uh...
You're insane.
Maybe.
But that's all I got for ideas right now.
No way!
If I had more of a running
start, I probably would've made it.
Yeah, I don't think so.
This is kind of weird, isn't it?
This wouldn't happen in real life...
You know, going to strange places, meeting a
total stranger, and then sleeping next to them!
I mean, you actually tried running up that wall!
You really are a weirdo! You know that?
Well, excuse me.
Kirito, can I ask you something?
Ask away.
I'm all ears.
Why did you risk your life like that to save me?
I can't just sit back and watch someone die.
I'd rather die alongside them than do nothing...
Especially if that someone's a girl like you, Liz.
Wow, you really are an idiot.
You're the only person who'd think like that.
Hey.
Hold my hand?
Uh...
Okay.
It's so warm.
Huh?
Even though you and me are just
these 1's and 0's in a virtual world.
I know.
What the...
Whatcha doing?
Hmm? Here. Look.
Is this... What I think it is?
Uh-huh.
It's that special metal we came all this way for.
Like you said, the dragon eats crystals,
and they turn to this in its stomach.
No wonder it's hard to find.
Yeah, but you found it.
What's it doing down here, though?
This hole isn't a trap like we thought.
It's the dragon's nest.
Re-really?
Uh-huh.
And that's not just an ingot.
That's dragon excrement.
You know, poop?
Huh
well, I guess this means we got what we came here for.
Still stuck, though.
Wait.
This is supposed to be a dragon's nest, right?
Yep.
'Cause dragons are nocturnal,
so it won't be long before it
comes... home?
It's here!
Wha... Wha... Wha-what are you doing?!
Hang on to me, Liz!
Almost there!
Wow.
Look at that!
Kirito!
You know what?!
No, what?!
Don't freak out, but I'm falling in love with you!
I can't hear a thing!
What did you just say?!
Never mind!
A one-handed longsword, right?
Yep.
Make it awesome.
I didn't imagine
the warmth of Kirito's hands...
The way I feel?
As soon as I've made the best sword I can...
I'll tell him.
Whoa.
The sword is called dark repulsor.
One of a kind.
And it's not even in the info brokers' directory.
Go on. Try it.
Okay.
Good? Bad?
It's real heavy.
It's a good sword!
Yay!
It feels like you forged your soul into it.
Okay.
You held up your end of the deal.
It's time for me to pay up.
So how much?
Um... well...
I don't really need any money.
Instead...
I'd like to be your exclusive blacksmith from now on.
What do you mean, exclusive?
What's wrong?
I mean any time you get back from the field,
stop by and let me do maintenance on your gear,
every day, from now till the end!
Uh...
Liz, I...
Kirito...
I just...
I...
Liz! I was so worried!
Asuna?
Liz!
Where were you last night?! I tried messaging you, but
you didn't answer, and I couldn't track you on the map!
Uh, sorry.
I kind of got stuck in a dungeon.
A dungeon?!
You went all by yourself?!
Unh-unh. I went with him.
Huh?
K-Kirito?!
Uh, hey, Asuna!
Long time, no see!
It's been, what, like two days?
Well, this is a surprise!
I didn't know you wanted to check this place out!
I wish you would've told me! I could've come with you!
I'm sort of confused. You know each other?
Yeah.
Both of us are on the assault team, so...
He said he was looking to get a more powerful
sword, so I told him about you and your shop.
Oh.
Why is she acting like that?
I swear, if you did anything weird to her...
I-I didn't do anything!
Then why'd you stutter just now, huh?
You know, you could try to show a little more compassion.
I almost got killed!
Like that's my fault!
Don't I always tell you not to fight solo?!
Right.
I get it now.
If this guy said anything rude, you'd tell me, right?
Liz?
Uh...
You want to talk about rude, try this!
First thing he does when he
comes in is shatter my best sword!
What?! I'm sorry!
Oh, come on. You don't have to apologize for anything!
He might be a little weird, but he's not such a bad guy.
Don't screw this up, Asuna!
He's a keeper.
But I told you! It's not like that!
Liz?
Sorry. I have to go pick up some supplies!
I'll be right back!
But y-you're gonna leave the store?
Hold down the fort for me.
Later!
What?! No, wait! Li...
Lisbeth.
I almost got away with it.
A couple more minutes, and I would've
gone back to my usual, cheerful self.
Liz, I...
How'd you know I was here?
I scanned the whole town for you from up there.
Figures you'd do something crazy like that.
Sorry if I worried you.
I'm fine now.
Must be all the excitement.
I'm not used to having adventures.
Anyway...
Oh, just forget everything...
I said.
Okay?
Liz, I...
I just wanted to thank you.
See, I...
I don't know.
I always thought dying was better
than surviving day after day...
Living with the guilt.
Kirito.
But then we got stuck in that hole, and
I was really happy we were still alive!
I realized that even here, our
lives are real and have meaning.
Thank you for helping me see that, Liz.
I guess it's what I've been looking for this whole time.
Yeah. Me, too.
I know what you mean! I was also
looking for something... something real,
hoping I'd find it.
The warmth of your hand...
for me...
That was real.
Do me a favor, okay?
Tell Asuna what you told me.
Liz...
I'm fine, really!
The getting-over-it part... that's gonna take a while.
Until I do, promise me...
Promise me you'll put an end to this world.
Till then...
I'll keep doing what I do best.
I promise I will.
I swear I'll beat the game.
If you ever need your weapons or
gear repaired, my door is always open.
Sure.
Don't forget, now!
You'll always be welcome at my shop.
Next time: "The Sword Dance of Black and White".