What are you talking about?
Why should wehave to share
these healing crystals with you?
Your pet lizards hashealing powers, you know.
But you never fight on the front
lines, so who are you to talk?!
You don't need to use any crystals!
Of course I do.
You're the popular one around here, Silica.
I can't expect the boys to help me when I need it.
Oh, come on.
It's not like that.
Fine. I don't care.
You want my items, take 'em,
but I'm never going to team up with you again.
I know there's a ton of other parties out
there who'd love to have me on their side.
Wait! Don't go! Silica!
I'm out of healing crystals!
Pina!
Pina! Pina!
Pina.
Pina!
Don't leave me all alone here.
What's that feather?
It's Pina, my best... friend.
You're one of those beast tamers, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
If I got here sooner, I could have saved your friend.
No. It's all my fault.
I was stupid to think I could
make it through the forest on my own.
Thank you for saving me.
You did what you could.
That feather...
Check and see if it has an item name attached to it.
Huh?
Hey, don't cry.
That mean's Pina's heart's still here.
There's a chance you can revive.
No way. Really?
Mm-hmm.
On the south side of floor 47,
there's a field dungeon called the hill of memories.
I heard somewhere that the flower
growing at the top can revive familiars.
Floor 47, huh?
I'd offer to go get it for you.
All you'd have to do is pay for the trip.
The thing is, the flower won't bloom
unless the familiar's master's there.
Thank you so much for telling me about it.
If I work hard to raise my level, then someday I could...
Sure, but the time limit's three days to revive it.
No way.
It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry, Pina.
It's okay.
You have three days.
Take this equipment.
It should boost you 5 or 6 levels, and if I
tag along, I'm sure everything will work out.
But... why would you do all this for me?
I'll tell you, but only if you promise not to laugh, okay?
I promise I won't.
All right.
It's because you look like my little sister.
I'm sorry.
Um... i know this isn't enough col to pay you back, but...
no, it's cool.
Besides, it works with why I'm here.
We'll be helping each other out.
Huh? Okay, then.
My name's Silica.
My name's Kirito.
I guess we'll be working together for a little while.
Hey, look! It's Silica!
Huh?
It took you a long time to get back.
We were getting worried.
Um...
You want to team up with us?
We'll take you wherever you want to go!
That's really nice of you to offer, but...
Well, I've sort of already agreed
to be in a party with him, so...
'Kay, later. Bye.
I didn't mean to put you on the spot like that.
Didn't know you had fans. You must be popular.
No.
They don't take me seriously.
They want me to be their mascot.
Maybe they're right.
They call me dragon tamer, and
I guess... it went to my head.
Don't worry about it.
Huh?
We'll make it in time, promise.
Okay!
Do you live around here, Kirito?
I'm on floor 50.
It's kind of far, so I was
thinking of getting a room tonight.
If you stay, I'll take you out for some cheesecake!
It's really good here!
Well, if it isn't Silica.
Wow, you made it out of the forest alive.
Good for you, girl.
Something wrong?
Oh, no. Nothing.
Hang on.
What happened to your little friend the lizard?
Did it run away?
Pina died saving me.
But... I'm gonna get Pina back!
Really?
I guess you'll be heading for the hill of memories, then.
I wonder if you'll be able to clear it at your level.
Of course she will.
It's not that difficult a level.
Oh, god, this girl's seduced anotherplayer.
No, it's not difficult, but you don't look thatstrong.
Come on.
Why does she have to be so mean?
Well... Is sword art online your first mmo?
Uh-huh.
A lot of people's personalities
change when they play games online,
and some actually like playing the game as the bad guy.
You see how our cursors are green?
Well, if you commit a crime against another
player, your cursor's gonna turn orange.
Then they become what's called a red
player... the worst, also known as player-killers.
They're all about murder.
They kill other players?!
In a normal game, they role-play as the
bad guy, have some laughs, and it's cool.
But... sword art online isn't normal.
It's definitely not a game.
Kirito?
I'm sorry.
Well, I think you're good, so...
I mean, you saved me, after all.
Looks like youcheered meup instead.
Thank you, Silica.
Aaah!
Wow, where the heck is our cheesecake already?!
Excuse me!
Our dessert hasn't shown up yet!
I wonder if he'd laugh if I told
him I wanted to talk some more.
Silica?
You still awake?
Kirito?!
I forgot to tell you some stuff about
floor 47, but it can wait till tomorrow.
No, now's fine!
Actually, I was just thinking I should ask you about...
that was so close!
Uh, what's up? Something wrong?
No! Nothing!
What's that thing do, Kirito?
It's a mirage sphere.
It's pretty.
This is the town area of floor
47, and that's the hill of memories.
I was thinking if we take this route, we can...
hmm?
What's wro...
shh!
Who's there?!
Um... who was it?
An eavesdropper.
But they can't.
I mean, you can't hear through
a door unless you knock first.
But if your listening skill is high enough, you can.
It takes practice.
Not thatmany players have it.
Why would they want to listen to us?
Wow!
This place is like a dream!
I know.
The whole floor is covered in flowers.
That's why they call it the flower garden.
Couples!
Silica?
What?! Nothing!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing! Nothing at all!
Come on.
Okay.
What's that for?
If anything bad happens while we're in
here, I'm gonna tell you to warp out, okay?
When I do, use this crystal.
You can jump to any town with.
But...
No "buts." Use it.
I understand.
Let's get going.
If we take this path, it'll lead
us right to the hill of memories.
Um, Kirito?
Aaaaah!
Calm down!
That thing's not thatstrong!
Help, Kirito! Save me!
But don't look!
Save me, but don't look!
That'll be...
Difficult.
Darn you! Put me down! Now!
You see anything?
Not really.
I hope you don't mind me asking,
but what's your sister like?
Why do you want to know?
Well, you said I look like her.
I know it's not polite to ask about your real life, but...
What's she like?
I call her my little sister, but she's really my cousin.
Huh?
We were raised like brother and sister
since we were babies, so I doubt she even knows.
But I know, and I guess that's the reason I avoided her.
Our grandfather's really strict.
When I was 8, he made us take
classes at the local kendo dojo,
but after a couple years, I stopped going.
Grandpa beat the hell out of me for that.
That's awful.
Anyway...
Then my sister stood up for me and told him to stop.
She said she'd train hard for both of us.
And she did. She trained hard.
She even made it to the nationals.
She did? How awesome!
Yeah.
I've always felt guilty for putting her through that.
I wouldn't doubt it if she hates god knows
she could have been doing something else.
Maybe that's why I wanted to help you.
In a weird way, it makes me feel like I'm paying her back.
There it is.
If you don't mind me saying,
you're wrong.
I don't think she hates you at all.
She wouldn't work that hard
for you if she didn't like you,
promise!
And I bet she even loves kendo!
There you go again, making mefeel better.
Maybe you're right.
Man, I hope so.
Okay, then!
I'm gonna do mybest, too!
Aaaah!
Kirito!
Is that reviving flower around here?
Yeah. Over there.
Go ahead. Pick it up.
You sure it'll bring Pina back to life?
Uh-huh.
I'm so glad.
There's a bunch of strong monsters lurking around here.
Let's revive it when we get back to town.
I'm sure Pina would want it that way.
Okay!
Is something wrong?
Whoever's hiding out there, come out... now!
Rosalia?
If you saw through my hiding skill so easy,
your detection skill must be really high, swordsman.
Ooh!
It looks like you were successful
getting your hands on the pneuma flower!
Congratulations.
Now, hand it over before you get hurt.
What are you talking about?
No one's handing anything over, Rosalia...
Not to you or the orange guild,
or should I say titan's hand.
You're their leader, right?
Nice.
But Rosalia's cursor is green.
It's an easy trick.
The green members find their victims, then they
lure them straight to the orange players for the ambush.
That was one of your pals last night eavesdropping on us,
wasn't it?
Then the reason you were in that
party with me and the others was to...
How perceptive.
I was observing their strength and
watching them earn all that beautiful money.
You were who I was excited about, and
I was so sad when you left the party,
but then you told me you were getting a rare item.
What I want to know is if you knew
about us, why did you bring her here?
Are you dumb, or does she have
you wrapped around her finger?
Nope.
You're wrong both times.
See, I've been looking all over for you, Rosalia.
What areyou talking about?
Remember 10 days ago?
You attacked a guild called the silver flags?
The leader survived, four didn't.
Oh, the losers with no money.
Their leader went back and forth from the
warp point to the front lines, morning till night,
and with tears in his eyes, he begged
everyone he met to avenge his dead friends.
But he didn't want you killed.
No, he wanted you to go to prison.
Do you have any idea how he felt?
Can't say I do.
Only idiots take this seriously.
So what if we kill someone here?
There's no proof dying here means you're dead I.R.L.
Anyway, it's time you started worrying about yourselves.
Kirito, there's too many of them.
We should get out of here.
No, it's okay.
You'll be safe if you stay here.
Keep the crystal handy till I say so.
Okay, but...
Kirito!
Kirito?!
Dressed in black, one-handed, no shield.
Holy crap!
It's the black swordsman!
Rosalia, that guy...
He's the beater who plays solo on the front lines!
He's with the assault team!
No way! He is?!
Why would someone from the assault
team be all the way down here?
Go on! Take him out!
And take everything he owns!
Die!
I've got to save him.
He won't last!
What's going on?
What the hell, you idiots?
Kill him already!
400 in 10 seconds, give or take...
That's about the total damage
the seven of you can inflict on me.
I'm level 78.
I got 14,500 h.P.
My battle-healing skill auto-regenerates
600 points every 10 seconds.
We could stand here all day,
and you wouldn't get anywhere.
That's not possible!
Want to bet?
If your numbers are high enough, you're invincible.
Mmos that use leveling systems are unfair that way.
My client spent his entire fortune on this
warp crystal, and he'll get his money's worth.
It's been set to the coordinates of the prison.
And I'm sending all of you bastards there!
Well, I'm green, and if you hurt me, you'll go orange...
I'm a solo player, got it?
I don't care if I have to play
as orange for a couple of days.
I'm really sorry, Silica.
This whole time, I was using you as bait to catch 'em.
I thought you'd be scared if
I told you the truth about me.
I could never be scared of
you 'cause you're a good person.
Um... do you really have to go?
Yeah.
I've been away from the front lines for five days.
I need to get back.
I... I think it's cool you're with the assault team!
I could try for 100 years and never make it.
Um... I...
You know, levels are just numbers.
And a person's strength in this world is just an illusion.
Sure, it's cool and all, but there
are more important things than that.
We should meet up in the real world.
That would be cool 'cause I like having you as a friend.
Okay. We will. I promise!
Well, ready to revive Pina?
Yeah!
Pina, when you get back, I'll have
lots of stuff to tell you about...
About the amazing adventure I had...
... and about this one day when I
got to have my very own big brother.
Next time: "Murder in the Safe Zone".