[SERINUMA]
Ah!
Gorgeous!
[SERINUMA]
School is out.
We were all invited to
Shima's summer home
for a little fun in the sun.
It's so beautiful!
[NISHINA]
It's quiet out here.
Unfortunately,
not right on the beach,
but we'll have a lot of privacy.
It's perfect!
Man! I've never stayed
in a room this big.
Kinda feels like I'm getting
away with something.
Cute.
Don't worry. We've got plenty
of rooms to go around.
Thanks for letting us stay.
Sure! What do you say
we get our swimsuits on
and head to the beach?
Yeah! I can't wait!
[NANASHIMA groans]
What is this, summer camp?
Why do we all have to
be in the same bedroom?
Take it easy.
Only you would complain
about a free vacation.
Chill out.
There's more to it.
This trip is a big deal.
I can't blow it.
She and I have to get closer
if it's possible.
Serinuma was cool enough
to give me another chance
after what happened with us.
I just wanna prove
myself to her.
But I can't!
You guys'll hover
around us like bugs!
Well...
Then you already know why
Nishina made us share a bedroom.
I hate her so much!
[IGARASHI] You might as well
take a breath and relax, Nana.
[NANASHIMA]
Ugh!
[SHINOMIYA]
I can't do this.
Why did I agree to come here?
I'm not an outdoors type
and I hate the ocean.
Pasty. Scrawny.
I don't even wanna
take my shirt off.
[SHINOMIYA groans]
This is gonna be humiliating.
--[knock on door]
--[MUTSUMI] Shinomiya?
Just checking.
You've been in there
quite a while.
Do you need some help?
[SHINOMIYA]
No, I'm fine.
Be out in a second!
Oh, that's good.
I was starting to get worried.
Hey, you taking
a dump in there?
We all gotta use that thing
so don't stink it up.
I wasn't!
Sure.
Go ahead and grab the plunger.
Shut up! You're disgusting!
Okay, that's enough.
Let's get going.
Like dealing with
a bunch of children.
[SERINUMA]
It's so warm!
[ALL yell]
She's so cute.
Ah...
Summer.
Dear Lord, we thank you!
[NISHINA]
Hey, boys!
How do you feel
about bodyboarding?
The water's waiting.
Bodyboarding?
Yeah.
I'm down to do a little surfing.
Same here.
I gotta show him how it's done.
[NISHINA]
Follow me.
[NANASHIMA] Can't wait to
see you fall on your face.
[IGARASHI chuckles]
Um... I don't really
know how to surf.
[SERINUMA]
Neither do I.
Maybe we can learn together!
Let's try!
Hi. I'm a beginner myself.
[SHINOMIYA]
I take it all back.
This is gonna be great!
Sure! How complicated
could it be?
[NISHINA]
Hey, Serinuma!
Whoa!
She's so cool!
I've been inspired.
Let's give it a whirl!
Yeah. She knows her stuff!
[SHINOMIYA] Ugh! Curse Nishina
and her unfair advantages!
Okay, then.
This should be
relatively simple.
Oh, yeah? You think so?
It's all about keeping
the right posture.
[yelling]
Shinomiya!
[SHINOMIYA gasps]
[SHINOMIYA]
That was so uncool!
You're not hurt, are--[yelps]
--Here we go.
--[SERINUMA coughing]
You too. It's tough.
Yeah. It is.
No big deal.
Hey, check it out...
There's seaweed on you!
It's a fashion statement!
Yeah?
[laughing]
We're accessorizing!
[SHINOMIYA]
Everything is going well!
Wow! Maybe this vacation
won't be so bad after all!
I have an idea!
Let's practice some...
[GIRLS gasp]
Talk about awesome!
They're so hot!
[SERINUMA]
Oh, wow.
[BOTH laugh]
That was the best!
Can you teach me that?
You're pretty good.
Be still my heart!
[SHINOMIYA]
All right, that's it!
This is no time for seaweed!
[SHINOMIYA]
Excuse me.
I'm gonna borrow this.
What... the heck?
[SHINOMIYA]
I will do this.
Don't tell me he's
gonna try and surf.
Hey, kid!
You can't do that
without practice, ya know!
[SHINOMIYA] I'm going to
show her how cool I can be.
Now!
[SHINOMIYA yelling]
He stood up without falling!
Nice work, Shinomiya!
You're actually riding the wave!
[SHINOMIYA]
I'm doing it!
[SHINOMIYA] I'm king of
the world, Serinuma!
I'm doing it!
I'm really doing it!
[SHINOMIYA yelling]
[gasp]
[ALL scream]
[NANASHIMA]
What the hell?!
Get off of her!
[CROWD yelling]
[SHINOMIYA]
Forgive me for offending you.
It was a mistake!
I wouldn't have aimed for those!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Cut the crap.
Yeah. We all know
you're a little pervert.
No.
Shinomiya isn't
that type of person.
It's okay. There's no
need to apologize.
You'll feel much better
once you fill your belly.
[NANASHIMA]
Ugh!
You're lettin' him off
the hook? Why?
If Serinuma has
already forgiven him,
then nothing needs to be said.
Why don't we eat some lunch?
Afterwards you can be on my
team for a game of volleyball.
Cool?
Yeah. I'd like that.
[SHINOMIYA]
She's an angel!
[SERINUMA]
What...?
[MAN 09A]
Eh... I'd give her an 8.
[MAN 09B]
What? Way too high.
I'm feeling generous
so I give her a 6 out of 10.
Hey, 6, get to walking
and grab us a few more beers!
[SHINOMIYA]
Who are these guys?
No class.
Listen.
Why don't you and I head
back out to find a beach ball.
We could start a game.
But Shinomiya
hasn't finished eating.
[IGARASHI]
You ladies go ahead.
We'll stay behind.
Okay.
I guess we'll see you
on the beach.
Yes! Check out those 10s!
[MEN]
Whoa!
[MAN 09C]
10 plus interest!
Being that hot
should be illegal.
Check out the rear on
that girl with the hoodie.
[MAN 09C] I'd love to
break off a piece of that.
--[SHINOMIYA] What?
--[NANASHIMA] Hi.
Hey! What's your problem?
You lookin' for a fight?
Let's all settle down.
[MAN 09C]
Who are you?
Hey, listen.
We don't wanna start trouble.
I mean it.
But you should be more
respectful to those girls.
If not... We'll have to make
sure you learn your manners.
I'll kill you.
Yeah?
Who do you think
you're dealing with?!
[MUTSUMI]
Are we clear?
Sure thing.
Got the ball! Come on!
[IGARASHI]
On our way!
All right, you can
be on my team.
Awesome!
Thanks for that.
Yep.
I don't think we'll have
to worry about them.
That's the first time I've
seen you angry, Mutsumi.
You okay?
Those men weren't
behaving nicely.
[SHINOMIYA]
Nishina led Serinuma away?
That means I'm the only one
who didn't do anything.
I'm a coward.
[SERINUMA]
Okay! Let's play!
[SHINOMIYA]
What was I thinking?
I can't compete with these guys.
How could I?
I'm not even in their league.
I... love...
food on a stick!
Barbecue! Barbecue! Barbecue!
I'm glad to see you happy.
But you know,
I could've had a chef
prepare the meal for us.
When we do all
the work ourselves,
it makes the food
taste even better!
Something wrong?
Nope!
Maybe I got too much sun today.
[SHINOMIYA] I've got
to get a hold of myself.
Serinuma needs someone
she can rely on.
Someone who isn't afraid
to take a stand.
A real man would protect her.
Hey! Be careful!
[NANASHIMA] Yeah, great!
Just put that anywhere!
[SHINOMIYA]
No...
[IGARASHI]
What was that about?
[SHINOMIYA]
I... I...
[NANASHIMA]
You're such a klutz.
[NISHINA]
We'll have to start over.
[MUTSUMI]
Easily done.
[SHINOMIYA]
I can't do this.
I... I'm going home.
[NANASHIMA]
Hey... kid!
[thunder rumbles]
[SHINOMIYA]
Why am I surprised?
Did I think they'd understand?
They're all laughing at me.
That's what I get for trying.
This was a waste of my time.
[SHINOMIYA gasps]
[SHINOMIYA] If I had
given up from the start,
I wouldn't be this miserable.
This is humiliating.
It's about to rain.
We have to find Shinomiya!
So, uh... Where did he go?
He's going... back home.
Okay.
Well, the woods are
in the wrong direction.
[MUTSUMI]
Poor Shinomiya.
[NISHINA] Am I supposed
to feel bad for him?
[NANASHIMA]
He ran into the woods.
[GROUP]
Idiot.
He might get lost!
Eh... He'll come back
on his own eventually.
Getting lost in the woods
is a real possibility.
If he strays off the path
he may not find his way back.
[GROUP gasps]
I won't leave him.
If one of us is missing,
we're all missing!
[IGARASHI]
That makes no sense.
[SERINUMA]
I'll be right back!
[NANASHIMA]
Wait a second!
Now we have to go in.
[NANASHIMA]
Fine!
[IGARASHI] I can't believe
I'm spending my vacation
chasing down another guy.
[SERINUMA]
Shinomiya!
[IGARASHI]
Where are you?
We have to find him
before the storm gets worse.
[NANASHIMA whimpering]
Come on.
It'll be easier if
you don't look down.
Loose boards.
Watch your step!
[MUTSUMI]
Thanks.
Are we sure Shinomiya even
crossed this swinging casket?
[IGARASHI]
There's nowhere else to go.
[ALL gasp]
Poor Shinomiya.
Let's go!
[screams]
[NANASHIMA] I can't do it!
Don't make me!
Nana. Let us walk around!
The rest of us
are trying to pass!
Just go! Hurry up!
I can't move!
I'll wait.
[SERINUMA]
I made it.
Just a bit farther!
[screaming]
I'm sorry!
[SERINUMA]
Oh.
[IGARASHI]
Heh... All good here.
It's not quite as high
as it first appeared.
We almost died!
Who could've guessed
that we'd all live?
I thought I lost you
to the abyss!
We still might be too
far down to climb up again.
Look, there's a pathway.
Detour?
Maybe.
There's an old hotel
around here somewhere.
It may lead us there.
Right! Let's regroup there.
Good luck!
See you later!
Serinuma!
Please wait until
we're with you!
She left!
Didn't even look back.
Um, we'd better go too.
He's right!
[SERINUMA]
Could he have gotten this far?
I should have caught up
with him by now.
[SHINOMIYA]
Help me!
[SERINUMA]
Shinomiya!
Is that you?
[SHINOMIYA]
Serinuma?
Where are you?
[SHINOMIYA]
Stay away from here!
I thought I heard yelling.
He's over there.
[SERINUMA]
I'm coming!
[SHINOMIYA]
No! Please, stop!
[SERINUMA]
Tentacles versus pretty boy!
Please... Don't look at me
while I'm vulnerable.
[SERINUMA]
I'll get you out of there.
How did this happen?
Well... Long story.
[SHINOMIYA] The vine got
caught on my ankle.
Then I fell.
I tried to get it off of me.
But for some reason it
twisted around my wrists!
I thrashed around
to break free.
But it made things worse!
So exposed! Helpless!
Yeah. It was terrible.
Sorry you saw me like that.
No! I'm happy
you weren't hurt!
Feel free to describe the
experience in vivid detail!
[SHINOMIYA] I must have looked
so weak and pathetic to her!
The group is searching for you.
We're meeting at an old hotel.
Back that way!
But... it's dark.
We can find it!
[SHINOMIYA]
Why now?
[SERINUMA]
Let's get going, okay?
[SHINOMIYA]
Yeah!
[SERINUMA]
This must be it.
[BOTH yell]
[SERINUMA] Creepy building,
but at least it'll be dry!
Let's stay here
until the rain stops!
[SHINOMIYA]
Uh... sure!
[SERINUMA] I hope
everyone is else finds shelter.
[sneezes]
You cold?
Put this on.
What?
Are you sure you don't want it?
It's getting colder.
[SHINOMIYA]
I'll be fine.
Well... thank you.
Means a lot.
There's no reason for you
to thank me right now.
This is all my fault.
I ran away from all of you.
Sorry.
I feel like I can't
do anything right.
That's not true.
[rustling noise]
Did you... hear something?
Hey! Show yourself!
[footsteps]
[BOTH yell]
[SHINOMIYA]
There's something in here!
[footsteps]
[SHINOMIYA] What do I do?
What do I do?
[CHANTING] I can save us.
I can save us.
[SHINOMIYA screams]
Where'd the chanting come from?!
I can save us.
Why do you look like that?!
Leave it to me!
All I have to do is use
my good luck charm
to deliver us from evil!
Oh!
I just remembered that
it was only an illusion!
But don't you worry!
I'll protect you in this scary
hotel in the middle of nowhere!
[SHINOMIYA] Calm down!
You're freaking me out!
[SERINUMA]
I can handle this.
I promise that you and I are
gonna get through this thing.
I'll be brave for
both of us, okay?
Sure. Thank you.
[SHINOMIYA]
She's shaking.
[SERINUMA]
Yeah! We're safe!
[SHINOMIYA]
She's as scared as I am.
This isn't about me.
I can't keep wondering
if I'm good enough.
I have to take action.
Don't worry.
[SHINOMIYA]
I can't lose my nerve.
I promise you
have my protection.
[MEN laughing]
[MAN 09B]
Losers!
[MAN 09A]
Yeah, right?
I swear, both of 'em
started to shake!
[laughing]
Hi, there.
Nice to see you again.
Now why'd you
two sneak in here?
Looking for some privacy?
[SHINOMIYA] Those are the
guys from the beach house.
Why are they here?
[MAN 09C]
Surprised?
Didn't Mommy ever
teach you to knock?
We said we'd beat the crap outta
whoever came to our hangout
and here you are!
Aww. You don't have your
knights in shining armor
to take up for you!
Lucky break for us.
But wait.
I thought I heard you say
you'd protect her... right?
Weren't you the chump that hid
while your buddies
did all the work?
You feelin' like a big man now?
Leave him alone!
[MAN 09B]
Take it easy.
[MEN laughing]
Please don't do this.
We learned our lesson.
[laughs]
That's adorable!
Get lost.
What am I
gonna do with you?
[SERINUMA]
No!
[SHINOMIYA]
Excuse me.
I told you to leave us alone!
[screams]
[SHINOMIYA]
Run! Don't look back!
[MAN 09B]
Quick, grab 'em!
[NANASHIMA]
Hi.
Coulda sworn I said I'd kill you
if you messed with our ladies.
You're gonna die.
[MEN scream]
[IGARASHI]
That detour we took was crazy.
I swear we heard a wild boar,
oh, and there were snakes!
[NANASHIMA]
And that was one freaky storm.
We almost didn't make it!
Hey, Nishina!
How 'bout ya tell us next time
if there's a public road nearby?
[NISHINA]
I told you, I didn't know!
[SHINOMIYA]
I'm sorry.
I caused a lot of trouble.
Sorry I ran off.
Thanks for everything.
It's all good.
Yeah, we're all used to you
losing it over nothing, dude.
It's endearing.
[laughing]
Next time we're gonna leave ya.
[SHINOMIYA]
It's true.
I'm not strong like they are
and I'm a bit of a coward.
I've got a long way to go,
and it may take me a while.
Regardless,
I am growing.
I may end up
surprising all of them.
Yeah.
Of course.
Learn to walk.
You poor thing.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
He is so adorable!
[SHINOMIYA]
That's right.
I'll keep going!
[NANASHIMA] Grow up, get a job,
and work until you're dead.
Life is meaningless.
[SERINUMA]
What's the matter, Nanashima?
[IGARASHI]
Let me guess.
You didn't bother to start
your summer homework
and now you're out of time.
[NANASHIMA]
Lemme copy yours!
I know you and all
the soccer club guys
cheat off of each other.
[IGARASHI]
Man, I would.
But... what's in it for me?
[NANASHIMA] Does our
friendship mean nothing?
Gimme a break!
[SERINUMA]
I'll let you copy mine!
All I want in return
is one little thing.
[IGARASHI, NANASHIMA]
We don't trust you.
[SERINUMA]
It's not what you're thinking!
Well, maybe it is.
Come with me to every one
of the otaku summer events!
[NANASHIMA]
It's cool. I'll just fail.