[SHINOMIYA]
Hello, Serinuma!
It's nice to see you!
It was a cowboy
and an astronaut.
[IGARASHI]
Hey, good morning!
[NANASHIMA]
What's up?
[MUTSUMI]
Serinuma.
Serinuma?
[MUTSUMI] It doesn't feel
like you have a fever.
Ugh! What are you doing?!
Serinuma, is something wrong?
You're acting strange.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't hide it.
The truth is...
...last night I fell... in love.
Who are you in love with?!
His name...
[SERINUMA] ...is Akane from
the anime Katchu Ranbu ! Ah!
The anime just started,
so this is new for us,
but I couldn't take it slow!
It was love at first episode!
We really got to know
each other last night
while I was reblogging.
I never slept but...
I feel great!
[squealing]
I guess I should've
seen it coming.
That man...
I've started using his
picture for the wallpaper
on my phone.
Of course you have!
You get it!
Wait a second.
This guy you're in love with...
is a character?
That's right!
Akane is the main
character's servant,
but totally loyal to him.
He'd do anything to keep
his lord safe and happy!
They are so in love!
And the main character has
a childhood friend turned rival!
There's a teacher he adores
so there's no telling who
he's going to want to spend
the rest of his life snuggling!
Make no mistake.
Akane is definitely in the lead!
When I saw them my
heart knew it was real!
[GROUP]
We get it.
Don't you love Shion?
What about him?
Of course I do, but my heart
always has room for more.
[SHINOMIYA]
How convenient.
Akane will do
anything for his lord!
Right? They are so in love.
They go to such great
lengths to stay close.
[NANASHIMA] So I guess the
plot is that these two dudes
have a thing with each other?
Let us tell you about the show!
[NANASHIMA gasps]
First, you can take
a look at the trailer!
My lord! Forgive me
for disturbing you!
Word from the
northern mountains.
The enemy has attacked!
Then we fight!
Akane, let us depart at once!
Right!
There are bowmen waiting
to ambush you outside!
What did you say?
[AKANE]
Get back here!
No! My lord!
And now we fight!
Ready?
Akane!
[AKANE]
Yes!
[AKANE] I will protect you
with heart, body, and soul,
even if it costs me my life.
[BOTH squeal]
It's just so perfect!
I feel it in my soul.
An amazing man. Precious.
Uh... Akane was the
naked one with the red hair
and green eyes, right?
Yep!
You like the one who
can turn into clothes?
Why did he disappear
after he hugged that guy?
"Katchu" means
armor and helmet.
Huh?
Akane is his lord's
exclusive armor and helmet,
so when they enter battle,
he can transform.
Into what?
Armor and helmet!
So... his boyfriend is a hat.
Go buy some armor.
What's the point?
He's an anthropomorphized
helmet and armor, right?
[SERINUMA]
Exactly!
What's that mean?
It means to give something
humanlike attributes.
People do it for
all sorts of things!
Animals, cars,
household appliances,
food, even countries!
[NANASHIMA]
This is getting weird.
Katchu Ranbu is unique
because the armor
doesn't fit anyone but the lord.
The lord's personality
perfectly complements Akane.
Their bond is eternal! Precious!
Yes! No one can come
between their fervent desires!
Isn't it great?
--Akane and Lord.
--Lord and Akane.
What? Perhaps you
misspoke, my dear girl.
Akane and his lord are
surely your true pairing.
It must be a mistake.
I guess you haven't had
the chance to read through
the opening and
closing theme lyrics.
It obviously implies
Lord and Akane.
[NISHINA] I'm afraid
you're misunderstanding
their relationship.
Servants always care
for their masters!
[SERINUMA] No, no, no!
Look, you aren't getting it.
A servant will put all
of his trust into his lord.
Yes, but Akane has devoted
himself to maintaining
Lord's comfort
despite hardship.
The embracing of his lord
in battle is symbolic
of the relationship
that they have forged!
[SERINUMA] Akane only transforms
because of the trust he has
in Lord!
[NISHINA]
Lord showcases vulnerability
in the transformation!
Even his body type
demonstrates that!
[SERINUMA] What show
are you even watching?
Akane has a much
more delicate build!
Please don't argue.
You're both making great points.
[NISHINA, SERINUMA]
As I was saying,
the pairing that you
love so much...
...is absolutely impossible!
[NANASHIMA]
Okay, what was that?
[IGARASHI]
I don't know.
Are you going to tell
me what's going on?
[SERINUMA]
What do you mean?
You didn't even
stop to say hello.
That was Nishina!
Got a problem?
Me? No way... just be cool!
[SERINUMA]
Here it is again!
Why is there so much
Akane and Lord?
These fangirls just
aren't getting it!
Hey, did something happen?
Kae and Nishina aren't speaking.
On the way to class they gave
each other the cold shoulder.
We're not sure.
They can't agree on
whose name would come first
in a couple, I guess.
No way! Please tell me
you're joking.
Why go on in a
world so convoluted?
We're better off dead!
Abandon ship!
It's that bad?!
Shipping wars
can ruin friendships.
It's bad.
Shipping what?
What's that mean?
[NAKANO]
Listen up, rookies!
We're caught in
the middle of a reverse
shipping war, soldiers.
When two sides can't agree
on the leader in a pairing,
the outcome can be devastating!
Oh, okay... but why?
Is there a reason why
they can't take turns?
There's no way!
Let's see here...
If you wanted to start
dating each other,
who would be the one most
likely to make the first move?
[BOTH gasp]
Not doing this!
Chill, it's hypothetical!
Would Nanashima
ask Igarashi out,
or would it be
the other way around?
In a fujoshi 's world, that can
change the entire relationship.
The dynamic always changes
based on personality
and core need!
[IGARASHI]
We get the picture!
Those two are arguing
over who asks the other
on a date first?
Which character holds the reins
in a romantic relationship
can be a big issue.
Don't take shipping
wars lightly.
This stuff is serious business.
Proud fangirls will always
stand by their pairings.
Even a small rift in shipping
is a rift in the friendship!
It's true!
Opposing opinions feel like
a betrayal to your fandom!
But they're not!
There's no helping them.
All we can do is pray
that they have a bond
strong enough to overcome.
Kae is one of the toughest
shippers I've ever known.
She doesn't get
over these things.
What? Are you for real?
[IGARASHI]
Poor Serinuma.
I hate seeing her like this.
[MUTSUMI] I'm sad that Nishina
isn't sitting with us today.
Well, I guess they're
still going at it.
Time to take action.
We've gotta do
something about this.
[SERINUMA]
Hello?
Oh, hi, Mutsumi!
How are you?
What? You'd like me to come with
you on a trip to Anime Ito?
[MUTSUMI]
Yes!
I've been studying
the Sengoku period,
and thought I might
check out Katchu Ranbu .
Wow! Do you really want to?
[MUTSUMI]
I do! It seems interesting.
[SERINUMA]
It is!
[MUTSUMI] There are a lot
volumes in the manga,
so I'm not really
sure where to start.
Any way could you meet me?
[SERINUMA]
I'll be right there!
[NISHINA]
How odd, Igarashi.
Since when are you
interested in Anime Ito?
[IGARASHI]
Since now.
We don't know what
we're doing. Come with us.
Mind telling me why
you're going at all?
[IGARASHI]
Serinuma has been down lately.
Nana and I thought
a gift might help.
[NISHINA]
Keep dreaming!
I would never go out of
my way to help you two
score points with her.
That's almost insulting.
[IGARASHI]
Huh...
And here I thought
you'd given her up.
I mean, you aren't
even speaking.
[NISHINA] Fine. I'll come
if you never call me again.
Thank you!
We'll be waiting by the
door when you get here.
[NANASHIMA] I gotta learn
Igarashi's techniques.
What a nice surprise!
We're on our way into Anime Ito!
What do ya know? Us too!
We're here, so might
as well go to a café!
[MUTSUMI]
Good idea.
[NANASHIMA]
I'm starvin'!
[SHINOMIYA]
This is what friends do!
No way!
Igarashi, you lied to me!
[IGARASHI laughs]
I wouldn't dare!
How are ya?
Since we're all here by random
chance and there's no way
it was planned,
might as well catch up!
[SERINUMA] How can I make
small talk with this stranger
sitting in front of me?
Oh! That's right!
I watched that show
you girls like!
You did?
Yeah! I saw it, too.
[NISHINA]
What did you think?
I thought it was gonna be dumb,
but once I ignored
the stuff I hated,
it wasn't that bad.
What he means is
that we actually liked it.
That's right.
The fight scenes
were remarkable.
[MUTSUMI] The designs on the
armor are historically accurate!
Fanboys?
They have to be.
I know, right?
The show is so good!
The original writer had
complete creative control,
so they couldn't
cut corners! Nope!
Things are looking good!
I think that
Princess Mitsu seems
like a pretty cool chick.
She's courageous.
Oh, yeah!
I mean, the touch of coldness
they gave her adds to the charm!
I have a theory
that she and the lord
are going to end up together.
It's obvious that
the lord has Akane.
Oh. I forgot.
[NANASHIMA]
You little idiot!
Well, I can tell ya one thing.
Akane is loyal!
He lays it all on the
line for that Lord guy!
So true!
The lord seems to really
treasure the friendship
that they share.
He does!
I checked the internet.
Seems like people enjoy
that pairing the most.
--Akane and the lord?
--The lord and Akane?
Your foolish ways
haven't changed.
Embarrassing.
People love Akane and Lord...
yet you cling to hope.
Pathetic.
Lord and Akane. It's canon.
There is no other option.
[NANASHIMA]
What's the matter with you?!
Why don't you ever
stop talking? Ugh!
[SHINOMIYA]
I'm reawy sowy!
Enough of this! I'm finished
quarreling with you!
A duel!
We'll write fan fiction!
Once completed we can put them
online for the world to see!
That's right! The one true
pairing will have the most hits!
How's that sound?
[SERINUMA]
I love that idea!
[NISHINA]
Let's set a few rules.
The format is short story with
a deadline we have to meet.
[SERINUMA]
I accept!
[BOTH growling[
Really? I think we just
made things worse.
[SERVER 06A]
Thanks for coming!
[IGARASHI]
Nishina.
You won't let this go?
No, I won't.
I can't sacrifice my beliefs!
I'll prove to her which
is the true pairing!
All right. But...
What then? What happens
when it's all over?
There's a chance this argument
might ruin your friendship.
Will you be okay with that?
I don't know.
[IGARASHI]
Well, I'm not gonna complain.
I don't mind having
less competition.
Hey, but at least you'll
have those bragging rights.
I'm sure that's just as good.
Shut up, Igarashi!
[IGARASHI] You should learn
to respect your elders!
[NISHINA] I've always
loved beautiful things.
I enjoy looking at them.
I enjoy making them.
As odd as it sounds, one could
call beauty a passion of mine.
But...
[SHADOW 06A]
What a cute drawing.
[SHADOW 06B] I'd expect
nothing less from the daughter
of such a wealthy family.
[SHADOW 06C]
Give your father my regards.
[STUDENT 06C]
Treat her nicely.
She has money.
[STUDENT 06D] She'll
never have to work for anything.
She's so lucky.
[STUDENT 06C]
It's not even that good.
[STUDENT 06D]
Of course she won first place.
[STUDENT 06E] Every year
her family gives the school
a ton of donations.
[STUDENT 06C] Yeah.
That's why she always wins.
[NISHINA]
Why would they say those things?
I put everything
into what I love!
I'll show them!
I'll try harder!
[gasps]
Just a dream.
Keep writing!
[NISHINA] I had to fight to earn
the respect I've been given
in this world.
I won't back down now.
[GROUP]
Why?
I'm concerned that you
might not be well-rested.
I'm still working
on my fan fiction.
Everything is running together.
I can't even tell
if it's good anymore.
Could you please read it for me?
Of course.
Mm-hmm. Very nice.
I like the concept.
There's potential here!
I'm so glad!
Make it clear how
the story is being told.
Maybe first person?
Third works just as well.
[SERINUMA gasps]
I had no idea!
[MUTSUMI]
When a character is speaking,
consider using quotation marks.
Why say yes to a fan fic
contest if she sucks this bad?
There goes her confidence.
[NISHINA]
What? Why would I give up?
[SHINOMIYA] Writing doesn't
come easy to Serinuma.
Her story is awful and she's
trying as hard as she can.
You've had years of
experience publishing stories.
So it's unfair.
Please give up.
This whole thing
is a waste of time.
Oh, really?
It's pathetic. And...
[NISHINA]
What were you saying?
Always so condescending.
Your opinion means
nothing to me.
My soul won't rest
until I prove my point!
I'll defend what's
beautiful to me.
Consider this your
only warning.
Stay out of my
business, little kitten.
She's so cool!
Nishina is putting
that boy in his place!
I bet he wants to
disappear right now!
You're saying...
she shoved you to the wall,
almost kicked you in the
crotch, and made threats
while everyone was watching?
You're so lame!
Huh?! Go see
for yourself then!
She's out of her mind!
She always defends
what's beautiful?
Uh-huh.
What's beautiful about imagining
two anime guys hooking up?
Those men are quite attractive.
I think it's more than that.
We'll see.
[NAKANO] A friendship on
the line, history in the making.
The fan fiction community
would decide their fate.
[NISHINA yelling]
[SERINUMA, NISHINA]
I'm done!
[BOTH yell]
[SERINUMA, NISHINA]
Send!
[IGARASHI]
Here we go.
[NANASHIMA] This thing'll
be over at 4 PM Monday.
Whoever has the
most views wins.
[SHINOMIYA] We're rooting
for you, Serinuma.
[MUTSUMI]
Wow. They're doing well.
[NAKANO]
Finally... the day had come.
It's time!
The moment of truth!
I win!
[SERINUMA]
How did I lose?
What a glorious triumph to
see my enemy on her knees.
What a pathetic fool
you've become!
Now cast your
eyes to the ground
and admit to the world
that you've lost!
I... I lost.
[NISHINA laughs]
What was that?
I can't hear you!
Speak up!
Hey. Chill.
[SERINUMA]
I... I lost.
But...
I can't do it!
They mean too much to me!
[crying]
[NANASHIMA]
Wait! Serinuma!
[SHINOMIYA]
Come back!
Are you satisfied?
[NISHINA]
Yes.
[IGARASHI]
You've won the argument.
What happens now?
[NISHINA]
Why are you asking that again?
You once told me that you're
drawn to beautiful things
and will do whatever it
takes to protect them.
Do you think it's beautiful to
make the woman you like cry?
[NISHINA]
It was here.
This is the place where
I first met her.
[NISHINA]
Finally.
This is the school I've chosen.
From this moment on,
everything will be different.
[FEMALE STUDENT 06A]
Look at that nice car!
[FEMALE STUDENT 06B]
Oh, yeah. I heard a super rich
girl might be coming here.
[FEMALE STUDENT 06C] Why would
someone like that come to
a plain public
school like ours?
[NISHINA] No. I can't
go through this again.
[SERINUMA]
I'm late! I'm late! I'm late!
[STUDENTS yell]
[NISHINA screams]
Oh! I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to fall on you!
Please don't die!
Just breathe; you'll be fine!
[NISHINA] A voluptuous angel
came to my rescue that day.
[NISHINA]
My very first doujinshi .
One sale would be nice.
Please feel free to take a look!
They're first issues!
[NISHINA]
No one is interested.
It's that girl!
I'd like to buy a copy
of each of your doujinshis.
[NISHINA]
She's so cool!
Thank you for your
purchase. Enjoy.
Would you mind telling
me your name?
Another seller just
put out an entire series
of boy love goodness!
Thank you!
I feel rather refreshed
after making that sale!
What's this? Look like a
message about my doujinshi .
[SERINUMA]
Dear Yokoshima,
Earlier today I bought
all of your books.
[NISHINA gasps]
It's from that girl!
[SERINUMA]
I hope you continue this series!
I feel like words can't even
express my love for your style.
You made my entire soul tremble!
[NISHINA]
My voluptuous angel!
Afterwards,
I started looking for her
in the halls at school.
She wasn't anywhere to be found.
I busied myself with work.
I was absorbed in my craft,
and gained popularity.
But on that fateful day,
we reunited without
even realizing!
[MALE STUDENT 06A]
Oh! Her name is Serinuma.
She's pretty cute!
Yeah. I heard she's
kind of a fangirl.
[MALE STUDENT 06A]
If she's that hot, who cares?
[MALE STUDENT 06B]
I guess,
but not too long ago
she was a huge fatty!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[NISHINA] This girl... and that
girl... are one in the same?
This must be...
...fate!
[NISHINA]
Oh, Serinuma.
She was always so beautiful.
That's enough!
I don't want to lose her
over something like this!
[NISHINA] She's more precious
to me than anything
I've ever known!
Aren't you going
answer your phone?
Looks like Nishina.
Well... so what?
Pick it up, please.
[SERINUMA]
No!
[IGARASHI]
Fine then.
[phone chimes]
It's not as bad
as you think it is.
Your awkward love story
still got a lot of hits!
It certainly did!
I'll read it again.
A loss is a loss.
I'm okay with that.
But... I'm her friend.
The story she wrote was amazing!
No! This can't be the
way things end for us!
I assure you that
our arc is far from over.
You have to know
how much I love you!
Really? Oh, Shima...
I'm here. Always.
Can you forgive me?
I'm so sorry!
As long as you forgive
me for my cruelty!
Please?
You made up;
that's enough hugging.
Yeah!
Does this mean you
finally know which couple
you wanna start shipping?
[NISHINA] I know exactly
how we can fix that.
[SERINUMA]
Yeah! I think so too!
The lord and Akane
will be versatile!
That's exactly why
you're my soulmate!
"Versatile" refers to a pairing
in which the leading position
can be switched from
one partner to another.
[NAKANO]
All's well that ends well.
[IGARASHI]
Nishina, are those new sneakers?
[NISHINA]
Yes, they are.
Thank you for noticing.
[IGARASHI] I've never seen
you wear shoes like that.
They're nice.
I have a collection of them!
[NISHINA]
Really? Be careful.
Small collections
can easily grow into
all-consuming obsessions!
[IGARASHI laughs] Mine isn't
bad compared to yours.
Does one person really need
that many plastic models,
or costumes, or books?
[NISHINA]
If you think it's bad now,
you should've seen it before
I had the shelving installed!
My collections were everywhere!