Well, it's this weekend.
The anniversary of Lord's death.
[GROUP]
Huh?
The lord in Katchu Ranbu
was based on a real man.
He was a samurai
named Hyakki Sametora.
Sametora?
That's an interesting
person to inspire a show.
There's going to be
a memorial service
held for him tomorrow at 7 AM.
Even if we left early,
we still wouldn't make it.
[SERINUMA gasps]
There are no tickets
for the night bus left!
Why don't we take my helicopter?
We can't!
The journey is far!
The road is long!
For him... I'll get there
without taking the easy way!
Inspirational!
You've touched my heart!
I'll stand proudly by your side
as we slum it like peasants!
You'd do that?
You realize we're the
peasants she's talkin' about.
[NISHINA] In that case,
it might be a good idea
for us go a day early.
[SERINUMA]
Okay!
And we'll need to figure
out a cheap place to stay.
Wait! You're not spending
the night together, right?
Well, we may have
no other option.
None of you have an
interest in history, do you?
Me!
Would you mind
if I tagged along?
My eyes!
We'd love to
attend the ceremony.
Bring us.
Aw! Let's go together!
All right!
[SERINUMA laughs]
It's so rustic
and charming! Nice!
I love the decrepit motif!
[SERINUMA, NISHINA giggle]
[NANASHIMA]
Yeah, baby!
Let's hit the hot springs!
Woo!
[IGARASHI]
Give it a rest, Nana!
[NANASHIMA] Aha!
Look at your little nipples!
[SERINUMA, NISHINA gasp]
What? Shut up!
[NANASHIMA]
They're like pencil erasers!
[SERINUMA, NISHINA] What on
Earth's going on over there?
[NANASHIMA] Come here!
I'm gonna twist 'em off!
[NANASHIMA]
Ha ha! I got one card left!
Reverse!
[NANASHIMA gasps]
For real?
Nana. Why don't ya draw four?
[NANASHIMA growls]
[NANASHIMA]
You jerks!
Oh, yeah?
I have your back, Nanashima!
I bet they were
cheating! Shameful!
Oh, you guys are goin' down!
[IGARASHI yells]
Nice throw!
Mr. Perfect forgot how to aim?
Lemme teach ya!
Comin' at cha!
Your turn!
[SHINOMIYA yells]
[NISHINA yells]
[IGARASHI yelling]
Uh, sorry.
Um... Totally fine.
[IGARASHI grunts]
[ALL yelling]
Are you okay?
Yeah. Thank you.
Hey, knock it off!
Want me to call the cops?
Get your butts in
bed and go to sleep!
[IGARASHI]
I scared her.
We certainly have a
lot of young women here
this morning.
How peculiar.
I wonder what brought them here.
[IGARASHI]
Anime...
[SERINUMA]
My lord.
Rest in peace.
That was the most beautiful
service I've ever been to.
They were so respectful
to his memory.
[SHINOMIYA] Let's go buy
a good luck charm!
[SERINUMA] Ah!
We can write prayers on them!
"I hope dear
Akane and his lord
will live happily
ever after. Forever!"
What do you all think of mine?
[ALL gasp]
Isn't it disrespectful
to ship a dead man?
What? Not sure. Look.
[GROUP gasps]
Merchandise? This is dirty.
Wow! Clever tie-in!
So what now?
Would any of you mind
if we met with Akane?
[GROUP]
Huh?
That way!
[CROWD chattering]
[squealing]
[SERINUMA]
It has battle scars!
[NISHINA] Visual proof
that he protected his lord!
[sighs] Their love is timeless!
Happiest day of my life.
Akane!
He's perfect!
[NISHINA]
Too good for this world!
Now we're crowded today,
so you kids need
to move along, please.
[SERINUMA]
I'll miss you!
[NISHINA] Would you
let us spend the night?!
Hey... look!
It's their precious Sametora!
My lord... So cute!
Adorable! Look at that face!
[IGARASHI] The character is
based on that guy?!
[NANASHIMA]
Which one is the improvement?
They're both gross.
[SHINOMIYA] How does a
dead samurai get more girls
than I do?
Hey.
How many times am I gonna have
to tell you kids to move on?
No, my lord!
We didn't get
enough time with him!
That's okay! I have an idea!
How would you like
to pay the lord a visit?
But how?
[NANASHIMA]
Mutsumi, you freak!
This is where
the lord was buried.
[SHINOMIYA]
We don't need to see this!
[SERINUMA, NISHINA]
My lord!
[IGARASHI] Um... are you
two ready to get going?
[MUTSUMI]
He's a happy lord.
You great man.
I hate to leave you.
[NISHINA]
Your grave is lovely.
Man, am I starving!
Maybe we should
take a break for lunch!
[NISHINA crying]
One or two pictures, okay?!
[NANASHIMA]
You're sick!
[SERINUMA sighs]
I'm glad we came.
This has been a perfect day.
I'm so happy!
[NISHINA]
Agreed. Splendid!
So cool!
The cutest gravesite ever!
I'm gonna make it
my wallpaper picture.
I think that's a terrific idea!
You need help. Bad.
Fun fact.
This is where they buried
his headless remains.
[MUTSUMI]
Sametora battled his son in war.
He won, then pleaded
to have his son spared
from imminent execution.
Though his appeal was accepted,
they demanded a
sacrifice in exchange.
Sametora had to take his own
life by performing seppuku.
[NISHINA, SERINUMA gasp]
[MUTSUMI] Moments before
he performed the act,
he discovered that his son
had already been murdered.
[SERINUMA]
Really?
That is so cruel!
[MUTSUMI] Enraged,
Sametora brutally slaughtered
a group of generals.
Their subordinates managed
to injure him severely,
but he refused to die.
There was a greater
battle to be fought.
[SERINUMA]
My lord!
[NISHINA]
He's the bravest!
[MUTSUMI]
In the end, he was beheaded.
Legend says that his head
began to laugh, then scream.
It escaped them by flying
to a small nearby island.
More specifically, that one.
[SHINOMIYA gasps]
His head can fly?
Long story short, it's been
said that he haunts the island.
Oh, dear. Should we go?
He might find us!
Well, there's only
one way to find out.
Let's go!
All right!
[GROUP]
You're nuts!
I'd have to advise against it.
There's a rumor that
the island might be cursed.
Folks around here
won't even talk about it.
Bad vibes.
That's enough for me. Serinu--
I wanna be cursed!
We gotta go now!
Maybe he'll recruit
us to join his legion
of undead minion slaves!
[GROUP gasps]
So... these are
the only boats available?
Ugly... and dumb.
Why the swans?
They have two seats a piece.
Guess we'll need to pair up.
[GROUP]
Pair up?
Hey! I know!
We can decide with a game.
Ready.
So rock, paper, scissors.
One, two, and... shoot!
[IGARASHI]
I won!
Wow. Lucky me!
Yeah! Luck.
Well, great! Ready to go?
I am. Thanks.
Let's have fun!
[IGARASHI laughs]
It's been years since
I've been in one of these.
Yeah... same here.
I need... to say...
I'm sorry... about last night.
I didn't mean to
fall on top of you.
I know that!
It wasn't a big deal.
Let's just forget it.
Yeah. You say that.
I can tell it bothered you.
[SERINUMA gasps]
[IGARASHI]
You can be honest.
Do you want me to back off?
[SERINUMA]
Yes! Well, no!
I think... uh...
This is... new to me!
And um... I don't have
much experience, so...
I'm not... used to it.
Get used to it. I'll help.
Uh, what?
'Kay?
Yeah.
Something's up.
[NISHINA]
I think so.
Let's gun it!
Pedal!
[BOTH yelling]
[IGARASHI]
Bloodlust!
[ALL yelling]
Why ya being so quiet?!
I know you cheated at
rock, paper, scissors!
Send the fool overboard!
Stop! Are you nuts?
Calm down! We'll fall!
Did you forget
Serinuma's in here?!
[yelling]
Good grief. Don't they realize
how dangerous that is?
It's okay.
How sweet. They're having fun.
Let's enjoy this.
Your kindness... relieves me.
Guess you're right!
The weather is perfect.
[SHINOMIYA]
Uh... huh?
Ugh! Where the heck
did this storm come from?
Oh, no!
[SERINUMA gasps]
What... Look out!
[IGARASHI]
A whirlpool?
[SHINOMIYA]
But how? This is just a lake!
[ALL yelling]
[ALL scream]
[SERINUMA]
I can't breathe!
[NISHINA]
Igarashi!
[SHINOMIYA]
Wake up!
[IGARASHI]
Where are we?
That island?
Where is everyone else?
Don't know.
Shino and I just woke up.
My phone.
It's dead. What now?
[SHINOMIYA]
Nanashima!
[IGARASHI]
Nana!
Nana! Hey dude! Nana!
Is he... breathing?
No. He's not!
Igarashi, you have
to do mouth-to-mouth!
Be the hero! Save him! Go!
[IGARASHI]
Huh?!
[coughing]
It's okay. You're safe.
Serinuma?
[gasps] Oh, no...
Save his life!
Looking good! Deeper now!
I heard somewhere it
helps to use your tongue!
Why are you taking pictures
when I'm trying
to save his life?!
Use your phone for
something besides fangirling!
I'm preserving the memories!
Yum. I got some great shots!
[NANASHIMA coughs]
Nana!
Are... we dead?
We're fine.
I hope.
You almost died,
but you were saved
in the nick of time!
Wanna see some
pics of your hero?
Stop kidding around and
call for some help! Please!
No luck.
[IGARASHI growls]
Oh, please, wake up!
Serinuma! Wake up!
She needs help.
I have to save her life.
[coughing]
Oh, Mutsumi!
I'm so glad you're awake.
Wait. What happened to
the rest of our group?
Really? Wow.
I'm sure that they're
all okay. Yeah.
[GROUP]
Hey!
[NISHINA]
Serinuma! Can you hear us?
Yes!
Hello!
I think I can hear her voice!
Over there!
I hear them!
I could've sworn they sounded
a lot closer than this.
Did we take a wrong turn?
No. We're walkin'
in a straight line.
I know!
We can keep track
of where we've been.
It's strange.
We should've seen them by now.
[NANASHIMA]
Where the heck are they?!
[SHINOMIYA]
What?
Our marker!
Same tree? Not good.
Here again...
Serinuma, I think we
need to turn around.
[crashing noise]
[MUTSUMI]
Serinuma!
Did you trip?
She's burning up!
So... cold...
She has to get warm somehow.
We have to get her out
of these wet clothes.
Forgive me.
I must...
This is freakin'
me out, you guys!
I can't take it!
Have we been going in circles?
[IGARASHI] We never
even turned off the path!
[NANASHIMA]
You think I don't know that?
[NISHINA]
Then how?
[SHINOMIYA] The old man
said this island was cursed!
[rustling noise]
[yelling]
You kids in some
kind of trouble?
[NANASHIMA]
We're saved!
Fuzzy cows...
Your fever's gone down!
[MUTSUMI]
Back into your clothes.
I promise not to peek!
Huh? What?
Where am I? What happened?
You fainted.
I brought you here to warm up.
What? You saved my life!
Funny. I woke up from the
best dream I've ever had!
Wonderful.
I was being snuggled
by a big cat.
So warm. So fluffy.
I wish it were real.
Uh... huh.
[BOTH gasp]
[NANASHIMA] Man, you really
helped us out back there.
[MAN 07B] Go ahead and pull up
a seat until the rain stops.
We appreciate all your help!
This feels so good!
Question.
Have you seen anyone
else around here?
We got separated from
our friends a while ago.
[MAN 07B] There's no need
for you to worry about them.
You'll be reunited
soon enough...
...in another realm!
[ALL scream]
Whatever it is
is catching up with us!
They look like some kind
of weird floating fireballs!
This can't be real!
We might be able to outrun them!
Come on!
Okay!
[BOTH gasp]
[GHOSTS moaning]
[SAMETORA]
My name is Hyakki Sametora.
This land is mine.
Any person who
dares step foot here...
...must face their death!
Prepare yourselves
for your demise!
Kill them!
[SERINUMA screams]
How did you do that?
The charm?
I bought it at the shrine.
It protected us.
Well, then. Let's try this!
I bought a charm too!
Check it out!
[GHOSTS moaning]
[SERINUMA] May those who shield
warriors become my vanguard!
[GHOSTS moaning]
Wow! And this thing
was so cheap!
Uh... How did you
know that incantation?
I was a shaman
fangirl for a while.
I taught myself!
True fans know these things.
Glad all that knowledge
finally came in handy!
Convenient. Neat!
[SAMETORA growls]
You insignificant fools!
No! I won't be able
to hold him for long!
Stay strong!
[SAMETORA laughing]
Akane! Lend me
your power! Iron love!
Sametora Flame-Horned Slugger!
[SAMETORA grunts]
Even the purest of
heart cannot defeat me!
We got him!
You aren't hurt, are you?
How do you know
moves like that?
[laughs] Watching anime
can sure come in handy!
[SAMETORA]
Your insolence is unforgiveable!
I will massacre your loved ones
and torture their souls!
Your heads will roll!
Stop this!
Listen!
Hyakki Sametora would
never say such a thing!
[SAMETORA]
Huh?
It's true!
The lord is full of love!
And ya know... It's sad!
'Cause the world
isn't fair sometimes.
Your ghost head decided
to haunt people.
What's your deal?
We have to let go
of things that hurts us.
Why spend eternity
punishing people for pain
they didn't cause?
Don't you want to remembered
for forgiveness you gave
to those who didn't deserve it?
My lord!
There are people need you!
Show us... how to love!
It's who you are! I know that!
[SAMETORA]
Very well.
Have I truly have gone down in
history as an esteemed figure?
My soul will rest
happily in knowing this.
Thank you for
remembering me as such.
Love will reign.
That is how it shall be.
[chuckles]
I am most satisfied.
My lord...
[IGARASHI]
Serinuma! Mutsumi!
[SHINOMIYA]
What a relief!
[NISHINA]
We finally found you!
You did!
There's something
freaky on this island!
I wanna go home now!
[IGARASHI]
What? Poison mushrooms?
Well... I'm sorry about that.
I mistook mountain mushrooms
for shiitake mushrooms
and served them in lunch!
Isn't that a good one?
They pack a wallop!
I always heard those things'll
make you hallucinate!
[laughing]
Hey! We could've all died!
Beautiful ladies everywhere.
I was in paradise!
We ate hallucinogenic
poison mushrooms?
We never got lost in the
woods or met that monster?
Or the lord!
I never gave Nana
mouth to mouth!
Now, that really happened.
I'm getting prints of these!
Hey! He and I have a
right to privacy, ya know!
That was a public act.
I'm so sad! It all felt
so real and amazing.
I finally got to meet my lord.
You met him?
[YAMADA] Sounds like you guys
had as good a time as I did!
[MUTSUMI]
A hallucination?
[MUTSUMI] I guess that's
what we'll call it.
[NANASHIMA] Aww,
I wanna go somewhere!
[SHINOMIYA]
Please do.
[NANASHIMA] Shut it! I'm tryin'
to figure out the best place
to go for a date!
I need ideas!
[SHINOMIYA] It's like a
sauna outside right now,
so don't plan anything outdoors.
[NANASHIMA] All right,
then where would you go,
smart guy?
[SHINOMIYA]
Um... the zoo?
[NANASHIMA] How many inside
zoos have you been to?
[SHINOMIYA] It was the
first thing I thought of!
Really, it doesn't
matter where you go
as long as you're punctual.
[NANASHIMA] That's the dorkiest
thing I've ever heard.
It's not normal to be an
hour early for everything.
It makes you look like
a time-obsessed loser!
[SHINOMIYA]
Hey!