[CROWD chattering]
A Christmas party! Let's do it!
[NANASHIMA]
A Christh--
Christmas party!
Oh. Sounds fun.
[NANASHIMA]
How about Christmas Eve?
If we all throw in some money,
we could book a karaoke room.
I'm in.
That works for me.
Me too.
[SERINUMA]
Little problem!
I've got plans.
But karaoke would've
been a lot of fun though!
Sorry.
[GROUP]
Huh?
What?
So you're busy? Why?
There's no way we'll hang
out together without you!
Not trying to be a pain,
but the second
Comiket happens to fall
on Christmas Eve this year!
Who gives a crap about Comiket?
What do you even
do there anyway?
Says here it's the largest
doujinshi exhibition market.
Fangirl stuff.
Hey. Didn't you already go
during summer vacation?
[SERINUMA]
Mm-hmm.
Wait a second.
Why would you need
to go twice a year?
Christmas only happens once!
Where are your priorities?
I'm sorry!
I've been saving up.
It's important!
I'm going to go,
and that's final!
[GROUP]
Ugh. Comiket it is.
Wow.
Looks like there's a
historical research group.
Seems interesting.
[MUTSUMI laughs]
Here you go.
It's great!
I always have so much fun!
This year, there's gonna be way
more than anime and manga.
They've expanded
to other genres!
Like foreign dramas
and songwriting.
There's so much to see and
I can't wait to check it out!
I know!
Let's all go to Comiket.
Serinuma won't miss the event,
and we'll still get to be
together on Christmas Eve.
[SHINOMIYA, NANASHIMA, IGARASHI]
Yeah, great.
Thanks for dragging us into it.
Oh. Are you going
with someone else?
I should've asked you that.
Not this time.
A is spending Christmas
with her boyfriend.
She's been looking
forward to it!
So I was gonna go
by myself this year.
If it sounds interesting,
you're all welcome to come!
[IGARASHI]
Can't wait.
[NANASHIMA]
[SHINOMIYA]
Can't wait.
Cool.
We'll go to Comiket
in the morning
and do some karaoke after.
How's that?
[GROUP]
Let's do it!
Hey, there! Morning!
[GROUP]
Yeah. Good morning and stuff.
[MUTSUMI]
Good morning.
[IGARASHI] Remind me
why we're here so early.
[NANASHIMA]
It's still dark outside.
[SERINUMA] If we aren't
there when it opens,
all the books will be gone!
[SHINOMIYA]
Oh, no.
[SERINUMA]
Okay!
Why don't you read this
guidebook on the train?
Here you go!
It should teach you
everything you need to know
about the event!
Onward!
Fandom lead us!
[SHINOMIYA] "Trampling may occur
so do not run or push?"
[NANASHIMA yawns]
We'll make this a quick trip
so we can come back and party.
[NANASHIMA]
What?!
Don't these people have
anything better to do?!
There's no freakin' way
they're all going to Comiket.
Can't be. I hope.
And it's only 7 AM!
[NANASHIMA]
The train was packed.
The platform had
a ton of people.
No pushing, please!
You can do this!
If you're here for Comiket,
the line to get
your badges...
[SHINOMIYA] The staff sure has
their work cut out for them.
[GROUP]
This is madness!
Oh, wow.
It looks like there are a lot
less people than last year.
I guess it's because today
is Christmas Eve.
Less... people?
This is less people?
Come on! We don't
wanna get separated.
Those in general admittance,
please come this way!
Sign-ups over here!
[SERINUMA] Why don't we wait
here until the doors open?
[IGARASHI]
Isn't that at 10 though?
Looks like we've
got some time to kill.
[GROUP gasps]
Two and a half hours?
[SERINUMA] These should
help keep you toasty!
I brought enough
for the five of us.
Don't want you to get cold.
Thank you.
[IGARASHI]
We'll do it.
[SHINOMIYA]
Only two and a half hours.
[NANASHIMA]
That's nothin'.
[SERINUMA] They didn't
realize it at the time,
but after the doors opened
it would take another hour
to get our badges.
Sorry about that, fellas.
Shall we take a look?
As we discussed... we can split
up to help Serinuma shop.
[GROUP]
We have to navigate all this?
You don't have to.
I appreciate the help.
I know it's a lot.
I don't think there's anything
here that we'd want to buy.
This is too much
to look for by yourself.
Okay, then. Thank you.
Have fun!
[SERINUMA] They're so nice
to help me with this.
I hope I'm not being selfish.
It's a lot to ask.
Sorry!
[NANASHIMA]
Shoulda known.
Can't believe we
volunteered for this.
What's with these girls
and their creepy smiles?
[GIRL 04B]
Love it!
We'd like... the new
issue... for our friend!
[GIRL 04A]
Sure!
[NANASHIMA]
Gah! How can he be so calm?
Has he bought this
kind of stuff before?
[IGARASHI]
Stay strong, Nana.
Remember why we're doing this.
[GIRL 04A]
I hope you enjoy it!
One down.
We can cross it off the list.
Uh, yeah.
The next one's gonna be...
at that booth over there.
[IGARASHI]
Just the one, please.
[GIRL 04C]
Yes, sir.
[NANASHIMA]
Here's the next one.
[GIRL 04D]
Help yourself.
[GIRL 04E]
Thank you very much!
[NANASHIMA]
Hurry, go!
Thank you so much.
[GIRL 04F]
We appreciate your business.
Those two sweethearts
just can't get enough!
Look, they're blushing!
I bet they read them together!
[IGARASHI, NANASHIMA]
We don't!
Give me all the
new issues, please!
Okay!
You're a talented artist.
Wow! That means a lot to me!
[MUTSUMI]
It's stunning!
Did you write and illustrate
the whole book?
Yes!
Amazing.
I admire that you've worked
so hard on your craft.
[GIRLS]
He's an angel!
Is he glowing?
My eyes! My eyes!
[SHINOMIYA]
Come on!
Will you stop flirting so
we can this over with?
I meant what I said.
We should slow down
to appreciate
all the artists' hard work!
[SHINOMIYA]
No we shouldn't!
I'm ready to get
out of this place.
[MUTSUMI]
Why? Isn't it fun?
No, it's not!
I don't like being around
so many people.
It's hot. The books
are way too heavy.
It smells bad.
I'm tired... and I hate this.
And the worst part...
[GIRLS squealing]
You keep disappearing! Stop it!
I'll try.
Stay with me!
Why don't we try this?
I know!
When we get finished let's visit
the historical research group!
I give up.
Okay. You win.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
What was that?
They're adorable!
[SERINUMA]
Whew! I hit the jackpot!
[laughs]
I guess the others
haven't made it yet.
It's still a little
early though.
[SERINUMA] I need to figure out
a good way to thank them.
[camera shutter clicking]
[SERINUMA yells]
[CAMERAMAN 04A]
Oh, yeah, that's the stuff.
Strike a pose for me, cutie?
Oh, I'm not cosplaying!
There's no need to
take any pictures!
[CAMERAMAN 04A]
Aw, don't be like that!
Just a few more shots.
Why don't ya turn around for me?
[whimpering]
[CAMERAMAN 04A]
Now this is a nice angle.
[NISHINA] What bad
manners you have, sir.
[SERINUMA gasps]
You should know better.
What's your problem?
A respected photographer always
carries himself with decorum.
You should never take
photos of a lady who refuses.
Can't you hear them? Listen.
Get lost, ya creep!
Guys like you
give us a bad name!
Loser!
[NISHINA]
What a disappointment.
[CROWD]
Go home! Go home!
Please... stop!
You'll never do it
again, will you?
You'll ask permission!
Now go on and think about that!
Fine, lady! Jeez! Sorry!
[SERINUMA]
That was nuts.
How kind you are to let him
off with a mere scolding.
[SERINUMA]
Thank you for stepping in!
Troublemakers pop up
every now and again.
Do take care.
[SERINUMA] Are you...
Sebasin from Gray Butler ?
You look wonderful!
Yes.
Oh! You look
so much like him!
Your cosplay is perfect!
I thank you.
[NANASHIMA]
Over here!
Ugh, this place is a maze!
We had a hard time
figuring out where to go.
[SERINUMA]
No big deal!
How fascinating.
So many men.
My goodness.
They should keep
a better eye on you.
What? Who's this weird dude?
My friend. A guy...
...was taking pictures of me!
Now.
I shall leave the rest to your
princes and excuse myself.
This was truly a
pleasure, m'lady.
[ALL gasp]
Adieu.
He... put his lips on her!
You're okay, right?
I'll go chase him down!
Ugh! No! I'm fine!
Some man was taking pictures
of me without permission,
but that guy stopped him!
Huh? Before we got here?
Sorry.
We should've met up
with you sooner.
It's not your fault.
Please don't worry!
Since we're together,
I have something to say.
Thank you for
being here with me.
And... I really owe you one.
You're awesome.
[NANASHIMA]
Finally!
You guys ready to party?
[IGARASHI]
Yeah! You know it!
[SHINOMIYA]
I'm just ready to sit down.
We've been walking for hours.
[MUTSUMI] I think I'm gonna
come back next year.
[SERINUMA] They didn't
realize it at the time,
but the crowds at the train
station would be even worse
than they were at the
beginning of the day.
So when it was finally time for
the karaoke Christmas party,
they were too worn
out to celebrate at all!
[SERINUMA screeching]
[NANASHIMA]
Aw, will you give it a rest?
[IGARASHI]
So tired.
[NAKANO laughs]
Do you think you
should've warned them
about how tired they'd get?
Comiket can be tough!
Y'know... I'm surprised
that I outlasted them.
I'm a warrior!
Your passions
kept you strong, girl!
Fandom power! Exactly right!
Oh, yeah!
There's more!
I met a Sebasin with the best
cosplay I've ever seen.
Got any pics?
I didn't even think about it.
Aww! I'd do anything
to get one picture!
[NISHINA]
That's good to know.
[NISHINA chuckles]
Why not take one now?
Uh... what?
You? How?
No way! You're a student here?
Ah!
Yep. I'm in class 1-F.
[SERINUMA]
He's a...
[NISHINA]
I'm Shima Nishina.
Pleased to meet you.
[SERINUMA]
He's a girl?!
[GROUP gasps]
It's... the weird guy!
How are you?
Let me introduce Shima Nishina.
This girl is a first year
like you are, Shinomiya.
Why ya keepin' her a secret?
I don't know her.
Grow up.
So, yeah.
Why does this guy
look like a girl now?
What are the odds that
someone with the best cosplay
I've ever seen goes
to school with us?
We met, and it turns
out that she and I
have a lot of things in common!
[BOTH laugh]
Well then I guess
that kiss doesn't count.
[GIRL 04O]
Nishina.
Wanna come sit with us?
What are you doing
for New Year's?
If you're free I'd love to have
you come over to my house
for a party.
Nishina!
We're gonna go
play some volleyball.
Wanna come be on my team?
That not fair!
I was gonna ask first!
[NANASHIMA] Why do I feel
as lame as you are?
[SHINOMIYA] I know you're dumb,
but can't you see?
She's part of their world.
[NANASHIMA]
What a brilliant tactic.
[SHINOMIYA]
We don't stand a chance.
I have to say...
It's a surprise to find out that
you go to our school, but...
I don't think you two
met by chance.
Oh. I did hear some
things about Serinuma
before going to Comiket,
but meeting her there
was a coincidence.
[NISHINA]
Was it too good to be true?
A delightful meeting
by random chance.
Perhaps we could
call it destiny?
I'd like to get
to know you better.
If you're interested,
I'd love to have you...
come home with me
so we can talk about anime.
[SERINUMA] She's inviting me
over to talk about Mirage Saga ?
I'm in!
Hold it!
Us too!
I was just thinkin' about
how I don't know squat
about that show you watch!
Right... you... guys?
I'd like to hear about it!
Talking about anime isn't
a waste of time at all!
You can count me in!
Mind if I join you?
Really?
You'll let me go on
and on about the show?
Dreams come true!
Yeah!
I can't wait to hear all
about the dudes you want
dating each other.
You know it!
Can't wait!
Well, then.
I'm more than happy
to invite you all.
However, if you'd like
to come over,
I do have to make one
very small request of you.
[SERINUMA]
It's a mansion!
We're happy to have you
home again, Lady Shima.
Please... come in.
My room is upstairs.
[NANASHIMA]
I don't get it.
What does this chick make
me feel like less of a man?
[SHINOMIYA]
I'm so inadequate. Pathetic.
[NISHINA]
Take a look.
This room is dedicated
to my figure collection.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh,
oh, my gosh!
So many little Shions to love!
Hello, babies!
Mama sees you in there!
[NISHINA] I bought this one from
last year's Wonder Festival.
That's cool!
So much detail! Wow!
Isn't this a limited-edition
figure by that famous sculptor?
Did you paint this yourself?
Yep... all me.
Great job!
[IGARASHI, SHINOMIYA, NANASHIMA]
Ugh. We've lost her.
[SERINUMA]
Gorgeous!
Tsuruga Castle. Hikone Castle.
Did you paint each
of these models as well?
Yes... they're scale models.
Oh, my.
I'm still quite amateur.
[NANASHIMA]
Fight it, Mutsumi!
Fight it!
This is all part of her plan.
I'm not gonna fall for it!
That's right!
[IGARASHI] Their hate
brought them together.
This is my costume room.
These are all the clothes I've
made for different conventions.
Whoa. I wish I could
make clothes like this.
[NISHINA] I have to say, the
dress you made for Shinomiya
was simply breathtaking.
I was quite impressed.
[SERINUMA]
You were?
I attended the play.
And you...
were the cutest thing ever.
Don't call me cute!
Don't you want me to
tell you how pretty you were?
[SHINOMIYA]
Of course I don't!
You think you're funny?
Yeah, you let her know!
I would never make fun of you.
You carried yourself
with such grace.
I was spellbound!
Thank you. I guess.
[NANASHIMA]
You fell for that?
There's no way you
idiots are this gullible!
[IGARASHI]
Easy, there.
She'll slip up... it's only
a matter of time.
Now. There's one room I can't
wait to for you to see.
[SERINUMA yelling]
[SERINUMA]
Comic books, graphic novels
limited edition releases,
rare prints, doujinshi for days!
This collection is hot
and ripe for the picking!
Unbelievable!
[screaming]
May... I... touch... them?
Please do.
[SERINUMA]
The Zebra Stripe series!
She's got all of them.
Why are there so many
I've never seen before?
So then... she's more
obsessed than you are?
Oh. I helped make that.
[SERINUMA, NANASHIMA]
Huh?!
That's my series. I draw.
I'm so honored that
you read them!
You're a freakin' liar!
No one can be good
at that many things!
What's wrong with you?
She's a fake!
Can't you see that?
So you're... So you're
the great author Yokojima?
[panting]
Yes. Give me one moment.
I'll prove it.
Here.
[NISHINA]
Does this convince you?
Are you some kind of goddess?!
[GROUP]
Whoa. She's good.
I want you to know...
I... love to read
Zebra Stripe books.
I always buy them.
And... I'm honored to be in
your presence; may I touch you?
I think... I just... I'm so
in love with your work!
Calm down, Serinuma.
That's so kind of you.
I'd love to draw
for you anytime.
Your wish is my command.
[echoing]
Marry me.
Cut it out!
Anyone can draw a picture!
Let me show you how it's done!
I got a B in art class!
A B is a perfectly
average grade!
All right! How's that?
[NANASHIMA]
I'm a failure!
The girl is rich.
Good looking. Talks cool.
She can do anything!
She's way too perfect!
How could I ever compete?
I'm throwin' in the towel.
[SERINUMA]
Wow!
This is Shion... isn't it?
[NANASHIMA]
Huh?
It's so cute!
Do you mind if I take it home?
You don't want that. It sucks.
No way! It's cute!
It's one of the best pictures
of Shion I've ever seen!
Okay... well in
that case it's yours.
I drew Shion too.
Mine has a little crown!
[SERINUMA]
Ah! Love 'em!
[NANASHIMA] She's happy with
anything as long as it's Shion!
[chuckles]
Now, then.
Do you remember when I told you
that I had one small request?
Oh... right.
Come this way.
[SERINUMA]
What are we doing?
I want the boys
to model for me.
Just for fun!
Huh?
You're a photographer too?
Don't you think that's
a strange thing to ask?
I get it.
[SERINUMA] You wanns get
a few shots of these hot men
together, right?
[NISHINA]
Yes!
[SERINUMA] They're totally
oblivious to how good they look!
[NISHINA]
Yeah!
They'll be perfect to use
as character references
for my next project.
[SERINUMA]
That's a great idea!
Let's go for it!
Okay!
Time to pair up, everyone!
Igarashi with Nanashima.
You guys are up first!
[NANASHIMA] What were you
two whispering about?
[NISHINA]
Looking good!
Bring your faces in.
Look into each other's eyes.
[NISHINA] Good! Keep your
lips parted just like that.
[NISHINA]
That's perfect!
Now how about resting
your chin on his shoulder?
[MUTSUMI]
Like this?
[SHINOMIYA squeals]
[MUTSUMI] Shinomiya, you use the
same laundry detergent as I do.
It smells so good.
Stop!
[SERINUMA screams]
This is heaven!
Why don't one of you lay
your head in the other's lap?
No! What're you, nuts?!
What?
I thought you made a promise.
We've done more than enough
to fulfill our commitment!
[SERINUMA]
Shima!
It'll be faster if we
show them how it's done.
Watch closely, boys!
[SERINUMA] You must gently
caress your partner's face.
It implies affection and catches
the eye of the viewer.
[GROUP]
What are we looking at?
Then you bring your
face close to his.
Slowly part your lips.
[SERINUMA gasps]
Sorry!
Oh, wow! I'm so embarrassed.
[NISHINA]
My dear... don't stop.
[GROUP gasps]
Get your grubby lips
off Serinuma!
Yeah... ew!
[NANASHIMA]
Are you crazy?
[SERINUMA]
This girl... kissed me!
[NISHINA]
I wasn't joking!
Hey! Listen!
Getting kissed by another
girl doesn't mean anything!
I can kiss you to get the
taste out of your mouth!
Me too! I'll kiss you right now!
[NISHINA]
I said I wasn't joking.
We'll have a problem if
you don't take me seriously.
Is that so?
[NAKANO]
Kae Serinuma, 17 years old.
Her first kiss was
with a handsome girl.
[NISHINA] Serinuma,
whenever I see you eat,
the food always
looks so succulent!
You're absolutely lovely.
[SERINUMA]
Really? Thank you!
I'd love to share a meal
with you sometime!
[NISHINA]
It would be an honor,
though I can eat enough
for the both of us!
[SERINUMA]
But you're so slender!
How do you do it?
[NISHINA]
Nothing special, I'm afraid.
Everyone in my family is slim,
so it's probably in my genes.
[SERINUMA] Well, in my family,
my brother is pretty skinny!
It might have something
to do with me always
stealing his candy
when we were little.
I'd gobble it up
before he even realized!
[NISHINA] I get the feeling
that you and your brother
share a special bond.