[SERINUMA] "A prince should
always be with a princess."
Who's the one in charge
of making rules like that?
[grunts]
--[GIRLS cheer]
--[whistle blows]
Nice one, Igarashi!
Thanks, man.
Nana... nice set.
Well, yeah. Surprised?
Talk about conceited.
[SERINUMA]
Score...
[laughing]
[SERINUMA]
Score...
Score!
So cute!
[SERINUMA] A prince should
be with another prince!
Why can't it be like that?
It feels so right!
The way they're hanging off
of each other is so precious!
My heart is about to burst!
Lord, thank you
for my daily bread!
[GIRLS scream]
[SERINUMA yelps]
[FEMALE STUDENT 01A]
I hope Nana is all right!
[MALE STUDENT 01A] Jeez,
he really knocked the wind
outta her!
Wake up! You're fine, right?
Snap out of it!
[SERINUMA]
It's okay.
Seeing you two together
is my last memory.
Thank you for that, Nanashima.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Don't you die!
Get up, Serinuma!
Finally awake.
Thank goodness.
Can you see, Kae?
I'm fine. What happened?
Nanashima fell on
top of you in P.E.
You hit the wall and passed out,
so we brought you
to the infirmary.
Yeah, that's right.
That smile makes me wonder
if he hit you too hard.
I can't stop thinking
about their beautiful display
of sportsmanship.
A 5x7 was unfolding
right in front of me.
[NAKANO] Oh, girl, if those
two are on the table
then it's gotta be 7x5.
I'll climb aboard
that ship though!
Well, I respect
your opinion...
but without a doubt
it's gotta be 5x7.
That's cute and everything,
but think about 7x5.
I'm pretty sure we can both
agree that it's the natural
order of things.
Hate to say this,
but you just don't get it.
Right back at ya, Kae.
[SERINUMA]
My name is Kae Serinuma.
This is my second year
of high school.
I'm a little... well, actually,
it's pretty obvious!
I'm what you'd call a fujoshi !
I'm heating up!
[SERINUMA] I love seeing hot
guys get along with one another.
Sharing things, rough-housing...
I can't get enough!
When I witness the
splendor of a passionate bond
between two guys,
my chest starts getting hot
and I can't help but pair them!
Even if they don't have
a real connection,
my imagination is
more than enough!
Any chance I get,
I'll picture them together!
This is the way I live
my life and I am not ashamed!
Even classmates are no exception
to the whims of my fantasy.
Don't you think Nanashima
looks a lot like Shion
from Mirage Saga ?
[NAKANO] Ooh, in that
bad boy sorta way, right?
[SERINUMA]
Yeah!
[giggling]
Pardon me. Serinuma.
If you're feeling better now,
would you stop hogging the bed?
We have a student
who's actually ill.
Of course!
Sorry about that, Shinomiya.
I'll leave you to it.
Let's get going!
[NAKANO]
Sure.
You seem fine.
I hope you weren't faking.
What was that?
You little--
It's okay!
[laughs]
[NAKANO]
What's his problem?
[SERINUMA]
That's Shinomiya.
He's a first year who's on
the health committee with me.
Well between you and me,
his bedside manner
could use some work.
How can a pretty boy
be so harsh?
[SERINUMA] I think the uptight
attitude kinda works for him.
A snootier guy can be a tease--
so more fun to dream about!
That's so true!
The colder he acts,
the hotter he gets!
[laughing]
[MUTSUMI]
Serinuma?
What happened... to your face?
Heya, Mutsumi.
Just a little accident.
I can see that.
Are you all right?
Totally. Thanks for asking!
That's good. I'm glad.
[NAKANO] Kae, you seem
to have this weird connection
with hot guys.
[SERINUMA]
What? You think so?
[NAKANO]
Mutsumi is really cute.
Maybe I should join
the history club, too.
Whaddaya think?
[SERINUMA]
I'm in clubs.
I wouldn't call that
a connection.
She's awake!
You okay?
All good!
That's a relief.
You really went
flying back there.
The whole class was worried.
Nana.
What do you want?
Do ya think you could
come over and apologize?
[NANASHIMA groans]
Uh... sorry about that.
It's just a little concussion.
You didn't get hurt
or anything, did you?
[NANASHIMA chuckles]
You're like a human cushion,
so I walked off
without a scratch!
Human cushion?!
[STUDENTS laugh]
Dude. Not cool!
In that case, I'm happy
I could be useful.
[laughing]
Nana! Stop being a jerk!
Let go!
We're sorry about everything.
[SERINUMA]
Quiver!
You could be a
little more sensitive.
Was that supposed
to be an apology?
If he wasn't gonna take it
seriously, why even walk over?
You shouldn't let it bother you.
You heard, right?
Nanashima was the one
who fell on me,
but Igarashi apologized for him!
So cute! Adorable!
I can't stand it!
Pairing!
Okay, maybe you should
let it bother you a little bit.
I couldn't if I tried.
Their sweetness
is just too much!
[SERINUMA]
The truth is...
It wouldn't matter if
I do have some sort of
unexplained connection
with hot guys.
A prince should
be with a prince.
I can't deny the
longing in my soul.
Yes!
Shun me and turn to one another!
Peeping from the sidelines
is the sustenance I crave!
That's where I belong!
[NAKANO] Shion plays a big part
in Mirage Saga tonight,
doesn't he?
Yeah, I'm pumped
for this episode!
Sorry in advance
for spoiling it online.
I'll try to hold back.
[NAKANO laughs]
Sure.
See you tomorrow!
Have a good night!
[SERINUMA] Everything was going
my way...until that night.
[SERINUMA (SONG)] ♪ We reached
out to the sky and then we ♪
♪ gave one devoted prayer ♪
♪ Slash through the darkness
and prevail until the... ♪
My strongest opponent...
Ready to fight?
[SERINUMA]
Oh, Shion!
Today's animation is gorgeous!
--[SHION grunting]
--[swords clashing]
[SERINUMA humming]
[SERINUMA whimpering]
[SHION screams]
[GUY 01A]
Shion?
No, please!
This can't be the end!
Stand up, I'm begging you!
Shion!
[SERINUMA whimpering]
[SERINUMA screams]
[MITSUKI]
What's wrong?
What's the matter, Kae?
[TAKURO]
Will you shut up?!
[TEACHER 01A]
Kae Serinuma?
Don't tell me
she's absent again.
[NAKANO]
It's been a week now.
She's not answering her phone
and she hasn't been online.
I hope she's okay.
[MITSUKI]
Kae?
Kae!
You can't just hide
in your room forever.
Come out!
Sweetheart, I'm worried
that you haven't been eating.
Takuro... I'll need
your help with her.
[TAKURO yawns]
Huh?
Well? Fix this!
You worried about your
little sister, right?
She's such a pain!
Hey, fatty!
Get your butt outta that bed!
Stop moping!
Gimme... the damn... blanket!
[SERINUMA]
No!
Enough is enough!
You can't keep this up or
you'll get sick and die...
Is that what you want?
[grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[SERINUMA]
Fine, you win.
My hair's all oily anyway.
I guess I'll take a bath.
I need to tell A
where I've been.
Shion...
What the...?
Who hung a poster
in the bathroom?
[SERINUMA]
Mom! Help!
There's something wrong
with the mirror!
My baby girl!
It really is you!
[TAKURO yells]
That's freaky!
[SERINUMA]
Is this real?
I feel so different.
It's strange...
but what can I do?
I guess this is the
way things are now.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Good morning.
[SERINUMA]
Oh, no.
Everyone's staring.
Does my uniform look that weird?
Why did I try to make it fit?
I should've stayed home!
Oh, A!
[crying]
I've missed you and
I should've reached out,
but I broke my phone!
There's no way...
Kae, what happened to you?
[STUDENTS scream]
Wait...
Are you really Serinuma?
You're like a totally
different person.
--How'd you do it?
--That's crazy!
[SERINUMA]
Please, stop!
Give it a rest!
Can't you see you're
freaking her out?
Back off!
You okay?
Thanks for the help, Igarashi.
[IGARASHI]
No prob.
[MALE STUDENT 01B]
You gotta be kidding me.
Kinda sad to see everyone
going nuts now that she's cute.
Right, Nanashima?
[MALE STUDENT 01F]
Dude is totally checked out.
Yeah. There's no way
that's Serinuma.
I guess you think
you're pretty hot stuff.
Please don't start.
But we'll never forget
what you used to be.
Got that?
Kae, come back!
[MALE STUDENT 01B]
Whoa! You made her cry!
[MALE STUDENT 01F] She was
only in class for five seconds!
[FEMALE STUDENT 01A]
You're the worst!
Me? No way!
[SERINUMA]
It's no use!
I can't even look at Nanashima
without thinking of poor Shion!
[SERINUMA crying]
Don't run in the halls!
You should watch
where you're going!
Sorry, Shinomiya.
I have to go now.
[SHINOMIYA]
W-Wait!
Why? What's wrong?
Well... we need to... go.
To the infirmary!
That's right!
You fell so you have
to go to the infirmary.
[SERINUMA]
Shinomiya is being nice to me?
He's usually acts so snobby.
[SHINOMIYA]
Here we are.
[SERINUMA]
Mutsumi?
Why do your arms
have scratches on them?
On the way to school,
I saved a kitten
that was stuck in a tree.
Dug its claws in
and wouldn't let go.
[SERINUMA]
That's such a sweet thing to do!
I'm glad you're back
in school, Serinuma.
[SHINOMIYA]
Huh?
Is there something wrong?
What's her name again?
[MUTSUMI]
Huh? Serinuma?
Kae Serinuma.
[SHINOMIYA]
It can't be true!
[SERINUMA] Guess I've changed
so much most people can't
recognize me.
[MUTSUMI] You've gotten
a little thinner, I suppose.
But it's still easy
to tell who you are.
I'm glad.
You're the only one who knew
it was me right off the bat.
[MUTSUMI]
Really?
You're the kind person
you've always been.
That's what matters.
That means so much to me.
[SERINUMA]
That's exactly right.
I'm still me.
I may look different, but
nothing has changed at all!
I was wondering if you'd
like to go see a movie
with me next Sunday.
[NANASHIMA]
Igarashi!
Get lost!
Man! You knew
I was gonna ask her!
Oh, yeah?
[SHINOMIYA]
Serinuma!
If possible, could I please
have a moment of your time?
Oh, there was something
I wanted to ask you.
Uh... uh...
[SERINUMA]
Right.
Nothing has changed... at all.
[SERINUMA]
Well? What do you think?
[NAKANO]
Ah!
It's cute, but there's no
way I'm letting you walk out
with those shorty shorts on.
[NAKANO]
'Kay, now give this a try!
[SERINUMA]
What? More clothes?
No whining allowed!
You're the one who asked
to borrow my wardrobe.
Jeez!
Sorry. You're right.
[NAKANO] Wow, I didn't think
this day would ever come.
Kae's going on a date.
[SERINUMA]
Really?
You think...
I can call this a date?
S'cuse us.
If you don't mind, Serinuma
and I were speaking in private.
Always quick to
make the first move.
Dude, you're obvious.
I'm sorry for running in terror.
That was rude of me.
Can I borrow the next book
in the series you lent me?
The last one was superb.
Wait!
I can't hear what you're saying
when you're all talking at once!
All right, I'll go first.
I was asking if you wanted to go
to a movie with me this weekend.
I was coming over
to ask you the same thing!
Me, too!
I... was, as well.
I didn't know what to do so I
ended up saying yes to everyone.
Like a dating game?
Yeah, an otome .
I don't understand why all
of this is happening to me!
[NAKANO sighs] Who could resist
asking out a cute girl like you?
Oh, yeah, how's that
top treating you?
[SERINUMA] It's a little
tight around my chest.
Is that right?
It'll be fun!
What's the problem?
I dunno, A. What if
I'm not ready for this?
No, Kae.
When a man hurts you...
other men can help you heal.
[SERINUMA]
Shion!
Time to get out there
to expand your guild
and explore new genres!
[SERINUMA] Fictional guys
are way easier to deal with!
Have you told your boyfriend
that you're an otaku yet?
No way!
It'd be over if he knew
all the stuff I'm into!
My advice is not
to let them know
how much of a fangirl you are.
'Kay! It'll be easy! I think.
[NAKANO] One night will
be a piece of cake!
Yeah!
[WOMEN giggling]
[WOMAN 01A]
So hot...
Oh, yeah... that's good.
[SERINUMA]
Look at those delicious men!
So perfect!
[slurps]
I could spend the rest
of my days watching them
just like this.
[IGARASHI]
Serinuma! Over here!
Hi. I'm sorry I
kept you waiting.
Don't worry about it.
So cute...
[IGARASHI]
Shall we?
[NANASHIMA] So who picked
this movie anyway?
[SHINOMIYA]
This way.
[SERINUMA]
All right!
No fantasies allowed,
starting right now!
Please wake up.
The evening is fast approaching.
[NANASHIMA]
Jeez, this is so boring.
I'm out.
[SERINUMA gasps]
It was actually
pretty good, wasn't it?
[NANASHIMA yawns]
Yep! Great movie!
[SERINUMA]
Good grief!
I got so distracted ogling
those two I didn't even
watch the movie!
The characters
were dull and the plot
was nowhere to be found.
Here, use one of these.
[SERINUMA gasps]
I'm fine, thanks.
I thought you might
appreciate something
for your runny nose.
I don't have a runny nose!
We both know that you do.
[SERINUMA]
What an unexpected delight!
A calm senpai who cleverly
handles his stubborn kohai .
Don't mind if I--
No more fantasies!
[SERINUMA]
I'll be right back.
Away, dark thoughts.
--Away, dark...
--[IGARASHI] Hey, wait.
Shh.
Igarashi?
[gasps]
[SERINUMA]
The others!
[IGARASHI]
Don't worry about them.
Come with me.
What are we doing?
Taking pictures?
Well...
I know we won't get
to be alone tonight,
so let me have you
to myself for a bit.
'Kay?
[SERINUMA]
What do I do?
I can't explain it.
My heart is beating so fast.
Now smile.
What the hell
is going on in here?
You're good.
How'd you figure me out?
[NANASHIMA]
You think you're that slick?
I know exactly what's
on your mind!
[IGARASHI]
I'm not that bad.
[SERINUMA]
Oh, my gosh!
An original 5x7 photo!
This national treasure belongs
in a museum but it's all mine!
[gasps]
How can I say that when
I just got all flustered
over a guy like
some normal girl?
What the heck is wrong with me?!
I'm losing it!
I don't think I can
do this for much longer!
Ready to order?
[SHINOMIYA]
I'd like a SLT burger meal,
with fries and a soda.
[SERINUMA] The Captain
Teke Teke Full Heart Set.
Super cute. I want it.
[SHINOMIYA]
What would you like?
I'll have black tea
and an apple pie!
[SERINUMA]
I've gotta ride this out!
[NANASHIMA (SONG)]  ♪ Teach me
all of the words that say... ♪
[SERINUMA] I'm dying to try
Shion's character song!
What are you going to sing?
I'm still picking!
You guys go ahead and I'll
do my song last, okay?
Sounds good!
[SERINUMA]
Letting them know I'm an otaku
would ruin everything!
I'll stay strong
even if it kills me!
Serinuma.
I hope you're feeling all right.
[SERINUMA]
I'm fine.
Really? Because you look like
you're going to be sick.
I'm fit as a fiddle, promise!
I'm having a lot of fun tonight.
If you're tired,
we could step into
a café to rest.
[SERINUMA] That's really
considerate of you,
but there's no need.
I should probably start
home soon anyway.
[SHOPKEEP 01A] Limited edition
Mirage Saga merchandise!
Available in this store,
only for today!
[SERINUMA]
No...!
This is the last shipment
from the manufacturer!
[SERINUMA]
What?!
[SERINUMA] Any special merch
will be gone in no time.
This is obviously some divine
intervention beckoning me in,
tempting me with precious goods!
What if there's something
super rare inside,
and this is my one chance?
I have to go check it out!
[NANASHIMA]
Hey, Serinuma?
What's the matter with you?
Uh, nothing!
[SERINUMA]
You're doing great!
Take some deep breaths and
focus on staying in control.
You've kept it together
all this time.
Don't throw it away now!
Not with the end in sight!
[SHOPKEEP 01A] We have
only one limited item left!
Sorry about this.
But I...
I have to go.
I have to go!
Serinuma!
[IGARASHI]
There she is.
[GROUP gasps]
I'm sorry.
I cannot deny it.
I'm an otaku.
Oh. Fangirl.
I apologize for
running off like that.
If I had let the opportunity
for rare merch slip away...
I'd regret it for
the rest of my life!
It's precious.
Seriously?
[SERINUMA] I'm still surprised
that you asked me out.
I really tried to act
like a normal girl,
but I didn't have it in me.
[SERINUMA]
It was all for nothing.
I blew it.
[SERINUMA] I worried so much
about not showing you my flaws
that I couldn't enjoy myself.
I'm so sorry.
[GROUP gasps]
[SERINUMA] But... I can't
pretend to be something I'm not.
Thanks for today.
I'll never forget it.
Sorry.
I mean no disrespect...
but what's the problem?
You have interests.
Isn't that a good thing?
There's no harm in that.
Your eyes are sparkling.
For the first time this
evening, you're glowing.
I like it.
You're lovely.
Thank you so much!
[GROUP gasps]
This is so much better than
the weird lifeless eyes
you've had all night.
I was starting to think
you had the personality
of a dead fish.
Ya know, I've seen anime
before... Evangahlion ?
[SHINOMIYA]
Don't worry about it.
[NANASHIMA] Why don't you pick
the next stop for the night?
[IGARASHI]
We're down for anything!
You mean it?
Thank you so much!
I know exactly
where I want to go!
We can check out
the store again!
Is that cool?
[SERINUMA]
And that's how it went.
We had such a great time!
They were all so nice to me.
And... This is the best part.
I got a 5x7!
Kae, why'd you even
go on a date with them?
And it's 7x5.
[NANASHIMA]
So spill it, Igarashi.
Have you ever had
a crush on anyone?
[IGARASHI]
Of course I have.
[NANASHIMA]
Oh, yeah?
Well, what's your type?
[IGARASHI]
What's with the interrogation?
[NANASHIMA]
You ashamed or something?
[IGARASHI] I guess I like a
mature girl who has a good head
on her shoulders.
[NANASHIMA]
No way!
I figured you'd want a girl
who's your age or younger.
[IGARASHI sighs]
It's not about age.
I just can't deal with girls
who are loud and childish.
[NANASHIMA] Your type of girl
sounds way too predictable.
Kinda dull.
I go for the ladies who
are upbeat and bright.
They're way more fun that way!