[NANASHIMA]
Here we go again.
Same people, same place.
Talkin' about the same old crap.
But I've been noticin'
things are startin'
to feel...
...different.
[IGARASHI laughing]
[IGARASHI]
It's time for today's handshake.
It'll help you get
more comfortable.
[SERINUMA laughs]
Um...
--Okay.
--Good!
So how do you feel?
Um... it's just a handshake.
No big deal.
Then why don't we
turn it up a notch?
[SERINUMA gasps]
[IGARASHI]
Too much too soon?
Sorry about that.
Let's start over.
[SERINUMA]
Uh, I guess that's okay.
Just the handshake, right?
Thanks for that.
I love the new episode.
Their bond got so much deeper!
Katchu Ranbu changed my life.
I'm glad we can share this!
[NANASHIMA]
And these two...
Ever since they had
that throwdown,
they're even closer
than they were before!
They're all over each other!
[LORD 06A] We have a
new skill! Take this!
Sametora Flame-Horned Slugger!
Oh. The Sametora
Flame-Horned Slugger.
How'd you know?
Remember my dream?
You performed that same
move with such grace!
I love it!
Good thing we had our
charms to protect us, right?
Your heroism is legendary!
You defeated a samurai
and his ghostly army!
It's so cool!
If only it were real.
Please wake up. Serinuma?
Wait... A dream?
But... No way.
Something wrong?
Uh... no.
[SERINUMA] Was it real?
Was it a dream?
I can't tell anymore.
[NANASHIMA] She doesn't
know how obvious she is.
Blushing around Mutsumi?
You gotta be kidding me!
Even Shinomiya is getting
somewhere with her!
[NANASHIMA]
I'm the only one falling behind.
[DIAMOND] As long as
Puri Puri Moon is here,
there will always
be stars to guide you!
Never fear!
[NANASHIMA] My one advantage
was that I kinda look like
the dead dude from
that anime she liked.
Now she's over it.
How am I supposed to keep
up with everybody else?
She's closer to them.
I don't like fighting
for her attention
with the rest of those dweebs,
but I don't wanna give her up.
[DIAMOND]
Ruby, we can't stop!
No matter how long it takes,
we have to keep trying!
[RUBY] If you believe,
all your dreams can come true!
[NANASHIMA]
Thought I was the man,
but guess I got ahead of myself.
They're walkin' all over me.
[KIRARI] Bubba, get up!
Our dance is starting!
[NANASHIMA]
Oh, yeah!
I wanna be Diamond this time.
[NANASHIMA]
Then I'll take Ruby!
[BOTH (SINGING)]
♪ Listen to ♪
♪ what my heart is saying ♪
♪ There is beauty
in being honest ♪
♪ And I know all of my
dreams can come true! ♪
♪ Puri Puri Puri Moon!
Yeah! ♪
♪ Sparkle, sparkle,
sparkle, and shine! ♪
♪ With your smile
bright as a gem! ♪
♪ I will let my heart
glow like a full moon ♪
♪ Every single day! ♪
♪ My heart! ♪
♪ Take a deep breath and
throw open your arms ♪
♪ Then let your dreams
fly you to the moon! ♪
♪ Puri Puri Puri Moon! ♪
♪ We'll always be
Puri Puri Puri Moon! ♪
Yay!
[NANASHIMA] How am I gonna
get anywhere with Serinuma
while I'm dancing away the
weekend with my little sister?
[KIRARI]
Bubba! It's time for my snack!
Right. Let's make some grub.
What kind of eggs?
Yummy! Fried, please!
You got it.
[NANASHIMA]
So I'll step up my game.
I'll get a date no
matter what it takes.
Puttin' it all out
there, startin' tomorrow!
Serinuma!
Would you like to take
a look at the chapter
I've been working on?
[NANASHIMA]
I didn't get a fair shot!
I would...
but I'm short on time
since I'm working
every day after school.
You work?
Is there a reason you got a job?
They're dropping
new like crazy next month!
It's gonna be huge!
The anime just started
so it's a pretty big deal.
I spent all my money on
the pilgrimage
so I'm totally broke.
There's no way I'm gonna miss
out on Katchu Ranbu toys,
albums, voice actor appearances,
the Katchu Ranbu Café,
oh, and the new stage show!
I gotta make some fat cash
as quick as I can!
I'll do anything for that dough!
My dignity is nowhere
near as important
as the merchandise I crave!
I won't be able to go
to any cons for a while.
Spending money on
my passions is essential!
I have no choice but
to join the workforce.
Uh... oh.
So where will
you be working?
Usami Land! Yep!
A flyer said they
were hiring part time!
I'll be working on the
Puri Puri Moon show!
Isn't that awesome?
I'll be playing Ruby!
I'd like to work on
the Puri Moon stage show.
That's right! Always watch
the cartoon. I love it.
Who's your favorite?
Favorite? Easy.
I think Puri Moon is awesome!
Puri Puri Moon
is the title of the show.
Why are you wasting my time?
Please, go home.
See? I'm an actor!
Oh, you have jokes.
I think I have the perfect
job for someone
with your unique skillset.
[NANASHIMA] They hooked
Igarashi up with his own boat
as the skipper of
The Amazon Cruise.
The Puri Puri Moon
show, please.
I can't work too often
because of due dates.
I draw... and comics
don't make themselves!
I also travel,
not much free time,
I'd be an asset to the company.
I'm not so sure
this would work out.
Oh, wait!
There is a place in the
park where we could use
the occasional new face.
[NANASHIMA] Nishina was assigned
to the pretty boy butler café!
No surprise there.
I've done some live theatre.
I'd like to apply for the
Puri Puri Moon show.
I'm more than happy
to work backstage.
You're a star!
I knew the perfect role
for you the moment I saw
your sweet face!
[NANASHIMA] Shinomiya was
cast as the cute little
Princess Usamimi!
[SHINOMIYA]
I'm not cute!
Such a nice show.
Uplifting, and kids
develop self-esteem.
[MALE CHIEF 08A]
Welcome to the team!
[NANASHIMA] Mutsumi was stuck
selling balloons as a mascot.
[NANASHIMA]
Finally.
Okay, so!
My sis and I watch
the show together.
I'm up to date with
the latest plot lines.
I know the songs.
I know the dances.
You're not gonna find
anybody better than me!
No way.
Oh... yeah?
Yes!
Diamond's pose!
As long as Puri
Puri Moon is here,
there will be stars
to guide you!
[MALE CHIEF 08A]
Dark Prince's pose.
Oh. You fools should give in.
For it's time to
summon the darkness.
--Hired!
--[NANASHIMA] I did it!
Looks like it's just you and me!
You ready for this?
You bet I am!
[NANASHIMA]
Yeah!
I finally have a chance
to get close to her!
Look who's king of the castle!
You're gonna play Dark Prince
in the Puri Puri Moon
stage show at Usami Land?
For real?
That's right!
That's so cool! Awesome!
I hafta watch it!
Listen.
I'll have to go to
rehearsals on the weekends.
That means I won't be with ya.
That cool?
I'm almost a grown up!
Go! Follow your rainbow!
You're gonna be awesome!
I'll be your coach if you
need help with anything.
[SERINUMA] A girl's heart can
glow like the moon anytime!
How was that?
Not too bad.
But for Ruby you gotta
put your hips into the pose
to get it right.
[NANASHIMA]
Ooh!
Wow, you're such an expert!
How are you so good at this?
You're a pro! Can we try it?
[IGARASHI] Things are going
pretty well for Nana.
A girl's heart can glow
like the moon anytime!
[IGARASHI] Too bad he
has to be such a dork
to get anywhere with her.
That's so cool!
You know all the dances
because your sister is a fan!
It's awesome!
Yeah, we watch it
together all the time.
I mean, I'm not into
that kind of thing,
but it's pretty deep
for a kid's show.
I totally agree!
There's so much great content!
[NANASHIMA]
This is freakin' amazing!
Serinuma and I are finally alone
together, and it's been great!
There's no one in our--
[IGARASHI]
Hey!
Mind if I walk you home?
[NANASHIMA]
No, no, no, no, no!
[SERINUMA] Are you finished
with your training, Igarashi?
Well, we've still got more
to work on, so beat it.
Nah, I'll wait.
Get out!
Not a chance.
[NANASHIMA] Igarashi comes by
every day to check up on us.
He's such a pain!
[NANASHIMA]
Who cares?
I'm not doing anything wrong.
[SERINUMA] We're still
meeting tomorrow morning
in front of the
ticket gate, right?
See you then!
[NANASHIMA]
I can't believe this.
It's happening!
I'm getting closer to Serinuma!
[footsteps]
You didn't eat breakfast! Bubba!
No time. I overslept.
[sneezes]
[KIRARI]
You sick?
No. I fell asleep without
drying my hair last night.
Wanna stay home?
I'll be fine! See ya!
[MAN 08A]
Go ahead and take your places.
Think of this as
a real performance.
[CROWD]
Okay!
Puri Puri Moon Diamond!
Ruby!
I'm Sapphire!
I'm Emerald!
I'm Alexandrite!
Well. Your time to shine.
Right.
[NANASHIMA]
What's up with this?
Something's not right.
[SERINUMA]
Nanashima!
Are you okay?
How's your head?
What's up?
[SERINUMA]
You have a fever.
The director said
you needed bedrest,
so a staff member drove us home.
You fainted in the
middle of rehearsal.
Everyone is so
worried about you.
I'm really glad you're awake.
I'm gonna stay here a little
while to make sure you're okay.
Oh, and I can make
you some food.
[SERINUMA]
She's staring at me.
Are you trying to be
Bubba's girlfriend?
[SERINUMA]
He's a good friend of mine.
We work and go to
school together!
[KIRARI gasps] Does that mean
you're in the Puri Moon
stage show with him?
As who?
I'm gonna play... Ruby.
Really? She's the best one!
After Diamond.
I like her, but I'm not
letting you steal my brother.
Nope.
I'm sure Nanashima
loves you very much.
He does.
When Mommy and
Daddy aren't home,
he makes sure I'm taken care of.
I gave him permission
to put his job first
while I handle
things around here!
I'm not a little kid, ya know.
--[KIRARI] Ha ha!
--[SERINUMA] Oh, I see.
I taught Bubba the
Puri Moon dance steps.
Are you learning them?
Hope so.
You're gonna have
to save the world!
Yup!
You can be friends,
but he's gonna marry me!
Got it?
[NANASHIMA]
Serinuma was in my bedroom.
Nana.
I've never been in a boy's room.
This is my first time.
Glad you're here.
Sorry it's small.
No way. It's just right.
Besides... A small... room...
...brings us closer, right?
I hope so.
Let's find out.
Nanashima.
[knock on door]
Did I wake you?
I've got your lunch.
Oh. Fever.
What? They left?
[DIAMOND]
Yeah, a while ago.
Nanashima wasn't feeling well,
so Serinuma volunteered
to take him home.
She went home with Nana?
[SERINUMA gasps]
Nana? What...?
[SERINUMA]
Why?
You're cute.
So hot...
Stop! Nana, are
you still asleep?
Let go of me!
[SERINUMA]
He won't get off.
What do I do?
Please wake up!
Let me go! Stop it!
Nana!
[IGARASHI] Dude, are you
out of your mind?
Come back!
What's up? She leave?
Wait!
No!
You've got to stop!
[IGARASHI growls]
[IGARASHI]
What's wrong with you?
Huh? Hey!
Love you!
When ya wanna get marr--Ah!
[IGARASHI]
Snap out of it!
[NANASHIMA gasps]
What? No!
I did that to her?
Really?
Yep.
No!
What's wrong with me?
I have to apologize to her!
[IGARASHI] This is going to
be a huge step backward.
[NAKANO]
She has a cold.
She told me she
wouldn't be in class.
You didn't know?
[NANASHIMA] She's won't answer
my calls and hasn't read
any of the messages I've sent.
She's ignoring me.
Of course she is.
Do ya think she's
gonna be at practice?
Who knows?
[MAN 08A]
Ruby's sick today.
[DIAMOND]
But what about the performance?
[MAN 08A] We'll have
to use her understudy.
[NANASHIMA] Maybe she'll
talk to me in person.
Probably not.
After what I did to her,
why would she?
I could go anyway.
Maybe she'll let
me explain and... No!
I have no right to speak to her.
[NANASHIMA]
Yo, I'm home.
[KIRARI]
Hi, Bubba!
Guess what? I drew this!
You can have it!
Aw!
You are such a good artist.
[KIRARI] This is Dark Prince
and this is Ruby.
Show it to the girl from
the other day, okay?
[KIRARI]
Yeah!
It's a good luck charm
so the show'll go well!
[NANASHIMA]
Kirari!
I'll be right back okay?
This won't take long!
[SERINUMA sneezes]
[UKE] Cut it out!
That's not what I meant!
[SEME]
Is that right?
That's not what
your body's saying.
[UKE]
Stop... stop it!
[SERINUMA screams]
Why do I like it
so much in fiction?!
But... when it happens
for real, it's horrible.
[SERINUMA]
I get it, but I'm still scared.
What do I do?
--[knock on door]
--[TAKURO] Hey!
You have a visitor.
Blonde guy.
[SERINUMA] Uh...
Uh, tell him I'm not home.
What? No way--
[SERINUMA]
Just do it!
What's wrong with you?
If your boy toys are buggin'
out, take care of it yourself!
[SERINUMA]
No!
I'm not ready to deal
with this yet!
[NANASHIMA]
Serinuma!
I know you're up there!
Please, listen!
I wasn't myself, but that's
no excuse for what I did.
I'm sorry that I hurt you.
I'm sorry for every time
I've been a jerk.
You don't have to forgive me!
Stop! Cut it out!
[NANASHIMA]
I want to earn your friendship!
But I'll back off for
good if you feel unsafe.
Will you please dance with me?
Just this once?
Shut up!
Why are you yellin'
in front of our house
like a nutcase?
You want people
callin' the cops?
Get outta here!
[NANASHIMA] Okay, okay!
Sorry! I'm leavin'!
Do me a solid and make
sure this gets to Serinuma?
[SERINUMA]
Should I go?
[MAN 08B]
Is she here?
Not yet.
[MAN 08A]
That's too bad.
We'll have to use her stand-in.
[SERINUMA]
Sorry I'm late.
Can I still go on?
All right. You sure?
[SERINUMA]
Yeah. I feel a lot better!
[MAN 08A]
Then go ahead and change.
You really came.
No prob.
Thank you.
Even though I know you
weren't in your right mind
the other day,
I'm still nervous about it.
I trust that you
wouldn't lie to me.
But I'll... need... some time.
I understand.
Thanks for coming.
Are you ready? It's showtime.
[CROWD chattering]
It's packed today.
[SHINOMIYA]
Can we sit up front?
[MUTSUMI] That space is reserved
for the younger children.
I suppose juvenile adults
count as children?
[MALE FAN 08A] It's first come
first serve on the seats, lady!
We ain't movin' for nobody!
You got a problem with that?
You can stay, but you
need to sit down
so the kids can see.
I can't believe those losers
haven't been banned yet.
They always come
to the live shows.
Why won't the staff
ever step in?
All right!
Take a deep breath and call for
Puri Moon as loud as you can!
Puri Puri Moon!
[GROUP]
Those are the costumes?
[MALE FANS] Puri Puri Moon
Moon Puri Moon Moon!
[WOMAN 08A]
Please sit down! [grunts]
Lookin' good, Diamond!
Check out those legs!
--Our kids can't see!
--[KIDS crying]
--Hey... sit down!
Just one touch!
[DIAMOND yelps]
[SERINUMA]
Diamond!
[NANASHIMA]
Puri Puri Moon!
It seems that we share
a common enemy.
Why don't we deal with them
before facing one other?
Shall we call a temporary truce?
Those aren't the
lines in the script.
What's going on?
Hope you don't mind.
I can take it from here.
Well!
It seems that Ruby and the Dark
Prince have formed a dream team!
Check 'em out!
Give those two a hand!
--[KIDS] You can do it!
--[MEN] You got this!
[KIRARI]
I love you!
[NANASHIMA]
Begone, fools!
Take a hint!
You guys gonna help me out?
I'll take care of this!
[SERINUMA]
Watch out!
[NANASHIMA grunts]
[SERINUMA]
Nanashima!
I've got you.
[NANASHIMA]
Serinuma.
Thank you.
[MALE FAN 08C]
Let go of her!
The Dark Prince is never
allowed to touch my Ruby!
[NANASHIMA]
I swear.
I will never hurt you again.
[SERINUMA] I believe you,
Nanashi--Dark Prince!
[SERINUMA]
Ready?
[NANASHIMA]
I'm with you.
[SERINUMA, NANASHIMA]
Dark Moonlight... Attack!
Our Dream Team
just saved the day!
You did it!
Thanks for taking care of that.
One group number to go.
[DIAMOND]
Sorry, everyone!
When I fell, I twisted my ankle.
I won't be able to dance.
Where's your sub?
[DIAMOND] I don't think
she showed up today.
[NANASHIMA]
I've got your back.
Let me do the dance.
Here it comes!
Hope you're ready!
It's time for the
Puri Puri Moon song!
[music plays]
[ALL (SONG)] ♪ Sparkle, sparkle,
sparkle, and shine! ♪
♪ With your smile
bright as a gem! ♪
♪ I will let my heart glow
like a full moon ♪
♪ Every single day! ♪
♪ My heart! ♪
♪ Take a deep breath and
throw open your arms ♪
♪ Then let your dreams
fly you to the moon! ♪
♪ Puri Puri Puri Moon! ♪
♪ We'll always be
Puri Puri Puri Moon! ♪
Way to go!
You're my friend.
I believe you. Thanks a lot.
Sure thing. I meant it.
[KIRARI laughing]
Nice going!
[KIRARI]
I knew it!
You played Diamond
during the group dance!
I know my Bubba's moves!
You were so good out there!
Because of you!
Great job!
I taught you well.
Sure did. Thank, Sis.
[SHINOMIYA laughing]
This might be the
happiest day of my life.
How exquisite!
You look cute.
Oh, gimme a break,
you guys!
It's not like I had a choice!
Yeah, right.
You just happened
to know all the moves.
I can explain!
[NANASHIMA] He's right!
I'm a walking punchline.
How could anyone
respect me in this get-up?
Do me the honor of
a quick photoshoot
before you change?
That's enough!
Do you think Nanashima looks
better in a dress than I do?
Both of you make
fabulous princesses.
That's right!
My brother's the
best princess ever!
Her, too?
Not Kirari!
[SERINUMA]
Nanashima has been respectful.
He's keeping his distance,
and I'm learning to
trust his friendship again.
For us, I think that's
the best decision.
Every situation is different.
[MALE FANS]
Sorry.
[MUTSUMI] Serinuma,
we're having our history club
presentation soon.
Would you like to draw
on our poster board for us?
[SERINUMA]
Sure! I'll do my best.
[MUTSUMI]
What a relief!
I'm not the best artist.
[SERINUMA]
That's surprising!
You always struck me as the kind
of person who could do anything!
[MUTSUMI laughs]
Oh, if only!
[SERINUMA]
Right?
I wonder what it'd be like
if we were good at everything.
[MUTSUMI] I'd imagine
our schedules would be
extremely full,
don't you think?
[SERINUMA]
You have a point there.
[MUTSUMI] I'm thankful
for the things I can't do!
[SERINUMA]
Aw, Mutsumi!
You have such a great outlook!
[MUTSUMI]
Let's celebrate our failures!