She's my girlfriend.
Please stay away from her.
And treat her with respect.
[SERINUMA]
O-Okay.
Was Mutsumi defending me?
Should I do something?
I don't understand!
[GROUP yells]
Is that supposed
to be some sick joke?
Explain yourself!
It's not true!
Oh... my.
How long have
you been here?
Since the "she's
my girlfriend" part!
Mutsumi? Why would you say that?
[GROUP] Why would you
say that, Mutsumi?
We're waiting!
[laughing]
That's a good one!
Really.
Surely you could have
come up with a better lie.
Not obvious?
He was protecting her from me.
He was?
What did you do?!
Nana!
Your anger might
get me hot and bothered.
Careful.
[KAZUMA chuckling]
I'm so naughty.
Occasionally it
gets out of hand!
Serinuma is so cute I
suppose I got a bit too bold.
Mutsumi was just...
keeping his brother in line?
We yelled at him.
The nicest guy we know
was sticking up for a friend.
Can you forgive us?
Aww. Without a doubt.
[KAZUMA]
Ah.
This family portrait is finally
starting to come together!
How cute.
You're all head-over-heels
for that girl.
Fun! Add my name to the list!
[GROUP]
Huh?
No vacancy!
Go away!
You're a teacher!
Give it up!
Can't do it.
Oh, and I'm technically
not a teacher yet.
I'm here to learn like you.
The details don't matter
when it comes to love.
They do!
What do you say? Date me.
How sweet. But my favorite
characters have my heart.
They do?
[laughing]
I think I can work with that!
[SHINOMIYA]
That guy is such a creep!
[NANASHIMA]
I hate the way he laughs.
[IGARASHI]
This can't go on.
[NANASHIMA]
We've gotta protect her.
[SHINOMIYA]
I agree.
[KAZUMA]
A moment of your time?
Sure! How are you?
[KAZUMA]
I've made a decision.
I have no problem
being second place.
Oh, I'm sorry.
First place is Shion and
second is a tie between
Captain Levi and Akane.
What? It can't be!
Who are they?
Very well, then
I'll be number three.
Third place is a
permanent hold by Miyuki!
Fictional characters
are my top sixteen.
Buggin' her already
and it's only 8 AM.
He's persistent.
Time to move out,
Captain Shinomiya!
Recapture Serinuma!
He will fall!
Destroy him.
Well, good morning!
Oh, good morning, how ya doin'?
Sorry to interrupt, but
Nakano was looking for you.
Didn't realize she was here!
What a nice talk! See ya!
Good job, kid!
Not yet.
He has to get away.
I'd advise you not to cross me.
You'd be in over your head.
Sorry.
When I see a young
woman being harassed,
I have no choice
but to intercede.
Oh? And what does that entail?
Believe me, it's not pretty.
Uh... so...
You know a lot about pretty.
I'll have to move on.
Actually, can you introduce me?
Why do you have that
picture on your phone?
Get rid of it!
Who doesn't know
about this princess?
Just between us girls, tell me,
how much did you enjoy
all that attention?
Don't be shy.
You're just my type.
[smooch]
[SHINOMIYA yelling]
[SHINOMIYA] He's the scariest
man I've ever seen in my life!
Do something, Nana!
Beat him up! I can't handle it!
Get a hold of yourself!
One man down. Who's next?
We decided to send our
weakest battalion in first.
He's not built for war.
I'll give it a try.
[KAZUMA]
Let's crank the heat up in here
by testing your knowledge.
If I call on you,
give it your best shot.
Students will be punished
if they answer wrong.
I give out kisses to slackers.
[GIRLS scream]
[NANASHIMA]
What kind of class is this?
[KAZUMA]
Tamura!
Who established the
Kamakura shogunate?
Minamoto, right?
[KAZUMA] Who was Minamoto
no Yoritomo's wife,
also known as the nun shogun?
Um, Masako.
[KAZUMA]
Narita.
Who was the retired emperor
that overthrew the shogunate
in the Jokyu War of 1221?
[NARITA]
That was Gotoba.
[KAZUMA]
You're next, Serinuma.
Um... okay!
[KAZUMA] Date Masamune
sealed a vow of love--
Tadano Sakujuro!
Very nicely done.
I feel like I need to
challenge you in particular
with something
a bit more difficult.
Now which lady-of-the-night
shared a provocative love story
with Hatakeyama Shigetada?
[STUDENTS]
Huh?!
No one could
answer that question!
[KAZUMA] Since Serinuma
is in the history club,
I thought I'd give
her a tricky one.
Let's see how she does.
No idea!
[NANASHIMA]
That's freaking sabotage!
[SERINUMA]
I have confidence in the Sengoku
guy-on-guy relationships,
but I'm lost with
everything else!
I can't even think
of any names to guess!
What do I say?
[IGARASHI]
Sir? Please.
Let me answer the question.
Why not? Sure.
Knock yourself out.
I don't know the answer.
[NANASHIMA gasps]
[STUDENTS whispering]
He won't even try.
Someone wants a smooch.
[STUDENTS laugh]
[KAZUMA] Sacrificing yourself
to protect the one you love.
Not bad, Igarashi.
[IGARASHI] I gave up my
dignity for her long ago.
Bring it on.
[NANASHIMA]
When I have kids,
they'll know what
a legend you are!
[KAZUMA]
Gotcha!
I was kidding! You get it?
I can't kiss students. Ethics!
The other teachers would
have my head on a platter.
[STUDENTS whispering]
[KAZUMA]
Besides...
I wouldn't want Nanashima
to feel neglected.
The hell? That's a lie!
Don't you worry.
I'm not gonna steal him!
[IGARASHI, NANASHIMA yell]
[STUDENTS whispering]
I knew those two were a thing!
Did you ever notice they
have matching keychains?
[GIRLS] Aw! Igarashi and
Nanashima are in love!
Oh, no!
I could do better!
The little Shions reveal it all!
[NANASHIMA] Those are the
keychains you gave us!
[NANASHIMA, IGARASHI]
The fangirl rumors have sealed
our fate.
Guess I can never
talk to Nana again.
Game over.
He destroyed us.
[NISHINA] You two are pathetic.
Stop sniveling!
That's it!
I'll go settle the matter!
Never send a man
to do a woman's job!
We salute! Good luck.
Yeah. Godspeed.
[NANASHIMA]
She's back!
How did it go?
Did you beat him
with lady power?
[IGARASHI, NANASHIMA]
Nishina!
Tell us! What did he do to you?
So weak...
[NISHINA] I'm sorry, but
there are already five of us
pursuing Serinuma.
There's no room for you.
[KAZUMA]
You're a writer, aren't you?
What do you think when
authors put themselves
into their fan fiction?
Is it a good story device to
have the main characters
fall in love with them?
"I have a crush on you!"
"Oh, Shion, I do on you too!"
"Does that mean you're ready
to take our relationship
to the next level?"
"So many people
are in love with me!"
"Date me or I'll
never forgive you."
"That hurts my feelings."
This happens in a high
school alternate universe.
You have my...
This is Yokoshima's
first self-published book.
Definitely a classic!
Please... stop!
My favorite part is the
original approach to anatomy!
The artist must've thought her
style trumped studying form
or using character references.
How gutsy was it that she ripped
off other people's designs
but didn't credit them at all?
[NISHINA yelling]
I fight... no more.
Don't leave us!
Nishina was supposed
to be our ace in the hole!
What did he do to her?
It's time.
We're out of options.
[NANASHIMA, IGARASHI] We're
gonna need Mutsumi's help!
My help?
[NANASHIMA] That's right! We
can't handle Kazuma on our own!
[MUTSUMI]
What can I do?
He's your brother... kill him!
[SHINOMIYA] You're the only
one who can slay the beast!
[IGARASHI]
We'll back you all the way!
[NISHINA]
Get moving!
There he is.
When you have some time,
I'd love to hear more about
your favorite characters!
Sure! I'll tell you now!
Let's start with...
[door opens]
Hey, you. What's up?
Um... Hello.
Can we talk a second?
Serinuma is a
close friend of mine.
I don't like how you've
been treating her.
[KAZUMA]
Is that so?
Please understand.
Her feelings are--
[KAZUMA chuckles] You must
think I'm toying with her.
Believe it or not, my interest
in her is quite real.
[KAZUMA gasps]
Over there!
What is it?
[MUTSUMI]
What are you doing?
Honestly!
I can't believe you
fell for that trick.
You've always been so naive.
Like taking candy from a baby.
[MUTSUMI]
Let me out, Kazuma!
Don't worry, I know your friends
must've put you up to that.
[MUTSUMI]
Why are you doing this? Please!
[KAZUMA]
You know better than anyone.
Sooner or later I
always get what I want.
Stay out of my way!
Later!
[MUTSUMI]
It's so dark.
I can't see anything,
and I'm too afraid to move.
Just like back then.
[KAZUMA]
That's awesome!
The shachihoko are all gold!
[MUTSUMI]
Yup!
The castles that
have gold shachihoko
are always the best.
You think so?
Yup!
[KAZUMA]
Dear Santa...
[MUTSUMI]
Please bring us Nagoya Castle.
Yay! Nagoya Castle!
I... don't have gold.
[MUTSUMI] Would you
like to trade with me?
What? Why?
[MUTSUMI] Because I thought
you wanted Nagoya castle.
Yeah, but you wanted it too!
I liked it, but I
want you to be happy.
Will you take it instead?
[KAZUMA growls]
Liar! You wanted Nagoya
Castle as much as I did!
[MUTSUMI]
No, I didn't!
[KAZUMA]
Stop it! Yes you did!
[MUTSUMI]
I don't want it!
[KAZUMA]
Yes you do!
[MUTSUMI]
No I don't!
[KAZUMA] I'm won't let you
out until you tell the truth!
[MUTSUMI]
Kazuma forgot about me.
I spent the entire
night trapped in there,
wondering what I'd done wrong.
I don't know.
[KAZUMA]
Oh, my dear, sweet brother.
If Serinuma is gonna
make me happy,
will you let me
have her as well?
[MUTSUMI] Why was he...
so angry back then?
I'm won't let you out
until you tell the truth!
[IGARASHI]
Dude, are you okay?
Yes. I am now.
[NANASHIMA]
He put you in a locker?
Now we have to
put a stop to this.
[SHINOMIYA]
Mutsumi.
My interest in her
is quite real.
[MUTSUMI] I had no idea he
had real feelings for Serinuma.
Who am I to tell him
that he shouldn't?
I'm lost.
How are we gonna stop this guy?
[MUTSUMI]
We're not.
[MUTSUMI] I'm sorry,
but I think I'm going home.
I don't understand.
[MUTSUMI] In the end,
this isn't about me.
If he's interested in her,
and she chooses him,
it would be wrong
of me to interfere.
Doing the right thing
should be easy.
Why does it hurt so much?
[SERINUMA]
Good morning!
Morning, Serinuma. Nana.
[NANASHIMA]
Yo.
We ran into each
other at the front door.
He walked me here!
What a treat!
All clear?
I was gonna keep him
from talking to her.
Been here all morning and I
haven't seen him walk in yet.
Good.
That guy'll be out of
our hair soon enough.
Just gotta keep them apart
until he's finished training.
Will do.
[PA system chimes]
[KAZUMA]
Good morning!
Your favorite student teacher
here, Kazuma Mutsumi!
I apologize for
the early disruption!
Something big is
about to happen,
and I'd love to invite
you all to the show!
Attention, Asuma Mutsumi!
If you're up for it...
I challenge you...
...to a duel of
Guard the Castle!
--[IGARASHI] Huh?
--[NANASHIMA] Guard... the what?
Guard the Castle!
[SERINUMA]
Allow me to explain!
So Guard the Castle is a
card game that was released
at the same time as
another popular card game.
People didn't
really get into it.
If you ask me,
it didn't get a fair shot.
It's perfect for fans
of the Sengoku Era.
Awesome! So much fun!
[RANDOM BOY 11A]
What is that?
[RANDOM BOY 11B]
Not a clue.
Do you remember the game?
It's simple enough.
We can meet in the gym to
play just like old times.
[STUDENTS gasping]
Students, feel free to
join us if you're inclined!
Please stop this!
Hi, Asuma! What a surprise!
[MUTSUMI] I heard
everything you were saying!
[KAZUMA]
That's good!
You know how it ends.
I get what I want.
Now you care?
You've rarely argued
with me, so I have to see
what will come next.
So this is your last chance.
Will you fight for
what you want?
You let it pass by...
I'm not asking next time.
Okay. Sound good?
Your call.
[RANDOM GIRL 11A] The Mutsumi
brothers are gonna go at it!
[RANDOM BOY 11C]
I'm there!
[RANDOM GIRL 11B]
Wouldn't miss it!
[RANDOM BOY 11D]
How theatrical!
[SERINUMA]
Mutsumi!
You're going to accept
his challenge, right?
I'm... not sure.
[SERINUMA laughing]
A brotherly duel!
When I played with Takuro
we'd always bet snacks.
Boy, was he was sore loser.
I was pretty good at it.
Whenever I won I'd eat
both of our snacks
right in front of his face!
What a nice memory
between you two!
Oh, there's no time
for nice when it comes to
Guard the Castle!
Defend yourself
and stomp the rest!
Well... I'm not
so sure about it.
Something wrong?
You look upset.
There is.
I've always given up
whatever I could.
I'm content with
whatever I have.
If everyone else is
comfortable, I'm happy.
I've never wanted anything
enough to fight over it.
I feel guilty.
Is there something
important at stake here?
[MUTSUMI]
Uh... Yes.
So share it... right?
We can't.
It's not appropriate
to share this.
Things have already
gone way too... far.
[SERINUMA sighs]
That's too bad.
So maybe you could
just give it to him?
I can't do that!
Oh. Sorry... too loud.
It's fine.
[MUTSUMI] When I think about
my brother taking this from me,
my heart aches.
I don't know if I could
let that happen.
[SERINUMA]
Okay.
Go for it.
I know it's hard.
But people sometimes
have to fight
even if it means
taking others down.
It's like when a popular
artist decides to put out
a limited-edition
volume at an event
and you and all
your friends want it!
You get up to take the first
train, line up, and wait.
What if there's only one copy
left when you finally get there?
Do you give it to your friend?
No can do!
Harden your resolve,
buy a copy with
a protective sleeve,
then just move on!
Shion says if you
show sympathy or pity,
you're being rude to your foe.
[MUTSUMI]
Always so warm.
I can't bear the
thought of letting go.
[MUTSUMI]
I'll do it.
Okay! I'll cheer you on!
And I'll win.
[NANASHIMA]
What's with all these people?
Huh. They don't have
anything better to do?
Guess they're bored.
[NISHINA]
Give me a hand!
Here, take these.
What are they?
[NISHINA]
We're cheering Mutsumi on!
Let's get pumped up!
We should also take a moment
to coordinate some cheers.
Wanna look professional
out there.
He has to win.
They're kinda neat.
You know? To support him.
I guess.
Exactly right.
Loud and proud. Show him.
You boys need to scream
his name in ecstasy
to let your friend know
just how much you love him.
[NANASHIMA] Wait, it's
gettin' a little weird now.
Brothers engaged in a
Guard the Castle duel?
Scandalous!
I can't wait
to see the show.
[RANDOM BOY 11E]
Here they come!
What's with that helmet?
[KAZUMA chuckling]
[SHINOMIYA]
Does that say "love"?
[SERINUMA]
Good luck, Mutsumi.
Kazuma.
You took that helmet
from the club room.
It's for the Sports
Festival Relay.
Well...
Don't you think
it suits this battle?
[MUTSUMI] This is the last
day that I allow you to do
whatever you please.
[RANDOM BOY 11F] None of us
get the rules, but game on!
[RANDOM GIRL 11C squeals]
I hope you win, Kazuma!
I'd give anything to dab
the sweat off his brow!
Ready!
Footmen special attack!
Not bad!
Trigger trap card!
With great mole snare!
[MUTSUMI]
My turn! Draw!
I end my go with
one card face down.
In defense!
[KAZUMA]
I activate my skill card!
Grade S enhancement!
Defense up 2000!
Oh. Wow.
Kazuma used a quick attack,
then came from behind.
His tactics are slowly
chipping away at Mutsumi.
They're both so
good at this game.
Kazuma fights aggressively.
No matter the cost,
Mutsumi is calm.
He's just using technique.
[SERINUMA]
Such a good battle!
[GROUP]
No idea what's happening!
Mutsumi is being cornered!
He needs our help!
Cheer! It's the only way
we can help him win!
The power of friendship
will keep him strong!
Oh! Sure thing!
[GROUP]
Asuma, you're our dude!
If you can't win,
then we're all screwed!
I know you can do it!
Kick his butt!
[MUTSUMI]
Reinforce rifle unit!
Encouragement squad!
Activate trap... Kunoichi!
Skill card...
Final Burst Strike!
This is amazing!
Mutsumi finally
has the upper hand!
Looks like you haven't changed
a bit, my sweet brother.
Always a fair
and frontal attack.
Your kindness is your weakness.
The general... has fallen.
Mutsumi!
[MUTSUMI]
I win.
Body double. Spy.
Wow. He won the match!
[cheering]
Don't know the rules
of the game or how he won,
but I'm glad he pulled it off!
You da man! Woo!
Congratulations, Mutsumi!
You had the nerve to use
a body double and a spy?
Really? You?
Funny... never suspected
you would play a hand
that's so close
to breaking the rules.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I couldn't let you
have your way this time.
Well done.
From now on,
if you want something...
Fight for it.
I'll do that.
[applause]
I'll put this back.
Sure. Thank you.
[SERINUMA]
Mutsumi! Congratulations!
[MUTSUMI chuckles]
Ha! I'm so happy!
Now you get to keep whatever
it was you were fighting for!
Hmm, so...
What was it that was
so important to keep?
Someone who's precious to me.
[MUTSUMI]
I like you.
I do.
[GROUP yelling]
[NAKANO]
Kae, why do you think we like it
when boys are together?
[SERINUMA]
There's a whole list of reasons!
It can be beautiful,
heart-wrenching, powerful.
Oh, I just love it!
[NAKANO] Do you think
you'll ever take a step
out of the shadows and
actually be with a guy yourself?
[SERINUMA]
You never know!
Every so often I'll think about
it and my heart beats faster!
What do you think it means?
[NAKANO] I think it means
that it might be time
to make your decision!
[SERINUMA]
Really? Um...
Are you sure it's not just
time for a new episode
of Katchu Ranbu ?
Maybe the manga
has a new chapter!
Uh... I think I'm ready.