Someone who's precious to me.
I like you. I do.
[GROUP gasps]
Can you repeat that?
Just once more.
I think I misunderstood.
Serinuma, I have... feelings...
[GROUP yells]
[SERINUMA]
Uh... What gives?
So spill it.
What were you trying to pull
in there with Serinuma?
Uh...
[NISHINA]
Well?
I was going to ask her if
she'd like to be my girlfriend.
[GROUP yells]
You told the boys you didn't
understand romantic feelings!
It can't change that quickly!
That doesn't make sense!
I just realized it.
What're you, nuts?!
Oh. I should be thanking you.
I never would have known.
I've fallen in love
with Serinuma.
[GROUP]
He's in love with her?
My heart is singing.
And I'm happy.
She has to know.
We won't let you! Forget it!
What? Why not?
Because it's selfish of you!
We feel the same way you do.
Get it? We all like her.
Oh, I see.
I suppose we all need
to confess our love.
[GROUP]
He makes it sound so easy.
Serinuma knows exactly
how I feel, man!
Does she?
Let's think about it. Um...
None of us have told
Serinuma how we feel.
What? Yeah, we have.
She must be mistaken, right?
Yeah.
[GROUP]
Uh... wait.
[MUTSUMI] You're all
free to do as you like.
But then...
Why waste more time?
[NANASHIMA] We pushed him
to take care of his brother
and now he's gonna
ruin our lives.
Yeah.
Looks like he's gonna
do the honorable thing
and be up front with her.
[GROUP]
We have to stop him.
Hi there!
I... have a request.
What's up?
I have an event at
the end of the month
and my comic is a
bit behind schedule.
Would you be interested
in coming over after class
to be my assistant?
Oh! Sounds fun!
I mean I've never done
anything like that before,
but it'll be neat to learn
about the process!
That's the spirit!
I appreciate it!
Sure! Oh.
I should tell Mutsumi
that I'll have to miss
a few club meetings.
[SHINOMIYA]
Leave it to me!
Don't worry your
pretty little head.
I'll let him know! Ha!
Cool! You don't mind?
Nope! I'm happy to!
Maybe I can pretend to be
one of those carrier pigeons
that we learned about in class!
[SERINUMA chuckles]
Well, okay.
Thanks a lot!
Carrier bird! Thank coo!
Don't start that!
Gah!
[NISHINA]
Let's get going!
Can't wait!
What? You're joining us?
There something
I can help you with?
I only need one assistant.
I'd have to be crazy
to leave you two alone.
Fine.
At least I'll get
work out of you.
Are you serious?
[NISHINA]
All right.
Looks good.
Please scan this for me.
More to come.
[IGARASHI]
Sure.
I'll be right back.
Going to the ladies' room.
Yep.
[NANASHIMA]
'Sup?
Nana... update.
Everything's in the clear
with Serinuma's older brother.
He's in.
Mutsumi won't be making
any kind of contact with her.
[IGARASHI]
Really?
How'd you get on his good side?
[NANASHIMA] I let him know
that Mutsumi was getting
a little too
forward with Serinuma.
You know how brothers are.
Oh, yeah? He's dead to me.
We got him. Mission complete.
[IGARASHI]
Cool.
'Kay, that's one thing.
And what about you?
All clear on this end.
I blocked his number.
No calls in or out!
[SERINUMA]
Okay! Let's get cracking!
[NISHINA]
We'll keep Mutsumi's mouth shut.
[IGARASHI] No matter how
dirty we have to play!
[VOICE 12A] The number
you are trying to reach
is currently unavailable.
Hey!
Did you know that
Ono no Imoko was a man?
Uh... Was there
ever any question?
Shinomiya?
What are you doing here?
Well... I'm interested...
in history!
Surprise!
Soga no Umako
was a man too!
[BOY STUDENT 11A]
Huh?
[VOICE 12A] The number
you are trying to reach
is currently unavailable.
[NANASHIMA]
So. How's it going?
[NISHINA] Serinuma has been
coming over to my place
after school.
For now, I don't think
she suspects anything.
[NANASHIMA]
One problem.
Takuro said Mutsumi found
a way to get to Serinuma.
[NANASHIMA] He sent her
something in the mail.
He won't take you!
[IGARASHI, NISHINA]
What was it?
[NANASHIMA] A stuffed animal
that says, "I like you"!
[NANASHIMA]
The horror!
It's okay,
we'll just try harder.
Yeah, it'll be a cinch!
[IGARASHI]
He has to give up eventually.
[SHINOMIYA]
Yeah, keep walking.
I'll do whatever it takes to
keep you away from Serinuma!
[SHINOMIYA]
The bathroom, huh?
How long does it take?
[SHINOMIYA]
No, no!
He climbed through the window?
Is he crazy?
This is the second floor!
[phone ringing]
[IGARASHI]
What's up, Shino?
[SHINOMIYA whimpers] I'm sorry,
he got away from me!
He's probably on his
way to her right now!
We have to find him.
[PA system chimes]
[MUTSUMI]
Kae Serinuma!
Hi there! This is Asuma Mutsumi.
I really need to talk to you.
If it's not too much trouble,
please meet me
on the roof today after school.
I wonder what he needs.
That's cheating!
Just like his brother.
Unbelievable.
Stop him! Get moving!
[IGARASHI growls]
Thank you for your time.
Mutsumi!
You've got a lot of nerve!
Yeah, ya jerk!
[MUTSUMI]
Why are you trying to stop me?
Listen.
If you have the freedom
to tell someone
how you feel about them,
why wouldn't you?
Now's the time.
If you're ready,
then meet me on the roof.
See you after school.
[TEACHER 12A] Pay attention.
My job is on the line.
[IGARASHI]
Mutsumi makes a lot of sense.
This is Serinuma's decision.
We can't keep tripping
over each other.
Maybe we've all
been avoiding this.
If she's not interested,
will we still be able
to hang out together?
Am I okay with
just being a friend?
[SERINUMA]
Uhh...!
[SHINOMIYA]
If I tell her everything,
what good will it do if she
doesn't feel the same way?
There's no going back.
[BOTH laughing]
[NANASHIMA]
I know I'd be good to her.
She's inspired me
to be a better person.
[SERINUMA laughing]
[NISHINA] I want to be
the one she chooses.
[SERINUMA]
Mutsumi?
Serinuma. It's nice to see you.
Uh, is everything okay?
You all look a little worried.
Um... what's up?
Well... I asked you here
so I could tell you that
I have feelings for you.
But then... I found out
that I'm not alone.
It's true. I really like you.
I like you.
I... I like you.
I like you as well.
So do I... I really like you.
[GROUP]
Will you be my girlfriend?
Aw... Stop!
You're making me blush!
Well, no of course
I don't mean that,
--keep it coming!
--[doorbell rings]
Someone's at the door.
[NAKANO] No, you don't
have to hang up.
One second, okay?
I'm sure this won't take...
Help me, A!
[BOTH yell]
Huh? They all asked you out?
[SERINUMA]
Yeah.
[NAKANO groans]
And they really put
themselves out there.
They were honest.
That's so awesome!
So spill it, girl!
What happened?
Well, um...
It's hard to explain.
We're not saying
this to put any kind
of pressure on you.
All of us have feelings for you
and it's been that
way for a while now.
Didn't mean to
put you on the spot.
Sorry.
[SERINUMA]
It's okay.
We think it's far that you
know exactly how we feel.
We'd never want
to rush you, but...
...you needed to know.
Come on! If they don't need
an answer right away,
why not savor the
process a little?
[SERINUMA]
I can't.
They deserve better.
I have to learn to
handle these situations.
And they're my friends.
I need to be truthful.
And... think this out.
I owe them that much.
You're right, Kae.
[NAKANO]
She's come so far.
I'm really proud of her.
So... Which one?
--What?
--Girl talk.
I'll name them,
and you tell me
what comes to mind.
Yeah? Ready?
Not sure.
[NAKANO]
Igarashi.
[SERINUMA]
5 x 7!
[NAKANO]
Nanashima?
[SERINUMA]
5 x 7!
[NAKANO]
Mutsumi?
[SERINUMA] His soothing
presence would help timid guys
come out of their shell.
[NAKANO]
What about Shinomiya?
[SERINUMA] He's a bit of a
klutz and very stubborn,
but the right man
could totally handle it.
[NAKANO]
And Nishina?
[SERINUMA]
The great author Yokoshima!
She's brilliant,
but so wrong about
Lord and Akane.
Will you give it a rest
with the fangirl talk?
It's okay to let yourself have
feelings for another person!
I just can't help myself!
It's tough!
I've always been more
comfortable on the sidelines!
I'm still learning!
I guess they brought
it on themselves
for hanging on this long.
You need time to
figure your feelings out.
How should I handle it?
Get to know them individually?
That might be a good start.
Yeah.
Wouldn't it be great
if you could follow
their character routes
like an otome ?
Too bad.
[SERINUMA]
I love it!
[NAKANO yelps]
If you're okay with it,
I'd like to go on separate
dates with each of you.
I'll get equal time
with everyone
and then make my decision.
A date?
That's right. Sorry.
I realized we never get alone
time, so why don't we?
It'd be nice.
Thank you for your patience.
Bye!
[IGARASHI]
Wait a sec!
It's finally happening.
She'll go on dates
with all of us.
I suppose that's the
best way to handle it.
We all get a chance with her
and then she's gonna choose?
Everything we've
been working towards
has come down to this.
[laughs]
So cool! Check it out.
[gasps]
Look how big that shark is!
That's the strangest
fish I've ever seen!
[IGARASHI] That's the
Asian sheepshead wrasse.
Oddly enough, they're
females when they're born,
but change sex once they mature.
Really? That's neat!
Wait, how did you know that?
I just know fish.
Okay. Research.
I wanted to impress you.
[SERINUMA]
Oh, yeah?
That's right. I'm smart.
[SERINUMA]
I wonder if I can stump you.
Why don't we give it
a try by the jellyfish?
[gasps]
Careful.
Yeah. Thank you.
[SERINUMA] Igarashi is
a lot of fun to talk to.
He's always
considerate and kind.
We get along really
well, actually!
And doesn't seem to mind
when I'm a goofball.
[IGARASHI] Why don't we
ride the ferris wheel?
It's all so beautiful
from up here!
Not as beautiful... as you are.
[SERINUMA] Every so often
he'll say something
really embarrassing.
[SERINUMA]
This is so awkward.
I gotta say something! Anything!
Nanashima?
[CLERK 12A]
Thanks for your purchase.
Have a good day!
[NANASHIMA]
Here.
When you come to
a place like this,
you gotta be down to have
a good time, ya know?
Let's do this!
Yeah, I'm with you!
We gotta hit
the coaster first!
[SERINUMA laughs]
[SERINUMA] Nanashima seemed
quiet in the beginning,
but once he loosened up,
he was his usual self.
He definitely knows how
to have a good time.
We had a blast together!
You're not Mommy.
[crying]
[SERINUMA]
What's the matter?
Where's your mommy and daddy?
I know! Wanna try
some of my popcorn?
Ah! She won't stop crying!
[ERI crying]
[NANASHIMA]
Bleh!
[laughing]
[SERINUMA]
What kind of face is that?
You're making my stomach hurt!
Eri!
[ERI laughing]
Honey! I was worried sick!
[ERI]
I'm sorry.
What a relief.
She got away from me.
Thanks a lot. Let's go!
[ERI]
Bye!
[NANASHIMA]
You gotta keep up with your Mom.
[SERINUMA]
I'm feeling a little different.
That was really sweet of you.
[NANASHIMA]
Huh?
She was so upset I froze up.
You handled it no problem!
Ah. Thank my sis for that.
She'd cry that way?
She's loved my
arsenal of funny faces
since she was a baby.
It's the one thing
that always worked.
[SERINUMA] Nanashima is
nothing like I expected.
[SERINUMA]
Aw, look at all that fluff!
Bet they're soft!
Hey! Want food?
Oops.
[SHINOMIYA laughs]
No big deal.
[SERINUMA screams]
Your hair! Oh, my gosh!
Shinomiya,
it's eating your hair!
Stop it! Let me go!
[SERINUMA] You have to keep
a close eye on Shinomiya.
Am I going to
have to buy a wig?
[SERINUMA]
No, it's all there! Promise!
I get shy when you laugh.
Sorry.
[SERINUMA]
If I had a little brother,
I bet it would
feel just like this.
[ALPACA 12D growls]
We're all gonna die!
Run, run! It's a wild alpaca!
--[SERINUMA screams]
--[SHINOMIYA] Look out!
[SERINUMA]
You're not hurt, are you?
It was the softest
thing I've ever felt!
Oh... great!
I'm sorry. This is one
jealous son of a gun.
He charges any couple
he sees out here.
[SHINOMIYA]
No big deal.
We should find him a date!
[laughing]
[SERINUMA]
I can always rely on him.
I'm so thankful
we've gotten close.
[SERINUMA]
Whoa!
[NISHINA]
This is my family's restaurant.
I reserved the entire place, so
please relax and help yourself.
Oh! I'll try!
[SERINUMA]
Shima is like a celebrity.
It can be overwhelming.
Sometimes it feels like we
live in two separate worlds.
When I have the time to take in
such beautiful scenery,
it makes me wonder what
Akane and Lord's honeymoon
would be like!
[SERINUMA screams]
I'd give anything to see that!
[NISHINA]
It would be so tantalizing!
They would stay in a nice venue
and never make it
out of the bedroom!
[laughing]
[SERINUMA] If Akane even
thought about leaving,
Lord would put a stop to it!
Oh, baby!
So hot. There'd be no
keeping them apart.
Akane would be
all about fulfilling
his lord's wishes!
[NISHINA] Considering how long
those two must've waited,
don't you think that it'd
be so sensual and romantic?
[SERINUMA]
Uh-huh. It's too nice.
My heart. Oh, man.
[SERINUMA] It's clear that
we're still soulmates!
We have so much in common!
[MUTSUMI] This is where
the Edo Five Routes started.
[SERINUMA]
Wow! And it was so long ago!
Don't we turn right here?
It hasn't changed a
bit since the Edo era.
Ha! It's still fascinating
that there's a forested area
like this within the city.
[MUTSUMI] Since we're here,
would you like to visit
the shrine?
[SERINUMA] Mutsumi always
talks in the most gentle,
soothing voice.
He makes me relaxed.
Have I told him how
much I appreciate that?
I like you.
[SERINUMA]
I know he meant every word.
[MUTSUMI] So what...
What did you wish for?
That Lord and Akane stay in love
and that their show
will go on forever!
I also wished that Shion
would come back to life
like nothing ever happened,
that Captain Levi
would show his softer side,
and that my top sixteen
would have another good year.
There's so much to ask for!
Same question!
I wished that...
That our time together
would never end.
[MUTSUMI] Serinuma,
I think I've always liked you.
I've just never put the
feeling into words before.
[SERINUMA]
Wha--?!
[MUTSUMI] It's funny
how friendship can teeter
on the edge like that.
I'll never forget.
You were the first girl
to take my breath away.
Thank you.
[phone chimes]
[SERINUMA]
What should I do?
I think the dates actually
made things harder.
They're all good people
with their own
charming personalities.
I feel like we've all
become best friends.
I know I've come
a long way, and...
...maybe there's
nothing wrong with going
at my own pace.
There's something missing.
I don't understand!
What's wrong with me?
[groans]
[SERINUMA] I feel like...
this should be way easier.
I've figured it out.
No matter who she chooses...
...we accept it.
[GROUP]
Agreed.
Finally.
I have an answer.
I've chosen...
[GROUP]
Who is it?
Right here.
[SERINUMA]
Shion from Mirage Saga !
[GROUP]
Huh?
They totally just announced
a whole 'nother season
of Mirage Saga !
Ah! And!
The ad had a mysterious
lurking shadow!
Without question it
had to be Shion, right?
There's no one else!
It just had to be him!
I didn't sleep a wink
last night because
I was looking through every
animators' blog for clues.
It looks like the production
is already in full swing!
I gotta be honest with you.
I don't think I'll have the time
to focus on anything else!
How could I possibly start a
relationship with anyone
right now when my
attention is being tugged
in so many directions?
There'll be so much
to learn and little hints
are already being scattered
across the internet!
Oh, and all the new faces!
A naughty little
pairing might be born!
You see what I'm saying?
No, it's gotta be Terra
and Shion hands down.
They're meant to be!
I've been patiently
waiting for so long!
My boy love dreams
are finally coming true!
Can't you just feel the magic?
I'm shivering in delight!
I can't stop thinking about it.
Oh! Anime Ito is having a sale!
Well, guess I
better head off! Bye!
[laughing]
[GROUP]
Wait!
[IGARASHI] Uh... Anybody
get what just happened?
[NANASHIMA]
You call that an answer?
Don't leave us hanging!
[SHINOMIYA]
Serinuma, come back!
[NISHINA] Is Mirage Saga
really getting another season?
[MUTSUMI] She looked
so happy as she ran away!
Isn't that wonderful?
[GROUP]
No, it's not!
[SERINUMA] The prince should
always be with the princess.
Who's the one in charge
of making rules like that?
I mean, come on,
look at these two!
I can't deny the
longing in my soul!
The princess lived
a life full of joy.
In fact, everyone else did too!
It was a heartwarming
happily ever after.
And she loved every second!
[laughing]