Igarashi, you're crazy.
You're really gonna
use that dorky keychain
Serinuma gave us?
Ah. Well, yeah.
It was a present.
Why is that crazy?
Dude, are you serious?
[SERINUMA] These are the
new mini action figures!
This is the
first one I've held!
Mini Shion is adorable!
As a thank you
for this evening,
I'd like all of you to have one.
Tonight was so special to me.
[laughs]
She gave us matching
anime character keychains!
I'm not gonna be
caught dead with that!
[laughs]
[NANASHIMA] You don't see
me laughing about it.
Guess she wants the four
of us walking around
showcasing those things
like we're her little fanclub?
What a turn-off.
I dunno.
It's kinda interesting.
No, it's dumb.
Maybe you should
go ahead and give up.
If you back out, that's one less
guy I have to compete with.
Yeah. You'd love for me
to do that, wouldn't ya?
[NAKANO]
Comin' in!
Leave it to me!
[grunts]
[GIRLS cheering]
[GIRLS]
That was awesome!
Go Serinuma!
I always knew you
were pretty athletic,
but I had no idea
you were this good!
Those moves were impressive!
My body feels so light!
I could play any sport I want!
Wow... let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
[NANASHIMA]
Now that I think about it,
she was always good at
those jumping exercises.
They were intense.
[clapping]
I've never seen anyone
pull off a receive like that!
I've never seen
anyone suck up so much.
The soccer club needs help?
That's too bad!
What happened?
Well...
Normally we have eleven members,
which is just enough
to play a game.
We have a practice
match next weekend,
but we're down one player.
I got injured.
[GIRL STUDENT 02D] Since you
seem so good at sports,
we were wondering if you could
take her spot for the game.
We'd be so grateful!
[GIRL STUDENT 02E]
Please!
You assumed she
could play soccer?
I've never seen Serinuma
kick a ball in her life.
Okay!
Huh?!
You really will?
Thanks a lot!
You're a lifesaver!
Uh, wait a second.
Maybe think about it a
little before you say yes.
It'll be fine!
Believe it or not, I actually
know a lot about soccer!
Huh?!
I'm a fan of...
Captain Tsubasa ,
Inazuma Eleven ,
and Giant Killing !
[NAKANO gasps]
A soccer game!
Are you prepared to compete?
Sure am!
I've spent years studying
by watching sports anime!
[IGARASHI]
Wow.
[SHINOMIYA]
Better than nothing.
[NANASHIMA]
Is this chick for real?
But still... It'll be
my first time playing,
so I definitely want to
squeeze in a practice or two.
Feel free to skip the
history club meetings
this week while you're training.
I'll cheer you on.
I'm supporting you too!
I'll even watch the game!
Would you allow me to coach you?
We could run a few
drills after school
and work on your technique.
Yes! That's perfect!
You guys are making me
so excited to do this!
I appreciate your support!
[NANASHIMA]
This is just sad.
[IGARASHI]
Just one problem.
I have my own practice so
I'll have to duck out early.
But I bet Nanashima
could take it from there.
He used to play soccer way back.
Yeah, there's no way
I'm doin' that.
It takes years to
develop that kinda stuff.
Doesn't happen overnight.
You let her on the field now,
and she's gonna slow
the whole team down.
Mark my words.
I'm gonna spend the
whole week practicing
so I'll be ready for anything.
Just take it from Tsubasa!
"The ball is my friend"... Yep!
Fangirling over
an anime about soccer
doesn't mean you
can play the game!
You'll look like an idiot!
An underdog can rise
to the top if they put
their heart into the work!
You planning on having
a little training montage
or somethin'?
You need to wake up and stop
living in a fantasy world!
Why are you being
so heartless, Nanashima?
Let's all calm down. It's okay.
Yeah, take it easy!
No reason to get this upset.
[NANASHIMA, SERINUMA growl]
I'm not gonna have any
part in this in this joke.
Do what you want.
[SERINUMA]
What's his problem?
I don't care what he says!
I'm going to put my all into
this and prove him wrong!
I can do it!
[SERINUMA]
Nice to meet you!
[SOCCER TEAM]
Thanks for coming!
All right, let's kick things off
with some warm-ups! Cool?
[SERINUMA]
Okay!
We'll start with some stretches,
then its twenty laps
around the school.
I'm so dead.
[SOCCER TEAM]
Fight! On! Fight! On!
[SOCCER PLAYER 02A]
Okay!
Sit-ups and reserve sit-ups!
Five sets of twenty!
Put your hands
behind your head
and keep your legs together.
[SOCCER PLAYER 02A] Next is
two sets of 10 push-ups!
[SOCCER PLAYER 02A]
Deep stretches now!
I'm dying!
[SOCCER PLAYER 02A]
Time to start practice!
That's all for today, ladies!
[SOCCER TEAM cheering]
Your first practice.
Well, how are you feeling?
I'm... great, why do you ask?
[IGARASHI] You
look like a newborn giraffe
learning how to walk.
[SERINUMA]
I feel... fantastic!
I'm a filthy liar!
This is ridiculous!
I've never been
an outdoor person!
I don't do sports!
I don't do sweating!
I don't even think
I have muscles!
My body will never
forgive me for this abuse!
Maybe you should take it easy
for the rest of the night.
I got this! Bring it on!
That's not too tight, is it?
Wrapping your foot limits
the range of motion
so you'll be less
likely to get a sprain.
Thanks! That's much better!
So glad we're on
the health committee!
You're the best, Shinomiya!
Well, um...
It's not a big deal.
I brought refreshments.
I never even thought of that!
Hey, so... How do you
think she's doing?
Who? Serinuma?
Yeah, her.
[GIRL STUDENT 02E]
Ugh. She's terrible.
[GIRL STUDENT 02D] Maybe we
should look for someone else.
She hasn't improved at all!
Yeah.
Do you think we'll be able to
find someone last minute though?
I guess anyone would
be better than she is.
[BOTH gasp]
You asked for her help.
Drop the attitude
and be grateful.
[NANASHIMA] Crap.
Why did I take up for her?
It doesn't have anything
to do with me.
[SERINUMA grunts]
[SERINUMA]
Gah!
My face!
[whining]
What was that supposed to be?!
Why are you out
here goofing around?
here watching me?!
I swear I'm trying my best.
Every time I kick the ball,
it flies back and
smacks me in the head!
Every time?
That's actually impressive.
I guess the ball doesn't
want to be away from me.
We're close.
[NANASHIMA]
No, you just suck.
Yeah. I guess.
I'll keep practicing.
[NANASHIMA] Now I know
why they called her terrible.
Listen.
Maybe... You should just quit.
You don't have to go
through with this thing.
Even if you spent all
your time practicing,
you wouldn't be able to keep
up with the rest of them.
[SERINUMA]
No.
[SERINUMA] You were right
about everything.
I wasn't prepared
for this at all.
It's a lot of work.
The other girls on the team have
been playing soccer for years.
I can't catch up to them.
It's my responsibility
to finish this.
I can't let the team down!
[NANASHIMA]
Look at her.
What choice do I have?
Give it another try.
You're probably doing somethin'
weird with your foot
when you go for the kick.
I won't know for sure unless
I watch your follow-through.
You said you don't
wanna quit, right?
Then I'll do what
I can to help you.
Let's figure this out.
[IGARASHI]
What's Nana doing here?
I wonder...
They had that huge fight,
but it didn't take him long to
come crawling back to her.
Let's be kind.
It's a beautiful thing
when people reconnect.
Good for them.
[whistle blows]
[FEMALE REF 02A]
Time out!
They're in stoppage time now,
and still down one point.
There's less than two
minutes left in the game.
What will they do?
This'll be hard to pull off.
I think I have an idea.
When we get the chance... will
you pass it to me at throw-in?
What are you gonna do?
It's too late to save
the game, Serinuma!
[SERINUMA]
We can't slow down now!
Let's give them all we've got
until the inning is over!
[GIRL STUDENT 02D]
Soccer doesn't have innings.
[SOCCER PLAYER 02A] But she's
right about everything else!
I can't believe they're
this close to winning.
If they can clear
the ball, it'll be over.
[MUTSUMI]
Serinuma got it.
This is her chance
to win it all.
All she needs is one good kick.
[IGARASHI]
That's the wrong direction!
[GROUP gasps]
She wasn't aiming at all!
[whistle blows]
[SOCCER TEAM cheers]
What just happened?
She shot it
backwards into the net!
There's no way!
Wow, I've never seen
anything like that before!
Seriously?
Who taught her
to kick like that?
[laughing]
She's gotta be
stupid or something!
That was the dumbest
thing I've ever seen!
[NANASHIMA]
Unbelievable!
This girl is hilarious!
I gotta see more!
[IGARASHI] I guess this means
you're not giving up yet.
Yeah. Sorry to disappoint.
[NAKANO] Kae, you still
smell like muscle cream.
Sorry.
Hey! It's almost time
for summer vacation!
That'll keep my mind
off the pain!
[NAKANO]
It'll be so fun!
Comiket, performances,
live concerts, talk shows!
All the awesome stuff will
make saving up so worth it!
All right!
Let's have some fun!
How exciting.
Serinuma, if you
fail the next test,
you'll have to take summer
classes to make up for it...
Just so you know.
I wouldn't plan
on having a vacation.
Serinuma bombed the
tests she had to take
after missing a week of school.
So she's trying to
make up for lost time.
And... this is
what it's done to her?
[NAKANO] She's trying to
memorize English literature
and translating Japanese
classics at the same time.
It's really sad.
[SHINOMIYA] Little by little,
she's going insane.
I... might miss
the Mirage Saga events.
And... I won't be able to
give Shion a final farewell.
I'll do anything to keep
from taking summer classes.
But I've gotten so far behind
I don't know where to start!
Shion, I'm so
sorry I've failed!
Oh. Thank you, Mutsumi.
Don't be sad.
I know you're not having
problems in history.
Which subjects are
you worried about?
Well, I guess... math
gives me some trouble.
Yes?
[SERINUMA]
And science, too.
[MUTSUMI]
Okay.
That's a start.
You'll catch up.
I'd be more than happy
to help you study.
Yes, please!
I would be so grateful!
We can start right after school!
Would you please help us
study too, Mutsumi?
Of course.
I didn't realize
you all needed it.
We do!
[GROUP] As if we'd leave
you alone with her!
[NANASHIMA]
This is my chance.
[MUTSUMI]
Then... we have this.
Do you understand?
[SERINUMA]
Yes! I do.
For the first time,
it actually makes sense.
Yeah? That's good to hear.
[SERINUMA]
I can always count on Mutsumi.
He makes it so easy
to understand.
Maybe I can pull this off!
[NANASHIMA]
Hey, kid.
Aren't you a freshman
or something?
Have you even been able to
keep up with what we're doing?
Don't worry about me.
In prep school we've been
doing problems like this
for a while now.
By the way, you put
the wrong answer
on question number two.
Would you like me to explain it?
Oh, yeah, he's right.
Looks like you messed up
on the formula.
[NANASHIMA gasps]
I did that on purpose!
Right. Your stupidity
is a choice, huh?
You expect anyone to
believe that you wanted
to put the wrong answer down?
[IGARASHI] Nana, being caught in
a lie is no reason to get upset.
[NANASHIMA] All right, smart
guy, you and me! Let's go!
[STUDENTS]
Get out of here!
We'd like to remind
all of our customers that
though we do appreciate
your business,
this is a family establishment
that does not condone
disruptive activity,
loud outbursts,
or coarse language of any kind.
[SERINUMA] We couldn't
stay in the library,
and the restaurant is
a definite no-go.
[NANASHIMA] Not many places
around here to study.
[SHINOMIYA]
There sure aren't.
[SERINUMA, IGARASHI]
No thanks to you two.
I know where we can go!
How about Serinuma's?
What do you say?
All right with you?
Huh?
[SERINUMA]
What do I do?!
It's not like I mind everyone
using my bedroom as a workspace.
They were awesome enough
to help me, after all.
[SERINUMA]
Just one little problem.
They don't need
to see all of this.
Jeez, it's bad.
I can't let them in on my shame.
They already know about you,
so that's no big deal.
It's those I'm not sure about.
I can't have this kind
of stuff lying around
when real boys come over.
[SERINUMA]
Okay!
Into the closet you go!
Forgive me, treasures!
I'll let you breathe again soon!
Until then, you're safe
and sound in here!
[doorbell rings]
Hey, we're here!
Sorry I don't have much space.
[IGARASHI]
This is perfect.
Ah, thank you.
I managed to pick up a little
before you got here,
but didn't have time
to do too much.
[chuckles]
[MITSUKO]
Kae!
I brought your guests some tea.
What handsome
young men you are!
[SERINUMA screams]
--[SERINUMA] No, no, no, no!
--[GROUP] What was that?
We don't need
any room service,
and why do you look
like a clown?
Sweetie.
So much to learn.
Now... when you invite
men into your home,
the least you could do
is whet their appetite
while looking your best.
They can whet their
own appetites after we
finish studying!
[SHINOMIYA]
So this is Serinuma's bedroom.
Man, this is lame!
Why don't you guys beat it and
give us a little privacy here?
[SERINUMA]
Um...
I think this part is
a little complicated.
Which part?
Question three.
Please... tutor.
Right now.
I could be teaching
her anatomy right now!
Do you have to be so lewd?
From the looks of your answers,
I wouldn't trust you
to teach her the alphabet.
Shut it, baby-face!
It's true.
Sitting in a girl's room
with three other guys
isn't the ideal scenario.
[NANASHIMA]
Yeah.
So why don't you hit the road?
No.
None of us are going
to get any one-on-one time
with her tonight.
Well, maybe we can still
get a peek at the goods.
Do ya dare me?
[SHINOMIYA]
Obscene!
[NANASHIMA] Right.
Like you don't wanna see this!
[yells]
[IGARASHI]
Those are her bedsheets?
[NANASHIMA]
She sleeps on him?
[SHINOMIYA] That's what you
get for being so nosey.
You knocked my pencil
under the bed!
[NANASHIMA]
Well, your majesty...
Allow me.
[NANASHIMA screams]
I talked the store
clerk into giving me
the display.
It's usually up for decoration.
I put it under the bed so you
wouldn't be weirded out.
[IGARASHI]
You had this sitting out?
Yeah.
It was right next to this.
[GROUP]
A shrine?
[NANASHIMA]
I don't get it.
[SHINOMIYA]
Me either.
I think this is
the same character
on the keychain she gave us.
[IGARASHI]
He looks just like you, Nana!
[NANASHIMA]
No, he doesn't!
I'm not dead!
[SERINUMA crying]
Did he pass away?
I'm so sorry.
He did.
May I pay my respects to him?
Yes, you may.
Please... come join us.
[GROUP]
This is insane.
[MITSUKO giggling]
[MITSUKO]
Kae knows what she's doing.
She's the spitting image
of me when I was young!
[TAKURO]
I'm home.
[MITSUKO]
Oh, hi, sweetheart!
You won't believe it, but Kae
has some special guests over!
[TAKURO]
Huh?
Four of the sweetest boys
I've ever laid my eyes on!
Oh... so cute.
[MUTSUMI]
Well, then, shall we begin?
[SERINUMA]
Yep!
Okay! Let's do this!
Don't be fooled!
Ah! What do you want?
[TAKURO]
Listen up, punks!
I've got somethin' to say!
Okay.
Here's a couple words
of warning for you dudes,
coming from one man to another.
You were probably
lured here by her looks,
but she suckered you in!
Serinuma is a psycho chick
totally obsessed with anime!
Uh... yeah, we know.
It's okay with us.
We gave our
condolences to Shion
right before you
came in the bedroom.
--[MUTSUMI] Uh-huh.
--[TAKURO yells]
[SERINUMA]
Get off!
You sound like a big jerk!
I like what I like, so what?
Not everyone is as
narrow-minded as you are!
[SERINUMA]
Narrow-minded!
You say that.
[SERINUMA gasps]
[TAKURO]
But what about this?
[SERINUMA screams]
[TAKURO]
Check it out!
She's a disgusting perv!
[SERINUMA]
Will you stop?
I'm allowed to be interested
in anything I want!
[GROUP]
Oh. It's boy love.
I hate you!
You gonna cry?
Pardon me.
If you don't mind, we're trying
to get some studying done.
[MUTSUMI]
Now, if you'll please...
--[TAKURO] Wait a sec!
--...excuse us!
I'm... sorry about
the way he acted.
Okay, everyone.
Why don't we help her
tidy up all these books?
[GROUP]
Yep. Sure thing.
There's no need
for you to do that!
I can handle all of this myself!
[MUTSUMI]
Wait.
Don't be so rough with them.
Aren't they important to you?
[SERINUMA]
Yes, they are.
[GROUP]
Thanks for having us!
[SERINUMA]
Oh. Mutsumi.
I don't know how to thank you
for all you've done for me.
[MUTSUMI]
There's no need.
Will you apologize
to your brother?
I acted so rudely to him.
I don't think
you were rude at all.
He had it coming!
[MUTSUMI]
Oh, I got this for you.
It's for the test.
[MUTSUMI] If you're ever torn
between different options,
this will help.
You can tilt luck in your favor.
[chuckles]
What a wonderful present!
[MUTSUMI]
Oh... you three.
Here's one for each of you.
Good luck on all of your tests.
Wow. Thanks a lot.
[IGARASHI] That was the
most fun I've ever had
in a girl's bedroom,
and all we did was study!
Unbelievable.
[NANASHIMA]
Tonight was awesome.
This is his way of apologizing?
Forgiven.
I passed!
No summer classes for me!
This girl is ready for vacation!
[GROUP]
Congratulations!
We should go hang
out at the pool!
That sounds like a good idea!
Just the two of us!
There are historical
sites we could visit.
[SERINUMA]
Uh...
And so I chose...
[SERINUMA, NAKANO screaming]
You're the greatest
boy band ever!
[SERINUMA] To attend every
single one of the otaku events
with A!
[SHINOMIYA]
When I was a kid,
I stayed down in
the dumps a lot.
[MUTSUMI]
Why?
[SHINOMIYA] People teased me
for being too delicate!
It was frustrating.
[NANASHIMA] Yeah, well I've
always pretty popular
because of soccer.
Igarashi has me beat though.
[IGARASHI] That's because I'm
still playing in high school!
Why did you ever quit?
[NANASHIMA]
It's exhausting!
How am supposed to do that plus
everything else I wanna do?
[MUTSUMI]
That reminds me--
The cultural festival
is coming up.
There are so many
fun things there!
[SHINOMIYA] Unless you're
stuck having to wear a dress.
[NANASHIMA] Aww, but you're
such a pretty princess!
[SHINOMIYA]
Do you ever stop talking?
[IGARASHI]
Dress or no dress,
I'm pumped to see what's
going on at the festival!