[SERINUMA] A new Mirage Saga
chapter just got posted!
So nice...
Terra and Shion.
Heaven. You two are perfect!
[SERINUMA yelling]
[SERINUMA]
Don't think about it!
You've gotta stop
obsessing over this!
[NISHINA] We'll have a problem
if you don't take me seriously.
It was a joke!
I'm sorry!
You looked so precious,
I couldn't resist
having a little
bit of fun with you!
Oh, right!
You really had me going there.
[SERINUMA]
She's such a troublemaker!
[NISHINA]
Do forgive me!
[SERINUMA] It's not like the
kiss meant anything!
Physical contact
is perfectly normal.
Snap out of it!
What's this?!
[GROUP]
A Valentine's contest?
[SERINUMA]
I saw it on their website!
Create a treat inspired
by a Mirage Saga Character.
I have to win. I need it!
There's even a grand prize!
A drawing by the lead designer!
I'd have to be insane
to let this rare opportunity
slip out of my fingers!
No! I can't let that happen!
Let's see. What to make...
[NISHINA]
Serinuma!
Hello there.
Oh. Hi!
Please move.
I'd like to have an intimate
discussion with Serinuma.
No surprise.
A little bit of advice for ya...
She's not interested.
Get lost. Now.
Hello!
You're entering the
Valentine contest, right?
Of course! What about you?
[NISHINA]
Yes!
It's exciting! Any ideas yet?
[NISHINA] I have few things
in mind, but I'm still deciding.
If you have any free time,
how about we try
each other's recipes?
Uh...!
Hey! You've spent
enough time with her!
You two are more
than welcome to join us.
Help yourselves.
Perhaps we should invite
Mutsumi and Shinomiya as well.
Let's do that.
And besides... I wager
that it'll be a lot of fun
to see you boys aching
to sample desserts
you'll never get to eat.
[NANASHIMA, IGARASHI]
She's such a jerk!
I'll be there!
I can make my own
desserts anyway!
Be my guest!
[SERINUMA] Are you ready to
make our chocolate character?
[NISHINA]
Absolutely!
Today we can try
a few things to see
what works best for us!
First, you choose
a picture of a character.
[NISHINA]
Isn't this from my doujinshi ?
Yeah! It's one of my favorites.
I should have asked you.
Would it be all right if
I used it for the contest?
Yes!
I'll draw a hundred more for
you if it would make you happy.
[SERINUMA]
You're so kind.
What do we do after that?
[SERINUMA] First, copy the
picture onto parchment paper
with a pencil.
Flip it over and trace the
image with a chocolate pen.
Then put it on the fridge
until it hardens.
Fill in the empty spaces
with colored chocolate,
take away the parchment
paper and voilà!
All done!
[GROUP]
Whoa!
[NANASHIMA]
It's so cool!
That's incredible!
With a picture like that,
they'll give you
the win for sure.
[SERINUMA]
It's not good enough!
This piece of trash isn't
capturing Shion's angelic beauty
at all!
[SERINUMA]
I've failed him!
I devour this pathetic
tribute as a sacrifice!
[NANASHIMA]
Please stop...
I think everyone chooses
character chocolates first.
I need ideas.
That's true.
If you'd like to stand out,
you'll need to be more original.
Let's make the piece 3-D.
3-D?
One second... a little...
...like this!
No way!
Nothing less from Yokoshima.
Brilliance pours from
everything you create.
Happy to help.
Together, you and I
can reach the stars!
Okay!
We're still here, ya know!
[NANASHIMA]
I'm done!
Mine turned out awesome!
My flower is the best!
Yes, it is.
Don't forget we're
here to support Serinuma!
[IGARASHI] She's been working
with that thing for hours,
but hasn't improved at all.
[SERINUMA]
I don't get this.
Why is it so tough to
make something in 3-D?
Aren't I in 3-D?
Or is that 4-D?
People make art look too easy.
Stop thinking and start working!
If you can't figure this out,
you won't make the deadline!
I'll help you.
You need to relax and let
yourself have fun with it, okay?
Yeah.
Thank you for the advice.
[SERINUMA]
She's so close!
[NANASHIMA]
Hey!
Let her focus!
Call me protective,
but I still don't think
you and Serinuma
should be left alone!
Neither do I!
[NISHINA]
You're too rough.
You said it yourself...
We're both girls, so why worry?
I disagree.
Personally, I think
Nana is dead on.
So why are you doing
all this for Serinuma?
[NISHINA] I suppose you could
say I'm drawn to things
that are cute and beautiful.
I can't help myself.
You're saying you only
like her for her looks?
I assure you there's
more to it than that.
Actually...
That sounds more like
your character than mine.
Yes! It took me over
three days to complete,
but it's done!
[GROUP] That thing doesn't
look like Shion.
[SERINUMA]
It's terrible, isn't it?
I worked on it for so long,
I can't tell anymore!
[NANASHIMA] It's okay!
I'd totally eat that thing!
[MUTSUMI] It's got uniqueness
only a true artist
could capture!
They're right!
Your eyes are drawn to it.
I'd call it an
eccentric masterpiece!
[SERINUMA]
Eccentric?
Idiot!
I didn't mean it! Sorry!
If you're comfortable with it,
why don't you submit my design
using your name instead?
No way!
I wouldn't feel
right doing that.
Thanks!
Wait a sec.
Isn't the deadline tomorrow?
If you wanna win that contest,
using Nishina's chocolate
might be the safer bet.
[GROUP]
That's true.
[SERINUMA] I spent so
much time practicing.
[SERINUMA]
It's so sweet.
Everything is clear now.
I know what I have to do.
What? You ended up sending
in the one you made?
You did?
Was there something
wrong with mine?
Not at all.
I thought about how it was
supposed to be a Valentine.
It's special when you
get something like that
from another person.
It was hard to look at,
but it came straight
from my heart.
There's no way I could
use anyone else's.
I'm really sorry
for wasting your time!
Don't worry!
You're such a loving person.
That's what makes you wonderful.
Well, what a nice
thing for you to say!
I almost forgot.
Here you go!
It's a small gift to say thanks
for being so nice to me.
I hope you like it.
This chocolate is really good.
Yeah.
She's pretty cute, huh?
You're saying you only
like her for her looks?
That sounds more like
your character than mine.
[IGARASHI] In the beginning,
it was about her looks.
But now...
[IGARASHI]
I don't wanna give her up.
I had no way of knowing that
a time was coming very soon
where my feelings
would be put to the test.
[IGARASHI]
Serinuma?
Oh. Hi!
[NAKANO]
Huh?
Kae?
Yeah? What's up?
Uh, what... what happened?
It's just been a... weekend!
[SERINUMA laughs]
Funny story!
I had a ton of that Valentine
chocolate left over,
and you can't let that stuff
go to waste, right?
Over the weekend
I started nibbling...
...and nibbling...
and before I knew it,
they were all gone!
Next thing I knew
I looked like this!
Crazy, huh?
Good morning!
Oh, really? Is it?
Are you feeling okay?
We learned in health class that
it's unsafe for your weight
to fluctuate quickly.
I appreciate you checking
on me, but I feel great!
[laughs]
Nana!
[SERINUMA] I'll go get the
teacher! Just hold on!
[SHINOMIYA]
What's wrong?!
[yelps]
[SERINUMA]
Shinomiya!
Oh, no! Please wake up!
We need help!
[SHINOMIYA] A dream. A dream.
This is a dream!
I'll close my eyes and drift
into a peaceful slumber,
and when I wake up Serinuma
will be normal again!
Right. She's gonna have
to lose the weight!
[IGARASHI] I don't think there's
anything we can do about it.
Well not with that attitude.
And don't say anything about
her having a good personality.
You're as bad as we are,
Mr. High and Mighty!
What's the point if she
doesn't have a hot body?
You're awful. That's offensive.
But...
I'm with you!
Yeah, boy!
Wow.
Oh, wow!
This is delicious!
Are you sure you
don't want some?
No way, it's all yours!
[NANASHIMA growls]
Why are you feeding
her all this food?!
Hey, Nanashima, you should
try a bite of this thing.
Are you any feeling
better now, Shinomiya?
Did you give her
all of these desserts?
I'm afraid so.
Her body is so
beautiful and soft
that I want to
keep feeding her.
I can't stop myself!
[NISHINA laughing]
You're tickling me, Shima.
Cut it out!
[SHINOMIYA, NANASHIMA]
You're not helping!
You made him cry!
Guess what?
I have to tell you about
the great news I just got!
[IGARASHI]
Oh, yeah? Go ahead!
They sent me an email about it.
Apparently, my entry won
the Valentine contest!
[IGARASHI, SHINOMIYA]
What?! It can't be!
[SERINUMA] They judges said
that only a true visionary
would have the bravery
to submit something
so off-the-wall!
[SHINOMIYA]
Bravery my--
[IGARASHI]
Shh...
I'm so happy
I can hardly stand it!
Oh! There's gonna
be an award ceremony,
and the director, voice actors,
and a few animators
will be there!
I'm so excited!
It'll be the best day of your
life so you have to be prepared!
I know! Let's get
our nails done!
[SERINUMA]
Yeah! That's a great idea!
Serinuma.
I wanna help you.
That day... It'll be awesome.
You deserve to look
as good as you feel.
Nanashima...
Yeah, so you gotta
lose the chub!
[IGARASHI, SHINOMIYA]
Have some tact!
[NANASHIMA]
Okay!
Do five more laps!
That's too much.
No way. It's great!
Look at her. Faster!
Um...
So why are they
doing this again?
I think Serinuma looks
beautiful just the way she is.
Why don't you go
get your eyes checked?!
[SERINUMA panting]
I'm gonna... pass out.
Serinuma! Are you hungry?
Why don't you take a break
to eat or drink something?
Okay!
A quick time-out and then
it'll be back to business!
Next up is five sets
of twenty squats!
Here goes!
I'm worried about you.
Have you been resting at all?
Not... really.
[NANASHIMA]
What am I missing here?
She looks awful!
[MALE TEACHER 01A]
Let's talk about fractions.
When we say "fraction"...
She's been exercising nonstop.
Why's she still big?
Slow down, man!
I'll add more to the list.
I think you might be
pushing her too hard.
She needs time to
build her strength up.
We're out of options.
I gotta be tough.
Yeah. I mean, it's
not like you want her
to stay the way she is, right?
I can't figure out why
she's not losing weight.
It's the kid.
[NANASHIMA]
It's time for a new routine!
Please explain it.
Right. It's the perfect
workout for a fangirl.
" Otagei !"
[MUTSUMI]
What are they doing?
It looks so neat!
It's a type of dancing that you
usually see at idol concerts.
You sure it's not
too intense for her?
She's fine.
Fangirls or whatever
love this kind of crap.
I practiced it at home.
It's quite simple.
Watch closely!
Hot and... ready!
Well? What did you think?
Wow. That's not embarrassing.
You're really good.
Why won't you
look me in the eyes?!
I loved it! I wanna try!
Master, will you teach
me to gyrate my hips
like you do?
Of course! No problem!
I think we should all
give this dance a try.
What do you say?
Uh... no.
Otagei is a style that's better
with a group of people.
Don't you want to
give Serinuma support
so she can reach her goals?
One, two... one!
What are we doing?
This lame dance...
is wearin' me out, dude!
One, two! I love working out!
How about we all take a break?
We don't wanna injure ourselves.
That's a good point.
Hey, Kae?
Yeah! So awesome!
Move and groove!
I love working out!
One, two, one, two.
This is for
fangirls everywhere!
[laughing]
[crack]
What was that sound?
Are you... all right?
[GROUP gasps]
Serinuma!
No more weight loss training.
I'm putting a stop to it.
Why?! We were finally
gettin' somewhere!
She hurt herself because
you pushed her too hard.
Frankly, you should be ashamed
of how you've been treating her.
[NANASHIMA]
You're nuts!
I was trying to help her out!
You've been terrible
since she gained weight.
Why can't you own up to
the fact that you're shallow?
What?!
[MUTSUMI]
Stop it.
Please calm down.
We're all to blame.
There's no point in arguing now.
Serinuma gets to decide
whether she wants to continue,
and we should support her.
Agreed?
I understand.
I'll be attending to her every
need until she feels better.
Can you believe
she said all that?
It's my fault! That dance!
My sexy moves were too much!
What? Don't ever
say that word again.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[SERINUMA]
Good morning!
Nice to see you.
How's your back?
I rested last night
and feel a lot better.
All good. Thank you.
Shima was nice enough to drive
me to school this morning.
It was my pleasure.
Ha. What a gentleman.
I could've done that.
Thanks a lot!
Yes, but I don't mind at all.
Be extra careful today!
How are you feeling now?
Can I get you anything?
I'll be here if you need me!
[bell rings]
[SERINUMA]
She's everywhere! I can't relax!
Would you... join me?
What's up?
Sorry.
It seemed like you
were starting to panic,
so I wanted to give you a break.
That's all.
Okay?
[SERINUMA]
This is exactly what I needed.
How did you know?
[IGARASHI chuckles]
It makes sense that
Nishina might be worried.
[SERINUMA]
That's true.
Everyone has been trying
so hard to help me.
I'm sorry for stressing you out.
I have to get it together!
Uh...
What was that?!
I'm pumping myself up!
If I'm gonna do this, it's
gotta be my way. Yeah.
I'll be committed, safe,
and do the best I can.
Even if I fail,
I'll still be proud.
'Cause I know I tried!
[SERINUMA]
I'm ready to get back in there!
[IGARASHI]
I see it now.
Serinuma is kind.
She's bright and smart.
I've never met anyone like her.
She's the same person,
no matter what she looks like.
What's up? Had lunch?
Nana. Listen.
I really do like Serinuma.
Huh? Yeah, don't we all.
[IGARASHI]
No. That's not what I mean.
I love her.
Her size makes
no difference to me.
Like this?
Like this.
Like that?!
I finally get it!
In the end, looks don't matter.
They don't if you walk
around with your eyes closed
all the time!
Don't lose my respect!
Wake up! Rise above it!
I love her now
more than ever before!
When did the world go nuts?
I don't even know you anymore!
[MUTSUMI] You're absolutely
sure that you're ready
to start working out again?
Yep! Thank you for
agreeing to train with me.
Serinuma, I'm your friend
and I'll always support you,
but I'm concerned.
Is your body ready
for this sort of activity?
[SERINUMA]
Don't worry!
I promise I'll let you know
if I need to slow down.
Perhaps you should
change your goal.
I'm not certain that you
can reach it by the date
of the ceremony.
[NANASHIMA]
Ha ha ha!
We can be of assistance.
That's right.
[NISHINA] Have you brought
more of your terrible ideas?
No, we have not!
[NISHINA] Then enlighten
us as to why you two
are holding hands.
[NANASHIMA]
Wow.
I guess you don't
know Serinuma that well.
Look at her!
[chuckles]
Momma likes what she sees!
There's nothing Serinuma
likes more than two dudes
who get it on.
So we made a game of it.
A point card reward system!
The closer she gets to her goal,
the more she'll get
to see us do together!
Brilliant!
[laughing]
So a hug!
How many points to
make you hug each other?
It's working!
You can earn it with
stomach crunches... fifty.
[SERINUMA]
That'll be a piece of cake!
Please be careful or
you might hurt yourself.
There's no rush.
Oh, right. Thanks.
Slow and steady.
I know you can do this.
[NISHINA]
That was considerate of you.
[IGARASHI]
You think so?
I care a lot about Serinuma.
And her health.
You know,
I started to wonder...
Am I the type of person
who only cares about looks?
At one time,
that might've been true,
and it was wrong of me.
I realized that I've never
met anyone like her before.
She's beautiful, inside and out.
It's clear to me now.
I think...
...I'm in love with Serinuma.
That's why I want
her to be happy.
I'll do anything for her.
I believe you.
If I may say so...
You have a beautiful spirit.
I reached my goal!
All thanks to you!
[NISHINA]
Astounding! Well done, Serinuma!
That's wonderful.
You sure worked hard.
We knew that you'd
be able to pull it off.
[SERINUMA]
Thanks!
It was a lot more difficult
than I thought it would be.
I kept going.
And you were with me
through every step.
[giggles]
You made it fun!
Thanks for everything.
[GROUP] We gave up so much...
for the cause.
[NANASHIMA] I don't know if
the sacrifice was worth it.
[SHINOMIYA] We should've
given it more thought.
There's only one reward left.
I can't wait for this!
[BOTH gasp]
[IGARASHI]
What's that?!
[NISHINA] I added it to give
her further incentive.
Just a little smooch.
[NANASHIMA]
Hell no!
Show the one you adore
you respect her hard work.
You wanted this.
[NANASHIMA yelling]
[NANASHIMA]
Wait!
What are you doing? Stop it!
[BOTH yelp]
[BOTH whimpering]
[NAKANO] And so... the Mirage
Saga Valentine Contest
Award Ceremony went even
better than she expected!
[MUTSUMI]
What's the matter, Shinomiya?
You seem down.
[SHINOMIYA] There was a
fight in my class today
and I got stuck in
the middle of it.
We all got in scolded.
[MUTSUMI]
That doesn't sound like you.
What happened?
[SHINOMIYA]
They stuffed my head in a toilet
when I reminded them that
fighting is for degenerates
with too much free time.
[MUTSUMI]
Poor thing.
I hope you didn't get hurt.
Let me comfort your ego.
[SHINOMIYA]
Uh... no thanks.
Physical rough-housing
isn't exactly my strong suit.
I'll use my mind to
outwit those idiots.
[MUTSUMI]
Oh, I see.
Well, good luck!
[SHINOMIYA]
Mutsumi, are you a good fighter?