After many years inside a Go
board, a spirit from the past,
known as Fujiwara-no-Sai,
has returned,
visible only to Hikaru Shindo.
A master of Go, Sai seeks
to play the Divine Move.
[theme music]
-He lost?
But he's as good as a pro.
[doorbell]
-Hi there.
-Well, hello, Akari.
-Is Hikaru at home?
-No, I'm afraid he's not here.
He's taking a Go class.
-Go class?
-Yeah, I know.
I wonder what's gotten
into him lately.
-Hikaru plays Go?
-Let's examine this game setup
a little closer, shall we?
Here, black descending
is a good move.
Even if white plays
the block here,
black plays an atari here.
The white captures two stones.
Black's next move will take
away white's potential eye
on this side.
And all the white
stones are dead.
-I don't have a clue
what he's talking about.
-Of course, you don't.
You're just a beginner.
-That way your opponent won't
guess how skilled you are.
Now, what would happen
if black took away
the eye before making the atari.
-19, 16.
-Very good.
If black plays here, white
lives by making the second eye--
-I wonder how good a
player this instructor is.
-He's a pro.
-A pro?
-That means he's
good enough that he
could make a living
just from playing Go.
-That's it for my lecture.
Let's play some games.
[japanese]
-Let's see now.
You must be Hikaru Shindo.
-Uh, that's me.
-Have you played Go before?
-Yeah, but only this one time.
And honestly, I felt like I
was watching the game more
than I was playing it.
-All right.
Then, we'll start with a
game of capturing stones.
-Huh, I know this one.
A black gets captured if white
puts a stone here, right?
-That's correct.
When we are just one move away
from capturing an opponent's
stone or stones, we say atari.
Here, this is another example.
Atari.
OK, Hikaru, try to escape.
-Well, let's see.
-Atari, again.
Atari.
-Hmm.
-Atari.
And atari, again.
Thank you very much.
-Huh?
This pattern is called
the Shichou or Ladder,
because it resembles one.
It's impossible to escape
from and appears quite often.
So look for it as you watch
the other players' games today.
-Uh, what should I do?
-Hikaru, are you
going home already?
-Just taking a break.
-Oh, what is this?
-A vending machine.
You put your money in,
and a drink comes out.
-Oh.
Oh.
-Oh, no, I'm late again.
Hikaru, are you learning
how to play Go, too?
-Uh, yeah, sort of.
I have this friend who
plays Go all the time.
We play every once in a while.
But it's not an easy game if you
don't know anything about it.
I came here to learn
some of the basics,
you know, like the rules
and stuff like that.
But it's harder than I thought.
-So you're just
killing some time here.
Oh, look.
They're showing the
match on TV right now.
-Hikaru, what is this device?
People are playing Go
inside that little box.
-Ah, we have a pause in play.
-I wonder what he's
thinking about.
-I wonder what indeed.
Even from his
opening move, I can
feel that Toya Meijin strives
for something exceptional
when he plays.
Something that we
cannot perceive.
-Oh, that's right.
They say he's the
one who has come
the closest to playing
the Divine Move.
-Divine Move?
-I know it's silly, but
I'm such a big fan of his.
-This man is no
ordinary Go player.
Like me, he yearns to
play the Divine Move.
-Our viewers might be interested
in hearing that Toya Meijin has
a son who aspires to be a pro.
-Yes, in fact, he's
quite a strong player.
-Hey, lady, don't you have
to go to class or something?
-Oh, yeah, that's right.
That Shirakawa Sensei is
really good-looking, too.
-Eh.
-Hello there.
Come on in.
-Is Akira Sensei here?
I was hoping he would
play a game with me.
-Uh, well, he's here.
But he might not want to play.
He hasn't played anyone
since that game last week.
All he does is replay that
one game over and over again.
-I heard about that.
That's the one where
he lost by two points
to a boy his own age.
-I'm leaving now.
-Uh, well, be careful
on your way home.
-Still here, Akira?
I bet your mother
gets pretty worried
when you stay out this late.
Akira's sure acting
strange, isn't he?
-Maybe, a little.
-That move and the next one.
It's like he was
playing a teaching game.
Could he really be that good?
No, there's no way.
There's no way a kid
could be that good.
I just don't understand.
Who is he?
[music playing]
-Well, that's all for today.
Don't forget your homework.
Take care on your
way home, everyone.
-See ya.
-Uh, Hikaru.
-Huh?
-Your social studies
scores have been very good
lately, though you do seem to
be daydreaming quite a bit.
Have you been
working with a tutor?
-Uh, yeah, yeah.
Something like that.
But uh, he can be a
real pain sometimes.
-Well, it's paying
off, so keep it up.
-I will.
Bye.
-Be careful on your
way home, Hikaru.
-OK.
-Wait up!
-Huh?
-Hey, Hikaru.
What's going with you lately?
You did all your corrections
in social studies,
but you're slacking
off in gym class.
And that's your best subject.
-Is there something weird
about doing the corrections
on my test?
-No, there's nothing
wrong with it.
Look, tomorrow's Sunday.
Do you want to
hang out together?
-Tomorrow?
I'm busy tomorrow.
I have to go someplace.
-Are you going to Go class?
-Uh, you know about that?
Well, yeah.
-You want to come, too?
-Me?
Let me think about it.
Hello.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
-I hope you don't
mind, but my friend
wanted to come along and
watch for a little bit.
-Hmm, not at all.
Anyone with an interest in Go
is most certainly welcome here.
Today, many players
open at a star point.
But the 3, 4 point
still has its fans.
By making the knight's
move enclosure like so,
we can effectively
secure that corner.
-Hikaru, do you understand
what he's talking about?
-Haha, not a word.
-But this is a good position.
And your opponent won't always
allow you to set up like this.
Let's say white goes here.
How should black respond?
-Hey, I know this one.
-Huh?
Ah, Hikaru, was it?
Well, where would
you place your stone?
-16, 5.
-It's 16, 5, just
below the star point.
-Ah.
-16, 5, here?
Oh.
-Huh?
-Eh.
-I thought you said you'd
never played Go before.
-Uh, was I wrong?
Sorry about that.
-On the contrary.
That's a very good move.
-Huh?
-We don't see it quite
so often nowadays.
But it was a popular
move in the past.
-Oh.
-Haha.
You can sit down now.
-OK.
Excuse me, why don't they
play this move anymore?
-Because the komi rule
wasn't in effect long ago.
-The komi?
-Well, black has the
advantage of playing first.
So white is awarded 5 and
1/2 points at the start
to compensate.
-Huh?
-Oh.
-In other words, if white's
final tally comes to 50 points,
black requires 56
points to win the game.
-Ah, 5 and a 1/2 points.
-So you've never heard of this?
-There was no such rule
during Shusaku's time.
-Hmm, it never crossed
your mind that black
might have an advantage?
-Now that I think about it,
I've never lost playing black.
-Give me a break.
-I see.
Komi is worth 5 and 1/2 points.
-Following the inception
of the komi rule,
it was felt that moving
on the diagonal like this
was a bit slow.
This particular move isn't
played too often anymore.
Nevertheless, in a lot of
ways, it is an exquisite move.
Place one stone if
you think Hikaru
is holding an odd number
of stones in his hand.
Place two if you think he's
holding an even number.
OK, Hikaru, count
out your stones.
-2, 4, 6, 8, 9, odd.
-I guessed right.
-Then you'll be black.
This is how we
determine who goes first
when both players
are of equal skill.
-Huh?
-Professionals
played these games.
Replay one of them so you can
get a feel for what Go is like.
I'll come back in
a little while.
-Ah.
-Hey, do you know
what to do, Hikaru?
-I think we're supposed to
set up our stones according
to the numbers.
Your first move is
right here, Akari.
-It's where?
-Uh, right here.
-Thanks for the
six stones, buddy.
-Huh?
-You sure do like giving
up your stones, don't ya?
-Mr. Akota is picking on
a weaker player, again?
Ah, the bully.
-Ha ha ha.
Don't take this personally,
but that was a dumb move.
I've never met anyone you
liked losing as much as you.
-Wait a sec.
-I can't take this anymore.
Hikaru, trade places
with that man's opponent.
I despise this braggart's
attitude and playing style.
-Sai?
-I refuse to stand by while
a stronger player ridicules
a weaker one.
I shall replace his frightened
opponent and engage him anew.
He will learn how it feels
to be on the receiving
end of such cruel play.
And then, when the game is done,
I shall chastise him soundly.
-Oops, sorry.
-What's the big idea, kid?
Your clumsiness just ruined
a perfectly good game.
-Sorry, it kind of
slipped from my fingers.
-Huh.
-I'll start picking them up.
-Hey, what are you doing?
No, don't touch that.
No, leave it alone.
Ah.
-Hikaru, I want you
out of here right now.
-Hey, did you bring me
here just to embarrass me?
-I didn't bring you.
You decided to follow me.
-Oh, forget it.
-You've angered the instructor.
And now, he's never going to
let us come back and play.
-Ah.
Huh?
Wait.
-By the way, there's
a Go tournament
for kids coming up soon.
-How about I take you to this?
Will that cheer you up?
-Hikaru.
-There's so much
tension in the air.
These kids are even
younger than I am.
Huh?
Those people over there
must be their parents
and family members.
Sai, this is incredible.
-Indeed.
Truly wonderous.
All these children.
Though my passion for Go
may be a thousand years old,
I see the same
fervor in their eyes.
This tells me that
a thousand years
hence, if I were to
search, I would still
find people with the
very same passion.
-You know, I wonder
if Akira Toya's here.
-Hello, Akira.
Mr. Hirosei wants
to know if you'd
like to play a
teaching game with him.
-I'm sorry.
I can't.
-Are you waiting for that boy?
-There are so many people here.
I'll never find him.
-That battle in the
upper left corner.
-Huh?
This one?
-The wrong move by black
will leave him dead there.
-Oh?
-The key move there is 1, 2.
-Oh, too bad.
You should have
played it one higher.
-Huh?
-Uh.
Oh.
-You there.
What's the matter with you, kid?
No comments are allowed
when the game's in progress.
-Uh, I'm sorry.
-Easy there.
Everybody, please calm down.
-Ah, Ogata Sensei, I was
about to take this unruly boy
off the floor.
-Good idea.
-Come with me.
-What?
-Sorry for the
interruption, kids.
Pick up your games where
you left off, please.
So tell me what happened.
-When I played 1, 3, that
boy said, oh, too bad.
Should have played
it one higher.
-He what?
-I just remembered.
When that boy was
here, I handed him
a flyer for the National
Youth Go Tournament.
-The one at the Go Association?
-Yes.
He didn't seem interested
when I showed it to him,
but he might have gone.
-Ah.
-Akira.
-Please, if he shows up, keep
him here till I get back.
-What's gotten into him?
He's changed.
-Maybe it's because
he's never met
someone he could
call a rival before.
-Unacceptable.
There's no excuse for a slip
of the tongue like that,
young man.
-Yes, sir.
-So how did you rule on it?
We decided to nullify
the match and have
the two boys start another game.
-Yes, you had no choice really.
-We're done with you.
Go home now.
-Sorry for all the trouble, sir.
Hmm.
-I'm glad that's over.
Now, tell me about the
move he commented on.
-Hey, son, your change.
-Boy, did I ever mess that up.
-I feel bad for those two boys.
-Ugh.
Huh?
-You should be more careful.
-Huh?
-He is the one.
The man closest to
playing the Divine Move.
-I heard there was
some trouble earlier.
-Yes, Toya Sensei.
-Take a look.
We need your advice on this.
-This game is such
that even a pro
would have to reflect a while.
But a boy commented on it.
-We were told he
merely glanced down.
-You don't say.
He recognized the key to black
survival at a mere glance?
My son Akira might
have spotted it,
but I didn't know there was
another child of his level
out there.
-And they let him go without
even getting his name.
-I'm sorry, sir.
-It doesn't matter.
If this boy's that
strong of a player,
then he will make his presence
known to us, sooner or later.
-It's all your fault, Sai,
for opening your big mouth.
Oh, so you want to fight, do ya?
Well, I'm never going
to play Go again.
How do you like that?
-Hikaru.
-Hmm?
-Akira?
-I found you.
I finally found
you, Hikaru Shindo.
[theme music]
-I see.
So you are the one
who beat Akira.
Put down three
stones, young man.
That's how I play with Akira.
That's how good he is.
-Me, a pro?
It's never even crossed my mind.
-A true Go player would never
say something so insulting.