[theme music]
-Huh?
I thought being a pro was all
about playing lots of matches.
When do you think I'll
get to play Toya, huh?
Any idea Waya?
-No!
-But now we're pros.
We've got a connection.
Me and Toya, me
and Toya's father.
We're all a part of
the same world now,
and one day I'll be
able to play them!
Me!
-He's right.
I'm not the one
connected to that world.
It's Hikaru.
It's him and him alone.
KUWABARA: I see that
kid managed to pass.
So, his name is Shindou?
He might be part of the new wave
that Ogata once talked about.
-Did you hear that?
They want me to play against
Toya Meijin in the next Shincho
Dan series.
-Please.
Allow me to play for you.
-But Sai, I can't let you.
-Please.
Let me play him, Hikaru.
-No!
Forget all about it!
Akira will be watching the game.
And so will Waya, and
Ochi, and everybody else!
It's gonna be on the
front page of "Go Weekly!"
Besides.
There's gonna be a reverse komi
handicap of 5 and 1/2 points.
That's what happened in
the Shincho Dan last year.
The new One-Dan player
has the advantage,
so it would be easy
for you to win.
You're too strong,
and if I let you play,
I'm gonna have your shadow
hanging over me again.
-Then let it be that way!
-Stop being so selfish, Sai!
This game's important to me.
-All right.
If you're not gonna
let me play now,
then tell me, when will you?
-Sai.
What's wrong?
I mean, you told me a
while back that you'll
be around for all eternity.
So, there's no rush for you
to play games right now.
You even said if I
died, you would simply
move on and find
someone else to inhabit.
Isn't that right?
-Hm.
HIKARU: Well?
-I can't deny that what
you've said is true--
-There, you see?
I'm just the second person.
There's also going to
be a third and a fourth.
-But Hikaru, you don't
seem to understand.
Lately, I've been starting
to feel very worried.
I don't know how much longer
I can stay in this world.
-If that's what
this is all about,
then you're worrying
over nothing.
Anyway, whenever I
let you play, I always
seem to get into
some sort of trouble.
Maybe the next guy you
inhabit will let you play.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Hikaru.
Does that mean he
has no intention
of letting me play again?
Ever?
OGATA: Kuwabara-sensei.
-Well.
Ho ho!
If it isn't Ogata.
It's been a while.
Nice to see you again.
We haven't met face to face like
this since the Honinbo title
match, hm?
The best of seven
series was a lot of fun.
-Even if I didn't win, I
learned a lot from playing you.
-You've been doing
very well recently, eh?
I hear you managed
to defeat Kurata
in quite a decisive
manner the other day.
-And what about you, sensei?
I've heard you've been
having a tough time.
-Well, you can't win 'em all.
Not when you get to my age.
But I won't be letting
go of my Honinbo title,
I can assure you of that.
-So why exactly are
you here, Kuwabara?
-Here, have one of these, Ogata.
It's an awful
habit we have, huh?
-I'm fine, thanks.
-So, you want to know
why I'm here, don't you?
I could ask you the
very same question.
This game today is with
a mere novice, a One-Dan.
Even though the
Meijin is playing,
I wouldn't have thought
it was worth someone
of your stature coming to watch.
I can only assume
you're here because you
have an interest in the
boy, because you think
he's going to be part of that
new wave of the world of Go?
-Do you know anything
about this Shindou?
Have you ever seen him
play anywhere before?
-That's why you're here!
I knew it.
I knew there was something
special about that boy.
I have a sixth sense
about these things.
-A sixth sense?
-Call it intuition, if you like.
All I did was walk past him, but
I just had a feeling, you know.
-How could you possibly
know from walking past him?
That's impossible.
WAYA: Shindou gets to go first,
and then it's you next week,
Ochi.
You guys are so lucky.
OCHI: You mean they
haven't called you yet?
WAYA: Not yet, but it
better happen soon.
-Ogata Nine-Dan and
Kuwabara Honinbo?
Good afternoon!
-Come on, Ochi.
Let's go sit over here.
Come on!
-What do you think
they're doing here?
I mean, they're some of the
best players in the world,
so why would they
come to watch this?
-They probably wanna see
how shindou does today.
Did you know Ogata
was watching him
when he played the
Young Lions tournament?
And he was the one
who invited Shindou
to joint Toya Meijin's
study session.
-Shindou was studying
with Toya Meijin?
-No, he actually
decided not to, but only
because he'd already started
studying in my group.
I've got no idea why
Kuwabara-sensei's here,
unless he's also got
his eye on Shindou.
-Uh.
-Hello.
-Hello, Mr. Ogata,
and Kuwabara-sensei.
WAYA: So he did come, after all.
-Hi, how are you?
-Hi Ochi.
I'm fine, thank you.
-He knows your name?
How come?
How do you two know each other?
-Young man, you're the son
of the Meijin, aren't you?
-Yes, sir.
My name's Akira Toya.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
-I suppose you're also here
to see how Shindou does.
-Uh, no, I was just--
-I see, I see.
Everyone seems
interested in him.
Even the Meijin.
He might have five
championship titles,
but he's keeping a close
eye on the new boy.
Fasinating!
-Is this match that important?
-All here for Shindou?
Who is he?
-He was a classmate,
a rival, and a friend.
That's all I know.
-And smile, please.
[camera snapping]
-My son Akira will be
watching the match today.
I've noticed he's been
following your progress
with a great deal of interest.
But he isn't the only one.
Both Ogata and myself have
been keeping a close eye
on your development.
And if you want
to know the truth,
I personally choose you
to be my opponent today.
-Huh?
-So show me how strong you are.
Don't hold anything back.
-Yes, sir.
(VOICEOVER) The
championship room.
The same room that Waya
and I snuck into last year
to look around.
And now I'm the one
who's playing in there.
Huh?
Sai?
Sai!
-Huh?
Shindou, please take your seat.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai,
move out of the way!
KUWABARA: So, Ogata.
How would you feel about
making this more interesting?
-A friendly wager, then?
Sounds like a good idea.
[laughter]
-It does, doesn't it?
-A wager?
-Now, there's a handicap
of 5 and 1/2 reverse komi,
but even with that, he'll have
a tough time against Koyo Toya.
-Yes.
I agree.
-Unless, of course, the
Meijin takes it easy and lets
him win, as a gift to welcome
him to the big leagues.
-No.
He'd never do that.
-No, I don't suppose he would.
-So, who are you betting on?
-I'll go for the boy.
-Hm.
Going for the long
shot, are you?
-Not at all.
I never make bets that
I don't think I can win.
Not me.
I know what you're
thinking, Ogata.
You wanted to be the
one betting on the kid.
Isn't that right?
-You forget that I'm one
of the Meijin's students.
There's no doubt in my mind
that he's going to win it.
-The way they talk
about Shindou.
Just who is he?
-Well, he was a
classmate and a rival.
And he's also a friend.
That's all I know.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Shindou.
You're about to play my father.
Ogata and Kuwabara-sensei
are watching your every move.
You've made it this far.
I've been waiting for this
moment for a long time.
What will your strategy be?
What kind of game are
you going to play?
-Uh, young man?
We need you to sit down now.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai!
-Hm?
Is something the
matter, Shindou?
-You OK?
-I'm really sorry, Hikaru.
I just wanted to sit
there for a moment.
-That's all right.
-Come on, Shindou.
Sit.
-Hm?
(VOICEOVER) Pull yourself
together Sai, and stop sulking.
I've got an important game here.
I understand how you feel.
But-- I know the thing
is-- Sai, I know a chance
like this doesn't come
along for you every day.
No, no!
If I let Sai play when there's
a 5 and 1/2 point reverse komi,
he'd win way too easily.
Then I'd get all kinds of
attention from everyone.
Wait a minute.
What if-- yes, a handicap.
If Sai had to work with
a different handicap,
his game would be
completely changed.
Toya Meijin gets
the second move,
and he has the 5 and 1/2
point handicap against him.
But if I gave Sai an even
bigger one-- let's see.
If Sai had to overcome
the handicap of 15 points,
he wouldn't be able to
play his usual game.
And that his true ability
wouldn't be so obvious.
-I'll do it!
I'll do it!
I'll plays as if I'm
facing a 15 point handicap.
-Sai.
Do you understand what
you're agreeing to?
Even if you get to move first,
trying to make up 15 points
means you'll have to
make a lot of over plays.
Don't forget, your
opponent is Akira's dad.
He could crush you
in this kind of game.
Is this really how you
want to play against him?
-It's time for play to begin.
The new One-Dan moves first.
Reverse komi of
5 and 1/2 points.
You'll have two hours
of playing time.
If you go into
overtime, you will
be allowed one minute per move.
-Huh?
Sai?
-When you're ready,
please begin.
-Onegai shimasu.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER:):
All right, then.
If that's what you really want.
Onegai shimasu.
How are you gonna
pull this off, Sai?
OCHI: It's been 20
minutes already.
-They have started the
game, haven't they?
-This kid must be
very determined.
-Are you sure it's
determination?
-What else could it be?
You're not saying he's too
nervous to pick up a stone?
[laughter]
-Shindou's up to something.
Or why else would he wait?
It's not like he didn't know who
his opponent was going to be.
Normally you would
come into the game
with at least some idea
about your first move.
He does realize he's only got
two hours of playing time,
doesn't he?
Wasting 20 minutes at
the beginning like this
is very unusual.
-You wouldn't catch me
using that much time.
-Yeah. Me neither.
-Well, this makes
me think he must
be planning something special.
After all, he's
quite extraordinary.
[laughter]
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Shindou.
-What is he doing?
SAI (VOICEOVER): So, I need
to finish 15 points ahead?
Hm, that's quite
a tough challenge.
It's not like this is some
player from a Go salon.
This is one of the
strongest adversaries
I'm ever likely to meet.
Someone who will fight down
to the last half point.
Yes.
The atmosphere around this
board is intense, exactly
as it was the time we
faced each other before.
No matter what the
circumstances are,
he will have to respond
to my every move.
My goal is to win by
more than 15 points.
I have no alternative but
to go on the offensive.
A fight where I
destroy my opponent,
or be destroyed in the process.
How far will I be able to go?
The upper right hand corner.
Star point!
[theme music]
SAI: I must play
the board perfectly,
all the way until the end game.
HIKARU: Do you think
you can do it, Sai?
SAI: Don't worry.
All of my attacks
may look random,
but there will be a
greater plan in force here.
HIKARU: Remember.
A lot of people are
watching us really closely.
SAI: And I'll give them a
game they'll never forget!
HIKARU: Next time.
A Game of Desperate Measures.
SAI: I just hope
the Meijin doesn't
realize what we're up to.