[music playing]
-Time for our last
study session.
And then we got summer
break and the prelims.
Good luck.
And hope you make it through
the first round of the exam
next month.
-Mhm.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): What was
Shindou so happy about?
Doesn't he realize we're
going to be opponents
as soon as the exam starts?
[music playing]
-The prelim matches for
the pro exam start today.
One a day for five days.
-And if you win three
of your five games,
you advance to the finals
taking place next month,
is that right?
-Mhm.
As long as I play
like I normally do,
I should get through to
the next round, no problem.
I know Waya and Asumi already
made it to the finals,
but it's good to know
some of the other Insei
are going to be here.
Hopefully it won't
feel so scary in there.
-It's not going to be easy.
The pressure will be
on you to perform.
[motorcycle engine]
[gasps]
-Hikaru, are you confident
your game's strong enough?
-Of course it is.
Stop worrying, would ya?
Huh?
He's not taking the exam, is he?
He's too old.
[motorcyle engine]
-Ah.
Summer's not the time to
wear a stinking helmet.
-Whoa.
That's onee mean looking guy.
-Hey there.
You doing this pro exam too?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Why
does he want to know?
Mhm.
-Me too.
Guess I'll see you inside.
-What's a gorilla
doing playing Go?
-Hey Shindou, why are
you just standing there?
-No one told me adults
would be taking the exam.
-Anyone can take it.
People come from all over.
-That's big.
-The only restriction is
that you have to be under 30.
Some of the entrants
used to be Insei.
Other entrants have
come from the world
of amateur tournaments.
-Hm.
-Get a good rest last night?
Sleep well?
-Mhm.
-Great!
-You even fell asleep while
you were practicing Go with me.
-Will you shut up?
[music playing]
-Wow.
-What's with the attitude?
-Huh?
-You always ignore people
when they're talking to you,
you little punk?
Oh yeah, that's right.
Just walk away, why don't you?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
What's with him?
-Could you keep the noise down?
Can't you see he
didn't want to talk?
-So?
All I did was ask him
where he was from.
It's not a tough question.
-The exam starts soon.
He just wanted some
peace and quiet.
-So you're saying it's my fault?
Huh?
He couldn't answer
a friendly question?
He'll never make it as a pro
with that sort of attitude.
No manners.
-Who is that guy, anyway?
-Think he's taking the exam?
-I hope not.
-Hikaru, let's go and put
your stuff away, shall we?
-Good idea.
-Hey, Hikaru!
-Fukui.
-How's it going?
Everything OK?
-Sure it is.
Sort of.
-He got intimidated by this
guy yelling in the lobby.
-I did not get intimidated.
-20 minutes to go.
-Huh?
-Last year, guess who
I had to play first?
None other than Akira Touya.
-Touya?
Of course.
Although he's a strong
player, he wasn't an Insei.
So he had to go through all
the prelims like everyone else.
-I remember during one
of the lunch breaks
Touya wanted to talk to
Waya, but Waya got all funny
and just told him to shut up.
And then ignored him.
I don't know.
It was weird.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I'm
following in Touya's footsteps.
Just one year behind him.
-You're on the right path.
If you keep going
in this direction,
you will eventually reach Akira.
-Yeah, you bet I will.
-Nearly time for
things to start.
[music playing]
-We will now proceed to select
pairings for the first match.
Please come forward when
your name is called.
Katagiri.
-Here.
-Draw a number for your seat.
-Muriyama.
-Here.
-Eh.
[coughing]
-Tsubaki.
-Yo!
OK, here I come.
-Hm.
That guy's a real loud mouth.
You think he's doing it on
purpose to try and put us off?
I don't like him at all.
If he messes with me before my
match, he's going to regret it.
-Shindou.
Shindou!
-Hikaru.
-Here!
-Hagino.
Seat 14.
-OK.
-Hikaru, try not
to get too nervous.
-Now Shindou, you're at seat 21.
At this point you may move
to the seat numbers allocated
to you.
Seat number one is in
the corner over there,
followed by two,
three, and so on.
[music playing]
-Hey.
-You ended up with the
worst opponent ever.
If you're not
careful, you're going
to need protection
from gorilla man.
I guess this isn't your
lucky day, huh, Shindou?
-Why did this have
to happen to me?
-Before you begin, you will
need to set your clocks
to two hours.
And your overtime allowance
will be one minute.
Black and white have
already been assigned.
-OK.
He's just another opponent.
Nothing special.
-When you're ready, begin!
[in unison]
-Onegaishimasu.
Here we go.
-Excuse me.
-Huh?
[music playing]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Oh come on.
Where is he?
[music playing]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): He's been
gone for like half an hour.
What could he be doing?
[music playing]
-Huh?
-At least now we can
continue on with the game.
[music playing]
-Come on, Hikaru.
Don't lose your composure.
[music playing]
-He put the stone
back in his bowl.
Why'd he do that?
-Ladies and gentlemen
it's time for lunch.
Please stop your clocks.
-Hey, you want to go grab
a quick bite to eat, kid?
-Who, me?
-You're one of the Insei, right?
So you've got to know the
best place to eat around here.
Show me.
-Hikaru, what are you doing?
Don't go!
-I don't think I have a choice.
-Tough luck, Shindou.
-A burger?
Don't be stupid.
I can't eat that.
Look, let's try this
place, what do you say?
Huh?
Don't look so worried.
This lunch is on me.
Save your allowance for
something else, kid.
-I wasn't really worried
about that, but thanks.
-So what is bugging you?
Now tell me, what
was your name again?
-It's Shindou.
-Well my name's Tsubaki,
just like the samurai.
Pretty cool, don't you think?
There was once a
mighty samurai who
went by the name
of Sanjuro Tsubaki.
-Yeah right.
-What, don't you believe me?
-Can I ask you something?
You know when you
disappeared for the first 30
minutes of the match?
Where did you go exactly?
-I went for a quick
ride on my bike.
It helps me to relax a bit.
Yeah, believe it or
not, even someone
like me feels the pressure.
Gets to us all in the end.
I ain't gonna win
unless I play my best.
And I play my best
when I'm calm.
You play when you're all tense,
and you're not going to win.
So I took a break for a
half hour just to chill out.
But you seem to be getting
more and more wound up.
We're given two hours to play.
It's totally up to
me how I use it.
-I never realized you
were allowed to do that.
-Well, how much
game time do they
give you to play as
an Insei student?
-Well, if you're in the
A league you get an hour.
But if you're in the B league?
Just 30 minutes.
-So I guess this
is your first match
with two hours of playing time.
-Yep.
-And that means this is
the first time you've ever
had a break in the
middle of the game?
-Yep.
-Explains why you let
me have the chance
to play the last stone.
-Huh?
-I made sure the
morning session ended
while it was still
my turn to move.
So now I can think about
my next move, while I eat.
Take my time.
And decide exactly
where I want to move.
-Oh.
-Nice position to be in.
You have no idea
where I'll move,
so you can't plan
anything of your own.
All you can do is wonder.
Seems all I have
to do is look at
and you wet your pants, kiddo.
-I'm not scared of you!
Not a bit.
-I guess most of your games
have been against other kids.
In which case, it's time
for you to wise up and learn
how things work in
the grownup world.
Eat up before your
noodles go soggy.
-I'm not hungry anymore.
-Hikaru is completely
intimidated.
There's no way he can win now.
[locusts]
-Oh!
-It's over, kid.
-Mhm.
-So, did you win?
-I win by four
and a half points.
Hey, thanks for the game, kiddo.
-Thanks.
You played a strong game.
-Oh, come on.
You can't let one little
loss get you down.
Pull yourself together.
I don't know about you,
but after that game,
I feel like I'm on a bit of
a roll, all because of you.
See you, kid.
-What a jerk.
-Um, Shindou.
-What's the matter?
Did you lose the game?
-Yeah, and all
because I didn't know
how important the last
move before the break was.
-What are you talking about?
-You're so silly.
It's no big deal.
-Are you sure?
-Sometimes it's better to forget
about the game during lunch.
What's important is
the change of pace.
I like going into the break
when it's the other guys turn,
and that way I get
a chance to relax.
-I don't care either way.
-I'm with the
gorilla on this one.
I like having a chance
to plan my next move.
Sometimes that extra hour
makes all the difference.
-You think too much about it.
You might make a mistake.
Anyway, the point
is, it doesn't really
matter who has the next
turn after the break.
It's not like we
have to seal a move.
-What's seal a move?
-Seal a move is seal a move.
You mean you don't know?
-Nope.
-You know that the big
title matches happen over
two days, right?
When they get to the
end of the first day,
the next move isn't played.
It's written down and sealed
in an envelope, ready for when
they start up
again the next day.
That way it's fair
for both players.
-Two days?
There are matches that
last for two days?
-I can't believe you
don't even know that.
Yes, there are matches
that last for two days.
Of course, only a few
of the world's top pros
actually get to play in them.
It's going to be a long
time before any of us
reach that level.
Now you've got to learn to
stop worrying about your match
during the lunch break.
And you've got to learn not to
let the other guy intimidate
you.
The only reason he quit
the room for half an hour
was to try and throw you off.
Scare tactics.
He had it all planned,
and you fell for it.
-I know.
-How are you ever going to
cope if you let something
like that affect your game?
Remember that once
we get to the finals,
we all have three hours to play.
Not two.
-Why are you making such
a big deal about it?
-Because I'm the one who's
playing gorilla man tomorrow,
OK?
And I'm going to beat him.
-This is my station.
I'll see ya.
-See ya later!
-Poor Shindou.
-Huh?
-He doesn't seem to know
very much about title matches
and stuff, does he?
-Guess not.
-And gorilla man
really freaked him out.
-That guy'd freak anyone out.
He's horrible.
-You know how we started
playing in a Go Salon?
We got to play all
sorts of adults.
And some of them were
pretty high ranking, too.
I get the impression
Shindou's never done that.
-Yeah.
And then we went on to
study with a pro for awhile.
-The only training
Shindou seems to have had
was a year in a
junior high Go club.
And he's had very
little experience
competing in tournaments.
I think he's only entered
a couple small ones.
-What are you getting at?
-With that sort
of background, how
come he's this close
to turning pro?
-Are you saying that
he's some sort of genius?
-I don't know about genius.
But have you noticed
how fragile he is, even
when he's playing well?
They say the faster you
rise, the harder you fall.
Not that it's anything
to do with me.
-Uh, Hikaru.
Your father and I have
to go out tomorrow.
Could you keep an eye
on the house for us?
-Sorry, I've got another
pro exam tomorrow.
-You what?
What exam's that?
-For professional Go players.
-Who's taking this exam?
-I am.
-And what's it for again?
-It's the pro exam, mom.
-Ah!
Oh my goodness.
So Hikaru, you're taking an
exam to play Go as a pro?
-Yeah.
-But Hikaru, why
would you do that?
You're just a teenager.
-So what?
Why shouldn't I take it?
There are other kids my age who
have already made it as pros.
-But Hikaru, you mean you want
to play Go professionally?
As a career?
Well you haven't mentioned
anything about this to me
before, dear.
-Oh, thought I had.
-Earlier on you
said another exam.
How long's this been going--
-Mom, stop bugging me!
-Don't you talk to me like that.
If you really want to
play Go professionally,
then I should know about it.
-What I want to do with my
life is my business, not yours.
-Now hold on.
I don't have a problem with you
playing Go in your spare time,
if that's what you want to do.
But not when your
grades at school
have been getting
worse and worse.
If you spent more time
studying, then you
could play Go or whatever
else you wanted to,
and I wouldn't mind a bit.
-Who cares about grades?
Once I pass the
pro exam, they're
not going to matter anyway.
-Oh!
-Now I understand why Waya's
so desperate to pass the test.
If you want to know,
I lost my game today.
Are you happy now?
-Hikaru.
-Call me when dinner's ready.
A pro?
But what is he thinking?
He can't be serious, can he?
-Gorilla man's here already?
Hm.
Why should I care?
I'm not playing him today.
He can't intimidate me anymore.
I've got to make sure he
comes nowhere near me.
-Nothing I can say will help
you with this one, Hikaru.
-Where is he?
I can't see him anywhere.
-Oh, hi!
-Hi there!
-Yo!
Good luck today, kiddo.
Don't let the fact you lost
yesterday get you down.
Remember, we only need to
win three out of the five
to get through to the finals.
Hahaha.
-Haha yourself.
-But as soon as you lose three
games you're out for good, kiddo!
-What is it with him?
I've only lost one game so far.
-Uhoh.
Shindou's letting it get to him.
[music playing]
-Ready, and begin.
-Onegaishimasu.
[theme music]
-Will you stop shouting at me?
Can't you see I'm trying
to concentrate here?
-The greater the pressure,
the harder it is to perform.
-I know, I know.
But you're not
making it any easier!
-All right, I'll be quiet.
But don't say I didn't warn you.
-Next time, the last
day of the prelims.
-Fate hangs in the balance.