[theme music]
BOY: I faced him before, in
the Young Lions tournament
last year.
He played a good game, even
gave me a bit of a scare.
But his end game
wasn't strong enough,
and I beat him by
6 and 1/2 points.
Afterwards, Toya kept
asking me about Shindou,
wanting to know
how he had played.
At the time, it
really ticked me off
that he didn't want to
know about me and my game.
But is Shindou
really was his rival,
that'd explain why
he was so interested.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): All right!
I can win this.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER):
The only way I
can measure Shindou's
true strength is
by playing him myself.
I knew it the moment
he came running up
to me the other night.
There was something
different about him.
All I have to do now is wait.
The match is set.
We're going to face
each other once again.
-Looks like he's managed to
fend off Shindou's attack.
But maybe that's exactly what
Shindou expected him to do.
Murakami was trying to
keep Shindou at bay,
but its taken him too
many moves to do it,
and it's cost him
a lot of territory.
-That's it.
I resign.
-He simply lost
the will to fight.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
-Now I can see why Toya
thinks of him as a rival.
MAN: Excuse me, Shindou.
Could I have a
quick word with you?
So, does this mean you're going
to be coming to all your games
from now on?
-Yeah!
Yeah, of course.
I don't want to
miss a single one.
-Fine.
Now, did you know the pairings
for the first around the Meijin
tournament qualifiers
have been sent out.
-Yeah.
I got the notice yesterday.
-In that case, you already know.
Your first opponent's
going to be Toya Three-Dan.
-Yes.
-Right now, Toya has
a very busy schedule,
so I'm not sure exactly when
you two are going to be playing,
but whenever it is,
I'll let you know.
Anyway, good luck.
There are a lot of
people out there
who've got high hopes
for your success.
-Thank you.
Sorry for missing so many games.
-Who are these
people you say have
got high hopes for Shindou?
-Ah, Mr. Amano.
For starters, there's Kuwabara.
I heard him talk about
Toya and Shindou as equals.
That kind of took
me by surprise.
-Really?
-Don't tell me you
think that way too?
-Well, yes.
I do.
-I don't understand what's
so special about him.
He has a lot to learn about
how to properly act like a pro.
Don't get me wrong, I'm happy
to see young people getting
involved in the game, especially
if they have real talent.
The pro exam start
this week, doesn't it?
I wonder who's gonna make
it through this year.
Whoever it is, I hope they
take things more seriously
than Shindou and
actually show up.
That Shindou kid-- what
do you think, Mr. Amano?
Does the game
really have a future
in the hands of
players like him?
-All right.
When you're ready, please begin.
-Onegai shimasu.
-Shinoda-sensei.
Got the pro exam underway?
Everything good?
-Yes.
It's the preliminary
rounds right now,
and the finals start
in a month or so.
-So, who are the
favorites this year?
Karawaki And Isumi?
-Isumi's definitely going to
be one of the front runners.
He looks very confident.
Not at all like last year.
-Oh.
That sounds very promising.
He used to have this fragile
side, which always let him
down.
-Mr. Amano, there are
people in the world of Go
who believe that,
unless someone's talent
flourishes at an early
stage, they'll never make it.
But I've always
felt that players
should be allowed to
develop at their own pace.
On life's journey, sometimes
a detour's the best route.
-Mind if I quote you
on that, Shinoda?
It'd be perfect for an
article in Go Weekly
if Isumi passes the exam.
Ochi and Waya seem to
be making good progress
since they became
pros last year.
Even Shindou's doing well
since he made his come back.
-And I hope the
players that pass
this year will follow
in their footsteps.
-He's not fooled
by any of my moves.
I have to try a
different tactic.
This is gonna be tough.
No!
How could I have missed that?
I should've stuck back
when I had the chance.
He's got himself out of
trouble with that contact play.
There's nothing I can do.
Black has no weak spots.
The game is
completely one sided.
-Uh, see you.
-OK, see you later.
First he beat Murakami,
and now Tsujioka.
Does thia mean the
new wave is coming?
I know Shindou's strong,
but is it the real thing?
-I resign.
AMANO: Toya is taking down
one high ranking player
after another.
The new wave is
coming, and Akira Toya
is definitely leading the way.
-I resign.
-Congratulations on
your win, Ogata-sensei.
First the Judan title,
now this one as well?
-Yes, thank you.
-Nogi-sensei, perhaps you'd be
willing to share your thoughts
on the game with us.
-He was hanging
in there, waiting
for the right opportunity.
Then he took it.
KUWABARA:
Disappointing, Mr. Nogi.
-Huh?
-10 years ago you won the Meijin
title three times in a row.
Now look at you, letting
yourself be pushed around
by the likes of Ogata.
-Kuwabara-sensei!
-I was watching the
game in the other room.
Mr. Nogi, we veterans
have a position to uphold,
and you've let the side down.
-I know you were successful
in defending your Honinbo
title against Kurata
recently, but can you
guarantee you're going to
be able to keep on winning?
-We've got the Meijin
tournament coming up next month,
and Mr. Ichiryu is going
into battle with Hatonaka.
But not to worry.
I'm sure that an old
timer like Ichiryu
who knows how to deal with
a young pup like Hatonaka.
We're not going to let these
greenhouses take over just yet.
-With all due respect,
Kuwabara-sensei, Ogata
here isn't exactly a greenhorn.
He has won two titles.
-Hm.
I've always been content to
stick with the Honinbo title
up to now, but
now that Ogata has
won a couple of
other titles, maybe I
should branch out and
make a serious try
for the Judan and the Gosei.
I've always done rather well
in my games against Ogata.
Haven't I?
Well, Ogata?
-As defending champion, I'll
be there waiting for you.
KUWABARA (VOICEOVER):
This isn't good.
He's beginning to look
and sound like a champion.
-Ogata-sensei?
-Good morning, sir.
-Good morning.
You've made impressive progress.
Two years ago I
was your opponent
in the Shinsho Dan series, your
first game as a professional.
I seem to recall having a 5
and 1/2 point reverse handicap
in that game, but I
still managed to win.
It was clear which one of
us was the stronger player.
Today, however, is an even game.
I'll be interested to
find out how much you've
improved since then.
-I did the recording for
that Shinsho Dan match.
It's amazing. back then
Toya was just a One-Dan,
and now he's made it
to the Honinbo league.
[buzzer]
-Onegai shimasu.
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
Publications.
Mr. Miyake.
How are you?
What?
Are you serious?
You heard this from where?
Yeah, OK.
Of course.
I understand.
-That was Miyake?
The reporter from [inaudible]?
What was he calling about?
-He wanted to let us know that
Koyo Toya has signed a contract
to play for Beijing in China.
-To play for Beijing?
If he really has
signed with them,
then he's going to be playing
in the Chinese team league.
-So what is the team league?
-It's the equivalent of the J
League we have here in Japan.
Each city has its own team.
-I've heard of teams signing
some of the top Korean pros,
but this is the
first time I've heard
of them signing one from here.
Wait a sec.
-Huh?
What?
What is it?
-Now that Toya-sensei
has retired,
is schedule isn't
tied up with all
the matches for the association.
Compared to here, the contracts
in China don't pay much.
But he'll have more freedom.
Plus, he gets to play some
of the best Go players
in the world over there.
No wonder he agreed to sign.
Yoshikawa.
-Yes?
-Get Toya-sensei on
the phone right away.
We need to get an
interview with him.
BOY: Yang Hai!
-Huh?
-Guess what I just heard.
Beijing have signed Toya Sensei
of Japan to be on their team.
-I know.
The news is all
over the internet.
-With him on board, Beijing's
gonna be a way better team.
And I bet it's going to
make the whole league more
exciting to play in now.
You know me and Wan
Sing play for Shanghai,
so we're gonna have to
toughen up our game.
-The way you're going,
anyone would think you're
a big Koyo Toya fan.
Yes!
He is the closest anyone's ever
got to playing the Divine Move.
-I wouldn't be so sure.
When the Divine
Move finally comes,
it's gonna come from here.
-From a computer?
-Yeah.
-They say it'll take another
100 years before they build
a computer program that's strong
enough to beat a human at Go.
-I'm not going to
need 100 years.
I found a sponsor who
can fund my research,
so I can do it much sooner.
There are people already
working on inputting data
for the program.
-Now I get it.
No wonder your team is
the worst in the league.
You're spending all
your time on this.
-This project has nothing
to do with my team's record!
Have you seen what my
winning percentage is?
-It's worse than mine, isn't it?
-O-- Ugh.
[phone ringing]
-There's no answer.
No matter how many times
I try to get through,
no one picks up.
-I've been checking out
a few Chinese websites.
It looks like the story
is true after all.
-I saw Akira this morning, but
he didn't mention anything.
Maybe even he doesn't
know about it yet.
-I just thought--
if Toya Sensei's
going to be playing for
Beijing from now on, that
means he's going
to have to travel
to China on a regular basis.
We'll need to get the
results from there.
I wonder how many games
he'll play each year?
I'd better check it out.
-"Go Weekly" is gonna have to
follow him and report on his
progress.
Things are gonna get busy
around here, right, Mr. Amano?
-Hm.
-Mr. Amano?
-Yoshikawa?
-Yes, sir?
-I get a sense that there's a
momentous change on the way,
don't you?
Something's about to
happen in the world of Go.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Toya.
I want to play you
as soon as possible.
I'm ready to face you.
[theme music]
HIKARU: What's gonna happen when
Toya and I finally come face
to face?
It's time to find out if
I've caught up to him.
We've had lots of time
to prepare for this game.
But without Sai around, I
could use some extra help,
even from Akari.
Next time, Shindou Versus Toya!