[theme music]
-Hello, everyone.
Good to see you again.
Forgotten me already?
I'm Sai!
Today, we have a fantastic
bonus episode of "Hikaru No Go"
especially for you.
We're going to
travel back in time
and see Hikaru when he
was in seventh grade.
I know you're going to
enjoy watching this one.
What?
Will I be in it?
Of course I'll be in.
I'll be looking better than
ever because, after all, I
am the star.
Isn't that right?
I'm off now.
Hope you enjoy the show!
-It's not fair.
That teacher is
always picking on me.
-Hm.
Let me see.
Could that have something
to do with the fact
that you fell
asleep in his class?
-You did too.
I'm supposed to be at the
Go club meeting right now,
but Tane's beat me
three times in a row,
so maybe I should
just skip it today.
-What?
You can't do that, Hikaru.
You told me you were
going to train extra hard
since Kaio beat your team three
to zero in the last school
tournament.
You have to go.
They're all waiting for you!
Tsutsui, Akari.
You can't let them down.
-Hmph.
Ah.
-Sorry about that.
-Don't apologize.
It's his own fault for
not paying attention.
-What do you mean it's my fault?
Don't blame me if you can't
hit the ball properly.
You guys are so useless.
I'm in the Go club
and I bet you I
can hit a lot better than you.
-Oh, is that so?
See if you can hit
this one, then.
-OK.
Get ready, 'cause it's gonna
go right over the fence.
-Oh, this looks like fun.
What are you going to do
with that big stick, Hikaru?
-Are you ready?
This is how we pitch
the ball on this team!
-Look!
He's throwing the
ball straight at us.
That was amazing.
The ball landed straight
in that man's glove.
-Take you by surprise?
Go club doesn't belong here.
-Oh yeah?
Sai, get out of the way.
That was just strike one.
Come on.
All right!
-Hey, what kind
of throw was that?
-It looks like
it's gonna be foul.
[crashing]
-Uh oh.
-It's Kaga.
-He's not the sort
of guy you mess with.
-Oh man.
-You go.
-Yeah.
It's your fault.
Move it.
-Kaga.
How are you?
-You're the one
who hit the ball?
You got any idea of
what you've done?
Well?
HIKARU: Whoa.
Sorry, it's a bit of
a mess in here, huh?
Did I break all the trophies.
-I don't care
about the trophies.
What I care about is right here!
-That's just an ordinary teacup.
What's so special about it?
-This is not just any teacup!
This is my favorite
teacup, loser!
-OK, I hear you.
I'll buy you a new one tomorrow.
-And don't bring me junk,
or you're gonna regret it.
-Oh boy.
How on Earth am I supposed
to know what kind of teacup
Kaga wants?
And I've only got 200 yen left
of my allowance to spend on it.
-Hm?
Look Hikaru!
There's one!
-Where? Let me see.
It's OK.
What?
5,000 yen?
No way.
I can't afford that.
We gotta look somewhere else.
MAN: This is a
Keicho flower bowl?
-A Keicho flower bowl?
-Sai?
-Back in the early Edo
period of the Keicho era,
there was a famous
ceramic artist
by the name of San Gai Yaimon.
-Yes, yes.
I've heard of him.
-Oh.
What else do you know?
-Well, I know that flower bowls
were one of his specialties.
Isn't that why the
bowls made by Yaimon
are called Keicho flower bowls?
-My, my.
You seem to be well informed.
-Hey, uh, Sai.
-This is quite a rare find.
It's a charming piece
of superior quality.
MAN: You have a good eye, sir.
MAN: No, not really.
-Sai, what's wrong?
-These don't come on
the market very often.
Are you interested?
-Hikaru.
That bowl he has is fake.
-Huh?
-Yaimon's flower
bowls were something
that Torajiro was very
knowledgeable about.
As a result, I became fairly
familiar with them too,
and this isn't one of them.
It lacks the brilliant
indigo color.
The glaze is poorly applied.
Even the shape doesn't
have Yaimon's elegance.
-I'll give you a deal.
1 and 1/2 million yen.
-1 and 1/2 million?
-That much for a fake?
-What?
-Uh, here.
Let me have a closer look at it.
-No. No, no.
Keep your hands off.
It wasn't me!
I didn't do it!
I'm not responsible!
-First Kaga's tea
cup, and now this?
-What's next?
-All breakages must be paid
for, even if you're a kid.
1.5 million!
-Hikaru, quick!
Tell him about the bowl.
-This bowl, it's not a
Keicho flower bowl at all.
It's a fake.
-Ha!
OK then, expert in
antique flower bowls.
Tell me why you think
it's not genuine.
-Well, it's because,
it's like, uh--
-The color isn't the brilliant
indigo typical of the period.
And the glaze isn't
applied very well.
And if this was a
real Keicho bowl,
its shape would be
a lot more elegant.
-Well, well.
Aren't we the little expert?
Impressive.
-That smile makes him look
like a big, ugly bullfrog!
You don't know how
much I hate bullfrogs.
-Have I got this right?
-It's a fake and you wanted to
charge me 1 and 1/2 million?
-Oh, my mistake.
Sometimes when I see
a sucker, these things
just seem to slip out.
-A sucker?
A-- Are you referring to me?
-But I've got a lot
of time for people
who know what they're
talking about.
-Be careful of him, Hikaru.
He's dishonest and
can't be trusted.
-Only 'cause you made me
interfere in the first place.
-Do you want to know the
secret to this business?
You need to know your
stuff about antiques, sure,
but you also need to
know about people.
You see, there
are only two types
of customers in this world.
The ones who know what they're
talking about and the fools who
don't.
-Uh.
-Guess which category you're in?
[phone ringing]
-Listen, kid.
Because you've got
such a discerning eye,
I won't make you
pay for the bowl.
Hello?
Yes.
Yes, I remember you buying that.
Charming piece.
You had it valued at 1,000 yen.
Why are you telling me?
I didn't make you
pay 200,000 for it.
Is it my fault you
didn't do your research
before you bought it?
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
People who buy things without
knowing their real value
deserve what they get.
So hey, quit your complaining
and talk to somebody who cares.
-Hey, uh, don't go.
-This is grampa's special bowl!
-Hey, you!
Put that down.
You're not allowed to
touch the merchandise.
You can't afford it.
-But this is my grampa's!
It's his bowl.
Someone stole it from
him six months ago.
Give it back!
-That bowl.
-Sai?
-Hikaru.
I know that bowl.
-You sure this is the bowl that
was stolen from your grandpa?
-Yes.
It was his favorite.
-I don't know
anything about that.
All I know is someone offered
it to me, and I bought it.
-I remember seeing this
bowl in the castle in Kyoto.
Torajiro and I were visiting
the castle to teach Go.
Without a doubt.
This is the very same
Keicho flower bowl.
-So you mean it's
the real thing?
-Please, sir!
Please give it back!
-Hmph!
It's probably a piece
of junk, but I'm not
gonna let you have it for free.
-He thinks it's a piece of junk.
He hasn't got a clue.
-That flower bowl is special.
It hides a secret.
This man has no
idea what a treasure
he's holding in his hands.
-You want to give it
back to your grandpa?
Then buy it.
100,000.
-Uh, what's wrong, Sai?
-I told you how much
I hate bullfrogs.
Look at him.
-100,000?
Just a few moments ago you
said this was a piece of junk.
-You're in my store now.
And in my store, I
charge what I like.
If customers think
it's expensive,
they don't have to buy.
-Come on.
Be reasonable.
-That bowl is my grandpa's!
Give it back!
-Hey!
Hey!
Get off!
Let go!
-Careful!
-Are you all right?
-No, I'm not all right.
She smashed one of my tea cups.
And she's gonna pay for it!
-It's not her fault!
You're the one who
pushed her over.
It doesn't matter
about the teacup.
You should be checking on her.
-Don't seem scared of
him now that he's not
smiling like a bullfrog.
-Did he hurt you at all?
-I'm fine, sir.
-This teacup is
worth 50,000 yen.
Pay up!
-Why should we believe you?
You've lied about everything
else in the store so far.
-What do you think, Sai?
-Why are you asking me?
I don't know anything
about tea cups.
Hikaru!
Look over there!
HIKARU: Where?
SAI: There.
A Go board.
It appears the owner of
this place likes to play.
HIKARU: Yeah?
So?
-Time for you to
pay up, young lady.
Or I'll call the cops.
50,000.
Hand over the money.
Come on.
Well, if you haven't
got the money,
then maybe it's time to
talk to your mom and dad.
What's your phone number?
HIKARU: Hey, mister.
-Huh?
-You play Go, don'tcha?
Want to play me?
-What?
Why do you want to play
Go all of a sudden?
-Well, I figure we could play
for the cost of the teacup?
-Wait.
Hold on, there.
What do you think you're doing?
-I'm beginning to like you, kid.
All right, then.
We'll decide this
over a game of Go.
-Sai?
Are you sure you can play
when you're like this?
-Did you see that
hanging on the wall?
This guy's got a
Five Dan certificate.
There's no way you
can beat him at Go.
-And that certificate
is no fake, either.
It's 100% genuine.
-You know what?
Maybe this isn't a good idea.
Are you OK, Sai?
-If you're too scared to
play, that's fine by me, kid.
We can forget the game.
-Too scared to play?
Who does he think he is?
-But if you do play, I'm not
going to take it easy on you.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
I don't know why
I said I like you.
You're an arrogant
little smart-alec!
-Hikaru.
-All right, then.
Let's play.
Sai, are you sure
you can do this?
What if he smiles
like he did before?
-Don't worry.
He won't be smiling when
I'm finished with him.
MAN: So I'll be going first.
Heh, heh.
It's been quite a while
since I played black.
So, what are we waiting for?
Let's get the game started.
-Hikaru, are you ready for this?
-Yeah.
-Upper right.
3, 4 point.
Go.
Next, 18, 5.
Hane.
8, 18.
The tiger's mouth.
Now, 2, 17.
Push in.
-(VOICEOVER) How can
this kid be so strong?
-What's wrong?
-This game's so one sided.
He's not giving him a chance.
I don't play much Go
myself, but even a beginner
like me could see
how good he is.
This kid is a much
stronger player.
[groan]
-I resign.
-Hm?
-Wow.
This kid's amazing!
-I don't believe it.
Beaten by a kid.
-Hm.
What a coincidence.
The same flower bowl I
saw all those years ago,
and here it is in
a place like this.
I've heard the palace
was running out
of money at the time.
Perhaps the bowl
was secretly sold
by someone in the royal court.
Yaimon's flower bowl
was so beautiful
that it distracted Torajiro
and I from playing Go.
We couldn't help but look at it.
Hikaru, you want to know the
secret of the flower bowl?
-What?
Hey, mister.
-Huh?
-Pass your Go stones
over this way.
-You want my stones?
What are you going to do?
-And the captured stones, too.
We'll continue the
game from where
we left off, only
we switch sides.
If I can turn this
game around and manage
to win while I'm
playing black, will you
promise to give back the
flower bowl to the girl?
-Huh?
What's that?
You want to try and
win with my stones
after I've already conceded?
That's impossible!
It can't be done!
You sure are one arrogant kid!
I'd like to see you try.
-That was a great idea.
Let's do it.
-Here we go.
-16, 2.
The knight's move.
Next, 3, 9.
Cut.
-(VOICEOVER) No way!
This is impossible.
-Deal's a deal.
Give her the flower bowl.
-You mean it?
He's gonna give it back to me?
-Where'd you learn
to play like that?
-Darn it all!
Take the flower bowl
and get out of here.
-But first, pour some of
the water from that vase
into the flower bowl.
-OK.
This one?
-What do you think
you're doing now?
-Why are you filling
it with water?
Grandpa never actually
used it for anything.
He just had it out for show.
He promised to give it to me
as a wedding present one day.
-(VOICEOVER) Seeing this flower
bowl again brings back happy memories.
Like me, this bowl has survived
through the generations,
experienced the passage of time.
-Look! an you see that?
-Wow.
-Oh!
MAN: How'd those flowers
start appearing in the bowl?
-So pretty.
-It can only be a flower bowl
when there are flowers in it.
People say it was Yaimon's
final masterpiece.
It looks different from
his other pieces because
of the special
glaze which changes
when it comes into
contact with water.
-But that's one of his
most famous pieces.
And you're saying that
this is it, right here?
Oh!
It's mine! All mine!
-No!
-Not so fast, mister.
Earlier, you said there
are only two types
of people in the world.
Those who know what they're
talking about and the fools who
don't.
And guess which
category you fall into.
Hand it over.
[sobbing]
-Thank you!
-You're welcome.
See you!
Case closed.
That was awesome.
SAI: Hikaru.
HIKARU: Huh?
SAI: I think we
forgot something.
HIKARU: Yeah?
Ah!
Kaga's tea cup!
KAGA: For real?
-Yep.
It's known as a Keicho teacup.
A masterpiece of the
early Edo period.
Not only that,
but the design was
painted by Songa Yaimon,
one of the finest
ceramic artists of his time.
-Oh, yeah.
And it's genuine?
-Yeah.
You can tell by
the elegant shape
and quality of the design.
Pieces like this
are hard to find.
-Huh.
How dare you mess with me!
[theme music]
HIKARU: I haven't been
playing Go for a while,
but then I run into Waya.
He wants me to start up again
and join the study sessions.
I also find out that Isumi's
gone to play in China.
He's gonna challenge some of
China's best young players.
One of them even
looks a lot like Waya.
Isumi better do
well on this trip.
If he doesn't, he could
lose the confidence
he needs to pass
the next pro exam.
Next time, Isumi No Go!