[theme music]
-It's raining?
[excited whispering]
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): Waya won.
If Shindou loses, then I get
one final chance in a playoff.
[excited whispering]
-I think they're done!
HIKARU: Isumi quit
the study group?
-And that's not all.
He also quit being an Insei too.
Usually everyone who
graduates the program
stays around until
the end of March.
-How could he quit
his study group?
He's been going there forever.
He can't just give it up!
And if he's not going to
the Insei classes either,
then what's he
gonna end up doing?
Waya, did you try
talking to him?
-I couldn't?
I thought calling him would
be kind of awkward, you know?
I knew I should
say something, so I
tried to catch him at one
of the Insei sessions.
When I got there, I
couldn't see him anywhere,
and that's when Shinoda-sensei
told me Isumi had quit.
-Well, does he know why?
-What did he say?
He seemed to think it wasn't
such a bad idea for Isumi
to quit.
-Well, how come?
-Here.
Areful, it's hot.
-Sure.
Thanks a lot.
-Everyone has to deal
with it their own way.
In Isumi's case, he just
needs a bit of time and space
to figure out where he stands.
-Ah huh.
-Just because he's not playing
with other people right now
doesn't mean that
he can't continue
to study the game in other ways.
For a player at
his level, there's
a lot he can learn by
replaying and analyzing matches
from the past.
And it's important
to realize when
you should take some time off.
-That's what he thinks.
I don't know if it
makes any sense, though.
-Sounds like Sensei's
just making excuses.
I wonder if Isumi's really gonna
give up trying to become a pro.
WAYA: Sensei did say he
was pretty sure Isumi would
be taking the pro
exam again next year.
-Really?
-Yeah.
And he was totally serious.
He told me his future as a
Go player isn't in doubt,
and he's going to be playing
the game for a very long time.
-Don't worry about Isumi.
He can take care of himself.
Focus on doing the best
you can in your own game.
You're a pro now, after all.
-That was pretty much it.
-And you're a pro as well.
-Mhmm.
-So, anyway.
If you're interested, I
thought I could teach you
how to be a recorder today.
-What, like recording matches?
-Yeah.
As new pros, we might
get called in to do it,
although they don't often ask
kids who are still in school.
All pro matches are
officially recorded
from the third
qualifying round on.
-But I already know how
to keep a game record.
-It's different for the pros.
Look.
Here's an example.
-Whoa, what's all this?
You've got to record the time
they took for each move as well
as the total time for the game.
-Hikaru, are you
sure you're up to it?
-Then they also
need a time keeper.
-Waya.
You know how to do all this?
-Yeah, of course.
-How does someone like
you know about it, huh?
-What are you saying?
-Was this the only reason
you wanted to meet up today?
-I'm doing this as a
favor to help you out!
Do you understand me?
-But I--
-Do you want me help or not?
-OK, OK.
-Hikaru's on his way.
He's finally stepped into
the world of the pros.
-I thought being a pro was all
about playing lots of matches.
-When do you think I'll
get to play Toya, huh?
Any idea, Waya?
-No!
-But I'll get to play lots
of different people, right?
Like you or Mr. Saeki?
Or maybe even someone
like Toya Meijin.
-Yes.
What about him?
Do you really think we'll
get a chance to play him?
-Listen, Shindou.
It's gonna be at least five
years before you get anywhere
near people like that.
-But what if I keep
winning and winning?
Don't I get to play them then?
-Well, Waya?
-Well, of course if
you keep winning,
you're gonna reach
the top eventually.
But get a reality check.
Any player lower
than a Four-Dan never
gets past the second round.
-But now we're pros.
We've got a connection.
Me and Toya, me
and Toya's father!
-Yes, yes!
-We're all a part of
the same world now,
and one day I'll be
able to play them.
Me!
-Me?
-I wanna play Murakame Two-Dan
from the Young Lions Tournament
again.
And then there's Ogata
Nine-Dan, and that old guy
who's holding on to
the Honinbo title.
-Don't get carried away!
-Hikaru.
-But the one I want to play more
than anyone else is Akira Toya.
-What about me?
-At least he's a
lower ranked pro,
so you might actually have
a chance of playing him.
But we don't get to choose
any of our opponents.
-It's done by a draw?
-Where do I fit in?
-Hey!
I'll get to go head
to head in matches
against Shirakawa-sensei
and Morishita-sensei.
-You don't listen, do you?
The high Dan players are
way off in the future.
-But we're all connected, right?
Which means I'll get
to play them one day!
From now on, I'm living
in the world of the pros.
-He's right.
I'm not the one
connected to that world.
It's Hikaru.
It's him, and him alone.
What will happen if he
doesn't let me play anymore?
-All right, all right.
You've made your point.
-I bet you I'll get to the
level of Two-Dan before you.
-(VOICEOVER) I've got 10
minutes before the match starts.
Hm?
-Good morning, to
you, Zama Sensei.
-And a good morning to you, too.
You know, I don't think
I ever congratulated you
on winning your sixth
Meijin title in a row.
Allow me to offer my
congratulations now.
-Why, thank you.
-It's a shame you
let the opportunity
to challenge the Kisei title
slip through your fingers.
Perhaps you wore
yourself out by playing
too many matches, Toya-sensei.
-It's entirely possible
fatigue played a small part
in losing that final match.
But even if I didn't add the
Kisei title to my collection,
I can assure you, I'm
in very good shape,
mentally and physically,
for today's match.
-And what about your son?
I hear he's also
in very good shape.
He's managed to stay undefeated?
-Yes, He's currently
at 20 straight wins.
-Oh really?
-His last defeat was in
the Shincho Dan series
just before he
turned professional.
That was against you.
I'm sure you remember
the match well.
-So today is your
opportunity for revenge
on behald of your son.
-Please, after you, Zama Osa.
I insist.
KUWABARA: Ah!
-What is it, Kuwabara-sensei?
Something interesting
in the paper?
-I was just looking at the
results of the pro exam.
-Why are you looking at that?
KUWABARA: I see that
kid managed to pass.
So, his name is Shindou.
-I don't know him.
Who is he?
-He's just a kid I passed
in the hall a while ago.
-So, you don't really
know him, then?
-Well, it was right over there.
Let's see, about six months ago.
I was coming out
of the elevator,
and I saw a group
of kids standing
around who looked
like they were Insei.
[gasping]
KUWABARA: As I
walked past that boy,
I sensed there was something
extraordinary about him.
-That's quite a first
impression you had.
So you think the
kid shows promise?
-Yes.
Very promising.
He might be part of the new wave
that Ogata once talked about.
The new wave sweeping
across the country.
Very promising, indeed.
HIKARU: I can't
wait to get started!
The spring.
It all starts in the spring.
I wonder who's going to
be my first opponent?
Any ideas, Sai?
Huh?
Sai?
What's the matter?
Come on, let's play.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Just as Hikaru is
anxious to start
playing other pros,
they're also anxious
awaiting his arrival.
They're not waiting for me.
They're waiting for Hikaru.
Hikaru.
Hikaru is the one.
KAWAI: You only came to see us
now to tell us you turned pro?
We've known about
that forever already.
-That hurts!
-How come you took so
long to come and tell us?
Don't forget it's
all thanks to me
you were able to turn
pro in the first place.
-What do you mean,
it's all thanks to you?
That's crazy!
-Why, you ungrateful--
-What's this?
-I can't believe a kid his
age passed the pro exam.
-I guess you never Shindou,
do you, Mr. Tarouchi?
He was playing here every
day during the summer break.
-You're not the only
person I played, Mr. Kawai.
-What was that?
-All the resultts
from the pro exam
were published in Go
Weekly a while back.
Here, it's all in
that article there.
-Ah.
So this kid is Hikaru Shindou.
-Make sure you remember
me when you win a title.
I want you to say, I got where
I am today because of Mr. Kawai!
-I'll never say that!
-Yeah, win a title for us.
Better yet, win four,
like Toya Meijin.
-Oh, no.
He's going to be the
holder of five titles soon.
-What's that?
Toya Meijin's got five?
-He will if he
wins the Oza title.
-He won both the first
match and the second match,
so his chances are
looking pretty good.
Zama Oza seems to be struggling.
-Really?
And how many wins do you
need to become the Oza?
-The Oza championship is
the best of five matches.
You win three, and
you get the title.
-Remember, he's defending his
Tengen title at the same time.
It can't be easy
for him right now.
-Tengen?
Is that another
championship title?
[confused chatter]
-How's this kid ever going
to win a serious title
if he doesn't even
know the names
of the major championships?
-Makes you wonder if he's really
got what it takes to be a pro.
-Yow!
I don't want you
embarrassing me, do you hear?
-Would you get off of me?
This has got nothing to
do with you, Mr. Kawai!
-What's that?
-All right, you
two, that's enough.
If you're interested,
you can read these old Go
Weeklys I've been collecting.
-Thanks, Mr. Fukawa.
-Oh, look.
There's Toya's dad
on the front cover.
It says he's competing
for the Oza title.
And here's the game record.
He's playing Zama Sensei.
Wow.
I never knew he was the Oza.
-Hikaru, this is only
part of the game record.
-Huh?
Let's see.
Here it is.
The rest of it's on the back.
There's another
match in this one.
The first game of the
Tengen championship.
Defending the championship
is last year's winner,
Toya Meijin.
Challenging him for the
title is Achiryu Kise.
Hm.
Oh.
Toya's dad's also in this one.
-Hikaru-- turn the page.
Turn it!
-Hmph.
Hm.
Now, let's see.
Toya Meijin.
Six straight wins?
Wow.
He's doing pretty well.
-How can I read
this article if you
keep putting things
on top of it?
-Better for ya?
Now, let's see.
What else do we have here?
I wish these were in
some sort of order.
The dates are all mixed up.
There's August, and
then there's May.
What's this one right at
the bottom of the pile?
Last January?
So out of date.
Huh?
It's Akira.
And that guy he's standing
next to is Zama Sensei.
I know what this is!
It's the Shincho Dan series.
-Hikaru, turn the page.
-We were there for that match.
Do you remember?
We watched it on TV
in the next room.
Ah, the Shincho Dan series.
So cool.
I'd forgotten I get
to play in that.
Wow.
I can't wait for
my first pro match.
What about you?
-Hikaru, spread this
paper out, would you?
-Yeah, the Shincho Dan series.
It snowed that day.
Huh?
The snow had just started.
This time it's my turn.
This match is going
to be the start
of my professional career.
Just as soon as
the new year comes.
AMANO: We really
appreciate you giving us
the time for this interview
so early in the year.
As the holder of five titles,
you must be busier than ever.
And also, there's your son's
achievement this past year.
We were all sorry when your
winning streak ended at 26
matches, but I'm
sure we can expect
even greater things
from you this year.
-I'll try my best.
-Hm.
-Well, I think we've managed
to get everything we need.
Thanks.
-Mr. Amano.
Yes?
-You know that event where
one of the top professionals
plays someone who's
just starting out?
-The Shincho Dan series?
You mean you'd take part?
The last couple of
times we asked you,
you turned us down because
you had such a busy schedule,
so we didn't really want to
bother you again this here.
But if you're interested,
we'd be delighted to have you.
-I'll do it on the condition
I get to choose my opponent.
-Huh?
-Oh.
Um, did you already have
somebody particular in mind?
-There's a player I haven't
seen for nearly two years,
but he's become a pro now.
-It can't be.
-Hikaru Shindou.
[gasp]
-I see.
That means by moving there,
my counterattack is blocked.
Hm?
Hey, what's up, Sai?
That look in your
eye's kind of scary.
You know what?
We should tidy up these papers.
You know how my mom gets
when she sees a mess.
She'll yell at me if she
sees my room like this.
I know you need them
spread out to read them,
but, uh, you don't want to
see me get in trouble, do ya?
-Go ahead.
You can put them away.
I've memorized all the
game records I need.
I know his game much better now.
[phone ringing]
-Huh?
I'd better get it.
Mom's out shopping somewhere.
Hello.
Shindou residence.
Yeah, what do you want?
I mean, yes, it's me.
The Shincho Dan series?
Yeah, I've heard of it.
Why?
Really?
And who would I play against?
Toya Meijin?
Yes.
Yes, of course.
Yes, I understand.
Did you hear that?
They want me to play against
Toya Meijin in the next Shincho
Dan series.
Remember last year?
Toya was playing Zama Osa?
Hey, I wonder-- Do you think
he's gonna come watch it?
Yeah, 'course he'll be there.
OK.
This is my chance to
show him how strong I am!
To show him I'm his equal.
-Hikaru.
-Yeah, what is it?
Please.
Allow me to play for you.
I want to play that man.
Let me play!
[theme music]
-This is gonna be my match, Sai,
and I can't let you interfere.
-Please I must play!
Stop being so selfish!
-This one that could be
my greatest challenge.
HIKARU: But everyone is
coming to see me play.
Waya, Ochi.
And one top player
thinks I'm gonna win.
Next time, Sai versus Meijin.
SAI: He's waiting for us.