[music playing]
NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past, known as
Fujiwara-no-Sai, has returned.
Visible only to Hikaru
Shindou, a master of Go,
Sai seeks to play
the Divine Move.
[theme music]
-I don't know.
What if he cheats
during a tournament?
-Huh.
-If he can do this kind of stuff
to adults in some Go salon,
what's going to stop him from
doing it to kids his own age?
He'd have no trouble
getting away with it.
I doubt anyone would even
notice, but I'd know and so
would you.
Do you think he could
play on a team like that?
I don't think I could cheat.
It's just not right.
-I hope that you've
got some kind of plan.
How are we going to stop him?
-I'm not quite sure.
We'll have to figure
that out as it goes.
I just hope that we
can get there on time.
-Hey, Mitani.
-I hope you brought your
money with you, kid.
After I win this young
man's 10,000 yen,
I'll gladly play you a game.
-10,000 yen?
SHU: You were here yesterday.
You going to play today?
-Nope, I'm just going to watch.
DAKE: Then close that
door and pull up a seat.
I can't concentrate with all
that racket going on outside.
-Sure.
Sorry
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Looks like they're still
in the middle of their game.
-I would really like to know
what's wrong with kids today.
Do an old man a favor, will you?
Tell your friend here
that he's supposed
to show a bit more
respect for his elders.
HIKARU: Huh?
DAKE: Your buddy isn't
pulling any punches.
He's a real aggressive player.
-I'd like to know what you
think you're doing here.
-I'm just a big Go fan, I guess.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Sai, look at the board.
Yuki's winning, isn't he?
Maybe he won't have
to cheat after all.
-I know your reason
for coming here,
but you're wasting your time.
-You've got it all wrong.
--[laugh] What are you
two talking about?
-How'd Yuki cheat anyhow?
Hikaru mentioned
that it had something
to do with how he
counted up his territory.
-I'll show you.
At the end of the game, the
player with the most territory
wins.
-Hm.
-OK.
Here's an example.
See this black shape?
Count up the intersections
inside it, OK.
-No problem.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine,
10, 11, 12.
KIMIHIRO: This territory
contains 12 intersections.
So it's worth 12 points.
At the end of the game, most of
the shapes look like this one.
Players rearrange their
stones into neater formations,
so they'll be easier to count.
As long as you only
move the stones which
are inside your own shapes,
the size of your territory
won't increase or decrease.
Then you can multiply
the width by the height
and figure out your score.
See?
Three times four
equals 12 points.
AKARI: Hey.
I think I get it now.
So he cheats by increasing
his own territory,
while decreasing his
opponents, right?
-That's absolutely right.
-Is it really that easy?
Won't someone notice?
-Huh.
I know that it's
hard to believe,
but it really is that simple.
Even with my slow clumsy hands
I doubt anyone would notice.
At the end of the
game, both players
are paying so much attention
to rearranging their stones
that they hardly ever notice
what their opponent's doing.
Players automatically
assume that no one
will do anything dishonest.
Go is about trust.
Cheating on a count
is the worst thing.
It goes against
everything a player is
supposed to stand for.
It's unforgivable.
Cheaters ruin the whole game.
-Oh.
Why would Hikaru want someone
like that to join the team?
MITANI (VOICEOVER): Why did
this guy want to bet 10,000 yen?
He's terrible.
He was probably
just showing off.
Well, his pride is going to wind
up costing him a lot of money.
-Young man, you think you've
already won, don't you?
Well, have ever heard
of an old saying that
goes, "it ain't
over til it's over"?
How about don't
count your chickens
before they've hatched?
You know that one, right?
-Yeah.
-Ha.
Think that's funny.
[laughing] You really shouldn't
laugh until after you've won,
and this game is far from over.
-Huh.
-Thanks for the advice.
-I know.
You're a pretty good listener.
You've got a bright
future ahead of you.
It's nice to meet such
a smart young player.
Excuse me, son.
Do you see that
ashtray over there.
Grab it.
Thanks a lot.
-Are you left-handed?
-Huh.
-You're pretty
sharp, you know that?
I'm very impressed.
-What's going on here?
-I suppose that the
fun and games are over.
You're about to learn
how grownups play Go.
Luckily for you, your tuition is
only going to cost 10,000 yen.
Why so quiet, hot shot?
You probably think some
clumsy old man can't catch up
this late in the game.
Well, you're wrong.
Play time's officially over.
-Sai?
MITANI (VOICEOVER): You jerk.
-Ha.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
That guy's playing
a completely different game now.
--[laughing] I'm
catching up, aren't I?
[grunt]
-That's five points for me.
10 points.
15 points.
-That man is cheating.
-What should we do, Sai?
DAKE: If I keep this up, you're
going to lose a lot of money
today.
-Huh?
What?
A stone's been moved.
When did that happen?
-Is something wrong
with you, son?
You look pale.
There's quite a bit of
cash riding on this game.
You should start paying
attention to what you're doing.
-Mitani?
-That's a very good move.
You don't give up
easily, do you?
I didn't expect you
to last this long.
[laughing]
[go pieces rattling]
MITANI (VOICEOVER):
This pointless.
He's a stronger player than
I am, and he's moving stones.
Oh, I'm going to lose.
And there's nothing
I can do about it.
-Game over, son.
Have you figured out who won?
I'll give you a hint.
It ain't going to be you unless
you cheat on the final count.
You're too slow.
Hurry it up.
MITANI (VOICEOVER): No way.
He's using my own
trick against me.
-Let's see, including the Komi,
I win by 12 and a half points.
That will be 10,000 yen.
Cheer up.
At least, you played
a clean honest game.
[sighing]
-You played well.
-Take it.
DAKE: Let me count that.
Five, six, seven,
eight, plus the change.
You're still 20 yen short.
Cough it up.
-Don't worry about it.
I'll loan you the money.
-Hey, Shu.
Can I borrow 20 yen?
I'll pay you back
first thing tomorrow.
-Please take it.
-Thanks a lot.
-Hey, kiddo.
Think you'll stop cheating now?
When you rip off
customers, they call me.
-Dake.
-I think I'd like to borrow
that 20 yen after all.
-Thank you.
-Wait a sec.
-What's your rush?
-Yuki.
-Get away from me.
-Watch it.
-What?
Are they running a daycare
down here or something?
-Where are you?
-Relax, Hikaru.
This is likely the best thing
that could have happened.
It's good medicine.
A cheater must feel the
pain of their own sting
before they can fully
realize the agony
that they inflict on others.
However--
-Sai, it was a trap.
Yuki was set up.
When his game
started, that old guy
pretended that he
barely knew how to play.
Remember?
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: I do.
Deceiving a child is a
cruel and a despicable act.
-Mitani learned his lesson.
And I know that's
important, but I
don't think it should
cost him 10,000 yen.
We should win that
money back for him.
Come on.
-I cannot sit idly by and allow
this sort of thing to happen.
We must teach this man a lesson.
He will not go unpunished.
-Hey, what do you think?
Who would you say is
the greatest Go player
in the world, living or dead?
-Hm.
Toya Meijin.
There's a couple of
younger players who
are pretty good like Kurata
4-dan or Ogata 9-dan.
GO PLAYER : I just read an
article where a reporter asked
a pro player that same question.
-Oh really.
GO PLAYER : You know
what the pro said?
Honinbo Shusaku
from the Edo period.
Can you believe that?
I nearly fell off my chair.
-Huh.
Go was much simpler back then.
They wouldn't stand a
chance playing today's game.
-Tomorrow, we'll give Yuki
back all of his money.
Then, I'll ask him to
join the Go club again.
Sai, are you sure
you can beat him?
He seemed like he was
a pretty strong player.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: I
saw his skill level.
He will lose.
-What if he tries to
move a stone again?
-I'll notice it immediately.
Then you can tell him that
you witnessed his deception
and challenge him to beat
you without resorting
to such dishonesty.
HIKARU: What if he
lies about his score?
-He won't get a chance
to count his territory.
I will force him to resign.
-That boy wasn't
always so mischievous.
He only began cheating recently.
Nobody seemed to
mind losing to him.
It was like giving money
to your own grandson,
but I couldn't allow
him to continue.
That's why I called you in.
It was too late to tell Yuki
that I knew what he was up to.
I figured it would have
upset him too much.
I guess I wound up upsetting
him any how, didn't I?
-You did what you had to do.
So did I. There's no
point in feeling guilty.
[laughing] My usual fee
is 20,000 plus the 10,000
that I gave you earlier.
For a grand total of
30,000 yen, my friend.
-I doubt that Yuki will ever
want to set foot in this place
again.
It's really too bad.
I'm going to miss
having that kid around.
-Huh.
It's a pleasure doing
business with you.
Now, I think I'll
hang out here and see
if another sucker comes in.
-Your work here is done.
Why don't you head on
home and leave me alone?
I think I've had
enough for today.
-That's cold.
I came down here
to do you a favor.
-Hey, mister.
I'm a friend of Yuki's.
I want a game.
[laugh]
-If beat you, I want
the 10,000 yen back
you took from my friend.
-No problem.
But if I win, you're going
to have to pay me 10,000 yen.
So do we have a deal or what?
-You will not lose.
-If you won't agree to
my terms, the bet is off.
Gambling is always a risk, son.
Don't you forget it.
SHU: That's enough, Dake.
Listen, kid.
Just go home.
You're too young to make
that kind of a wager.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI:
Don't listen to them.
I will defeat this man.
Hikaru.
HIKARU: Fine.
If I lose, I'll
pay you 10,000 yen.
DAKE: Now we're talking.
Grab a chair, and let's
get down to business.
SHU: Stop this.
-Let's set a handicap.
All right.
-Don't bother.
I'm not going to need one.
-Are you sure about that?
-Young fool.
He's nuts.
Kids these days have
lost their minds.
M
-Aren't you confident?
Now, you already know that
I'm a pretty strong player.
Maybe you wouldn't mind telling
me just how good you are.
-I'm not quite sure.
Uh, well, I'm probably about
as good as Honinbo Shusaku.
--[laughing] You're
a really funny guy.
Keep those jokes coming.
Shusaku, that's priceless.
-The only person who'd have
any hope of beating Shusaku
would be Toya Meijin.
That'd be a great
match to watch.
-Pass me those blacks stones.
I'll play using my left
hand out of respect
for the great Shusaku.
Shall we begin, Honinbo?
-3-4 in the upper left.
17-5.
6-17.
COMMENTATOR (ON TV): The
catcher signals the pitcher.
The batter glances
toward the dugout.
We're still waiting
for that next pitch.
-Hm.
COMMENTATOR (ON
TV): Strike three.
COMMENTATOR 2 (ON TV):
Hey, after those first two
fast balls, there was no way
he could have hit that pitch.
COMMENTATOR (ON
TV): Foul ball's up.
It's heading for the outfield.
That's going to be an easy out.
These hitters are
having a tough day.
So far it's shaping up
to be a pretty slow game.
-Hm?
[chair scraping]
-Hm.
[sigh] That didn't take long.
Do me a favor, and don't play
any more kids in here, OK?
He's a child.
I don't understand how you
can take his money like that.
I suppose that he
brought this on himself.
He must have been out of
his mind to challenge you.
Listen, you can finish
your tea, but after that, I
want you to leave.
Now, let me have a look to see
how well the boy managed to do.
[groaning]
-What's with you?
-Hm.
What happened?
DAKE: He was as good
as-- as Honinbo Shusaku.
COMMENTATOR (ON
TV): There it goes.
Oh, and it's a grand slam.
What an absolutely
incredible hit.
Nobody could have
seen that coming.
-Once I give Yuki
his money, he'll
be sure to join the Go club.
We'll finally have
three members.
Then we'll be able to compete
in the upcoming tournament.
We did it, Sai!
[theme music]
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: The tournament
is only a short time away.
Your training is
progressing well.
HIKARU: I just hope our
team sticks together.
We've got to win this year.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: Akira
will be a strong opponent.
Every day his knowledge
of the game increases.
HIKARU: All he cares
about is having
another rematch against me.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: Next
time, no cheating allowed.
HIKARU: All I care
about is beating Kaio.