[theme music]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Toya.
You and I have to
play each other.
I know that you've always
wanted to play against Sai,
but he isn't here anymore.
Except he is in my game.
He's in every one of my moves.
But I can't expect you
to understand that.
I'll make myself strong
enough to beat you.
I'm gonna play at
your level now.
Oh, hey Toya.
We finally get to
play each other again.
-The last time the
two of us played
was in a school Go
club tournament.
Two years and four months ago.
-It's been a long
time since then.
-I know.
It's been too long.
-Now it's your chance to
see how strong I've become.
If he counters with an approach,
I'll use a pincer attack.
Then I'll spread
across the board
ready for an all out battle.
Here I am, playing him at last.
It's our first game since
the Go club tournament.
No, Sai actually played the
first half of that game.
Toya.
This is it.
Our first real match
against each other.
He's made a pincer move.
It's time for me
to break through.
So that's how he's
gonna play it.
Even if I can squeeze him out,
once we get into a battle,
I'll be one move short.
I'll slide instead!
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): He's reading
the game all in one moment.
It feels like I'm up against
one of the top ranked players.
Huh?
Mr. Yun, are you sure?
This is one of Shindou's games.
It sure is.
I happened to be at the Go
salon when he was playing
and brought a copy out with me.
-From what I can see,
both black and white
are playing like pros.
But there's something
about white.
Shindou was the
one playing white.
Black was played by a Korean
Insei named Su-yeong Hong.
I wanted you to see
this game record.
-Hm?
-I know how truly
disappointed you
were when Shindou played
so poorly against you.
But now, he is a
much better player.
-Oh, hello.
This is Amano.
How's the pro exam going?
Mm-hm.
Ah.
-It's been decided?
All three of them?
You mean there's
not even a playoff?
So that must mean that
Waya's beaten Fuku,
and Shindou must've beaten Ochi.
-You're always setting your
sights on players above you.
Maybe you should
pay more attention
to who's coming up from below.
-From below?
-There's someone else
you should worry about,
and he's right behind you.
There are only two
young pros out there
who I feel threatened by.
You're one of them, and
the other's Hikaru Shindou.
I suggest you keep
an eye on him.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): I wanted to
find out how strong you were,
and now I know.
There's no doubt in my mind.
You're my rival.
Sai.
[phone ringing]
-Hello, publishing division?
Ah, thanks for getting
back to me so quick.
So, is everything in order?
Good, thanks a lot.
-Does anyone here know Korean?
I'm not sure how to
pronounce this kid's name.
Looks like the first part
of the character for flood.
Hong, perhaps?
-Do you mean the boy who
defeated [inaudible]?
I know his name.
It's Su-yeong Hond.
-Su-yeong Hond.
Age 14.
Seems Korea's produced yet
another young superstar.
-A player from Korea
just set a new record
for most consecutive wins.
A 16-year-old named Yong Ha Ko.
-It's amazing what the players
in Korea are accomplishing.
They have a lot of
young talent there.
-Hm.
Su-yeong Hong, Yong Ha Ko.
I wonder if they'll be on the
team that's coming from Korea.
-What team's that?
I haven't heard about it.
-Well, nothing's
been confirmed yet,
but there's talk of a new
junior cup tournament.
A big corporation
wants to sponsor it.
It'll be an
international competition
with teams from China,
Korea, and Japan.
And all the players
who are on the teams
have to be 18 years or under.
-A China, Korea,
Japan junior cup?
-Just 18 and under?
-We don't stand a chance.
Japan doesn't have any
players that age who
can compete against China and
Korea at that high a level.
-What about Akira Toya?
-Oh.
-Toya won't be enough.
We're gonna need
more than one player.
-Ochi's been doing well.
I'd choose him.
-Well, that's an idea.
Is he still undefeated?
-Yeah, I think so.
And I heard he's only 14.
That's pretty impressive
for a kid his age.
-I agree, but don't
you think Ochi
is a bit out of their league?
He'd have a tough time
competing against the Chinese
and the Koreans.
Nope, we've only got Toya.
AMANO: There's always Shindou.
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Shindou should be on the team.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Shindou.
Sai's shadow is here.
The shadow fades and reappears.
There's someone else within you.
All this time, that's
what I've been watching.
I've been watching that shadow.
MAN: Hikaru Shindou?
-Wha--
-Are you sure?
-Surely you can't
mean the same boy
who was skipping
all of his games?
-You really think
he's that good, Amano?
-Yes.
I believe he has a
lot of potential.
He'll be right at the
top with Akira Toya.
-What makes you so sure of that?
-Prominent players like
Koyo Toya, Kuwabara Honinbo,
and Ogata Judan have all been
keeping an eye on his progress.
They must be interested
in him for a reason.
-Ah.
Now you mention it, I
remember Toya-sensei
asked to have Shindou as his
opponent in the Shinsho Dan
Series.
-But he played
terribly in that game.
No sign of a strong
player there.
-Mm-hm, yes.
But you know what's interesting?
Kuwabara-sensei and the others
didn't lessen their opinion
of him because of how
he performed that day.
And ever since I found
out Toya considers Shindou
to be his rival,
I can understand
why they feel that way.
And if they've all got
high hopes for Shindou,
I can see no reason
to doubt them.
-You're kidding?
His rival?
-You know, that says a lot
about how good a player he is.
-Hm.
You know what?
I've heard that rumor too
about Kuwabara-sensei thinking
there's something
special about Shindou.
-You know, just the
other day I overheard
Kurata talking about him, too.
-Oh!
Shindou's playing
Toya this week.
That's a game I gotta see.
-From the way he
reacted, he obviously
thinks highly of Shindou.
-Really?
Is it just me, or is
everyone keeping an eye
on what this kid's doing?
-So, what's his game record like
since he started playing again?
-He's gone undefeated
for eight games now.
-Oh wow.
-I think this is great.
We need more youngsters like
him to give the higher ranked
players a run for their money.
-You know how the
older guys are.
They won't go down without
a fight, that's for sure.
-But Ogata-sensei's already
started the onslaught
by winning the Judan title.
And it won't be long before
Kurata makes his mark.
MAN: No, no.
Forget those two.
Young Toya's the one
to watch out for.
He's got champion
written all over him.
MAN: Wait a minute.
Isn't today the day Toya
and Shindou play each other?
-When I think about
the future, my heart
pounds with excitement.
-Eh?
-Ah?
-Huh?
-Mr. Amano?
-We all know of Akira Toya.
But there's also Shindou.
And Ochi.
And with Waya and the
others filling up the ranks,
there's bound to be a huge burst
of energy into the world of Go.
-That's right.
The power of youth.
The dawning of a new age.
-You bet.
And Toya will be
leading the way.
-And Hikaru Shindou could
have enough potential
to be as good a player as him.
-At last, Japan will be able
to compete with the world!
And we can make a comeback.
Right, Mr. Amano?
-This is great.
Think how many more copies
of Go Weekly we'll sell.
-We don't know
anything for sure.
We'll have to see
how things turn out.
That's enough dreaming for now.
All right.
Back to work!
[buzzer]
-I'm having a good game so far.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Wow.
They've been
playing really fast.
OCHI (VOICEOVER):
This is complicated.
They're attacking
all over the board.
SAEKI (VOICEOVER): It's
quite a battle going on,
but Shindou seems to be holding
his ground against Toya.
Good for you, Shindou.
-Hey, Saeki.
You want to join me for lunch?
Food tastes better with company.
That's what I always say.
I'd ask Akira, except
I know he doesn't
like to eat during a big game.
So come on.
-Uh-- uh, but I--
Mr. Ashiwara!
No, no--
-So much for us Morishita
students sticking together.
-Hm.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): We
stopped for the lunch break
just after Toya
played a shoulder hit.
It looks like he's gonna leave
the battle in the upper right,
and work on building
up the lower left.
When we start again,
I'll play a knight's move
and attack him where
his defense is thin.
Then Toya will to
connect, so I need
to make sure I stay
alive on the inside.
The lower left is too
small to help with that,
so the question is how can
I approach from the top?
I could be at a disadvantage
here No, it's still close.
We have a long way to go.
Oh!
Everyone's left for the break.
Toya, what are you
doing for lunch?
OK.
Well, I think I'm gonna head
out before we run out of time.
He's not even gonna eat?
-Sai.
-Hm?
-While we were
playing this morning,
I thought of Sai
from the internet.
-Toya.
I'm sorry I'm not
Sai, but I wish I was.
-It is you.
-What do you mean?
-He's a part of you.
There's another side to you.
Another player.
And the Hikaru Shindou I
played when we first met,
that was Sai.
-Toya.
Toya, listen, I--
-There's someone
else within you.
I can see him.
[theme music]
HIKARU: For years, no
one knew who Sai was.
I kept him a secret.
He could never be
connected to me.
Until now.
Has Toya really seen him?
I didn't think I'd
ever see him again,
but I'm going to
get one more chance.
Next time, A Nostalgic Smile.