NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past known as
Fujiwara-no-Sai has returned,
visible only to Hikaru
Shindo, a master of Go,
Sai seeks to play
the divine move.
[theme music]
-I want to enter the
Young Lions tournament.
I mean, I have to.
Otherwise, no one
will believe me
when I tell them I'm going
to defeat Akira Toya.
I have to enter that tournament
if it's the last thing I do.
I want to make sure
he knows I'm going
to catch up to him one day.
Loya!
-Oh.
Hey there, Shindo.
So what's up?
[chuckling]
-Hah.
I finally made it.
Look.
Starting today, I'm
in the A-league.
-Hm.
Big deal.
You're in last place.
-Come on.
Aren't you going to
congratulate him?
-Not until he passes me.
-Stop being so mean, Waya.
-You don't get it.
Now that I'm in
the A-league, I can
go for the Young
Lions tournament.
-So you can go after
Toya, you mean.
Have you forgotten that to
get into the tournament--
-I've got to be in the top 16.
Yeah.
I know that.
It's one step at a time.
First was to get
into the A-league.
Next, I've got to
climb a few places.
-I know you're excited
about this Shindo,
but there's one thing
you need to remember.
-What's that?
-Don't think it'll
be an easy ride,
because we're your
opponents now.
-You managed to make
it here much faster
than we thought you would.
-Give him a break, you guys.
Stop hassling him.
-We're not hassling him.
We're giving him spirit.
-Huh?
-Well, good luck, Shindo.
-Hey.
Thanks.
-Good luck.
-Yeah, good luck.
-The same from me.
-And me too!
-We're all glad you
made it to the A-league.
-Hikaru!
They're expecting
you to respond.
-Uh-- ah, thanks.
I'll look forward
to playing you.
-If you're already, it's time.
Let's begin.
-Onegaishimasu.
-Hm.
-Huh?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
I didn't realize
they gave you more time
to play in the A-league.
I can't let myself be
intimidated by the fact
that these are all
A-league players.
After all, I'm one of them now.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Hikaru
has taken his first step
toward his goal.
-Hm.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): This guy
sure takes a long time to play.
-Hm.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): No
wonder he's in the A-league.
He thought a lot
about that move.
I mean, it's a
strong move, but--
-Huh?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): There's
no point getting worried.
I have to come back at him
with an even stronger move.
I know I can do it.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
You've taken your play
to whole new level, Hikaru.
Huh?
But there's still a lot
of room for improvement.
-Hm.
I resign.
[sigh]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I won.
This is the first time
I've ever played Fuku.
He doesn't really
plan his moves at all.
Not like that guy
this morning who
took forever to make a move.
Fuku's different.
All instinct.
This is much easier.
I remember sensei
being impressed
with how I'd played
three games at once.
Maybe I play better this fast.
Whoa.
I won by half a point.
That's two wins in a row now.
-No need to rub it in.
-Oh.
Sorry.
-That's OK.
Forget it.
-I thought I had
you cornered here,
but then you went and
made a great comeback.
-But you were in
control after that.
It got way too complicated.
I lost track.
-I couldn't believe how
fast you played your stones.
-Yeah.
Everyone says that.
Hey. want to play another game?
-Sure.
Why not?
We've got time.
Go's really awesome.
Don't you think so?
-You know, that's what
Waya always says too.
-What's he like as a player?
-He's pretty good.
But I still manage to beat
him every time we play.
-Wha?
Well, if you can beat him
and I can beat you, then
maybe I'm a better
than I thought was.
-Hikaru, it's your turn to move.
-I know that.
Whoa.
You've really spread
yourself out over here.
-That's because I'm
building up my territory.
It's going to be my turf.
-Oh really?
In that case, I'm going
to land on your turf
and build a fortress
of black stones.
-Oh, no!
He landed right in the middle!
-Will you two keep
the noise down?
There are still people
playing in here?
-OK.
-Sorry about that.
-Hey, guys.
So who won the game?
-Hm.
-You're kidding me.
That means you won two games.
-I hear that you
can't beat Fuku.
[clears throat]
-You should keep
your mouth shut.
-I was only telling the truth.
-Before you start
acting invincible,
remember that I'm going
to be your next opponent.
You won't win three in a row.
-We'll see.
-Just you wait.
[chuckling]
-Hahah.
Two wins.
I'm on a roll.
-I know it feels good to put
together consecutive wins,
but don't forget.
Your first opponent
next week will be Waya,
and he seems determined that
he's going to win that game.
-We'll see how good he
is, once we start playing.
-Yes.
I suppose you're right.
I don't think we've ever watched
one of his games, have we?
-No.
But it'll be fun to find out
what kind of a player he is.
Come on.
It's your turn to play.
Go.
-Yes.
[grunting]
-Huh?
[shout]
[laughter]
-I think this is
going to be fun.
-You bet.
-Good morning.
-Oh.
Hey, guys.
Have you seen Waya?
-Yeah.
Over there.
Waya: Internet Go
is a piece of cake.
-Easy for you say, but I don't
know anything about computers.
Since my cousin's
giving me his old one,
I guess I should learn.
-What kind?
-You know, I got no idea.
But once my cousin's got
it all set up for me,
maybe you could show me
how to play Go on it.
-Yeah.
Sure.
Whenever.
-They're talking about
playing on the internet.
-That's where you play
against complete strangers
in a little box, isn't it?
-Huh?
Shindo?
You mean you've
actually played online?
Oh.
You can use a computer?
Way to go.
-Uh-- well not a lot.
Just a few times in
an internet cafe.
-I'm the one who played.
Not you.
-I don't have a
computer at home.
-Aw, too bad.
You get to meet any
good players online?
-Actually, quite a few.
It's a good way to
practice your game.
Sometimes even the
pros are on there.
-They play amateurs?
-Not all the time.
And it's just for fun.
Nobody uses their real
name, so sometimes it's
hard to tell for sure.
-Cool.
-There was one time where
a pro used his real name.
I remember being
surprised that he did it.
-Did you play him?
-Yeah.
At first I thought it was
just an amateur using his name
as a joke, until he thrashed me.
[laughter]
-Who was it?
-Ichiryu-sensei.
I did a bit of
checking up afterwards,
and it was definitely him.
-A real pro, huh?
-There's lots of them online.
There was one guy who seemed
to be as strong as the pros,
if not stronger.
He was online for
about two months
and then he just disappeared
and never came back.
-Stronger than the pros?
-Online for about two months?
-Well, sounds like a lot of fun.
Once I figure out the
computer, let's play.
-Sure.
-Waya, do you remember the
name of that guy you thought
was stronger than the pros?
-Yeah.
It was Sai.
-Oh my.
-That's what I was afraid of.
-It was during the
summer break last year.
I only played him
once, but I logged on
to watch a lot of his other
games with other players.
-So I have played
Waya after all.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): You
played hundreds of people.
-He was an amazing player.
As far as I know, he never lost.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I've never
known him to lose either.
-And not just amateurs.
He managed to beat one of
the top pros from Korea.
-Oh?
They have pros over in Korea?
WAYA: Even Toya skipped an exam,
so he could play against Sai.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Yeah.
I remember that.
-Anyway, he was a really
awesome guy to watch online.
Once summer break was
over, I kept logging on
to see if he was there,
but he never returned.
I'd like to play
him again some day.
Every time I log
on to play Go, he's
the first person I look for.
Although he played against
lots of different people,
he never chatted with
anyone, so his true identity
was like this big mystery.
No one knew who he was.
And then one day,
for some reason,
Sai sent me a message
after our game.
-What?
-Of course he beat
me, but then he
sent me a message
saying, strong, aren't I?
Don't you think that's
kind of childish?
-Huh.
Zelda.
Of course, you replied by
saying you were an insei.
I can't believe you were Zelda.
-Hikaru!
-Huh?
-Hm.
-How do you know about
my chat with Sai?
-If you're all ready,
it's time to begin.
-Onegaishimasu.
WAYA (VOICEOVER):
It couldn't be.
Shindo-- could he be Sai?
No way.
Never in a million years.
-Huh.
[sigh]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
We and my big mouth.
-Hikaru.
Worry about it later.
Hikaru.
Right now you have to focus your
attention on the game at hand.
Hikaru!
Did you hear what I just said?
Are you paying any
attention to me whatsoever?
You're going to lose
if you listen to me.
I mean, you'll lose if
you don't listen to me.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): I saw
lots of Sai's games online.
There's no way they
can be the same person.
Sai's a much stronger
player than this.
Still, it's kind of
weird, but there's
something about the way he
plays that reminds me of Sai.
Ah!
I can't let myself
get distracted.
But if he's not Sai, how
did he know about the game?
Could it be him after all?
No.
It can't be!
[panting]
I resign.
-Huh?
-You did it, Hikaru.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): That's
three straight wins.
[laughter]
-That's it.
Now I get it.
Shindo!
-Huh?
-You're Sai's
student, aren't you?
-What?
-You were sitting
right behind him
when he was playing me online.
Come on.
Admit it!
-Nearly right.
He wasn't behind
me. he was in front.
-So if you're learning
Go from this Sai,
then it would make
sense why Toya's
so dead set on playing you.
It's got to be because he
recognizes something of Sai
in the way you play your game.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): He's
sort of got it right
and he's sort of got it wrong.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Waya is
an intelligent young man.
-Answer me, Shindo!
How do you know about
my online game with Sai?
-Hm.
[whimper]
[clears throat]
-Waya, it was a total
accident that I happened
to see that game
between Zelda and Sai.
-Huh?
-Remember I told you I went
into this internet cafe?
Well, I was waiting
for a computer
when I saw someone
playing go online.
I tried to look over his
shoulder at the game,
but it was already over.
Then the chat caught my eye.
I guess that's why
I remembered it.
-What did he look like?
-I don't know.
He left before I got
a chance to see him.
[sigh]
-Hikaru, you've become
quite accomplished liar.
-No thanks to you.
-So you don't know him.
You played a good game, Shindo.
A lot of really great moves.
I think you're going
to be a strong player.
Maybe even as strong as Sai.
-Three straight wins.
And one of them against Waya.
[whimper]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
The next guy I
played seemed intimidated by me.
I guess I must have
been playing well.
-I resign.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): My
fourth win in a row.
It was great.
I thought I was on my way.
But then, I lost
game after game,
and started to wonder if I
was getting worse, not better.
It was pretty depressing.
-It was a real long
shot, but you did it.
I never thought you'd
actually make it
into the ranks of
the top 16 so fast.
-Now you're qualified for
the Young Lions tournament.
Way to go!
-Congratulations.
-Aw, thanks, guys.
-It wasn't that long
ago you were hanging
around the bottom
of the B-League.
-That.
Doesn't mean he's
any better than us.
-He set himself a difficult goal
and he managed to achieve it.
Why can't you be happy for him?
-I don't do that sort of thing.
-So when does the Young
Lions tournament take place?
Do you think Toya--
-Do you ever think about
anything else but Toya?
It's starting to get annoying.
-The tournament
starts next month.
It takes place on Saturdays when
there aren't any insei classes.
-It doesn't just
happen on one day.
Because there's 16
pros and 16 insei,
that's a lot of matches
that have to be played.
About three Saturdays total.
-All the first round
matches are the insei
versus the pros-- without
a handicap, of course.
-What was it like last year?
-The insei that won their
first matches were--
-Just five of us.
Isumi and I went on to win
our second round match,
although that's
as far as we got.
-It's awesome you got
that far against the pros.
-No, it's not.
-Huh?
-You've got to be able
to beat some of them,
if you want to
pass the pro exam.
The Young Lions is a good
way to see if you're ready.
-Will Kurata 5th Dan be playing?
-Nah, I doubt it.
I think he's over the age limit.
-Aw, hope I don't
have to play Sayaki.
-Why?
He's in your study
session, right?
-The most important
thing is that we all
make it through the first round.
-Hey.
Did you hear that Nakayama's
going to be there?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Toya, last time
we met I couldn't
give you an answer.
-Why wait?
Why don't we play
a game right now?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Now I'm ready.
Let's play.
ANNOUNCER: Mitsuru Mashiba,
age 17 from the Chiba region.
Studying under Hiroshi
Mizoguchi, 9th Dan.
[applause]
Akira Toya, age 13 from Tokyo.
Studying under Koyo Toya Meijin.
[applause]
[laughter]
TOYA: Mr. Ogata.
Mr. Ogata!
Mr.-- uh.
-Hello, Toya.
Welcome to the pros.
-Uh.
Thank you, sir.
I'm looking forward to it.
[chatting]
-Kimihiro, I just wanted to
say thanks for everything.
-Don't be silly.
I'm the one who should
be thanking you.
The only reason our Go club can
keep going is because of you.
Thank you.
We've had a lot of fun.
-Kimihiro, take care.
-You too.
-Thanks.
[laughter]
-Tetsuo.
Tetsuo.
-If it isn't Shindo.
-Before you go, you know
when I played that game
against the three of you?
Well, I just wanted to say--
-Ah forget it.
Doesn't matter.
You just take care of yourself.
-Hm.
I'm going to be the
best Go player ever.
-Hey, Shindo.
I'll look forward to seeing
your name in the papers
once you become a pro.
[shouts of goodbye]
-Just you wait!
It won't be long.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
The best player ever.
[theme music]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Go club's really
changed since graduation.
SAI (VOICEOVER): They'll
need another player
if they're going to
enter tournaments.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Something
else must be going on.
Akari and Yuki are ignoring me.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
There's certainly
are lot of tension in the air.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Next
time-- a place to return.
What?
They don't want me to come
to the Go club anymore?
SAI (VOICEOVER): I told
you things were tense.