NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past
known as Fujiwara-no-Sai
has returned, visible
only to Hikaru Shindou.
A master of Go, Sai seeks
to play the Divine Move.
[theme music]
AKIRA (VOICEOVER):
Excellent move.
He's put up a wall
in front of me.
-Huh?
-I'm not gonna
bother you anymore.
You'll never have
to see me again.
-Hey, wait up, Akira!
If you keep on chasing
your phantom image of me,
one day I'm gonna
catch up to you.
-Hm.
Is that so?
-I want to thank you for
all the help you gave me.
-Hikaru.
-I'm not coming back.
Summer break's almost done,
and school's starting soon.
Well, Sai, if you can't play
on the internet anymore,
I guess there's no other choice.
You're gonna have to play me.
-Really?
But you haven't offered
to play a game against me
before, Hikaru.
HIKARU: I don't really
wanna play against you.
After all, that means I've got
to move two players' stones.
What a pain.
SAI: But how are
we going to play?
You don't have a Go
board in your room.
SAI: I don't have stones either.
-Nice move.
-Huh?
-You've gotten stronger.
Really?
I have, haven't I?
Getting worried?
-I'm reducing your handicap.
-The game's over?
If you're giving up, you're
supposed to say, I resign.
-Ugh.
I'm a lot stronger
than you'll ever be!
You shouldn't let one little
compliment go to your head!
-Handicap or no handicap,
I just won the last game.
Don't be such a sore loser.
-Hey, guys.
Miss Tamako got some
money from the club budget
and used it to buy a
couple of Go boards
and two sets of stones.
-Cool.
Can I look at them?
-New boards?
HIKARU: Whoa, look at that.
It folds in half.
What's this thing
made out of, plastic?
I've seen these in toy stores.
-I didn't choose them.
-Guys!
I found a new member!
Come meet everyone.
-I'm Kumiko.
-Aw.
She's just a girl.
Just a girl, what
do you mean by that?
KUMIKO: Wait!
-Kimihiro's graduating soon.
We need to find a
guy to replace him,
or else we won't be able
to enter tournaments.
-Akari, I don't know
anything about Go.
Are you sure it's OK?
-Of course I'm sure.
I'm gonna teach you
everything you need to know.
-When did you become
a Go instructor?
-Know what I did this summer?
I practiced!
I've been going to Go
classes for months now.
HIKARU: Seriously?
AKARI: Seriously.
HIKARU: You went by yourself?
AKARI: That's right.
HIKARU: What's gotten into you?
-Know what?
The Go club's gonna
be great this year.
Too bad I have to
study for my exams.
-But you're still going to
come play once in a while,
aren't you?
-This got stronger
over the summer break.
-So you've improved?
Let's play a game.
HIKARU: I won't be
needing a handicap.
You sure about that?
AKARI: Yuuki, why don't
you teach us some strategy?
YUUKI: Uh.
AKARI: Come on.
It'll be fun!
YUUKI: Aw.
HIKARU: Hey, Kimihiro.
How much would a Go board
and a set of stones cost?
KIMIHIRO: Maybe about
10,000 yen for everything.
HIKARU: Wow.
That's not cheap.
I guess I could see if my
grandpa will buy me one.
KIMIHIRO: That's
an expensive gift.
HEIHACHI: I haven't seen
you in a while, Hikaru.
I heard you started playing Go.
HIKARU: You just found out?
I've been playing
for more than a year!
-I also heard that you joined
a Go club at your school.
-It's funny you
should bring that up.
I was hoping you
could do me a favor.
HEIHACHI: A favor, huh?
I'm sorry, but I've
already promised your mom
that I wouldn't give
you any more money.
I'd like to help you out,
but she made me give my word.
-I don't want any money.
I want you to get me
a Go board and stones.
-Is that all?
I thought you already
had one of those.
If my grandson wants a
Go board, then that's
what he's gonna get.
I'll pick you up a
nice folding one.
OK?
-I'd really like one that
has legs on the bottom.
Will you get me
that kind of board
if I beat you with no handicap?
-You-- You actually think you
can beat me in an even game?
You don't know how
good I am, do you?
See all these trophies?
I won the eighth annual
Local All-Star Cup,
and the third annual
Neighborhood Go Championship.
I've won so many of
them, I lost count.
-I've seen these a
million times, you know.
The longer we keep
talking, the less time
we have to sit down
and play a game.
[grumbling]
-If you beat me
in an even match,
then I'll give you this board.
-But it's used.
-What are you saying?
This is a valuable antique here!
-Huh?
There's another board.
You remember?
The one that you keep
up in your attic?
HEIHACHI: You mean the board
you found before you passed out?
You wouldn't want it.
HIKARU: I wouldn't?
HEIHACHI: It's
supposedly haunted
by a ghost that wears
a nobleman's hat.
-That's quite a story.
HEIHACHI: Don't tell me
you're afraid of ghosts?
My older brother used to collect
all sorts of unusual things.
He stumbled across that old
board in an antique shop.
After he died, I inherited it.
But I've never seen the ghost.
Who knows?
Maybe my brother made
the whole thing up.
SAI: I wonder what
he'd do if he knew
that I was here now with Hikaru.
Over a century ago,
I was with Shusaku.
And before that, I played Go
in the Heian imperial court.
A thousand years have
passed since that time.
And yet, I still find myself
sitting before a Go board,
studying this game.
How much longer will
I be able to pursue
my selfish indulgence?
-Ah!
I really messed up.
No!
All my stones are
about to be captured.
-Mm-hm.
Yep.
Look at the board.
You wasted a move when you
placed your stone here.
You should've played there
and protected this shape.
-Ah.
Do you mind if I change my move?
MAN: Of course not.
-Thanks a lot!
-That was nice of you.
You're in a good mood today.
-I'm trying to keep
the game moving.
-You've been a completely
different person ever
since Akari started
coming to class.
-Hey, I'm just being
a nice guy, OK?
-We haven't seen
Hikaru in a while.
How's he doing?
-Good.
His game's gotten much
better over the summer.
-I think I remember that boy.
He seemed like a nice
enough young man.
You used to come here with
him, isn't that right?
-That's right.
-Let me ask you a question,
just between us girls.
Do you have a little
crush on Hikaru?
-What?
We're just friends.
-Don't be embarrassed.
There's nothing
to be ashamed of.
It's obvious you took
up Go to impress him.
-It is?
-Anyway.
When you get the chance,
please tell him to drop by.
I wanna hear all
about his training.
-Sure.
I think I better start hanging
out with people my own age.
-Hm.
-OK.
It looks like I'm a
few stones behind you.
-Hm.
-Grandpa, can you
stop being so noisy?
It's really distracting.
-You've improved quite a
bit since we've played.
And you've only been
practicing for one year.
-You have-- You've become
a really strong player.
-Honestly?
-Guess this is why you can't
underestimate children.
You are quite a
talented opponent.
-Really?
Does that mean I'm winning?
-Don't get too carried away.
Even if you manage to
play a perfect end game,
you're still gonna lose.
-Aw.
There goes my Go board.
-Told you I was good,
but you wouldn't listen.
I beat Mr. Inoue from Katsua,
and that man's a legend.
-I think you're exaggerating.
I've never heard of him.
-A Go board with legs.
All right, I'll tell you what.
I can probably afford to get
you one of the cheaper ones.
If that's what it takes to
encourage you to play more,
then it's a small price to pay.
-Thanks, Grandpa.
[doorbell]
MAN: Delivery!
MITSUKO: Oh, I'll sign for that.
Hikaru, there's a package
for you in the front hall.
HIKARU: Woo hoo!
MITSUKO: What?
50,000 yen?
-I know.
Grandpa bought it for me.
-That board cost a lot.
I hope you remember
to thank him.
-Of course I did.
[humming]
-I really didn't think you'd
keep playing Go for this long.
Well, you keep at
it, OK, Hikaru?
-I don't believe it,
I don't believe it!
It's too good to be true!
Hikaru has his own Go board.
I never thought
this day would come.
-Now we can practice
whenever we want to.
This is gonna be awesome!
-Enough talk!
We have to play
the game right now!
-Let me go.
Will you look at this board?
It's brand new.
We're gonna be the
first people to use it.
SAI: Hikaru, you can have as
much of a handicap as you like.
-And just what is
that supposed to mean?
I don't need a handicap.
I want to have an even game.
You choose for color.
-But that's not possible.
How can I pick up any stones?
-I see your point.
I'll be black, and
you'll be white.
The Komi is 5 and 1/2 points.
Are you ready to play?
SAI: Sure.
-Here we go.
-4, 3, please.
4, 3, Hikaru.
-Huh?
Oh, that's right.
I'll place your stones.
-I'll take 17, 16.
-This is annoying.
I wish you could
do this yourself.
-It's not that bad.
You'll get used to it.
-Why don't you sit over there?
I can't concentrate with you
looking over my shoulder.
-Just a moment.
-That's much better.
Your move.
-10, 3, please.
-Here you go.
-Wait.
You accidentally put my
stone in the wrong spot.
-Uh-uh!
Look.
10, 3 is right there.
-10 3 is over here.
I'm sitting on the
wrong side of the board!
Everything is upside down!
How can you expect me to
play under these conditions?
-You don't have to tell me
where you're gonna move!
Just point to where
you want to go.
See?
This is much easier, isn't it?
-That tastes just about right.
HIKARU: You're
being a real jerk!
This game is over!
How am I supposed to win if
you're gonna play all out?
[nervous laughter]
-What is your problem?
You took it easy on Akira
the first time you faced him.
Would it kill you to play
a teaching game with me?
-Don't be upset.
I'm sure you'll feel better
after we play another game.
-Keep it down!
You're yelling so loud,
the walls are shaking.
Who are you talking to?
-I am not yelling!
Sai, clean this mess up for me.
-What?
But how?
you know I can't pick things up.
Hikaru?
Are you listening?
TSUTSUI: 53, 54, 55, 56.
You beat me by two points.
-Yeah!
I gave you two stones,
and I still won the game.
-Darn it!
-Huh?
[gasp]
-You know what bugs me?
I'm going to be so busy
studying for my entrance exams
that I won't get a chance
to hang out with you guys.
You're turning into a
great player, Hikaru.
It's too bad we won't
have time for many games.
The club's grown a lot.
All you are going to have a
really amazing time this year.
Yuuki, Akari, and Kumiko
are great teammates.
I can't wait to
watch the four of you
in the winter tournament.
But you'd better
find another member.
You'll need one more guy to
sign up for team tournaments.
-What if I make a new poster?
It worked for us last year.
-I'm glad that you've stopped
playing so recklessly.
You've learned a lot.
-We all felt pretty bad
when Kaio defeated us,
but we're going to show them a
thing or two this time round.
-I resign.
-Hold on.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
-Same to you.
It was a good match.
-I must resign.
-Thank you for the game.
-Really?
You want to keep playing
me through to the end?
-I resign.
-Thank you.
It was an interesting match.
[groan]
[crying]
-We weren't good enough
to beat Kaio last time,
but wait until they see
how much I've improved.
They'll never know what hit 'em.
-He's got that crazy
look in his eyes.
[laughter]
-Wow.
You're sure playing
well today, Mr. Akota.
-I appreciate your compliment,
but you ain't seen nothin' yet.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
-Hm.
Your skills have developed a
great deal in the past year.
That Go club of yours
is doing a fantastic job
with your training.
-The boy's still got a long way
to go if he wants to beat me.
I'm the best of the best!
-I hope you'll keep
visiting us, Hikaru.
They don't keep you too busy
at your middle school, do they?
(VOICEOVER) He's concentrating
so hard on the game
that he doesn't even hear me.
-Thanks for everything, Sensei.
And thanks for the
game, Mr. Akota.
It was a lot of fun.
-Huh?
Hold on, I'm coming.
See you next week, Sensei.
Why don't you ever wait?
Don't forget to practice!
-I let my guard down
because he's a kid!
Who's have guessed he'd
turn the tables on me?
I have no idea how
he managed to make
such an incredible comeback.
I should have never let
that compliment of yours go
to my head.
You're not gonna tell anyone
I lost to him, will you?
-He's extraordinarily.
-Wha--
-You're too quick
to blame yourself.
You didn't make
any real mistakes.
And neither did Hikaru.
he made a great comeback.
I've never seen a young
man with that kind
of focus and discipline.
Either the coach of his Go club
is a very talented teacher,
or Hikaru is very
passionate about his game.
-Hm.
Is something
bothering you, Hikaru?
-I was thinking.
It takes an experienced
player to recognize
how strong their opponent is.
-Huh?
-I figured that out in the
middle of today's game.
I was able to see how
talented Mr. Akota is.
-But you won.
Doesn't that prove you're
a better player than he is?
-It does.
It won't be long before I'm
good enough to beat Yuuki.
-It's too bad you couldn't have
played this good at last year's
tournament.
Maybe then Akira wouldn't have
yelled his head off at you
and made a big scene.
-Don't remind me.
(VOICEOVER) Akira.
Improving my game a little won't
make a difference against him.
Oh, yeah!
Hikaru Shindou
beats Yuuki Mitani!
I beat Yuuki!
And I did it without a handicap!
-Don't let it go to your head!
I've won dozens of games
against you, you know?
You've only beat me once.
I want a rematch.
HIKARU: I win!
YUUKI: A remathc!
You got that?
HIKARU: You'll lose again.
YUUKI: Choose for color!
-(VOICEOVER) I always thought
that Hikaru would catch up
to Yuuki one day, but I can't
believe that he's already able
to beat him.
How does he learn
so quickly, anyway?
I can't wait for this
year's tournament.
We might actually defeat Kaio.
It just might be possible that
Hikaru will make it happen.
It'd be amazing if
he can pull it off.
I hope he stays focused.
-Are we going to spend
the day reading manga?
-I need to get a textbook
for one of my classes.
You can help me look for it.
It's around here somewhere.
-I'll be glad to help you study.
-Let's see.
Where is it?
Doesn't that guy play for Kaio?
-Huh?
Hold on.
Do you have some
free time right now?
-Uh-- uh--
[theme music]
SAI: You're coming to
a cross road, Hikaru.
HIKARU: I know.
If I want to become
stronger, like Akira,
I'm going to have to
practice with new opponents.
But I also want to keep playing
against the guys in the Go
club.
SAI: The captain
of the Kaio team
will give you advice
on what to do.
HIKARU: That guy?
He's such a know it all.
All he does is talk, and
talk, and drink black coffee.
SAI: Next time.
The Road to Turning Pro.
HIKARU: Is the club
turning against me?