NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past
known as Fujiwara-no-Sai
has returned, visible
only to Hikaru Shindou.
A master of Go, Sai seeks
to play the Divine Move.
[theme music]
AKIRA: That would be me.
-Huh?
-I'm Kaio's number
three player, Shindou.
Surprised?
-Akira?
You're Kaio's number three?
-Look!
Toya's wearing a Kaio uniform.
-I read that he's gonna be a
huge star once he turns pro.
-What's a guy like
that doing here?
I thought he was an Insei.
-But if he's an
Insei, then he's not
allowed enter any
amateur tournaments.
Akira's playing
for Kaio this year?
You've gotta be joking.
-We're facing off against
Kaio in the first round.
-Toya's gonna be playing in
the number three position?
-What?
Are you serious?
That means he's gonna
be my opponent, right?
Oh, I'm dead meat, guys.
GIRL: So this is the
great Hikaru Shindou
that Toya keeps talking about?
It's nice to finally
meet his rival.
I've been looking forward
to watching you play.
I wanna see if you're as
good as they say you are.
-So you're the ones
on Kaio's Go team.
-Hm?
-I hear you guys are good.
Too bad you lost to Haze
Middle School last year.
-Who are you, anyway?
Kaio and Haze are facing
off in the second round.
I'm the guy who's gonna
defeat your captain.
-That's big talk.
Do you really think
you're strong enough
to beat Kishimoto?
-Hidaka.
-Matani would do
anything to win.
Even cheat.
-Kimihiro, Yuuki
gave us his word.
Don't embarass him.
-Kimihiro?
I remember the last tournament.
You won on a fluke.
Senpai knew that if he hadn't
made that one little blunder,
he would've easily defeated you.
Sound like Haze relies
on luck and deception
to come out on top.
You've really got quite a team.
Aren't you the
seventh grader who's
been placed in first position
to take a strategic loss?
-What?
What exactly do you
mean by strategic loss?
Oh, come on!
Yuuki's amazing.
He plays 10 times
better than I do.
You'll see.
He's our strongest player.
Challenge him and you'll
find out for yourself.
-Uh.
-Nice to meet you.
My name's Kishimoto.
I'm Kaio's team captain.
I look forward to
having you make it
through to the second round.
We'll play a game worthy
of the first position.
-Come on.
Do you honestly think he'll
make it past the first round?
Guess we'll find out.
-She's got a point.
The first round's tough.
-I meant what I said.
You're ouir captain, and
you're our best player.
You can win without
having to cheat.
-I think that it's time to
get this tournament started.
-Sure, let's begin.
-Please stop your games
and put your stones away.
The tournament is
about to begin.
ANNOUNCER: Attention,
all participants.
Here are the first
round match ups.
When I call out
your school's name,
please go to your
assigned seats.
In the boys' division, Iyu
Middle School versus Hamachi
Middle School, table A. Kawahagi
Middle School versus Tai Middle
School, table B. Haze Middle
School versus Iwata Middle
School, table C. Kaio Middle
School versus Sowara Middle
School, table D.
YUUKI: I'm playing black.
-Onegai shimasu.
-He's fast.
BOY: What did I just do?
YUUKI (VOICEOVER): I am good.
And my opponent knows it.
Even Kimihiro,
who hates my guts,
thinks that I'm 10
times the player he is.
-We'll play a game worthy
of the first position.
YUUKI (VOICEOVER): I'll give
him a game he won't forget.
-I resign.
KIMIHIRO (VOICEOVER):
That was quick.
-I'm gonna go watch Kaio.
The guys at the Go salon
were strong opponents,
but they were all self taught.
Now.
These students, they
can get this good just
from playing in a
middle school Go club?
-I resign.
KISHIMOTO: Thank
you for the game.
If it isn't Mitani
from Haze Middle.
Did you learn
anything from my game?
YUUKI (VOICEOVER): I get it.
This jerk thinks I'm some
unskilled seventh grader
playing as a team captain
for strategic reasons.
That handshake
was just for show.
I bet he thinks I'm too
pathetic to talk to.
I don't mean to
upset you, but it
doesn't look like
Hikaru's was going to win.
All right.
I wanna make a deal.
I'll stop cheating if
you win your match.
I've got my sights on
Kaio's captain, Kishimoto.
So, right now, you'd
better not lose.
You got that?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
I'm really starting to mess up.
I've got to do something.
-Looks like you're about to lose
-You're laughing at me?
You really shouldn't laugh
until after you've won,
and this game is not over yet!
-What?
-Something about these
boys has changed.
Hikaru's game has matured.
He has really improved.
But he is not the only one.
Akira Toya's game
has matured, too.
BOY: White, 72 and 1/2 points.
TSUTSUI: Black, 56 points.
All right!
I won by 16 and 1/2 points.
Thanks for the excellent game.
BOY: Congratulations.
-That was a great match.
Thanks.
-Thank you.
You're a skilled opponent.
-Yes!
-BOY: I resign.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
-You were playing a lot
slower than you usually do.
-Sensei?
I was trying to
stay calm so that I
wouldn't make any mistakes.
-Hazi Middle School won
all three of their matches.
-Huh?
Did you watch their matches?
I'd like to know
how Hikaru played.
Was he focused?
-I suppose you'll
find out soon enough.
ANNOUNCER: We will
now break for lunch.
The afternoon session
will begin at 1:00.
Please make sure
you're back on time.
-Wanna go to the cafeteria?
-Good idea.
We should ask Toya
to come with us.
-What?
-Hidaka, can I talk
to you for a minute?
-What's up?
-Hikaru, time for lunch.
-I'm not hungry.
-What's wrong?
Hikaru?
-That was a great
comeback, Hikaru.
-I know!
I was awesome, wasn't I?
And nobody can say that
was a fluke, either.
I did it all on my own.
Did you notice how
much Ive improved, Sai?
I mean, I'm way better
than I was before.
-True.
But you have yet
to defeat Kimihiro.
-Hmph
-And now your next opponent
shall be Akira Toya.
-Just remember,
I'm gonna play him.
-You've already made it very
clear you don't want my help.
-We both know that
Akira's dying to play you,
but I don't see how
that's my problem.
It was the Haze
Middle School Go club
that signed up to compete
in this tournament.
Unfortunately, you
aren't a member.
-Yes.
I know that, Hikaru.
-Aw, why couldn't
Akira have waited
until I was a bit stronger?
Now he's forced me
into playing him today.
HIDAKA: Well, what is it that
you wanted to talk to me about?
Let me guess.
You've just heard the story
about Toya getting bullied?
KISHIMOTO: Did it really happen?
HIDAKA: Yeah.
KISHIMOTO: I'm not surprised.
Toy's had a lot of
trouble fitting in.
-Three guys put together
a plan to get rid of him.
They wanted to
humiliate him so he'd
be too ashamed to
stay in the Go club.
-Focus.
-His game has started
to fall to pieces.
-Those jerks.
they should have realized
that no matter what
they did to him, nothing
was going to stop him
from competing in
the tournament today.
-He doesn't back down.
I've seen it before.
When he was yelling
at Mr. Yun, he
had this intense
look in his eyes.
- --me to play in the
number three position!
You were the one that said
I was the only person who'd
have a chance against Hikaru!
Remember?
Please, sir.
The only reason I joined this
club was so I could battle him.
But Sensei--
-OK, Akira.
You can play as
our number three.
-Toya's aware of how
selfish he's acting.
I bet he feels pretty guilty.
HIDAKA: I'm sure he does.
Think he'll quit
the Go club when
the tournament is finished?
KISHIMOTO: Yep.
Everything should go back
to normal once he's gone.
HIDAKA: Sure,
that's what you say.
But I know how badly you
wanted to play against him.
You can't kind your
disappointment from me.
Come on.
We'll get some lunch.
-Akira's been gettin'
pushed round, huh?
He probably had it coming.
He only thinks about
himself, you know?
-Why would others
choose to hate him?
Imagine how difficult it was
for him to play third position.
He was clearly the best
choice for team captain.
-Yeah, I know.
Who's go to all that trouble?
You're the one he's after.
Sai?
You should play him.
-Are you sure?
You were so eager to
play in this tournament.
-He's all yours.
Good luck.
-There you are.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
It's almost time for the
second round match-ups.
Here.
I brought you some lunch.
Don't you want to eat?
-Thanks, but I'm
really not that hungry.
What are the other guys up to?
-They're playing a
practice game together.
-Are you serious?
I thought they hated each other.
-They really want to win,
so they're working together.
And Mitani says
he's going to try
as hard as he can to
beat Kaio's captain.
I don't think he likes him.
And Kimihiro?
He's just as
determined as Yuuki is.
It's amazing.
They're finally
working as a team.
Can you believe it?
We should probably
head back now.
[sigh]
-Cheer up.
I'm sure you'll play awesome.
-Yeah.
-Well, I guess I'll
see you inside.
-You're troubled.
It's OK.
I'm fine.
Stay focused on the game, Sai.
Akira's going to come at you
with everything he's got.
If you're too busy worrying
about me, you're gonna lose.
Let's go.
-He's correct.
I must control my emotions
and play cautiously.
Hikaru.
-Hey, man.
What happened to you?
-Hm?
-I heard that you
didn't eat lunch.
Are you OK?
-Are you gonna be able to
beat Kaio on an empty stomach?
-Hm?
-Huh?
ANNOUNCER: If you're
playing a practice game,
please put it away your stones.
We're about to begin the
second round of matches.
When you hear your
school's name,
please go to your
assigned tables.
Table A, Kaio Middle School
versus Haze Middle School.
Table B, Iyu Middle School
versus Tai Middle School.
-Come on.
That's us.
ANNOUNCER: And in the girls'
division, Table F, Kaio Middle
School versus Sowara
Middle School.
-Kaio and Haze,
please take a seat.
-I hope you're ready.
We've been waiting a really long
time for this day, haven't we?
Finally, this is our big
chance to defeat Kaio.
We'll all do our best.
-I'll try my hardest.
With a little luck, I
might even win again.
[theme music]
HIKARU: The second
round's starting,
and we'll finally
get to face Kaio.
SAI: Akira has prepared for
this game for a long time.
HIKARU: Sai.
If you play him,
then I won't know
how much better I've gotten.
SIA: Will you play him instead?
HIKARU: I gotta see if I
can beat him on my own.
Yuuki and Kimihiro
could win too,
and then we'd take down
last year's champions.
Next time, The Third Match.
SAI: It's time to show Akira
how far you've advanced.