[theme music]
-Isumi's definitely gonna
be one of the front runners.
He looks very confident.
Not at all like last year.
-First you beat Murakami,
and now Tsujioka.
-We're not going to let these
greenhorns take over just yet.
-With all due respect,
Kuwabara-sensei, Ogata
here isn't exactly a greenhorn.
He has won two titles.
-Hm.
WOMAN: It's amazing.
Back then Toya was
just a One-Dan,
and he's made it to
the Honinbo league.
-Miyake called to say that
Koyo Toya signed a contract
to play for Beijing in China.
-I get a sense that there's a
momentous change on the way,
don't you?
Something's about to
happen in the world og Go.
The new wave is
coming, and Akira Toya
is definitely leading the way.
-If it isn't Shindou!
What are you doing here?
Are you scheduled
to play a game?
-Hi, Mr. Kurata.
No, no game today.
I'm here for my study session
with Morashita-sensei.
-I just saw the pairings for the
Meijin tournament qualifiers.
Your first match is
against Akira Toya!
-Yeah.
And you know what?
It's all thanks to you.
-Thanks to me?
How?
-The only reason he has to play
in all the qualifying rounds
this year is because you
managed to beat him last year.
He's made it to the finals
in every other tournament,
but not the Meijin.
It seems like he doesn't
want to come down
to my level or something.
-Well, what do you expect?
He is Akira Toya, after all.
-I know, but he's so busy
playing in other tournaments,
our game hasn't even
been scheduled yet.
I should get going.
-Hey!
Shindou!
Tell you what.
If you beat Toya,
make sure to bring
that half signed autograph.
-What?
Autograph?
-Remember, when I
gave you my autograph,
I only signed half of it.
If you bear Toya, I'll sign
the other half for you.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Oh no!
What did I do with it?
-Think of it as
a special reward.
How about that for motivation?
-Well, thanks but I don't
really need extra motivation.
-What?
You don't need any
extra motivation?
You sure it's wise to be
that confident against Toya?
-Well, no, I wouldn't
say that exactly.
-Well, OK then.
I hope your game gets
scheduled really soon.
I'm gonna look forward
to seeing the results.
See you!
-Uh, bye.
Hope your game gets
scheduled really soon.
-Yeah, I wonder when
I am going to play.
-Oh no!
I'm gonna be late for
the study session.
-Ever since he
started playing again,
Shindou's improved immensely.
I've got no idea what happened
to him while he was out
of action, but
whatever it was, he
seems to have put it
all behind him now.
-I resign.
-No doubt about it,
Shindou's turned
into a very strong player.
One of the best.
-This block you played here
was what really did me in.
It was like you planned
it from the start.
You managed to break through
every single one of my groups,
so in the end, there
was nothing I could do.
-Shindou, if you keep
playing like that,
you're gonna do just fine.
HIKARU: Yes sir!
-And Saeki, you gotta
do better if you
want to beat Koyo Toya's
protege, Ashiwara!
SAEKI: Yes, sir.
-And as for you, Waya.
-I don't know if
I wanna hear this.
-What are you talking about?
Of course you do.
Don't slack off,
or Shindou's gonna
pass you in no time at all.
-Yeah, I kind of
already know that.
-Play me next.
Are you up for it, Shindou?
-OK.
Onegai shimasu.
Toya.
I'll play against
you anytime you want.
I'm home!
Some mail came for you today.
The Go Association sent you
this notice of your next game.
-My next game?
No way!
They finally scheduled it.
Two weeks from today.
Toya.
Let's see.
This is Toya's game record
from the Honinbo championship.
From now on, our
game has started.
Toya, you and I have
to play each other.
I know that you've always
wanted to play against Sai,
but he isn't here anymore.
Except he is in my game.
He's in every one of my moves.
But I can't expect you
to understand that.
I'll make myself strong
enough to beat you!
I'm gonna play at
your level now.
You ready?
AKARI: Aw, I've gone
way down in the class
ranking since the midterms.
GIRL: You've got your
rankings already?
We didn't get ours yet.
I bet our teacher
just forgot about it.
-See you later, Akari!
-Goodbye!
Huh?
Hikaru?
-Hm?
Oh, uh, hey Akari.
-I just wanted to wish you
luck for your game against Toya
tomorrow.
-How'd you know
when I was playing?
-I saw it listed in "Go Weekly."
You know, the column
where they tell
you the schedule of all the
upcoming tournament matches?
You must get really nervous
the day before a big game.
-What do you mean?
-I don't know.
You've just got this
serious look on your face.
-Hm.
This match against
Toya is a big one,
so maybe I'm a
little bit nervous.
Hm.
Akari.
What are you up to right now?
-What?
Nothing, really.
Interested in playing some Go?
It might help me take my
mind of tomorrow's match
if I play a game with you.
-I'd love to have a game
with you, but I don't think--
I'm not sure--
-All right, come on.
Let's go to my place.
Hm?
What's the matter?
-Hikaru.
You've changed.
-You think so?
-Yes.
For sure.
Maybe it's just 'cause
you're a pro now,
but you seem much more mature.
-I've noticed a
change in you too.
-Really?
You mean it?
So, tell me.
How do you think I've changed?
-Hm.
You've gotten shorter.
-I haven't gotten shorter!
You're taller!
[laughing]
-Hey, don't laugh at me.
You can be such a jerk
sometimes, you know that?
MITSUKO: Are you leaving, dear?
-Yes.
I'm going now.
-I'm leaving now.
-You've got a big
game today, Saeki.
-That's right.
Against Koyo Toya's
protege, Ashiwara.
-Can you imagine what
Morashita-sensei's
gonna say if you lose this one?
He'll blow his top.
-Thanks a lot.
Like I need any more pressure.
-Good morning, Saeki.
How are you?
-Uh, Mr. Ashiwara--
-Good morning to you too, Waya.
-Oh, hey there.
Good morning.
-Well, I guess I
should wish you luck.
Here's to a good game.
-You know, I've started
to realize something.
-Yeah, what?
-This rivalry with
Toya-sensei's students,
I think we feel it
just because we're
in Morashita's study class.
I mean, doesn't
it seem like we're
the only ones getting worked
up before our matches?
-I don't even want to
think about it right now.
-Hey.
Waya.
Mr. Saeki.
-Hi, Shindou.
-Oh, hello.
-Good to see you.
-Guess what?
Isumi gave me a call last night.
He told me he just
passed the pro exam.
-Really?
That's great!
But isn't there still a few
more games left to play?
-Well, yeah, but
he's undefeated,
so his win yesterday
means he's through.
-That's awesome!
-And he wants me
to look after him
and give him a few tips
now that he's a pro.
I better work hard if I'm
gonna stay ahead of him.
-So, Isumi passed the exam, huh?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Uh, hey, Mashiba.
-Well, it's about time.
He sure took long enough.
-Mashiba!
-Now he's a pro, he'll
probably move up the ranks
pretty quickly.
He's a strong player.
Every year, another bunch of
guys come on to the scene.
Doesn't make it easy
for the rest of us.
I'm not gonna lose today, Waya!
-What was that all about?
Is he your opponent?
-You got it.
And you're gonna be
playing Toya, right?
[ding]
-I won't know until I play him.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Toya.
-Ochi.
What were you and Toya talking
about just before you came out
of the elevator?
-Well, he started
the conversation
by offering me congratulations
on my winning streak.
-Yeah, and then what?
-I told him my winning streak
was nothing compared to him
making it all the way
to the Honinbo league
and playing for the title.
Then I asked him
about today's game.
I said something about
how it's probably
going to be an easy
win against Shindou.
-Then I bet he said, yeah,
of course it'll be easy.
He thinks he's such
a big shot, and only
has to face the top
ranked players now.
Come on, Ochi, tell me.
What did he said?
-He said, I won't
know until I play him.
-Huh?
-Don't you remember back
when Shindou was an Insei?
There was a rumor
around that Toya
considered him to be a rival.
-Well, yeah.
But none of us
took it seriously.
We all thought it was a joke.
Maybe it was true, after all.
-We can't just sit back and
let these two take over.
-You're right.
They haven't seen what I can do.
-Waya?
-Huh?
-You're my opponent
next week, right?
My winning streak
will keep on going.
-You little nerd!
I'm gonna crush you!
-I'd better take some of
that fighting spirit of yours
with me.
-Yeah!
Let's give it all we got, Saeki!
-Uh, hey, Toya.
We finally get to
play each other again.
-The last time the
two of us played
was in the school
Go club tournament.
Two years and four months ago.
-It's been a long
time since then.
-I know.
It's been too long.
-I happened to see your
game against Zama-sensei
in Go Weekly.
It was really close.
I mean, you played
great, but the lead
he built up early in the game
was impossible to overcome.
-He's the former Oza.
I wasn't expecting to
beat someone like him
on my first attempt.
However, the next time we
meet, things will be different.
I won't be the same
player then that I am now.
-I've had a chance
to see how strong you
are by looking at the game
records of your matches
against Zama-sensei
and Hagiwara Nine-Dan.
Now it's your chance to
see how strong I've become.
It may be two years and four
months since we last played,
but I haven't been
wasting my time.
[buzzer]
-Onegai shimasu.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): OK, Toya.
Let's begin.
3, 4 point in the
upper right corner.
Hm?
That was fast.
He's not playing like he's
got five hours on the clock.
He's playing speed Go.
It's like he's been
waiting for this game.
He didn't respond
to my approach.
Instead, he decided to
make an attack of his own.
If he wants to go
straight on the offensive,
that's fine with me.
He's not the only one.
I've been waiting
for this game too.
[theme music]
HIKARU: Toya's putting
a lot of pressure
on me by playing so
quickly, but I'll
play my strongest game ever.
I'll play just like Sai.
And that's when
Toya will realize.
-It's you.
-He thinks I'm Sai!
Next time, The Power Within!