NARRATOR: After many
years inside a go board,
a spirit from the past known as
Fujiwara no Sai has returned.
Visible only to Hikaru
Shindo, a master of go,
Sai seeks to play
the divine move.
[theme song]
-Can't see him.
I wonder where he could be.
Huh?
-Hikaru!
That was a terrible move!
What?
Although he made a mistake,
he didn't let it throw him.
He drew his opponent
in and managed
to turn a bad move around.
Hikaru.
-I wonder how Shindo's
been doing in his match.
-Toya is there.
And why is
Ogata-sensei watching?
-6 and 1/2 points.
-6 and 1/2 points?
That's a big gap.
-These pros are
way better than us.
-Hey, it turned out to
be a really good game.
Thanks.
-Shindo.
-Huh?
What's up, Waya?
-Too bad you lost the game.
-That's OK.
At least I played well.
-So I see.
-Hm.
Huh?
How did Toya do?
-He won, of course.
Finished ages ago.
-Oh, never mind.
I wanted to play him.
Missed my chance.
-He was watching you.
-Huh?
-I saw him looking
over your shoulder.
He was watching you like a hawk.
It was really intense.
-How did you know
where to find me?
-I've seen you in
here before, so I
figured it was worth a try.
-You seem to be making good
progress in the Young Lions,
but I get the impression you're
not happy about something.
-Uh--
-I can tell your
heart isn't in it.
It's obvious there's
something bothering you.
It's Shindo, isn't it?
-You left the
tournament before I
had a chance to talk
to you yesterday.
There was something
I wanted to ask you.
-I guessed as much.
I'm surprised you didn't
come and find me sooner.
The same fish food, please,
but a little more this time.
-Ogata-sensei.
-You do know I'm playing
Kuwabara-sensei for his title.
That means I'm going to
be away for quite a while.
I need to focus on
winning the title match.
Of course, I need
to watch my step,
or else a young player
named Akira Toya
might take the title before me.
I'll give you a ride home.
Want to stop for some
sushi along the way?
-Ogata-sensei!
I need to know about
Shindo's match yesterday.
Something happened, didn't it?
Something important.
-Important?
Like what?
-By the time I got
there, Murakami 2-dan
was easily overpowering
Shindo in the end game.
But that's all I saw.
-So Shindo lost.
Isn't that enough for you?
And it was by 6 and 1/2 points.
-From what I saw, he should
have lost by way more than 6
and 1/2 points.
Which means he must have put up
a pretty strong fight earlier
in the game.
Has Shindo really
improved so much
that he can hold his
own with the pros?
-You saw the board for yourself.
-Yeah, I know, but that's
not the whole story!
I can't work out how
they got to that point.
It doesn't make any sense to me!
Something unusual happened.
You have to tell me what
was that Shindo did!
-Hop in the car.
I'll take you home.
-If you've got
questions about Shindo,
why don't you ask Murakami?
He is the one who played him.
-I tried to, but--
-You want to know
what Shindo did?
Why are you so
interested in that guy?
He lost!
I won!
An insei ranked 16th?
He was easy.
And I'm the one you'll
be playing next,
so I suggest you start
worrying about me.
-I see.
You didn't like his
know it all attitude,
so you got your own
back by humiliating him
in front of everyone.
That'll teach him.
Poor guy.
-Forget about him!
What did Shindo do?
-I thought you said you didn't
care about Shindo anymore.
-Huh?
-There were times when he
was playing very skillfully.
-Huh?
-After making a
careless mistake,
he used the move
to his advantage.
It was a smart choice.
He didn't let the
fact that he made
a mistake affect the
rest of his game.
He drew his opponent
in and managed
to turn the game in his favor
with that one innovative move.
There's no rush.
-Hm?
-You'll get all the
answers you need
in just a couple
of months' time.
-The pro exam?
-That's right.
He's following the same
path you've been taking,
only he's doing it a year later.
--[sigh] This time yesterday,
we were all taking part
in the Young Lions Tournament.
I can't believe
it's over already.
It's boring having to
go back to normal again.
-Not many of us made it through
the first round this year.
There was Asumi, Ochi, and
Adachi, and that was it.
-Ochi won the second
round match two.
-Yeah, but I don't think
he stands much chance
of getting through
the third round.
It's so depressing.
-You did really well, Waya.
Your game was so close.
Could have gone either way.
You were playing as
good as the pros.
-Yeah.
Sensei made a point
of telling you that.
-You've got to give
credit where credit's due.
Ochi's been awesome recently.
I haven't been able
to beat him for ages.
What about you, Isumi?
-We're about even, I think.
-Yeah, it's the same here.
Me and him are a
pretty good matchup.
-Hey, have you
guys ever noticed?
When Ochi loses, he goes and
locks himself in the bathroom.
-In the bathroom?
-I just noticed him
doing it recently.
After he loses, he
goes into the bathroom
and won't come out
for the longest time.
-You're kidding, right?
-If you listen carefully,
you can hear a tap,
tap, tap and strange mumbling
noises coming from inside.
If he loses his next
game in the Young Lions,
he'll do it for sure.
You'll hear him go tap,
tap, tap, like that.
-What do you think
he's doing in there?
-That is so weird.
-Even if his opponents
a really good pro,
and he's expecting to lose,
he'll still go in there
and then tap, tap, tap.
-Ew, creepy.
-Um, I'm playing
Ochi this afternoon.
-Well.
We want to see him
hide in the bathroom,
so you'd better
beat him, Shindo.
-He's not good
enough to beat Ochi.
He just lost by 6 and 1/2
points in his Young Lions game.
-It's too bad you didn't get
the chance to play against Toya.
-It's all right.
Yesterday I could feel
my game getting stronger.
The only way I'm going to
improve is if I keep playing.
I need more games like
the one yesterday.
More and more and more.
-Whoa.
-I know I can become stronger.
I know it!
Whoa!
Sorry!
Here!
You OK?
-Were Ogata 9-dan and Akira
Toya watching that game
because they were
interested in Shindo?
-Thanks.
Have a nice day.
-The way you've
been talking, I'm
thinking we need to watch
out for you this summer.
-Why?
What's happening?
-The pro exam, of course.
-Oh, right.
-What's wrong with you?
How could you forget about that?
That's the only reason
we're here as insei.
Once exam time
comes around, you'll
get to play all the games
you could ever want.
Dozens of games.
Day after day after day.
Hello!
We'll be fighting each
other not to get eliminated.
There'll be no
more Mr. Nice Guy.
Anyway, hope you beat
Ochi this afternoon.
-Thanks.
-Hey Waya, guess
who you're playing!
-Oh, not you again.
Give me a break.
-Not looking forward to it?
-Shut your pie hole!
-You're still having
trouble beating Fuku
after all this time?
-Just a run of bad
luck, that's all.
-Komiya has the same
problem with Fuku.
-That's weird, because
I can beat him OK.
-Yeah, well, that's you, Isumi.
-Come on, Shindo, let's go.
-What?
Oh, right.
Sorry.
-What happened?
You looked like you were on
another planet or something.
-Got anything to do
with Kuwabara-sensei?
-Who's Kuwabara-sensei?
-You mean you don't know?
-He doesn't know anything.
That guy's famous.
He holds the Honinbo title.
-Honinbo?
That's pretty big.
-Is everything all
right, Kuwabara-sensei?
-I'm not sure.
You know, I sensed a rather
unusual presence just now.
-Oh, my.
You didn't see a ghost, did you?
-No, no ghost.
Something about that boy.
He's an insei.
I suppose I'll have
to keep it on him.
-Honinbo's one of the
major titles that's
been passed down for
generations and generations.
-It started in the
early Showa period.
After the first
tournament, the winner
started to give himself
the name Honinbo,
and then the tradition sort
of carried on from there.
-Huh.
-You've heard of some of
the other titles, right?
Like Meijin and Oza?
Well, the Honinbo
is like that, only
it's older than
the rest of them.
-So that old guy
calls himself Honinbo?
-I'm not sure I like that.
-Ogata-sensei is challenging
Kuwabara for the Honinbo title
right now.
-Ogata-sensei is that good?
-They play the best of seven.
The series of matches are
spread out over a few weeks.
Ogata-sensei won the
first game the other day,
and round two is going to
be happening this week.
-Anyone who wants
to try and challenge
the Honinbo for
the title has to go
through two years of
preliminary matches
before they get a
chance at the big one.
-No way!
It takes two years?
-You really don't
have a clue, do you?
Ever thought about
doing a bit of research
into the world of go?
-I can do all that
once I've turned pro.
-With that attitude,
he might just make it.
-I need to keep playing.
I know I can become stronger.
I know it.
I have to.
-Hm.
Hikaru, you should have played
a large knight's move there, not
a small one.
-A large knight's move?
But you've been telling
me that I should always
use a small one.
-They're both very similar,
but the large knight's move
involves a slightly
more advanced technique.
So up to now, I've encouraged
you to use the small knight's
move because it makes it easier
to predict what will happen
in the game and reduces
the opportunity for error.
Now, if you use the
large knight's move,
it makes things
more complicated,
and you have to plan
your game accordingly.
-OK.
-Hikaru, I think you're ready to
take on that sort of challenge
now.
-Right.
Hm.
-Why the hesitation?
-I am getting
stronger, aren't I?
-Yes, you are.
Since the Young Lions, you've
been playing at a higher level.
Why do you ask?
-I was thinking about Akira.
It's kind of weird,
knowing that we're
both playing in the
same room as each other.
I'm in there playing on Sundays
and every other Saturday,
but as a pro, he's in there
on Wednesdays or Thursdays.
Even though we never
actually see each other,
I can feel his presence
there in the room with me.
It's like a fire burning
inside pushing me on.
I've gotta work
really hard on my game
so I can pass the pro exam!
-Yes, summer will be
here before we know it.
-You bet.
And then I'll get my
chance to play Toya.
-Hokkaido, here I come.
-Good evening, Ogata.
-Have you just arrived?
-Yes, that's right.
It's so easy to travel
to Hokkaido nowadays.
Here's an idea.
Why don't we skip
the prematch ceremony
and go for a night on the
town, just the two of us?
-No thanks.
I'm afraid I'm not
really interested.
-You're no fun at all.
-Oh, look, honey, that's
Kuwabara, the championship
go player.
-That's nice.
I've never heard of him.
-Excuse me!
I don't suppose you've got a
pen and paper you could borrow,
do you?
-Come on, dear,
don't be so childish.
-How can you think
of going out when
we got two days of
matches ahead of us?
-You need to lighten up.
Stop taking things so seriously.
-Sorry to interrupt, but
aren't you Kuwabara Honinbo?
-Yes, that's me.
What can I do for you?
-I was wondering if
you'd be willing to let
me have your autograph.
I'm such a big fan.
It would mean so much to me
if you would do me the honor.
-If an old guy like me is
getting all this attention,
it doesn't say much for the
future of go, does it, now?
Wouldn't you agree, Ogata?
-Ogata?
-How's this?
I hope it's all right.
-Thank you.
Thank you!
-Now, Ogata, you may have
beaten me in the first match,
but I won't allow
it to happen again.
Anyone who tries to take the
title of Honinbo away from me
will find this old man won't
give up without a fight.
-Kuwabara-sensei,
there is a new wave
about to sweep the world of go.
-What do you mean?
-I can feel it coming.
The next generation is
coming up through the ranks.
A wave of new young pros.
-Huh?
Is that so?
-I want to be there when
this wave crashes on shore.
I want to be there to take them
on as the holder of the Honinbo
title.
-Excuse me, gentlemen.
All the preparations for the
ceremony are now complete.
If you would please follow me?
-All this talk of
waves means I've
lost my chance to sneak
out and enjoy myself.
-Hey, everyone.
-Hi.
Did you hear the
latest news yet?
Akira Toya has
moved up to 2-dan.
-What?
Already?
Oh, wow.
It won't be too long.
I'm gonna catch up
to you, Akira Toya.
Just you wait.
-Yes!
And he resigns!
One more win for Waya.
Shindo's game has improved
a lot since the Young Lions
Tournament.
I'm gonna have to make sure
I don't let my guard down.
Kadowaki?
-You sure about that?
The same guy who held
the Student Meijin
title, the Student Honinbo
title, and the Student Joketsu
title at the same time?
That Kadowaki?
-You've got it.
He's the same guy, all right.
Everyone was talking
about him back then.
What's he up to now?
-According to the
rumors on the internet,
he's going to take the pro exam.
[theme song]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
This Kadowaki guy
sounds like someone we
need to watch out for.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Well, he certainly
has an impressive reputation.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Just
like Kuwabara Honinbo,
out to defend his title.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Ogata-sensei has made it
through to the seventh and
final game of the series.
The decider!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Next
time, Ogata vs. the Honinbo!
SAI (VOICEOVER): It
looks like you've
got a fight on your
hands in the pro exam.