[music playing]
[theme music]
-I want to know your name.
-Ah.
-Tell me.
What's your name?
I need to know
what your name is.
-My name's Hikaru Shindo.
Hope you remember it.
-Hikaru Shindo.
I got it.
-Shindo.
I won't forget your name.
It'll stay in my memory forever.
Hikaru Shindo.
[rain falling]
[train whistle]
-Well, Sai, the pro exam
is finally going to start.
-That's right.
-I have to pass this exam.
Otherwise, there's no way
I'll catch up to Toya.
-Hm.
-Hey, Shindo.
-Hi there, Waya.
-You've got to calm
yourself, Hikaru.
-Yeah. Yeah.
I know.
-Is everything OK?
You're looking
really tense today.
-I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
-It's OK to be nervous.
We're all a bit that way.
-Morning, guys.
-Morning, Fuku.
-We can put our drinks
in this fridge, right?
-You think it's OK to
keep my sandwich in there?
-Don't see why not.
-Hi, Shindo.
-Good to see you, Isumi.
-Hey kiddo, long time no see.
-Oh no.
It's you.
-Hey, show some respect
for your elders.
-Yes, Mr. Tsubaki.
I'm sorry.
-That's better.
I guess that must be the guy
that Shindo was so afraid of.
-Yeah, looks like it.
-So are you glad you made it
through to the finals, kiddo?
-Uhh.
-Well?
-Hm.
-What you looking at?
[groaning]
-Hm?
-Actually, now that
I think about it,
you're not as ugly as Mr. Kawai.
-What's that?
Who's Mr. Kawai?
-Mr. Kawai is the one who
always does this to me.
-What do you think you're doing?
You should be
messing up his hair.
Not mine.
-I'm way too scared of
Mr. Kawai to do it to him.
[laughing]
-But when it comes
to playing Go,
you're a much stronger
player than Mr. Kawai is ever
going to be.
-Well, nice of you to recognize
talent when you see it.
I'm looking forward
to playing you, kiddo.
Because I just can't wait to
beat you again. [laughing]
-What makes you
think you're going
to win so easily this time?
-Hikaru.
-Say what you want.
It won't make any difference.
IIJIMA (VOICEOVER):
Shindo's changed
since I saw him
play in the prelims.
-If anyone wants to order
themselves a box lunch,
we've got a sign-up
sheet over here.
-Oh.
What have they got?
-Don't know.
Let's see.
-Just make sure you put your
order in by 10:00 o'clock.
-You having some?
-Nah.
I brought my own lunch.
My mom packed it for me.
-Hm.
-Hikaru, you're not intimidated
by gorilla man at all now.
I know I thought if I
give him some attitude,
it would take my
mind off the test,
and I wouldn't be so nervous.
-Such a magnificent strategy.
-OK.
Let's go and check
out the room where
I'll be playing the matches.
-Lead on.
[clock ticking]
-The finals are played as
a round robin tournament,
with matches taking
place three days
a week on Tuesdays,
Saturdays, and Sundays.
It lasts for over two months.
This year, there's 28 finalists.
-Do you have to draw
for your opponent
like you did in the
preliminary rounds?
-Yeah, that's right.
But only the top three
players pass the exam.
-Only the top three?
-Look.
That's one of the guys that
beat me in the prelims.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI
(VOICEOVER): Hikaru
is more prepared for these
matches than he was before.
Hikaru, your heart is
racing like a warrior
about to go into battle.
In your battle with Su-Young,
you gave it everything you had
and you were victorious.
The confidence you
gained in that match
has made you anxious to compete
again and prove your skills.
-Hello, Shindo.
-Huh.
Hey, Iijima.
-I heard that you got through
to the finals with a buy.
Pretty close call, huh.
-So what if it was a buy?
I made it through, didn't I?
Same as everybody else.
ANNOUNCER (ON LOUDSPEAKER):
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time to begin.
Everyone please make their
way to the match room.
-All right.
We're going to be drawing
names for the matches.
Please come forward when
your names are called.
Nakamura.
-Here.
-Next, Hayashi.
HAYASHI: Here.
-Sasaki.
SASAKI: Here.
-I'm number four.
-Nakamura, number four.
We need you to keep hold
of your piece of paper.
OFFICIAL: Shindo.
-Over here.
We only draw numbers
on the first day.
After that, all the
pairings have been preset.
I pick number seven.
Once you have your number,
you play everyone else
in the order that's
on the pairing chart.
And my opponent on the first
day is going to be Iijima.
-I got Shindo.
-Each player will have
three hours for the game.
Overtime is one minute per move.
White has a five and
a half point Komi.
And now, let's begin.
-Onegaishimasu.
-Ah, the lunches.
I better start putting
the orders through.
Huh, let's see.
Hm.
Where's he going?
They've only been
playing for five minutes.
[sigh]
-Just trying to keep the
nerves under control.
And another one?
[motorcycle revving]
-This sort of thing never
happens during a regular match.
I suppose it is a pro exam.
The stakes are much higher.
-Is there something
the matter, sir?
-I think the level of
nervous tension in here
is starting to get to me.
I don't think I can stand
and watch them anymore.
I'm going to go and hang
out in the staff lounge
until the lunch break.
-All right.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): I'm not
just here to pass the exam.
My goal is to finish as
the number one player.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
It's finally begun.
The pro exam is going
to be a tough battle.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Only three
people can pass the test.
NASE (VOICEOVER): I
have to take my time.
HONDA (VOICEOVER): This
year is going to be my year.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
How can he be so calm?
Is it because I'm his opponent,
or is it because he got
used to the exam?
Whatever it is, he's
completely different from when
he was playing in the prelims.
I have to start out
strong from day one.
The pro exam only comes
around once a year.
-It's time for the
lunch break, everybody.
So please stop your clocks.
[chatter]
-Hey, kiddo.
You ready to go for lunch.
-I already told you.
I've got my own lunch.
-Hey, don't get smart with me.
-Those two look like
they're getting along.
Hikaru's not scared
of him at all.
-I bet you it's
because we took him
to play all those
matches in the Go salons.
-In the Go salons?
-He said he'd never played
in one before, so we thought,
why not?
Isumi and I decided
to let him practice
at a couple of different places.
-But he's your
competition, and you just
made him a lot stronger.
-Those destined to become
strong will become strong
no matter what you do.
That's what Morishita
Sensei keeps telling us.
-But that's no reason
to go out of your way
to help him right
before the pro exam.
How could you be so stupid?
-We weren't being
stupid, were we?
I mean my sensei told me I've
gotten much better since we
started hanging out
with Shindo at the study
sessions and stuff.
-Yeah.
I guess I can see
the connection.
Your game has
definitely improved
since we've been helping out.
-Oh really?
I'm playing well right now.
I mean I can feel it.
This year's the year
I'm going to pass.
Hey, you want to go check
out the pairings chart?
-Now, when am I playing Shindo?
Here it is.
Right near the very end
on the second to last day.
Looks like me and you are
playing in match 13, Isumi.
-And I'm playing Shindo
right before I play you.
Shindo in match 12,
and you in match 13.
WAYA: Cool.
-What Iijima said
about Shindo, you
think we did the wrong
thing, helping him?
-Well if Shindo does
manage to pass the exam
and we don't, we will
look pretty stupid.
[chatter]
-I think that's
everyone, so let's begin.
[groaning]
-Good game.
I resign.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
[sigh] There's
a total of 27 matches
to play, so I shouldn't
get too excited
about a single win.
-Hikaru, your attitude is
really starting to mature.
-I resign.
-Well, that's it.
It's over.
-I resign.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Time went by so fast
that school started up
again before I knew it.
And it's a win by six
and a half points.
-I resign. Thank you.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): The only
players undefeated so far are
me, Isumi, Waya,
[gasp] and Shindo.
It doesn't matter.
I'm still going to pass the test
without losing a single game.
-I resign.
-Thank you for the game.
-Looks like you've won.
-Only four people have
won all six games.
-Yeah.
-Isumi, Ochi, Waya, and Shindo.
-Waya seems to be
in really good form.
You've already played your
game against him, right?
He managed to beat both of us.
-I can understand Isumi and
Ochi six games in a row,
but Shindo's got be a fluke.
-It's still early on, so
I wouldn't worry too much.
Even if you lose
the first six, you
can still pass if
you win all the rest.
Besides, winning six in a row
isn't always a good thing.
A single defeat
after that could lead
to a collapse in confidence.
OK.
Time to go.
See you.
-Winning every game,
isn't always good?
How can it not be good?
I'm going to go
for a clean sweep.
-What's with him?
The pro exam's only just begun.
-Anything could happen.
But I can't believe
Shindo's winning streak's
going to carry on for long.
NASE: Iijima, you played
Shindo in the very first match,
didn't you?
So, uh, what did you think?
-He was really calm
and in control,
which I wasn't expecting,
and it threw me off.
I think that's why lost.
Something's changed about him.
You'll see what I mean when
it's your turn to play.
It wouldn't surprise
me if he actually
ends up passing the exam.
-Hm.
-Instead of attacking white
with a knight's move here,
you could use the
diagonal and then
be in a much stronger position.
-Yeah, I see.
-Well I'd better be going now.
-Thank you very much
for coming to see us.
I thought Iwasaki 7-dan
was easy to understand.
He'd be a much better teacher
for you than that Kujiari
8-dan guy who came yesterday.
He was so awful.
Tell me.
How on earth did
someone as young
as you get so good
at playing Go?
I remember when I used
to invite pros over
to play teaching games and
you used to sit and watch us.
You must have picked up a lot
of good hints from watching
those sessions,
because it wasn't long
before you were beating me.
[beep]
-And look at us now.
Here I am inviting pros
around to help you study.
Oh, hello there.
It's me.
Can you bring in some whiskey
and water to go with it?
I can't tell you how proud
I am that my grandson wants
to be a pro player.
Your father was useless.
He wouldn't even
touch the stones.
I'm going to take you to
Go salons to practice.
I'll get pros to
teach you every night.
I don't care how much it
costs if that's what you want.
If we do all that, do you
think you can pass the pro exam
and get the top score?
-Well, that's what
I'm aiming for.
In the last set of
rankings, before we
started to doing the
pro exam, I overtook
Isumi to become the
number one insei.
-Now, let's see.
We've already got different
pros booked in every night
this week.
But there's still
space next week for us
to invite Toya 2-dan over.
-Toya 2-dan?
-Last year, he finished with
the highest score of anyone
in the pro exam.
I was thinking it
might be useful to get
some tips from him, you
know, considering he recently
took the exam and he's
closer to your age.
His opinion is
probably going to be
more relevant than some
of these older pros.
Is it not a good idea?
-No.
It's OK.
I don't mind.
I've never played Toya 2-dan.
I've always wanted
the opportunity
to compete against him.
Once I pass the test
and become a pro,
we'll both be ranked at
about the same level.
So the two of us will be rivals.
-Huh.
Six straight wins.
Shindo!
He's won six games in a row.
It doesn't mean anything.
There's a long way to go before
the pro exam is finished.
It's only six wins so
far, but there's still
only four people who've got this
far without dropping a game.
And Shindo was
one of those four.
Just how good is he?
I have to know.
AKIRA'S MOTHER: Akira, someone
from the Go Association's
on the phone for you.
-Uh-huh, they want me to give
him lessons at their home.
Well, no, I'm not that
busy, but I-- would you
mind telling them no for me.
It's just that I need to
spend time concentrating
on my own game right now.
I hope they understand.
Yes.
Thank you.
What?
He's an insei.
Why didn't you say he
was an insei before?
And he's in the middle
of the pro exam.
I'll do it.
Yes.
Can you set it up for me?
Shindo.
This is going to be my chance
to see exactly where you're at.
[theme music]
HIKARU: Can you believe it?
Akira's agreed to
be a tutor for Ochi.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: He must
sense you right behind him.
HIKARU: The guys don't
think I'm going to make it.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: One
game at a time, Hikaru.
One game at a time.
HIKARU: I've got
him in my sights.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: Don't let
yourself get carried away now.
You have to pass the test first.
Remember.
HIKARU: Next time,
the challengers.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI:
You're not the only one
who will be disappointed if
you don't make it through.