NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past
known as Fujiwara-no-Sai
has returned, visible
only to Hikaru Shindou.
A master of Go, Sai seeks
to play the Divine Move.
[theme music]
-Huh?
Doesn't that guy play for Kaio?
Do you have some
free time right now?
-Uh.
-Hello.
How are you doing, Kishimoto?
-Fine, thanks.
Grab a seat, and
I'll be right there.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I
wonder what's going on?
He said he wanted to
find out some stuff.
Maybe this is about those couple
of games I had with Akira.
I still don't get why he
brought me to a Go salon.
He could've talked to
me in the bookstore.
Oh no!
I totally forgot to get
that textbook for my class!
So, are you going to
tell me why I'm here?
-I want to see how
strong you really are.
-Huh?
-Let's get started.
-Those two kids really know
how to play a game of Go.
You, uh, know either of them?
-See that taller boy over there?
That's Kishimoto.
He's an amazing player.
You should try and see if
he'll play you a game later.
-Yeah, that kid's pretty good,
but what about the shorter boy?
He might actually be
the stronger of the two.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): You
want to see how good I am?
Fine.
I don't need Sai.
I've practiced long enough
to show you a thing or two.
I'm way better than I was
at the last tournament.
-I'd say you're about as
strong as our co-captain.
This exchange was
a really good play.
Those weren't impulsive moves.
You have the patience
not to rush the game.
-(VOICEOVER) Kaio's first
just gave me a compliment?
-I still don't understand why
Toya considered you his rival.
You're not even
close to his level.
I wonder if there's
something else about you
that I haven't noticed.
-I don't know.
I think Akira just
overestimated how good I
was at the tournament last year.
I guess that's why he
got so disappointed when
he saw my true ability.
-Oh really?
There's got to be more
to the story than that.
There must be something
about you that intrigues him.
Let me give you a
piece of advice.
You should go after Toya.
-Huh?
Uh.
Oh yeah.
I-- I'm going to play
him again eventually.
I'll catch up to him one day.
-There is a big gap
between you and him.
-Wha--
-And I'm not talking about
your differences in strength.
I'm talking about how passionate
you are in pursuing your goals.
Toya is more determined
than you are.
You didn't see what he was
like in the Kaio Go club.
He went after you with every
ounce of energy he had.
He wasn't gonna
let you get away.
You're running out of time.
If you wait too long, you'll
never catch up to him.
One more thing.
Toya's already
passed the pro exam.
-Is that really true, Kishimoto?
-Let me get this straight.
You're talking about
Akira Toya, right?
-Yes.
-I thought the pro exam took
almost two months to complete.
He won't be finished until
the end of the month.
-I'm just repeating
what my sensei told me.
Toya's pro career
begins next April.
I wonder how he'll do.
Maybe he'll get
lucky win a title.
-A pro?
Nah, he's way too young.
An eighth grader
can't become a pro.
-A lot of top players were only
teenagers when they turned pro.
Many of them passed the
exam while they're still
in junior high.
You seem surprised.
-Of course, most people don't
really know much about that.
-The world of Go is full
of unusual surprises.
-What about school?
-Pros don't go if
there's a game scheduled.
-No way, they skip classes.
Don't their teachers care?
-Good one, kid.
-A pro?
He sure doesn't waste any time.
I can't believe it.
He's still a kid.
I mean, I figured he would get
through the pro exam some time,
but I didn't think it
would be this soon.
I always thought you had to be
a lot older to become a pro.
-A lot older?
You better start
chasing after him.
Toya's getting farther
and farther away from you.
He officially becomes
a pro next spring,
and he's sure to advance
faster than anyone else.
If you wait until then,
it'll be too late.
If you don't put your
all into it right now,
you'll never catch up to him.
-Right.
I wish I could've found out
about this stuff sooner.
I just thought that, as long
as I kept on playing Go,
I would eventually
catch up to Akira.
-You're not taking this thing
seriously, you know that?
I'm actually more disappointed
than I am surprised.
Before the tournament, Toya
was going all out after you.
What were you doing?
Well, it doesn't
matter to me that much.
You mind if we end this game?
Sorry to take up so
much of your time.
-Hate to interrupt your game.
Can I get you another
cup of coffee?
-No thanks.
I should get going.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Everybody thinks
that Akira was chasing me,
but he was really after Sai.
I'm playing with
everything I got,
and it's the best
I can do right now.
MAN: If Toya's already
passed, does that
mean he won all his matches?
MAN: He had one
loss, but that was
because he didn't
show up for a game.
MAN: He forfeited?
-Yeah.
He skipped the first day.
It was the last Sunday
in August, I think.
He must have had something
pretty important to do.
MAN: He missed the first exam?
No way.
You gotta be kidding.
-The last Sunday in August?
That's the day we played online.
KISHIMOTO (VOICEOVER): I'm not
talking about your differences
in strength.
I'm talking about how passionate
you are in pursuing your goals.
-Wait a sec!
What do I have to do
to take the pro exam?
-Huh?
-The exam only takes
place once a year.
You'll have to wait until next
summer if you want to take it.
-Listen.
I don't think you're
strong enough to pass it.
-Maybe you should
become an Insei first.
Do you know them?
They're at the Japan
Go Association.
-Yeah.
You should study with
other strong players,
and then take the exam.
-Let me just say this.
You're still not good
enough to become an Insei.
You need to train more.
SAI: Hikaru.
MAN (VOICEOVER): You have
to pass a special test
before you can become an Insei.
The test happens
four times a year.
The next one's in December.
How does it work, again?
I think you play a
game against a pro,
when he judges your ability.
Hm.
And, of course, you
don't pass if you're just
an average player.
BOY (VOICEOVER) Hikaru.
KISHIMOTO (VOICEOVER): Toya
is getting farther and farther
away from you.
He officially becomes
a pro next spring,
and he's sure to advance
faster than anyone else.
-What's the matter?
-Nothing.
-Your friend made it
seem like becoming
an Insei was impossible.
-Who cares if it's impossible?
I am not giving up.
-What was that?
-There's a huge gap
between me and Akira.
I finally see that now.
If I really do want
to catch up to him,
I'll have to ace
that Insei test.
And then I'll have to
beat all the Insei.
I'm going to be a pro.
I'm going to pass the exam
without losing a single match.
I've made up my mind.
I'm not giving up.
I don't care what
Kishimoto says.
Akira didn't stop chasing
you, and I'll never
stop chasing him.
Akira was shaking
at the tournament
because he was
intimidated by you.
But he refused to back down.
-You're right.
It's not impossible.
Not at all.
If you pursue Akira with every
ounce of strength you have,
you'll catch him.
Hikaru, we've been here
before, haven't we?
HIKARU: We came here to
watch that kid's tournament,
remember?
-What an impressive school.
This must be the place
where the Insei study Go.
-Do you think it would be
fun to take classes here?
-There's probably
a bunch of mean
looking guys like Kishimoto.
-Don't get down.
You'll make plenty of
friends and rivals.
And they'll both
help you improve.
-I've got find out
how to take that test.
I'll worry about all
that other stuff later.
-These are the steps must
take to get closer to Akira.
Now, let's get started.
-All right!
Follow me, Sai!
-Hikaru!
Look at these artificial fish!
They're just like the
ones we saw before.
They're so realistic,
aren't they?
I wonder how they were made.
I'll never get tired
of watching them.
-You're driving me nuts!
-So you want to take
the December Insei test?
You don't mean the examine we're
having this Sunday, do you?
We're no longer
accepting applications.
Sorry.
-But you gotta be joking.
I want to take that test
as soon as possible.
-I'm afraid I can't help you.
Don't worry, there'll be
another test next March.
-I came all the way here
because I wanted to be an Insei.
Come on.
-My hands are tied.
HIKARU: Akira's getting further
and further away from me!
-There's no need to get upset.
I'm just trying to do my job.
HIKARU: Please, can't
you do this for me?
I won't tell anyone.
-I know that boy.
-I can't break the rules.
I'm sure you can
understand that.
-What's the problem?
-Ogata-sensei.
-Who's he?
Do I know this guy?
I think I've seen him before.
-The boy insists on
taking the Insei test
so he can enroll in January.
-Is that so?
Hm.
-He just showed up
here a few minutes ago.
I already told him the
application deadline
has passed.
The boy didn't bring any
game records with him,
and he doesn't have
a sponsor, either.
-I'm sorry to interrupt,
but we've got to get going.
-I've met this boy before.
I will sponsor him.
Please allow him
to take the test.
-I'll give him the forms.
-Thank you.
-What's that kid's
story, Ogata-sensei?
-I've been asking
myself the same thing.
-Huh?
-(VOICEOVER) I'm finally going
to learn the truth about him.
HIKARU: Now I
remember who he is!
-Huh?
-It's him.
He was the same guy I
saw with Akira Toya.
-Please, keep it down.
We don't want to disturb
the other people.
-Aw, sorry.
-(VOICEOVER) This
boy is unbelievable.
Why did Ogata-sensei
insist on sponsoring him?
All right.
This is your Insei
application form.
Please fill it out carefully.
On the day of your
exam, you'll need
to bring it back, along with a
resume and three of your game
records.
There's also an application
fee and a game fee.
You'll have to pay both
before taking the test.
One more thing.
You have to bring
a parent with you.
-Ah!
I gotta pay a bunch of fees,
and bring my mom or dad?
-That's right.
-Got that?
-Let's see.
An application, a resume,
and three game records?
What's a game record?
-You mean you don't know?
-What's wrong?
-This boy wants to
become an Insei,
and he doesn't know
what a game record is.
-Is this some kind of joke?
Why don't you just
tell him to go home?
-I can't.
I told Ogata-sensei
I'd help him.
He's sponsoring the boy.
-Huh?
Ogata-sensei's his sponsor?
-What is a game record?
Boring.
I've gotta use these
forms to record my games.
How am I supposed
to fill these out?
Man.
It's just like doing homework.
Hm.
Yuuki and Kimihiro know
how to do all this.
I'm sure they can help me out.
-You can finally
see the road ahead.
I'm proud of you.
-You're absolutely right.
Hm.
I've started getting
closer to Akira.
-Good news.
I found a new member
for our Go club.
-That's awesome, Yuuki.
-Thanks, man.
Do you want to meet him?
-How's it going, everyone?
YUUKI: Natsume and I
are in the same class.
He says he knows how to play.
-I had my first game
of Go this summer.
I guess that makes me a rookie.
-Now Haze Middle will be able
to play in the tournament
even if Kimihiro is too busy.
-Yep.
We've got our team.
-What's up, guys?
-Who's that?
AKARI: Is he really
gonna join our club?
You'll have enough players
for the tournament!
-And we're not just gonna
enter the tournaments.
Hikaru is 10 times better
than he used to be.
And with him and me,
we're going to win.
We can throw the top game.
We'll still pick
up two wins if we
play in the number two and
number three positions.
-Kaio won't know what hit 'em.
I hope.
-What's so funny.
Are you guys telling
jokes, or something?
-Guess again.
-Hold on.
I don't know this guy.
Is he a new member?
-That's right.
Haze Middle School is gonna have
a boy's team and a girl's team
competing this year.
Isn't that amazing?
-I didn't know about this.
-You have a third player?
-Yeah.
You already met her.
Hikaru brought her in.
She said she would
play for us if she
got to compete in
the tournaments.
-I totally forgot about her.
At least now there'll
be an experienced player
on the girl's team.
-See, th three.
I told you so.
-Akari, am I gonna have to
play in the tournament, too?
-That's the plan.
-Wait a minute!
-I've got something that
you'll want to read.
-Hm?
-Take a look at this.
There's an article in here
that I could hardly believe.
It said that Akira Toya
just passed pro exam.
-Huh.
Oh, yeah?
-What's with you?
I thought you'd be surprised.
-Is that your news?
Kaio's captain already
told me all about it.
-You were talking
with Kishimoto?
Where did you see that creep?
-The mall.
We ran into each other
in the bookstore.
I guess it was
about a month ago.
He said Akira was going to
start his pro career sometime
next April.
[sigh]
-Know what else?
I've decided that I don't
want to lose to that guy.
That's the reason I've
been studying Go every day.
-I get it now.
You've been pushing yourself.
That explains why
you've improved.
-Thanks.
I guess you're right.
I've grown a lot.
I bet I'm good enough
to take that Insei test.
-Insei?
-You're kidding, right?
-Pretty cool, huh?
Don't look so shocked.
I've got to do this.
Kishimoto said I
need to get serious,
or I'll never catch up to Akira.
Anyway, they asked me to
bring three game records
on the day of my test.
Do you guys know how to
fill in one of these forms?
Kimihiro, you'll help me, right?
Uh, what's wrong with you guys?
-Have you thought this through?
-Hm?
-You wanna be an
Insei, that's fine,
but you won't be allowed to
compete in amateur tournaments.
-What?
-Hikaru?
-Hm.
Now you know.
At least you didn't waste
your time on that test.
Now, let's forget about all
this Insei stuff, shall we?
Come on.
Well play a game.
-Uh.
-What's going on?
Hikaru?
-You need to choose.
It's us or them.
You'd have to quite the Go club.
Are you prepared to do that?
[theme music]
SAI: Are you going to
stay in the Go club?
HIKARU: It's a tough
decision, but I
know I gotta give Kimihiro
and Yuuki an answer.
SAI: Kaga has his own opinions
on what you should do.
HIKARU: I don't even know if
I'm good enough to an Insei yet.
SAI: They can help you find out.
HIKARU: Really?
Next time, the Haze
Middle School Go club.
SAI: They'll challenge
you to a game
unlike any you've had before.