[theme music]
-I'd love to win a title!
Kurata Meijin's got a nice
ring to it, don't you think?
Maybe that's how I'll sign
my autograph, Meijin to be!
There.
-Who's he?
-Ask him, Hikaru.
-Excuse me.
What's your name?
-Don't you know who I am?
Atsushi Kurata,
professional Go player.
Soon to be the Meijin,
or the Honinbo.
The ones to watch out for
are the younger players
still coming up the ranks.
That's why I'm more afraid of
Akira Toya than his father.
The games I play against
those ranked below me
will be life and death battles.
I gotta go, but I'm
gonna remember your name.
The kid who's an expert on
Honinbo Shusaku's handwriting.
HIKARU: In the Shincho Dan
series, Ochi won his game,
but Waya lost.
-Hm.
HIKARU: And then, in March--
-What?
You've got to be kidding me!
-Waya!
Noise the noise down.
-You won't believe this, Sensei.
Shindou said he's never
heard of the Otayai.
-Oh really?
You haven't heard
of them before?
-It's obviously some
sort of big game.
So why don't you
just tell me, Waya?
-Some sort of big game?
-You're so clueless!
Do I have to tell
you everything?
You couldn't even
do the timekeeping
until I showed you how.
-How am I supposed to
know unless you tell me?
-The Otayai are
the games you play
as part of the Dan
promotion league.
-You managed to become
a pro without ever
learning about this?
-You have to admit, the way
Shindou's progressing so fast
is pretty amazing.
-Yeah.
I remember when he first started
coming to my Go study sessions.
And now take a look at him.
-He did have an
excellent teacher
to guide him along the way.
-Oh really?
-Well, I'm glad both of
you passed the pro exam.
That should keep the
rest of us on our toes.
But now you'll only meet
lower ranked players
in your Otayai games
and the qualifiers.
It'll be good
experience for you.
-Just a sec.
What's this Dan promotion
leage you were talking about?
-As a pro, you'll play about
10 Otayai matches each year.
They use those results to
determine your ranking.
Saeki here is a Four-Dan.
Suzuki and myself
are both Seven-Dan.
-I'm gonna be a Five-Dan soon.
-Hey there, Saeki.
Toya's student Eshiwari
is a Four-Dan, too.
You better make it to
Five-Dan before him.
-What's the big
deal with us having
to beat Toya Meijin's
students all the time?
-Every year starts with
the Otayai matches,
but the real fun
begins in the summer.
That's when we start playing
the qualifying rounds for all
the different titles.
You end playing two,
maybe three games a month.
-Is that all?
Doesn't seem like
very much to me.
-If you make it through
the first few rounds,
then you're gonna have
to play a lot more.
Take Akira Toya for example.
He's already through
to the second round
in both the Honinbo and
Meijin championships.
He's gonna be
playing more games,
and my guess is he's gonna
be the center of attention.
-All right! everyone listen up!
Stop Akira Toya at all costs!
-Come on, Saeki.
You should know better than
to mention Toya's students
in front of the sensei here.
-Are you sure you really
wanna wear a suit?
-Mom, it's OK.
This is gonna be a big day.
It's the new One-Dan certificate
preservation ceremony.
-You mean presentation ceremony.
It just doesn't look right,
you wearing a suit and tie.
You're still at school, and
a suit looks so grown up.
-Ochi's still in
middle school like me.
So's Toya.
They'll both be dressed up.
-Oh.
What are you kidding
yourself into?
I'm really worried about you.
Do you have your
health certificate
and resume with you?
HIKARU: Yeah.
Oh, by the way,
Mr. Saeki said I'll
need to open a bank account.
-A bank account?
Oh, OK.
Uh, is that for when
you start getting paid?
-That's right.
I don't think it'll
happen straightaway.
And I'll also have
to file tax returns.
-Tax returns?
HIKARU: Waya!
Hey.
-You're on time, for a change.
-Huh?
If it isn't Hikaru Shindou.
-Hello, Mr. Kurata.
-No, you cannot
have my autograph!
You missed your chance.
-I still don't want
your autograph.
-Hmph.
Ha.
-Mr. Kurata.
-So, how do you and
Kurata know each other?
-I met him a while ago at
an amateur Go festival.
I thought he was really weird.
Do you know him?
He's not important, is he?
-He had the most wins last year,
and he played the most games.
-Him?
The most wins?
-You got it.
Lots of the players are here
today to receive awards.
Player of the year is
going to Toya Meijin,
then there'll be all
sorts of other awards.
Female player of
the year and so on.
Akira Toya's won the award
for best percentage of wins,
and also one for the
most consecutive wins.
-He's gonna be here?
With two awards?
-The big awards are the real
reason everyone's come to this.
Our certificates are just extra.
-I see.
-Oh, come on.
You should be proud of yourself.
Don't forget, it
was only a year ago
when Akira was standing
where you are now.
-Yeah, but that's different.
-How do you think Akira
advanced to the level he's at?
He was focusing on
one game at a time.
-Got to take it
one game at time.
-You OK, Shindou?
-I wonder who my first
opponent's going to be.
I can't wait to find out.
-That's the spirit.
Just one step at a time.
-Maybe it'll be me.
-Hm?
-Then again, your
opponent doesn't
have to be a One-Dan at all.
It could be a Two-Dan,
or even a Three-Dan.
-It's Toya.
I can't believe it.
I have finally made it.
We're both pros now.
I wonder what he
thinks about that.
Toya!
Over here!
Finally we--
-That guy is such a jerk.
Who does he think
he is, ignoring you?
He makes me so mad.
Thinks he's better than
us 'cause he's doing OK.
Well, I guess he's
doing better than OK.
Darn.
-Hey, guys.
-Hi.
-What's the matter with you?
-I wont just catch up to him.
I'll be better than him.
Mr. High and Mighty.
-There he is.
-Huh?
Ah, Toya.
Have you seen the pairings
for the Otayai yet?
The office should have
sent them out by now.
Maybe you didn't get your copy.
You'll never guess who your
first opponent is going to be.
-I know.
-Uh, testing, testing.
In a few moments, we will
begin the awards ceremony
and the presentation
of certificates
to the new One-Dan players.
If everyone could please start
making their way to the--
[applause]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I'm
going to catch up to him.
And I'm going to
be better than him.
-Well, there's not
much else to go over.
The association is glad to
welcome the three of you.
MAN: Now, if you'll open up
the packages in front of you,
we can go through each of the
items and explain them to you.
-This is cool.
The Otayai pairings
chart, right?
-Yes, that's right.
It's a list of all
the Otayai opponents
you'll be facing
in the year ahead.
-Huh?
Where am I in here?
-Near the end of the list.
-The name of your first opponent
can be found immediately
to the right of your own name.
-Now, let's see.
Shindou.
Yeah, here we are.
My first opponent is
going to be-- Toya?
(VOICEOVER) My first
opponent is going to be Toya?
MAN: We'll be sending
you confirmation
of the actual dates
of your games,
but lower ranked players
usually play on Wednesdays.
-Akira Toya.
MAN: The higher ranked players
meet on Thursdays, so make sure
you keep your Wednesdays
free for the future.
-Your first game against Toya.
You couldn't ask
for a better start.
-Do you think he
knows about this?
-Yes.
He's declared war on you.
Think back.
You saw that look in his
eyes as he walked past.
It appears he already knew
he was going to play you.
He's preparing himself for
the long awaited battle.
Here's your chance to
show him your strength.
Are you ready, Hikaru?
-Yes, I'm ready!
-Hm?
-Just you wait, Toya!
-Although you
forced me to resign
in the first game, Sensei, now
we're even at one win each.
-I'm already looking
forward to our third game.
HIKARU: Hi, Mom!
I'm home!
MITSUKO: Hikaru,
you've some mail here
from the Go association.
HIKARU: Huh?
SAI: It's finally happening.
-Yeah.
My game's on April the 4th.
My first game as a
pro-- against Toya.
Huh?
Mr. Saeki?
-You're late.
-No, I'm not.
There's half an hour
to go before it starts.
-I got here early, just for you.
I figured it might
help calm your nerves
to have a friendly face around.
-Oh.
I remember on my first day, I
got here hours ahead of time.
When we actually
started playing,
I was so nervous my
fingers could hardly
pick up the stones.
That doesn't seem to be
the case with you, Shindou.
-It's not like I've never
met my opponent before.
I'm not really nervous.
Excited, yeah.
But I'm not nervous.
-You're playing Toya?
-Mm-hm.
(VOICEOVER) Doesn't look like
Waya or Ochi have games today.
-Shindou, what are
you doing for lunch?
-What?
-If you want to order
something, you do it over here.
-We can order food?
Wow.
-Or if you want, you
can eat out with us.
-Sure.
-The match room is set up
the same as when you're here
as an Insei, but
with one difference.
Tea is provided.
Although if you don't
want to drink tea,
they let you bring in your own
coffee, or whatever you want.
-Cool.
I guess that's another
benefit of being a pro.
So, who's your opponent
going to be today?
-A woman called Sakurano.
You seem a lot more
relaxed now, Shindou.
Which is good because you
were looking a little tense
when you first arrived.
-What?
You really think so?
-It's not good to be too
relaxed before a game, either.
So let me teach you a
little trick of mine.
-Kay.
-Get a picture of
Morishita in your mind.
-Stop Akira Toya at all costs!
-Oh, man.
That pressure's too intense!
-This is the moment
you've been waiting for.
You're a much
stronger player now.
You must be very excited.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I'm
ready for you, Toya.
-Huh?
Hikaru?
(VOICEOVER) This reminds
me of Akira the last time
they played.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
That was a while ago.
During the summer tournament.
The third round game between
Haze and Kaio Middle School.
Back then, Toya was
chasing after Sai.
Now I'm the one
chasing after Toya.
And I think I understand
what he was feeling.
What he was going
through at that moment.
SAI (VOICEOVER): You're about
to confront the opponent who
intimidates you the most.
You'll never know how
much I envy you right now.
I long for the day when I can
be in that position once again.
To face the one I fear the most.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): My
first professional game,
and this time you're
playing me, Toya.
Not Sai.
Me!
Where is he?
He's late.
[buzzer]
-Onegai shimasu.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Toya.
-Shindou.
May I have a word with you?
-Sure.
[heartbeats]
-Toya won't be able
to make it in today.
We just got a phone call.
The office is in a total panic.
Toya Meijin collapsed
and has been
rushed to the hospital
in an ambulance.
-No!
[theme music]
SAI: Toya Meijin has to stay
in the hospital for a while.
HIKARU: He's got a
computer with him
and it's connected
to the internet.
SAI: That means we could
have a game against him!
HIKARU: I don't know, Sai.
Last time we played online, we
almost got in a lot of trouble.
SAI: Please.
You must challenge him!
HIKARU: Next time.
The Acknowledgement of Sai.
SAI: This could be my
chance at the Divine Move!