NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past
known as Fujiwara-no-Sai
has returned, visible
only to Hikaru Shindou.
A master of Go, Sai seeks
to play the Divine Move.
[theme music]
-So, did you pass?
-Huh?
-Mm-hm.
-Any idea who this guy is, Waya?
-No, but I saw him
outside in the hall.
I overheard him say he
was gonna beat Akira Toya.
-Of course I am.
I'm his rival and he's mine.
Why would I make that up?
-But he's way better than you.
-I'll catch up to him someday.
You'll see.
-Aw.
All those losses.
Toya's so-called rival
has six straight losses
in the B league.
-Yeah, what's your point?
What's it got to do with you?
-Wait, I've got it.
Maybe you two are rivals
at playing Shogi, not Go.
[growling]
-Don't pay any attention to him.
You're getting stronger
all the time, Hikaru.
-And I guess your ranking's
a whole lot better?
-Take a look.
-Hm?
Let's see.
Waya, Waya.
What?
He's number six in the A league?
OK.
So you're pretty good.
-Sure, compared to you,
last place in the B league.
-But, you still lost
to Toya twice in a row.
-So what if he beat
me twice in a row?
I'm still way closer to
his level than you are.
But I'm not even on his radar.
He couldn't care
less if I exist.
-What are you talking about?
-Hm?
I'm just really
mad because I let
myself be intimidated
by him in the pro test.
It didn't matter
how good I played.
I mentally lost the
game before it started.
-Yeah.
I also got to play
against Toya once.
And I lost!
-What a surprise.
-Who cares about Akira Toya?
I'm just gonna rise to the top.
-Who was that?
-Ochi.
He's a kid from the sixth grade.
-Oh.
-He came here about a
year before you did,
and he started off at the bottom
of the B league, like you.
-What's his rank now?
-He's number three
in the A league.
-Third in the A league?
Whoa.
WAYA: I think he's planning to
take the pro exam this year.
I wanna pass the pro
exam this year as well.
If I can do that,
then I don't have
to go to my stupid high school.
-I guess you don't like
going to school, huh?
I hate it it's so
boring sitting around
in a class for hours
and hours every day.
-I hear that.
-I'll be in ninth grade when
I take the test next summer.
If I pass, I'll finish school
and begin life as a pro.
-I have to pass the
test this year too.
-Yeah?
How come?
-I'm going to be 18
pretty soon, and that's
the age limit for
being an Insei.
-But you don't have
to be an Insei.
You can still take the pro
exam right up until you're 30.
-Yeah, I know all that stuff,
but it's more about how I feel.
The last two years, I've gone
into the test as the number one
Insei and I still didn't pass.
-Hm.
-If I don't make it
this year, I don't
know if I wanna take it anymore.
-How many people
actually pass the test?
-Only three.
-What?
Three?
Is that all?
-You've got a long way to
go before you stand any sort
of chance, Mr.
Six-Losses-In-A-Row.
-He's right.
A long way.
MAN: I cut my losses there.
Now, if you look
carefully, this sequence
leaves black at a disadvantage.
-All right.
So you think I should focus on
going after those two stones
there?
MAN: Right.
You should extend here.
MAN: Then I could win the
match from that one move?
MAN: Um, probably.
-Probably?
What's your opinion on it, Toya?
Uh, Toya?
-Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
-What's the matter?
Too busy dreaming about
finally becoming a pro.
-No.
-I can't believe it's
finally happened.
Akira Toya turning professional.
-But I still don't
understand what
you thought you were doing
playing in a school Go club.
Any ideas, Ogata?
-I don't know, but he seemed
to have a lot more spirit
back then.
Go's more than just technique.
When there are two players with
a similar technical ability,
a game can often
be decided by which
one has the greater
mental strength.
And right now, Toya,
you just don't have it.
-Hey.
I don't think I'm any
different from before.
-I don't know about you
guys, but I've never
noticed a lack of spirit
when I've played him.
-Well, you wouldn't notice
because he beats you
all the time.
You play against him
every day Meijin.
You must be able to
tell the difference.
-Once he starts competing
professionally in April,
the results will
speak for themselves.
Ashiwara, I think you
should concentrate
on your own progress.
I'm surprised you haven't got
beyond the preliminary rounds
by now.
-Uh, yes sir.
-Hm.
-Do you have any
plans this Sunday?
-Uh.
-There's someone
I want you to see.
AKIRA: I wonder what he means.
-Hey, Shindou!
You actually won.
-Ha ha!
Yep, I did it.
-Your one and only win.
-My winning streak's
gonna start here.
-Hm?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Akira?
-Huh?
That's Toya.
What's he doing around here?
-Hey!
Hey, Toya.
Toya!
-What do you
think's up with him?
Maybe he's looking for an
instructor or something.
-Don't think so.
-Huh?
-He came here to check up on me.
-What are you talking about?
In case you didn't notice, he
just completely ignored you.
There's no way you
and him are rivals.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): He said
I'd never see him again.
But he's waiting for me.
He's waiting for me to
rise up to his level.
-You didn't know that
Hikaru had become an Insei.
-Is that what you
meant when you said
you wanted to show me something?
So what if he's managed
to become an Insei.
I really don't see what
that's got to do with me.
-I get the impression that
he's chasing after you, Akira.
-Ah, Akira Toya, you're here!
-Good afternoon.
-Oh, perfect timing.
Could we get an
interview with you?
I'm interested in your
thoughts on turning pro,
about your father,
that kind of thing.
-Sure, I don't mind.
-Come up to the PR
department when you're ready.
-I'll be right there.
-Appreciate it.
Nice to see you, Ogata-sensei.
-I guess I'll head up there now.
-OK.
I'm going to go home.
I just thought
seeing your friend
here might be a bit of
a motivation for you.
-Heh.
You think you're
funny, don't you?
How could he be a threat
to me at his level?
But even if it is true
that he's chasing after me,
I'll move so far ahead
of him that he'll never
catch up to me.
He won't even come close.
-Looks like he was all
the motivation you needed.
OGATA (VOICEOVER): It's gonna
be interesting having that kid
around.
I suppose he'll remain here
as an Insei for a while.
I can't wait to see
him competing as a pro.
That is, if he's good
enough to make it that far.
[surprised whispering]
-Imanishi.
Where are you going?
-Hey!
-You can't storm out like that
just because you lost a game.
-You were playing
Imanishi, right?
-Yeah.
-Did he make a big
mistake or something?
-Mm-hm.
Totally misread the game.
-I think he's just a bit on
edge because of his high school
entrance exam.
-Thanks, man.
-He said his grades
were going down.
-Makes sense.
Improve your game
or study for school.
I know which one I'd choose.
-That's fine if you
can make it as a pro,
but Imanishi's still
in the B league.
-No wonder he was so mad,
making a stupid mistake
and losing to
someone like Shindou.
-Thanks a lot.
Hey, Toya never seems to study
for school either, does he?
But he still got into Kaio,
so he must be really smart.
-Right.
Doesn't that make you mad?
-Not really.
Doesn't bother me.
-Well, it bothers me.
Then he goes and passes the
pro test on his first try.
He's gonna be playing in
the Shinsho Dan series soon.
HIKARU: Shinsho Dan?
What's that?
-You really don't have a
clue about anything, do you?
The Shinso Dan series
is where the guys who
just turned pro
play against the top
ranked veterans in the game.
-It's like a big
debut for the rookies.
-What a way to start.
-The new pros officially
begin in April,
but until then, they play
in the Shinsho Dan series.
-Oh.
-There was a really
good game last week
between Mashiba and
Kuwabara-sensei.
It was awesome to watch.
-Who's Mashiba?
-He used to be an Insei like us.
-Oh, so he's one of the
guys who actually passed
the test, unlike Waya and Isumi.
-You shut up!
-So, how did the
Mashiba game turn out?
-Kuwabara-sensei beat him
so easily, it was a joke.
-Oh, I see.
WAYA: Toya's debut game
should be coming up soon.
-He seems to be getting
further and further ahead of me
all the time.
WAYA: It's not just Toya.
Once they pass the test,
everyone who becomes a pro
gets way better.
And as long as we
keep failing the test,
we're not gonna make
any progress at all.
-Hm?
Who's that?
-Shindou.
-Huh?
So, who is he?
-That's Zama-sensei, the Oza.
-The Oza?
-It's only one of the
top titles you can win.
Come on.
Learn the names of the major
championships, will you?
-Zama-sensei.
I'm glad I caught you.
-What is it?
-The date for your game
in the Shinsho Dan series
has been set.
We'll send some
official notification.
-Who's my opponent?
-It's Akira Toya, the
son of Toya Meijin.
-Akira, huh?
I've heard about him.
Quite the reputation.
-The students of Toya Meijin
say he's a really strong player.
-I'm sure they wouldn't dare
say anything bad about him.
So, the series is
underway now, huh?
How are the old pros?
Have we been making a
clean sweep of the matches?
-No, some wins and some losses.
-Ah.
Obviously some of the rookies
are putting up a fight.
These games are just for show.
You know what?
Maybe I should let him
beat me by half a point.
That'd make everyone
happy, wouldn't it?
-It'll make the front page.
Toya Junior's amazing debut.
-It would be great publicity
for the association, that's
for sure.
-Kuwabara-sensei
played last week.
How did his game go?
-He was playing against Mashiba,
one of the former Insei.
-I'll take it.
-I don't know if he was nervous
about playing Kuwabara-sensei
or if he was over awed by
the fact he was playing
in the championship
room, but Mashiba
seemed to self destruct.
When Mashiba finally
decided to resign,
Kuwabara-sensei said, (SHAKEY
VOICE) oh, is it over?
As if he'd been playing
the game in his sleep.
-Poor kid.
Sometimes Kuwabara-sensei
can be really cruel.
-Well, we're all looking
forward to your game.
The major title holder
against the talented newcomer.
I hope it's a good one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-What?
Today?
-Didn't you see the schedule
up on the bulletin board?
This afternoon, Toya's
going up against the Oza
in the championship room.
-Really?
I wanna watch.
WAYA: You can.
Follow me.
The board in the
championship room
has a camera installed
directly above it.
There's a TV down here
you can watch the game on.
-Whoa.
-There it is.
There's no way we can
watch the whole thing,
because we gotta go play our own
matches, but, once we're done,
we can come back
here and maybe we
can catch the last
half of the game.
-I was hoping we could
see the whole thing.
While we're here, wanna
check out the room itself?
-What?
Are we allowed?
-Here it is.
The championship room.
-I can't see anything.
It's too dark.
-Hikaru!
-Hm?
Sai?
-My senses are tingling
with excitement.
The intensity of this room
is so strong it almost hurts.
Oh, the anticipation's
getting too much to bear.
-What do you think?
It's a pretty awesome
room, isn't it?
-So the pros play
their matches in here?
-Course not.
Pro matches are normally played
in the same room we play in.
This room's only used for
the big championship matches.
-Oh, I see.
WAYA: They use this room
for the Shinsho Dan series
as a way to get all the new guys
excited about winning titles.
Next year, it'll be me in here.
MAN: OK.
Now we just need to take a
few photos before the match.
[camera clicking]
Get a lot of shots of the kid.
I predict he's going to be
a big name in the future.
-Whatever you want, boss.
-Right.
Let's have a couple of you
facing each other and chatting.
-What do you want to
talk about, young Toya?
-I'm going to give this match
everything I've got and more.
Hope you have a good game.
-Of course.
I'm counting on it.
Now, there's no need to be
intimidated by my title of Oza.
As pros, we're all
on the same level.
There's no chance of
winning if you're too timid.
You must think of me as
a One Dan, like yourself.
-Yes.
I fully intend to.
ZAMA (VOICEOVER):
He fully intends to?
What a precocious brat.
MAN: OK, just a few more.
ZAMA (VOICEOVER): This
calls for a change of plan.
I'm going to destroy him.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I wonder
is Akira started his match yet.
-Hikaru.
I think it would be wise
for you to concentrate
on your own game.
-Uh, yeah, yeah.
-I'm guessing you've been
in this championship room
before, Toya.
-Actually, this
is my first time.
-I know you haven't
played in here before,
but what about with your father?
He's played here more
times than I can remember.
You must have tagged along
with him once or twice.
-Nope.
I've never been in here.
Not even as a time keeper or
keeping a record of the scores?
-You normally learn
about those sort of jobs
when you're an Insei,
but I was able to skip
that part of the process.
-Huh?
You've never been an Insei?
-Wait a minute, I'd forgotten.
The new pros are the ones
who do those jobs, right?
I guess I'd better learn before
I officially start in April.
ZAMA (VOICEOVER): He really
is a precocious little brat.
He's not the least bit nervous.
-Gentlemen, it's time
for us to begin the game.
-The new One Dan
player goes first
and will be given a handicap
of 5 and 1/2 points.
Each player will be
allotted two hours.
If that time runs
out, the players
will enter over time
with one minute per move.
Everyone ready?
Prepare to play.
-Onegai shimasu.
[music playing]
-Well, well.
Ashiwara.
-Oh, hello there.
Oh, of course.
You're one of Toya
Meijin's students.
-Yeah, but I'm also
friends with Akira,
so I wanted to come
and support him.
He doesn't have many
friends around his own age.
-That would explain it.
I couldn't figure out
how he could be so calm.
The new kids are
usually so scared.
They get intimidated playing
guys with that much experience.
But young Toya
didn't bat an eyelid.
On the other hand, Mashiba,
you were a complete mess.
-Kuwabara-sensei was
a nightmare to play.
The way he slammed
his first stone down,
I thought it would
crack the board.
-He was obviously
trying to psych you out,
and you went and fell for it.
-That sounds just like
Kuwabara-sensei to me.
-Well, it'll be interesting
to see what happens today.
[theme music]
HIKARU: I've gotta see
Akira's game no matter what.
I have to see him play if
I'm ever gonna beat him.
SAI: One step at a time, Hikaru.
HIKARU: He's been playing
an awesome game up 'til now.
He can't let it end like this.
SAI: I'm sure he won't
back down easily.
Just be patient, Hikaru.
Just be patient.
HIKARU: Next time.
Akria Versus The Oza.
I can't wait to see how it ends.