[music playing]
[theme music]
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
It's almost over.
Don't panic.
It's going to be hard for
Shindo to make a comeback now.
Try to ignore them.
I'm playing Shindo now, so
forget about Toya and Su-Yong.
[alarm sounding]
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): I went for
an atari from the wrong side.
HIKARU: Sai, did he
just move his stone?
Changing your mind
after your fingers
have left the stone means you
have to forfeit the match.
Sai, did Isumi take his
fingers off the stone
before he moved it?
-It did look as though
that's what happened,
but I can't say for sure.
If he did move the
stone, he should
be disqualified immediately.
Hikaru?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): He
hasn't said anything.
Is it because he didn't
actually let go of the stone?
Or is it because--
no, he wouldn't.
I have to know if his hand
came off the stone or not.
Do you think it'd be
OK if I just ask him?
[gasp]
-You are not really going
to confront him, are you?
Hikaru!
--[sigh] Isumi's
still undefeated.
I've got one loss, and only
three of us can become pros.
-Hikaru, don't you want
to finish playing the game
and win on your own merits?
You do have a strategy
for a comeback.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
It's not going to work.
I know it.
If we keep going, he'll beat me.
But if I challenge
him about that move,
I'm guarantee to win.
Isumi's been trying for
years to pass the pro exam,
and he hasn't done it yet.
That just shows how
important every win is.
I need to win.
The reason Isumi's
not saying anything
is because he wants to win, and
he's hoping I didn't noticed.
-Hikaru, just be
careful that you don't--
-Isu--
-I'm resigning.
[sigh]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): He knows
he cheated, so he resigned.
At least, I won the game.
This is a big win for me.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Shindo?
Is the match over already?
Huh?
Shindo's recording the result.
How did he win?
Isumi was in total
control of the game.
What happened?
[gulping]
-Sai, why do I have a weird
feeling about this win?
[gulping]
WAYA (VOICEOVER):
Isumi, you're not
playing anywhere near
as good as usual.
So you lost to Shindo yesterday.
You shouldn't let it
get to you like this.
You haven't said a word to me.
That's not like you, Isumi.
Sure.
It must have been a tough loss,
but you've got to get over it.
If you let it
affect you this bad,
you're going to
ruin your chances.
No one here is easy to
beat, especially me.
-I resign.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Yes!
This year I might
make it through.
What's gotten into him?
I can't worry about it.
I've got to focus on my
next match against Ochi.
-Hm.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
I'm not playing good at all.
I shouldn't have a
problem beating Fuku.
But after I took that
win from Isumi yesterday,
I can't get the thought of
that match out of my mind.
It shouldn't have
ended that way.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI (VOICEOVER): I
was afraid this might happen.
Yesterday's victory has left
a bitter taste in his mouth.
He's fallen too far behind.
He should concede the match,
but he's determined to play on.
HIKARU: I lost by nine
and a half points.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI
(VOICEOVER): Hikaru.
-The reason I lost my match
today was all because of Isumi.
How could he do that to me?
He completely ruined
my concentration.
He ruined everything.
-Hikaru.
Hikaru.
-I had given up.
I could have won.
I knew it was only
a slim chance,
but I had a plan for a comeback.
I could have done it.
When I saw him move the stone,
I knew I had a chance to win,
and I jumped at it.
I wanted to win
whatever the cost.
But that was the easy way out.
I was weak, so I tried
to win by default
instead of playing the game.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: Hikaru.
-Huh.
-Hikaru, we could always
finish the game now.
I can take Isumi's place
and play as he would play.
You can find out if you'd
have won with your comeback.
Move on with a clear conscience.
-I want to be able to
trust in my own ability.
I want to be strong.
I'm never going to
play another match
like the ones I played
yesterday or today ever again.
-Hikaru, you know something,
that sort of resolve
is worth losing a game
or two along the way.
So are you ready to begin?
-Mhm.
[train whistle]
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Today,
my opponent is Waya.
I have to play my
best against him.
He's probably my biggest threat
to getting through the exam
undefeated.
I used to be worried about
Isumi, but not anymore.
Not since, he lost both of his
games against Shindo and Waya.
But I still can't work
out how Shindo beat him
unless Isumi made
some sort of mistake.
But he doesn't normally
make those kinds of errors.
There must be
something on his mind.
You lost your nerve
against Shindo, huh?
Remember, on the day you
played the game against Shindo,
I was telling you
about Akira Toya.
I wonder if you were
thinking about that,
so you lost your concentration
and made a mistake.
Is that it?
Are you not going to tell me,
because you don't want anyone
to know what really happened
in your game with Shindo?
Well?
Am I right?
Come on.
Just answer the question.
-Hey, Isumi.
Hm.
Ochi, what were you guys
talking about just now?
I hope you weren't asking him
about his match with Shindo.
He hasn't even told me
anything, so there's
no way he'd talk to you.
I've got no idea
how or why he lost,
but he needs to get that match
out of his system and move on.
I wish he'd talk about it.
I can't figure him out at all.
-He made a mistake.
That's all.
When I saw their game,
Isumi was in control,
and I was sure he
was going to win.
So I went to watch
your match instead.
And when I looked back
after that, it was all over.
There's no way the
game could have turned
that quickly unless
Isumi made a big mistake.
-A mistake?
-I don't know exactly.
But the point is, Isumi
couldn't deal with it,
and it affected his
game against you.
Whatever happened in that
game also affected Shindo,
because he went on
to lose against Fuku.
Unless we've been
overrating them both.
-Yeah, maybe.
Well, it's starting
to look like you're
going to have no problem
passing the pro exam.
-Yeah, I know.
Nobody's going to
beat me, not even you.
-Morning, guys.
-Hey.
GO OFFICIAL (ON LOUDSPEAKER):
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time to begin.
Everyone please make their
way to the match room.
-Look at him.
Do you think he's still
depressed about what happened?
How could he have made
a mistake like that?
Something must have
distracted him.
-Hikaru.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Yeah, I know.
I've got to stop
thinking about it.
-That's right.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I'll be OK.
I've got everything
under control.
GO OFFICIAL: When you're
ready, please begin.
-(GROUP) Onegaishimasu.
I stayed calm and everything
went right in today's game.
Now, let's see.
How did Isumi do?
Oh.
-Are you done yet?
I need to stamp mine.
-Ochi.
Oh, so you beat Waya.
-Hm.
-Are you OK?
-I don't think I
played a bad game.
Things were looking good
for me on the left side,
but then he got me
on the defensive.
Started jumping
around the board.
The game was really close.
I ended up losing by
two and a half points.
What about you?
-I won.
Waya, I'm worried about Isumi.
He lost again today.
He was playing Fuku.
[gasp]
OCHI'S GRANDFATHER: I
guess that's it then.
You had me fooled for the
longest time in this area.
Oh dear, oh dear,
it looks like I'm
going to have to add another
stone to my handicap.
Are you sure you want to
be playing someone like me
in the middle of your pro exams?
Shouldn't you be
playing someone better?
-Uh-uh.
I don't mind.
It's a nice change of pace.
-Hm.
Did you see the Go Weekly?
Toya 2-dan won his
game in the first round
of the Meijin
Tournament prelims.
OCHI: So?
-He also won his match
in the second round
of the Honinbo Tournament.
He hasn't lost a single game
since his debut as a pro.
That's an impressive
record, huh?
Don't forget.
He's been kind enough
to offer you the chance
to play with him as often
as his schedule permits.
I think you should
take him up on it.
-I don't need Toya.
I beat Waya, and I've
already beaten Honda.
I'm going to pass
the exam undefeated.
-Pass the exam undefeated?
[laughs] Sounds promising.
But don't get too
over confident.
You haven't played
that Isumi boy yet.
I think you said that
out of all the players
he was your main rival.
-I'm really not
worried about him now.
I'm going to make it through
this exam undefeated.
That's going to
boost my confidence
when I become a pro for sure.
Isumi's playing so bad
he's not a threat anymore,
and beating Shindo
should be easy enough.
I got nothing to worry about.
[laughing] I'm not going
to need Toya's help.
I hear you even lost
to Fuku yesterday.
Too bad.
I was kind of disappointed.
You were my biggest hurdle
to getting through this exam
undefeated, but not anymore.
You haven't even recovered
from that game against Shindo,
have you?
I don't know why I ever thought
of you as a serious threat.
My goal of staying undefeated
is much easier now.
Thanks to you.
ISUMI: Ochi.
-Huh?
-Shut your mouth.
GO OFFICIAL: When you're
ready, please begin.
[theme music]
HIKARU: What a showdown
between Ochi and Isumi.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: Ah.
It's nice to see Isumi back
to his normal self again.
You should pay
attention, Hikaru,
because your final match
will be against Ochi.
HIKARU: I can't wait.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: Three
weeks left of the finals,
and there's still
everything left to play for.
HIKARU: Next time, "Three
Weeks Isn't Enough."
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI:
Watch out, Hikaru.
Ochi's getting some
extra coaching.