[theme music]
-Please.
Let me play him, Hikaru.
-No!
Forget all about it!
If I let you play,
you'd win for sure.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Shindou.
You've made it this far.
I've been waiting for this
moment for a long time.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Yes, a handicap.
If Sai had to work with
a different handicap,
his game would be
completely changed.
I'll do it!
-Shindou took 20 minutes
on this first move.
That doesn't seem like
a very good start to me.
It'll be interesting to see
how the Meijin responds.
-Lower right corner, star point.
-The tension's
too much in there.
-Tell me about it.
I'm exhausted already.
-It's the first time anything
like this has ever happened,
but I didn't get the impression
that Shindou was nervous,
did you?
-No.
-Akira's watching in
the other room, right?
Let's see if we can
get a comment from him
on that long opening move.
Ogata-sensei?
And Kuwabara-sensei, too?
-That game took a long
time to get started.
What was the reason
for the delay?
Technical difficulties?
-What?
No.
Everything's going according
to plan on our end.
It's Shindou.
He took 20 minutes to
make his first move.
I hope you don't mind me
asking, Kuwabara-sensei,
but why are you here today?
To watch Shindou play?
-But of course.
I've decided to take
an interest in the boy.
I walked past him
and knew something
was special about him.
-What?
How could you even know that?
I mean, you've never
even seen him play.
That's absurd.
-Strange, but true.
He claims it's intuition.
-What?
-Make fun of my
intuition if you like,
Ogata, but if you don't
take it seriously,
you're never going to beat me.
MAN: Well, however
it happened, it's
quite impressive for a
young player like Shindou
to be noticed by
Kuwabara-sensei.
Not to mention the interest
you're taking in him, Ogata.
And did you know that Toya
Meijin asked specifically
for Shindou to be his
opponent in this game?
-Ah.
Did he?
-No way.
-Hey, Waya.
Who is Shindou?
-Well, he is out-- Oh forget it.
Stop asking me that.
OCHI: OK.
-The Meijin's only interested
because Akira considers Shindou
to be his rival and he
wants to test his strength.
-Is this true?
Is he your rival?
-Uh, well, uh--
KUWABARA: No, no, no.
This has got nothing
to do with Akira.
The Meijin has his own reasons
for wanting to play the boy.
-Really?
And what are they?
-Let's just say he's got a
very good intuition, like me.
-13, 14.
A cap.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): A cap move?
-What's Shindou doing?
I can't believe he
started his attack!
It's so early in the game!
WAYA (VOICEOVER):
What's he up to?
I don't get it.
-Exactly the response I wanted.
Good.
Unless I go on the
offensive right away,
there's no chance of winning.
I will lead him into
a complex battle
with moves that will be
hard for him to read.
Now I need to
create some opening
on the board that
will lure him in.
And then, when he does go in
for the kill, my path to victory
will become clear.
Lay the next stone at 18, 16.
Wait.
He's not playing the
way I thought he would.
He's being too cautious.
If he continues like this,
I'll be left with no choice
but to take even greater risks.
Well, so be it!
Now, 18, 19.
Block it.
-I don't understand what
Shindou's trying to do here.
He's being so
aggressive, he's going
to overplay his hand
if he's not careful.
-Hm.
-He stretched
himself pretty thin.
-His formations aren't good.
-Well, Akira.
It looks like Shindou's
got a long way
to go before he rivals you.
-Hm.
-If he captures these stones,
then it's all over for black,
right?
-Yes, that would seem
like the obvious choice.
-Then why isn't my
father capturing them?
-Hm.
Maybe he doesn't want to
end the game that quickly.
You know?
Give the newcomer
a fighting chance.
-What do you think, Ogata?
-Black's obviously at
a big disadvantage,
but I have no idea what
Toya-sensei's strategy might
be.
-He knows how to
trust his intuition.
TOYA MEIJIN (VOICEOVER):
At first glance,
it looks like black's
game is about to collapse.
But reading further
ahead, I get the sense
this could become
quite dangerous.
I'm not gonna fall into the
trap my opponent has set for me.
Hm?
On the surface, his game
is exceedingly reckless.
But there's something
deeper going on.
There's definitely
more to it than that.
This boy is a new One-Dan.
He's a mere 14-year-old child.
There's a strength
I sense around him.
How could he possess such power?
OGATA: The battle
in that one corner
has spread right out
across the board.
It's as though Shindou decided
to expand his game by attacking
in random places, hoping
to confuse his opponent.
-There's not too
much he can do now.
-It's obvious what the result
of the game's going to be.
Black's going to be wiped out.
Wiped out!
-I've never seen him
play like this before.
-Why's Toya-sensei holding back?
He should finish it off.
-I know young players
have a tendency
to throw caution to the
wind, but he's gone too far.
It just won't work
against the Meijin.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Shindou.
-What do you know?
He resigned.
I told you he was going to lose.
Poor Shindou.
He must be very disappointed.
-Hey, Waya?
-Hold on.
Those guys are going to
start reviewing the game.
-Well, I guess that
means I've won the bet.
However, this hasn't changed
my opinion of Shindou.
-What an intriguing
game of Go that was.
Oh, and Ogata-- the next
time there's a game like this
and you want to
have a little wager,
my money's still on the kid.
OGATA: You coming, Akira?
-Huh?
Yeah, sure.
I'll be along in a minute.
Kuwabara-sensei?
-Hm?
You want my opnion?
-Yes.
-Let me see.
Shindou's strategy
starts to make sense
if you consider the possibility
that he might have actually
given himself a large handicap.
-What?
Gave himself a handicap?
Are you sure about that?
-Mm-hm.
-But he's playing my father.
That'd be crazy!
[laughter]
-I'm not saying I understand
why he'd do such a thing.
But it's an interesting
possibility, isn't it?
[laughter]
SAI (VOICEOVER): It's over.
-I wish we could have played
the game without a handicap.
-Huh?
-I have no idea why you
played the way you did,
but you cannot hide the strength
of the spirit inside you.
-Huh?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I
think he must have realized
that we put our own
handicap on the game.
And it sounds like
he somehow knew
Sai was playing through me.
-As we played, I could
sense an intensity from you
which is normally only found
in veterans of the game.
Next time we play, let's
make it an even game.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Yes.
Next time.
-Well, that was quite a game.
Let's discuss the first move.
AKIRA: He put a
handicap on himself?
Why on earth would he do that?
-Young Shindou is proving to
be more and more interesting
all the time.
-There's something I don't
understand about him.
When I played him
two years ago, it
was almost like I was
playing my father.
He was such a strong opponent.
KUWABARA: Oh?
-But it was strange.
The next time I played
him, over six months later,
it was like he was
a different person.
His game was so weak.
-Stop messing around!
-What?
What's wrong?
-Like he was a
different person, eh?
Well, that's very unusual.
-If I'd known he was as
weak a player as that,
I'd never have
considered him my rival.
Never in a million years.
I was so angry.
I felt like he tricked
me, or something.
Then when I bumped
into him later on,
he said the weirdest
thing to me.
-Now, listen.
If you keep on chasing
your phantom image of me,
one day I'm gonna
catch up to you.
-The next time I saw him,
he'd become an Insei.
And now look at him.
He just finished
playing my father
in the championship room.
-Sounds to me as if
you're the one responsible
for him joining the
world of the pros.
Tell me, Toya, what's
your first name, again?
-Akira.
-Akira Toya.
Akira Toya.
I'll have to remember that name.
[laughter]
-Oh.
Hello, Akira.
-So, how's everything
going in there?
-Well, I think there might
be something up with Shindou.
No matter what
anyone asks him, he's
just sitting there,
not saying a word.
I don't know if
you're interested,
but I overheard the recorder say
something which surprised me.
-Really?
And what was that?
-Apparently your father
told Shindou the next time
they play each other, he
wants to play an even game,
with no handicap.
-What?
My father said that?
Are you sure?
-Mm-hm.
Although when we
tried to get the story
direct from your father, he
wouldn't confirm or deny it,
so we're going to be able
to use it in the article.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): My
father, the Meijin,
wants to play Shindou in an even
game the next time they meet?
-Huh?
Hey, Akira!
Aren't you coming with me?
Akira?
Akira!
-I don't think he
quite figured out
the you were the one playing
him in that game, and not me.
But you gotta hand it to him.
He knew something was up.
He knew it wasn't a
bunch of reckless moves.
-Next time we play, let's
make it an even game.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Yes.
Next time.
HIKARU: You are going to want
to play him again, aren't you?
-Yes.
-I wonder if I can
make it happen.
-You wonder if?
You have to do better than that.
-I'm sure I'll figure
something out someday.
-You'll just have to wait.
-Someday?
-When?
When?
-How should I know when?
Whatever it happens?
Today was an important
day for me, too.
My first game as
a pro, remember?
So don't be so selfish.
I gave up a big chance
to let you play.
You don't get it, do ya?
I--
-I'm very sorry.
-It's your own fault.
You're the one who
decided to inhabit me.
Shusaku was a lot
better than me, right?
But there's one big
difference between us.
He let you play all his
games, all the time.
What was his first name again?
Torajiro, wasn't it?
I don't understand why he never
wanted to play by himself.
Didn't he want to
be a Go player?
What a loser.
-You see, that's because-- the
thing is-- it was all my fault!
When I returned to this world,
I was so desperate to play--
and I didn't know I
would meet you, Hikaru.
I thought Torajiro
was my only chance,
so I took it and forced
him to let me play.
-Huh?
Now, hold on a minute.
I know that Torajiro died young.
Was that because
you inhabited him?
Tell the truth.
-Huh?
No, no, no, no.
You don't understand.
Torajiro was a good person.
A terrible epidemic
struck his village,
but instead of escaping,
he risked his life
to look after everyone
who'd become sick.
And then-- And that's
why-- Poor Torajiro.
He was intelligent, and truly
kind to everyone he met.
-Hmph.
So, you think I'm stupid
and not kind to anyone.
-Hikaru.
-Father.
I heard that after
the game today,
you told Shindou that
next time you play,
you wanted it to be an
even game with no handicap.
-Yes.
TOYA (VOICEOVER):
My dad's the Meijin,
and he wants to have an even
game with Hikaru Shindou?
Shindou-- just who are you?
[theme music]
SAI: I am Fujiwara-no-Sai.
Being here with Hikaru
is the third time
I've been placed in this world.
My sole purpose has been
to play the Divine Move.
But I could not come close
to it during my match
against Toya Meijin.
So, is there another
reason why I'm here?
HIKARU: Next time,
Fujiwara-no-Sai!
SAI: I will find out why
I've been brought here
to guide Hikaru!