[theme music]
IJIMA (VOICEOVER):
Shindo's changed
since I saw him
play in the prelims.
-Hikaru, you're not intimidated
by Gorilla Man at all now.
-I know.
I thought if I gave
him some attitude,
it would take my
mind of the test,
and I wouldn't be so nervous.
-Such a magnificent strategy.
-OK.
Let's go and check
out the room where
I'll be playing the matches.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
It's finally begun.
The pro exam is going
to be a tough battle.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Only three
people can pass the test.
HONDA (VOICEOVER): This
year is going to be my year.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): I'm not
just here to pass the exam.
My goal is to finish
as the number 1 player.
-Six straight wins.
Shindo?
He's won six games in a row?
-Finally, you made it here!
-Hm?
-Today's the day I get to
play my match against you.
I was so excited, I didn't
sleep a wink last night.
Don't get upset when
you lose to me again.
I'm sure you've won all the
games you played up to now.
But I'm going to
show you it's been
nothing more than
a lucky streak.
-Oh, I see.
So if I beat you
today, that's going
to be just another fluke, huh?
Or will that finally prove
that I'm better than you.
-Hm?
So you think you can talk
back to me now, do you?
What happened to the
jittery little punk
I played in the prelims?
You look so relaxed now.
-I might look
relaxed, but I'm not.
Every time I come here,
I get really nervous
just like you, Mr. Tsubaki.
-Huh?
What do you mean?
-You feel nervous, so you decide
to bug other people, right?
It calms you down.
And that's what you did
to me back in the prelims.
-No way!
-Well, at first, I thought
it was some kind of strategy
of yours to try and put me off.
-A strategy to put you off?
I never do something
as mean as that.
-[laughs]
You're always shouting.
So can you blame me
for thinking you would?
-Hey, Shindo!
How are you?
-Oh, hey!
You better give me a ride on
that bike of yours, some time.
-Uhh.
Uh!
That kid's really changed
since the prelims.
There's no way I'm
going to lose to him.
OCHI (VOICEOVER):
Shindo's changed.
That's what Ijima
said about him, too.
Hm.
-Ladies and gentlemen,
it's now time for lunch.
So please stop your clocks.
[chatter]
TSUBAKI: So what if you got
the next move after lunch?
It doesn't make any difference!
-But you told me
at the prelims it
was good to have the lunch break
to think about your next move.
-Yeah, but that was the prelims.
We got way more time
to play in the finals.
In the finals, you need to use
your lunch break to chill out.
-You're just saying
that to confuse me.
-Hey!
What are you talking about?
I never said anything
to confuse you!
BOY: Keep the noise
down, will you?
-You talking to me?
This is a public area, isn't it?
If you don't like the
noise, go somewhere else!
-You don't take
anything seriously.
Must be nice having a
cushy job to fall back
on if you fail the test.
-What?
You think I've got a
job to fall back on?
You're dead wrong!
Sure, I took time off
work during the prelims.
But now we're in the
finals, I had to quit.
The exam goes on for two months.
If I ask for time off
every time I played,
they would have fired me.
-Oh, never mind.
Probably, it wasn't
that good a job anyway.
-Oh, yeah, kid?
-It doesn't matter
how good a company is.
None of them would give
us this much time off.
They don't understand.
That's why I have
always worked part-time.
-Really?
-This is the fifth year
I've taken the test.
I thought you would have
recognized my face by now.
Mind you, this is the first time
I've made it past the prelims
to the finals.
MAN: You live here in Tokyo?
-Yeah.
-I've come all the
way from Nagano.
It cost me almost 20,000
yen just to get here.
On Tuesdays, I just
come down for the day.
But on the weekends, I
stay at a friend's place
in Tokyo-- saves on
expensive hotel bills.
-Yeah, I'm in a hotel, but
money's not the only problem.
I've got too many
things on my mind.
It's hard trying
to get to sleep.
I'd much rather stay
at a friend's place
than some small hotel room.
It'd be a good change of
pace and help me relax.
-Sounds to me like the
students who live here in Tokyo
have it real easy, ha?
How come you're not studying
for something at college
like the rest of them?
You're smart enough, ain't you?
-What's the point
of college if you're
going to become a professional?
-There are a lot of
people who do it.
They get into one of
the top universities,
and then they focus on
passing the pro exam.
-But don't forget the kids who
pass the test while they're
still in high school.
They often go back to college
and get more qualifications
after they've become a pro.
MAN: Yeah, remember that one guy
who went on to become a lawyer?
Seems like if you
can make it as a pro,
you can do just about
anything you want.
-The important word being "if."
Let's not talk about it anymore.
-Humph, it doesn't really matter
if you're smart or stupid.
The only thing that matters
is beating your opponent.
-You know, Mr. Tsubaki,
people might listen to you
more if you didn't
shout all the time.
-What?
-He-he.
MAN: He's right.
Sometimes the things you
say really irritate people.
-[chuckles]
-Come here and say that!
-Well, lunch is nearly over.
Time to go.
-When you're ready,
please begin.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
All these players
come from different backgrounds.
They have different
strengths and weaknesses.
But they all have one
thing in common-- a passion
for the game of Go.
The rules of the
finals are simple.
The three players who
win the most games
will join the ranks of the pros.
-[grunts]
I resign.
-Well done, Hikaru.
You've defeated Tsubaki.
-Hm, let's see.
Great games.
Isumi, Ochi, Waya, and even
Shindo are still undefeated.
[clock ticks]
-Waya lost a game?
His opponent was Adachi.
-What about you, Isumi?
Did you win?
-Yeah.
-We've still got
a long way to go.
Waya has done well to get
this far without a loss.
I've only lost two.
I can still make it.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): Shindo
won his game today.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): I
play Isumi in match 15
and Shindo on the very last day.
MAN: How did you do?
BOY: Terrible.
[moans]
And tomorrow's the
10th match already.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): The
10th match tomorrow.
And then I get to
meet with Toya.
BOY: I'll see you later.
[gate closes]
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): According
to the scores posted
on the internet, Ochi
hasn't lost a match so far.
He obviously has talent.
I wonder what he'll
say about Shindo.
This is my chance to find out
what level he's playing at now.
It could just be my
imagination, but I
can sense Shindo's
footsteps behind me.
[train horn honks]
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
AKIRA: It's Toya.
-Come in, come in.
We've been expecting you.
-Onegai shimasu.
OCHI (VOICEOVER):
Why does everyone
make such a big deal about him?
He seems normal to me.
[gasps]
This isn't a teaching game.
He's playing to win.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Ochi's
game is pretty good.
He's probably the best
insei around right now.
But I won't let
him take my place.
If it turns out he's anywhere
near as strong as I am,
then his match with Shindo is
going to be very interesting.
When they play against
each other, I'll find out.
Is Shindo really worthy
enough to be my rival?
-Sorry about that.
I didn't mean to
keep you waiting.
Are you all right?
You ran straight to the bathroom
as soon as the game was over.
I thought you were
never going to come out.
-Everything's fine now.
-You sure?
-I said everything's
fine, Grandpa!
So just leave me alone!
GRANDPA: OK, please continue.
[door shuts]
OCHI (VOICEOVER): So
this is Akira Toya.
Now, I know why everyone has
such a high opinion of him.
Once I become a pro, he's
going to be my rival.
-I was told this was supposed
to be a teaching game.
But it looked like you
wanted a real match,
so I didn't hold anything back.
I played you at full strength.
Do you want me to
review the game now?
-I think I already
know the reason I lost.
I was quite aggressive
when I tried
to surround the right side
with these two moves here.
That turned out be a mistake.
Once I was cut off, the game
was pretty much over for me.
I should probably
have extended instead.
-That's definitely
part of the reason.
But you also spent too much
time worrying about territory
when what you should be
doing is using your strongest
areas to attack.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER):
Ochi and Shindo
play each other on the
last day of the exam.
That means there's still
a month and a half to go.
I should be able to raise the
level of Ochi's game by then.
-If you moved here,
black would be solid.
Huh?
[sighs]
I was checking out the
Go Association's website.
I noticed only three of you
have won every game so far.
You, someone named
Isumi, and Shindo.
-No, Shindo lost today.
-Shindo lost?
Who beat him?
-Someone I never saw before.
-What was the game like?
-I've got no idea.
You know how long
the pro exam is.
It can be pretty tiring.
Maybe he just had an
off day or something.
Besides, it's only one match.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Hm,
so Shindo lost a game.
-What's the big deal about
Shindo all of a sudden?
Is there something
I should know?
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Huh!
Now, that I think
about it, there
was a rumor going around when
Shindo first became an insei.
He said he was
Akira Toya's rival.
He was stuck way down in the B
league, so no one believed him.
But what if the rumor is true?
-I'd be interested to find
out what you think of Shindo.
-I don't think he is strong
enough to be a threat.
The players I'm
worried about right
now are Isumi, Waya, and Honda.
Close behind them, there's
Adachi, Komiya, and then, maybe Shindo.
And just for the
record, so you know,
I've never lost a
game against Shindo.
-I see.
And when was the last time
you and him played each other?
OCHI: About three months ago.
-Three months ago?
Not very recent, is it?
OCHI (VOICEOVER):
What's with this guy?
-You're playing Shindo
later in the finals.
On the last day, right?
AKIRA (VOICEOVER):
That gives me some time
to train Ochi for the games
so he can play as I would.
-Tell you what, Ochi,
if it's OK with you,
I could tutor you as
often as you like.
-Wait a minute.
You're not suggesting I'm
going to need your help
to beat Shindo, are you?
-Nah, no.
I never said you
couldn't beat him.
It's just if you want to achieve
your goal of passing the test
undefeated, then a few
extra study lessons with me
might help.
That's all.
-Oh, now, I get it.
-Now, you get what?
-Rrh!
I know what you're doing.
You're just using me!
Using my game to measure
Shindo's skill level!
-Hm.
-I can beat him on my
own without your help!
You understand?
-Kosuke, what's going on?
-And besides, why is someone
like you concerned with Shindo?
It doesn't make sense!
-I'm sorry.
I think that's probably
enough for today.
-For today?
You're never coming back!
-Kosuke!
-You may not think of me as
much of a player right now.
But one day, I am
going to be a rival.
Get out!
-[grunts]
I've got no idea what
this is all about,
but I apologize for my
grandson's behavior.
Maybe we can give you a call and
arrange another study session
if we need it.
We appreciate you coming out.
-He won't be coming back.
I don't need him.
-Kosuke.
-I'll wait to hear from you.
-Uhh.
Kosuke!
-Humph.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Shindo?
Why Shindo?
Once he got promoted
to the A league,
he kept moving up
in his rankings.
Now, he's in the pro
exam with just one loss.
-He's changed.
He's stronger.
-Uh.
-Ah, Honda, you're leaving.
Anyone still playing in there?
-Just one game left.
SENSEI: I see.
I wonder how long
their going to be?
Hm.
-See you later, sir.
That win for me today
means I stay at two losses.
You guys are the
front runners now.
You and Ochi are the only ones
who have won every game so far.
Shindo and Waya
have only lost one.
-The pressure is really on
for me to make it this year.
You see, this is my last chance
to take the test as an insei.
HONDA: I totally understand.
I'm only one year
behind you, remember?
My parents have told
me if I don't make it
by the time I'm
20, then I've got
to find something else to do.
ISUMI: Hm.
I know we can keep taking
the pro exam until we're 30.
But I figure if
I don't pass now,
I'm never going to be a pro.
HONDA: Hey, Isumi, you're
playing Shindo next,
aren't you?
No hard feelings, but
I hope he beats you.
Because if you and
Ochi don't start
losing a game here
and there, I'm
never going to have a
chance of passing this exam.
ISUMI: [chuckles]
Yeah, but if I let Shindo win,
he might end up overtaking me.
-His run of good luck's
got to come to an end soon.
ISUMI: You sure about that?
Even though he has
lost a game, he
managed to turn things around
and win a solid match today.
-Hm, do you remember what
Ijima told us about him?
He said Shindo had changed.
And we'd find out when
we played against him.
ISUMI: And after
Kamiya lost to Shindo,
he said he had
done much stronger.
-Well, it doesn't really
matter how strong he is now.
The important thing is none of
us can afford to lose to him.
-Of course not.
-Tomorrow is your big
match against Isumi.
Don't be nervous and give
yourself an upset stomach
like you did the day you lost.
It's important for
you to be prepared,
both mentally and physically.
If you can do that,
then I'm confident you
will gain another victory.
Hikaru?
-It's your turn to move, OK.
Sai?
You should really start
paying more attention
or you're going to lose.
-[chuckles]
Me lose to you, Hikaru?
Tell me something.
In all the time
we've been playing,
when have you ever
won a game against me?
Haah!
You've got some nerve!
I'll cut you down and--
-Hikaru!
Now, what in the world
is he doing up there?
[hikaru and sai bickering]
-Why are you making
such a racket up there?
-What do you think of Shindo?
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Loss number
2 for Shindo coming up today,
courtesy of Isumi.
Let that be your answer, Toya.
-Try and stay calm.
Play my normal game.
It'll be fine.
-You know what I just realized?
You haven't been
doing that thing where
you put the winning
stamp on your hand
like you did in
the preliminaries.
-Huh, you're right.
Yeah!
Let's go and mark
me as a winner!
Ha-ha!
-Great.
Uh, Hikaru, your
opponent in today's match
is standing before us.
-Huh.
-Hm?
[music playing]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): If I can
beat Isumi in this match,
then I'll have the
momentum I need
to make it all the
way through the exam.
SAI (VOICEOVER): There seems
to be some other people who
are interested in how
this game turns out.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): It's
weird playing someone
you know when there's
so much at stake.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Remember
to stay focused, keep calm,
and just play like
you normally do.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Next
time, an ill-fated moment.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Yes, but for who?