NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past
known Fujiwara-no-Sai
has returned, visible only to
Hikaru Shindou A master of Go,
Sai seeks to play
the Divine Move.
[theme music]
-I've got an idea.
We can tie up his
hands and feet and make
him place the stones
with his teeth.
-I kinda like that idea.
-Huh?
-Hm?
Where's Ito and Kojima?
Anyone seen them?
-I saw them earlier.
-They snuck out of here
about 15 minutes ago.
I think they were with
that new guy, Okumura.
He's a seventh grader.
-Do you know where
they were going?
-No.
-Wow.
This place is a
real mess, isn't it?
The Go club used to meet
here, way back when they only
had a few members.
I need you to clean
up all this stuff.
Mr. Yun's direct orders.
He wants to convert
this whole place
into a break room for the
girls so they can use it
during the next tournament.
So, do you think
you can help us out?
Someone in the seventh
grade's gotta do it.
I noticed you were looking
pretty bored today.
This should keep you
busy for a while.
-No problem.
Look at all these old
magazines and game diagrams.
Some of this material dates
back to the early Showa period.
This book is so old!
A classic joseki.
It reminds me of the first
time I played Hikaru.
Normally, black would
play right here,
and then atari underneath.
That's usually accepted
as a good move.
But he extended and
used an outdated joseki.
It's still a strong move,
but it creates an opening
that can be taken advantage of.
Hikaru never gave me
the chance though.
He overwhelmed me
before I could attack.
Normal skills aren't going
to be enough to defeat him.
If I ever want to
surpass him, I'll
have to invent a
brand new joseki.
-Let's play a game while
you straighten up the place.
-Hm?
-Toya, I didn't
say you could stop.
I don't wanna see you
looking at this board.
I just told you to do something.
What are you waiting for?
-Sorry.
Are you asking me to play blind?
-Mm-hm.
-I don't understand.
You asked me to come
in here and clean up.
-It's not your
job to understand.
It's your job to do what
your senpai tells you to.
If you wanna be a member
of the Kaio Go club,
then you're gonna have
to do as you're told.
You got that?
-Even a pro would find it
difficult to play a game blind.
This isn't Shogi, you know.
Go is played on a
much larger board.
-But you are the
great Akira Toya.
Aren't you supposed
to be a future Meijin?
No one can hold a candle
to you at the tournaments.
We all know that.
I wish you'd just turn pro
already, win your four or five
titles, and retire.
But you won't do that, will you?
You'll stick around our Go
club and constantly remind
everyone of how much
better you are than us.
Hm.
This is a real surprise.
I would've never guessed
that our best player would
be afraid of a
friendly little game.
-So I'm your best player?
-I thought so, thought you
were, but I'm not sure anymore.
-If I am the best,
then I should be
able to beat you
with my eyes closed.
I'm going to accept
your challenge.
Call your first move.
-Fine.
16, 4.
The star point.
-4, 15, star point.
-4, 16 it is.
I'll take 16, 17, the small eye.
AKIRA: 4, 4, the star point.
-4, 4.
Right on the star point.
You're gonna make
me a legend at Kaio.
You know that, right?
I'll be the guy who beat
Touya in an even game
without a handicap.
But I need one more favor.
-Hm?
-Try not to make this
too boring, all right?
If you could avoid making
too many wrong moves,
it'll probably make my victory
a little more memorable.
-I don't mind if
you brag, but please
wait until after you beat me.
It'll be more satisfying.
-Aren't you clever?
You're the one
who said that even
a pro would have
trouble playing blind.
We'll see how good you
are, won't we, Toya?
Approach at 6, 4.
AKIRA: 3, 6.
-6, 6.
AKIRA: 4, 14.
-Toya's been in there awhile.
Do you think he's
struggling yet?
-Probably.
Playing Go without looking
is practically impossible.
-Yeah.
-We actually found a
way to make Toya play
with his hands and feet tied up.
We're brilliant!
-It's my turn to
defeat the whiz kid.
-Not yet.
Ito's probably
still playing him.
-I know, but I want to
see Toya in a cold sweat.
Hey, guys.
I get to play next.
Ito.
What happened?
You resigned?
But you're barely
halfway through the game!
-I wasn't expecting
another challenger.
I'd be happy to play a game
against you too, Senpai.
-Ito was defeated because
it was one on one.
Toya beat him quickly
so he wouldn't
have to remember a lot of
moves, and I'll get beaten too.
Toya can't be defeated by one
lone player, but against two--
-Okamura!
Get in here right now!
-Hm?
-You and Kojima are
both gonna play.
-Wha-- So Akira's supposed to
face two opponents and still
not look at the boards?
-In a one on one game,
we don't stand a chance.
-That's crazy!
-Two games at the same time?
-Something wrong?
Are you afraid?
No one's forcing you to be here.
Go ahead.
Walk away.
But if you chicken
out and run home,
you're just leaving this room.
You're leaving the Kaio Go club.
We don't want you here!
-Hm.
Call out your first moves.
But know this.
I'm not gonna make this
easy for either of you.
-What's wrong?
A future Meijin has
just challenged you
to a friendly game.
-Fine.
16, 4, the star point.
-4, 16, star point.
-4, 16, at the star point.
-17, 4, the small eye.
-4, 3, the small eye.
-16, 17, the small eye
AKIRA: 4, 4, the star point.
-16, 17, the small eye.
AKIRA: 4, 16.
-Approach at 6, 17.
-16, 15.
-15, 3.
OKAMURA: 13, 17.
AKIRA: 17, 17.
KOJIMA: 17, 15.
-17, 14.
-17, 18.
-17, 16.
KOJIMA: 3, 3.
AKIRA: 5, 3.
OKAMURA: 5, 17.
-4, 17.
KOJIMA: 6, 6.
-7, 5.
ITO (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Kojima isn't half
the player I am,
and Okamura is just
playing terrible.
-5, 18.
ITO (VOICEOVER): At
this pace, they're
gonna lose faster than I did.
-Come on.
What's taking you so long?
-Uh-- b-- block at 4, 18.
-About time.
KOJIMA: 2, 4.
-Extend at 10, 4.
-Um, 6, 18.
Got that?
-(VOICEOVER) What
a horrible move.
-Huh?
Hello?
Why do you take so long with me?
You're playing
quicker with Kojima.
-(VOICEOVER) Something's
wrong with Toya.
Both these games
have barely begun,
and he's already slowing down.
But not against Kojima.
Why's he struggling
against Okamura?
Ah!
That's it!
Okamura may be a weak
player, but Toya's still
gonna lose to him.
He won't last
another five minutes.
-It's your turn.
Hurry up, already.
[laughter]
OKAMURA: This is
getting ridiculous!
I haven't got all day, you know?
-(VOICEOVER) Okamura
plays go like a child.
His moves make no sense.
They're awful.
Toya's trying to follow
the field of a game.
The logical flow of moves.
That's how he can remember
what the board looks like.
But Okamura isn't
making expected moves,
and that's missing
up Toya's rhythm.
Akira is too dependent
on logic, but that's not
going to work here.
This is hilarious.
-10-- 17.
-All right.
10, 17.
Toya, I've already one
of my stones there.
-Focus.
Side extension.
4, 9.
-4, 9.
OK.
This game has started
to fall to pieces.
Now all I have to do is
tighten up my strategy.
(VOICEOVER) The only
strategy you should use
is your awful technique.
-My turn.
Approach at 3, 14.
-I'll take 4, 11.
OKAMURA: Extend at 10, 4.
-17.
6.
-(VOICEOVER) I've got you
cornered now, don't I?
Any minute now I'm gonna
see you crash and burn.
HIDAKA: Toya?
Are you in here?
-Hidaka-senpai?
-Ito?
Kojima?
Ah, Toya.
You promised me a
teaching game today.
Come on.
Hm.
You're a seventh grader.
What are you doing here?
Answer me when I talk to you.
-It's like-- it's kind of
like we were just, uh-- uh--
-Mr. Yun wanted this
room cleaned up.
He said I should-- I should, uh,
get a seventh grader to do it,
so I asked, uh,
Toya to help us out.
OKAMURA: I wanted Toya to
play a teaching game with us,
but he seemed kind of busy,
and his hands were full.
So I thought that maybe
he could, well, you know--
-Spit it out.
-I asked-- we asked
him to play us blind.
-Idiots!
Do you two think you're too
good to help him clean up?
You guys have really
got a lot of nerve.
You should be ashamed.
And you!
Are you behind all this?
-No.
Not really.
I just--
-Toya!
You should know matter.
What were you thinking?
I'll take care of
cleaning up, all right?
I want you to sit down
and finish up your games.
AKIRA: Ah, Hidaka-senpai?
I agreed to play both
these matches blind.
I gave my word.
I am sorry.
-Don't be stupid.
I'm not gonna stand here
and allow this bullying
to continue.
-But I said I would.
-Stop it.
-Just stop talking and
listen for a change.
You've been nothing but trouble
ever since you got here.
What's worse is that you
brought all this on yourself.
Why did you accept
their stupid challenge?
You're encouraging them!
If you hadn't come
here, this wouldn't--
Akira, what I mean is-- you're
not just a Kaio student,
you're also an important
member of our Go club.
You should hold
your head up high.
You owe it to yourself
to play them fair
and square, and
beat them that way.
Don't let anyone
push you around.
-Right.
I understand, Hidaka.
Oh.
These games shouldn't
take more than about
five minutes to finish,
but after that, I'd
be happy to play a
practice game with you.
I'm so sorry to
keep you waiting.
Let's continue.
HIKARU: Kimihiro!
Where are you?
I found us a new member.
And she already
knows how to play.
-Really?
-Ah--
-This is great.
Now we can enter the tournament.
-So, uh, you know
how to play Go?
-Of course I do.
-Not that it matters.
Our club is open to anyone
who wants to learn the game.
-What are you talking about?
It's better if we get an
experienced player on our team.
-I'm afraid it doesn't
matter how good she is.
-Hm?
-She still won't be
able to compete with us.
The boys and girls are
split into two divisions.
Nice try, though.
-That's right.
I forgot.
We could throw some pants
and a jacket on her.
She'd pass for a
boy, no problem.
-What a waste of time.
You said all I had to do
was play in the tournaments.
I'm too busy with volleyball
to deal with this stuff.
-Wait!
-Hikaru, you really
shouldn't have said that.
-Let's see if I got
this straight, OK?
There has to be three
members on a Go team?
-Yep. you got it.
And we're still one guy short.
It'd be great to
find a decent player.
The stronger the better.
Got any suggestions, Sai?
-You should consider
asking Akira's father.
He's a very strong.
-I can see it now.
Toya's dad would look really
cool in a school uniform.
Hey, I've got a great idea.
We can put up a new poster.
It'll have a life and
death problem on it.
Whoever solves it gets
invited to join our team.
-Just calm down.
The person doesn't
have to be good.
We'll take anyone!
-Doesn't Kaio's club have
dozens and dozens of members
to pick from?
-Yeah, they do.
They the cream of the crop.
Hmph.
It's so unfair.
-Come on.
We who we are, right?
Who'd wanna go to Kaio?
I wouldn't.
-Hm.
Wait up!
Ito, the eighth greater.
He just told me he's
quitting the Go club.
I just thought that you
might wanna know that, Toya.
Your presence has put
everyone here on edge.
Our members are
nervous around you.
Even I'm nervous around you,
and I'm the captain of the club.
I have to tell you something.
I've actually been meaning to
ask you to play a teaching game
with me, but I won't.
Kaio can't afford to see their
captain humiliated by a younger
player.
What I'd really like to do is
to sit down and battle it out
with you, like Aoki did.
But I don't have that luxury.
Not like you, Toya.
You're here because of
some childish vendetta.
I've heard all the stories
about your big showdowns
against that bot who goes to
Haze Middle, Hikaru Shindou.
That must really drive you
nuts, losing to some kid
your own age.
I think you should ask
yourself one question.
Is it really worth it?
Every one in the Go club is
suffering because if you.
You've caused nothing but
problems since you arrived.
-Hikaru keeps
refusing to play me.
I don't know why, but to be
honest, I don't really care.
If he won't face
me alone, then I'll
do whatever it takes to
force him into a match.
Even if it means playing in
a middle school tournament.
You've accused me of
causing nothing but problems
since I arrived.
-Huh?
-Shindou's playing at
the next tournament.
Think that'll be a problem
for your precious club?
So, choose.
Kick me out because I might
embarrass you, or accept
I'm the only player who's
got a chance at being Hikaru.
[theme music]
HIKARU: Guess what, Sai?
I found someone
else at my school
who knows how to play Go!
He's really good.
He might be better
than Kimihiro.
SAI: There's something
about him that troubles me.
HIKARU: Oh, come on.
If he joins the club, we'll
win the tournament for sure.
Next time, the Third Player.
-SAI: Hikaru.
He's cheating!
HIKARU: No way!