NARRATOR: After many
years inside a go board,
a spirit from the past known as
Fujiwara no Sai has returned.
Visible only to Hikaru
Shindo, a master of go,
Sai seeks to play
the divine move.
[theme song]
-You actually won!
-(LAUGHING) Yep, I did it!
-Akira?
Hey, Toya!
He came here check up on me.
-What are you talking about?
In case you didn't notice, he
just completely ignored you.
There's no way you
and him are rivals.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): He said
I'd never see him again.
But he's waiting for me.
He's waiting for me to
rise up to his level.
-OK, just a few more.
-This calls for
a change of plan.
I'm going to destroy him.
-They're so lucky.
They've finished,
and now they're
going to watch Akira's match.
-Huh?
-I know we played
against him, what is it?
A total of four times now.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Yeah, but we've
never seen him play anyone else.
And now he's playing the
[inaudible] and I'm stuck here!
-Hikaru, Hikaru, why don't you
let me play this game for you?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Huh?
-I'll finish it
off as quickly as I
can so we can go and
watch Akira's match.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Don't be silly.
[knocking]
-Hello.
May we come in?
-Oh, hey there, Waya.
Good to see you, Sumi.
-Mashiba.
-Nice to see you both.
So how have you been?
-Pretty good.
-We can replay the game for
you so you're up to speed.
-You want me to be white?
-All these extra spectators
because Toya's playing.
-So Isumi, think this will
be the year you finally
get to pass the pro exam?
-Uh, hope so.
-Isumi's a pretty good player.
Maybe better than me.
I guess luck was on
my side when I passed.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): I'd like to
wipe that smile off his face.
Then he might stop gloating.
-Making your own luck
is part of the game.
I suppose you want to be
one of the first players
to take down Toya?
-Uh-huh.
The thought certainly
crossed my mind.
-No offense, Mashiba,
but but you're
never going to be good
enough to defeat Toya.
Even Zama-sensei is
finding it tough.
See?
He had to use a
double hane here.
-Hm.
That's a very strange
move for an oza
to make against a new 1-dan.
It strikes me as
a bit desperate.
-He should have made a
good solid connection here.
Maybe he's just trying out some
new tactics against the rookie.
-Isumi, want to replay the game?
-Sure.
-Toya has been playing a
superb match up to this point.
-Yeah.
What do you bet Zama-sensei is
chewing on the end of his fan?
-Oh, yeah.
That's such a weird habit
for someone of his standing.
Tell you what.
I'll go take a look.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
At last, it's over!
Let's see, how'd I do?
-All right, Hikaru!
You won by 2 and 1/2 points!
That's great.
Let's go!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Yeah, yeah.
I kind of got distracted
thinking about Akira
during the game.
-OK, 20 and 40 and 50.
58.
-It's no good.
I'm 2 and 1/2 points short.
So you won.
-Thanks a lot, and good game!
-You know this move?
-Huh?
-Do you think I made the right
counter-move to your attack?
You really seemed like you
knew what you were doing there.
-Uh, well, I, uh--
-Hurry, hurry!
Don't you want to see
the end of Akira's match?
Hurry!
Let's go!
-Hm.
Yes, you played that very well.
But if your opponent had
responded differently,
you might have been in trouble.
-He's not going to--
NARRATOR: HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Analyze the game!
-Now in this situation--
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Why'd
he have to come and give us
a lesson now?
We need to get out of here!
-Please, sensei!
I promise I'll go
over the game with him
later on when we get home!
Just please let him go now!
Please please please please
please please please!
-Huh?
Whoa.
He's really going for it.
-That throw in by black
was a very aggressive move.
It certainly puts the
pressure on white.
How he responds now could change
the whole course of the game.
If he cuts black off,
the next few moves
could be costly for both sides.
-He captured instead
of cutting it off!
He felt threatened
and compromised.
-I don't believe it.
Did you see that?
The oza shied away
from a battle.
-What would have happened
if he played a cut here?
Or here?
-Hm.
Both sides would be in
a dangerous position.
-Zama-sensei probably
just avoided the battle
because he knew he
could afford to.
-I don't think so.
He's not the sort of
person to take chances,
especially against
someone like Toya.
He seems flustered to me.
-Imagine the
humiliation if he lost.
Now he's backed into a corner.
He's trying a
different approach.
-He may not even get the
opportunity to fight back.
-I can't believe Toya's leading.
Come on!
Hang in there to the finish!
-Calm down.
The oza's bound to have a
few more tricks up his sleeve
before he's done.
TOYA (VOICEOVER): I won't go
on the defensive just yet.
I'm still in a good position.
There's going to be a
public record of the game,
and it's a safe bet
Shindo will see it.
I'll show him.
He'll be jealous
of my every move.
-A knight's move?
-I don't understand
what he's trying to do.
He should be protecting the
lower half of the board.
-He's gone and left himself
wide open to an attack.
-Nah, don't worry.
-I'm sure he knows
exactly what he's doing.
-Why is he still attacking?
I've never seen anyone
play like that before.
-He's vulnerable.
Zama-sensei will take
full advantage of that.
-But he's having
to think about it.
I've never seen
anything like it.
-How's Toya doing?
-Huh?
-Someone else coming to watch?
-Shindo.
About time.
-Hey, guys.
How's the game been going?
-We'll show you if you like.
We can replay it
from the beginning.
-Toya's playing black
and the oza is white.
Not only did he start first,
but they gave black a 5 and 1/2
point komi.
-Why'd they give him a komi?
-A top pro playing a new 1-dan?
They've got to have one
to keep it competitive.
-Although such a small
handicap still makes it
tough for the new guy.
But none of the top pros take
these games too seriously,
so it kind of balances out.
-Are you saying the
oza might let Toya win?
-Normally, yeah.
But it doesn't
look like it today.
The oza's giving
it all he's got.
-Whoa!
He played there?
-Yeah.
Then white captured
instead of cutting.
The oza's not taking any
chances in this game.
He's being real cautious.
-He knows it's a tough match.
He's biding his time, waiting
for the smallest error.
Then he'll pounce
and take control
of the board when he's ready.
It's a dangerous strategy,
but he wants to win.
-Hm.
-Then instead of
protecting his territory,
Toya went and played here.
-What?
Why'd he go and do that?
It's an interesting
choice, but I
don't understand why he'd
leave himself wide open.
-Huh?
He's decided to go
in for the attack!
-Black must've known that white
would attack sooner or later.
The question is, how's
he going to respond?
What are you going to do, Toya?
And what about you, Zama-sensei?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Akira,
you're playing an awesome game.
-If he only played
defensively, Toya
might have been able to win.
But he keeps on attacking.
There's got be something
driving him on.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I think
I know what's driving him.
Akira, there's a message for me
in here somewhere, isn't there?
I'm going to keep improving my
game and then catch up to you!
Just you wait!
It's going to happen!
For sure, it's gonna happen!
-Huh?
It's snowing!
-1,000 years may have
passed, but some things
remain the same.
Snowflakes falling, fierce
battles on the board.
Every move tells
a story revealing
the innermost thoughts of
those who play the game.
The clatter of stones on the
board echoes through the air.
The tension is exciting!
-How could he be a threat
to me at his level?
But even if it is true
that he's chasing after me,
I'll move so far ahead
of him that he'll never
catch up to me.
He won't even come close.
TOYA (VOICEOVER): I don't
care who might be chasing me.
There are 500 pro players,
and my sights are set on them
and them alone.
I'm going to beat them all.
You don't matter to me, Shindo.
-Don't underestimate me.
-Huh?
-Did you think
I'd fall for that?
Take a look at
this move, junior.
-[gasp]
-You were planning to play
your stone in that position
after securing this
area, weren't you?
You were too slow.
One of your father's students
might have gone for it,
but not me.
Hey, have you've forgotten
who you're playing?
Did you think you
could outwit me?
I think you'll find
the game is even.
-He got caught off guard.
-The oza's last move has
made it extremely hard
to predict the outcome.
You've got to hand it to him,
he's playing like a champion.
-Now for the end game.
-This is going to
be really close!
-Hm.
-Hikaru?
The game's concluding, but it's
difficult to tell who will win.
-Come on, Toya!
-Huh?
-He's been playing such
an awesome game up to now!
He can't let it end like this!
If he can just hang
on, I know he's
got enough strength inside
of him to win this match!
-[gasp] He's forcing the play.
He'll get cut off.
-You think so?
-He's pushed it too far.
It could be over.
It all depends on
how the oza responds.
-He resigned.
-OK.
Let's review the game.
Even though he lost, I thought
he played a respectable game.
Very proficient.
-Yes, he certainly had the oza
on the right there for a while.
-We should go and offer our
congratulations on a good game.
-Isumi, um, do you
think they'd mind
if we snuck in and
said hi as well?
-Next year, I'll be in there.
-Yeah.
Sure.
-It's getting late.
We should go.
-Hey, Shindo, we're leaving.
-I think I'm gonna
stay a bit longer.
-Whatever.
See you.
-Akira went for the
knockout and it didn't work.
I guess you're not the only
one who can beat him, huh, Sai?
You know what?
I'm gonna remember
everything about this match
for a long time.
-Indeed.
The way Akira played
today was truly memorable.
-Yeah!
I really liked it.
It was cool.
Wow, look at all this
snow! [laughing] Woohoo!
Woohoo!
If Akira keeps playing
as good as this,
he's really going to be worth
pursuing as an opponent,
don't you think?
[laughing] Yeah!
-Don't forget that you've
come a long way too, Hikaru.
-Yeah, but it's all
thanks to Akira.
Maybe with him
ahead of me, I could
become a meijin, or
an oza, or anything!
TOYA (VOICEOVER): If Akira
Toya had never met Hikaru,
he would have walked
the path destined
for him without any diversions.
But now when he
stops and looks back,
he pulls Hikaru along
the path with him.
It's almost as if--
as if fate had put him
here to help Hikaru develop
and grow stronger as he
walks his own path through life.
[theme song]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I've got
to make it into the A League!
SAI (VOICEOVER): Why are
you in such a hurry, Hikaru?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): If
I'm not in the A League,
I can't compete in the
Young Lions Tournament.
That's where Akira
will be playing next.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Are you
sure you're ready for that?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Bring it on!
Next time, Fear and Impatience!
SAI (VOICEOVER): Turn
your fear into courage.
Then you'll be in
a position to win!