[theme music]
-Sit down and I'll play
a teaching game with you.
-I'm not playing
any teaching game.
-Huh?
I can't let my guard
down for a single minute.
This guy's stronger
than I thought.
If I lose, then that's it.
It's all over for me.
Hey, you!
You're going to
have to tell me what
your name is, if I
don't win this game.
-Oh yeah?
You're going to remember
my name all right.
-Hm.
What's happening here?
Is there something
special going on today?
Oh.
Hello, Mr. Yun.
We've got a match in progress
between a Japanese insei
and a Korean insei.
-An international showdown, huh?
Huh?
That's the boy from
Haze middle school.
-You mean you know him?
-Yeah.
I recognize him.
He's an insei?
Are you guys sure about that?
-That's what the kid
said when they got here.
He's playing Mr.
Ryu's nephew who
happens to be
visiting from Korea.
-He's an insei ready?
It can't be.
That's impossible.
Now what was his name?
I think it was Shindo.
I remember the first
time I saw him play.
I was very impressed by him.
-Huh?
-You played extremely well.
[sobbing] But the
next time I saw him,
his performance
was disappointing.
And I wasn't the only
one was disappointed.
His opponent, Akira Toya,
obviously felt the same way,
judging by his
reaction to the game.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
-Same to you, It
was a good match.
-I know a whole year
has passed since then.
But could he really
ahve improved so much
that he's now an insei?
-Come on.
I can't lose to him.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Oh man.
There's no way--
no way I'm going
to lose to a guy like him.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Even though this all
started with an
argument, the end result
is an absolutely
wonderful game of Go!
Both of them are playing
such inspired moves.
And they're
responding with moves
that are equally inspired.
They're both desperate
to win the match.
They're throwing
caution to the wind.
Yes.
It is as though their hands
are moving of their own accord,
forging a new path
with each stone.
How radiant they are
as their game improves.
But there can only
be one winner.
Which one of them will follow
the path that leads to victory?
YUN (VOICEOVER):
This is remarkable.
Even though the Korean
boy has the advantage,
Shindo's holding his own.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): They're
both playing a risky game
with some tough moves, but
Shindo's still slightly behind.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Shindo!
YUN (VOICEOVER):
What's he intending
to do with that last move?
-Hm.
He just made a big mistake.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): What do you
think you're doing, Shindo?
What kind of move was that?
YUN (VOICEOVER):
What's happening?
Was that a careless mistake or
was a part of a bigger plan?
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): Shindo.
SU-YEONG (VOICEOVER): Did
you make a wrong move?
Oh well.
That's too bad.
I guess it was the
best you could do.
SAI (VOICEOVER): No one realizes
what Hikaru's strategy is.
He's playing at a level far
above anyone in this room.
[gasp]
SU-YEONG (VOICEOVER): I thought
that move of his was a mistake,
but now it's put him
in a great position.
[groan]
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
That move Shindo
made earlier wasn't
a mistake at all.
He was anticipating a battle
for the upper left corner.
-Hm?
YUN (VOICEOVER): He
was fully aware he
was going to lose ground
in the middle of the board.
But now all of a sudden change,
Shindo has the advantage.
-You think we made
that move, he could
have been thinking
this far ahead?
Did he plan the whole thing?
-Huh?
SU-YEONG (VOICEOVER): The
game could go either way,
but I can still win
by-- by moving here.
He was going after that stone?
I should have seen it coming.
I can't let it bother me.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
Su-Yeong's managing
to catch up with Shindo.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Uh-oh.
Shindo's lost territory.
-Hm.
-I don't believe it.
Shindo wins by one
and a half points.
-What an amazing match.
Really intense.
-You're telling me.
It had me guessing right
up to the very end.
-Kudos to both players.
They should be proud of
that game, win or lose.
-What an attack by white.
What a game.
-Su-Yeong, you OK?
[sobbing]
SU-YEONG (VOICEOVER):
I-- I lost?
I haven't been beaten like
that in a long, long time.
I played one bad game,
and then paid for it
by dropping down a class for
the first time in my life.
My game's been
messed up ever since.
Then this guy appears
and challenges me.
So I take him on.
I played a tough game, but
he stayed right with me.
I'm just as good as he is.
Even though he won,
I won't be defeated.
I'll come back to an
Japan and play you again.
But next time as a pro.
-I want to know your name!
-Huh?
-Tell me what's your name.
I need to know
what your name is.
-My name's Hikaru Shindo.
Hope you'll remember it.
Hikaru Shindo.
-Hikaru Shindo.
I got it.
-Su-Yeong.
He's so disappointed in himself,
he can't hold back his tears.
That's the way it should be.
-Huh?
-He was advancing so
smoothly up the ranks
that dropping down a class
came as quite a shock.
He felt ashamed and he
didn't want to admit it.
He tried avoiding
all the frustration
that was building inside him.
-I think this is yours Su-Yeong.
[cheering]
-He's going to be OK.
Su-Yeong goes back
to Korea tomorrow,
and I have no doubt
his game is going
to improve because of
what happened here today.
-Shindo.
-Huh?
-Who's that?
-Um-- he's a-- I--
-Hikaru, don't
you recognize him?
It's the man from the Go club.
-I'm Mr. Yun, advisor to
the Kaio School Go club.
You probably don't remember me.
-You're from Kaio Middle School?
-If my memory serves
me right, this
is the third time we've met.
The first time I saw
you, I was astonished
by how well you played.
And to think you were
only in grade school.
-Actually, I think that
was one of my games.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): -Right.
-The second time was
last year's tournament.
I had high expectations of you,
but you didn't live up to them.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
But after seeing
him play today, your opinion
of him has changed, hasn't it?
-Now I've seen you
play a third time.
I have to say I'm amazed.
-I knew it!
I knew it!
-As I was standing there
watching the two of you
fight it out, I saw
strong aspiring pros.
You handled a difficult position
with great skill and maturity.
-Wow!
Did you hear that?
Hikaru?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Yeah.
What a great compliment.
And it's for me!
Not Sai!
-When I think back to
when I first saw you,
that wonderful game of Go you
played that helped Haze win
the school tournament--
SAI (VOICEOVER): Thank you.
That was all my doing.
-I didn't believe a
student in sixth grade
could be capable of such
a high level of play.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Of course not.
-But today's match was every
bit as impressive as that one.
SAI (VOICEOVER): No.
You've got it all mixed up.
That was me.
-And now I'm convinced.
The person who played that
magical match and the person I
see here are one and the same.
I won't forget your name.
It'll stay in my memory forever.
Hikaru Shindo.
-Well should we go home?
Great game today.
You did really good.
-I can't believe the pro
exams start next week already.
Next time we see each other,
we'll be in the exam room.
-Remember.
The exam isn't at
the Go Association.
The matches all take
place at the study center.
-Got it.
-See you later.
-See you.
Sai, what do you say
we head home too?
OK?
Ahh.
You know what?
I'm kind of good.
Isn't it awesome?
The teacher from Kaio
thinks my game is so strong
that he believes it was me
who was playing in the school
tournament!
He actually believes he was
watching me and not you.
In his eyes, you never
even existed, Sai.
[gasp]
SAI (VOICEOVER): I
don't don't exist?
-Once day, I'm going to erase
Sai from Akira's memory too!
SAI (VOICEOVER): Erase me?
-Remember the name--
Hikaru Shindo.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Why
am I suddenly feeling
so apprehensive?
What does this mean?
[theme music]
SAI (VOICEOVER): The big
day has come, Hikaru.
Time for you to
take the pro exam.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
I have to pass
if I want to catch
up with Akira.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Gorilla man's back.
This time, don't let
him intimidate you.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I
think I can handle him now.
SAI (VOICEOVER): That's
the spirit, Hikaru.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Next
time-- the pro exam begins!
SAI (VOICEOVER): Remember,
only the top three
can go to become pros.
There is a long struggle ahead.