NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past
known as Fujiwara-no-Sai
has returned, visible
only to Hikaru Shindou.
A master of Go, Sai seeks
to play the Divine Move.
[theme music]
-Is it it true?
I can really play as
much Go as I want?
-Yeah!
Let's get started.
S-A-I. Sai!
OK, let's do it!
[beep]
-Huh?
-Is everything OK?
-Uh, someone sent me a message.
Can you tell me what
they're trying to say?
-Uh, let me have a look.
He's saying that you're
too good a player.
He wants to know
if you're a pro.
He seems impressed.
HIKARU: That's because
he's not very good.
-Don't you wanna answer him?
HIKARU: Ugh, no way.
-Then you have to bring
the cursor over to this box
and click here.
Why are you looking at me?
Watch the screen.
-OK.
-If you don't want to answer,
just close the dialog window.
-Thanks for the help.
-Not a problem.
Let me know if you
get stuck again.
-I think I need some
computer lessons.
-I am astounded.
Can you tell me, how
does this-- this box let
us play against so many
different opponents?
-How should I know?
-Oh.
Hey.
Do you think people are inside?
-Right.
Time for a new game.
We'll find someone
who's Japanese.
Sai, would you quite doing that?
Let's see.
-The way he responded
seems a bit immature.
I bet this person is a kid.
-Look, it's zelda.
I hope you're ready
for another game, Sai.
-Oh!
This is the happiest
day of my life!
I get to play more Go games.
-I don't think I've ever
seen you this happy.
-I get to play more Go games.
I get to play more Go games.
-This is just the
beginning, Sai.
We've got the whole summer!
-Wait a minute.
This guy's Japanese.
And I think he
might even be a kid.
-Is he skilled?
-I don't know.
-Please be cautious.
Last time you clicked on the
wrong spot and ended our game.
-I already told you,
I'm still trying
to figure out how to
use this computer.
BOY: This is weird.
Who's this Sai?
He's good.
HIKARU: Well, what do you think?
Is this guy any good?
-He's strong.
Strong as any I've faced.
1, 10.
-If you're impressed,
then he must be amazing.
[beep]
-What?
He just resigned from the game.
-A player with his skill
is able to quickly judge
the positions on the board.
He must've realize how
strong I was and decided
that continuing the
game would be futile.
The weaker the player,
the more likely
they'll continue the match even
if their defeat is unavoidable.
Remember when you used
to make that mistake?
-Aw, be quiet!
Hey, h--- how's it going?
-Pretty good, thanks.
Need any help?
-Could you send
this guy a message
that says, strong, aren't I?
-All right, but pay attention.
You gotta learn how to type
these messages on your own,
you know.
There you are.
-Thanks a lot.
-Have fun.
-This whole internet thing
is actually pretty awesome.
You're an excellent player.
Who are you, anyway?
I'm an Insei.
An Insei?
-Hey, Hikaru?
Could you finish up
when you get a chance?
My shift's gonna be over soon.
-I was just about done, anyway.
Looks like this zelda
is trying to turn pro.
He must practice all the time.
-Please stop your games.
It's time for lunch.
We'll meet back here in an hour.
BOY: Something
bugging you, Waya?
-Eh?
-You're acting kind
of strange today.
Did you make a mistake in
the first half of the match?
-You're crazy.
I never mess up.
Leave me alone.
How come this had to
happen to be right
when I'm taking my pro test?
Look at that guy.
He's totally freaking out.
-That's and awful move.
WAYA: Everybody's waited
all year for this.
And so have I. I've
got to pass this exam.
Why does that kid
look so relaxed?
Huh?
You're Akira Toya!
-Hm?
Hello.
-Isn't he famous?
-Toya Meijin is his dad?
-I can't believe he
has to take the test.
-Are you sure it's really him?
I thought he'd be taller.
-I hope I don't
have to play him.
-You honestly didn't
know he was here?
-Yeah.
-I knew he was taking the test.
I found out this morning.
-Seriously?
-Yeah, because I'm playing
against him in today's match.
I have no chance.
He's already got me beat.
-When was the last time
you heard a pro whining
about the strength
of their opponent.
You're never gonna beat
him with that attitude.
-You try and win against him.
-Sorry to interrupt,
but are you both Insei?
-Yep.
My name's Fuku.
This is my first time
taking the pro test.
My buddy Waya has already
failed the exam twice.
Right?
-Why'd you tell him that?
-What luck!
I finally try and
become a pro player
and there's no way I
can win my first match.
-You're just giving up?
You haven't even
finished the game yet.
Pull yourself together and
show Toya's who's boss!
-Is there a reason why
you're acting so crazy today?
Did something happen to you?
-I was playing this guy
on the internet yesterday.
He was way better than I
was and beat me easily.
With that kind of skill,
he'd have to be a pro, right?
You know what this guy does?
He sends an online
message taunting me.
It said, strong, aren't I.
-That doesn't sound
like something
that a real professional
player would right.
-I don't remember
asking for your opinion.
-You're being loud.
Everyone's staring.
-(VOICEOVER) I need
to forget about Sai.
I'm gonna get my three wins and
get through the preliminaries.
But why can't I get
him out of my head?
-Hm.
So this is Sai.
You were last year's
US Representative.
I'd like to know what
you think of him.
-He's great.
I'd love to have the
chance to play him online.
-Now that the word's
out, he's constantly
receiving game requests.
You'll have to wait in
line if you want a match.
-That's too bad.
I suppose I have to
just sit back and watch
like everyone else.
-More and more people are
logging on just too watch Sai.
His popularity seems to
be growing by the day.
-Teacher.
Do you think this mystery
player could be a pro?
-I'm guessing that he isn't.
I've never heard of
a professional who
played against
amateurs this often.
-How did he get so good?
-Where'd this guy come from?
He never loses.
-He's better than
anyone I've ever faced.
-(VOICEOVER) I've only
had one match against Sai,
and he wouldn't chat with me,
regardless of how many messages
I sent him.
After asking around, I
discovered that he never
chats with anybody
Why does Sai insist
on keeping his identity secret?
-I'm leaving for the World
Amateur Championship this week.
Once I get to Japan--
-I'm going to track Sai down.
-He's not going to be able to
be able to hide in the shadows
forever.
[wind chime]
-(VOICEOVER) So, what
exactly do I know about Sai?
He started playing
in July, and he only
goes online in the
middle of the day.
He must have a lot
of time on his hands.
I wonder if he's even got a job?
-Because it's
getting warm outside.
-July and August.
Summer break.
There isn't any school.
It can't be!
He's a kid.
ANNOUNCER: Over the
past decade, I've
had the fortune of watching
our competitors steadily
improve as they begin to play
Go at a much higher level.
I have never seen such
dedication for this game.
It's my pleasure
to welcome players
from more than 50 countries
to this year's tournament.
Your participation is
proof of Go's popularity
throughout the world.
There will be a total
of eight matches.
Two games will take place every
day for the next four days.
Remember to focus,
to try your hardest,
and most importantly,
to have fun.
If any of our participants
haven't been assigned a game
yet, please visit our
registration booth
in the main lobby as soon
as you get the chance.
Good luck to all of you,
and have a great tournament!
-(VOICEOVER) Sai's
an amazing player.
I've known that since the
first time I saw him online.
I've watched tons of his
matches over the past month,
trying to find any
weakness I've noticed
he's been acting differently.
Something about him has changed.
Is he trying out
some new strategies?
Can a player like
him get any stronger?
-Have a safe trip, Seinsei.
I hope you can find
out who Sai really is.
-He's unbelievable.
That guy's beaten every
opponent he's ever faced.
-(VOICEOVER) I'm itching
to find out more about Sai,
but that'll have to wait.
I'll have plenty
of time to search
for him after the competition.
Right now I've got
to stay focused.
-(VOICEOVER) I have to bring
the championship back to China.
I can't let anything
distract me.
The only thing I should be
worrying about is winning.
I'll look for Sai once
the tournament is over.
-Will the contestants
please choose for color?
You may now begin your games.
-Morishita-sensei,
I'd like to thank you
for agreeing to serve as
our head judge this year.
-Organizing this tournament
must be exhausting.
-Once the competition
starts, most of my work
has already been done.
The toughest part of my job is
getting all these participants
into Japan.
Arranging visas for this many
players can be quite tricky.
Each country has its own
set of rules and regulations
for traveling here.
We do whatever we can to help,
and usually all our efforts
are rewarded.
Go is truly an
international game.
MORISHITA: Waya.
-Sensei?
-So, is this a student of yours?
-Waya?
He sure is.
I asked him to
help us out today.
Hm.
What's with that
look on your face?
You OK?
A few of these
international competitors
might have some spare
time between matches.
I want you to play a
couple of games with them,
just to see how
good you really are.
I'm not expecting you
to beat a top amateur,
but you should be evenly matched
against some of the lesser
players.
I know that you
won't let me down.
An inexperienced competitor
could learn a lot
from my best student.
Right?
[laughter] Waya managed to
make it through the pro test
preliminaries with a record
of three wins and one loss.
I bet it would have been
four wins if he haven't
had to face Toya-sensei's son.
-Do you mean Akira Toya?
I heard he was taking
the test this year.
MORISHITA: You'd better
pass the main exam.
-Sensei?
-Hm?
-Listen.
There's this really strong
player you should know about.
-Hm?
Are you talking about Toya?
I know he's good.
-Forget about Toya!
I'm talking about this
new guy I saw on the net.
-Someone on the internet?
Did you check to
see if he was a pro?
-He's always online, even
on scheduled game days.
-Sounds like he's an amateur.
A few of them are
incredibly strong.
Japan's top amateur,
Shimano, is playing today.
He can give a pro a
run for his money.
-He's much better than him.
-Huh?
Are you serious?
How good is he?
-(VOICEOVER) You wouldn't have
a chance against him, Sensei.
But I can't tell you that.
How good?
Uh--
-It's not important.
These so-called amateurs are
getting better every day.
-Give me five minutes.
He's probably online right now.
-We can talk about this later.
Don't you have some work to do?
[knocking]
WAYA: Is anyone here?
-Who are you?
-Hello.
I'm Waya, an Insei.
I've been looking for a
computer with internet access.
Would it be all right
if I used one of yours?
-Sure.
Go ahead.
That laptop is already online.
-Thanks a lot.
I won't take long.
-He's not logged in.
Argh.
I'm all finished.
Should I turn it off?
-No.
Don't worry about it.
I'll do it later.
-OK.
-Hm.
I'm resigning.
-Thank you for the
challenging game.
-Sai.
All right.
I know he's from Japan.
Is Sai a world amateur
representative?
I doubt it.
This guy isn't half
the player he is.
I bet I'm not the only person
here who's battled Sai online.
I wonder if any of
these competitors
traveled all the
way to Japan just
to get a glimpse of
the mystery player?
How am I gonna find him?
He could be standing
right beside me,
and I wouldn't even know it.
-Sai.
(VOICEOVER) Wh-what?
Did he just say what
I thought he said?
-Just where have you been?
-Huh?
-Now you come with me.
-Uh, sure.
-This young man is an
aspiring professional.
-Ooh!
-I'm really sorry, but I don't
have time for this right now.
-What are you talking about?
Let him have six stones.
WAYA: You've gotta
be kidding me!
-(VOICEOVER) He's good,
but not good enough.
It's not him.
-(VOICEOVER) Sai.
-(VOICEOVER) I don't get it.
Where are you, Sai?
[theme music]
HIKARU: It looks
like Akira's gonna
start playing online, too.
SAI: He wants to
know my identity.
HIKARU: Everybody's trying to
figure out who you are, Sai.
Come on.
Let's challenge Akira to a game.
SAI: By playing him, we
risk revealing ourselves.
HIKARU: Don't tell me
you're gonna avoid him?
SAI: I'll play him and
use a new strategy.
HIKARU: Next time, Deja Vu!