-Who, who's there?
-That's, that isn't
the best move.
It's not even a good move.
[theme music]
[raindrops]
-Oh, Akari.
My grandpa's place
is just up ahead.
-Hikaru, I told you we should
have gone straight home.
-Grandpa, Grandpa,
we're coming in.
-Are you sure this is OK?
-Oh, yeah.
This place is just full of junk.
-Let's get out of here, Hikaru.
This place is creepy.
Should you be touching that?
-Well, my parents
cut off my allowance
after I got only eight points
on a social studies test.
Hey, maybe this is
worth something.
-Hey, check it out.
It's a five in a
row board, right?
-An old Go board.
I wonder if my grandpa
used to play on this?
Oh, I bet we could
get a lot for it.
-You sure this is OK?
-Don't worry.
I bet Grandpa's forgotten
all about this old board.
I'll just brush the dirt
off and shine it up a bit.
Good as new.
That's funny.
This stain here
isn't coming off.
-Uh, what are you talking about?
What stain?
-This one.
-Show me.
-Right here.
-Huh?
There's nothing there.
Look.
-It's right here.
-You can see it.
-That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
-You can hear me?
You can really hear
what I'm saying.
-I don't see a stain.
-Who, who's there?
-Stop it, Hikaru.
You're scaring me.
-At last.
I have found the one.
-Grandpa, is that you?
-I'm going home.
-To the gods I
offer my gratitude.
For once again, I can
finally, I can finally
return to this world.
[thud]
-Hikaru, what's wrong?
Hikaru?
Help, something's
wrong with Hikaru.
-Who are you?
-I am Fujiwara-no-Sai.
-Sai, what are you?
-During the Heian period, I held
a position as a Go instructor
to the emperor in the capital.
It was such a happy
time for me, to be
able to play Go every day.
One day, the other instructor
approached the emperor
with a suggestion.
He said, sir, I believe you only
have need for one instructor.
Please allow the two
of us to play a game
to decide who shall
keep their position.
-Oh, OK.
So you played a game, right?
Who won?
-The game was dead even.
Everyone's attention was
focused on the board.
It was only by mere
chance that I saw it.
There was a white
stone in his Go bowl.
He waited for an
opportune moment,
and then he slipped the
stone in with his prisoners.
-You mean he cheated?
-And then, just as I was
about to protest, was that?
-Scoundrel.
Just now, I saw you take a
black stone from your bowl
and place it among
your prisoners.
-What?
But I just saw you
do the same thing
with a white stone
from your bowl?
-What a pitiful
attempt at an excuse.
While all eyes were
fixed on the board,
you shamelessly took one
of my stones from your bowl
and placed it among
your prisoners.
-No, you are the
one who did that.
-Silence.
That's enough.
I refuse to believe that
two members of my court
would commit such a discourteous
offense within my presence.
Now, on with the game.
-Unable to calm myself with
this disturbing turn of events,
I lost the game.
I was banished from the capital.
My reputation tarnished by
the allegation of treachery.
I had no other skills,
no way to make a living.
Two days later, I cast
myself into the river.
Unable to find peace, my soul
was trapped within a Go board.
It seemed like an
eternity, until one day
on the island of Enoshima
in the Setto Sea.
I heard a child's voice.
His name was Torajirou.
Sweet child, if
you are able to see
the stains of my wretched
tears, then perhaps you
have some small space
within your soul
in which to house my own.
Torajirou was an
aspiring Go player.
And by the age of 20, he
had surpassed his teacher.
He became known as
Honinbou Shusaku the 14th.
Honinbou Shusaku?
-But Torajirou fell
victim to an epidemic.
And one night in his
34th year, his time came.
-So those must've been his
blood stains on the Go board.
Does this mean you appeared
to me because you still
want to play Go?
-Yes, for I have yet to
play the Divine Move.
-Hey, Hikaru, I heard you rode
in an ambulance yesterday.
-Hmm?
Yeah.
-Uh, Hikaru?
-Hikaru, are you
feeling all right?
What happened to you yesterday?
-You know, I'm not really sure.
When I woke up, it
was already morning.
-Pass them to the
person behind you.
All right, then.
Begin.
-Uh.
-Ooh, a history test.
-You, again?
-Is everything all right?
-Uh, I, yeah, sorry.
-Then, please sit down and
continue with the test.
-Yes, ma'am.
So yesterday wasn't a dream.
-'Twas no dream.
-And what's your name, again?
-It's Sai.
-You really love Go, don't ya?
-Oh, yes.
-And you really want
to play Go, don't ya?
-Yes.
-Too bad.
I don't think I'm ever
going to play the game.
-Ahh.
-Ugh.
-What's wrong?
-Is he all right?
-What did you do to me?
-Nothing.
I, I didn't do anything.
-Hikaru, are you OK?
-I'm worried, Hikaru.
Do you want to see
the school nurse?
-I think I'm OK now.
-You must have felt
my intense sorrow
at the thought of not being
able to play Go again.
-Man, a thousand years
of disappointment
is hard on the stomach.
Couldn't you, ya know,
go bother someone else?
-Probably not.
-Uh.
I guess it wouldn't hurt
to play once in a while.
-Huh?
-But my head belongs to me.
And don't talk to me unless
I talk to you first, agreed?
-Agreed.
-Oh, what was his name, again?
-10 more minutes.
If you're finished,
you can go back
and double-check your work.
-Oh, I can't remember.
Hey, Sai, you know anything
about the Tempo reform?
-Tempo, the one started
by counselor Mizuno?
-Huh?
-Yeah, that's the guy.
-I remember him well.
We played a game of
Go at the castle once.
A fascinating--
-OK, that's enough.
You know anything about Perry?
-Perry?
-Perry, the guy with the
black ships and stuff.
-Ah, you mean, Commodore Perry.
-That's the one.
Which bay did Perry sail into?
-Uraga Bay.
He certainly caused
quite an uproar.
-Uraga.
Hey, Sai?
-Yes?
-You can pretty
useful sometimes.
-What are you mumbling
to yourself about?
Are you finished?
-Almost.
-Well, keep at it.
-How rude.
Your teacher walked
right through me
without even an excuse
me or I beg your pardon.
Hikaru, there seems to
be a lack of etiquette
in this modern world.
-Yeah, yeah, just stop making
such a racquet in my head.
Once we're done here,
I'll take you somewhere
where you can play Go, OK?
-Oh, there certainly
are a lot of people
in this city of yours.
-Yeah, Tokyo's a
pretty big place.
-So, tell me, where are
we going to be playing Go?
-At a Go salon.
-Really?
-My grandpa goes
there sometimes.
He says it's a place where
old guys who like Go hang out.
-So people still enjoy Go as
much as they did in my time.
-Hello, there.
Welcome.
-Hmm.
Gee, it's like a
nursing home in here.
-Is this your first time here?
-Yeah, everything in
this place is new to me.
Can anybody play?
-Certainly.
Just write your name
down here, please.
Uh, what's your skill level?
-Skill level?
I'm not too sure.
-Oh?
-See, I've never really
played anyone before.
But I think I'm pretty good.
Hey, there's a kid over there.
Can I play him?
-I know he's your age, but--
-Are you looking for
someone to play against?
-Yeah.
-Come on.
I'll play you.
-But this boy's never--
-Follow me.
-OK.
-Wait a minute.
There's an entrance fee.
-Huh?
A fee?
-Oh, this is his
first time here.
How about letting
him in for free?
-Well, sure Akira.
Whatever you say.
-By the way, I'm Akira Toya.
What's your name?
-Hikaru Shindo.
I'm in the sixth grade.
-I'm in the sixth grade, too.
-This is a lot
better than playing
against one of those old guys.
-What's your skill level?
-Don't know.
Don't have a single clue.
I think I'm going to be pretty
good at this game, though.
-You don't know, but you
think you're pretty good.
Well, why don't you put down
four or five stones for now.
-Put down stones.
A handicap?
Well, I don't need one.
You and I are
about the same age.
-No handicap against Akira Toya?
Who does that kid think he is?
-All right, then.
You go first.
-I hope you don't mind.
I'm kind of a slow player.
[crying]
-Sai, are those tears of joy?
Oh, I guess I can't blame you.
Not being able to play the
game you love for 140 years.
-Very well, Hikaru.
Let us play.
-Yes.
-3, 4 in the upper right.
17 across and 4 down.
-17, 1, 2, 3, 4.
-Huh?
The way he holds his stones,
he must be a beginner.
-3, 4, in the lower right.
16, 17.
-16, 17, this must be it.
-3, 16.
-16, 5.
-A diagonal.
-14, 4.
-He holds his stones
like a beginner.
But he's making
good solid moves.
He is pretty good.
-Well, what's the matter?
Isn't it your move?
-Oh, sorry.
-The shape of his
joseki appears outdated.
And why does his hand
keep stopping and starting
over the board?
-Um, 14, 11.
Ah, here it is.
-He's not intimidated
by my attacks at all.
In fact, he's
countering them easily.
-That white stone is yours.
Take it.
-Uh, this one?
-Yes.
-19, 15.
-He took it.
Is that OK?
-18, 14.
-I, I can take this one, right?
-Yes.
-What just happened?
-Those nine white
stones just died.
Eventually, you will take
them as your prisoners.
-That many?
Wow.
This is going to be an easy win.
-No, this boy is not that weak.
We did not capture those stones.
He sacrificed them.
-Really?
Look closely.
-Oh.
-I still have a chance.
Losing those nine
stones in the upper left
hurt, but I still control
the center of the board.
-Are we going to win?
-Maybe.
4, 13.
Now, 8, 5.
-8, 5, where are you?
There it is.
-Huh?
That's, that isn't
the best move.
It's not even a good move.
He played it to see
how I'd respond.
It's like he's
testing my strength.
He's measuring my skill
from a level far above mine.
-See ya later.
-Thank you.
Ah, game finished?
-Yep, all done.
I think it was a little too
soon for a match after all.
You know, I'm so slow.
It kind of tired me out.
-Oh, dear.
Oh, by the way,
there's a Go tournament
for children coming up soon.
Take a look.
-Oh?
-Why not check it out?
-I'll think about it.
And thank you for letting
me play here today.
Bye.
-Come again.
He might even beat Akira
in another 50 years maybe.
-He lost?
That's ridiculous.
I mean, he's as good as a pro.
So he must have given
him a handicap, right?
How many stones?
-None, the boy played
black and went first.
-How much did he win by?
-Two points.
-So Akira actually won,
if you count the komi.
-It's not just the two points.
He was playing on a
higher level than I was.
-Wait a minute.
Is this true, Akira?
You lost?
That's impossible.
That boy said he'd never played
a game before in his life.
-Never played a game
before today ever?
Who, who is he?
-Huh, I'm not used to this.
I'm exhausted.
Did you have a good time
playing the game again?
-Oh, yes.
-Good.
Now, when we get home, we're
doing some social studies
homework.
-Anything you say.
-Great.
You wanna race?
-I would love to.
-1, 2, 3, go.
[theme music]
-This move, and this move, too.
It's as if he was
playing a teaching game.
No, there's no way.
There's no way a kid
could be that good.
I finally found
you, Hikaru Shindo.