NARRATOR: After many
years inside a go board,
a spirit from the past
known as Fujiwara-no-Sai
has returned, visible
only to Hikaru Shindou.
A master of Go, Sai seeks
to play the Divine Move.
[theme music]
-You coward!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
I'm gonna make
him wait until I can
play as good as him.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Wait.
It isn't him.
It's me.
I'm the one who's scared.
I'm the one who's running back.
If that's your plan, then I'm
going to do the same thing.
I won't back down.
-Hm.
Here it is.
What do you think?
-That's the one we've
been looking for.
CLER: Will there
be anything else?
HIKARU: Um, yeah.
I'll take this, and this.
-Your total comes to 1,600 yen.
-I got you a copy of that
manual you asked about.
It's the same book
that Tetsuo ripped up.
-I'm certain that it'll
be an enlightening read
for both of us.
Perhaps you and
Akari would benefit
from studying the book together.
-Akari?
This stuff's way too
advanced for her.
-Why's that?
-Listen.
She can't tell the difference
between Othello and Go.
-Othello?
What is that?
-It's another game
played with stones.
Uh oh.
Look how dark it is already.
If I don't get home soon,
my folks are gonna flip out.
I wish I had brought
a watch with me.
There's gotta be a
clock here somewhere.
Found one.
Oh no!
It's almost 7:30.
Huh?
Toya Meijin has one the Judon.
This is his fourth major title.
Akira's dad is really cleaning
up at the tournaments.
He's unstoppable.
SAI (VOICEOVER): That man's
skill has reached a new level.
Higher and higher he goes.
HIKARU: I wonder what
Akira's doing right now.
BOY: Why's he replaying
old games by himself?
-He probably thinks
we're not good enough
to be his opponents.
-You heard of Toya Meijin?
The guy who holds
four major titles?
That's his dad.
-Yeah, I saw him
on TV yesterday.
Four titles.
It's unbelievable.
Personally, I'd be
happy to win just one.
-His father's the best
of the best, isn't he?
-He's the king of Go.
-Yep.
-And we've got his son, the
prince, sitting right there.
-Think he's any good?
-They say that one day,
he'll surpass his dad.
-Yeah, right.
I dare you to challenge
him to a game.
-What am I, crazy?
You play him.
-Akira.
Your dad's an amazing player.
Please congratulate him for me.
Winning the Judan like that.
It is quite a victory.
-Uh, oh.
Thank you, sir.
I'll be sure to pass that along.
MR. YUN: This boy's a mystery.
He so unemotional.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): You're
the reason I'm here, Hikaru.
I joined this club
because of you.
Kaio means nothing to me.
There's only one thought in
my mind, catching up to you.
I'll train all day, every day,
until I get to play you again.
And once I've defeated
you, maybe I'll
finally be able to
achieve the Divine Move.
BOY: I gotta throw in the towel.
You're just too good.
Wow, I'm impressed.
You're really in the zone today.
-Yup.
-Wanna play again?
Come on.
-Naw, maybe later.
-Aw.
-Thanks for the game.
-Yeah, you too.
That was awesome.
-Akira.
Would you like to play a game?
-Oh?
-Look at this.
-Yeah, OK.
Why don't you pull up a chair?
-Onegai shimasu.
-What is he doing?
-He's sure got guts.
-What's going on?
I'm a seventh grader and I
don't know everybody's name yet.
Who's the guy over there?
The one playing Akira
Toya Is he any good?
-That's Aoki, and he's
our third best player,
behind the team
captain and co-captain.
He's in the ninth grade.
-Oh.
BOY: In other
words, Aoki's going
to lose his place on the
team now that Touya's here.
There's only room
for three players,
and someone's got to go.
He's a nice guy, always
helping us with our training.
-Yeah.
Looks like he's
taken the initiative
to settle the question of woh
gets the last spot on the team.
If he loses, he'll
come to terms with it.
He's pretty thick-skinned.
-He hasn't lost yet.
This will be interesting.
-I resign.
[gasping]
-That was fast.
-Toya, I learned a
lot from this game.
I want to thank
you for playing me.
-Any time.
-That Toya sure has
got a lot of nerve.
GIRL: This is the
legendary Kaio Go club?
everyone seems
totally depressed.
And it's all because
of that Akira Touya.
I've always wanted to
play Go at this school.
Can't anyone match him?
It's not fair.
-Wake up.
It's your move.
-Hold on.
I've got it!
I just got the best idea ever.
I'm gonna play Touya.
I have a plan.
I know I can't win, but
I won't lose either.
Let's play, me and
you, what do you say?
-That'd be great.
-Who's that?
-Some new kid.
He's in seventh grade.
I hope he's good.
-What should we set
your handicap at?
-I don't need one, as
long as I go first.
Is that all right with you?
-Sure, OK.
-Cool.
Onegai shimasu.
-Onegai shimasu.
-That kid is out of his mind.
-He's an idiot.
-No kidding.
-Toya's gonna crush him.
-This should be fun to watch.
AKIRA: That's a
strange opening move.
-(VOICEOVER) As long as I
control that center point,
I've got this game in the bag,
and there's nothing you can do.
-(VOICEOVER) A copycat.
Hm.
-(VOICEOVER) He's
figured it out.
It doesn't matter, though.
The center point is mine, and
as long as I mirror his moves,
there's absolutely nothing
he can do to stop me.
I'll reflect his skill
right back at him.
He'll wind up beating himself.
-Did you see that?
Toya hesitated.
-Heh.
-If that's the way
you want to play--
(VOICEOVER) This guy's
trying to trick me.
Hm.
I won't fall into his trap.
If he expects me to
stop mirroring him,
he's got another thing coming.
Oh, no!
-It's your turn to move.
-I resign.
That guy knew my
weaknesses before I did.
It's like he read my mind.
-What was going
through your head?
Toya's too smart to fall
for such a simple trick.
-Chill out.
Go easy on the poor kid.
-He lured you into filling
in your own liberties,
and you took the bait.
Or he could have used a ladder.
It doesn't matter, though.
[groan]
-Either way, you still
would have lost the game.
-Hold on.
If you're so smart,
why don't you play him?
-BOY: You better
caln down, newbie.
I don't want you to go
and do something stupid.
You'll wind up embarrassing
the Kaio Go club.
-Someone should put
Toya in his place.
He's messing up everything.
-Do you think he's going to be
our team captain at the next Go
tournament?
-Probably.
He's practically a pro already.
They say he's going
to be a future Meijin.
-I'm not sure if I
should have asked him
for a game or an autograph.
-I left my autograph
book at home,
but maybe I could
challenge him to a match.
I could brag all
about it one day.
Everyone would know I faced
off against a real live legend.
If I managed to
capture a stone or two,
I might even get a signed photo.
Wow!
BOY: I think you're setting
your goals way too low.
Huh?
[car horn]
-Akira!
Over here.
-Miss Ichikawa, what
are you doing here?
-Hello, there.
I thought you might
want a lift home.
-Are you sure?
It's kind of far.
-You're gonna get soaked.
Come on, get inside the car.
Wel, don't just stand there.
Get in.
You promised me a
teaching game today.
I hope you haven't
forgotten about it.
-I would never break a promise.
-Are you hungry?
I've got some cake
and coffee for you.
-Did she just say
cake and coffee?
It's not fair!
-Now that I think
about it, maybe I
would enjoy humiliating
that little brat.
-Senpai!
-I'm behind you 100%.
But how can you beat
him without a handicap?
You'd be better off running
for class valedictorian.
At least it'd be easier.
-He's got to have
some kind of weakness.
But what could it be?
-In a fair fight, Toya
can easily defeat me.
There's no doubt.
-Huh.
-Bit shot.
What are you thinking?
Spit it out?
-We've got to surprise him.
Catch him totally off guard.
BOY: But how?
You've got a plan,
right, Senpai?
-What a storm.
It's starting to
rain pretty hard.
-We should get going.
-OK.
I wonder why Akari showed up?
-Aw, who cares?
We don't need her, anyway.
TSUTSUI: You were kind of
hard on her the other day.
You really shouldn't have
yelled at her like that.
-I've known her for a long time.
She's got thicker
skin than that.
Relax, it's not a problem.
She's fine.
-You owe her an apology.
Invite her back to the club.
-Give me a break!
Go is a boy's game.
You should get that
through your head already.
SAI: I'm afraid that's not true.
-Huh?
-Many women throughout the
Heian capital played Go.
They were quite
skilled, you know?
-Look, everyone.
Master Sai has chosen
to pay us a visit.
-Both Sei Shonagon
and Murasaki Shikibu
were avid Go enthusiasts.
-Huh?
-You learned about them
in class yesterday.
Remember?
-What?
I did?
Oh, Sai?
-Yes?
-Pretty cool, huh?
-No.
I was merely playing
along with your joke.
-Really?
-I've seen you use that
device several times now.
-You thought my
umbrella was awesome
the first time I showed
you how it worked.
-What did she say?
-Me?
Nothing.
-I'll see you
tomorrow, all right?
-OK.
I'll see you later.
-The Go board has remained
unchanged for centuries,
and the umbrella is the
same as it's always been.
HIKARU: I guess you're right.
You know, they never were
very good to begin with.
They don't keep you totally dry.
And your feet still
wind up soaking wet.
They're easy to lose, they're
hard to hold in your hand.
How come they never improved it?
Seems kind of silly, doesn't it?
-Yes.
-They can put them
a man on the moon,
but they can't make
a decent umbrella.
-What did you say?
You can't be serious.
I wish you wouldn't
tease me like that.
It's cruel to even suggest that
a man could travel to the moon.
-Yep.
We've already gone there.
I'm serious.
I could show you
pictures if you want.
-Impossible!
That couldn't have happened.
Right, Hikaru?
It's really not polite
to tell such tall tales.
That's certainly the
most ridiculous story
I've ever heard.
I mean, just consider
it for a moment.
Man on the moon.
[laughter]
SAI: Hikaru, listen to me.
Did man really
travel to the moon?
The same moon that floats
in the sky at night?
HIKARU: You got it.
Took you long enough.
SAI: If man can go
to the moon, then
why are umbrellas
still umbrellas?
HIKARU: Uh-- huh?
-It doesn't matter how
we set up the game.
As long as I manage to beat
Touya without a handicap,
I don't care what we have to do.
-Now, don't get
too carried away.
-I'm with you.
Beating him is all
that counts, guys.
It doesn't matter how do it,
as long as we come out on top.
What if we waited until he
got really, really sick, like
if he had the flu or something?
BOY: If he was ill, he
wouldn't come to school.
-We could always challenge him
to a game in the karaoke room.
I'd turn up the
music so loud, it'd
be impossible for
him to concentrate.
-He's still find a to defeat me.
We've gotta put him at a huge
disadvantage for this plan
to work.
-I've got an idea.
We could tie up
his hands and feet
and make him place the
stones with his teeth.
-I kinda like that idea.
-Huh?
-Hm.
There.
BOY: I'll teach that
wonder kid a thing or two.
When I'm done with him, he'll
never touch a Go stone again!
I swear it.
He'll regret the day he ever
set foot in the Kaio Go club!
[theme music]
HIKARU: Akira's
gonna have to play
a game without
looking at the board.
SAI: It's a very
difficult challenge.
HIKARU: More like impossible.
If he doesn't win, he might
quit the Kaio Go club.
SAI: You should think about
your own club, Hikaru.
You need another player.
HIKARU: Next time, Eyesore.
I'll find someone!