[theme music]
-I don't think he's here either.
I don't understand Sai.
Why wouldn't you want to
come back to Torajiro's home?
-OK, that's it.
I've had enough.
Why can't you get it
through your thick skull,
I never said anything
about 50,000 yen.
Where did you get that idea?
Huh?
Come on, say
something, you moron.
-Mr. Kawai, what's wrong?
-Don't give me that attitude!
I'm not done dealing
with you yet.
-You held up five fingers.
That means 50,000, right?
Anyone with half a
brain would know that.
-No, it does not.
It means 5,000 no 50.
-Not my problem.
You should have made
that clear at the start.
It's too late now, you loser.
-Who are you calling a loser?
You're the loser.
-Let's get out of here.
-Are you with that guy
in the sunglasses who's
causing all this trouble?
-Uh, yeah.
-A little word of advice.
Around here it isn't
such a good idea
to brag about being
a Giant's fan.
You've got to remember,
this is home territory
for the Hiroshima Carp.
I know Shuhai brought up
the subject of baseball,
but even so.
-Baseball?
-Your friend should have know
better than to insult the Carp.
He deserves whatever's
coming to him.
-Him and his big mouth.
-Just leave whatever cash
you've got and get out of here.
Think of it as a
cheap go lesson.
-A lesson from you?
Who do you think you are?
Play another game,
then we'll see
who needs to be taught a lesson.
-Oh, forget it.
Forget it.
It would be a waste of my time.
-Mr. Kawai, come on.
-Hm.
-If you want to get
yourself into a fight,
them I'm going to go home.
-Can't you wait for one game?
It won't take long, I promise.
SHUHAI (VOICEOVER): Is
that who I think it is?
-Hurry up.
Get your stones off the
board so we can play.
-Do it yourself.
I'm done with you.
-What do you mean?
-What about you?
You want to play a game?
And I'll tell you
what, if you win,
I'll forget about the money
your friend here owes me.
-Oh, you don't know what
you're getting yourself into.
You're in for a surprise.
he may look like an
ordinary kid to you,
but he-- -I know who he is.
He's Shindou, the pro, right?
[growl]
-Huh?
That kid is a pro?
-But he's just a boy.
MALE SPEAKER 1 (VOICEOVER): He
doesn't look like a pro to me.
MALE SPEAKER 2 (VOICEOVER): He's
the same age as my grandson.
-So if you know he's a pro,
how come you're so confident?
-I saw one of his games in
Go Weekly against the Meijin
in the Shin Showdown Series.
He played badly.
You'd expect the pros to
play better than us amateurs,
wouldn't you?
-Just who are you anyway?
-Mr. Shuhai is going
to be representing
Japan in the next world
amateur championship.
He's probably the best
amateur in the country.
-The best amateur
in the country?
-When I play pros from Gonzai,
I play without a handicap.
So 5,000 yen really is
a cheap lesson for you.
-You're pitch-hitting for me.
-What?
I don't wanna.
-Get a move on.
You're going to teach
this guy a lesson.
-Wait a minute.
Mr. Kawai.
-Sit down and play, all right?
Now, this will wipe the
smirk off your face.
-Didn't you hear me?
I already said
I'm done with you.
-Hey, I'm counting
on you, kiddo.
Don't lose.
-Mr. Kawai, you sure
this is a good idea?
-All right, then.
Let's have ourselves a game.
-Mr. Shuhai is actually
going to play a pro?
-This I got to see.
Come on, let's watch.
-I'm going to play first.
[japanese]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Looks like I'm
playing whether
I want to or not.
-By the way, what
brought the two of you
all the way out here?
-A little break.
-But why come here?
-We wanted to visit all the
different Honinbo Shusaku
sites.
We even found his grave.
-You know Shusaku has a
memorial in Tokyo too?
-Huh?
There's one in Tokyo?
-Yes.
Although Shusaku spent his
childhood here in Innoshima,
once he began playing in the
castle games, he moved to Edo.
After his untimely
death, his followers
built a second memorial there.
You didn't know?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Torajiro
has another memorial?
-Do you know where
it is in Tokyo?
-Who really cares
about that right now?
Concentrate on playing the game.
-Your friend is right.
You don't want to lose
to an amateur, do you?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): If Torajiro
has a memorial in Tokyo,
then maybe that's where Sai is.
That's got to be it.
Sai would never have
made it out to somehwere
as far as Hiroshima.
He's still in Tokyo.
He has to be.
-So where's this memorial?
-I'll find out after
the game's finished.
You focus on winning, OK?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai.
I want to go back home
right now, back to Tokyo.
-The kid's playing real fast.
-You can tell he's a pro.
-You're not using
any of your time.
You should probably
think about your moves.
-What do you think you're doing?
Take your time.
Don't rush.
If you play that fast, you're
going to make a mistake.
-Looks like you're
going to have to wipe
the smirk off your face.
-Take it easy there, kiddo.
Please, just play
more carefully.
Didn't you hear me?
Slow down!
-Hm.
Hm.
-Look at that.
I think the kid's playing even
faster than he was before.
-I sure hope he's not
underestimating Shuhai.
MALE SPEAKER 2 (VOICEOVER):
The kid's bluffing.
Thinks he can get
Shuhai all flustered.
Not a chance.
-You think he's bluffing?
If you knew Shindou, you'd
know he doesn't bluff.
-He might be playing fast,
but he knows what he's doing.
He's just a kid, but without a
doubt, you can tell he's a pro.
SHUHAI (VOICEOVER): Now that
he's captured the corners,
he's got more territory than me.
Even though I'm using
my time to think,
he's still managing to
stay one step ahead of me.
-Feeling the pressure yet?
-You keep out of this.
We've just started.
Like the Hiroshima Carp, I
don't show my real strength
until the later innings.
SHUHAI (VOICEOVER):
Don't rush the game.
I've got to take my time.
It's hard not to get sucked
into playing at his pace.
If he won't slow down, I'll
have to try another tactic.
I'll set a trap and force
him into making an error.
Huh?
He saw right through it
in the blink of an eye.
-Playing this fast ain't fair.
He's just doing it to get
his opponent all flustered.
-Are you sure?
Most people would
have made a mistake
by now playing like that.
-I don't understand how he
can make his move so quickly.
Surely, he's not making
it up on the spot?
-Nope, he's got plenty
of time to think.
-Hm?
-Look.
While Shuhai is thinking
about his next move,
the kid is already planning
how he is going to respond.
KAWAI (VOICEOVER):
This is amazing.
Shindou is a completely
different player
from when I saw him last year.
How could he have
changed so much?
-Take that.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Chances are pretty
good that he'll
bump my stone here.
If he doesn't, he'll
attach over here,
and I'll play on the other side.
Yes.
Now, if I can get over
here, I'll stay in control.
-OK, I resign.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Yes.
-Whoo.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Sai, how'd I do?
-Huh?
Why are you looking at me?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
Sai isn't here.
He's in Tokyo.
-So where exactly is
this Shusaku memorial?
-It's in Sugamo, at the--
what's it called now?
Oh yes, at Honmiogi.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Honmiogi in Sugamo.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
OK, you ready to go home?
-Uh, sure.
-Not so fast.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Uh-oh.
What's he going to do?
I know I beat him, but
it was only a game.
-I'll give you both a
ride to the station.
Follow me.
-But?
-I never expected you
to give us a ride.
What's up?
You feel like you've
got to be nice to us
because the kid demolished you?
-Don't think so, seeing as how I
demolished you first, remember?
-Dah.
Hey, you want to let
me take over the wheel?
I'm a professional
cab driver back home.
-This isn't your
town, so you wouldn't
know where you were going.
You stay back there.
-What?
-Stop fighting, would you?
I just want to get there
as fast as possible.
-You're in a rush, huh?
Then I'll take you
to a station where
you can catch the bullet train.
-Whoa.
This guy drives
crazier than I do.
-Yeah, believe me,
that's saying something.
-I got an idea, Shindou.
I know that you beat me today.
I'll be coming up
to Tokyo to play
in the world amateur
championship.
How about you and me
meeting up for a rematch?
-Hey, I'm not letting him
play someone like you.
-No one asked you, so be quiet.
-Hikaru Shindou.
I can't believe he's
still in the ninth grade.
That kid's got a bright future.
One day he's going to have
the world of Go at his feet.
That's for sure.
But that game he played
against Toya Meijin
in the Shin Showdown
Series, it was terrible.
He played so badly.
It doesn't make any sense.
-Hey.
Where are you going?
What's the big rush anyway?
-Sai?
Sai?
Hey, Sai.
Where are you?
Sai?
Come on, I know you're here.
Sai, it's me.
Sai.
Where are you?
Come on, Sai.
Sai?
Sai!
It doesn't look like
he's here either.
Sai.
-Hey, you seen enough?
Oh boy.
You've been running all over the
place at these memorials sites.
What's going with you?
Are you looking for something?
You tried the Go Association?
They got all sorts of
affluent Go in there.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I
already looked there.
He wasn't at Grandpa's either.
Sai, where have you gone to?
-Are you all right?
Huh, kiddo?
-Would you get
your hands off me?
Just leave me alone.
-Wait.
Where you going?
You could at least say goodbye,
or come by the Go salon.
Everyone there's cheering
for you, you know?
I give up.
I don't even understand
why we went to Hiroshima
in the first place.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I'm home.
-Hikaru, where have you been?
You could have called me.
I've told you before,
you need to tell me
where you're going
when you go out.
You've got a lot going on.
I understand, and
that's OK, but you
have to realize
you're still a child.
Hikaru, come back here.
-Sai?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Playing
against that Shuhai guy
was tough.
I'm beat.
-You try the Go Association?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Maybe I should
go take another look,
just to be sure.
-Huh?
Hikaru, wait a minute.
Where are you going?
-Go Association.
-But it's late.
What about dinner?
Hikaru!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I
guess he isn't here.
Sai.
Why did you just disappear?
It doesn't make sense.
I remember him saying
something about it
at Grandpa's house, something
about him leaving me.
But I didn't take him seriously.
I mean, I never thought
he would disappear.
I never imagined it
could actually happen.
-Who's there?
Shindou, what are you
doing here so late?
Did you forget something?
-Is there anywhere
here I could--
-Huh?
What's that?
-I know this sounds silly, but
where could I see a ghost here?
-You want to see a ghost?
(LAUGHING) Well, the
building is fairly old,
and it is night time, so I guess
the chances are fairly good.
-Thanks anyway.
-Wait.
Let me think.
I did hear about this one room.
-Which room?
-Uh-hm.
I'll show you.
[theme music]
-If I knew Sai was going
to disappear like this,
I would have let him play
all the games he wanted.
Toya wants to have
a game against me,
but what's the point
of playing anymore?
Without Sai around, I'm never
going to get any better.
From now on, I
won't play anyone.
That's it.
I'm finished.
It's all over.
Next time, I'm never
going to play again.