[theme music]
-I've always known what
a strong player Ochi is,
but I never once thought
he could beat me.
-I resign.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
Thank you, Ochi.
You helped me
refocus on my game.
-Hey, Isumi.
You're back in the running.
-Our match is set for
the very last day.
Watch out, because by then,
I'm gonna be much stronger.
-Hi, Grandpa. It's Ochi.
I would like you
to call Toya Tudan.
-I want to know if you're
familiar with this match.
Black was played
by a Korean Insei
by the name of Su-yeong
Hong, and Hikaru Shindou
played white.
-Huh?
Hold on.
You said Shindou
was playing white.
If this match shows
the kind of level
Shindou's playing at right
now, then three weeks
won't be enough!
It won't be enough time!
-I think you've
got plenty of time.
Especially now that I'm
here to work with you.
-I resign.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
-Thank you.
-Adachi and Komiya
had five losses each
when they faced
off, and Komiya won.
Really?
-Yeah, and all five of the
front runners won their games.
Did you?
-Yeah, I won, but I
already had six losses.
Feels like I'm on
the edge of a cliff.
-And 'cause I've
got seven losses,
I guess I'm just hanging onto
the edge for dear life, huh?
I'm not giving up.
I still have a chance.
-See you later, Mr. Tsubaki.
-See you.
That kid's turned
into a monster.
You, me, Komiya and
Adachi have all got
matches left against
the front runners.
If we beat them, the field
will be wide open for us.
-We can't afford to lose,
whoever we're playing.
-Yeah.
-Please begin whenever
you are already.
[music playing]
-You actually beat Honda?
-Mm-hm.
It was a good game.
Don't act so surprised.
-That's great, Asumi.
-I wish you could've seen it.
I was really on top of my game.
When I have a game
as good as that one,
it reminds me that I gotta keep
trying to make it as a pro.
-It's all over.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
-It was a fine game.
You played well.
-(VOICEOVER) I couldn't
beat any of the top five.
They're not gonna break
under the pressure.
This is the end of
the line for me.
This time last year, Akira
Toya was so far ahead,
everyone else had to battle
for the two remaining spots.
My time will come next year.
-So, did you win?
-Mm-hm.
-And I was doing so
well in the prelims.
Next year, I'm gonna be too old
to take the pro exam because
of the age limit, so this
was my last chance at it.
Now I know I'm not gonna pass.
-Mr. Tsubaki?
-Well, guess I finally lost my
grip on the edge of that cliff.
-Hey.
Didn't you once
tell me you wanted
me to take you out for a ride?
-Yeah.
-Come on.
Let me give you a
ride to the station.
-What is it, Hikaru?
TSUBAKI: Hey!
-Huh?
-What are you waiting for?
Come on, let's get going.
HIKARU: OK, I'm coming!
Whoa.
Mr. Tsubaki, slow down a bit!
-How many losses you got now?
Three?
-What's that?
I can't hear you!
What did you say?
-You're hanging in
there at the top.
-I said I can't hear you!
In the month between
the prelims and exam,
and all the way
through the finals,
your game's been
getting stronger,
but mine didn't improve one bit.
That's the difference
between you and me!
-Mr. Tsubaki, I can't
hear a word you're saying!
-Hey, your name's
Shindou, right?
-What?
-I'm passing my dream
of being a pro onto you.
-I can't hear you!
-What I said was, I'm passing my
dream of being a pro onto you!
-Thanks for the
ride, Mr. Tsubaki.
TSUBAKI: No problem.
-And, uh, thanks
for what you said.
-What?
Oh, yeah that.
I'll be cheering for
you, but if you slack off
in the last few matches,
I'll never forgive you.
-Thanks, Mr. Tsubaki!
See you later!
-When you two first
met, I was worried
that you were intimidated,
but now look at you.
-Come on, Sai.
Let's get out of here.
Hm?
Sai?
AKIRA: I told you,
that move won't work!
You play a move as obvious as
that, and it'll all be over.
That extension combination
you played over here
has gone and left
you out of position.
What you should have
done was given him
some space, then waited out
to see where he attacked.
I told you about how to
play this three days ago.
You're not taking
this seriously!
-I am taking it seriously.
What I don't understand
is why you're
so obsessed with
me beating Shindou.
What's the big deal?
When you showed me that match
he played against the Korean
Insei, I had to admit,
I was pretty surprised.
But I've had my
moments of inspiration
and played matches like that.
-I seriously doubt it.
I know exactly what
your skill level is,
and you've never
played like that!
-I wanna know why you're so
preoccupied with Shindou!
-I'll show you a match played
two years ago with no handicap.
-The Shusaki diagonal?
AKIRA: I was white.
-And black?
Who was playing black?
Whoever it was, their moves
are pretty old fashioned,
but besides that, they
seem to be pretty good.
His moves are smart.
They expose the weaknesses
in white's game.
He's a very strong player.
Who is black?
It couldn't be!
-Yes. It's him.
-This is Shindou?
But that's impossible.
I know Shindou!
I knew him when he
first became an Insei!
I played against him
before in study sessions.
-And right here is
where I resigned.
-You what?
I don't believe it!
This was two years ago?
-I was defeated.
-There's no way
Shindou could have
played this game two years ago.
-You're right.
That's why I've never shown this
match to anyone before today.
You're the first
person to have seen it.
-I don't believe it was him.
-I didn't think you would.
But I was there.
I was the one who
played this match.
I know it happened.
-This isn't the Sindou I know.
Who is he?
-That's what I want to find out.
All right.
Let's get back to the game.
-I resign.
-Yes!
A 3 and 1/2 point win.
-That was win number 19, Hikaru.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
Yeah
-Huh?
-Hm.
That was a very important move.
It means the power has now
shifted in black's favor.
-Huh?
-I resign.
HONDA: OK, great.
I've still only got four losses.
Hang in there, and I
might get into a playoff.
Five matches to go.
I've got a good chance
of making it through.
-A playoff?
What's that?
-If there's a tie for
third place in the exam,
they play another match
to see who goes through.
-Oh, I see.
-Huh?
(VOICEOVER) A playoff.
Since I have three
losses, chances
are I'm going to
be in the playoff.
-That move where Honda
played the wedge was
what decided the match.
-At first I thought
he'd invaded too deep,
but when you look back at
it, it was a great move.
-That one move cost
Isumi eight points.
They were already
in the endgame,
so there was nowhere else for
him to make up the lost ground.
-Hm?
-Guess that's it for Isumi now.
-That's not it for him!
Not yet!
-Oh, yeah?
And maybe if you lose one more,
you might be in a playoff.
-That's not gonna happen.
I'm gonna make it through.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): And so am I.
-Five matches left.
So close to reaching my goal.
I'm almost there.
-Congratulations, Ochi.
-Well, thank you very much, sir.
-No matter what happens
in your last two matches,
this win means you're
guaranteed to pass the test.
-Yes.
-I bet you were quite
nervous in your game today.
-No.
-No?
Very impressive.
I figured you'd
be tense since you
were on the verge of passing.
-Someone told me if I focus
on achieving a higher goal,
passing the pro exam would
just happen naturally.
I was just following
their advice.
-A goal higher than
passing the exam?
What could be more
important than that?
-Beating Hikaru Shindou.
-Shindou?
But you've already played
him in the study sessions.
And you won, didn't you?
-Shindou's a
different player now.
It's not the same.
-I see.
Well, I know his progress
has been dramatic recently,
but I didn't think he
was that different.
Anyway, well done on
making it through.
-Thank you, sir.
-And best of luck on
your remaining matches.
-Hey, Ochi.
I hear congratulations
are in order.
-You're just saying that.
You don't really mean it.
-What is it with you?
You could have just acted
polite and said thank you.
-So, how did you
do in your game?
-Oh, I won.
So did the others.
Shindou's on a bit
of a winning streak,
holding firm at three losses.
Honda and Isumi also won.
The front runners
haven't changed.
You probably don't care anymore,
now that you're through.
-Waya, your next game's
against Shindou, isn't it?
-Yeah.
I've only got two losses.
If I manage to beat him,
then I'm through as well.
Then you and me can take it
easy and watch everyone else
fightin' it out
for the third spot.
-What makes you think I'm
going to take it easy?
I don't play Shindou
until my very last match.
-Huh?
-It's a really
important game for me.
In fact, as far
as I'm concerned,
it's probably the most important
game of the whole pro exam.
-Whoa.
I had no idea you considered
Shindou such a big rival.
You kept that quiet.
-I want to find out where
he gets his strength from.
That mysterious strength!
-Mysterious strength?
-I'm looking forward to
seeing how you do against him.
Good luck.
-Thanks.
See you later, Ochi.
-This is the
Shindou that I know.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): I won't know
for sure until I play him,
but I'm not gonna
lose Not to him.
Not to Shindou!
WAYA: Yes!
I win.
Maybe one more before bed.
Huh?
Ah!
Sai?
No way!
He's online now?
He hasn't been on here
since last summer!
Hm?
Huh?
Ah-- Ah!
Ah!
Grr!
What?
You're not Sai!
You can't play Go!
You're an impostor!
Sai was a legend online!
How dare you use his name?
I remember.
I once thought Shindou must
have been taking lessons
from Sai, or something.
-Zelda.
Of course you reply by
saying you're an Insei.
I can't believe you were Zelda!
-How do you know about
my chat with Sai?
It couldn't be.
Shindou-- could he be Sai?
No way.
Never in a million years.
He's got some
mysterious strength?
I don't think so.
I'm gonna beat him
and pass the exam.
-Two matches left.
-Yes.
-And next on the list is Waya.
I was just thinking,
remember all that stuff
he said to me after
I finally managed
to make it up into the A league?
-Yes, of course I remember.
-You played a good
game, Shindou.
A lot of really great moves.
I think you're gonna
be a strong player.
Maybe even as strong as Sai.
-When Waya said that, he
inspired me to try even harder.
-That's probably true.
-I'm gonna win.
He'll find out just
how strong I am!
[theme music]
HIKARU: Two matches left,
and the one against Waya's
gonna be a big one for me!
SAI: He's well prepared
for this match.
HIKARU: We both need the win
if we're gonna make it through.
SAI: Just be careful not
to let the pressure affect
your game, Hikaru.
You know what you can be like.
HIKARU: Next time,
Hikaru Versus Waya.
SAI: It will come down
to one decisive move.