[theme song]
-It's so depressing.
I've gotta go through
all the qualifying rounds
for the pro exam.
Ryo's given up being an
insei, so I'm on my own.
I'm beginning to wonder if
I should just call it quits.
Oh, by the way, do
you know what I heard?
A bunch of players from the
Kyusekai went on this trip
to China.
They were like goodwill
ambassadors for the Japanese Go
Association.
-Oh yeah?
Good for them.
-The interesting thing is that
one of the players on the trip
was Isumi.
-Isumi?
No way!
-So the flight from Tokyo
to Beijing is four hours.
And now are we going
to be getting a taxi?
How long do you think it'll
take to get to the China Go
Institute?
-It's only about 30 minutes.
I can't believe you guys have
never been to China before.
Hey, Isumi.
When you left the Nine
Stars Club last year,
I thought you would
give up the idea
of becoming a
professional go player.
-There's no reason why Isumi
can't take the pro exam again.
He's more than a match for most
of the pros I've come across.
-Easy.
I wasn't saying he's
not strong enough.
I just thought he
got discouraged
and didn't want it
enough, that's all.
-I took some time so I could
figure out what I wanted to do,
that's all.
Sorry to make you
worry about me.
-Anyway, the fact that
Narusawa-sensei invited you
on this trip to play
these goodwill matches
shows he thinks you've got what
it takes to make it as a pro.
-Yeah, I hope so.
And I intend to pass
the exam this year
to repay his confidence in me.
-You'd better.
You're 19 already, and
time's ticking away.
-What are you talking about?
He's got plenty of time.
I didn't pass until
I was in my 20s.
-Sakurano, that was you.
But Isumi is Isumi.
-Hey, what does that mean?
How many games do
you think we're
going to have to play
over the three days?
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
I've done as much
as I can to prepare for
the qualifying rounds
of the pro exam which
begin in two months time.
I'm going to treat these
goodwill matches here in China
as if they were the
pro exams themselves.
-I resign.
-You see this move?
Why did you go there?
Every move you made from that
point on cost you stones.
Hm?
-Hm.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): I
wasn't able to recover.
He was too strong for me.
-You didn't play that bad.
Come on, cheer up.
-Let's grab some lunch.
Take your mind off it.
-I didn't play that bad?
-Hm?
-The point is I didn't
play that good, either,
and I should have been better.
I haven't lost my confidence.
I'm just mad at myself.
I didn't want to lose,
so I allowed myself
to get all tense, and then I
couldn't play my best game.
-You sure you would have won
if you'd played your best?
-Hm.
-Well, you've got another chance
to try again this afternoon.
SAKURANO: Come on, Isumi.
Let's go eat.
-I remember coming
here with Sai.
I practiced playing go
using a pebble in the dirt.
It all started when he found
one that looked like a go stone.
Kind of like this one here!
He told me to play
the stone as if I
was putting it on a go board.
I tried to look cool
and snap it down,
but it flew right
out of my hand.
Sai.
-Hey, Shindo!
-Huh?
Oh, hi, Waya.
-What are you doing?
You find something in the dirt?
-No, not really.
Anyway, what are you doing?
I've never seen you
around here before.
-I was on my way over to
your house to find you.
Morishita-sensei is
furious with you.
Why haven't you been coming
to the study sessions?
You've been skipping
matches, too!
You didn't even call the Go
Association to let them know.
What's the matter?
Can't take the pressure
of being a pro?
Say something!
I'm trying to help you out here,
but if you won't talk to me--
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
How can I tell him
I couldn't care less
about go anymore?
And I can't tell him
anything about Sai.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-Did you hear I've moved
into my own place now?
The insei guys are coming over.
You want to join us?
It'd be great just to hang out.
-Nah.
-Shindo, you're the
only one from our group
who is not playing right now.
I've won two out of
three games so far
in the Dan Promotion
League, which is OK.
But you should see Ochi.
He's played four games,
and hasn't lost yet.
Honda, Komiya, the rest
are all studying hard
for this year's pro exam.
And did you hear about Isumi?
He got invited to go on
a trip to play in China.
-Isumi's gone to play in China?
-Yeah.
Listen, Shindo, last year
we had to really battle
to pass the pro exam, because
we were up against Isumi.
Without us around this time,
he's going to pass for sure.
He's going to be so
mad if he finds out
you bailed so soon
when it could've
been him in your shoes.
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
-Hm.
-You want to play go.
I know it.
Let's play a game right now!
I'll go first.
16-4, the star point!
I bet you thought of what
move you're going to make.
So come on, tell me what your
next move is going to be!
-[screaming]
-Shindo, come back here!
[growl] Stupid idiot!
-I can't believe our
three days are up already.
Once we've said our good byes
to Mr. Liu and the others,
it'll be time for
us all to head home.
-We've got an hour or so we.
Should go to Tienanmen Square.
-I wouldn't mind going shopping.
-You're kidding me.
We're in Beijing.
You can go shopping anywhere.
Right, Isumi?
Huh?
-What's the matter?
-I know I should've
told you this earlier,
but I think I'm going
to stay an extra day.
I want another game
against that young kid.
-Isumi.
-Come on, just what do you
expect us to do while you play?
-Uh, well, I meant I
would stay here by myself.
-Oh.
So this young kid--
is that Zou-si?
-I remember him.
I managed to win, but
it wasn't an easy game.
He was a tough opponent.
If the kids play that
well, then the standards
of the China Go Institute
must be very high.
-Why are you so surprised?
This go institute
is pretty amazing.
The pro players here
have been selected
from all across the country.
China is made up of
different provinces,
like the prefecture
districts we have in Japan.
The best players
from each province
are invited to come and
study here in Beijing.
They train every day, and all
their expenses are covered.
The Institute even provides
their accommodation.
SAKURANO: What?
They actually live here as well?
-Yep.
Once they start making a
lot of money or get married,
then they usually move out
and rent a place of their own.
So the players living
here at the Institute
tend to be teenagers, or
the ones in their early 20s.
-Wow.
-So this kid you've
been talking about
is one of China's top players.
Even though he's so young, he
lives here with the other boys
away from his parents.
He has incredible talent.
SAKURANO: What does
he do for school?
-This is his school.
-I guess they'd have to provide
some sort of education program
for the kids.
Still, they're all
pros, aren't they?
-Can I help you?
-Huh?
-Oh, hello, Mr. Li.
-Hi.
One of our group was
just saying how much
he'd like to play Zou-si
again before he goes home.
-Oh really?
-He really doesn't feel like
he played his best yesterday.
-I'd be very grateful.
-I happened to see
that game yesterday.
He played quite well,
but Zou deflected
every one of his attacks.
I can understand why he'd
want to have another chance.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): It doesn't
matter how good Zou is.
I didn't play my best, and I
don't want to go back to Japan
with that hanging over me.
I need to go into this year's
pro exam with the confidence
that I'm playing at
the top of my game.
-Sorry to disappoint
you, but it's not
going to be possible
for you to play Zou
because he's leaving town today.
-Oh.
-He has games scheduled
out in the provinces.
In fact, he's
probably already left.
-He won't be back
for a few days.
But hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't you stick
around Beijing for a while
and study with us until
he gets back into town?
-Mr. Liu!
-Stay here?
-Our practice rooms are like
a training ground for pros.
You'll see them in
there every day.
You'd be welcome to join them.
I understand your frustration
at losing your game to Zou,
so if you can, stay
for a few days.
What do you think?
Is that OK?
--[laughing] Anyone willing
to work hard is welcome here.
All you need to do is find
yourself a hotel nearby,
and you're all set.
-Well, Isumi?
-It's your decision.
What are you going to do?
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): I hadn't been
expecting something like this,
but it might be a great
opportunity for me.
-OK.
I'll stay a few more days.
-Oh.
-Huh?
-I don't know how much you've
heard about this place.
It's where all of the
elite players get together.
It can be demanding.
If their game records fall
below a certain level,
we send them home.
They all come here with great
potential, but not all of them
manage to fulfill it.
-Mr. Li is one of
the go instructors,
but he also teaches the
kids about life skills.
-This is the main practice room.
It's where they study new
moves, past game records,
and where they have
practice games.
It's a very fertile training
ground for the pros.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
They're all so young.
And all of them are pros?
I shouldn't let
that intimidate me.
I study with pros back in Japan.
Why should this
be any different?
-They begin their studies
at 8:15 sharp every morning,
and the session goes-- huh?
-Huh?
-Sneaking out of class again?
Don't think you can get away
with it when I'm not around.
-I wasn't skipping class!
I was in the bathroom!
-Don't lie to me.
-Huh? Waya?
[murmuring]
-Uh, I'm sorry.
-Waya?
-It's the name of one
of my friends in Japan.
They look so alike,
I thought it was him.
-Mr. Li, what's a Waya?
Was he talking about me?
[laughter]
-Your attention,
please, everyone!
-Huh?
-This is Isumi,
visiting from Japan.
He'll be studying with
us for the next few days.
-Isumi?
-Is he a pro?
-No, but I expect he will
be by the end of the year.
-Yes, I'm taking the pro exam.
Pleased to meet you.
-Hey Isumi, Isumi!
-Huh?
-Does your friend Waya have
an outie as good as this one?
-Lur Ping!
-Oh, what do you know?
It's lunchtime.
-Not so fast, Lur Ping!
That child is trouble.
-As you might have
guessed, Lur Ping
isn't great at focusing his
attention on his go studies.
And he knows exactly how
to get under Mr. Li's skin.
He's always getting
himself into trouble.
-Some kids are always
going to be a handful.
Are you sure he's old
enough to be a pro?
-Absolutely.
-He was invited to come here
last year when he was only 11.
-I think it's about
time for lunch.
Hope you're feeling hungry.
-Yeah.
-Everyone has their meals
here on the first floor.
While you're here, you're
welcome to join us.
Once you're done
eating, I suggest
you look for a hotel to stay at.
You should have plenty of time.
The lunch break
is two hours long.
-Thanks.
-Study hard now.
If you make the most of your
next few days here with us,
you should be a better
player by the time you leave.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): I'll try.
Huh.
Lur Ping.
Careful!
I can't let my guard
down just because I
met someone who looks like Waya.
-The afternoons are
dedicated to playing games
with a 90 minute
limit per player.
We play in a league format.
It helps raise the
stakes for everyone.
I'll add your name to the list.
This group is made up of
the lower ranking players--
1 through 3-Dan.
All you need to do is find
someone who's available
and start playing.
-Mr. Li!
-Hm?
-Can I play Isumi first?
-If you really want to.
Is that OK with you, Isumi?
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): Me?
Play him?
Should be an easy game.
He's just a kid.
-Huh?
-All right.
I'll play against you.
-Hm.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): Hm.
I underestimated him.
I figured he was a kid, so
he couldn't be that strong.
But he is a pro, and
he's studying here,
so he's one of the elite.
-Isumi.
You were too aggressive.
This move here was a mistake.
You were quite successful
in defending yourself
from black's overall
attack, but not
quite strong enough when
you were in close quarters.
-You thought you could
defend yourself with that?
What do you take me for, a fool?
You could never beat me.
Not when you play
like that. [laughing]
Hang in there.
Keep studying hard.
-Now, Lur Ping.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): He mocked me!
-So, how was he?
-Nothing special.
-You beat him, then.
-In this situation,
instead of advancing
to the top of the board, try
moving towards the bottom.
-Makes a lot of sense, seeing
as black's waiting at the top
and down the right hand side.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER):
These guys are
looking at the board
in a whole new way.
I could never join
in their discussion.
They've been studying here
for months, sometimes years.
Surrounded by other
elite pros, they
get to play from
morning to night.
I thought that if I stayed
here, I would learn a lot,
but if all that
happens is I lose
my confidence, then
what's the point?
No.
I'll be fine.
I'm just angry with myself.
That's OK, as long as I don't
let it turn into self-pity.
These guys are only in
their teens and early 20s,
but they're among the
best in the country--
stronger than a lot of
older, higher ranked players.
What am I doing here?
-Isumi.
-Uh, yes?
-Want to play a game
of lightning go?
10 seconds per move?
-Uh, OK.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): I played
a lot of 10 second go
during my spare time
when I was an insei.
This kind of game
depends on intuition
instead of reading the board.
-Onegaishimasu.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): He's
about the same age as me,
but he's way stronger than me.
He's like the equivalent
of Japanese 9-Dan.
-I resign.
-What?
Giving up already?
It's too soon for that.
-Huh?
-If black plays
hane here, white has
to back off or
fight to the death.
-So white has no option but to
cut first and then exchange.
Black would lose the initiative,
but none of his stones
would be in danger, and
he'd be in the lead.
-I thought if I
sacrifice my stone,
I'd get nothing in return.
But if he exchanged--
why did I resign so soon?
-Thanks, guys.
We should clear the board.
-It's OK.
I'll do it.
-Fair enough.
-Uh.
-What's this I hear about
you being from Japan?
I've been hanging out
in my room all day,
so I guess I missed the
formal introduction.
My name's Yanghai.
Pleased to meet you.
-Thanks.
I'm Isumi.
-So what's up?
You're looking pretty tired.
Where are you staying
while you're here?
You got a hotel or something?
-Yeah.
-You want to save some money?
I've got a spare bed in my
room you're welcome to use.
Interested?
I'm in room 303.
-I didn't think it was allowed
to stay overnight here,
especially not foreigners.
-Come on, who's going to know?
I don't care.
Mr. Li goes home at 5:00,
so he'll never find out.
Beats an expensive hotel.
-That's nice of
you, but no thanks.
-Oh.
And why not?
-I kind of wanted
some time on my own.
And it'll only be
for a couple of days.
-Well, the offer's still there.
I was hoping you'd
be able to tell me
something about the hot new
bands coming out of Japan right
now.
But I guess if you take go
seriously enough to come study
in China, you probably
don't have much time
to keep up with the music scene.
You interested in a game?
-Nah, I'm done for today.
-Oh.
Too bad.
You must be really tired.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): During
last year's pro exam,
after I lost three games in a
row to Shindo, Waya, and Fuku,
all it took was one win against
Ochi to regain my confidence.
It was my game
that kept me going.
Back then I believed in myself.
I trusted in my own strength.
But now, here at the
China Go Institute,
I'm not really sure
what my strength is.
Will my game keep
me going this time?
[theme song]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Next time, we're
going back to when
I first met Akira.
No one our age can come
close to defeating him.
But the kid who holds the
Children's Meijin title
shows up and is
ready to take him on!
It's Akira Toya in a match
against a young champion.
We'll see if there really is an
opponent who can rival Akira.
Next time, "Fateful Encounter."