[theme music]
-Look at this.
HIKARU: It isn't
just a tournament.
They've got everything
to do with Go here.
Teaching games, classes.
But you know, I
didn't think there'd
be this many people here.
-Hikaru.
Hikaru!
Over here!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Looks like this
is helping to
cheer him up a bit.
I'm glad we decided
to come here.
-I wish we could've played
the game without a handicap.
Next time we play, let's
make it an even game.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Yes.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): The match
didn't turn out so well for Sai
in the end, but it seemed
like a good idea at the time.
-Hikaru.
Can we go and watch
one the games?
Hm?
-Sure!
And don't forget
that next week we've
gotta watch Ochi's
Shincho Dan match.
He was bugging me a
lot about my game,
so I want a chance
to get back at him.
I'll put him in his place.
SAI (VOICEOVER): He's trying
so hard to be nice to me.
He was right.
My selfishness ruined what
was an important game for him.
It was all my fault.
From now on, I won't ask
to play any more matches.
Well, not often, anyway.
MAN: That'll be 1,500 yen.
Thank you very much.
GOKISO: Instead of
selling those cheap fans,
you need to try and move some
of those expensive Go boards.
-Gokiso-sensei.
A top of the line board like
that is a bit of a hard sell,
but I managed to get rid
of three of the others.
-Oh, yeah?
Which ones?
MAN: These ones right
here, made of kaya wood.
On special at 200,000 yen.
-You call this kaya?
You might be able to fool most
of the amateurs in this place,
but I wouldn't pay more
than 80,000 for this.
-Uh, sensei, sh.
-You got a marker pen
lying around somewhere?
I think we can improve
on your special sign.
That should be more effective.
-Oh.
You're a much better
salesman than me, Sensei.
-Don't be stupid.
I'm a professional Go player.
Remember, I'm the one
who pulled the strings
to get a space selling
stuff at this event.
Now get more money
from those suckers.
-Oh, look!
That cluster's about
to be captured.
He's caught an atari.
-Hm.
HIKARU: I don't know
what he's going hm for.
The next move is obvious.
He's got to defend the cluster!
-How could he miss that?
HIKARU: He'll get captured
and that'll be it.
-Doesn't he realize he
could have won the game?
It's more stressful
watching this
than watching a
professional game.
GIRL: Aren't you
gonna play a game?
You can still sign up.
-Uh, no thanks.
I'm just watching.
-You might not wanna
play, but what about me?
I just promised I wouldn't
ask him to let me play again.
I can't help it!
MAN: A new Go board?
I've been thinking about that.
One day I'll get around
to splurging on one.
-Instead of one day, why
not make today the day?
They say studying on
a good quality board
will help you improve your game.
-Oh.
They're just selling Go
boards and other stuff.
-Were you expecting more?
-This one's a special offer
for today only at 250,000.
And this one's a
steal of a deal.
Only 200,000 for
a board made out
of top grade, domestic kaya.
-Kaya?
I don't think it is.
No, this is definitely not kaya.
It looks similar, but it's not.
-What is kaya, anyway?
-A special wood used
to make Go boards.
Your grandfather's
board is made from it.
Kaya is used for
all the best boards.
-What about mine?
-It's katsura.
-Oh.
You mean, this
isn't really kaya?
-Like you would
know the difference!
You're just a kid!
-What's going on over here?
Stop interfering with
this man's business.
-I'm not interfering!
SAI (VOICEOVER): Hikaru.
Place a stone on the board.
-Hmph.
-No!
What do you think you're doing?
-Thought so.
Sounds too dull for kaya.
So that means--
-Look at this.
You put your filthy fingers
all over my merchandise!
You pesky little brat!
MAN: Is everything all right?
Is there a problem
I can help with?
-Nothing I can't handle.
This kid decided to play a stone
on one of expensive Go boards,
that's all.
-The only reason I
did that was because--
-If you make any more
false accusations,
we'll make you pay
for that Go board,
seeing as how you damaged it.
MAN: Um, I think I
should wait until I
get a bit better at playing Go
before I buy a brand new board.
Thanks, anyway.
-Wait!
Are you sure?
-Young man.
Go boards are made of soft wood.
They dent easily if
you're not careful.
Plus, they're very expensive.
Promise me you
won't do that again.
-I'm sorry.
Hmph.
-But we--
MAN: Honinbo Shusaku
used that board?
-Hm?
-Is this is for sale, too?
How much?
Six million?
Whoa.
-It just came in.
We acquired it from a very
well respected antiques dealer.
This is the very same
board that Shusaku-sensei
played on when he went to
Takamatsu to give lessons.
-Did you go to Takamatsu?
-I traveled all over with
Torajiro, so it's hard to say.
MAN: After the game, his
opponent asked Shusaku-sensei
if he would autograph
the board for him.
Which, of course, he did.
MAN: He signed it?
-It's signed by Inta--
I want to see this.
Hikaru, that signature isn't
Torajiro's handwriting.
-What?
You're kidding!
You mean it's fake?
-Huh?
What are you doing, you brat?
This signature is
absolutely genuine!
Now get lost!
-Hm.
-Sir, please don't go away!
-How dare he lie like that?
-That is not
Shusaku's handwriting.
-I have no doubts
that this is genuine.
-You see, even a pro says so.
You'd question a
the word of a pro?
-If he was a real pro,
he wouldn't be lying.
I get it.
He must be the one who
forged the signature.
-You!
Who do you think you are
talking to Mr. Gokiso?
Like that?
-What seems to be the
problem this time?
-How dare you dishonor
the name of Torajiro
with a forged signature?
-Yeah, how dare you?
What?
-Is there a problem?
-Well--
-Mr. Gokiso, maybe
you should head over
to your teaching session,
which starts shortly.
-Don't worry.
No one's going to
believe a teenager.
It's our word against his.
-So?
MAN: A forgery, huh?
Are you sure about that?
HIKARU: Yeah, those
two are big liars.
And those other boards aren't
real kaya wood, either.
-I knew it.
-What do you mean?
-I had a suspicion
about these boards.
They must be shin
kaya, not genuine kaya.
-Hm?
-Well, it's not like I'm
an expert or anything,
but the guy who was here
selling boards last year
was someone who
really knew his stuff.
He was nice enough to
teach me a few things.
Shin kaya looks a
lot like real kaya,
but actually it's made
from imported spruce.
It's not a bad wood.
I mean, it's got a lovely
grain and everything,
but it's way cheaper than kaya.
And because of that,
there are a lot
of crooked dealers out
there who pass one off
as the other to
make a fast buck.
HIKARU: I see.
How come the guy from
last year isn't here?
-Mr. Gokiso, he insisted
we use this new dealer.
And of course, we
couldn't refuse.
-Why not?
-An event like this depends on
the good will of pros like him
if it's going to succeed.
I'll try and keep an eye on this
Go board dealer from now on.
Thanks for bringing
it to our attention.
-I don't know.
I thought coming here
would be a lot of fun,
but this has kind of ruined it.
Wanna watch another game?
Oh man, I don't think I've
ever seen you this angry.
-Sai?
Hikaru, over there.
That scoundrel is
playing a teaching game.
-Oh yeah!
And that guy he's
playing is the one
who they were trying
to sell a board to.
-Oh dear, oh dear.
You've gone and left
openings everywhere.
-And the upper
left corner's dead.
-Let's face it.
You're never going to
improve your game until you
invest in a decent
quality Go board.
-He's being really mean.
-You're right.
He's not teaching him,
he's tormenting him.
Treating him like a fool.
This is no way to
play a teaching game.
-So you're saying
there's no hope?
-Don't give up yet.
There's still hope.
-You've still got a
chance to save the game.
Hang in there, mister,
and you can do it.
-How could he possibly
make a comeback from here?
But if you insist, let's
continue, shall we?
-It's OK.
I think I've had enough.
-But hey, the kid
behind you says
you can still win the game.
-Why don't you play in my place?
-They s actions speak
louder than words.
So here's your chance, kid.
-Hikaru, sit and play.
-Are you sure?
He is a pro, after all.
-I know I can win this game.
And if I do, he has
to promise to stop
selling the board with
the fake signature.
-OK.
Gotcha.
-Well, then, you're
actually gonna play.
-Here's the deal.
If I win, then you've gotta
stop selling the board
with the fake Shusaku signature.
-Hmph.
It's such a long shot.
Sure, why not?
HIKARU: Then it's a deal.
(VOICEOVER) Won't he suspect
something if I let you play,
Sai?
-This man has no respect.
He sees you only as a child.
If he loses to you, he'll be
too humiliated and embarrassed
to tell anyone about it.
-In that case--
he's all yours, Sai!
Here we go!
14, 4.
One point enclosure.
-So, do you guys have
anymore questions?
-Kurata-sensei, I'm
afraid we're out of time.
-Well, I think we've
covered everything.
It looks like we'll
have to stop there.
Thanks very much.
Thank you.
-Kurata-sensei, I'd love it
if I could get your autograph.
-Oh, yes.
Yeah, of course!
-I'll be rooting for you
to win the title this year.
-Oh, me, too!
Kurata Meijin's got a nice
ring to it, don't you think?
Maybe that's how I'll
sign my autograph.
Meijin to be.
There.
[laughter] Better not
show that to Toya Meijin.
-Sensei, sign
something for me, too?
-Sure.
How about the Kisei title?
Sentabi, Kisei Atsushi Kurata.
-Do one for me
with Honinbo on it.
-No problem.
Eventually the Honinbo,
Atsushi Kurata.
-Thanks. I love it.
Hope it won't be too long
before you get there.
-I'm one of the ones who booked
a teaching session with you,
Sensei, and I can't wait.
I'm going to learn so much.
-You betcha!
MAN: I wish I'd gone with you
instead of that other guy.
-Oh?
What do you mean?
Did something happen?
-Well, just a while ago
I had a teaching session
with Gokiso-sensei.
-And what's the
matter with that?
-It was horrible.
-Horrible?
-It felt like he
was setting me up
to fail so he could say
things to put me down.
MAN: That's awful.
There's gotta be an explanation.
There must be
something going on.
-It's just a rumor, but
I heard Mr. Gokiso's
been in financial trouble since
the stock market went down.
-I don't care
what's up with him.
There's no excuse to take
it out on us like that.
-In the end, I got so fed up
with him I just quit the game.
Even though there was this
kid behind me who said
I still had a chance of
winning if I stuck at it.
-Once you're that far
behind against a pro,
it's pretty much impossible
to make a comeback.
-That's what I thought, too.
-Let's face it.
The idea of a kid being
good enough to beat a pro
is just too
ridiculous for words.
MAN: Oh, there you are.
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Do you remember that boy?
The one who took over
your game for you?
He's giving Gokiso a good run.
-What?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I
think we've done it.
It's down to the endgame.
Sai is so awesome.
He made moves I would
never have thought of.
-This can't be.
I don't believe it.
How could I have
underestimated him?
I can't figure it out.
MAN: Over here?
MAN: Let's have a look.
-Huh?
-Was this the game?
-What do you want, Kurata?
-Hey, don't clear those away.
I want to see!
-Well, maybe I don't
want you to see,
'cause I played such
an embarrassing game.
If you saw it,
you'd laugh at me.
And I'm not having that.
-What?
Was it that bad?
Shame I missed it.
-Excuse me.
-Wait.
His promise!
-Hey!
We had a deal, remember?
KURATA: You there.
So you won the game?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): It
wasn't really me who won.
It was Sai.
-So what's the story?
You managed to come all the
way from behind to beat him?
Seriously, no way?
You're kidding?
I mean, this guy is a major pro.
If you managed to
beat him, then--
-Hey, wait.
I think I've seen
you somewhere before.
You're not a pro, are you?
-I only just started as a pro.
My name's Shindou.
-Ah-ha!
Now I've got it!
I read about you in Go Weekly!
Yeah, I remember.
You're one of the new
One-Dans, aren't you?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
What's with this guy?
-Tell me something.
I heard you say you
had a deal with Gokiso.
What was it?
-The deal was--
-Boards for sale.
Oh, Sensei!
I'm sorry.
None of this merchandise is
anywhere near the quality
that a man of taste like
yourself would want to buy.
Don't even bother looking.
-Genuine kaya?
Yeah, right!
And you're charging 200,000?
-This is-- well, you see, it's--
-What?
-I can explain.
-Come on, then.
We're waiting.
Explain.
-I put the wrong price tag on.
See?
Here's the right one.
I'll change it right away.
It's a good thing you
brought it to my attention.
Thank you.
Sensei?
Is there anything else?
-Didn't you already sell
some of those boards today?
-Well, I'd need to check.
-I'd like you to bring
me all the receipts
from your transactions,
so I can check them.
Yes good idea.
-What?
You want to see the receipts?
-Right, then.
Now-- this is it?
I haven't got a clue what
Shusaku's handwriting's
supposed to look like.
So this is--
-It's a fake!
-A forgery!
-How do you know?
-I just do.
-No doubt!
-Yeah!
I'm telling you, it's a fake!
-I'm supposed to take
your word for it?
-Yes.
-Now, about this board--
-Mm-hm.
-You must remove the board with
the forged signature at once.
then come and see me
privately in my office.
-Be he won't be back next year.
Nope.
[laughter] Just for the
record, beating Mr. Gokiso
is no big deal.
Now, if you had
beaten me, that would
be something to brag about.
Gokiso's over the hill.
He's past it.
-Who's he?
-Ask him, Hikaru.
HIKARU: Excuse me.
What's your name?
-Don't you know who I am?
Atsushi Kurata,
professional Go player.
Soon to be the Meijin.
Or the Honinbo.
-Are you that strong
a player, Mr. Kurata?
-You betcha.
It's not that hard to
beat the players that
are ranked above you.
The ones above me
are all desperate.
Even Toya Meijin has
reached his peak.
The old man Kuwabara
tries to make everyone
think he's invincible.
But he's desperate, too.
All that posturing
of his is a bluff.
He'll do anything to hang
on to his Honinbo title.
He'll be debated someday
soon, and if it's not by me,
that'll only be 'cause
Ogata beat me to it.
The ones to watch out for
the younger players still
coming up the ranks.
That's why I'm more afraid of
Akira Toya than his father.
The games I play against
those ranked below me
will be life and death battles.
But that's still a ways off.
I gotta beat those
above me first.
Then deal with the others.
-He seems to be very
confident, doesn't he?
-Hey, what's your
name again, kid?
-It's Shindou.
Hikaru Shindou.
-Huh.
I'm kind of surprised
you never heard of me.
Oh, well.
Hey, give me one of those fans.
-Huh?
-Hm.
Take this, my compliments.
-Sorry tobother you, Sensei,
but those fans are for sale.
I'll need you to pay for it.
-Don't be shy.
You can keep the autograph.
-Uh-- I don't want
your autograph.
-You don't want-- but
everyone wants my autograph.
Why don't you?
-Give me that.
I'm a professional
too, you know?
I'm signing it.
-Hm?
What have you done?
You've ruined it, you fool!
You've gone and ruined my
precious, beautiful, priceless
autograph with your
ugly handwriting!
-Uh, your writing isn't exactly
a piece of art, Mr. Kurata.
-Oh how true.
Unlike Torajiro's.
-Well, if we doesn't want
it, you can have it back.
-Uh, thank you.
-You're weird, you know that?
Really weird.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Look who's talking.
-Look what time it is!
I'm gonna be late for
my teaching games!
I gotta go, but I'm
gonna remember your name.
The kid who's an expert on
Honinbo Shusaku's handwriting.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Who, me?
An expert.
-I still think you're
gonna regret not keeping
that fan with my
autograph on it!
HIKARU: Hey, Sai.
How you feeling now?
-Much better, thank you.
Much better.
-An expert on
Shusaku's handwriting?
He's a strange kid,
that's for sure.
[theme music]
SAI: So, Hikaru.
Who is your next
opponent going to be?
HIKARU: It's Toya!
-That's great!
This is the game you've
been waiting for.
HIKARU: I know
I've gotten better,
but I'm not sure if I've
reached his level yet.
SAI: You'll soon find out.
It looks like he's ready
to wage war against you.
HIKARU: Next time,
Hikaru Versus Akira.
SAI: There'll be
a surprise that's
going to shock the world of Go.