[theme music]
-What's the matter, Sai?
SAI: Your move here.
It looks like the kind
of move I would make.
-Really, you think so?
I tried to imagine
where you'd play,
and that's what I came up with.
When I play Waya, it's
gonna be a tougher
match than the one against Ochi.
Ochi's already passed
the exam, so he
won't be as desperate
to win as Waya.
I'm starting to feel kind
of nervous about this game.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): This is
gonna decide the match.
If I can turn this
shape into my territory,
he's gonna lose for sure.
If his stone stays
there, he'll win!
-You can do it.
You'll be joining the pros.
WAYA (VOICEOVER):
I'm almost there,
as long as I don't rush
and make any mistakes.
I'm gonna make it, Sensei.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Hikaru.
WAYA (VOICEOVER):
Come on, Shindou.
You don't need that
much time to think.
-I, uh-- I resign.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): I guess
that means Honda's out.
I knew his chances of
passing were pretty slim,
but now there's no way.
-Huh?
-I'm sorry.
I think I'm gonna walk.
-OK, if that's what you want.
I've got a feeling some fresh
air might do you some good.
-Cheer up!
You can always try
again next year!
[bawling]
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Just
three of us left now.
Me, Isumi, and Shindou.
We're all fighting for
the two remaining places,
and one of them's gonna be mine.
Honda's out of the picture, so
if I win this one, I'm through!
I'm gonna be a pro!
-Hm.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): What's
taking so long, Shindou?
Just make your move.
It doesn't matter where
you go, because you're
gonna lose anyway.
SAI (VOICEOVER): There's
one way and one way only
for black to survive, but
it's a difficult move to see.
-Hm.
I can't see a way out of this.
But-- But if I was
Sai, if it was him
playing, not me, with all
this space on the board,
he'd find a way to make
the black stones survive.
Where would he move?
OK.
Imagine he'd been
playing this game,
and then imagine that I'm
playing in Waya's place,
and that I'm making the
same moves as he would.
If I was Waya, what
plan would I use
to try and kill off
the black stones.
Is there any way those
stones can survive?
There's just no way.
That's what I'd be thinking.
The game would be over.
Black would be finished.
But then, just when things
were looking hopeless,
I'd look up at Sai.
And then he'd-- He would--
WAYA (VOICEOVER): I
figured he might do that,
but it's useless for
him to keep going.
Why didn't I see that?
How could I have missed it?
Can he come back from here?
No!
It's impossible!
SAI (VOICEOVER): He found it.
It took him time,
but he found the way
to turn the board
to his advantage.
Now if he can just
keep his concentration,
he has chance of winning.
At last.
Hikaru has found the way,
the narrow and winding path
to victory.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): He can
make an eye in the center.
But I can't just
ignore my own group!
He's got me trapped either way.
I can't kill them off now.
Those black stones I thought
were dead are back in the game!
-Now listen, you're
going to pass.
Let me say it one more time.
You're going to pass.
You gotta be confident, Waya.
If you do that,
you'll join the pros.
WAYA: Sensei!
-I resign.
-But--
SAI (VOICEOVER): It
was a great match.
Hikaru has proven he's
the better player.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
-Yeah.
Thanks for the game, Shindou.
-Sai.
-Huh?
That was the name of the
player on the internet.
He was awesome.
You remember the first
time I played you?
I told you something.
I said I thought
you could someday
become as strong
a player as Sai.
-Mm-hm.
Yeah, I remember.
-Well, today you did it.
You played as well as Sai.
-Thanks, Waya.
SAI (VOICEOVER): He's right.
Hikaru has taken his game
to a whole new level.
[sigh]
-OK!
Last opponent is Ochi.
-So, aren't you going to
tell me how it went today?
-If you're really
interested, I won.
-Congratulations.
That means you'll pass the
test with the best game record.
-You couldn't care less.
-Hey, that isn't true.
You've managed to prove
what a good player you are.
I'm impressed.
-Don't you want to know
how Shindou's been doing?
Or are you waiting until his
match with me to find out?
-Well, uh, how did he do?
-He won his game.
So he stays at three losses.
-Interesting.
-I knew it.
Hmph.
(VOICEOVER) He only cares
about what happens to Shindo.
Even though I'm the one who will
finish the exam in first place.
-What's bothering you?
Good evening.
-Toya-sensei, I just had
to come and say thank you
for all you've done.
With your help, Kosuke
was able to pass the test
and finish in top position.
Oh, please feel
free to sit down.
-Thank you.
-You know, I've been thinking.
I'd like to throw a
party to celebrate
Kosuke becoming a pro.
AKIRA: That sounds
like a good idea.
-Yes.
And we would be very honored
if you could come and join us.
-I don't think we should
be talking about that yet.
Let's wait and see if Ochi
manages to win his final match.
We don't want him to lose focus.
-Hm.
Yeah, you're right.
Even though he's guaranteed
to pass the test,
another loss wouldn't look
very good on his record.
It's strange, but I
get the impression
you're not convinced Kosuke is
going to win his last match.
-No, not at all.
It's just, you should never
underestimate your opponent.
Whoever they are.
-Well, of course.
I agree with that.
But by the way
you're talking, it
sounds like you don't think
Kosuke's good enough to win.
This last opponent of yours
can't be that much of a threat,
can he?
Kosuke?
-Shindou's no threat to me.
-Underestimate him,
and you'll lose.
-And what if I win?
What if I actually beat Shindou?
Maybe then you'll start to
treat me like a serious rival.
If I win, I want you to help
me get into Toya Meijin's study
sessions.
-All right, then.
If you win, I'll ask my
father to invite you.
-That's wonderful!
You don't know how
grateful we are.
I can't think of a
better place for Kosuke
to continue his studies.
He'd practice with the best.
I mean, Ogata Nine-Dan is
one of the Meijin's students,
and he's at the top
of his game right now.
What an amazing opportunity
that would be for you.
All you have to go in
win your last match.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Shindou,
I'm ready for you!
-I feel kind of sorry for Waya.
I don't think he
can beat Fuku today.
-Yeah, I know.
He usually has trouble
playing against Fuku,
and this time he's gonna
be under a lot of pressure.
-You know what I think?
There will be a playoff
between Isumi and Waya.
-What about Shindou?
-Huh?
-Who do you think's gonna win?
Shindou or Ochi?
-I think it'll be Shindou.
Ochi's already through, right?
So he doesn't need to
go all out for a win.
-I'm not so sure about that.
-What do you mean?
-Have you forgotten
what Ochi can be like?
I know he lost that
one game against Isumi,
but he wanted to get
through undefeated.
-I guess you're right.
He's not going to let Shindou
win without a bit of a fight,
is he?
-Mm-hm.
I tell you, if I had to pick
the odds in their match--
-Well, what would they be?
-I'll say 50-50.
-50-50?
Your opinion of Shindou
sure seems to have gone up.
-Ah, Sensei?
Should we be thinking
about a playoff?
-Yes, as far as I remember,
Isumi has four losses,
and Shindou and Waya
have three each.
Of course, it all
comes down to how
they do in their matches
today, but a playoff
looks very likely.
If Waya and Shindou
both lose their games,
then we'll have three
people tied at four losses.
How does a playoff work when
there's three players fighting
for the two remaining places?
-Well, if that happens we'll
have to draw for the pairings,
have the first match tomorrow,
and the second one on, uh-- oh,
dear.
I can see this is
going to be tough.
-Shindou.
How long have you been there?
-A while.
-Why didn't you say hello
so we knew you were there?
-You were so busy
gossipping about me,
I didn't want to interrupt.
Well, I'm here now.
Hi.
-Hi.
Shindou?
-Huh?
-Uh-- it doesn't matter.
-Been to the match room yet?
Anyone in there?
-I think Fuku's there.
I haven't seen Isumi
and the others yet.
-Oh, OK.
I'll go check.
-Just now, what were yo
going to say to Shindou?
-If he wins today, then
he'll have made it through
to become a pro.
I was gonna wish him
good luck for the game,
but then I thought
it would be better
if I didn't say anything.
-Why?
-Wishing him luck isn't
going to make the slightest
bit of difference now.
He's under so much pressure,
I'm sure he doesn't need someone
like me reminding him how
important the match is.
We're the ones who need some
luck around here, not him.
Oh, what am I
gonna do next year?
Hm.
-So, shall we head
to the match room?
-Sure.
Tell you what.
I'm gonna go outside and get
some fresh air before we start.
Huh?
Ochi.
-Hey, Shindou.
You ready to lose today?
-Don't just stand there.
Say something!
You aren't gonna let him
insult you like that.
At least tell him that's
what you were going to say.
Come on!
-That's what I was gonna say!
OCHI: I've been playing Akira
Toya almost every night,
just so I can bet you today.
-Toya?
Ochi's been training with Toya!
-That's why I know I'm
gonna win this match.
[theme music]
HIKARU: Toya's been
helping Ochi get
ready for the game against me.
SAI: He may believe there's
someone training you.
HIKARU: Toya's gonna have
to recognize me as a rival
if I win this game.
SAI: That won't be easy.
They've developed a strategy
specifically to defeat you.
HIKARU: Next time,
Hikaru Versus Ochi.
SAI: It's your
biggest challenge yet.