[theme music]
SAI (VOICEOVER): Hikaru
is starting on the path
to the Divine Move.
It won't be me that finds it.
It'll be Hikaru.
The destiny set by the spirits
of Go cannot be changed.
-That's weird.
Is it my imagination,
or has the stain
started to disappear
since last time I saw it?
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Just as I feared.
Destiny will take its course.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Hm, maybe
it's always been like that.
It's so long ago,
I don't remember.
-Hey, there, Hikaru.
-Yeah?
-What are you doing tomorrow?
Your grandmother and I were
planning to go see a play.
You interested in
coming with us?
-A play?
I've got this Go
seminar tomorrow night.
They're putting me up in
a hotel and everything.
There's going to be about
150 people taking part.
I have to do teaching
games, stuff like that.
-What?
You?
-I'm not the only one.
There'll be a few other
pros there as well.
-Fancy a game with your grandpa?
If you don't have to rush off.
-Sure.
And tell you what, if you beat
me, I'll give you 1,000 yen.
-Why you little rascal.
You're on.
-Hikaru.
-Hm?
-I'd rather we went home so
you could have a game with me
instead.
You can play your
grandfather any time.
-I don't know
what's got into you.
We play each other all the time.
I don't see grandpa
very often, so I
should take the chance
to play him when I can.
Come on, let's go, Sai.
-But Hikaru-- Hikaru, I-- wait.
You don't understand.
I'm going to be
leaving here soon.
-Come on, aren't you ever going
to stop worrying about that?
It's ridiculous.
You've been around for 1,000
years and everything's fine.
You better not be trying to
make me feel sorry for you
just so you can
get your own way.
Because that's
not going to work.
You've been acting
selfishly lately,
and I'm getting tired of it.
I'm going to play grandpa,
and you'll just have to watch.
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Oh, Hikaru.
He doesn't understand.
[music plays]
-Hi.
Is this where you check in?
-Yes, hello, Shindo.
Here is an updated
schedule for you.
You're staying in room 303 along
with Mr. Nagai and Mr. Yokoi.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Mr. Ogata's
going to be here to too?
Oh, I better keep a low profile.
I don't want him
bothering me about Sai.
-Seiji Ogata is one
of those rare pros
who can play any style of Go.
But his opponent, Ms.
Haruki, is the kind of player
who keeps on fighting back.
Well, well, that's
an interesting move
from Ogata-sensei.
Hm.
I have a feeling he'll regret
that move later in the game.
But I should be
careful what I say,
or I'll get myself into
trouble with Mr. Ogata.
-Ashiwara.
-You see what I mean?
[laughter]
-This ending here won't
give immediate results,
but it has another purpose.
If you decide that you
want to push through,
this movie is going
to help you force
your way towards that goal.
Of course, there's
more to it than that.
-Ah, it's making sense.
-Shindo.
What are you doing
still playing?
Isn't it way past your bedtime?
-Gah, Ogata-sensei.
-Hey, there's no reason
to be all scared.
I just came to play a little Go.
-Have you and him
been out tonight?
-Yeah, I took him
out on the town.
We had to celebrate him
winning the Judan title.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Ugh, maybe
a bit too much celebrating.
-Hey, Shindo.
-Yeah?
-Let me play Sai.
-But Ogata-sensei, I already
told you I don't know Sai.
How can I let you play
him if I don't know him?
-Hikaru, I think
we should play him
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai,
you're being selfish again.
-It's OK for me to play him
when he's in this condition.
I'm sure he won't
know I'm his opponent.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Really?
What's the point?
He doesn't look in good
enough shape to play.
You wouldn't want a game with
someone when they're like that.
SAI (VOICEOVER): I may
never have an opportunity
to play a serious
game against him.
-It doesn't really
matter how it turns out.
If I can go a little
way towards fulfilling
the demand he made to
you at the hospital--
-Let me play him.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Uh huh.
I guess it wouldn't hurt.
Playing you might be
a nice way for him
to celebrate his Judan win.
-Come on, Shindo.
Let me play Sai.
-I've got a better idea.
Why don't you and
me have a game?
-What?
Now?
-Can you believe the kid
wants to challenge Sensei
by playing him in
that condition?
-Well, you're not
Sai, but I guess
you're going to have to do.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): He
doesn't look too good.
I don't know if he'll
even be able to play.
But a game against you might
help him feel a bit better.
What's with the long face now?
I'm letting you
play him, aren't I?
Hm, geez.
I'll let you play
for Mr. Ogata's sake.
But you've got to cheer up.
Because it's starting to be no
fun hanging around with you.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Why?
Why Hikaru and not me?
Spirits of Go, tell me!
Why Hikaru?
Why him?
Soon I will be gone and
only he will remain.
I cannot help feeling
envious of him.
He has his whole
future ahead of him.
But that's not all.
I don't want to leave him.
I didn't want to
leave Torajiro either.
The memory of him on his death
bed is still very strong.
He said to me, "Sai, I'm sorry."
I didn't want him to go.
But I was given no choice.
I'm sorry, Hikaru.
I will have to leave you soon.
[grunting]
-I didn't know you were in here.
Sorry if we woke you.
-No, that's OK.
Just turn out the
light, would you?
-We should have enough
light if we play over here
by the window.
Sit down.
-You're still thirsty?
-It's been a long and I'm tired.
That'll be my handicap.
I doubt I'm going to put up
much of a fight in this game.
-Easier for me to win.
Don't expect me to take
it easy on you, OK?
-Hey, hey, you can't
treat it like a real game
when I'm in this state.
Save your tough guy act
for an official match.
I already got an idea of
what your skill level is.
I was there watching when you
played your Shinshodan Series
game.
Kuwabara-sensei and
I were taking bets
on who was going to win.
Kuwabara got in
first and bet on you,
which meant I was left with
no choice but to bet on Toya.
But if you want
to know the truth,
my money would have
been on you as well.
-Hmph, right.
You expect me to believe
you when you're like this?
-You really are a brat.
Although I am a lot more
tired today than unusual.
Winning the Judan Series
title is a big deal.
So I think I deserve to go
out and celebrate a bit.
Toya-sensei's retirement was
turned everything upside down.
Even though I won
the Judan title,
people won't recognize
me as a champion
unless I can successfully
defended it next year.
You'll see.
I'm going to be the
best in the world.
So, Shindo, like I said
before-- let me play Sai.
-Settle for playing me?
-Sure. Why not?
16.
You go first.
-Onegaishimasu.
-Yeah.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Well,
it looks like I've won.
It's all over.
-Wait.
-You made a big mistake on
an easy life and death play.
You must be really
out of it to do that.
-My mistake hasn't got
anything to do with it.
Let's face it, you played well.
You went on the attack over
in the upper right corner.
My keystones were useless after
that, so what was the point?
After that, my
heart wasn't in it,
so I played some
pretty reckless moves.
I'm surprised it took
you that long to beat me.
-Maybe if we'd played
earlier in the day.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Was it really
worth letting him play Sai?
If he actually knew who
he'd been playing against,
I'd have been in big trouble.
But then again, he couldn't
have figured it out
while he's like this.
-Well, good night, Mr. Ogata.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): It's kind
of sad, him losing this way.
-Some of those moves
were masterful.
There was no mistakes.
It was as if I was playing Sai.
[chuckling] But that's absurd.
I'm just imagining things.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Hopefully that game's
got him off my back for a while.
I'll skip out of here
early tomorrow morning
so I don't bump into him again.
Sai?
-In the actual game, white
went after black's eye space
by playing here.
Now what would have
happened if white
had connected in
the center first?
White would wait for this move,
and then go on to play an--
-Ogata-sensei,
how are you today?
-Have you seen Shindo?
-He went back home
early this morning.
He'd finished all his
teaching sessions,
so I guess he didn't see
any point in staying.
[yawn]
HIKARU: I don't know
why I'm so tired.
I had a chance to
sleep on the train.
I can barely stay awake.
-Hikaru, I would
like to play a game.
-Now?
I haven't got the energy.
I'm too tired.
I gotta get some sleep or else
I might get sick, you know.
But I guess a quick
game first will be OK.
Well, come on, sit down.
Here we go.
SAI (VOICEOVER): 140
years ago, Torajiro
allowed me to guide him.
If Torajiro existed
for my sake, then
I have existed
for Hikaru's sake.
And what's more, Hikaru will now
exist for someone else's sake.
Then that person will be
there for someone else.
And so it will continue,
year after year,
millennium after millennium.
The long path that leads us
all toward the Divine Move.
My part in the
journey is now over.
Hikaru, this is it.
Hikaru?
Oh, can you hear me?
Hikaru, It was fun
being with you.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
It's your turn.
What are you waiting for?
Hm?
I said it's your turn.
Sai?
[ending theme]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Sai, where are you?
He isn't at grandpa's
where I first saw him.
Where else could he have gone?
I'm gonna find him, no
matter what it takes,
or where I have to go.
But where do I start?
Torajiro's grave!
He could have gone
to see Torajiro.
Next time, Is Sai Really Gone?