[theme music]
-I, um-- I don't play Go
on the internet, either.
But the thing is, there's
this friend of mine
who's played lots of times.
And I know he'd
love to play you.
He's wanted to forever.
And the name he uses
when he plays is Sei.
-All right, then.
It'll be a nice distraction
from the pressure of the Judan
championship games.
-Toya-sensei.
You're gonna play your
best against Sai, right?
-I've made up my mind.
If I lose to your
friend, then I will
retire as a professional player.
I won't play again.
The game will take place
one week from today.
We will begin at
10:00 in the morning
and have a tie limit
of three hours each.
-Thank you for doing this.
-I can't see Koyo
Toya's name anywhere.
-Well, I'm sure
he's really busy.
He's got pro games to play.
Toya is the Meijin
champion, after all.
-Do you think this Koyo
Toya is really him?
I mean, it could be
anyone, couldn't it?
-No, it's him, all right.
He beat the pro Achiryu
just the other day.
Achiryu's one of the top
players in Japan right now,
so if he managed
to win against him,
then there's a good
chance this actually
is the real Toya Meijin.
You know, internet Go is getting
more interesting every year.
-It reminds me of the
time Sai was online.
-Oh yeah.
I remember that guy.
A few years ago, when
I was representing
the US in the international
amateur tournament,
he was the player everyone
was talking about.
You know, we never did
find out his true identity.
-Mm.
MAN: Frank, Is that you?
-Hm?
-We haven't seen
you around for ages.
-Hello, Mr. Ewyer.
Work's been keeping me
fairly busy these days.
-Well, we missed having
one of the best players
from the Netherlands in
our midst, that's for sure.
What do you say to a quick
game, you and me, eh?
-Sure, why not?
-By the way, I saw Koyo
Toya play the other day.
-Oh really?
-Toya Meijin of Japan.
I didn't know he
was in the country.
-He's not here.
I saw him play online.
-Toya Meijin's playing
on the internet?
Are you sure it's really him?
-It's hard to say.
The guy he was playing
wasn't the strongest opponent
in the world.
And he logged off before
anyone had the chance
to chat with him about the game.
-Hm.
Sounds like an imposter.
A few months back, some guy
showed up pretending to be Sai.
He soon disappeared again.
-Who's this Sai?
-Ha!
You've never heard of Sai?
He caused quite a sensation
on the net a while back.
Easily as strong a
player as Toya Meijin.
-That's quite some comparison.
What else do you know about him?
-He's a mystery.
He did identify
himself as being JPN.
-JPN, huh?
So, he's Japanese.
-(VOICEOVER) When I went to
the international amateur
tournament in Japan a
couple of years ago,
one of my goals was to try and
find out who this Sai really
was.
Everyone knew about him
from his games online,
but no one knew
his true identity.
Then without any warning, he
disappeared from the internet.
I wonder if he'll
show up online again.
MAN: Oh, that's it.
There's no way Ogata
can come back from this.
-Guess that means
it'll all be over soon.
-The Meijin is too strong!
-Must be enormously
frustrating for Mr. Ogata.
He was doing so well at
the start of the series.
-If he'd won, he'd
have taken the title.
Ogata Judan.
-He's been in good
form lately, and he's
playing better than ever.
It's just a matter of time
before he wins a championship.
-I bet he'd be the
first to agree.
It takes some nerve to challenge
your teacher for a title.
Ogata tries so hard to act cool,
but I see right through him.
He makes the press believe
he's no more than a practice
partner for Toya Meijin,
when in reality he
wants to take away the title.
-But defeating Toya Meijin
is a huge obstacle for him
to overcome.
-Don't forget, Toya collapsed
with a heart attack last week.
He looks much better, but who
knows what toll its taken?
He hasn't been released
from the hospital.
-He's got his wife here
to help look after him.
-He's fine.
He's the sort of
guy that'll be back
at full strength in no time.
MAN: Looks.
Like they're finished.
MAN: Hm.
I'd say he's won by
6 and 1/2 points.
Let's go review the game.
Ogata you played a little
too cautiously here.
Toya picked up on it and
used it to his advantage.
This is the point where he
took control of the game.
-Yes, I knew I was going
to be in trouble when
white decided to play there.
-I was expecting black
to make a counterattack
by connecting here.
-Sure, that makes sense.
-So, the game was over
from that point on?
-Certainly looks like it.
The rest of the game was good,
a fight across the board.
But that one mistake was
what cost you the win, Ogata.
-Excuse me, Toya-sensei.
I just wanted to say, I
hope you're feeling better.
-I'm feeling great, thank you.
In fact, I could play the
fifth match right here and now.
-I gather you haven't
been officially
released from the hospital yet.
-He likes being
treated like a king,
so of course he's
not been released.
And besides, he started
playing Go on the internet.
-You're playing online?
-The other day, I noticed
someone called Toya logged on.
Never in a million years
did I think it would be him.
I mean, Toya-sensei
is the last person
you'd expect to see online.
I thought, I'm gonna teach
this imposter a lesson.
How dare he impersonate
the Toya Meijin.
So I challenged him to a game.
-No way.
Ichiru Kisei versus Toya
Meijin on the internet?
-He showed no mercy, attacking
every little mistake I made.
It's really him, I thought.
What on Earth's doing
here of all places?
Then he captured
one of my stones!
-It's just to keep me occupied
until I leave the hospital.
I prefer the feel of
stones in my fingers
more than a keyboard.
-Oh, so you won't be going
online for much longer, then?
-Well, if you'll
excuse me, gentlemen.
I should get going.
-Mr. Ogata-- Don't you want
to go for a drink with us?
Ogata-sensei?
-Anyone else get the
impression he's upset?
-It's getting late.
Maybe we should be
heading back, Sensei?
We don't want your wife to
start worrying about you.
-Oh, all right.
Let's call it a night.
So, the Judan series is now
tied at two games apiece.
The title's going to be
decided in a final game.
-You seem a lot
better today, dear.
It's so lovey here.
I wish we could stay longer.
Why don't we take a bit
of a detour on our way
back to the hospital?
-I'd rather not.
I don't wanna take any
time out right now.
I've got another game
I have to focus on.
-What do you mean
by another game?
The fifth match of the Judan
series isn't until next week.
-Ah, hello.
Hello.
You're not playing
Go again, are you?
You were playing in that
championship all day yesterday.
You must be worn out by now.
-It's amazing what a win
can do for his energy level.
I'm sure he thinks
he's invincible.
-I've heard that before.
But don't forget, the
reason you collapsed
was because you were
pushing yourself too hard.
I really think you should
get some rest today.
I'll let you play online
if you can assure me
it's just for fun, and
there's no stress involved.
-It helps pass the time.
Although, there are still some
games I can't afford to lose.
May I ask a small favor, doctor?
Can you make sure I don't
get any visitors tomorrow?
-Why's that, Mr. Toya?
-I'd like a day to play Go
without anyone disturbing me.
-Oh, boy.
Always Go.
Does he ever do anything
but play this game?
I don't know how you put
up with it, Mrs. Toya.
Hm.
If you could pull yourself
away from that computer
for a minute, please?
I'm sure you're fine, but no
harm in doing a quick check up.
Well, it looks like
everything's back to normal.
Now, I can't tell a Go
player not to play Go,
but from now on, I'd like you to
watch your health more closely.
I think it'll be
OK to release him
the day after
tomorrow, as planned.
And I'll leave a
note with the staff
that no visitors are
allowed tomorrow.
-Thank you, Doctor.
-Don't worry about coming
to visit me tomorrow.
And tell Akira he
doesn't have to, either.
-Akira said he had plans to
spend the day in a study group
with some other
young pro players,
so I don't think he'll
have the time to stop by.
-Good.
That's fine.
-Huh?
So, this Koyo Toya I'm
playing right now--
he's certainly strong enough
to be Toya Meijin of Japan.
Yes.
It has to be him.
No one else I know could
play this quickly, and still
make such great moves.
[gasp]
-It's really him.
Toya Meijin is actually
playing against Lin Shin Lee.
Lee doesn't stand a chance.
There's no way he
could win this one.
[phone ringing]
-Hello, Frank here.
MAN (OVER PHONE): Morning.
It's me.
You've got to turn
on your computer.
Koyo Toya is playing.
-Yeah, I know.
I've been watching.
I logged in about
half an hour ago.
There's no question.
This has to be the real Toya.
It's great.
No doubt at all.
I mean, who else could crunch
an opponent like Lee so easily?
-Morning, how are you?
FRANK: You know
who he is, right?
He's China's top amateur player.
He was international
amateur champion last year.
That's right.
Did you see?
He's resigned.
Oh, yeah.
It'll be great if we get to
see more games like this one.
-I don't know yet.
FRANK: OK. Bye.
-What's all the
excitement about?
-Toya Meijin of Japan
is playing Go online.
You have heard of
him, haven't you?
Toya Meijin!
-Uh--
FRANK: I know that more and more
pros have been playing online
in the last couple of years,
but to have him playing?
This is amazing!
What am I going to do?
I'd love to challenge
him to a game online,
but how does
someone like me even
go about asking
someone like him?
Oh, what am I going to do?
HIKARU: Toya Meijin is
such an amazing player.
Look at this game.
The move he made
here is unbelievable.
I never would have thought
of a move like that.
You should see what they said
about it in the magazine.
They've got interviews
with pros who
say they've never
seen anything like it.
SAI: Sometimes there
are possibilities
that can only be seen
by the person playing.
There is an enormous
difference between being
a spectator of the game, and
being a participant in it.
There can never be the
same involvement or passion
when merely watching
from the sidelines.
How could there be?
Only the ones playing can
see deep into the game,
far into the depths
of the universe that's
found within the board.
That's why you can only begin
to know an opponent's true power
when you face him in
person across the board.
MITSUKO: Hikaru!
Akari's here to see you.
-Huh?
Really?
-Yeah.
-What are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed
to be at the Go club?
Did you skip out of it?
-No, I didn't.
It's just that
everyone else seemed
to have other stuff to do today.
So I thought I'd
come around and see
if you wanted to play a game.
-What? With you?
-Well, if you're busy, then--
-Yes, I'm busy.
Of course I'm busy!
(VOICEOVER) We've got a
big game to play tomorrow.
SAI: It wouldn't hurt to
give her a game, Hikaru.
-Sai?
-I don't mind playing her.
I'd like nothing better.
-Are you sure?
-Hikaru, that's not
very nice of you.
Akari came all this way.
-I know.
I'm sorry.
I guess I've got time
to give you a game.
If you're still interested.
-Really?
Thanks, Hikaru!
-I'll bring you some cake and
tea a little bit later on, OK?
-Thanks, Mrs. Shindou.
Sounds great.
Hm?
I didn't realize you
were studying tonight.
I'm sorry.
-It's fine.
Don't worry.
So, have you gotten any better
since the last time we played?
-Oh, yeah.
Way better.
I learned a lot more about
the game from Kaneko.
We've all been practicing hard.
-Hm.
-Mitani drops in and out
when he feels like it.
Same as before.
We've got the big tournament
coming up in June.
It's the last one for us now
we're in the ninth grade,
so we're hoping Mitani
will show up for that.
Can I put down nine stones?
Is that OK?
-You won't stand a chance
if you only put down nine.
You gotta put down
more than that.
-Hikaru, nine stones will do.
That's enough for me to
make sure it's a good game.
-All right, then.
Put down nine.
-OK.
-I'm not sure why you
want to play this game.
I mean, this is Akari
we're talking about here.
How's that gonna help you
play Toya's dad tomorrow?
Aren't you just
wasting your time?
-Playing against
someone like Akari
will be a good way for
me to calm my nerves.
There's no pressure in this.
-Well, if you say so.
Onegai shimasu.
-Onegai shimasu.
17, 6.
-Next stone, 16, 13.
Thanks.
-Hm.
SAI: 15, 6.
-This is how Hikaru used to
play when he started out, too.
More than two years have
passed since I came back
to this world.
It was soon after my return
that I learned of Toya Meijin.
From the first time
I saw him, I sensed
that he and I shared
the same path.
The path towards
the Divine Move.
-Next time we play, let's
make it an even game.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Yes.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow will be my chance.
My chance to make
the Divine Move.
[theme music]
HIKARU: You finally get to have
your game against Toya Meijin.
SAI: Yes.
My dream has become a reality.
HIKARU: Your identity's
a total secret.
You think that gives
you the advantage?
SAI: No.
This will be evenly
matched battle.
HIKARU: And it could
be his last game ever.
Next time, Sai Verses Koyo Toya!
SAI: It may be my
last game as well.