[music playing]
NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past, known
as Fujiwara-no-Sai has returned.
Visible only to Hikaru
Shindou, a master of Go,
Sai seeks to play
the divine move.
[theme music]
[thud]
-Let's see.
Including the komi, I
win by 12 and 1/2 points.
That will be 10,000 yen.
Cheer up.
At least you played
a clean, honest game.
[music playing]
-I came to the science
lab, like you asked.
Now give me my 10,000 yen.
-Uh-uh-uh.
First I want you to
promise that you're
going to be in our Go club.
Then I'll give you
back your money.
-If that's all it takes, sure.
I'll join.
I might as well.
I can't play at that Go
salon anymore, can I?
-Hey, you still owe me 20 yen.
-No problem.
-You wanna play a game?
-It will cost you 1,000 yen.
-Hahaha.
No, no betting, OK?
We're both Go club members now.
You mind if I play white?
-It really doesn't matter to me.
-And no cheating.
You got that, Yuuki?
-Well, we'll see.
-I'm serious.
Kimihiro!
-Hm?
-Yuuki has agreed
to join our club.
He promises to stop cheating.
Right?
-What's wrong?
Don't tell me you're
still upset I tricked you
into making two moves in a row.
I can't believe you were
dumb enough to fall for that.
-Hikaru told me everything.
He said you cheat when you're
counting up your territory.
-Hehe.
-That's not all I can do.
I also move stones.
And sometimes I hide
them in my pocket,
and use them when I'm
counting up my score.
See, I play to win.
-Don't worry.
He's just kidding.
Yuuki can be pretty
sarcastic sometimes.
It's just the kind of guy he is.
-Hikaru?
Oh, hi, Yuuki.
-What do you want?
-We baked cookies
today in Home Ec class.
I thought I'd share them.
Here, help yourself.
-Thanks a lot.
-Hey, can I have one of those?
I'm starving.
-No cookies for cheaters.
-You told her?
Is there anyone around
here that you didn't tell?
-I didn't see anything
that wasn't true.
Why don't you relax?
I only told these two.
-So you won't cheat?
-I won't, I won't.
-You want one too?
-Yeah, thanks.
Now that Yuuki's here,
you guys can finally
enter the tournament.
-Tournament?
You can count me out.
-Excuse me?
What are you talking about?
That's the reason we wanted
you to join in the first place.
-Like I care.
-You're a member
of this club now.
That means you have to compete.
-No way.
-What's your problem, anyway?
Hey, Kimihiro, he might
actually listen to you.
-Forget it.
We shouldn't force
him to do something
that he doesn't want to do.
-Why not?
We're running out of time.
At this rate I doubt
we'll find someone else.
The tournament is only a
couple of days away, you know.
What happened to all your
big talk about beating Kaio?
-Even if Yuuki agrees
to play, there's
no guarantee that we'll win.
-Is Kaio's team really
as good as they say.
-Yeah.
They're a middle
school club, right?
How good can they be?
-I can't believe I'm
actually hearing this!
You're nothing compared to them.
You don't stand a chance.
just
-Hold on a second, Kimihior.
You won against them in the
last tournament, remember?
-That was luck.
My opponent made
a stupid mistake.
-Hm.
What's your point?
Are you trying to
say that I wouldn't
stand a chance against
a team like that?
All right.
I'll play for your little club.
-So that means you'll compete
in the tournament with us?
-I'm not afraid of
Kaio's big, bad Go club!
-You have no idea how
good they really are.
You make me laugh.
-Like I said, I'll win.
It's that simple.
-Gah.
-Come on.
Let's start this game.
-Oh, yeah, right.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
I really hope
he's not planning to
cheat against Kaio.
He can't actually believe
he'd get away with it.
KIMIHIRO (VOICEOVER):
If he gets caught,
what's going to happen to
Haze Middle School's Go club?
[nature sounds]
-Ah, time for me to resign.
Thanks for the game.
-We'll have to play again soon.
Can we skip our
analysis of the game?
-Hm?
-Unfortunately I have
some unfinished business
I need to take care of.
The tournament is going
to begin in a few days.
Mr. Yun will probably announce
the three players sometime
today.
Touya and I need to determine
our difference in ability.
It would be best to figure
that out as soon as possible.
If he does wind up as
team captain this year,
it'll be because he beat me.
I don't want to
hear any whining.
-Touya?
-Hello?
-Do you want to play a game?
[muted conversations]
-We'll have one with no
handicaps, all right?
-Well, all right.
-Senpai, how does
our Go club pick
which three members
get to compete?
Does the strongest
player automatically
become the team captain?
-Well, not every team
is chosen that way.
But usually that's
how it's done.
-Uh, how about you
concentrate on your own games?
-Sure.
[music playing]
TOUYA (VOICEOVER): It
won't be long, Hikaru.
I'm catching up to you.
I hope you're ready!
-Touya, Haze Middle School's
application just arrived.
Here, take a look.
-Hikaru's in third position?
-My guess is that
it's a strategic move.
Sometimes schools don't
place their members
in order strength.
I assume that their new
teammate, Yuuki, is probably
the weakest of the three.
If they're
deliberately forfeiting
the game between the
two team captains,
they must think they'll win
the two remaining matches.
Their club president,
to Tsutsui,
will be their co-captain.
And Shindou will be their
number three, like you said.
It's an interesting
move, I have to admit.
I wouldn't have predicted it.
-Sensei, I want to play
as our number three.
-Hm.
-Mr. Yun.
-I'll think about it.
[music playing]
-I do agree, you
are our only player
who could beat Hikaru Shindou.
-Thank you, sensei.
-I withdraw.
-Thank you for the game.
[gasping]
-The better player
has won this time.
-Don't underestimate yourself.
You were much stronger
than I expected.
-You completely overpowered me.
-I paid too much attention
to the center of the board.
You played a much
more balanced game.
-You're cutting points
hurt you, so you
couldn't secure your groups.
-I connected here
out of desperation.
Oh that was a bad move.
After that, I was
on the defensive.
And you wouldn't let up.
I didn't have a chance
to make any strong plays.
I could never turn professional.
I understand that now.
-Everyone, may I have
your attention, please.
We've received a lot of
applications for the upcoming
tournament.
Several schools will
be participating.
I'm sure you're
all eager to know
who will be playing
on our team this year.
I'll read the boy's
division first.
The captain will be
Touya, seventh grade.
The co-captain will be
Kishimoto, ninth grade.
And in the number three
position, Kuno, ninth grade.
And now for the girl's division.
-That's not fair!
I thought we agreed that I
would play in the number three
position!
[murmuring]
Sensei.
[music playing]
[nature sounds]
[beeping]
-How are you this
morning, Kuwabara sensei?
-Hello!
We haven't bumped into each
other for quite some time.
Now that you're here, I've been
meaning to tell you something.
I'm going to challenge you for
the Gosei title next month.
I've been looking
forward to facing you.
It'll be a stimulating game.
-I've already heard.
I recently had the pleasure of
watching you overpower Ogata.
That was quite an impressive
play, for a man your age.
-You're not exactly a
spring chicken yourself.
How many titles do you hold?
Four?
Five?
It's getting hard to
keep track these days.
-After I'm done taking yours
away, I'll have five titles.
-Haha.
Ah, these youngsters leave a
lot to be desired, don't they?
Winning a title is
admirable, but they're not
good enough to hold onto it.
The younger players
are inconsistent.
Nobody really stands out.
The new non-rank title
holders are nothing special.
Even the Insei are
getting weaker these days.
Ah, how's your son?
I hear he's not an Insei.
-That's right.
We practice together a lot.
He likes to play the
pros who come to visit.
Akira takes the
game very seriously.
-But he hasn't taken
the pro exam yet?
-No.
He's keeping busy.
He decided to join his
middle school's Go club.
[water running]
-When I heard that you
wanted to play Go at Kaio,
I allowed you to.
The principal felt your
presence would help encourage
the other students,
so I didn't object.
But why do you insist on
entering this tournament?
I'd like to know what's
going through your head.
You're a talented player.
Listen.
You're too skilled to be playing
children in middle school.
I don't think someone
with your ability should
be challenging weaker opponents.
You really ought to
know better, Akira.
-Right now I'm not
going to spend my time
worrying about what
everyone else thinks of me.
If Hikaru Shindou plays in that
tournament, then I will, too.
I have no choice
but to go after him.
I don't mean to
upset you, father.
But my goal is to
reach your level.
I've worked hard to
develop my abilities
and to grow confident and
be proud of my skills.
I thought that if
I kept studying,
if I kept moving forward,
I would eventually
play the divine move.
But I was wrong.
None of my training
had prepared me
for an opponent like Shindou.
I was completely
helpless against him.
There was no way
that I could win.
It's strange, he's different.
Brilliant!
I've never seen
anything like it.
It's tormenting me!
He isn't like you, father.
Or even Mr. Ogata.
I can't figure
out how he learned
to play the game like that.
It's all I ever think about.
I've got to keep chasing him,
until he agrees to face me.
[music playing]
KOUYOU TOUYA (VOICEOVER):
There's fear in his voice.
But he still wants to
challenge his opponent.
I've never seen Akira
act this way before.
This is the kind of courage
that helps a person grow.
He is stubbornly pushing
forward in spite of himself.
This is indeed how he
will advance closer
to the divine move.
-Just listen!
I want to know why
you didn't select
me to play in the
number three position.
You were the one that said
I was the only person who
would have a chance
against Shindou, remember?
Please, sir.
I only joined this club
so I could battle him.
-Enough.
This is just a
middle school club.
I've made my decision.
Our strongest player
should be team captain.
That issue is not
open for debate.
And that's final.
-But sensei!
-I'm not finished yet.
The Go club here at Kaio
sets a standard of excellence
which other schools
respect and follow.
I did say you were
the only player who
have a shot at defeating Hikaru.
But this is a place
of learning, Akira.
And the school must come first.
I'm the teacher,
and I have to stick
to what's best for the club.
You will play in first position.
-I thought--
[crying]
--just this once.
Just this one time.
I promise I'll quit the
club after the tournament is
finished.
I might never get another
chance to face him.
This could be the only
opportunity I have!
Sensei, I'm begging you!
Say something!
-Very well then.
[muted conversations]
-Hey there!
You made it!
-Uh-huh.
-I'm glad you came.
I wasn't really sure if
you were going to show up.
I thought you might be
afraid of Kaio's team.
-Who's afraid?
Kimihiro, why are you running
with those black stones?
If you keep that up, all
these stones on the other side
will be captured.
-Huh?
Who asked you?
-Are you OK?
Yuuki, I want to
ask you something.
If you're such a
strong player, then how
come you had to win by cheating?
-Oh, there you are!
-You didn't have to come here.
You're just going to get bored
and want to leave, you know.
-I've been looking
forward to this!
Kimihiro's been teaching me.
You want to prove it to you?
I know how to capture stones
and how to count territory.
-Oh.
-You jerk!
And to think I spent all morning
making lunches for you guys.
-Huh?
Great!
Thanks Akari!
-Hey, I brought one
for you, too, Yuuki!
-Huh?
-Follow me, Akari.
I'll show you where
you can put that stuff.
Come on, let's go.
-Lead the way!
-Want to play?
What do you say?
-I'll pass.
-Your friends don't
seem very happy.
Are you all right?
-Hey, isn't that Shindou
from Haze Middle School?
-Huh?
-Is that him?
-Looks like it.
-He defeated a very
strong Kaio player
at last year's tournament.
-No way.
-He was still a sixth
grader, but pretended to be
in middle school so he could
participate in the competition.
Everyone was impressed by
his incredible victory.
It was a truly magnificent game.
-Are they still staring?
Don't let their
comments affect you.
Focus on your game, try your
best, and you'll be fine.
-Right.
I'll do my best.
Then I'll beat the
pants off my opponent.
I can hardly wait
for the first round,
it's going to be awesome!
-I don't know if it'll
be all that easy, Hikaru.
Your opponent will be trying
his hardest to win, too.
-I know that.
The only reason I came here
today was to beat Kaio.
I can't afford to get
eliminated in the first round.
I'll give everything I've
got against Kaio's number
three player in
the second round.
Who knows?
We might just win
the whole tournament!
-I'm sure that Kaio's
number three player is just
as determined as you are.
Be ready.
-Ah.
The tournament should
start any minute now.
I can't wait to find out
who I'll be playing against.
-That would be me.
-Huh?
-I'm Kaio's number
three player, Shindou.
Surprised?
-Akira?
You're Kaio's number three?
-Do you remember when you
refused to play against me?
-Huh?
-I do.
You said you wanted to
play in tournaments.
I finally got you cornered.
-You're here to play me?
You're after Sai!
[music playing]
[theme music]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): The first
round is about to begin,
and the Kaio team's acting
like a bunch of jerks.
They're even making
Kimihiro mad!
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI
(VOICEOVER): You need
to ignore them and
concentrate on your own game.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Do you think I'll
get to play against
Akira in the next round?
Next time, a personal resolve.
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI
(VOICEOVER): You may not
advance that far Hikaru,
you're losing the first game.
[music playing]