[theme music]
-In the month between
the prelims and exam,
and all the way
through the finals,
your game's been
getting stronger,
but mine didn't improve one bit.
That's the difference
between you and me.
-Mr. Tsubaki, I can't
hear a word you're saying!
-Hey.
Your name's Shindou, right?
-What?
-I'm passing my dream
of being a pro onto you.
-Waya.
Your next game's against
Shindou, isn't it?
-Yeah.
I've only got two losses.
If I manage to beat him,
then I'm through as well.
Then you an me can take it
easy and watch everyone else
fighting it out
for the third spot.
-What makes you think
I'm gonna take it easy?
I don't play Shindou
until my very last match.
It's a really
important game for me.
In fact, as far
as I'm concerned,
it's probably the most important
game of the whole pro exam.
-Whoa.
I had no idea you considered
Shindou such a big rival.
You kept that quiet.
I wanna find out where he
gets his strength from.
That mysterious strength!
SAI (VOICEOVER): There's
no sign of the hesitation
or fear that he once showed.
His counting and end game
used to be his weak spot,
but now his game
is very precise.
Could the fact that his
game is now fully ed
have anything to do with me?
-What's the matter, Sai?
Your move here.
It looks like the kind
of move I would make.
-Really, you think so? I tried
to imagine where you'd play,
and that's what I came up with.
When I can't think of a move,
I put myself in your shoes.
Sometimes it works
out for the best.
-Put yourself in my shoes?
-Yep.
It isn't that hard, you know.
We're always playing together.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Always together?
But for how long will that be?
I once thought I
would live forever,
and I would be with Hikaru
for the rest of his life.
And when his time
finally came to an end,
I would return to
the Go board until I
was released into
the world again.
But, now that I think about
it, how can I be sure?
Nothing is certain.
Nothing.
-When I play Waya,
it's gonna be a tougher
match than the one against Ochi.
Ochi's already passed
the exam, so he
won't be as desperate
to win as Waya.
I've got one more loss than him,
so there's even more at stake
here for me.
Darn it.
I'm starting to feel kind
of nervous about this game.
-If it's any
consolation, I'm sure
Waya's feeling exactly the same.
-Yeah, I know.
Just two matches left.
-That's right.
At the moment, my worries
really aren't that important.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
Waya's already gone
down to the match room.
-What's his problem?
He just wants to watch
our game so he can gloat.
He thinks he's better than us
because she's passed the exam.
-Excuse me, young man.
-Hm?
-You don't happen to know where
I can order my lunch, do you?
-Sure.
Over here.
Uh, here you go.
-Thanks a lot, son.
Oh, by the way, Shinoda-sensei,
the Insei instructor,
can't be here today.
He asked me to fill in
for him while he's gone.
And your name is?
-Shindou.
It's Hikaru Shindou.
-Well, Hikaru Shindou, how
have you been doing in the exam
so far?
-I've got three losses.
If I can win my last two
matches, then I'm through.
-Really?
Is that so?
In that case, good luck.
-Thank you.
I better get going.
-Hm.
Young man.
Your face seems familiar.
Have I met you somewhere before?
-What?
I don't know.
-Yes, we've definitely met
before, but for the life of me,
I can't place where.
Hm.
-Any ideas, Sai?
-None at all.
-Oh, well, never mind.
I'm sorry to have kept you.
Bye.
Hey!
I remember.
You're that kid from the
youth Go championships
who couldn't keep his mouth
shut and ruined the match!
-Now I recognize him!
He's the one who pulled
you into his office
and threw you out
of the tournament!
-What?
Oh, too bad.
Should've played it one higher.
-Unacceptable.
There's no excuse for a slip
of the tongue like that,
young man.
Oh no.
That's him?
I already apologized
for that, didn't I?
Besides, remember?
It was you who said what
the move should be, not me.
-Yes, but you're the one
who said it out loud.
-I remember thinking that you
had a special talent for Go.
You just said you were
close to passing the exam?
Well, now I can see you
were well on the way
to becoming a pro even then.
-It doesn't look like he's
gonna get mad at me, does it?
-Not really.
-Interesting.
This explains how you managed
to see that one, two move so
quickly.
-You didn't see that move!
I saw it.
I remember that match clearly.
You could never have seen it.
You didn't!
I-- Ugh.
All right, maybe now Hikaru.
-Maybe now what?
-Maybe now you'd see it.
-Yes!
I know I should have
kept quiet, but I just
couldn't help myself.
-I recall Mr. Ogata
and Toya-sensei
showing some interest in you.
I'm gonna have to tell
them that I bumped into.
-Oh, they already know I'm
here and I'm taking the exam.
-What?
They're following your progress?
I have to say I'm impressed.
Good luck in your
last two games.
I'm looking forward to them.
Bye.
-Thanks.
The way he just acted
right now reminds
me of that teacher from Kaio
after the match with Su-yeong.
-And now I'm
convinced, the person
who played that magical match,
and the person I see here,
are one in the same.
I won't forget your name.
It'll stay in my memory forever.
Hikaru Shindou.
-He saw how strong
a player I was.
And this guy?
I know he sees it, too.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Why does
this make me feel so uneasy?
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and
gentlemen, it's time to begin.
Would everyone please make
their way to the match room now?
-Hello there, Shindou.
You ready for the big game?
-Yeah!
SAI (VOICEOVER): I have to
put aside my own worries.
Right now it's more important
to watch over Hikaru.
-All right.
When you're ready, please begin.
-Onegai shimasu.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Sensei.
-Waya, you've been studying
with me for five years now.
It's your fourth
time doing the test?
That's a lot.
If at first you don't succeed--
-Kazuo!
I don't want to hear you
talking like that to our guest.
Listen up, Waya!
You've been playing
very well this year,
but if you can't pass this time,
you're out of my study group!
Understand?
-Dad, you shouldn't talk
with your mouth full.
-Calm down, dear.
-He's got enough pressure as it
is without you threatening him.
-You've only lost
two games so far?
-Thanks very much for the meal.
-I think you're gonna
make it through.
-Shigeko, you're as
bad as your father.
Stop making him feel
so uncomfortable.
-Huh?
-I'll help.
-Great.
Thank you.
-You did tell your parents you
were eating here, didn't you?
-Yes, sir.
-Get a move on with
that washing up.
You and I have some
more studying to do.
-OK.
-Kazuo, you'll have
time to drive him home
once we're finished?
-Sure, Dad.
[giggling]
-Promise you'll buy
me a little something
when you become a pro?
-Shouldn't you be the one buying
him something if he passes?
-Sayaki bought me a present to
celebrate when he became a pro.
-All right, enough!
I want you two out of here.
You'd think they'd show
some interest in the game,
considering who their father is.
All that time I wasted
teaching you how to play.
-Maybe we weren't
meant to be good at it.
-Or maybe it's 'cause you
were a bad teacher, Dad.
-So, are you going
to pass this year,
or is this going to
be our last lesson?
-Huh?
(VOICEOVER) Sensei-- I--
SAI ( VOICEOVER): Waya's
white stones are in a secure
position.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): This is
going to decide the match.
If I can turn this
shape into my territory,
he's going to lose for sure.
He'll have no choice
but to attack.
Your turn.
Huh?
He's made his move.
If his stone stays
there, he'll win.
But if I eliminate
it, then I win,
and I finally pass the pro exam.
Can I do it?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Can I stay alive?
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Is
there any way black can
fight back from here?
Any way he can survive?
Sensei?
-Waya.
-Yes, sir?
-You've always been a
very nice young man,
ever obedient and
willing to learn.
Which is all very good.
But you can't stay
coddled forever!
Do you hear me?
WAYA (VOICEOVER): If black plays
there, then I'll extend here.
No, wait.
If I back down
without a fight, it
will only make things
harder later on.
He won't go there, anyway.
-I've taught my fair
share of students.
Most of them could
never make it as a pro.
But you?
You're better than most.
I think you've
got what it takes.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Even if
black attaches to my two point
extension, I can let it go.
Yeah, I can attack him
over there, instead.
-Listen to me.
You will pass.
Let me say it again.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): Yes.
-You gotta be confident, Waya.
If you do that, you'll
be joining the pros.
WAYA (VOICEOVER): There's
no way black can win.
I've done it!
SAI (VOICEOVER): Oh really?
There is one way
that black can win.
It's hard to see and difficult
to pull off, but it's there.
The question is,
will Hikaru find it?
-Hm.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Come on.
Why can't I see it?
I know there's a
way for me to win.
WAYA: Sensei.
Finally, I've made it!
I'm gonna be a pro!
[theme music]
HIKARU: Ochi has been
teaming up with Akira?
SAI: Ochi now believes
he's strong enough
to defeat you in the last match.
HIKARU: First I gotta
finish my game against Waya.
He thinks he's already won.
SAI: The game is very
close because he's
playing the best he can.
HIKARU: Well, so
is everyone else.
Isumi's gonna have to win if
he wants to pass the exam.
Next time, Come
Back From the Brink.
SAI: Who's going to make it?