[theme music]
-[gasps]
That move I just
played, it was exactly
the same move he'd have played.
He was here.
I've been looking
for him everywhere.
And he was here all the time.
The only way for
me to see him again
was by actually having a game.
I promise from now on, I'm
going to play all the time--
dozens, hundreds, even
thousands of games against you,
Isumi, and Waya and
Ochi and everyone.
I'm leaving now.
-You're really going to a game?
-Yeah.
-Is it just the one game today?
-No, I told you yesterday.
I'm going to play every day.
Can you let to school know I'm
not going to be there today?
-[sighs]
Hm.
-[panting]
-Whoa.
You'll be promoted to
3-dan if you win today?
-Yeah.
-Aren't you supposed to
be playing that kid who's
been skipping his
games for months now?
-Yeah, that's right.
I win by default, and then
they can move up the rankings.
-Well, jeez, lucky for you.
-To be honest, I would
have rather earned
the promotion by actually
winning the game. [chuckles]
[elevator bell dings]
[gasps]
-Good morning, everyone.
-Huh?
-So, Shindo, you made it.
Great!
He just had to pick
today to be the one
day that he's going to show up.
-What's up?
Did Shindo actually
make an appearance?
-Yeah.
Hey, Tsujioka.
-He's going to be my opponent
in the next game I've
got scheduled.
I'm glad he's back.
I've been wanting to play
him for a long time now.
-You want to play against him?
-Hmm.
-Yeah.
Ever since I heard this
rumor that Toya considers
him to be his rival,
I've wanted to see
what all the fuss was about.
-Toya and Shindo are rivals?
-I never heard that before!
Huh?
Are you really sure about that?
I mean, Toya's already made it
through to the Honinbo League.
-Good morning, excuse me.
-Huh?
-Toya!
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Shindo.
-Grr.
[grunts]
[clock ticks]
[buzzing]
-Onnegai shimasu.
ALL: Onnegai shimasu.
MAN (VOICEOVER): I faced him
before in the Young Lions
Tournament last year.
He played a good game, even
gave me a bit of a scare.
But his end game
wasn't strong enough,
and I beat him by
6 and 1/2 points.
Afterwards, Toya kept
asking me about Shindo,
wanting to know
how he had played.
At that time, it
really ticked me off
that he didn't want to
know about me and my game.
But if Shindo really
was his rival,
that would explain
why was so interested.
I need to play a
solid game here,
keep control of my territory.
All I need to do is hold
steady until the end game,
and I'm going to win for sure.
He's going to find out just
how weak his end game is.
[school bell rings]
TEACHER: Good
afternoon, everyone.
Bow.
-Mr. Suzuki!
-Hm?
What is it, Kaneko?
AKARI: What?
Are you sure, Kaneko?
Hikaru's not coming
to school today
because he's got
a match to play?
-Yep.
In the next two or
three days, he's
off to do some sort of study
session thing for the Go
Association.
I don't think he's going to be
spending much time in school
if he's got all this Go to play.
-Good!
Hikaru's finally cheered up!
-That's great!
-I can't wait to see
how he's going to do.
This is awesome news.
-Good for him.
-Mr. Suzuki said he wasn't
worried about Shindo
missing a bit of school to
play Go since we've only
got a few classes left
before the summer break.
This way, he gets to be
happy and do what he wants.
-Hah, first he says he's
going to quit being a pro.
Next thing you know,
he's skipping classes
so he can play.
That guy's so selfish.
-Did you ever hear
of the pot calling
the kettle black, Mitani?
[girls giggle]
-What's that?
-You only show up for practice
whenever you feel like it.
And then you tell us you
want to enter the tournament
and expect us to
put you on the team?
-Hah, I bet the
only reason Shindo
went back to being a pro
was because he's too lazy
and got bored studying
for his entrance exams.
-Oh, and I guess you study
in the library all the time,
and you're in the honor roll.
Is that it?
-Shut it!
-[laughs]
-You know, if it
wasn't for Mitani,
we wouldn't have
been able to enter
a boys' team in the tournament.
-And you guys did so well!
You made it to the final!
I know Kaio ended up beating
you three to nothing, but still!
-And you girls really
had a great first round,
winning three in a row.
-Yup, I know!
I couldn't believe it.
It was so exciting!
[girls giggle]
-It's not fair.
You guys are all
in the third year,
so you're going to be
leaving the Go Club soon.
[groans]
What am I going to do?
I can't play on my own.
-But, Koike, when this Go
Club was first started up
by Tsutsui, there was just
one person who belonged to it.
-He was the only one?
AKARI (VOICEOVER): Yeah.
Tsutsui started the
club all by himself.
Then Hikaru joined, and
I tagged along with him.
After that, Hikaru managed
to drag Mitani into it.
So it didn't take long for
the club to get bigger.
Later on, we invited Kaneko
to join as a temporary member.
And then Natsume and
Kumiko came, too!
Anyway, that's how we all got
together at the Haze Go Club.
-Wow.
-Sure, it's fun to have a
lot of people in the club,
but you've got to
start somewhere.
So why not start with you?
-From now on, this
Go Club is going
to have to be run by you, Koike.
-You mean, it's my club?
-You bet it is.
All yours.
-[laughs]
-Go Club is mine now.
-Maybe you'll even
beat Kaio one day.
-That's impossible.
-[laughs]
AKARI (VOICEOVER): The
Haze Go Club is changing,
and so are we.
Even Hikaru, who decided
to quit playing as a pro,
has started up again.
Right now, I bet he's
sitting at a Go board
with one of those
intense looks he
gets when he's in
the middle of a game.
-Oh, not again.
Why am I such a terrible player?
-No, you're not.
I just had a few lucky moves.
-No, let's face
it, I'm the worst.
WAYA: I thought it
was a good game.
-Oh, thank you.
That game was closer
than you think.
You focused on your
strengths, and you almost
pulled off a win.
You played a strong game.
-You think so?
-Aah.
Oh, by the way, Isumi?
-Hm?
You went over to Shindo's
place, didn't you?
-Uh-huh.
-Oh, you never told us.
So how's he doing?
Is he all right?
-Yeah.
Well, I don't know
what happened.
But whatever it was
he was going through,
he seems to have
gotten over it now.
We even played Go.
-That's good.
What a jerk!
Making us worry
about him like that.
Hm?
What the--
[group laughing]
MAN (VOICEOVER): Surrounding
his territory might not
be enough here.
It's time to fight back!
-Hm.
SAKAMAKI (VOICEOVER): So Hikaru
Shindo decided to show up.
-[sighs]
These kids, I don't
understand them nowadays.
AMANO: Ah, Mr. Sakamaki.
-Hm?
-That was a pretty
big sigh, just now.
What's going on?
Is something wrong?
-Oh, it's nothing.
Mr. Amano!
-Sorry.
-Huh? [sighs]
Hm, mm, mm.
-Huh?
Good.
[phone rings]
-Hi, Ogata here.
Ah, Mr. Amano.
-I hope you're well.
And I hope I'm not
disturbing you.
Well, I've got some news
about Hikaru Shindo.
You seem to take an
interest in him before,
so I wanted to let you know.
-Yes?
Yes.
Oh.
You mean he started
playing again?
I see.
Well, I appreciate you taking
the time to give me a call.
Bye.
Hm, Shindo's back in the game.
-Yeah?
Really?
I-- I'll get right on it.
-Hm.
-I was looking for
the editor-in-chief,
is he not here?
-Ah, Kuwabara Sensei!
-Maybe you could
give him this for me?
It's the manuscript
he's been waiting for.
-Thank you for bringing
it all this way.
-I was in the area on
some other business.
So it wasn't any
trouble to drop it off.
-That's very nice of you.
Hm.
-Hm, something on
your mind, Mr. Amano?
-Well, I was just
thinking about something
you mentioned to
me the other day.
Do you remember we had a
conversation about Hikaru
Shindo, the new 1-dan player
who had been missing his games?
You said you were sure he'd
come back to play again, right?
-That's right.
I gather you were about
to tell me I was correct.
-You were.
But what I can't figure
out is why you're also
concerned about this
one particular boy.
Because it's not
only you, there's
Ogata Sensei, Kurata Sensei,
and even Toya Sensei.
-[laughs]
What makes him so special?
I believe that's something we've
all been trying to find out,
no?
AMANO: What?
-There's no hurry, Mr. Amano.
We'll learn more soon enough.
Mark my words.
I've got a sixth sense
about these sort of things.
[guffaws]
-What does he mean
"sixth sense"?
[music playing]
-Hm.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): All right!
I can win this!
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Hm.
There's no way I can win.
He's better than anyone
else in this room.
-Hm.
-Uh, um, I resign.
Thank you very
much for the game.
-Thank you very
-Hm.
-I resign.
TSUJIOKA (VOICEOVER): Hm?
Toya's finished, too?
What?
He's leaving?
Doesn't he want to watch
Shindo's comeback game?
If he considered
Shindo to be his rival,
he would have wanted to
check out how he's playing.
Of course, maybe this
whole rival thing
was nothing but a rumor.
Huh!
Unless-- no, it couldn't be.
-Hm.
TSUJIOKA (VOICEOVER):
Maybe he thinks
a game against such a low-ranked
opponent isn't even worth
worrying about.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER):
The only way I
can measure Shindo's
true strength is
by playing him myself.
I knew at the moment he
came running up to me
the other night, there was
something different about him.
TSUJIOKA (VOICEOVER): Now
that I think about it,
the Meijin qualifying round
pairings were posted yesterday.
And Toya must already know who
his first-round opponent is.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): All I
have to do now is wait.
The match is set.
We're going to face
each other once again.
[theme music]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): The
pro exam is starting,
and everyone is focused
on making it through.
And I better focus on getting
some wins, too, or else,
I won't be going
up in the rankings
like Toya has been doing.
Some of the older players
are having a tough time
hanging on to their titles.
But the big question
is, what's going
to happen when I finally
get to play Toya?
Next time, "The Race Is On"!