[theme music]
-I resign.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Huh?
But--
SAI (VOICEOVER): It
was a great match.
Hikaru has proven he's
the better player.
-Sai.
That was the name of the
player on the internet.
He was awesome.
-Mm-hm.
Yeah, I remember.
-Well, today you did it.
You played as well as sai.
-Shindou's no threat to me.
-Underestimate him
and you'll lose!
-And what if I win?
What if I actually beat Shindou?
Maybe then you'll start to
treat me like a serious rival.
HIKARU: Ochi.
-Hey Shindou.
You really to lose today?
I've been playing Akira
Toya almost every night,
just so I can beat you today.
-Toya?
You've been playing him?
-That's right.
Almost every day.
-How come?
-Because he wanted to.
He spent more time helping
me than he planned to.
-I don't get it.
Why would he help you
practice for the pro exam?
-Let go of me!
I wanted some
coaching from a pro.
You got a problem with that?
-But a minute ago, you told
me you played against Toya
just so you could beat me.
-Yeah, and your point is?
-Why did it have to be Toya?
You're not telling
me everything.
-I don't know what
you're talking about.
But I've been studying with
Toya to improve my game.
-Ochi!
-Hm?
-Did Toya-- Did he-- When he
played, did he say anything?
What I mean is, did he
say anything about me?
-And right here is
where I resigned.
-You what?
I don't believe it.
And this was two years ago?
-I was defeated.
Never underestimate Shindou!
-Well?
-Of course he didn't
talk about you.
Why would he?
Don't flatter yourself!
Sure we talked
about the pro exam,
but in all the weeks
we played together,
he never mentioned you once.
I doubt he even knows you exist.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Hikaru.
OCHIL Have you got any idea
how good a player he is?
-Huh?
-He hasn't lost once since
he turned professional.
Undefeated since April.
He's better than
anyone else around.
I mean, think about it.
Why would he even give
you the time of day?
-I know he's good.
It's not like I don't
take him seriously.
-Of course, Toya thinks my
skills are very advanced.
Our match today is gonna be the
most important one of the exam,
and even Toya's
interested in it.
-What did he say about it?
-Well, you he me, If I beat
you, then I'll become his rival.
-Oh really?
-Yeah.
-If you beat me?
What do you think
he meant by that?
-Uh, what he meant was, i-- if
I won all my remaining matches,
then he'd allow me
to be his rival.
It's got nothing to do with you.
That's what he meant.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I don't know
if I can believe him or not.
What if Toya's using
him to get to me.
-The point is, if
I beat you today,
Toya's gonna
recognize my strength
and see me as his rival!
-In that case, if I beat you,
Toya's gonna see my strength,
and I'll be his rival!
You'll see.
Both of you!
-Hmph!
-Ochi!
-Huh?
Ochi?
What do you think's up with him?
-I thought I heard
Shindou's voice.
Sounded like they were
arguing about something.
-It's all right.
Just a little pre-match battle.
-Are you sure he's
going to be OK?
-He's just psyching himself up.
Weird because
there's no pressure.
He's already passed.
But that's Ochi for you.
-You know what?
I have a feeling
Ochi's gonna win today.
Shindou will never pull it off.
Think him and Waya will
end up in a playoff?
-Hm?
WAYA: Talking about me
behind my back, are we?
-Oh, hi Waya.
-Hey there.
-So, one match to go.
How you feeling?
-I'm feeling fine.
Why would I?
-Your final opponent
is your nemesis, Fuku.
If you lose, you're
gonna have to face
Isumi in a tough playoff.
-Aw, come on!
You think I don't
already know that?
-You realize if Isumi
happens to lose today,
you and Shindou
would automatically
pass the test without
needing a playoff?
Then again, when you look at who
he's playing, that's a big if.
-Yeah.
Isumi's gonna win
this game no problem.
He'll be waiting to see
how the rest of us do.
-OK.
That's enough talk
about everyone else.
I gotta focus on
my own game now.
My whole future's at stake here.
-And what future is that?
-What?
-Well, you said that your
whole future's at stake.
But what do you think's gonna
happen to us in the future?
What will happen to all of us?
-The time has finally come.
-Yeah!
And I'm gonna win.
Hm?
Hm.
I can Sam's Toya's behind Ochi.
Toya is using him to
see how well I do.
I just know it.
I'm almost there.
You hear that, Toya?
I've almost made it
up to your level.
OCHI (VOICEOVER):
Shindou has no idea
how strong a player Toya is.
If he did, there's
no way he'd dare
suggest that they
could be rivals.
The more I played
against Toya, the more
I could feel his
power, his strength!
We played each other every
day with one goal in mind.
To beat Shindou in
this match today!
I won't lose those game.
Not with Toya behind me.
Who have you got
behind you, Shindou?
-Hm.
ANNOUNCER (VOICEOVER): The
final day of the pro exam.
Three months and 27
matches have gone by.
You've all put up a good fight.
One of you has already made
it through to being a pro.
For others, this game
will be a deciding factor.
And for some of you, a future as
a pro is looking less certain.
But you must keep going.
To all of you, I
want to say continue
playing with passion and
pride until the very end.
And then you'll know
these last three
months have been worthwhile.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is time.
When you're ready, please begin.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai first
appeared to me two years ago.
In the same way that
you've been pursuing Sai,
I've been pursuing you.
-Stop messing around!
-What?
What's wrong?
(VOICEOVER) I'll never forget
that look on your face.
-Hey, wait up!
Akira!
If you keep on chasing
your phantom image of me,
one day I'm going
to catch up to you.
-Is that so?
Why wait until then?
Why don't we play
a game right now?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Toya!
Toya, if I win this
match today, then I'll
finally be a pro--
just like you!
Are you ready for me?
SAI (VOICEOVER):
The strategy Ochi's
using is quite interesting.
Although the match is
still in its early stages,
it's obvious that he is
a very skillful player.
But I can see a glimpse of
Toya's influence in his moves.
That influence is an
obstacle that certainly
won't make things any
easier for Hikaru.
I see.
He's confident he can hold
onto the top side of the board.
If he neglects to
strengthen that area,
there'll be an opportunity
to infiltrate his position.
A peep is the only move to make.
Their positions are
about equal right now.
Ochi may be the stronger
player, but Hikaru
seems to be rising
to the occasion.
Hikaru.
What are you doing?
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Ha.
I think you've
underestimated me, Shindou.
-Huh?
-Looks like it's about to
start pouring out there, hm?
-Yeah.
And it was so
sunny this morning.
Now, let's see.
This one's yours,
Sensei, and here's mine.
Grab these for me, would you?
-Yes.
Of course.
-Thanks.
It'd be nice of the rain held
off 'til everyone made it home.
-Isn't always the way?
The one day I
forget my umbrella,
we get a torrential storm.
-Time for lunch.
Please stop your clocks.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): If I
can keep playing like this,
I'm going to win.
-Hikaru, make sure you
eat a proper lunch.
-Yeah.
I know.
Huh?
-Huh?
OCHI (VOICEOVER): He's
taking a long time to think.
It's not like him at all.
I've got him on the run.
All that training Toya
gave me wasn't for nothing.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Why
did I make that move there?
Now Ochi's got
control of the game.
How am I going to
come back from this?
Come on.
It can't end this way!
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Feeling
the pressure, Shindou?
You thought that move would
work as a counterattack,
but you've just left
yourself wide open.
No!
That's not right.
This isn't a simple
counterattack.
There's some hidden
strategy behind it.
You can't fool me that easily.
-Huh?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER)
He played a peep?
Oh, that was the last
thing I was expecting.
SAI (VOICEOVER): An
interesting move.
This is obviously the result
of this training with Toya.
Now Hikaru has to go
back to the drawing board
and rethink his entire strategy.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Black
was played by a Korean Insei
by the name of Su-yeong
Hung, and Hikaru Shindou
played white.
OCHI (VOICEOVER): Hold on.
You said Shindou
was playing white?
I thought he made a mistake
earlier on in the game,
but he was really anticipating
the battle over here.
If this match shows
the kind of level
Shindou's playing at right
now, then three weeks
won't be enough!
it won't be enough time!
-Never underestimate Shindou!
OCHI (VOICEOVER): I
would never do that.
If he plans 100 moves
ahead, I'll plan 101.
If he plans 1,000,
I'll plan 1,001.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): He
ruined my whole strategy!
If I'm not careful, I'll be
in an even worse position
than before.
This could be the end for me.
I've gotta make a good move.
I've gotta stop him from
gaining anymore ground!
OK.
Calm down.
Calm down!
I still have a chance to turn
this game around and gain
control.
I can't let it slip
out of my hands.
I'm gonna make this work.
No more weakness.
No more mistakes.
-Still hanging in
there, Shindou?
So you've decided
not to give up.
But I took too long
before making my move.
Did I give him time to
get his confidence back?
No.
Well, if that's the case, here's
an attack that will crush you!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Take that!
[theme music]
HIKARU: Only two matches
are still going on.
Me against Ochi and
Waya against Fuku.
SAI: And if you
don't win, you'll
be facing Asumi in a playoff.
HIKARU: But if I
win, I'll finally
make it to the level of pro.
SAI: To defeat
Ochi, you will need
to find a way to outsmart Akira.
HIKARU: Next time, The
Final Day of the Pro Exam.
SAI: Who is it going to be?