[theme music]
DOCTOR: Now, I'll
let you play online
if you can assure
me it's just for fun
and there's no stress involved.
-It helps pass the time.
Although, there are still some
games I can't afford to lose.
-From the first
time I saw him, I
sensed that he and I
shared the same path.
The path towards
the Divine Move.
Tomorrow will be my chance.
My chance to make
the Divine Move!
WOMAN: How long do
you think you're
going to be at the
study group, Akira?
-It's probably gonna
last into the evening.
-That long?
You will be home in time to
have dinner though, won't you?
-You're not going
down to the hospital?
WOMAN: Your father told me
not to bother him today.
-Hm?
Really? How come?
-He says he doesn't
want to be interrupted
while he plays his internet Go.
They're releasing him
the day after tomorrow.
What he should be
doing is getting
as much rest as possible.
Sometimes I wonder
if playing Go is
the only thing you and your
father ever think about.
-Well, I better get going.
The time's gone by so fast.
Soon my father's going
to be out of the hospital
and back at home.
When he collapsed 10 days
ago, I thought the worst.
It happened the day I was
scheduled to play Shindou.
I won't get a chance to play
him again until next month,
when we're in the
Young Lions tournament.
But I'm not going to sit
back and wait until then.
I can always watch his
matches against other pros.
That should be enough for me to
gauge his strength right now.
And the day will soon be
here when I figure out
what kind of player
he really is.
It's weird how my father started
playing Go on the internet,
not wanting visitors
and everything.
He never showed any
interest in using a computer
before he went in the hospital.
SAI (VOICEOVER): At
last, the day has come.
-OK, Sai.
You ready?
-Yes.
-Hi, come on in.
-I thought Mitani's
sister worked here.
Did she quit, or is
it just her day off?
-You can use this one here.
-OK, thanks.
I wonder if the
Meijin's online yet.
I can't believe he said
he'd retire if he lost.
That's crazy!
-If I lose to your
friend, then I'll retire.
I won't play again.
-He sounded pretty
serious about it.
Ah, he's just like Akira.
Neither of them can stand
the thought of being beaten.
Come on, log in.
Sai?
There he is.
If Sai manages to beat
him, will he really retire?
An even game with a 5.5 komi.
Three hours each.
There we go.
He has five championship titles,
and if he suddenly retires,
there's gonna be chaos.
It's seriously bad news.
Toya-sensei gets to go first.
This game feels really intense,
even over the internet.
It's the same intensity I felt
during the Shincho Dan series,
only stronger.
This is Toya Meijin.
His first move.
I guess it doesn't really
matter to me if he retires.
I'm going to get to watch a
great game and be a part of it.
One of the best games ever,
between Toya Meijin and Sai,
right here, right now.
-I'm home.
WOMAN: Yoshitaka!
You're coming home just now?
Where have you been?
No one plays Go all night long.
-I went to Saeki's
place to play.
It got kind of late,
so I stayed over.
WOMAN: How many times
do I have to tell you?
Call me if you're
not coming home.
I tried calling your
cell phone for hours,
but you turned it off.
-Sorry.
WOMAN: Did you have
any breakfast yet?
-Yeah, stop worrying.
Ugh.
Maybe I should do
the same as Saeki
and start looking
for my own place.
If Sensei could get me
some teaching jobs or game
recording, I'd be able
to make extra money.
Add it to my match
earnings, and it
should be enough to cover
rent for an apartment.
But I'd have to make my
own meals, do laundry.
Eh.
I haven't played Go
online in a while.
WOMAN: Yoshitaka!
Are you gonna be home
for the rest of the day?
Are you staying for
lunch and dinner?
-Yeah, I'll eat here, thanks.
Sai?
The impostor's back again?
What an idiot.
Didn't he learn his lesson?
I guess it could be
someone else this time.
Hm?
Koyo Toya?
The Meijin's playing a game?
It can't be him!
It's gotta be some
jerk using his name.
Another impostor.
There's no way he would
ever play Go online.
If Morishita-sensei's not
gonna spend his time doing it,
neither would Toya Meijin.
Besides, I thought he was
still in the hospital.
But, if he was in a private
room, I suppose he could play.
Hm.
It couldn't be him.
He doesn't have time
for this kind of stuff.
Looks like he's
playing right now.
I wonder who his opponent is.
Sai?
There's no way those two
are playing each other!
They're just getting started.
Toya Meijin playing against Sai?
If it is really them, this
is going to be an epic game.
They've each got three
hours of playing time.
For an online game?
Hm.
What if it is the Meijin?
And what if-- it's Sai?
What if it's really him?
[phone ringing]
[groan]
FRANK: Hello?
Mr. Ewyer.
Yeah, it was good
to see you, too.
So, why are you calling me
in the middle of the night?
Yeah?
Koyo Toya's playing
a game online?
OK.
And who is his opponent?
Huh?
No!
-It's Sai!
The one you told me
about the other day.
How on earth would
I be able to tell
if he's the real
thing, or an impostor?
-I've got to find out!
Sai against Koyo Toya.
Come on, come on.
Let's see.
Must be about noon in Japan.
Uh, Koyo Toya and Sai.
Here it is!
-So this is the notorious Sai.
Well, well.
He is a worthy opponent.
MAN: Look, it's Sai.
-So it is.
And he's playing a
game against Koyo Toya.
-Hope you didn't
mind me coming over,
but I thought it'd be more
fun to watch it together.
Look at the playing time.
Three hours each.
Is going to be a long game.
-Whoa.
This is awesome.
MAN: All right if I make coffee?
MAN: Yeah.
And make some for me, too.
This is quite a surprise.
Sai's online again.
If it's really him.
After his game against Akira,
he just seemed to disappear.
And that was two years ago.
Does this mean
he's back for good?
-What a game it's going to be.
Sai versus Koyo Toya.
-The moves seem pretty
straightforward so far.
The question is, how
is it going to develop?
TOYA MEIJIN: He is
no mere amateur.
But he's different from any
other professional I've played.
I made a promise to
retire if I lose the game.
And I have no intention
of going back on my word.
But if I'm the one who wins--
you will tell me your name.
MAN: This is incredible.
Sai is back.
And what's more, his opponent
is none other than Koyo Toya.
I just played Koyo
Toya the other day.
I'm convinced that this player
has to be Toya Meijin of Japan.
And Sai seems to
be doing a good job
of holding his own
against the Meijin.
It must be the same Sai.
The one who was
online two years ago.
-So, he's going
on the offensive.
I can see through your strategy.
All right, then.
-Huh?
Toya finally made another move.
Huh?
This is-- Sai's plan.
He'd been waiting for
him to play there.
Is that the best the
Meijin could come up
with after thinking about
it for all that time?
-You think I'm playing right
into your hands, don't you?
However-- by going
for the capping move,
and then building
steadily on it,
my position is stronger
than you anticipated.
-This has got to be
the Meijin playing.
What a game.
I never imagined it would turn
out to be as exciting as this.
When Sai made the move
to go on the attack,
he seemed to have the
advantage there for a while.
But looking at it now,
well, that advantage
has been completely wiped out.
What an awesome game!
Way to go, Toya-sensei!
-Now you'll see what my game is.
The Meijin, a true master of Go.
I will not fall back.
I will win this game.
And you will tell me your name.
BOY: Toya Meijin was lucky
it wasn't more serious,
but you should see his schedule
for the next couple of months.
He's supposed to be
traveling all over the world
to play a ton of games.
If he doesn't take it easy,
he's gonna collapse again.
-Now, come on.
-All the more reason
for young pros
like us to get out there
and win a few titles.
Only to help ease the
pressure on him, of course.
-Well, Ogata's
making some headway.
They're at two games
each in the Judan series.
-And Kurata's going to be making
a challenge for the Honinbo
title, which is coming up.
We've gotta follow their lead.
-Hey, guys.
What's up?
-You took your
time getting here.
-Thanks for coming.
-I didn't know you were
going to be here, Toya.
-Yeah.
I thought it would be
good to invite him.
-He's pretty good
at analyzing games.
We might learn a
thing or two from him.
-I hard about your dad.
How's he doing?
Is he better now?
-Yes.
-You saw him the other
day in the Judan series.
He's in better shape than you.
-They're releasing him
from the hospital the day
after tomorrow.
He was going to spend today
playing Go on the internet.
-The internet?
Toya-sensei?
-But he doesn't seem the type.
BOY: Do you think
he's online right now?
You have a computer.
Turn it on.
-I hardly ever use the internet.
For Go, or anything else.
-What's the point of even
having a computer, then?
-I keep all my game
records on here.
Now, let's see.
Just a sec.
What name does he use online?
-Just his real name.
BOY: Toya.
-Aw, so cool!
I never thought about playing
Go on the computer before.
-Found it.
Koyo Toya.
-Let me see.
-Look how many people
are watching the game.
-It's not every day a
champion plays online.
BOY: Oh.
BOY: Is this it?
BOY: Wow.
-What a showdown.
Check out what's going
on with white at the top.
-And things look interesting
down at the bottom left.
-So, uh, who's in control?
BOY: You know, guys, it's not
easy to tell from this board.
-White looks like he's in
a better position to me.
-Well, I don't know about that.
Black is Toya-sensei, right?
-Even, so white is--
-Don't forget they're
playing an even game.
If white's playing this
well with no handicap--
-Whoa!
They've both got three
hours of playing time.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Three hours?
This is no ordinary opponent.
Who's he playing, anyway?
-Um. Let's see.
Looks like his
opponent's called Sai.
-Sai?
-Who is this guy?
-No idea.
-Never heard of
him, but he's got
to be a pro to play like this.
-You'd think so.
-Hm.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): It can't be!
It's Sai!
He's back in the game!
And he's playing my father!
[theme music]
SAI: For two years, Akira has
waited for me to reappear.
HIKARU: He's played
you before, so he'll
be watching the
game really closely.
He's gonna want to know how
his dad found out about you.
SAI: The decisive battle
will be in the endgame, when
a single stone stands
between victory and defeat.
HIKARU: But who's gonna
be able to find it?
Next time, After a
Millennium Comes the Answer!
SAI: I'm about to discover
why I came back to this world.