[theme music]
-If I beat you today, Toya's
gonna recognize my strength
and see me as his rival!
-In that case, if I beat you,
Toya's gonna see my strength,
and I'll be his rival!
You'll see.
Both of you!
OCHI (VOICEOVER): I
won't lose this game.
Not with Toya behind me.
Who have you got
behind you, Shindou?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): If
I win this match today,
then I'll finally be
a pro, just like you.
Are you ready for me?
-Here's an attack
that will crush you!
-Take that!
-Hi.
We're from the Go
Association magazine.
Nice to meet you.
We're here to do some
interviews with the new pros who
passed the exam.
-You're a bit early for that.
There's only one player
who's through for sure,
and I doubt we're gonna find
out who the other two are today.
MAN: That's what we heard.
We checked out the game
records before we came.
We could be looking at a
three way playoff, right?
-Yeah.
It's gonna be a while
before the results are in,
so make yourself comfortable
and I'll grab some tea.
-Thanks.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): There!
OCHI (VOICEOVER): I'm
in for the attack!
He won't know what hit him!
No!
How-- How could I
have missed that?
Shindou's stones!
SAI (VOICEOVER): There was one
weakness in Ochi's game plan
that he didn't anticipate,
and Hikaru discovered it.
Hikaru's stones at the
bottom right of the board
survived the attack and
made up the lost ground.
It's anyone's game now.
Toya.
The player you see
before you now is Hikaru.
The player you lost to two
years ago was actually me.
You can see my influence
in the way Hikaru plays.
I'm sure you must
have been wondering
who your opponent was back then.
Well, that was me,
Fujiwara-no-Sai.
But now you need
to pay attention
to Hikaru, who grows stronger
every day under my guidance.
Toya.
The next time we meet,
you won't be facing me.
You'll be facing Hikaru Shindou.
-Oh my.
The more I play,
the more I realize
I've got so much to learn.
-Yes.
But I think you have
definite potential.
-Thank you very
much for the lesson.
-You're welcome.
Huh?
-I hear your father managed
to defend his Meijin title.
Please, send him
my congratulations.
One day, maybe it'll be you
who's gonna have the title.
I'll be cheering for you.
-Thanks.
I'll try my best.
-Well, I better get going.
Thanks for everything.
AMANO: Ah, Toya.
-Hm?
You're from the magazine?
-I'm Amano.
We met before.
I wondered if you
had a few moments.
I'd be interested in doing
an interview with you
about your long winning streak.
You're at about 20
consecutive wins, right?
Now, when you think
of winning streaks,
Kurata comes to mind at 25,
and Kuwabara-sensei with 27.
But they're experienced
players and you're
a rookie, which makes
it even more remarkable.
Do you ever think about
breaking the record?
-Not really.
-And what about your
ambitions for the future?
Do you want to be a greater
player than your father?
Do you dream of being
the best in the world?
Toya?
-Yes?
-We've been thinking
for some time
that we'd like to
do an article on you
in the association's
monthly magazine.
We started out with
the idea of talking
with you and your father,
Toya Meijin together,
but I think the article would
be just as strong with you
on your own.
And, well, some say
it's too soon for this,
but I want to call it pro
players for the 21st century.
It would be great to get
some comments from you
that would help lead the
way for a new generation.
How about after
you're done teaching,
we get something to eat
and do the interview then?
-I've got another appointment
after I finish up here.
I'll be done teaching
by 7:40, so it's
gonna be pretty late by the time
I actually get to Ochi's house.
-Well, never mind.
We can do it some other time.
I apologize for disturbing
you during your break.
-Oh, that's OK.
-Well, now, is it
that time already?
I'd better call the study center
and see how they're doing.
The results of pro
exam might be in.
-Wait!
Can I come too?
Uh, you see, I want
to know the results!
-There are still two
matches going on,
and both are crucial to find out
who's going to pass the exam.
Two of the players are
tied at three losses each,
and then there's
that guy out there.
He's at four losses, so he
must be a nervous wreck waiting
to hear the final results.
His chances of
making it through all
depend on how these
two matches turn out.
-It's raining.
[excited whispering]
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): Waya won.
Which means that he's the
second one to make it through.
He's gonna become a pro.
It's what we've all been
aiming for from the start.
We used to hang out
together and laugh
about what would happen
if we got promoted.
But only three of
us can become pros.
Now all that's left is
Shindou's match against Ochi.
If Shindou loses, then I get
one final chance at a playoff.
[excited whispering]
-I think they're done!
-Who won?
No-one.
No-one's coming.
I mean, if Shindou lost, then
we'd have to go to a playoff,
and someone would come get me.
They would tell me that
I'm needed for the playoff.
I guess that means Shindou won.
[laughter]
-Kosuke, you can't
mope around forever.
Now, of course I understand
you're disappointed
you didn't meet that Shindou
boy today, but remember,
you still managed to pass the
test with the best record.
You'll get plenty
of opportunities
to get even when you
play each other as pros.
We've got to start making
preparations for that party
I promised you.
[doorbell]
-Huh?
-Don't bother answering it.
It's probably just Toya.
-It's all right.
Thanks.
I'll goo see who it is.
Yes?
-It's Toya here.
-Ah, hello.
I thought your coaching
sessions ended yesterday.
Unless you're coming by to find
out how Ochi did in this match
today?
-Uh, no.
I found out the results earlier.
-If you don't mind me
asking, why are you here?
-I know it's getting late,
and I should have called
or something, but I
was kind of hoping
Ochi would be able to
replay the match for me.
-He says he's not interested in
replaying a match that he lost.
-All right, then.
I understand.
I'll go now.
-Honestly, sometimes
you can be so difficult.
-1 and 1/2 points.
And what a huge 1 and
1/2 points they were.
Shindou showed great
strength and determination
by not giving up.
Now I think I can understand
why your goal of beating him
was so important to you.
You also played a
good game, Ochi.
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): So,
Shindou, you're on your way.
Soon we'll be
meeting face to face,
and then I'll get to see what
kind of player you really are.
I'm going to finally find out.
Come on, Shindou.
I'm waiting for you-- in
the world of the pros!
WOMAN: Congratulations.
Hikaru told me the
news this morning.
MITSUKO: Thank you.
-I'd already that he'd become
a professional a couple of days
ago.
Honestly, I have to admit
I'm a little surprised.
It's hard to believe he's done
so well in such a short time.
Although, as one
of his teachers,
maybe I should have paid a
little more attention to what
was going on.
-You think he would
have mentioned it to us.
We are his parents, after all.
Oh, dear.
This is all very
sudden, and I can't
help feeling a little worried.
-But why are you worried?
Is he going to be
missing a lot of school?
-Oh, I wish I knew.
-Now that he's a pro, he'll
be getting paid to play.
Do you, uh, know how much
he's going to be making?
-He really hasn't told
us anything about it.
I'm concerned he might
start to ignore schoolwork.
Or if he's off playing
Go all the time,
he might end up losing
a lot of his friends.
He's still only a teenager.
-Yes, I know.
-And then, what happens
about high school?
There's another
employee who also
pased the test, called Waya.
He's a year older than
Hikaru, in the ninth grade,
and I heard he's going to
skip high school altogether.
-But surely Hikaru
wouldn't think
of doing something like that.
-He hasn't mentioned
anything yet.
It's still a year away before
he has to make that decision.
-They'll let him go to
high school, won't they?
Then again, maybe if he's out
earning lots of money as a pro,
he wouldn't need to.
I really don't understand
the world of Go at all.
-It's a mystery to me, too.
Anyway, I thought I
would try and meet
with the parents
of this boy, Waya,
and see if they can answer
some of the questions I've
got about this whole thing.
-Uh-huh?
-When I talked to
Hikaru about it,
he just shouted at me
to mind my own business.
But how can I do that?
I'm his mother.
Of course it's my business.
-I know.
-I-- I didn't tell him I
was coming here to see you.
[school bell]
-On the positive side,
he doesn't actually
start as a pro for
quite a while yet.
Not until next spring, is it?
Now, you will keep in touch
and let me know how things go?
-Yes.
And thanks for your help.
-Hey.
-Look who it is.
So, I've heard
you've become a pro.
-That's right.
-Well.
-Huh?
-I guess I should
wish you good luck.
-So Sai, you think the
Go club's playing today?
-I don't see why
they wouldn't be.
-Hm?
SAI: Look, it's Akari.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
It's hard to believe
the club Kimihiro
started is still going.
-Should we get started?
-Hey, did you hear
the news bout Hikaru?
I heard he passed the pro exam.
-Yep.
He told me about it himself.
-Wow.
-Who's this Hikaru guy?
Is he the one that used
to be in the Go club,
and went off to become an Insei?
-Isn't it awesome?
-Mm-hm.
I'll see if I can get
him to drop by sometime.
We should have a little
party for him to celebrate.
-You all right?
-I'm OK.
-I can't imagine what it must
be like to actually make it
to the level of a pro.
-Me, either.
You know what?
Maybe we should all pitch
in and buy him a gift.
To say congratulations.
-Hey, everyone!
I'm here!
-Koneko!
You decided to come back again?
That's great!
-But what about your volleyball?
-Well, I thought I'd
concentrate on playing Go.
The last time the three of
us entered a tournament,
we didn't even manage to make
it through the first round.
I want to make sure we do
way better than that when
we compete in the
tournament this year.
-You bet we will!
I can't believe you're
serious about it.
-We'll h train hard.
-What do you think the chances
are that Yuuki will show up?
-He'd better.
Otherwise we won't be able to
enter the team competition.
-What if you just wrote his
name on the application form?
you can always change it later.
-We can't do that.
He's already said he
won't be on a team.
-Oh, it's gonna be fine.
Natsuma, you need to
take more initiative
if you're gonna be the
captain of the Go club.
-Huh?
-She's right, Captain.
-Who asked your opinion?
-What's all the fuss about?
[gasp]
-Mitani!
What are you doing here?
-Fuss? What fuss? No fuss.
-Good to see ya, Captain.
Captain?
-Yeah.
You're gonna be captain of the
boys' team in the tournament,
right?
-What are you talking about?
I never said I was gonna
play with you guys,
let alone be your captain
in some tournament.
Listen up, Kaneko--
-I don't know.
-You gotta do it.
-You know you want to.
-Hey, Shindou!
I heard a rumor going
around the class
that you're gonna be a
professional Go player.
Is that true?
-Yeah, it is.
Guess that means our Go club
must be one of the best around.
With you on the team,
it's a sure thing
we're going to win
every tournament!
-I can't enter even
if I wanted to!
I'm a pro!
Oh.
You can play?
So I guess being a pro
isn't much fun then.
HIKARU: What would you
know about being a pro?
-Hey!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Toya's
already been a pro for a year,
and now I'm about
to join his world.
Get ready for me, Toya.
[theme music]
-I get to be in
Toya's world now,
and I'm gonna play
all the top pros.
-It takes time.
HIKARU: First I wanna get a game
against Toya, and then Ogata,
and the Meijin!
SAI: Your first opponent
is going to be announced.
HIKARU: Whoever it is,
I'll be ready for them!
Next time, Into the
World of the Pros!
SAI: I wonder if Hikaru
will need me much longer.