NARRATOR: After many
years inside a go board,
a spirit from the past known as
Fujiwara no Sai has returned.
Visible only to Hikaru
Shindo, master of go,
Sai seeks to play
the divine move.
[theme music]
-I resign.
[sigh]
-I used to think that you were
capable of the divine move.
I was wrong.
-I'm having a little
trouble trying
to figure out my next move.
Should I try to connect here?
-But what if your opponent
puts you in atari?
-I hear that Akira-sensei
is taking the pro test.
-Oh?
Yeah, so it seems.
-I heard the same thing
this morning from Mr. Muroi.
-Miss Ichikawa, is
Toya taking the test?
-Yes.
-Ah, so it is true.
Well, that's really big news.
The world of go is going to
get pretty exciting next year.
-I have to admit, I'm
a little surprised.
I was under the impression
that Akira-sensei
had decided not
to take the test.
Do you have any idea
why he changed his mind?
Did something happen?
-I don't know.
I asked him how things
were going at the go club,
and he told me that
he'd had enough of it.
He said it was just
a diversion anyway.
-Could I get another cup of tea?
-Be right there.
-Hey, the NCC Cup
is about to come on.
-Sign up for an
annual subscription
to Go Weekly Magazine and you'll
save 10% off the cover price.
-Thanks to the internet, you
can now play go against people
all over the world.
This computer's already online.
Why not give it a go?
-Seat 29.
Here it is!
-Don't you think we're kind
of far away from the front?
How much fun is this going to
be if we can't see the match?
-You worry too much, Hikaru.
A couple of pros
will be analyzing
each move on a huge board.
-Are you serious?
If there's people
talking during the game,
won't it bother the players?
-I don't think they mind.
-Oh, look at that go board!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I'm glad
Sai sounds like he's having fun.
-The game should
start any minute now.
-Good afternoon, everyone.
Welcome to the 14th
annual NCC Cup.
We're about to begin game
five of the first round.
Today's match will be
between Kikuo Fujisawa 9-dan,
and Koichi Takada 7-dan.
Please give them a
round of applause.
[applause]
-Our commentators
are Murase 9-dan,
assisted by Yoshinaga 2-dan.
Now the match is about to begin.
Mr. Murase, can you
give our audience
a quick rundown on what we can
expect to see in today's game?
-It'd be my pleasure.
As we all know, Fujisawa 9-dan
has set his sights on both
the Mejin and--
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
I'm not really
proud of what I did to Sai.
He was really looking
forward to facing Akira,
and I wound up playing instead.
Oh, man.
I have to find out.
I know Akira's more
skilled than me,
but I'll never know how big that
gap is until I play him myself.
I have to make my move!
-Stop messing around!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Akira wanted
to play against Sai so much.
What I did to him was horrible.
-A fascinating move!
I'd like to take a closer look
at some of these formations.
Look here.
My guess is that white will
probably take this point.
-You're at 25 seconds.
6, 7.
-White 4-12.
-Aha.
-Sensei, it seems your
prediction was great.
-Well, I'm not a TV analyst
just because I'm good looking,
you know.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Hm.
I just don't know
what I should do.
I want to let Sai
play once in a while,
but then I'll wind up the
king of the fluke wins.
But forcing him to watch my
games all the time isn't fair.
-This friendly match has now
turned into a fierce showdown.
-You're at 20 seconds.
1, 2, 3, 4.
-Black 4-13.
-That seems like a rushed move.
-What just happened?
I haven't been watching
the game at all.
-It appears this stone
is about to be captured.
-You're completely right.
He could have attempted
an atari from this side.
But would it have worked?
Let's give it a try and see.
So if white played here,
then black would move here.
-Kimihiro, how long do you
want to keep watching this?
-Are you bored already?
We're not even halfway
through the match yet.
-I'm going to go hang
out in the lobby.
Catch you later.
-Hold on!
-Don't leave!
-I can't sit still
without doing anything
for the whole afternoon.
-This isn't fair! (CRYING)
I had been looking forward
to this all week!
-Relax.
-[crying]
-Hey, look, they're
selling some cool go books.
-Huh?
-And over there, you can
play go on a computer.
You want to try?
-Huh?
-Come on, let's go check it out.
-Did you come here
with your father?
-Uh, no.
I'm with a friend.
-Oh, you're a go fan, huh?
Do you have your own computer?
-Uh, no, I don't.
-That's too bad.
Did you know that you can
play go on the internet?
-Can you show me how?
-Absolutely.
That's what I'm here for.
This boy is in the
middle of an online game.
He's playing as black.
Look.
His opponent has just placed
a white stone on the board.
Now it's black's turn to move.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
What's this guy doing?
He shouldn't play there.
Told you.
-[growling]
-Hey!
What are you doing?
This isn't a video game.
I'd better send his
opponent an apology.
Sorry for quitting in
the middle of the game.
Oh.
-What did he say?
You loser.
You shouldn't quit just
because you lost a few stones.
Grow up, moron?
-I wasn't fast enough.
-Oh, that's really cool!
-I bet this person is a kid.
-Really?
What makes you say that?
-Well, just look at his
username and the kind of message
he writes.
-What's a username?
-It's a name you can
use on the internet.
-Zelda?
And you think it's a kid, huh?
-That's my guess.
You see, when you're
online, you don't
have to reveal
what you look like,
or how old you are, or
even your real name.
Look.
All these people
from other countries
are playing here, too.
JPN stands for Japan, CHN
is China, and CAN is Canada.
There are also many players from
Germany and the United States.
-What's NLD?
-The Netherlands.
People on this list challenge
each other to matches.
The whole process is
really quick to learn.
Here.
I'll show you.
The first thing you have to
do is send a game request.
So you pick up an
opponent, click on match,
and see if they accept.
It's pretty simple.
See?
Want to give it a try?
-I'm not ready.
I've still got a bunch of
questions I'd like to ask you.
Would you mind showing me how
I can start playing a game?
-All right.
Where should we start?
Do you want to see how
to find our website?
-Yeah.
-OK.
We should open up a new window.
Now I'm going to
run a search for--
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): You don't
have to reveal who you are.
This is great.
-You click here and here.
-Sorry about this.
I'm still not very good at go.
-Don't worry about it.
What should you do if
white escapes here?
-Hm.
I'd move here.
How's that?
-Good.
-Are you sure?
Should I have played here?
-They're both good moves.
You're learning fast.
-Thanks.
That's nice of you to say.
-Hey, guys.
What's up?
Hm?
Hikaru isn't here?
-Aw, he's playing
go on the internet.
-That didn't take long.
When did he leave?
-What didn't take long?
-We both went to see a
professional game yesterday,
but he got bored pretty
quickly, so he took off.
It's kind of hard to get that
guy to sit still sometimes.
He didn't even bother to
ask who won the match.
-Huh.
Seriously?
-So where did he go?
-He was hanging
out in the lobby.
There was an online go
demonstration set up out there.
I have no idea why he
was so interested in it,
but he spent the entire
afternoon listening to this guy
explain how it worked.
It was really hard
to get those tickets.
I had to buy them
weeks in advance.
It's weird.
Why did he make such
a big deal about it?
He doesn't even own a computer.
-Yuki's sister has a part
time job at an internet cafe.
He could use a
computer there, right?
-Where is it?
-It's not far.
Hikaru ran out of here as
soon as I told him about it.
I bet he's down there
right now playing
against online opponents.
-Huh.
-Kimihiro, want to play?
-Maybe later.
-Come on.
-Oh, all right.
How are the practices
coming along, anyway?
-Yuki taught me about
the ladder and the net.
-Great.
-The schoolyear will
be ending pretty soon.
What are we going to
do about the go club?
-I'm taking some study
classes this summer.
That'll keep me busy.
-That's right.
You have to get ready for your
high school entrance exams.
And Hikaru-- he'll probably
spend the whole break
on the computer playing
go on the internet.
-I think maybe I'll go
back to the go salon
and see how the guys are doing.
-That's cool.
I've been thinking
about taking a few go
classes at the same
place Hikaru used to go.
Next semester, I'm going
to find two other girls
to be in our club.
I'm really looking forward to
competing in some tournaments.
-Akari, why don't you enter
a one on one tournament?
-Because I want
to play on a team!
You guys were having an awesome
time competing together.
It seems pretty obvious that
team tournaments are way
more fun.
-Mmhmm.
I agree.
We may have lost to Kaio,
but we sure had lots of fun.
-You're right.
I can't wait until the
next team tournament.
-[laughing]
-I just had an idea.
Why don't we meet once a
week during summer break?
-All right.
I could probably manage that.
-Yeah, me too.
-I'll help you get started.
So you wanted to check
out the World E-Go Net?
-Yeah.
-Well, I can help you
find their website,
but I'm afraid I don't really
know very much about go.
-That's no problem.
I'm sure I'll be able
to figure it out.
I'm a pretty quick learner.
-Huh.
World E-Go Net.
Here we go.
One second.
Hey, is that it?
-Yep.
You can play go against people
from all over the world.
-That sounds pretty amazing.
You do know how to surf
the internet, right?
-Sort of.
It wouldn't hurt to know
how, but I just want to play,
so it shouldn't be a problem.
-Hikaru, you were
looking at a device
similar to this
yesterday, but this one
doesn't seem to be as flat.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
You're right,
but the insides
are all the same.
-I don't understand.
Can you show me how
this device works?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sure.
I'll let you play as
many games as you want.
Come here and check this out.
-What?
Hikaru, are you serious?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Guess
you'll have to wait and see.
-I was wondering.
Do you know where Yuki
learned to play go?
-He first learned it
from our grandfather.
Then when he was in
elementary school,
there was this one teacher he
practiced with all the time.
After he graduated, he started
hanging out in go salons.
-Huh.
-Is he a good player?
-Uh, of course.
He's awesome.
-Huh.
Is that right?
How about you?
-Me?
I don't know.
I'm OK.
-If you're just OK, then why
you so excited about playing
against people all
over the world?
-Long story.
-I'm sorry about that.
It doesn't matter
how good you are.
You think you can
handle it from here?
-Uh-huh.
Are you sure I
don't have to pay?
-It'll be fine, but
please don't tell anybody.
And you should only play
on days I'm working.
-You can trust me.
-Just let me know
when you're done, OK?
-I will.
-Later.
-First, we'll need a name.
How about Sai?
-Is it true?
I can really play as
much go as I want?
-Yeah.
Let's get started.
S-A-I. Sai.
OK, let's do it.
-That's right, Mom.
Next month, I'm going to be
spending about a week in Japan.
I'm excited.
I've been chosen to represent
the US in the World Amateur
Championship.
There'll be some
tough opponents.
How many?
I'd say there's
around 50 countries.
Each one sends a single player.
Winning first place at the
US preliminaries was hard,
but this is going to be
the ultimate challenge.
Well, I've got to
agree with you there.
Asia is incredibly strong.
China, Japan, and Korea are
all going to be hard to beat.
We placed eighth
last year, but it's
going to be more difficult
this time around.
Well, it's because
of the internet.
I can always find a
skilled opponent online.
It gives competitors
everywhere the opportunity
to train against
powerful players.
Some people are saying
Japan is getting weaker,
but I don't know if that's true.
[laughs] I'll do my best, OK?
Huh?
Someone's asking me
for an online game.
Thanks for calling, Mom.
All right.
Bye.
Sai?
Never seen that name before.
Well, I might as well
see what this guy can do.
-He accepted our challenge!
[laughing]
-Teacher, it's time
for my go lesson.
-Shh.
-Hm?
-Keep quiet.
Our teacher is in the
middle of a game right now.
He's training online for
next month's World Amateur
Championship.
-Hm.
-Oh well.
I guess there's no lesson today.
-Grab a seat.
I've got some time
if you want to play.
-That would be great.
I really want to
work on my game.
-In a couple of years,
maybe some of us
will be skilled enough to
help our teacher train.
-Our teacher is really talented.
He's representing
the Netherlands
for the second year in a row.
It's an honor to be his student.
-I was really impressed when
he finished in sixth place
last year.
Maybe this year, he'll
manage to break Asia's grip
on the top five.
-I've heard that
his employers have
been getting pretty
upset with him.
He's so passionate about
teaching that he's already
opened up his won go academy.
-What if he gets fired
from his current job?
He's a good assistant professor.
[laughing]
-Huh?
-Sensei?
-Huh.
[gasp]
[laughing]
I get it now!
He's a pro!
I should've known!
Of course.
That's it!
You never know who you're
playing on the internet.
I heard that pros
in Asia sometimes
play online against amateurs.
But I wouldn't have
believed it if I
hadn't seen it with my own eyes.
-Sensei?
-What happened?
-I'm sorry to ask,
but did you just lose?
--[laughing] That's
an understatement.
I think slaughtered
would be more accurate.
He was so strong I almost
had a heart attack.
Whoever he was, he
just logged off.
That's the first time
I've seen that name.
I suppose I could ask some
of my contacts about him,
but I doubt anyone's
ever heard of this Sai.
Who could he be?
-You really enjoyed that, huh?
-Yes!
-Great.
We've got the whole
summer ahead of us.
We can play every
day if you want to.
-Really?
You will allow me to
play every single day?
-I'll let you play so
much go you'll never
want to see a bowl
of stones again.
-Oh, thank you!
[theme music]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
This is totally cool!
We're going to get to
play against Zelda!
SAI (VOICEOVER): Zelda?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
That's his username.
I think he's a
really good player.
SAI (VOICEOVER): There are so
many players across the world,
and now they all know my name.
Will we be discovered?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
We'd better not,
or else I'm gonna have to
do a lot of explaining.
Next time, Who Is Sai?
SAI (VOICEOVER): How long can
you keep my identity a secret?