[theme music]
-Did you hear about Shindou?
The Chairman of the Players
Association, Murota Nine-Dan,
gave him a call.
-Yeah? And?
-He asked Shindou if he was
missing games because he
was sick and offered the chance
to take a leave of absence,
but he didn't even
bother to reply.
-What an idiot.
-Think he'll quit being a pro?
-I don't know.
Looking at him now, it's hard
to believe he was Toya's rival.
-Having talent is
a waste of time
if you don't put
it into practice.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): If I
start having the urge to play,
and if I start playing
Go again, then Sai
will never come back to me.
That's how I feel.
I can't help it.
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): It's
good to be back home again.
With the qualifying rounds
of this year's pro exam
just around the corner, the
competition is heating up.
The former holder of three
collegiate titles, Katawaki,
has announced he
will be entering.
I can't believe
it's here already.
I wonder how the
others have been doing.
Let's see the results
of last week's matches.
Ochi beat Machiba,
Waya had a by.
Shindou-- He lost by default?
-Ah!
Isumi!
You don't look any different.
I figured since you were
spending all your time
training, you'd have grown
a beard or something.
I was surprised when
I got your call.
So, how was china?
What was like?
What's wrong?
-Well, if it isn't Le Ping.
You've grown up fast.
-Uh-- Yeah, so, after that,
Le Ping followed me around,
wanting to play against
me all the time.
I guess it was good he
was working on his game,
but I didn't get
much time for myself.
-He was a pest, huh?
-I know he's just a kid, but
he's a really strong player.
In the end, I enjoyed
hanging out with him.
He sort of became
my best friend.
Once I gave him
some Waya medicine.
-Gave him what?
-You know that
special medicine you
take whenever you
get a stomach ache?
Well, one day Le Ping
had a stomach ache,
so I gave him some.
I figured he looks exactly like
you, so it was bound to work.
-What kind of dumb
logic is that?
-It helped get rid
of his stomach ache.
From that moment on, he
and I became good friends.
-Cool.
What about your game against
the other kid, Zou-si.
Did you beat him?
-No, I lost.
And because of
that, Yang Hai lost
his bet and his MP3 player.
But the next time we played
against each other, I beat him,
and after I got
my visa extended,
we played a few more times.
Anyway, I played as much as
I could during the past two
months.
I got the chance to meet some
of China's best up and coming
players.
-Some of the games
were pretty tough,
but I still managed to
win quite a few of them.
The important thing is, I've
got confidence back in my game.
-Way to go.
You said you wanted to
ask me about something.
What was it?
-Oh yeah.
Here.
I haven't seen a copy
since I went away.
Did you know it says
Shindou lost by default?
I've been wondering
what happened.
Is he sick?
I mean, I want to see
him again before I
get started in the pro exams,
but I-- What is it, Waya?
-This isn't in the first
time it's happened.
He's lost more than
once by default.
He's lost a lot.
-What?
-WAYA: It's been
like this since May.
-Careful!
WAYA: I don't know why,
but he's completely
lost interest in playing Go.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai.
-Hello Isumi.
-Well, hello, Mr. Amano.
It's good to see you again.
-Narusawa-sensei told
me you'd been away.
Studying in China, wasn't it?
So, when did you get back?
-The other day.
-I'd love to hear all about it.
Maybe over coffee sometime?
Eh?
-Sure.
-Wonderful.
I'll be in touch with you soon.
Bye for now.
ISUMI: Uh, Mr. Amano?
-Hm?
-Have you heard about Shindou?
Do you know what's
happened to him?
-You mean Hikaru,
the new One-Dan?
-Yes.
I don't understand
what's going on.
Why would he miss
all those matches?
Do you know?
-Sorry, I don't.
It's funny, but
Ogata-Judan was asking me
the same thing just
a few minutes ago.
-He's worried about him, too?
Ogata-sensei?
Can I talk with you?
You played Shindou?
when?
-Couple of months ago.
Towards the end of
Golden Week, at one
of those seminars organized
by the Go Association.
As far as I know,
he hasn't played
in any games or
tournaments since then.
ISUMI: When you two played,
did you notice anything unusual
about him?
-I don't remember.
Let's just say, I was a little
bit worse for wear at the time.
-Thanks for the ride.
-Don't mention it.
If you find out
what's going on, I'd
appreciate it if
you'd let me know.
-Sure.
So, he hasn't been
coming here either?
-No, he has not, but if
he did show his face,
I'd give him a piece of my mind.
I'd ask him what in the world
does he think he's doing.
-Something must've happened
for him to simply stop playing.
-Like what?
-Well, unfortunately, I don't
know of anything for sure.
Mr. Kawai, what about the
Shusaku pilgrimage he went on?
-What?
Do you mean Shusasku
as in Honinbo Shusasku?
-Yeah.
It was near the end of
Golden Weej, I think.
I happened to bump into
him while I was working.
Oh, did I mention that
I drive a taxi cab?
-So, you bumped into him and--
-He looked like he
was going on a trip,
so I asked him
where he was headed.
Said he was going to Hiroshima.
I'd never been there, so
I decided I'd take a break
and go with him.
It sounded like it was
an interesting place,
being Shusaku's
birthplace and all.
When we got there, the kid
ran all over the place.
We started at the
Ishikiri shrine,
where they've got the
Shusasku Memorial Museum.
We went to the Jikanji
Temple at Irozaki Hachimangu,
and then we went back to Tokyo.
Ha even dragged me to the
Honmyo-ji Temple in Sugamo.
We sure crammed a lot in.
-So.
You spent all that
time with him.
Was he OK?
Did you notice anything weird?
-I don't know about that.
The only thing I can
think of is he always
seemed to be in such a hurry.
He never stayed very
long in one place.
You know, it was like he
was searching for something
important.
-Searching for something?
ISUMI (VOICEOVER): Shindou.
Why aren't you playing anymore?
Here's your place.
You're gonna tell
me what's happened.
I'm sorry for just
dropping by like this.
-Oh, well, he should
be home from school
soon, so if you
don't mind waiting.
Oh, how about I
get you some tea.
-Oh, don't make it just for me!
Hm.
That's a lot of dust.
It hasn't been used in months.
What's up with you, Shindou?
-I'm home.
-Shindou, hi.
-It's only you.
Hi.
-Hikaru.
You went up the stairs
in such a hurry.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
It wasn't Sai.
I knew someone was here
and thought that maybe,
just maybe, it
might have been him.
But it wasn't.
Oh well.
-Isumi hasn't been here long.
If you give me a minute, I'll
get some tea for you too.
-I don't want any.
-Thanks.
This is great.
-You're welcome.
Make yourself at home.
-It's been quite a while.
How are you?
-Good.
I heard that you went to
China and did some studying.
-Yeah.
I was there for a
little over two months.
I just got back a
couple days ago.
Look, I didn't come
here to talk about me.
What's been happening, Shindou?
Waya says you've been missing
your games and the study
sessions.
Shindou?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Here we go again.
All I want to do right
now is get out of here.
But I can't do that to Isumi.
I can't just bail on him when
I haven't seen him for so long.
-I remember you telling me
once thar Toya was your rival.
Do you think you can
never catch up to him?
Is that why you don't
want to play anymore?
-Toya's got nothing
to do with it.
And what exactly did you mean
by never catch up to him?
-Obviously you haven't heard.
You should see the way
he's been playing lately.
He's incredible.
-What does it say there?
Promotions?
Huh?
Toya's already made
it to a Three-Dan?
-Now look in the
preview where it
shows the games
playing this week.
You see today's date?
Hagiwara Nine-Dan versus
Akira Toya Three-Dan.
Honinbo championship,
third round qualifiers.
Through to the third round?
-Huh?
Kuwabara-sensei!
I thought you were supposed
to be playing right now.
Is the game finished already?
-Far from it.
My opponent, Mano, is taking
so long to think about his move
that I decided to come out
here for a bit of a break.
How's young Toya doing in there?
-Oh, it's a battle.
Both players are
having a tough time.
Can you imagine what
an upset it would
be if Toya actually
managed to win?
A 15 year old Three-Dan.
Only in his second year
as a pro, and already
through to the
Honinbo round robin.
Kurata sure gave you a run
for your money in this year's
final, but if young Toya is one
of the challengers next year,
you'd better watch
out, or you're
going to lose your title.
The new wave you once talked
about will finally be here.
But you've got to wonder
what happened to Shindou.
I seem to remember you
were watching his progress
with a great deal of
interest, along with Ogata,
and even Koyo Toya.
-I'm not worried.
Hardship and doubt are
necessary for any Go player.
No, Mr. Amano.
I'm not worried
about him at all.
-Huh?
-Shindou got himself
dragged into the world
of the pros because
of young Toya.
As long as Toya's doing
his best to reach the top,
I guarantee Shindou
won't be far behind.
He will return-- so he
can face the opponent he's
meant to play.
-By the way you're
talking, you make it sound
as though it's Shindou's
destiny to be Toya's rival.
I think you overestimate him.
-I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
Even Toya believes it.
-Toya's gotten this far already?
-If he wins the
game today, he'll
make it through to
the final eight.
Then he can enter
the lead to challenge
Kuwabara for the Honinbo title.
-He's turned into a
really strong player.
But how strong?
-It's obvious you still
care about the game.
So tell me why you
won't play Go anymore?
-Well, you see, I'm not really
interested in this stuff.
Besides, isn't it up to me
whether I quit playing Go or not?
-You?
Quit Go?
Are you serious?
Look, Shindou.
We're going to play.
-Wait.
Isumi, no.
I don't want to.
Just leave me alone.
I wish everyone would
stop worrying about me.
-I don't want to play because
I'm worried about you.
-Huh?
-I need this.
I need you to play
me one more game.
This is why I came
to see you today.
-But, Isumi, I--
-Do you remember the
last time we played?
It was during the pro
exam, nearly a year ago.
I went for atari
from the wrong side.
-Hm?
-I-- I-- I decided to resign.
What else could
I do after moving
a stone I'd already
placed on the board?
But it wasn't an easy
decision for me to make.
I seriously considered seeing
if I could get away with it.
I hate myself for it.
Shindou, that game was the
last time the two of us
ever played against each other.
Before this year's
pro exam begins,
I need to wipe the slate clean.
Please.
For me.
I really need you to
play this game with me.
-But Isumi--
-Please, Shindou!
One game!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I want
to, but if I play Go again,
Sai might never come back.
[theme music]
HIKARU: Isumi really wants me
to play him in the rematch.
I've been thinking
about quitting as a pro,
but I can't give up on a friend.
I hope Sai understands how much
this one game means to Isumi.
During the game,
something amazing happens.
Next time, Sai Was Here!