[theme music]
-We all know of Hikaru Toya, but
there's also Shindou, and Ochi
and with Waya and the
others filling up the ranks,
there's bound to be a huge burst
of energy into the world of Go.
When I think about
the future, my heart
pounds with excitement.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Toya
-You and I have played
each other twice.
Both times at the Go salon.
You are Sai.
You have to be.
I know you Shindou.
I know your game better
than anyone else,
and that's how I can tell.
I'm the only one who could know.
There is someone
else inside you.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Toya.
-Never mind.
I'm not make much sense, am I?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Toya can see Sai.
Until now, I was the only
one who knew who he was.
Sai, Toya has found you.
He found you.
-It's you.
Your life is in this game.
It means everything to you.
It's something that
doesn't change,
and I think that's
the way it should be.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Wow.
Hm, my life is in this game.
It means everything to me.
Toya, you're right
about that but only
because Sai is in my every move.
-Maybe one day, when
I have the time,
I'll tell you the whole story.
-Shindou.
What did mean by that?
-What?
What are you talking about?
-There's something
you're not telling me.
What is it?
-Look, never mind.
Forget it.
Anyway, you're the
one who told me
my life was about playing
Go, and you're OK with that.
-Well, yeah, I
did say that but--
-Then, that's it.
End of story.
-Then why did you say
you'd tell me one day?
-I didn't.
I said maybe, like way
off in the future, dummy!
-Dummy?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I'm home.
MITSUKO (VOICOVER): How'd
everything go today?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
I'm so tired.
The game was over real
quick, but afterwards, we
spend forever discussing it.
Don't you want to know who won?
MITSUKO (VOICOVER): Well, not
if you don't want to tell me.
Besides, I don't know
anything about Go.
All I care about is whether
you're doing OK or not.
If you want a bath,
you'll have to wait
until your father's finished.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): That's OK.
I don't want one anyway.
MITSUKO (VOICOVER): How
about something to eat?
You must be hungry.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Not really.
I think I'm going to
go straight to bed.
(SIGH) Wha-- I'm wearing shoes.
-Oh, this must be a dream.
It's hard to tell because
everything seems real.
Who knows, this
might not be a dream.
Well, if this really is a
dream, then something good
could happen in it.
Hopefully.
Sai!
It's you?
You came here to
see me in my dream?
Is that it?
(LAUGHING)
Sai, guess what happened today?
I finally got to play Toya.
Can you believe it?
It was the first round
of the qualifiers
for the Meijin tournament.
was such a great game.
I, um, I didn't
actually win the game.
But from now on, we're going to
play each other all the time.
Hundreds of thousands of
games, me versus Toya.
And not just in
tournaments, we promised
to play as often as we
can over at his Go salon.
But I can't tell Morishito
Sensei because he'll get mad.
By the way, Isumi finally
passed the pro exam.
Isn't that awesome?
And Mitani took part
in a tournament.
Oh, you wouldn't believe what's
going on sine you disappeared.
There's so much to tell you.
A lot has happened.
Sai, why did you disappear?
You told me you wanted
to play Go forever, so
why'd you disappear?
It doesn't make any sense.
What were you feeling
when you left me?
Was everything OK?
Were you upset about something?
Or were you smiling
when you left?
I hope everything was OK.
Hey, Sai, guess
what else happened?
Toya said he can see
someone else inside of me.
I panicked.
I didn't know what to say.
But in a way, I was glad
that he noticed you.
he can see how much
influenced my game.
Hm?
Sai, you OK?
Sai?
Don't go!
Say something, would ya?
Don't leave me!
Don't go!
For me?
-Sai.
MITSUKO (VOICOVER):
Hikaru, it's past 7:00.
You're going to be
late for school.
-It's OK.
I'm up.
I'm coming.
MITSUKO (VOICOVER): Are you sure
you've got everything you need?
-Yeah, I'll be at the
Go salon after school,
but I'll come home
in time for dinner.
-Hm.
-If you try saving those stones,
your position will crumble.
-OK, but what if I
played it this way?
Then it would've been better
if I hadn't moved here
in the first place.
-Isn't that young Toya
Sensei over there?
Who's he playing?
-Oh, that's Hikaru Shindou.
He turned pro last year.
-Really?
Does he stop by here often?
Regular customer?
-Hm-huh.
Recently, he's been coming
in here all the time.
-The two of them
are good friends?
-Ah, um, sort of, I guess.
-It's starting to
get ugly up there.
Time to make a quick exit.
-Yeah, let's get out of here.
-Not again.
-What's wrong?
TOYA: Don't say, is that
so with that tone of voice.
You know I'm right, Shindou.
-Who says, you're right?
You missed this descent here.
How obvious.
-Oh, if you're
talking about obvious,
what about the
attachment you missed,
and how many time are you going
to keep saying is that so?
-They're really going at it.
Those kids are
passionate about Go.
-Sure, if you say so.
TOYA: You've said it four
times in this game, not three.
-Like you can talk.
You said, yes, I see at
least six times already.
-Now way, I did not.
I'd never say it
that many times.
-Did too!
-I do not!
-I'm going home!
-Don't forget your bag.
You see, those two fight like
they're still in grade school.
-You say, he only
became a pro last year,
and he thinks he's
a match for Toya?
That kid's get some
nerve if he thinks
he can challenge someone who's
made it to the Honinbo league
already.
-Why is that so weird?
I'm only a three dan.
-Wah!
-No matter how strong
you are, everyone
has to start as a one dan.
And you can only move up the
rankings one level at a time.
You're dan ranking has nothing
to do with your strength.
Shindou is only a one
dan now, but nobody
should underestimate him.
-Those two we're fighting
earlier, weren't they?
-Oh, yes.
-I wish I could play more
high ranking players.
-Yeah?
So who's your opponent today?
-Kowasaki, three dan.
It's my third game in
the Honinbo qualifiers.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Toya is already
battling against some of
the top players in the game,
and I'm still just a one dan.
I have to advance through
the first qualifying round
in every tournament,
not just the Honinbo.
All the games are against
the lower ranking guys,
but it's something I gotta do.
-OK, I'm hungry.
-Are you going somewhere
for lunch, Shindou?
-Yeah.
-I ordered mine,
so I'll stay in.
-K.
-Time for some katsudon.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-You're his friend,
why's he still a one dan?
Do you know?
Why is someone as good as
Shindou still only a one dan?
WAYA (VOICEOVER):
Well, you see, you
remember the guy who skipped all
of his games earlier this year?
GUY AT GO SALON (VOICEOVER):
Oh, yeah, I think so.
Why?
-That was Shindou.
By not showing up, he lost
a lot of games by default.
Even if his winning
streak continues,
it'll be a long
time before he earns
enough points for a promotion.
So he'll be a one dan
for quite a while.
-But that seems so unfair.
He's way too good to
play at this level.
He's the strongest
one dan around.
WAYA (VOICEOVER):
Shindou's practically
won his game already.
The obvious response to
blacks indirect connection
would have been to extend.
But I guess he thought
that was too easy
and decided to make a
contact play instead.
That move was perfectly timed.
-Hey, Waya.
-Huh?
Shindou, what have
you got there?
-You mean this?
I saw it in the shop
and decided to buy it.
-You bought that?
-I did, yeah.
OK, let's finish this game.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Sai, one day,
you and I are going to play
the divine move together.
[theme music]