[theme song]
SAI (VOICEOVER): 140
years ago, Torajiro
allowed me to guide him.
If Torajiro existed
for my sake, then
I have existed
for Hikaru's sake.
And what's more, Hikaru will now
exist for someone else's sake.
Then that person will be
there for someone else.
And so it will continue,
year after year,
millennium after millennium.
The long path that leads us
all toward the divine move.
My part in the
journey is now over.
-Hey, Sai?
Where are you?
Are you trying to hide from me?
I'm only playing because
you wanted me to.
I'd rather be sleeping.
This is annoying.
Where are you?
Hmph.
Forget it.
I'm going to bed.
OK, Sai, cut it out.
This isn't funny.
Huh.
Hm?
Hm.
-What are you doing?
-This is really weird.
-You can say that again.
You've been acting
strange lately.
-Maybe I lost him on the
way back from the hotel.
No, he definitely
came home with me.
-Huh?
-It wasn't just my imagination.
We were playing go up in my room
until just a few minutes ago.
-Is something the
matter, Hikaru?
-I did leave the window open.
There's no way he
would have jumped.
Maybe he was carried
off by the wind.
Hey, mom?
I'm going out for a while.
-Uh, wait a minute.
Where are you going?
-I don't know.
Out somewhere.
Go association.
-OK then.
-OK, if he was carried
off by the wind,
then he could have taken it
as a chance to go anywhere
he wanted.
But he's been around
me for over two years,
and nothing like this
has ever happened before.
I don't understand.
He's not here.
Sai?
Huh.
Hey there, Sai.
You in here?
Sai?
Well, he's definitely not there.
Where else could
he have gone to?
He can't just disappear
all of a sudden!
No.
He couldn't have.
-Hikaru, what's so
important you can't even
stop to say hi to your grandpa?
-Nothing.
Sorry.
-So what's up?
Did you forget something
the last time you were here?
-[gasp]
-The blood stain.
It's completely gone.
But why?
How is that possible?
Sai was playing go
with me in my room.
It was just like normal.
That's what we always did.
Last time I was here,
I remember thinking
the stain looked lighter.
And that's when Sai was
talking about disappearing.
What did he mean by that?
He couldn't have-- couldn't
have gone for good.
Could he?
That's crazy.
He wouldn't have left
without saying goodbye.
The two of us have been
together for all this time!
-Hikaru, are you
sure everything's
all right up there?
If you stay up there too
long, the ghosts of the attic
might come haunt you!
-That's exactly what I want!
-Huh?
-Grandpa, do ghosts
ever just disappear?
-They disappear when they can
rest in peace-- when there's
no more unfinished business
for them to deal with on Earth.
-That's what I thought.
-Huh?
Hey, Hikaru, wait!
Going home already?
-Sai couldn't have
gone, because he
hasn't mastered the
divine move yet.
He'd stay for however long it
took-- for thousands of years.
He's gotta be in my room.
He must be hiding somewhere.
I mean, he was
there this morning!
I'm home!
Sai?
I guess he decided
to go somewhere.
He's never done it
before, but there's
no reason why he couldn't
learn to do it if he wanted to.
He has been kind
of moody lately.
He probably thought he needed
a break from everything,
so he went off somewhere.
Maybe he could actually fly.
Well, if he learned
how to do that,
he could have flown
off to any place!
The least he could've done is
told me where he was going!
[phone ringing]
-Yes?
Hello?
Oh, Hikaru!
Why'd you run off
all of a sudden?
After coming all
this way, you should
have stayed so we could
play a quick game.
What?
What do you mean, where
would a ghost want to go?
How on Earth would I know?
-Come on!
You must have some kind of idea!
I need to know!
-You're serious about
this, aren't you?
-Maybe he'd go back to his
own grave, or a place that
held special memories for him.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I don't
think Sai even has a grave.
So what place would
be special to him?
-Sorry, Grandpa.
Gotta go.
I think I've worked it out. Thanks.
-What? H-Hikar--
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Sai wasn't in the attic
where we first met.
What if he's gone somewhere
from another part of his life?
-Torajiro.
I remember Sai saying he
met Torajiro in Inoshima.
This is what I was looking for.
Now let's see.
Inoshima is where?
Near Hiroshima?
Gah, but that's like
hundreds of miles away!
Here it is.
He always complained
about me, but he never
had a bad thing to
say about Torajiro.
[scoff] So what?
I spent lots of
time with Sai, too.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I'll do
whatever it takes to find you.
You can't just leave
without saying a word.
That's not fair!
I'm going to find you, Sai!
-What am I doing?
Inoshima's so far away.
I don't know if I can
make it all the way
there and back in a day!
But if I don't go, I
might never find him.
So I have to try.
It's going to be worth it if
I can find some sort of clue
to help me figure
out where he is.
[honking]
-Hey, kiddo!
Where are you going?
Can I give you a ride anywhere?
-Hi, Mr. Kawai.
-The train station, huh?
You going on a trip?
Now, correct me if I'm wrong,
but isn't Inoshima the place
where Honinbo Shusaku was born?
It's nice out there.
I'd love to have
a break like that.
I had to work all the way
through Golden Week this year
without a day off.
OK, that settles it.
Just let me swing by the office
so I can drop off the car.
-What?
-I'm coming with you
to Inoshima, kiddo.
-Look at that.
Isn't that the best view of
Mount Fuji you've ever seen?
It looks great!
-It's only a mountain, and
you can see it anytime.
-Aw, don't be so grumpy.
You're not going to be very
good company with that attitude.
-Well, I never asked
you to come with me.
-Now we've got to find the
bus that takes us to Inoshima.
-What, you mean like
that one over there?
It says Inoshima on the front.
Hurry up!
We don't want to miss it!
We'd better make a run for it.
-They'll wait for us.
Why do kids always have
to be in such a rush?
-Is that the ocean?
-Of course it is.
Don't you know
shima means island?
What do they teach you
kids in school nowadays?
Won't be long until we're there.
Once we get off, the
Shusaku Memorial Museum's
just a 15 minute walk away.
-Shusaku Memorial Museum?
-That's right.
It's on the site of the
house where Shusaku was born.
That is where you
wanted to go, isn't it?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
A memorial museum?
Would Sai have come here?
Maybe.
But I bet it would just
give him the creeps.
-Well, here we are.
What do you think?
Aren't you excited?
-Sai, are you here?
-The actual museum's at
the back of the property.
-Hey, Sai!
Why are you hiding from me?
He doesn't seem to be here.
Sai?
It looks like I came all the
way down here for nothing
after all.
-Hey, what are you
doing over there?
The museum's this way.
What were you doing,
praying or something?
-Where is he?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
He isn't here.
-Look.
See that really ancient
go board over there?
-Huh?
So this board-- it's the one
Torajiro played on as a kid?
-Who's Torajiro?
-That was Shusaku-sensei's
name as a child.
And yes, he and his mother used
to play on that very board.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai?
Sai, can you hear me?
Sai?
-Now, if you come
this way, you can
see where Shusaku-sensei
is buried.
-Hey, why are you always
running off on me?
Kids today.
Never walk when they can run.
He's a professional
go player, you know.
And he just became a
1-Dan earlier this year.
-Really?
How wonderful.
-He's always wanted to see
where Honinbo Shusaku was born,
so I thought, why not
bring him here on a trip?
And here we are.
-Sai!
Sai?
Where are you?
Huh?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): This is it.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai.
Where have you gone?
I wish I knew what happened.
[sigh] I can't give up yet.
I have to keep looking.
[gasp]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
It's no good.
He's definitely not here.
Where the heck
could he have gone?
I came all this way
to look for you.
Come on, Sai!
Please!
Why won't you answer me?
You can hear me, can't you?
-You spent a long time
at his grave, kiddo.
I had no idea you were
such a fan of Shusaku.
-You don't get it.
-It's OK, I won't tell anyone.
But I already know where
I'm going to take you next.
-Huh?
-The Takehara Hosenji Temple.
The lady at the museum
recommended we pay a visit.
She said it was one of Shusaku's
favorite places to play go.
-This is the actual
go board that Shusaku
used when he was here.
And in here, we have the stones.
-Wow, the real thing?
Shouldn't this be behind
glass or something like that?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I
remember Sai telling me
about this place.
He came here with
Torajiro a long time ago.
-Obviously, we take a great deal
of care to store them properly.
But we also feel it's
important for people
to see them close up so they
can connect with the past.
-You mean I'm allowed
to play a stone?
[laughs] Just wait until I
tell the boys at the go salon!
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai? Sai!
I don't think he's here, either.
I don't understand, Sai.
Why wouldn't you want to
come back to Torajiro's home?
-Going home?
You've gotta be kidding me!
You can't go from Tokyo to
Hiroshima and back in a day!
It's too late to travel now!
-I don't care.
I want to go.
I told my mom I was only
going out for a little while.
And I've got school
in the morning.
-Fine, but you'll be
going home on your own.
I'm staying to visit more
Shusaku sights tomorrow.
-What?
You mean there's more?
-The monk at the temple told
me about a couple other places
we can stop by.
-I want to see them!
The thing is, I
don't have the money
to stay the night in a hotel.
-How convenient.
I'll lend you the cash.
-Wait, I need to
call home first.
-Hey, the phone's this way!
-What's the matter?
You haven't even
touched your food.
We had a busy morning checking
out those other places.
You must be really hungry.
I know I am.
Take your time, why don't you?
I'll see you later.
-What?
Where are you going?
-Remember that sign we saw
earlier for a go salon?
I'm going to go have a game
with some of the locals.
I'll take care of the bill here.
You can come and find
me when you're all done.
-[sigh]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): Sai.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
I've searched
everywhere I could think
of, but I couldn't find him.
Not yesterday, not today.
If he's not here, I guess I
should head back to Tokyo.
I know!
Maybe he went back
to my room when
I was looking for him down here!
If he's there when
I go home, I'm
gonna promise to bring
him back here someday.
It'd be so great to show him
around all the different places
I went to.
He'd love it!
I know Mr. Kawai wanted
to stay a bit longer,
but I'm going back to Tokyo even
if I have to drag him with me!
-Mr. Kawai?
Are you there?
-50,000?
-Huh?
-Don't try anything with me,
you idiot, or you'll regret it!
-You're the one who
suggested it, not me.
-Yeah, says who?
-Says me.
You lost, so now you pay up.
-Uh, Mr. Kawai?
[theme song]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): OK,
so Mr. Kawai got himself
into a tough situation.
But why did I have to
end up getting involved?
All I wanted to do was head
back home to Tokyo, not play go!
And this guy is no pushover.
He's representing Japan in
the next World Amateur Go
Championship.
Next time, "Hiroshima's
Top Player."