[theme music]
HIKARU: You are gonna wanna
play him again, aren't you?
-Yes.
-I wonder if I can
make it happen.
-You wonder if?
You have to do better than that!
-I'm sure I'll figure
something out someday.
You'll just have to wait.
-Someday?
When?
-How should I know when?
Whenever it happens.
Today was an important
day for me too.
My first game as
a pro, remember?
So don't be so selfish.
I gave up a big chance
to let you play.
You don't get it, do you?
I--
-I'm very sorry.
-It's your own fault.
You're the one who
decided to inhabit me.
-Poor Torajiro.
He was intelligent and truly
kind to everyone he met.
-Hmph.
So you think I'm stupid
and not kind to anyone?
-Hikaru.
Why did the spirits
of Go bring me
back to this world
to be with Hikaru?
His progress has been
truly remarkable.
And as his teacher, I'm
both proud and happy
to see him do so well.
But what about me?
Will I play Go again?
This existence is painful.
Finally an opportunity
came along for me
to face a Go master,
someone I hoped
would help me in my journey
to find the Divine Move.
But it wasn't meant to be.
I couldn't play as I usually
do, and so against him,
it was impossible for me to
have the perfect game I wanted.
If I am unable to
achieve the Divine Move,
then why am I here?
How long must I wait?
It all began over a
thousand years ago.
Every day, I would play
Go at the imperial palace.
Then came that fateful day when
I played another instructor
to see who would have the
honor of teaching the emperor.
There was a white
stone in his Go bowl.
He waited for an
opportune moment,
and then he slipped the
stone in with his prisoners.
And then, just as I was about
to protest-- What that--
-Scoundrel!
Just now, I saw you take a
black stone from your bowl
and place it among
your prisoners!
-What?
But I just saw you
do the same thing
with a white stone
from your bowl!
-What a pitiful
attempt at an excuse!
While all eyes were
fixed on the board,
you shamelessly took one
of my stones from your bowl
and placed it among
your prisoners!
-No, you were the
one who did that!
MAN: Silence!
That's enough.
I refuse to believe that
two members of my court
would commit such a discourteous
offense within my presence.
Now, on with the game.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
Unable to calm myself
at this disturbing turn of
events, I lost the game.
I was banished from the
capital, my reputation tarnished
by the allegation of treachery.
I had no other skills.
No way to make a living.
Two days later, I cast
myself into the river.
But I didn't want
to stop playing Go.
Unable to find peace, my soul
was trapped within a Go board.
It seemed like an
eternity, until one day,
on the island of
Enoshima in the Seto Sea,
I heard a child's voice.
His name was Torajiro.
Sweet child.
If you are able to see the
stains of my wretched tears,
then perhaps you
have some small space
within your soul in
which to house my own.
From that moment, I was
able to play as much
Go as I wanted with him.
-He changed his name to
Shusaku, and before long, he
won the title of Honinbo.
Together with him,
I was confident I
would be able to
achieve the Divine Move.
But he could not win the
battle against the epidemic.
Torajiro Honinbo Shusaku.
For all eternity,
I will never forget
the time I spent with him.
Eternity.
HIKARU: Sai.
If that's the way
you wanna play.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Yes.
And then you appeared, Hikaru.
HIKARU: That's funny.
The stain here isn't coming off.
AKARI: Uh, what are
you talking about?
What stain?
HIKARU: This one.
-Show me.
HIKARU: Right here.
-Huh?
There's nothing there.
Look.
-It's right here!
SAI (VOICEOVER): You can see it?
-That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
SAI (VOICEOVER):
You can hear me?
You can really hear
what I'm saying!
-I don't see a stain.
-Who-- Who's there?
SAI (VOICEOVER): To the
gods, I offer my gratitude,
for once again, I-- I-- I can
finally return to this world!
But I have to admit, I
was worried at first.
Here was a boy who had
never even picked up
a Go stone, let alone
played the game before.
HIKARU: You really
love Go, don't you?
SAI: Oh yes.
HIKARU: And you really
want to play Go, don't you?
SAI: Yes!
HIKARU: Too bad.
I don't think I'm never
gonna play the game.
[sobbing]
-What's wrong?
-Is he all right?
HIKARU: Aw, couldn't you, you
know, go bother someone else?
-Probably not.
HIKARU: I guess it wouldn't
hurt to play once in awhile.
SAI: So tell me, where
are we gonna be paying Go?
HIKARU: At a Go salon?
Gee, It's like a
nursing home in here.
Hey, there's a kid over there.
Can I play him?
-I know he's your age, but--
-Are you looking for
someone to play against?
SAI (VOICEOVER): That was
when I met Akira Toya.
I believe our meeting
was destined by fate.
So, fate had brought
Akira and Hikaru together.
-Yes!
-3, 4 in the upper right,
17 across, and 4 down.
17, one, two, three, four.
-The way he holds his stones,
he must be a beginner.
SAI (VOICEOVER): By
being with Hikaru,
I was able to battle Akira Toya
for a total of three games.
3, 4 in the lower right.
16, 17.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): 16, 17.
This must be it.
SAI: 3, 16.
-3, 16.
-Now 8, 5.
-8, 5.
Where are you?
There it is.
AKIRA: That's-- that
isn't the best move.
It's not even a good move.
He played it to see
how I'd respond.
It's like he's
testing my strength.
He's measuring my skill.
From a level far above mine.
SAI (VOICEOVER: Akira
Toya was a player
who had amazing
potential, even though he
was the same age as Hikaru.
Then, the following match.
-Have a seat.
-Uh, OK.
(VOICEOVER): Hey, this
crowd doesn't even bug him.
SAI (VOICEOVER): At that
time, I made a decision
to change tactics.
Or is he waiting
for the diagonal?
Very well, then, I shall comply.
The 15, 16 point.
The diagonal.
Now, we shall see.
-I-- resign.
HIKARU: Sai?
SAI: He has conceded.
Akira knows that he
cannot win this game.
-What?
-Although he was scared,
he showed bravery
by confronting me.
Our next battle was not face
to face, but over the internet.
-Excellent move.
He's stronger than anyone
I've ever faced before.
He's put up a wall
in front of me.
But if it's not
Hikaru-- then who's
on the other side of this board?
I won't give up.
There's nothing I can do.
The game is over.
-You're still undefeated.
Phew.
I couldn't tell if that
was actually Akira.
You think it was him?
-It's him.
I'm sure of it.
-How'd he do?
Was he a tough opponent?
Sai?
-Yes.
He played a strong game.
His instincts for the
game are quite developed.
He's a patient opponent, and
doesn't make impulsive moves
when his stones are in danger.
-Hm?
It sounds like he's
gotten a lot better.
-He played well, but I am the
one who has become stronger.
-Huh?
-You too, Hikaru.
You're much stronger now.
-Seriously?
-You've learned a lot.
You spent the entire summer
watching all of my matches.
(VOICEOVER) So,
together Hikaru and I
have learned the modern
game of Go from the battles
with Akira Toya.
Akira has pursued me, and
Hikaru has pursued him.
How could I have
forgotten that other game?
The time I played him at
Hikaru's Go club tournament.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): There is
one thing I'd like to know.
Have I gotten any closer
to catching up to you?
I want to play.
Akira, you've never
stopped chasing after Sai.
Well, now it's time for
me to chase after you.
I've got to catch up to you.
-All right.
13, 4.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
I'll play at 11, 8.
Then how would I follow that up?
-Hikaru, I said 13, 14.
SAI (VOICEOVER): I
have to find out.
Sorry, Sai.
I know Akira's more
skilled than me,
but I'll never know how big that
gap is until I play him myself.
I have to make my move.
[gasp]
-You played 11, 8?
-I'm gonna play now.
SAI (VOICEOVER): That was
the first time I recognized
Hikaru's own ingenuity and
imagination as a player.
He didn't want to be
told where to move.
-Stop messing around!
-What?
What's wrong?
If you keep on chasing
your phantom image of me,
one day I'm gonna
catch up to you.
-Is that so?
Why wait until then?
Why don't we play
a game right now?
SAI (VOICEOVER):
From that day onward,
Hikaru began to forge a
tireless path toward Akira Toya.
In pursuit of him, he became an
Insei, he passed the pro exam,
and he became truly strong.
Hikaru.
-I wanna know your name!
Tell me what's your name.
I need to know
what your name is.
-My name's Hikaru Shindou.
Hope you remember it.
Hikaru Shindou.
SAI (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Now that I think about it,
it was around that time
I stopped playing anyone
other than Hikaru.
Even though there were
plenty of opportunities
to play much stronger players.
Hikaru.
Are you not going to
allow me to play anymore?
Just when I was getting close
to reaching the Divine Move?
Tell me.
I need to know.
Why have I been brought back to
this world to be with Hikaru?
Please answer me!
I've been waiting, but I see
you're not going to tell me.
Hikaru!
-Huh?
-Wake up!
Hurry!
Rise and shine!
It's time to get up!
-What's with all the noise?
It's too early in the morning.
Can't you keep it down?
-It's time to get up
and play a game with me!
-Huh?
Oh, come on.
I haven't even
had breakfast yet.
I don't wanna.
SAI: I'm not taking
that as an excuse!
We have to play.
Otherwise I'm never gonna be
able to achieve the Divine
Move!
You're all I have, Hikaru!
HIKARU: What's
gotten into you, Sai?
Let me go back to sleep.
SAI: No, listen.
I've come to the
conclusion that this
is the only way, so come on.
Come on!
HIKARU: Wake me up
in about an hour.
SAI: Hikaru!
Hey!
Wake up!
HIKARU: Goodnight.
SAI: I need you to play.
Hikaru!
[theme music]
SAI: Hikaru.
These men are selling
fake signatures.
They have no honor.
HIKARU: I believe you, but
what can I do about it?
SAI: Just let me play.
I'll teach them a lesson!
HIKARU: Maybe we should teach
this guy Kurata one, too.
He's bragging like he's
a champion already.
SAI: Just give me
the chance, Hikaru.
HIKARU: Next time,
Kurata Six-Dan.
SAI: I will show my
strength once more!