[theme music]
SAI: Interesting.
This is a good place
for the Hikaru to learn.
I've been his main
opponent for so long now,
but against all
these other players,
his game will gain new strength.
In the game of Go, a mere half
point lead over your opponent
is all it takes to win.
When the match is
even, both players
start the game as equals.
Once you have the slightest
lead, all you have to do
is protect it.
But giving a handicap
to an opponent
can be the equivalent of losing
20 to 30 points of territory.
In that case, your game
must rise to a new level
to steal that territory back.
There's no choice.
You have to go on the offensive.
Once you've developed
that ability,
it can be used during
an even match when
you need to make a comeback.
-Good morning everyone.
-Good morning!
-Oh, here you are.
Well, come on.
Let's get started.
-Huh?
But what about the table fee?
-Oh, don't worry about it.
It's fine.
-Hey, hey.
I guess it's OK.
-What's OK, dear?
-Hm?
Oh, waving the table
fee for the kid.
-Onegai shimasu.
-You bet.
Onegai shimasu.
-Good morning, Toya sensei.
It's good to see you.
-We're very glad
you could make it.
-Thank you for
inviting me today.
MAN: Have you got no respect?
What do you think you're
doing, putting your cup down
on the Go board?
Put it on the table.
-Yes sir.
We're sorry.
-It's so nice to see everyone's
playing each other for fun
even though the festival
hasn't started yet.
-They're only here
because they love to play.
-So, who are the
four people I'm going
to be playing
against this morning?
-One of the city councilors,
his secretary, and two
of his financial supporters.
-Just to let you in
on a little secret,
the councilor's not
very good at go.
I know this is
unusual, but could you
fix the game so he wins?
He can be very difficult
to deal with if he loses.
-The thing is, he's one of the
major sponsors of the festival,
so we need to keep him happy.
He likes to show off by
insisting on a low handicap.
It'll be hard to let him
win, but do what you can.
-I'm sure it'll be fine.
MAN: Hey!
Why was there no one
to meet me at the door?
-Oh, sir.
Please forgive me.
I had no idea you'd be
arriving this early.
-I came early because I wanted
to see Ms. Chieko Sakurano.
Perhaps you can tell
me where she is.
-I'm sorry, there's
been a change of plan.
Ms. Sakurano couldn't
make it today.
-What's that?
-She only told us at
the very last minute.
We have a replacement.
-Toya Tudon has agreed
to play in her place.
-Toya Tudon?
I'm not gonna play against
some snotty-nosed kid.
-He's one of the rising stars
in the world of Go right now,
and his father is Toya Meijin.
-Hmph.
So he's the son of a champion.
Big deal.
Never mind.
Can you get me some iced tea?
-Yes, sir.
If you'll come this way.
-I'm sorry about that.
-That's OK.
-Now that you know
what he's like,
you can see why we asked
you to lose to him.
-Right.
Let's get this show on the road.
-Hm?
-Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you all for coming.
And now we're ready to begin.
-Onegai shimasu.
-Five stones.
-In that case, I
guess I'll need six.
-And what's your handicap?
Three stones?
-Yes.
I was once told by a
pro in a teaching game
that three was appropriate
for my skill level.
-Well, if you're
playing with three,
then I'm playing with
three, and not a stone more.
-Are you sure three's
going to be enough?
-Yes.
I beat pros all the
time with five stones.
-Very well, then.
Onegai shimasu.
-Onegai shimasu.
MAN: Stop looking so serious.
-Huh?
-Professional Go is
a very social game.
You gotta learn to be
a little friendlier.
MAN: Could you fix
the game so he wins?
AKIRA (VOICEOVER): Four of them.
-Is there something the
matter, Toya Sensei?
-No.
Shall we start the game?
-64 points.
You have finished, haven't you?
-Now it's my turn.
-Do you find it hard
counting points?
-What?
-Don't tell me the boy wonder
here wasn't even counting.
-Of course I was counting.
I know roughly
how much I've got.
-Knowing roughly
isn't very precise.
Next time, try and end in a tie.
I want you to intentionally
end the game in a draw.
-Intentionally?
-That's right, intentionally.
You need to watch
your opponent's moves
and take into
account any handicap
so the game can end in a draw.
It helps if the
game's even, got it?
Once your mid-game
formations are set up,
you'll have to start
calculating what the end game
score will be.
You'll see it's quite difficult.
The situation is going to change
with every move your opponent
makes, so you'll have to keep
readjusting your calculations.
And, since your goal
is an exact draw,
you can't afford to
be even one point off.
To make things harder, it's not
enough to simply end in a draw.
You have to play the
game at your normal pace.
No slowing down to
think too much about it.
-Hikaru!
This sounds like fun!
MAN: One more thing.
-You mean there's more?
-You're not allowed to
play badly on purpose
and then try to make
it up at the end.
You need to play the game
well enough that your opponent
doesn't realize
you're forcing a draw.
-But I do know.
Play your usual game.
This can be a practice run.
-Hikaru, let's do it!
-OK.
MAN: Why don't you give it try?
-All right.
Onegai shimasu.
-Hm.
Playing for an intentional draw?
-If you manage to do it, then
we'll play with two boards.
-Two?
And try and draw both games?
-Aw, come on, Boss.
That's asking too much.
-Then, if you succeed with
two boards, move on to three.
-And if I do that, try four?
-It's easier said than done.
Believe me.
-Boy oh boy, don't let
that head get too big.
-You'll never be able to force
a draw without exact counting.
Let's see how well you do
against Domoto, for starters.
-Oh man.
-Feeling a little
bit nervous, are we?
Imagine what it'll
be like with two.
Next to impossible!
-No it isn't!
Hikaru, you can do it!
You can do it!
AKIRA (VOICEOVER):
After only 10 moves,
I can tell how strong they are.
The two guys on either
side are average players.
Their handicaps are about right.
As I suspected,
this guy's nowhere
near as good he thinks he is.
Now him.
He's the strongest
one of them all, ready
to take full advantage
of any openings.
-(VOICEOVER) You've only
just turned pro this year.
You've probably been
given instructions
to lose to my boss.
I bet this is the last place
you want to be right now.
How does it make
you feel knowing
you've been told to let him win?
But unfortunately,
you have no choice.
You may be just a kid,
but you're still a pro,
so you better make sure it
looks good when you lose.
-I managed to get a draw!
-Well done, Hikaru.
-Atta boy!
-Lay off the hair, would you?
You know, I guess it's not as
hard as I thought it would be.
-You might be interested to know
that every pro I've ever met
can force a draw,
and they can normally
do it 100 times out of 100.
-The boss has a point there.
You know, I said atta boy.
I take it back.
You're an Insei, right?
So it's no big deal if you
force a draw against one.
-Come on.
-All right.
Let's take it to the next level.
-Two boards.
-Great!
That means I can play.
-Hold on a minute.
-Where am I gonna sit?
Domoto, you've already played.
Let me take your place.
-Aw, come on.
MAN: You don't have to be
a strong player, right?
So I could play, too.
-Come on, guys.
I don't care who I play.
-Remember that
against two opponents,
you have to double
the calculations.
It's not going to be easy.
-And against three,
it'll be triple.
I know.
I think I got it.
-You sound fairly
confident about dealing
with two opponents.
But three's going to be
a whole different game.
-Hurry up!
I can't wait to see
you play three at once.
Hikaru!
-Calm down.
I haven't even played two yet.
-Then hurry up and
begin the game.
-Oh, boy.
OK, two boards.
Here I go.
-(VOICEOVER) Even though they've
all got different handicaps,
I seem to be closing the gap.
I'm 15 points behind him, and
10 points behind this one.
If I sacrifice some stones
on the right hand side,
that should be enough here.
But this guy, I'm only six
or seven points behind him.
-Hm?
(VOICEOVER) Why is he
looking so serious?
He seems to be focusing all
his attention on my board.
He's going all out against me.
I can see it in his eyes
He's not holding back.
Oh, now I get it.
He has no choice but
to let my boss win,
so he's going to make it up by
trying to beat the rest of us.
The other two won't be a problem
for him, but I'm no pushover.
That's why he's decided
to concentrate on his game
with me.
It seems being forced to
lose really annoys him.
Now that I've
figured it out, I'm
going to do all I can to
beat him, and humiliate him.
Yeah.
The son of the Meijin.
-Young Toya is very impressive.
He's the same age
as my grandson,
but there's a world of
difference between them.
-I'm a bit concerned he's
going to be too good.
our guests came here
for a teaching game,
and they won't appreciate it if
he decides to really beat them.
-I'm sure he knows
better than to do that.
Remember, he is a professional.
-Yes, I know but,
I'm still worried.
(VOICEOVER) I'll let him
get two points closer
by forcing him to
attack and capture.
Here I can gain four points
with a reverse sentei,
and here -- I've got every
move figured out right
through to the endgame.
If I play it right, everything
should go as planned.
But he's not gonna
let me do that.
I'll have to adjust
my plans each time.
Adjust.
OK.
And with that last move
of his, the game is over.
-There's nowhere else to go.
-Nope.
(VOICEOVER) It looks
like I've lost.
No.
I've won.
AKIRA: Black, 63 points.
-White, 63 points.
It's a draw?
-I did it!
Both games finished in a tie.
-Why, you-- I guess you're
not an Insei for nothin'.
-Stop doing that.
I hate it!
-So now he'll play three games,
and I get to be in one of them?
-No.
You're not going to do that.
-Oh, and why not?
-Because I'm the one
who's gonna be playing.
-Who says?
No way!
That not fair, Soga.
-Life's not fair.
You just be patient
and wait your turn.
-Hikaru, this is
so much fun. you'll
be playing against four next.
Imagine.
-Give e a break.
I haven't even played three yet.
-And here, you went for
atari on these two stones
too soon, which meant white
was able to secure territory
in the center of the board.
Except for those
couple of things,
you played a really good game.
-(VOICEOVER) In the end,
he failed to beat me.
But the other games should
be no problem for him.
He's still got that look
of intense concentration.
What's going on?
-Oh.
Look, it's a draw.
-Hm?
-Well, I was really close
to winning the game.
Bet you didn't expect to lose
those four stones I took,
did you?
-You're right.
When you made that
move, I thought
you were going to return
here with another move.
-(VOICEOVER) A draw?
Again?
Could he have done
it intentionally?
There was nothing in my game
that was out of the ordinary.
In fact, it should have been
difficult for Toya to beat me.
I was told a three stone
handicap in a one on one match
should be enough.
But for him to do it
while playing four games
simultaneously, and still
finish the game with a draw?
It's impossible!
It has to be a coincidence.
-So, that's 20, plus 20
is 40 My total is 77.
You've got 77, too?
A draw?
-Huh?
-Aw!
All I needed was one more
point and I would have won.
And there was me thinking I'd
played a pretty good game,
gave even if I say so myself.
-Don't tell me your game
ended in a draw, too?
-You mean he tied against you?
I hope you're not suggesting
you're as good as me.
I started with a
handicap of three.
You started with six.
-No, no, no, no.
I just thought it was a
bit unusual, that's all.
-Unusual or not, from
now on when I play a pro,
I can reduce my handicap
to three stones.
[laughter] Oh, I nearly forgot.
Your handicap was three.
How did you do?
-Ended in a draw.
-Oh, dear.
That's just so-- what?
-An interesting coincidence.
-Coincidence?
-Let's see.
It looks like you caught
up in the endgame.
Let me check and see
if I've got anymore.
I think gonna be close.
Now, 10, 20-- oh, no.
It's a draw.
Too bad.
I thought I stood a
chance of winning there.
What?
What's the matter with you guys?
-All four of us?
Do you think something so
unusual could possibly be-- no,
no, it couldn't.
Or could it?
Could someone really
do something like that?
I just can't figure it out.
I mean, I played the
way I always play.
No different.
Ah!
-Let's back up and go through
the game from the first move.
When you're ready.
-We hope you're not
too angry with us
about what happened in there.
-Don't worry about it.
It's fine.
I think they were more
amazed than angry.
Between you and me, it's not
a bad thing for the counselor
to be humbled
every now and then.
-Hm.
I'm very sorry.
-Well, I hope you
learned your lesson
from all this,
young master Toya.
If you have to make
a point, try and be
a bit more subtle about it.
-Yes, sir.
COUNSELOR: I can't wait to
tell everybody I played a pro
and got a draw, with only
a three stone handicap.
MAN: Oh, yes, sir.
MAN: Well, sir, perhaps I
could challenge you to a game
sometime.
COUNSELOR: I think I've had
my fill of Go for a while.
MAN: You know what?
COUNSELOR: What?
MAN: Those pro players
are quite impressive.
-Hey, Toya.
There you are.
-Mr. Ashiwara.
-What's this I hear
about you playing
four boards simultaneously
this morning?
-It was nothing.
-Nothing?
Yeah, right.
What were you thinking?
-Well, they needed
a replacement.
So when they asked
me, I said I'd do it.
-You just don't get it!
There's no reason
for you to be wasting
your talents in a
place like this.
You should be concentrating
on your Dan promotion matches.
And you know the
Honinbo tournament
prelims have started.
If you advance in
those, then you're
going to have to be ready
to play in a lot of games,
so you shouldn't be
putting your energy
into festivals like this.
You'll tire yourself out for
the important matches ahead.
Has something been
bothering you recently?
-No, not really.
I'm fine, thanks.
-OK.
If you say so.
But I'm afraid I
don't believe you.
I've been watching you, and
you seemed a little preoccupied
lately.
Like you've got something
big on your mind.
-Oh, really?
-Relax.
It's not a huge deal.
It's not like you've got someone
chasing after you, is it?
-Maybe.
Now he's passed the
pro exam prelims.
It doesn't matter.
-You're one point away
from a draw on my board.
-Just one point?
-One measly point.
But that's all it takes to fail.
Too bad.
-Well, if you just kept
your big mouth shut!
-Are you trying to blame
me for the fact you failed?
-Yes I am!
-Why you--
WOMAN: I know he only
missed out by one point,
but he did manage to draw
on the other three boards.
Isn't that good enough?
-Plenty good enough, I'd say.
In all my years
running this place,
I've never seen anyone improve
as much as this kid has,
and he's done it right
in front of our eyes.
-All right.
That's enough of that.
Let's have another game!
-Wha--
-How about a draw
on all four boards?
-Oh well.
Guess we'll have to keep
playing until he does it.
-Mm-hm.
Onegai shimasu.
[theme music]
HIKARU: A new player
on the scene, huh?
SAI: And he's from Korea.
Just imagine!
People travelling from all over
the world to play Go with us!
HIKARU: He's sure got
an attitude problem.
I wonder why.
SAI: Try not to antagonize him.
HIKARU: Next time,
Only One Can Win.
SAI: We know very little
about this opponent, Hikaru.
Beware.