NARRATOR: After many
years inside a Go board,
a spirit from the past
known as Fujiwara-no-Sai
has returned, visible
only to Hikaru Shindou.
A master of Go, Sai seeks
to play the Divine Move.
[theme music]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I want to be
able to play a stone like that!
-Hikaru!
-S-Sai?
Did you just take
control of my hand?
-Come back!
-I guess I'm to blame.
I'm the one who found him on the
street and dragged him up here.
MAN: Well, is he good?
KOYO: There was nothing
wrong with his strategy.
He had good, solid moves.
As good as a pro, in fact.
MAN: So it wasn't just luck.
KOYO: Keep in mind, I only
saw him play a few stones.
I don't know how strong
a player he really is.
-I see.
-There was one thing.
-And what was that, sensei?
-It's nothing.
That last move he
made was interesting.
Taken for what it was,
it was a bad move,
but there was
something about it.
-You went too far!
You took control of
my body, didn't you?
You're inside my head, but
that's not enough for you,
is it?
No, you had to take control.
I can't place a
stone down like that!
-No!
You're mistaken.
I can do no such thing.
And even if I could, I wouldn't.
-You're saying I put
that stone down myself?
SAI: That's right.
HIKARU: Stop lying.
SAI: Look.
Try it again with this pebble.
Hold it in your fingers.
-OK, like this?
SAI: Yes.
-I'm gonna snap it down!
See, I told you
I couldn't do it.
SAI: But Hikaru.
You really did play
that stone on your own.
You didn't even place
it where I told you to.
HIKARU: Sounds like an excuse.
I was just sitting there,
and you took over my body.
SAI: Fine, then.
Go ahead and think
that, if you want.
But Hikaru, you were the
one who made that move.
You're becoming more
familiar with the game,
and you want to start
playing on your own.
It's undeniable.
-You know, Akira's dad
sure plays the game
with a lot of style.
Akira's been learning
from him for a long time.
Me?
I can't even hold
the stone right.
What a difference, huh?
SAI: Hikaru.
Try it once more,
with this pebble.
-Will you forget it?
I'm not the one
who did it, anyway.
-Hikaru.
-Hey, Akari.
-I just came from your
house, and you weren't there.
What have you been
doing all this time?
-I've been playing Go.
-Go?
Again?
You must really like it, 'cause
you've been playing it a lot.
-Go is stupid.
I don't like it one bit.
-Oh.
Here.
-Huh?
-My sister gave them to me.
Her junior high's
putting on a festival.
Wanna go?
-Naw.
-Oh, why not?
It's gonna be a lot of fun, and
we get to eat free takoyaki.
HIKARU: That's OK.
-I'll meet you in front of Haze
Junior High at 2:00 on Sunday.
HIKARU: Do whatever you want!
AKARI: Hikaru!
HIKARU: You know,
I think I'll have
ramen when I get home tonight.
AKARI: Just be
there at 2:00, OK?
[barking]
-Hikaru, why don't you go?
-Oh, please.
If anyone sees me walking
around a festival with a girl,
I'll never hear the end of it.
-I think that young
woman is fond of you.
-That's exactly what
I'm talking about, Sai.
Show up at 2:00, Hikaru.
She stood me up!
SAI: Is this a festival?
Like at a temple school?
-Yeah, yeah.
I guess something like that.
I mean, usually
they're a lot of time,
except for today I didn't
bring any money with me.
-Here!
I've got some takoyaki.
-I could sure go for
some of that right now.
-Hikaru, look over there.
-Huh?
-They're playing Go.
Can we go over there?
Can we, can we, can we?
-OK, but just for
a little while.
TSUTSUI: All right.
Here's an intermediate problem.
You have to solve
it in three moves.
-First black attaches right
here, then white goes here.
-OK.
But how about if
white goes here?
-Oh, it was right
there in front of me.
Wow, that was really
difficult, son.
-Hikaru, what is that book?
-Huh?
-The Go Matches of Toya Meijin.
-It's the grand prize if you
can solve all the problems.
Would you like to sit
down and give it a shot?
-Hikaru, I want it, I want it!
-All right, already!
Now get off me!
-Have a seat.
-OK.
Thanks.
-What grade are you in?
-Me?
Oh, I'm in the sixth grade.
-Then let's start
with a simple one.
Here.
Try this.
-You know, I think I
can solve this one.
Don't help me, OK, Sai?
-I won't.
-Mm-hm.
[applause]
-Here's your prize.
HIKARU: What?
Pocket tissue.
I want you to give
me a harder problem.
-Oh, an overachiever?
Can you handle it?
HIKARU: You're up, Sai.
-SAI: I'm ready.
-This one's for a
Dan level player.
Even I'd have problems
with this one.
Solve it in three moves.
Huh?
-No way!
TSUTSUI: You got it.
MAN: That was quick.
MAN: It was instantaneous.
TSUTSUI: You've won
an orange juice.
-Look, I want that book, so gve
me the hardest one you've got.
-Whoa, you want the
hardest one in the book?
OK, then.
If you can solve this one, then
you're at Akira Toya's level.
-Did you say Akira Toya?
I know him.
Is he supposed to be
a pretty good player?
-Oh, yeah.
He's probably good enough
to take the test to go pro.
He likes to play teaching
games for adults,
so that should give you
an idea of how good he is.
Akira Toya might be able
to solve this problem.
Here you go.
The first move is the key.
-Akira would be able
to solve this one.
Hm.
Let's see.
SAI: Do you want
to try it yourself?
-Huh?
-The first move goes here.
-What's the big idea?
-Heh.
Go's a game for losers.
That's what I think
of Akira Toya, too.
Know why? 'Cause I've
already beaten him at Go.
Ha ha!
Shogi is a thousand
times better.
Heh, heh, heh.
-Akira's as good as a pro.
How could someone
like you beat him?
-'Cause I'm better than him.
You moron.
-His name is Tetsuo Kaga.
He used to be in the same
Go class as Akira Toya.
SAI: That boy just solved
a rather difficult problem
with ease.
Who is he?
-Hey, Tsutsui, have you
been able to get your Go
club off the ground yet?
Or are you still pretty
desperate for members?
You know, I could join if
you made it worth my while.
-A Go club?
-Oh, yeah.
I've been talking to
the school about it.
But there's no club yet.
We only need three members.
Then they'll recognize
us as a cloud
and let us enter tournaments.
-You know, I'm
awesome at this game.
I'm about 1,000 times
better than you.
-I do not want the
help of a guy who
would do something gross
like stick gum on a Go board.
-That's funny.
The other day you
were begging me
to join your club so you could
play in the team tournament.
-Take it.
Just take your stupid
prize and get out of here.
-The Go Matches of Toya Meijin?
I told you, I hate Akira
Toya, and I hate Go, too!
I hate them!
-Hate him?
What did Akira ever do
to you, you big jerk?
-You want to know my reasons?
You givin' me attitude?
Time for a lesson.
This is what happens to
punks with big mouths.
I like your guts.
Watch my hands.
Choose a hand.
Pick the right one, and I'll
tell you the whole story.
But if you don't, I'll make
you wish you'd never been born.
-Stop playing around, Tetsuo.
Go on.
Just go home.
-Just like I figured.
A big talker with
nothing to back it up.
SAI: Hikaru, don't do it.
He's a player.
He likes challenges.
Settle your differences with Go.
He will leave you alone after
I've soundly defeated him.
-There's no
guarantee you'll win.
You just said he's a player.
Well, you know what?
I can play, too.
SAI: Wait.
-This one.
-Hikaru!
-Huh?
-I was right about you, kid.
You got guts.
HIKARU: There's no stone!
TSUTSUI: You're a jerk, Kaga.
-I love playing this joke.
The look on your face
was so priceless.
Forget about Go.
It's a lame game.
Come and join the Shogi club.
I'll teach you
everything I know.
-Just shut up!
I'd rather die than
learn Shogi, especially
from a big creep like you.
TETSUO: What?
TSUTSUI: Stop it, you two!
-You say you Akira?
I bet you cheated,
just like you did now.
Either that, or he felt sorry
for you, and he let you win.
You probably started
playing Shogi
after you ran away from Go.
TETSUO: Tsutsui, let him go!
Now you've gone too far!
I'll show you what I can do.
I'm the best!
If I lose, I'll get down
on my knees and apologize.
But if you lose, you have to
jump into a freezing pool!
-Fine by me.
Let's go!
-Three, four point in
the upper right corner.
-That is such a lame
way to hold a stone.
-Never mind how I hold
my stone, you jerk!
SAI: Enclose the corner.
TETSUO: You're going to regret
that attitude when I beat you,
kid.
Smart-mouthed kid.
He doesn't know what
I had to go through.
No one does.
MAN: Tetsuo!
Tetsuo, come here.
Why can't you beat that boy?
You know who.
Akira Toya.
You're always
second best to him.
You're two years older.
You should be ashamed.
-I really do try to win, Dad.
But Akira's too good.
-Win today, or else.
I won't tolerate
losers in my house!
What can I do?
You're better than me, and
that's all there is to it.
You're the best player in here.
In fact, you play Go
better than anyone.
And one day, I'll
beat you, and I'll
go from being number two to
number one just like that.
Keep an eye out for me, OK?
You ready?
Let's get started.
-Should I, uh, let you win one?
-What?
Lose on purpose?
Don't treat me like
a nobody Don't you
dare treat me like a nobody.
I'd always thought
of him as a rival.
But he didn't think
anything of me.
It didn't even matter
if he won or lost to me.
After we counted the
Komi, I realized I'd won.
But the game had
been ruined for me.
My father gave up on
me once he realized
I'd never be the best as
long as Akira was around.
I'm not a nobody.
Know what?
This kid-- he's pretty good.
TSUTSUI (VOICEOVER): Wow.
This guy can really play.
TETSUO (VOICEOVER): Hey.
What's going on here?
He's got me playing on the run.
SAI: 11, 15.
Atari.
11, 14.
Connect.
What a delight.
Though this boy is
not at Akira's level,
he plays the most interesting
counters to my every move.
I could easily
finish him off, but I
want to savor the
pleasure of this game.
TSUTSUI (VOICEOVER): Black
is taking a risk here.
It might turn out OK,
but he has to be careful.
The shape is about even.
No-- it favors black.
-9, 19 point.
-Really?
No way.
-Akari?
-He's gonna lose it.
He just--
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I
guess she did show up.
TETUSO: Hurry up and play!
-Huh?
Sorry.
-Hikaru, not that spot!
-Wait!
Hold it!
TETSU: Hold it?
You're kidding, right?
-Oh, no.
They've all been captured.
SAI: It can't be helped now.
12, 15, atari.
-I'd say that last move just
cost you the whole game.
-Get outta here.
All those stones?
-Well, you want to give up now?
Boy, that freezing pool's
gonna cool you down.
-No-- I--
[theme music]
HIKARU: Sai!
You told me we could win.
TETSUO: Tsutsui,
looks like we now
have the members for
the Go tournament team.
SAI: I think I understand now
why I was drawn to Hikaru.
Once you've placed a
stone, it cannot be moved.
Every move is crucial.