[music playing]
[theme music]
-Thank goodness.
I shouldn't be so surprised
he made a mistake.
It's not like I'm playing Koyo
Toya, or Kuwabara, or anyone
like that.
This is a kid who
only just turned pro.
[gasp] Then again,
this is the first time
Shindo's ever
played one-color Go.
I can see that Akira Toya
isn't the only one coming up
from the lower ranks that
I need to watch out for.
There's someone else now.
-[gasp] Toya Meijin is retiring?
What are they talking about?
I can't believe it.
He wouldn't, not out of the
blue like that, not him.
-As head of his
support organization,
Toya did call to apologize
for not letting me know.
It came as a complete surprise.
I have arranged a
press conference
to give you more details.
All I can say at the
moment is that he
said was for personal reasons.
-Ms. Ichikawa.
-I know.
I'm just as shocked as you.
-He's left us no choice.
We're going to have
to call an emergency
meeting of the directors.
We've got one of the major
championship sponsors
on the line.
[phone ringing]
-Do you think there's
something wrong his health?
-Well, that's it.
I'm going to go
find out for myself.
-He can't retire, not yet.
How can I take one of his titles
away from him if he's retired?
-This retirement
has nothing to do
with him losing
the 2-dan series.
If losing a title meant you
had to consider retiring,
then I would have to give
up as well, after the Oza
crown was snatched from me.
-When we played that last
game of the 2-dan series,
I felt as though I was
seeing a new side of Toya.
He had such a different energy.
So why on earth would he retire?
Why now?
-How are we organize
the championships
without a title holder?
-Maybe the challenger should
just win the title by default.
-No, we should hold
playoffs to fill
the other spot of
the championships.
We could have a five or
seven game playoff series.
-I heard this rumor Toya Meijin
lost to some amateur player
on the internet.
So I got my hands
on the game record.
And boy, was I ever surprised.
It was a fantastic game.
Without a doubt, these were
two top players battling it out
for the board.
All this talk of
him being depressed
about losing to an amateur
called Sai is pure bunk.
None of it's true.
But the one thing that's
bugging me is we've
still got no idea which pro
is using the same Sai when
he plays online.
Well, better not stay
chatting all day.
Gotta run.
Can't miss the bullet train.
My wife would be angry if I was
late for the memorial ceremony
her family's having.
-Early retirement?
How could you do such a
selfish thing, Koyo Toya?
-I wonder if you can help me.
My name's Akiro Toya.
I'm looking for the match room.
-Glad you made it.
I'll show you the way.
-Ah, Toya, you're here.
We heard the news about
your father's retirement.
Everyone here's very worried.
We knew he was
sick, and wondered
if that was the reason for
his decision to quit playing.
How's he doing?
-Oh, there's nothing
wrong with his health.
He's fine.
But thanks for your concern.
MIYAMATSU: Oh, that's a relief.
The information
we get here isn't
very reliable at
the best of times.
There's another
rumor going around
that he hasn't even told
you why he's retiring.
Is that true?
-Yes, I don't think he told
anyone, not even my mother.
But she did tell me
something interesting.
-Akira, there's no
reason for any of us
to be worried about your father.
Just look at him.
If he wasn't so sure that this
was the right thing to do,
he wouldn't be so at
peace with himself.
-But he's going to miss playing
all those matches, won't he?
-I don't think so.
There are always people
coming around our place who
want to play him.
That's not going to change.
-Oh.
-Follow me.
-His fans are going to miss him.
Does he realize how disappointed
they're going to be?
-It's no good trying to
persuade him to change his mind.
I guess it's now going to be
up to me to take his place.
-Oh.
-The match room's up the
stairs, and on the right.
,
but he's the holder of four
titles.
Yet he seems so sure of himself.
That kid's going
to go a long way.
-You'll be sitting here.
-Well, Akira, Hi.
-Uh, Ichirayu Sensei,
what are you doing here?
-I was about to ask you
the very same thing.
I have to admit,
this isn't somewhere
I'd normally visit to play Go.
My in-laws live here in Nagoya.
They're having this
big memorial ceremony,
so I thought I'd check
out the local scene
while I was in town.
Did they put you
up in some hotel?
It wasn't too bad, huh?
-It was fine.
-And how's the
former Meijin doing?
-When I left, he was playing go.
Morishita Sensei
and Okuba Sensei
had dropped by the
house for a visit.
-I had no idea Okuba
Sensei knew your father.
What about Kurata,
seen anything of him?
-Yes.
-Ichiryu Sensei.
-If it isn't Miyamatsu!
How have you been doing?
MIYAMATSU: I'm good, thank you.
What brings a player of
your stature out this way?
ICHIRAYU SENSEI: Well, I've
come to cheer you on, of course.
Why else?
MIYAMATSU: Come
on, you're joking.
[music playing]
KURATA: Thank you very
much for the game.
KOYO TOYA: Thank you
very much for the game.
-Something has been bugging me.
You say you can continue
playing Go after you've retired.
But I don't see how it
can possibly be the same.
I mean, aren't there aspects
of the game that can only
be developed when
you're fighting
to win a championship title?
-Kurata, that may be
true for younger pros,
such as you and Akira.
There's certainly a lot you can
learn from competitive play.
But in my case, it's different.
I'm glad to free myself
from all the obligations
that come with
playing at my level.
I don't have to spend
days on the road just
to go and play a game.
My time is my own again.
--[laughing] So now you
can sit back, relax,
and have everyone come to play
you in the comfort of your own
home, just like I did today?
I'd love to come again.
That is, if you'd let me.
-By all means.
You're welcome any time.
-Mr. Kurata, I learned a lot
from watching you play today.
Thank you.
I'm going to work hard
on my game with you
and Mr. Ogata as my targets.
I know I lost to you in the
second round of the Meijin
Series qualifiers.
But I'm going to work
hard, so that one day I
can avenge that loss.
-You're always setting your
sights on players above you.
Maybe you should
pay more attention
to who's coming up from below.
-From below?
-There's someone else
you should worry about.
And he's right behind you.
There are only two
young pros out there
who I feel threatened by.
You're one of them.
And the other's Hikaru Shindo.
-[gasp]
-You've probably
never heard of him,
because you're so focused on
us guys who are above you.
Well, to be honest, if
I hadn't have bumped
into him at some event
I was at, I probably
wouldn't have
noticed him either.
But then I got a chance
to play him myself.
-Shindo.
-I suggest you
keep an eye on him.
-Shindo.
(THINKING) Even
players like Mr. Kurata
have started to notice him.
If only I didn't have
to be here in Nagoya.
I'd be able to watch
him play in Tokyo.
Shindo.
-I don't understand
why he's retiring.
Didn't he earn, like, hundreds
of millions this year?
-Yeah, so?
-Even if you're set
for life financially,
you don't just give up the game.
MALE SPEAKER: No.
-Do you know which
opponent you've got today?
-Some new kid, called Shindo.
He won his first round
match by default.
So this will be his first game.
-How come?
-His opponent never showed.
He was scheduled
to play Akira Toya,
but that was the morning
Toya's sensei collapsed.
-Oh yeah?
So this really is the first
time he'll play a game as a pro.
The kid's going to be a nervous
wreck today, don't you think?
Oh, hey.
How you doing?
-Morning.
-(THINKING) The records
from last year Young Lions
tournament said that he lost
in the first round to Murakami.
And he didn't do so well in
the Shinshu-dan Series, either.
-Uh, good morning.
Nice to meet you.
-(THINKING) because this is his
first time playing in a major
tournament, he's
bound to be nervous.
As a 3-dan, I can't
afford to lose to him.
[music playing]
-(THINKING) The board's 19
by 19, just like normal.
But somehow it seems smaller.
It's weird.
But I've got a feeling that
I'm not going to lose this one.
-(THINKING) Hikaru is starting
on the path to the divine move.
[buzzer]
FUJIWARA-NO-SAI: (THINKING)
It won't be me that finds it.
It'll be Hikaru.
The destiny set by the spirtis
of Go can not be changed.
[music playing]
-(THINKING) This is
a difficult game.
Actually, he's
making it difficult.
I've got to change the momentum
of the game, or I'm dead.
Get the momentum.
Ah, I think I might have
overplayed the top side.
Black's attacking, and gaining
ground while he does it.
It's no good.
I've got to make some
eyes on the board,
even if it means I
have to overplay later.
The important thing
is to hang in there.
-(THINKING) Making eyes
isn't going to save him.
While he's spending
moves on that,
I'll build myself a huge lead.
[music playing]
-(THINKING) Not good enough.
-(THINKING) Whoa.
I managed to connect his plan.
But now he started
going on the offensive,
attacking my other positions.
I could be in trouble here.
The only area on the board
where I can regain some ground
is over on the left hand side.
I have no choice
but to go for it.
[music playing]
-(THINKING) Hikaru's
really coming into his own.
This is it.
--[sigh] (THINKING) I admit my
attacks are pretty reckless.
All he needs to do
is defend himself.
But he's not even trying.
He's going for the
counter attack instead.
-(THINKING) I had no idea
he'd improve this much.
-I resign.
-Thank you very
much for the game.
(THINKING) I wonder how
Shindo did in his game.
-Ishihara, you were
playing Akira Toya.
How'd it go?
--[sigh] I'm never
going to beat that guy.
-What?
ISHIHARA: No matter how
hard I study the game,
I'll never beat him,
as long as I live.
AKIRA TOYA: (THINKING) I
haven't figured it out yet.
But that whole thing with
Sai got me wondering.
Shindo, why did you
appear in my life?
Why do I feel like I
have to pursue you?
And why do you keep pursuing me?
Why?
-So, what did you
think of my game today?
I'm totally on a roll.
That guy wouldn't
resign, when it
was obvious he
was going to lose.
He was so stubborn.
He kept playing, and playing.
He probably went into
the game thinking
there was no way he could
lose to a kid like me.
This isn't right.
Huh?
Hey, what's up.
It's your turn.
-What did you think you were
doing with this move here?
You have the audacity to
think you're such a big shot
when you're making
moves as bad as this.
-So it wasn't the greatest
move in the world.
Fine, OK.
But you don't need
to get all mad.
-You're not a strong enough
player to defeat me yet,
Hikaru.
-Hmph.
Yeah, says who?
--[wimpering] You're not strong
enough to defeat me yet,
Hikaru.
Please, it can't end here, not
until I know you can defeat me.
-Hey, you can't even pick
up a stone without me around
to help you, let alone play Go.
Sorry.
Come on, let's play.
Sai?
Fine.
-All right, then.
Let's continue.
-Just forget it.
You're the one who quit playing
in the first place, not me.
-Hikaru, no!
-(THINKING) I don't
know what's bugging him.
But I've had enough of it.
Burglars broke into
grandpa's house last night?
-Yes, I just finished
speaking to him on the phone.
Grandpa said there's
nothing to worry about.
He and grandma are OK.
But a load of stuff
from the attic is gone.
-Huh?
-Hikaru, the Go
board, do you think
the Go board is still there?
-You mean the one released
you from after 140 years?
-That one?
-It gave me the creeps, all
those blood stains on it.
But I guess the board
means something to you,
because it reminds you of the
time you spent with Torajiro.
-We need to go and check.
Please.
-(THINKING) What's up with him?
Last night he was all grouchy,
and itching for a fight.
And now look him.
[sigh] Oh well.
The Go board's still here?
It wasn't stolen?
GRANDPA: That old thing?
No, no, no.
They went for stuff
they could sell.
You name it, they took it.
But it's good to see you.
I appreciate that you
were concerned enough
to come around.
It's been a while.
-Dad said he didn't know why
I was so worried, because you
only had a load of junk in here.
-Oh, he did, did he?
-Yep.
-Really, just like
your grandmother.
She's been trying to get me to
clear this place up for years,
says the robbers have just
given me a head start.
-Here it is.
That's weird.
-[sigh]
-(THINKING) Is it
my imagination,
or has the stain started to
disappear since last time I saw
it?
[music playing]
-Why has Hikaru been
chosen, and not me?
Tell me, spirits of Go?
Why?
Once I disappear, only
you will remain, Hikaru.
-What are you talking about?
You're not going anywhere.
Ogata wants to
challenge you to a game.
-I'd rather spend
the little time
I have left playing against you.
Next time, farewell, Hikaru.
-I'm sorry, Hikaru.
But I will be leaving soon.