[theme music]
ASUMI: Shindou?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Not now, Asumi.
-I heard you haven't been
going to any classes or games.
Waya's really worried about you.
Hey, wait, Shindou!
What's wrong with him?
MAN: He's quit being a pro?
-Yes.
-You're sure it's Hikaru
we're talking about?
-Yes.
-I can't believe
he'd stop playing.
It just doesn't seem possible.
He put an incredible
amount of effort
into passing the
pro exam last year.
He was so committed.
At least that's what I was
told by his previous teacher.
-Mm-hm.
-Did Hikaru actually tell
you he was going to quit?
-Oh, no, no.
But he's been
skipping his matches.
He hasn't been playing at all.
-Not been playing?
-No.
There were a couple of games
back in April that he went.
Now they keep sending
him reminders,
but he doesn't
even look at them.
He hasn't been to a
single game since then.
-I remember that he took
some time off and went out
of town right
around Golden Week.
When he later told me that
he'd gone to Hiroshima,
I thought it was
something Go related.
But he didn't play
any matches there?
-That's right.
-I had no idea he
was skipping games.
His attendance record at
school has been excellent,
so I just assumed
everything was OK with him.
Look, I'm sorry.
I don't really follow Go.
Otherwise I would have realized.
When you're a teacher
and your student
comes to school in
his work, you don't
tend to worry
about his progress.
Well, has he said
anything to you about it?
-Not a thing.
I've tried asking him
about it, but he just
won't tell me what's going on.
But he's changed.
He used to be full of energy.
Sometimes he was so cheerful,
it was almost annoying!
I'm sure that he has
a lot on his mind
now that he's become
a professional,
and that's why my
husband and I decided
we shouldn't interfere too much.
We'd leave him alone
and see how things went.
But it's been going
on for so long,
we just don't know what to do.
-Don't worry about it.
I'll look into it and
see what I can find out.
AKARI: Hikaru!
-What's going on, Akari?
-Hikaru.
I think you owe
me an explanation.
-Hm?
"Go Weekly?"
Since when have you
been reading that?
-Since Koike gave it to me.
There's something here
I don't understand.
You know they do a
list of all the results
of the professional Go games?
By your name it says
lost by default.
-I told you I wasn't
playing anymore, didn't I?
-What?
You were talking about
playing me, weren't you?
You thought I wasn't good
enough for you now you're a pro!
You're serious about
this, aren't you?
Are you gonna quit being a pro?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): If
Sai never comes back.
It's possible.
I'm thinking about it.
-You selfish jerk.
AKARI: Oh no.
Mitani.
-I don't know what the heck
is going on with you, Shindou,
but you left the Go club
so you could become a pro.
-You're not gonna be a
pro, what are you gonna do?
-Entrance exams
are coming up soon
and I need to study for them.
Akari, what are you
doing after school today?
You want to study with me?
-She doesn't have the
time to study with you.
We got practice
for a tournament!
-Another tournament.
-Oh, it's just another
tournament, huh?
Who do you think you are?
Have you forgotten
how much you wanted
to beat Kaio when you
were part of the Go club?
Back then, it was more than
just another tournament!
-Mitani--
-I'm gonna play in
this next tournament.
Natsume, Koike and me
are gonna challenge Kaio,
and we're going to crush them!
-What?
You never told us
you wanted to play.
Are you sure, Mitani?
-Jealous, Shindou?
As long as I'm in
the club, you're
never gonna play with us again.
We don't need someone like you!
Come on, Akari.
Forget about this loser.
Let's get out of here.
-But Mitani--
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): The school
tournament is coming up again.
I promised Kimihiro I'd help
get his go club started,
so that's what I'm gonna do!
Check it out!
I managed to track down Yuuki!
Listen, Yuuki.
There's this Go tournament
that's coming up pretty soon.
A bunch of middle schools
will be competing.
-What's your point?
-Well, we wanna play this year.
Our goal was to defeat Kaio.
I had to find out.
Sorry, Sai.
I know Akira's more
skilled than me,
but I'll never know how big that
gap is until I play him myself.
Go was the only thing
that mattered to me.
Maybe the next guy you
inhabit will let you play.
-That kid!
He makes me so mad.
What does he think he's doing?
Giving up?
-Calm down.
You got like that last
time you read "Go weekly."
-Were you rooting for
someone and they lost?
-Another game lost by default.
How long is he gonna
keep doing that?
-Hey, Tsubaki, you
finished your lunch yet?
The boss wants to play
a game of Go with you.
-There goes my break.
-Gotta keep the boss happy.
Earn a few brownie points.
-He's such a lousy
player, but if I
don't let him win-- I hate it.
-What's going on?
Is Tsubaki good at
playing Go, or something?
-He must be pretty good.
He took the pro exam last year.
-No way, him?
-I had no idea someone
like that worked here.
Maybe it's time for me to
start taking up that game.
-Look, he made a mess of this.
-How come that copy of "Go
Weekly's" scrunched up?
-If you want an
answer, ask Mr. Kawai.
-Hmph.
-Don't you hmph me!
That paper is here
for everyone to read.
Shindou forfeiting his game
is no excuse to crumple it up.
-Ugh.
-What do you thinks
up with Shindou?
That's a lot of games
he's lost by default now.
-What's the point in
us cheering for him
if he doesn't even play?
-I'm sure he's got a very
good reason for not playing.
Give the boy a chance.
You just need to be a
little more patient.
Really.
You guys give me
such a headache.
-It's all very well
telling us to be patient,
but can't they kick
him out of the pros
is he misses too many games?
-Do you think that's true?
-How am I supposed to know?
-Fukawa, what do you think?
-I guess they could, but
I don't know for sure.
-Kick him out?
Don't say that!
Not after I went all the
way to Hiroshima with him
and paid for his hotel.
That brat!
-Mr. Kawai, please!
-I only just scraped
through that game.
Ochi.
-Hm?
-You finish your game too?
Considering you were
just in the bathroom,
I'm guessing you probably lost.
I mean, we all know how you lock
yourself in one of the stalls
when you lose.
-Actually, this
time I had to go.
In fact, my winning
streak is still intact.
Unlike yours, Waya..
-You're such a nerd.
-Did you hear about Shindou?
The chairman of the Player's
Association, Murota Nine-Dan,
gave him a call.
-Yeah, and?
-He asked Shindou if he was
missing games because he
was sick and offered the chance
to take a leave of absence,
but he didn't even
bother to reply.
-What an idiot.
-Think he'll quit being a pro?
-I don't know.
-Looking at him now, it's hard
to believe he was Toya's rival.
-Having talent is
a waste of time
if you don't put
it into practice.
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): I remember
the school tournament.
That was a lot of fun.
Mitani was our captain,
Kimihiro was our second,
and I was there as number three.
Of course, I was the
worst player on the team.
It was exciting when we beat
Iwata 3-0 in the first round.
I can still remember the
faces of the guys we played.
Sai.
Sai!
GIRL: Hey, Shindou!
You heading home?
-What do you want?
-Well, since you've got
nothing better to do,
you can do a favor for me.
-What do you mean I got
nothing better to do?
-I could be wrong,
but someone who's
been skipping all his games
must have some free time.
-Hmph.
-Come to the Go club
and play Mitani.
-Hm?
Mitani?
-He wants to play in
a tournament so bad,
but he doesn't have
anyone to practice with,
so I thought maybe
you could help.
I'd play him, but
I'm not good enough.
-Sorry, but no.
-No? Why not?
-Kanako.
-Hm?
-I don't want you asking
stupid favors for me.
He's the last person I
want to practice with.
-Yeah, well maybe I wasn't
just asking him for you, OK?
If Shindou plays
against you, that
means I get to play
against Natsume and Koike.
-What's going on?
Kanako?
Mitani?
Hikaru?
-I was just trying to help.
We're all trying to
do our best here.
Otherwise, I
wouldn't have asked.
But if that's how Mitani feels
about it, then nevermind.
I guess it's better for the Go
club to practice without you.
Sorry to bother you.
-Uh, Hikaru.
Listen.
We're playing in the
tournament next Sunday.
At least come and cheer us on!
-We don't need him.
-Hikaru.
-This tournament is what
we've all been dreaming of.
-I don't wanna let anyone down .
-Ugh!
What a terrible game.
I played so bad.
Akari, give me
another chance, OK?
-Sure.
The atmosphere's
so intense in here.
-The boys take it too seriously.
AKARI (VOICEOVER): When
Hikaru was in the Go club,
he used to be like that.
I wonder what happened.
Go was so important to him.
He couldn't have
forgotten how that felt.
-Now that we're
in our third year,
this is the last chance for
us to play in a tournament.
Let's give it all we've got.
-Mm-hm.
All right.
Ready for another game?
-Of course I am.
Mind if I play first?
-OK.
-They've probably
started playing already.
It's OK, Sai.
I won't be playing.
You understand?
I'm just gonna watch.
[heartbeat]
-Hm?
Huh?
There's Akari.
She's sitting in the middle.
That must mean she's
playing in the number two.
Why's she taking
so long to move?
It's a simple life
and death problem.
Don't rush it.
Take your time to
think it through.
Yes!
And there's Mitani.
Huh?
I can't.
I just can't allow
myself to play.
What?
Is that Shindou?
HIKARU (VOICEOVER): If I
start having the urge to play,
and if I start playing
Go again, then Sai
will never come back to me.
That's how I feel.
I can't help it.
[theme music]
HIKARU: Isumi's
come back and he's
determined to meet up with me.
All sorts of people
are wondering
If I'll play again,
because if I don't, Toya'll
get so far ahead of me
I'll never catch up to him.
Even though Isumi played
lots of games in China,
he says there's one more he has
to play, and it's against me.
Next time, A Determined Visitor.