[music playing]
[theme music]
-What about you?
You want to play a game?
-Just who are you, anyway?
-Mr. Shuhei is going
to be representing
Japan in the next world
amateur championship.
He's probably the best
amateur in the country.
-You're not using
any of your time.
You should probably
think about your movies.
Huh?
-He might be playing fast.
But he knows what he's doing.
He's just a kid.
But without a doubt,
you can tell he's a pro.
-[gasp] (THINKING) I set a trap.
But he saw right through
it in the blink of an eye.
-(THINKING) This is amazing.
Shindo's a completely
different player
from when I saw him last year.
How could he have
changed so much?
-(THINKING) Yes!
Whew.
Sai, how'd I do?
-If a ghost is going to
appear anywhere around here,
it'll be in this room.
-[gulp]
-It's at the end of the hallway.
-There's actually
a room down here?
I always thought
it was a dead end.
-Well, there is.
And here we are.
Hope I've got the right key.
You sure you never
knew about this room?
-Mhmm.
[gulp]
-Some light to see
what we're doing.
-[gasp] Oh wow, look at it.
Oh.
What is this place?
There's so many books.
-Yeah.
They're kifu, game
records from long ago.
This room is where we've
been storing all of them.
The [inaudible] is the
oldest one we have.
-All this old stuff.
Is that why you thought there
might be a ghost in here?
--[laughing] Well,
at least we tried.
I guess the ghosts don't
think we're worth haunting.
-Hmm.
-Did you want to have a
look at anything here?
-No thanks.
That's OK.
-You sure, after
coming all this way?
-Oh, OK.
Uh, something by Shusaku.
-Interesting choice.
Now let's see.
Shusaku was from the
[inaudible] period.
Where would that be?
-I can't believe
I've never checked
out any of Shusaku's
game records.
-Really?
You haven't seen
any of them before,
not even the ones
that get published
in modern collections?
You should take a look at
some of the game records
from history.
You might learn something.
Now what's this here?
Ah, here we go.
-Oh!
-Hey, what are you dong?
-Sorry. I'm sorry.
-You've got to be more careful.
These are valuable.
-I know.
I'll leave these here
for you to look at.
HIKARU: Uh, thanks.
-I've got a bit more work to do.
Come get me when
you're finished.
I'm leaving in about 30 minutes.
You'll have to be done by
then, so I can lock up.
-(THINKING) These are the
matches that Sai played.
At least, it was Sai
playing through Torajiro.
-And don't damage any
of these books, OK?
HIKARU: I won't.
(THINKING) I know what kind
of player Sai is today.
But how strong was he back then?
[music playing]
--[gasp] (THINKING) This
move Sai made, it's awesome.
He must have thought about
every possible angle.
It's the kind of move that
would make any opponent give up
the will to fight.
Sai, he was a-- he
was a total genius.
I should have let him play
for me whenever he wanted to.
But no.
I always wanted to
be the one to play.
If only I'd realized before.
Toya would've been
much happier if he'd
been able to play
Sai instead of me.
He was a genius.
And I should have let him
play every single game.
Of course.
That must have been
what Torajiro did.
When Torajiro first met Sai,
he already knew how to play Go.
And he was interested in
becoming a good player.
Because of that, he
could see straight away
how strong Sai was.
That's why he let
Sai play through him.
Oh!
Man, when I started I didn't
know the first thing about Go.
So I had no idea how
much of a genius Sai was.
All I ever thought about
was me wanting to play.
Even when I realized
how good Sai was,
I had to keep on
playing on my own.
I was so selfish.
I was such a fool.
[sobbing]
Sorry, Sai.
[gasp] Oh no.
Why didn't I let Sai play all
the games from the very start?
What an idiot I've been.
Anyone can see it
would have been better
to let him play instead of me.
Every game, every
game, every game.
I don't need to play.
I'll never be so selfish again.
I promise.
Spirits of Go, just
bring him back.
Bring Sai back to back
to me, turn back time
to when we first met.
Let me start over!
[weeping] [wailing]
[music playing]
-Hey, what's up, Toya?
You know, it's almost time
for us to start playing.
-Thanks.
I'll be right there.
(THINKING) Why isn't
Shindo here yet?
-(THINKING) He's
going to be late.
Where is he?
I hope he didn't sleep
through his alarm.
-(THINKING) I was counting
on being able to see him play
today.
Don't tell me he's not
even going to show up.
-(THINKING) looks like Toya's
also wondernig where Shindo is.
The game's about to start.
[ticking]
[buzzer]
[japanese]
TEACHER: The four
examples in front of you
all include sentence modifiers.
These are what affect the
central noun in the phrase.
So let's look more
closely at the differences
between these four sentences.
-(THINKING) Sai,
if you come back,
I'll let you play
every single game.
I promise.
I won't stand in your way.
You can play all you want, just
as long as you come back, Sai.
[music playing]
-Any idea why Shindo isn't here?
-Not a clue.
And it's time to get started.
We can't wait any longer.
-He should have been at the
dan promotion league game
this week.
He didn't show.
-No way.
Is he OK?
-Is he sick, or something?
-I'm sure he would
have phoned to let
them know if he was sick.
He never went to Morashida's
sensei study session, either.
There's something
else going on here.
-Argh!
(THINKING) Shindo.
[church bells]
-What?
Fujiwara-No-Sai doesn't exist?
-I don't know why you're
looking at me like that.
I've done as much
research as I can.
You said he was an aristocrat
who taught the emperor
to play Go in the Heian period.
Well, not according
to my research.
And I even got the boss
to double check it for me.
-That's impossible.
Because I know.
Sai does exist.
-Oh, come on.
How could you know that?
Have you got any
proof to back it up?
-No, OK, maybe it
was wrong of me
to categorically
say he didn't exist.
I guess it would be
more accurate to say
we don't know if
he existed or not.
The point is, we
have no evidence
to say for sure one
way or the other.
-Oh, thank you.
-(THINKING) We don't know
if he existed or not?
Of course he existed.
And I'm the only
one who knows that.
-Hikaru?
[giggling] How are things going?
What were you
talking to Mr. Matsui
about, just a moment ago?
-Nothing important.
-By the way, did
you hear I managed
to reduce my handicap
against Kaneko by one stone?
[giggling] It would be great
to have another game with you
some time.
HIKARU: I'm not
going to play again.
-Oh, don't be such a meanie.
Last time we played, I
learned so much from you.
How's life as a pro?
Is it hard work?
-I told you, I'm never
going to play again.
-Huh?
I suppose we're not good enough
for you now you're a pro.
Is that it?
Forget it.
[music playing]
-(THINKING) No more study
sessions with Morashita Sensei.
And no more visits to Mr.
Kuwai's [inaudible] either.
-See ya later.
-(THINKING) Toya had his
sights set on playing Sai.
But I wanted them set on me.
That was never going to happen.
There's no way I could have
ever reached Sai's level.
Sai, why did you disappear?
-Hey, Waya.
You got things pretty
neat and tidy in here.
-That's easy when you
don't have any stuff.
Man, this place is empty.
-You haven't even got a fridge.
What do you do for food?
You can't eat out all the time.
And how are you going
to do your laundry?
-I'll just take it home.
Mom's going to do it for me.
And I'll probably eat at
home most of the time.
Or I could always go
over to sensei's place.
-You haven't moved out.
The only thing that's
different is where you sleep.
-All I need is a Go
board, and some stones.
-This is awesome.
I wish I could move
out, and live on my own.
-You can stay over any
time you like, Komea,
as long as you bring
snacks with you.
There's going to be a
group of pros coming over
to play every Saturday.
-Oh yeah?
Who's coming over?
-Sayeki, Okada,
Nokayama, guys like that.
-What about Shindo.
-I would have invited him.
But he hasn't been at the Go
association for a while now.
-So what do you think's
happened to him.
-Don't know.
Morishita Sensei is
taking it personally.
And he doesn't want
to see him again.
-Hey, listen, Waya, can I
sit on your Saturday session?
I mean, I know
I'm not a pro yet.
I don't have any other
classes on Saturday.
So it would be cool
if I could come.
-Sure you can come.
You can all come.
-It's OK for Honda and Kumiya..
They're both strong
enough players.
But me, I'm at a
way lower level.
I'd hold you guys back.
-You're never going to improve
with that sort of attitude.
-It's so depressing.
I've got to go through
all the qualifying rounds
for the pro exam.
Riyo's given up being an insei.
So I'm on my own.
I'm beginning to wonder if
I should just call it quits.
Oh, by the way, do
you know what I heard?
A bunch of players from the
Kusekei went on this trip
to China.
They were like goodwill
ambassadors for the Japanese Go
association.
-Oh yeah?
Good for them.
-The interesting thing is that
one of the players on the trip
was Isumi.
-Isumi?
No way.
-Ah, so he did decide to
keep on playing Go after all.
-Hm.
-I guess that means he'll
be taking the pro exam again
next year.
-Of course, he's not
an insei anymore.
So he'll have to go through
all the qualifying rounds
in a couple of months.
-It'll be good to see him.
Maybe we'll get to play him
in some of the later rounds.
-So Isumi went to China.
That's going to be interesting.
[music playing]
-Oh, uh, hi there, Toya.
-I was, uh, looking for Shindo.
Do you know where he is?
-Hikaru?
We're in different classes, so
I don't see him around much.
-If you're looking for
Shindo, he's in the library.
-Oh, that's where he is.
-If you want to
find the library,
go through the front door.
Then head up to
the second floor.
-Thank you.
-You saw Hikaru in the library?
What was he doing in there?
-Nothing much.
To tell you the truth, he
seemed a bit out of it.
-You sure it was Hikaru you saw?
-Uh huh.
-That's not like Hikaru at all.
I hope everything's OK.
-(THINKING) Sai, after he played
that game against Toya Meijin
on the internet, he
seemed to change.
Did something happened to
him that I didn't know about?
-Shindo.
-Hmm?
-[sounds of alarm and surprise]
-Huh?
HIKARU: Toya, what
are you doing here?
I don't believe this.
You come here, and
sneak up me like that?
You almost gave
me a heart attack.
Don't ever do that again, OK?
-Shindo, why didn't you
come to the Young Lions
tournament, or the
dan promotion league?
You didn't show up there either.
-I didn't go because
I'm not good enough.
-Hmm?
What do you mean
you're not good enough?
Of course you are.
-There's no point in me playing
Go anymore, and that's that.
-Hmm?
STUDENT: Would you
keep the noise down?
-I think you're more
than good enough.
-Huh?
Toya?
(THINKING) The only
reason you think
that is because you're
looking at Sai instead of me.
I'm never going to play again.
--[gasp] (SHOUTING)
You can't do that.
You have to play, you hear?
-(THINKING) The one you're
waiting for isn't me.
It's Sai.
But now Sai has disappeared.
I'm sorry.
-Shindo!
-(THINKING) I'm sorry,
Toya, but Sai is gone.
I wish I could let you play him.
But he's gone.
-Shindo, wait.
Have you forgotten
why you became a pro
in the first place?
-(THINKING) Why did you
have to leave me, Sai?
Why?
-You became a pro so
you could play me.
Hey, Shindo!
(THINKING) Shindo.
-Sai!
[music playing]
HIKARU (VOICEOVER):
Next time, we're
going back to when I
was in seventh grade.
There's this girl who's
trying to get back
an expensive bowl that was
stolen from her grandfather.
Me and Sai want to help her out.
We're going to
play a game of Go.
And the winner gets the bowl.
But the owner of the
store says he's a 5-dan.
This won't be an easy match.
Next time, [inaudible]
flower bowls.