-Nowhere left to run, bozo.
ANNOUNCER: Well, folks,
it looks like Blue Rose
has him cornered.
Her cutie escape
move, how classic.
And at the eleventh
hour, the lightning bolt
kung fu master Dragon
Kid makes the arrest.
-Well, there's no questioning
your results, dear,
but you might want to
use a little more flair.
-More flair?
-You know, lay on the charm
a bit, get some buzz going.
-So keep kicking ass but
do it with style, right?
-Would you please
watch your language?
We've been over this a
million times already.
Would it kill you
to be more ladylike?
-What's wrong with how I talk?
-Look, your parents
entrusted you to my care,
and I'm going to
see to it you're
raised like a proper
young woman, all right?
Hey, why don't you
try that clipon?
-I don't wanna.
-Oh, come on now, it's a
gift from your parents.
-I'll do anything else
you ask, all right?
But there's no way I'm
putting that thing on.
[theme music]
-So, how was it?
Did you sleep all right in the
chamber I developed for you?
-Feeling fit as a fiddle.
-Are you still in pain?
-Don't worry, I'm fine.
That palm face bastard's
attack was a joke.
-Actually, your wounds
were quite extensive.
My chamber speeds up healing.
BARNABY BROOKS JR: Well, you've
got endurance, if nothing else.
WILD TIGER: If nothing else?
Did you really have
to tag that on?
-But I just told you
that it was my chamber.
-Tiger, we have an emergency.
Get to the training center ASAP.
-What is it?
-You'll see when you get here.
-He's adorable.
-I could just eat him up.
-Yes.
-Me?
You're kidding, right?
-Afraid not.
-Hey, what's going on?
Who's the kid?
-It's the mayor's son.
He and his wife have last
minute business to attend to
and he wanted Tiger to
keep an eye on the boy.
-Huh?
-Why couldn't they have just
gotten the kid a babysitter?
-There's been a string of
kidnappings lately targeting
children from wealthy families.
The mayor felt safer
leaving his son with a hero.
-What does he think we
are, his personal staff?
-Well, like it or not,
that's your assignment now.
Take care of little Sam, got it?
-Man, how did I get
stuck with baby duty?
BARNABY BROOKS JR: This
is perfect for you.
-Seriously.
-I bet you're going to make
an awesome dad someday.
-Someday?
He already is an awesome dad.
-What are you talking about?
-What?
Didn't I ever tell you?
It's true.
I have a 9-year-old little girl.
-Huh?
-Oh my God, that means
you have a wife, too.
-Actually, we lost her to
illness five years ago.
Aw hell, look, there's no
need to dredge up the past.
Sleeping dogs and all that.
-That makes sense.
Well, at least now
we know why you
were chosen for this assignment.
-Did you have a
good nap little guy?
-What the hell?
-Oh that's right, it
completely slipped my mind.
He's a telekinetic NEXT.
You'll have to be a bit careful.
-Thanks for the head up.
-Get him to stop crying already.
-OK.
Stand back, guys.
I got this.
Who's a big boy?
Sky high.
[baby cries]
-Sky high?
Thanks and thanks again.
-Piece of cake.
Cheer up, little buddy.
Oh no.
Pass.
-No, honey, I don't
do the baby thing.
-But maybe what this situation
needs is a more feminine touch.
-There, there.
You're okay, baby.
Oh no, that's just rude.
-Hey, Blue Rose, how about you?
Okay then.
Forget I asked.
Dragon kid, you give it a go.
-What am I going to do?
You said you needed a girl.
-Hello?
You are a girl.
-Yeah, but I'm not girly.
-Hey, looks like
he's sweet on ya.
-Ni hao.
-So why exactly do
I have to be here?
-You're my secret weapon.
If he starts crying
again, I need you around
to calm him down.
-Why did you bring
him over to my place?
The mayor asked for
you, Papa Bear, not me.
-Ah, come on, we're supposed
to be a team, right?
Besides, I don't want the
kid wrecking any of my stuff.
-But you thought it would
be OK to wreck my things?
-What?
Like your computer?
So a laptop breaks?
Big deal.
He's a scary looking
guy, isn't he?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That's the precious heirloom
you didn't want him to break?
Some boys never grow up do they?
-You collect toys?
-Not exactly.
You see, this was a
gift from my parents.
-Happy birthday.
-Here son.
This is for you.
Happy birthday.
-Cool.
I love it.
Thank you.
-Oh, I see.
Sorry.
I think he wants to get
his hands on your robot.
-Just try to be
careful with it, OK?
-Don't tell a baby that.
Did your mommy pick out
that flower pattern for you?
So cute.
-Huh?
You're kidding right?
-You know, it might not
look too bad on you either.
-Oh please, whatever.
-You'd be cute as a button.
-I don't have any interest
in being cute, OK?
It's funny.
My folks gave me
something just like this
and I couldn't care less.
-Hey, now look.
You've got to understand what
it's like for parents when
they're picking
out a gift for you.
Even if they're
far away, they're
thinking about you
in that moment.
-Who cares?
They don't know the first
thing about my feelings.
-All right, easy now.
Try to keep an open mind,
he does have a point.
You should always treasure the
things your parents give you.
-Sharings not really
your strong suit, is it?
-That one?
-Doesn't smell right.
-Well, on to the next.
-Here I come.
Ugh.
-It was worth putting
you through all
those special classes.
-That's right, you're
the pride of our family.
No, the pride of
the entire country.
-Here Pao-Lin, wear this on your
road to becoming a famous hero.
-OK.
-Dinner's ready.
Come on now.
You're hungry, aren't you?
I'm not giving up that easy.
-Please, no more messes in here.
-Let me take care of this.
-But I went through all
the trouble of making it.
Wait, are these--
-There, there.
That's a good boy.
-Are they out?
-Like a light.
-Today really bummed me out.
It's sad to think
a kid could know
so little about her
parents feelings.
-Are you talking
about Dragon Kid?
-Hard to ignore.
I send stuff to my daughter too.
Can't help but wonder
what my kid thinks of me.
-So, how are your
injuries doing?
-Don't tell me you're
worried all of a sudden.
-Well, the only
reason you got hurt
is that you were
trying to protect me.
-My endurance is
all I've got, right?
-As far as I can tell.
-So, uh, all that
data that popped up,
did you complete
that all on your own?
-Yeah.
-Digging all of this
stuff up by yourself
must have been one hell
of a rough road, huh?
-I've been searching
desperately for 20 years.
I watched my parents
get murdered.
That single day has been
haunting me for my entire life.
-You saw it then?
Did you get a look at
the murderer's face?
-I think I might have,
but I can't remember it.
My memories of that day
are pretty faded by now.
The only thing I can
still see clearly
is the tattoo on his hand.
-Tattoo?
-I've been chasing the
murderer for most of my life,
with only this mark to go on.
And then one day, I
just turn on the news
and there it is staring
me in the face again.
-I hereby sentence the
accused, J.G. Benjamin
to 250 years of
solitary confinement.
Court is adjourned.
-Hold on, that mark, what is it?
I finally found you.
I'm not letting you get away.
-Get back young man.
-Not until he tells me
what those symbols mean.
You know.
Please tell me.
Ouroboros.
-Ouroboros?
What is Ouroboros?
-I had established a
link between this symbol
and some group called
Ouroboros, but the one lead
I had went up in smoke as
the man I stumbled across
went mad in prison
and eventually died.
It's been two
decades, and I still
haven't caught up with
my parents' killer.
If only I could remember
what the bastard looked like.
-Trust me, I get why
you're frustrated,
but maybe you need
to ease off a bit.
You're not going to force
the memories to come back
and racking your brain
like this isn't helping.
I wouldn't worry about it.
You're going to find the guy.
-Hey, hey.
Morning you guys.
It smells like a bar.
What do you say
we go for a walk?
-Oh, I'm in heaven.
Breath it in, sisters, that's
the smell of money in the air.
-This place is teeming
with high society types.
-Get a load of this over here.
-Yeah, sis.
I'd say this one is
ripe for the picking.
[doorbell ringing]
-I shouldn't have
been so careless.
-Oh please, shut up.
I'm trying to get some
friggin' sleep here.
-Miss Agnes.
-Do you know how long I've
been ringing this bell?
-Thanks for going
through all the trouble.
-Well, believe me, I
didn't do it for your sake.
We need to make sure
nothing goes wrong.
This is the mayor's baby.
-Well, we better
not screw it up.
-So where is the baby?
-He's been pretty quiet.
I think he's still sleeping.
-Start talking.
How do we get in touch
with your family?
-And don't even bother giving
us the runaround, honey.
I can smell lies.
-Leave him alone.
-I don't have all day.
[phone rings]
-Where are you two?
-Your daughter's a
little busy right now.
-Who is this?
-If you want your kids back,
bring 1 million stern dollars
to warehouse number three
at the West-Bronze Docks.
-What?
-And if you even think
of going to the cops,
the kiddies are dead, OK?
-Kidnapped them?
-How the hell could
you let this happen?
What are we going to do if those
people hurt the mayor's baby?
-What are we sitting around for?
We should just go get them.
-Are you crazy?
They're holding Pao-Lin and
the baby hostage out there.
-Don't worry.
I have a plan.
The kidnapper only
heard your voice.
When we get to
the meeting point,
you'll pose as the
kid's mother and keep
them occupied as
long as you can.
Then me and the
old man here will
rush in and snatch the kids.
-Damn it, don't over here.
-All right, lady,
hand over the money.
-You're the serial
kidnappers that everyone's
been talking about on
the news, aren't you?
-Oh man.
It's so crazy how famous we are.
-Although kidnapping
sounds so ruthless.
-Think about it, all we're
really doing is babysitting.
-The only thing is our
fees are a little high.
-My children, are
they still safe?
I want to see that they're OK.
-Hold it.
You're not their
mother, are you?
-Something's wrong.
I'm not smelling a lot of
green on this lady, sis.
-Don't screw with us.
We can smell your
lies a mile away.
-You take care of Agnes.
Come back here.
-Are you all right?
-My skirt is filthy.
This is one of my best outfits.
You round up those
hussies, you hear me?
-Got it.
-That hurts.
Hey, I've seen you before.
Oh wait, you're a
hero, aren't you?
-Yeah, and what if I am?
-Doesn't smell like
it pays very well.
Go figure.
-That's none of your business.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
But come on, can't you look the
other way for little old me?
-Look, that's not going
to work on me, OK?
-Please, don't listen to him.
He loves it.
-Oh, get over yourselves.
What do you think
I am, an idiot?
Damn.
-That's what you get for
letting your mind wander.
-Stop right there.
-Good idea.
Ask them to stop.
I'm sure that'll work.
-Well, he's not sweating, is he?
He's sleeping through
his own kidnapping.
You smell like trouble, kid.
Spill it.
Are you a NEXT, like me?
-You?
-That's right, and the
same goes for my sisters.
Mary can sniff out
money from a mile away.
Lily has the knack for
sniffing out a lie.
And then I, of course,
have a nose for danger.
We decided to put our
powers to use and start
a babysitting service.
And kids like you with your oh
so loving mommies and daddies
are always our best customers.
-My loving parents?
-Don't play dumb.
I mean just look
at that baby's hat.
The yellow marigold
is a symbol of health.
-A symbol of health?
-It's obvious how much
your folks care for you.
I'm guessing they'd pay anything
to get you back safe and sound.
-Here Pao-Lin, wear this on your
road to becoming a famous hero.
-Oh come on, now, it's a
gift from your parents.
-But there's no way I'm
putting that thing on.
-I don't think I like
what I'm smelling.
-Mari, we got some
heroes butting in.
-What did you say?
-Damn it, where the
hell did they go?
-They're coming.
What do we do?
-The scent of danger
is wafting in.
Start the car, were out of here.
We'll leave the girl behind.
-But why?
-The kid's a NEXT.
She's a liability.
-Huh?
-The baby is a NEXT too.
-Will you do something already?
-Undo these handcuffs,
and I'll think about it.
-Not going to happen, OK?
-Electricity won't
work against me.
-You don't want to lose your
special hat now, do you?
Come on, let's put this back on.
Don't worry buddy,
we're almost done.
-This is insane.
They'll kill us all.
So much danger.
-We surrender.
-Want to see me go full power?
-Hang in there, Dragon Kid.
-It's cool.
I took care of it.
-Huh?
-With a little
help from this guy.
-I didn't get to
do a thing today.
-What the hell was that?
-Bunny, what's the matter?
-Thank you.
I really am in you're debt.
I hope it wasn't
too much trouble.
-Oh goodness, of course not.
-You're gonna miss
him, aren't ya?
-Are you kidding?
Don't be silly.
-Hey, what you got there?
-What?
This?
Well, it's just something
my parents got for me.
-Well, how about that?
Makes you look really cute.
-You think so?
[phone rings]
-Hello?
Hey, Kaede.
-Hey dad, what's up?
-I was just wondering,
you know that one hair
clip I sent you, you
still have it, right?
-Huh, sure?
That gets used everyday.
-Oh good, I'm glad.
-Grandma wears it.
-Oh great.
[theme music]
-Just what the hell are you?
-Hey there, folks, Kotetsu here.
I'm the member of
Tiger and Bunny
that likes to eat ice cubes
out of his juice glass.
Hello, paid vacation.
Bomb threat?
Well, so much for my R&R. Next
time on "Tiger and Bunny."
See ya.