[music playing]
ANNOUNCER: This is
"Hero TV" breaking news.
Mass thugs have hijacked an
armored truck in West Silver
and are on the run with over
3 million Stern Dollars.
The cops are in hot pursuit.
This is a riveting action.
COP: Damn it.
Hang on!
Aaaghh!
ANNOUNCER: Unbelievable!
They took out a police cruiser.
It doesn't look like
the authorities can
stop these
bloodthirsty criminals.
And yet there is still
no sign of any heroes.
As you know, only one daring
program brings you ongoing,
up-to-the-second coverage of
supercharged heroes battling
crime and natural disasters.
The only rescue
entertainment show
that ranks vigilantes by points
and, at the end of the season,
crowns the undisputed
King of Heroes.
You're watching "Hero TV Live."
[MUSIC - UNISON SQUARE GARDEN,
"ORION O NAZORU"]
ANNOUNCER: And here
comes our first hero.
It's the Bourgeois Open
Flame Broil, Fire Emblem.
Will he bring the heat
for another arrest today?
-A camera, push in close.
-I'm all over it.
ANNOUNCER: Fire Emblem is
catching up to the suspects.
Oh, what phenomenal
driving skill!
-Got one on our tail.
-Eat dirt!
[machine gun fire]
[cackles]
-Uh!
ANNOUNCER: He's gonna
use his fireball attack.
ROBBER: Aaaaiiii!
ANNOUNCER: What
a merciless move!
-Can't you go any faster?
-Settle down!
ANNOUNCER: The suspects are
losing control of the vehicle.
And another hero
is on the scene.
The Bull Tank of the
West Coast, Rock Bison!
Rock Bison has been struggling
in the rankings all season.
It's good to see him
back in the game.
-Ha-ha!
hey!
Don't-- don't even
think about it.
Hold on.
Come here.
Oh!
ANNOUNCER: It appears Rock
Bison can't extract his horns.
And now the villains have
commandeered a taxi cab.
[sirens blaring]
-Oh no!
ANNOUNCER: And who
should drop in?
The Lightning Bolt Kung-Fu
Master, Dragon Kid.
Oh, look out!
She's charging up her arms
for her lightning attack!
[sizzling]
[villains scream]
ANNOUNCER: A sizzling
double arrest!
Talk about a shocking victory.
As usual, the Hidden
Hero, Origami Cyclone,
can be seen in the background.
And so another crime
prevented by-- oh, wait.
What's this?
One of the robbers
is still on the run!
-Get this train moving.
ANNOUNCER (ON HUGE
TV): This is terrible!
According to new information,
the remaining suspect
has taken control of
a crowded monorail!
[passengers exclaim]
-So what now?
We should probably pull
out and not interfere.
-And ruin my show?
The hell we will.
-But there are innocent
people involved now.
-Look.
What's that?
[siren blaring]
-[scoffs] Great.
ANNOUNCER: I don't
believe my eyes.
It's the Crusher for
Justice, Wild Tiger.
I hope he's careful this time.
-Cut to commercial.
-Aahh!
-Tiger, you reading me?
We need you to hold for
a 30-second commercial.
-You gotta be kidding me.
I am not waiting for ads
while people are in danger.
AGNES (ON COMM):
Hey, listen to me.
If you do it my way,
there'll be more suspense.
WILD TIGER (ON COMM):
Screw suspense.
A real hero only
cares about one thing,
and that's keeping the peace.
Wild Roar!
-Damn him.
So stubborn.
Keep rolling.
ANNOUNCER: Hold the phone!
It appears Wild Tiger is
activating his Hundred
Power, which makes his physical
abilities 100 times stronger!
-Go faster!
-I can't!
[grunts with effort]
ANNOUNCER: Incredible!
-Stop the train!
-I can't!
[brakes squealing]
[passengers screaming]
-Hunh!
Uhhh-yahhh!
[glass shatters]
[whimpers in terror]
WILD TIGER (ON COMM):
Give it up, scumbag!
Huh?
-You fool!
He's below you!
-Gah?
Where'd that come from?
ANNOUNCER: The suspect
has escaped to a blimp!
Blazing into the fight, it's the
Wind Master himself, Sky High.
That's right-- this
season's leader
and reigning champ has
come to save the day!
[cheering]
-What a jerk.
Showing up after I've
done all the dirty work.
Hunh!
[muffled grunting]
[whimpering]
-Don't try anything
funny or else.
-You don't try
anything funny or else.
-[gasp] Sky High?
You're a dead man!
-Ah?
Oh!
Aw, damn it!
ANNOUNCER: Ah!
The suspect's
rocket has exploded!
Oh, the humanity!
-Aaaahh!
ANNOUNCER: Controlling the
wind to save innocent lives--
just what we'd
expect from Sky High.
He truly is the King of Heroes.
-Sky High's so amazing!
ANNOUNCER: Look out!
The blimp is gonna crash
into that building!
[glass shattering]
[boom]
-Sky High!
Please, save me!
WILD TIGER: Don't worry!
Wild Tiger, at your-- augh!
Service.
Ahhh!
-Yeah.
Think I'll wait for Sky High.
-Oh, is that right?
You're gonna die
if you-- aaaahhh!
ANNOUNCER: Dear me!
The blimp's heading straight
for that cruise ship!
[passengers exclaiming]
-Gahh!
Seriously?
[screaming]
[ice crackling]
FEMALE SPEAKER: You boys
done fooling around yet?
-Huh?
ANNOUNCER: Every male
fan knows the cold wind
that just blew in.
Protecting the cruise ship
with her freezing liquid gun,
it's the icy superstar of
the hero world, Blue Rose!
-All right, get me a close-up.
-My ice is a little
cold, but your crime
has been completely put on hold.
ANNOUNCER: Absolute perfection!
[cheering]
WILD TIGER: All she cares
about is racking up points.
(SHOUTING) I caught the suspect.
Doesn't that count for anything?
Ugh.
[gunshot]
-Huh?
-Camera C. [gasp]
[panting]
-You shot me?
-I told you to stay
out of it, man!
--[heavy sigh] What
a day I'm having.
ANNOUNCER: Wild Tiger took
a bullet to the chest,
but he's all right.
ROBBER: Aaaauuuughhhhhh!
-Ew!
Stop!
[gunshot]
[screams]
ANNOUNCER: It's her
patented Cutie Escape!
-She's just running away!
[gunshot]
Oh!
Ugh.
ANNOUNCER: Wild Tiger
leaps into action!
-Huuuuuunnhhh!
Huh?
ANNOUNCER: He ran out of time.
Remember, Wild Tiger's Hundred
Power only lasts five minutes.
-Oh, boy.
ANNOUNCER: Tiger has
lost his superpowers!
This could mean
curtains for our hero.
[screaming]
[shrang]
Aaaaggghhhhhhhh!
[ghostly whoosh]
-Mm-- what the?
Who the hell are
you supposed to be?
-The guy who just
saved your life.
-Aaaauuughhh!
-Oh yeah.
ANNOUNCER: Look!
It's-- um, who is that?
[shrang]
-Huh?
-Aaaaahhh!
ANNOUNCER: Our mystery man
has apprehended the crook!
-Auugh!
Nnnghh!
-Hah.
ANNOUNCER: Could this be the
birth of a new superstar?
The season ends with
a surprise victory
by a mysterious new hero.
[cheering]
-Huh.
-Cut to a commercial.
[music - blue rose, "let's go"]
WILD TIGER: Hey.
So who's your sponsor, anyway?
-Don't have one.
-Wait, you're telling
me you're a free agent?
Why'd you stick
your nose in this?
-Come on, does it really matter?
I made the arrest.
-And showing your face.
Why would you take off
your mask in public?
Are you crazy?
-Huh?
-It's a basic rule.
A hero's secret identity
has to remain a secret--
-Secret, huh?
-Uh--
-Times are changing, old man.
Better keep up.
-Old man?
This is it!
The moment you've
all been waiting for.
We're about to reveal the winner
of this season's "Hero TV."
BEN: What were you
thinking, Kotetsu?
I mean, bending that track?
And did you have to smash the
windows in the train like that?
KOTETSU: Well--
BEN: So much mayhem.
You realize how much
that's going to cost?
-Hey, if I worried
about all that stuff,
I couldn't do my job.
-Well, you better
start worrying,
or else you might just
find yourself out of a job.
-Listen, I'm sorry.
-You do understand who made
you a hero, don't you, pal?
-Hmm.
My sponsor, sir.
-Good answer.
Now get to that award ceremony.
-Thanks, Ben.
ANNOUNCER: Fire Emblem.
Rock Bison.
Dragon Kid.
Origami Cyclone.
Sky High.
Blue Rose.
Wild Tiger.
Which hero--
-Hey.
-You're late.
-So when are they gonna
announce the winner?
-Right now.
-All right.
-We know it's not gonna be you.
-Shut up.
-[laughs]
ANNOUNCER: The points
have been tallied,
and it's time to
crown a new champion.
One of these fearless
heroes is a heartbeat away
from winning all the glory!
-Mm.
ANNOUNCER: With an
unprecedented 12,730 points,
the King of Heroes is Sky High!
[cheering]
ANNOUNCER: And
now, your champion.
-I could not have done this
without everyone's help.
Thanks, and thanks again!
[cheering]
[fireworks exploding]
-[sigh]
ANNOUNCER: And now with
an important message,
here is the CEO of
Apollon Media as well as
the president of the OBC.
Give it up for Albert Maverick!
-I'd like to take a moment
to introduce someone
very special to our viewers.
Come on up.
-Huh?
[cheering]
MAVERICK: This bright
young man has just
won the approval of
the Justice Bureau,
so you'll all be seeing
a lot more of him.
Please welcome the city
of Sternbild's newest
hero, Barnaby Brooks Jr.
[crowd roars]
-Hm.
Ugh, what a clown.
-Be nice.
-His superpower may sound
familiar to some of you.
When activated, this young
man's physical strength
is increased 100 times.
-Uh?
-But it only lasts
him for five minutes.
And yes, it's the exact
same power as Wild Tiger.
However, he also has
the power of youth,
which is why I'm hopeful our new
hero won't need to be rescued
as often as someone
else we know.
[laughs]
-Gah.
[giggles]
MAVERICK: As you know,
individuals with superpowers,
known as NEXT, began
appearing 45 years ago
due to some sort of mutation.
-Hey!
-I'm out of here.
MAVERICK: We still
don't know what
triggered these rare abilities.
However, we do know that
the NEXT have kept us safe.
Battling chaos,
crime, and injustice,
these brave fighters
have earned our trust
and become our heroes!
[crowd roars]
-Good evening.
-Mm.
"A veteran hero who made
his debut 10 years ago.
He may be past his
prime, but he is"-- ugh.
Huh?
Give me 10 Wild Tigers!
-Whatever.
[cell phone ringing]
-Hey.
What's up?
ANTONIO: Are you seriously
ditching the after-party?
KOTETSU: Op: Ah, those
things are too stuffy for me.
-There's tons of free food
and all the suits are here.
KOTETSU: Op: Say hi
for me, will you?
ANTONIO: Hello?
Hello?
[sigh] Ahhh!
-Hmm, Bison's got some
junk in the trunk.
Hmmm,
-Stop-- stop-- get off of me!
-You got your screen
time out there, as usual.
Keep it up.
It's great exposure.
-I won't let the
sponsors down, sir.
I mean, I hope not.
-You're not listening.
My catch phrase is stupid.
Can't your company
let me change it?
-That domineering attitude of
yours is why people love you.
Why change what works?
-It's all about the fans.
Thanks, and thanks again.
-Hello, Mr. Maverick.
-Ah.
I knew promoting
you to producer was
the right choice for "Hero TV."
But I never expected you
to pull in these ratings.
-Well, when it comes to creating
a spectacle, I stop at nothing.
[phone ringing]
KOTETSU: Yeah, yeah, coming.
Yello?
KAEDE: Op: Dad?
-Honey!
What's going on, Kaede?
-Tomorrow's my recital.
You didn't forget, did you?
-Forget?
I said I'd be there, and I will.
Ow!
-You mean it?
You're not gonna have to
work like you usually do?
KOTETSU: Op: No way.
Tomorrow you are gonna be the
cutest little girl on stage,
and I'm gonna be the first
in line to see you perform.
I wouldn't miss
it for the world!
MRS. KABURAGI: Op: You
said that last time.
-Gah.
You know, you
should say something
when you take the phone, Mom.
-(QUIETLY) I saw you on TV.
Do you have to pay for all that?
KOTETSU: Op: Heh.
Real funny, Mom.
All I'm saying is
that you should really
try to be more careful, dear.
-Yeah, I know.
MRS. KABURAGI: Op: I mean it.
If something horrible
were to happen to you,
I'd have to tell little
Kaede about your work
as a superhero at your funeral.
She'd be so heartbroken.
-You always worry too much.
MRS. KABURAGI: Op:
Well, can you blame me?
A man who's away from his family
and faces criminals every day
just to make a living?
Of course I worry.
KOTETSU: Yeah, I know.
Believe me, I know.
-Huh?!
BEN: I'm sorry, Kotetsu.
KOTETSU: Ben?
A buy-out?
-It was the only option.
Ad revenue kept
falling and we were
lucky to find a buyer
willing to take on our debts.
Here.
KOTETSU: Huh?
Who's this Lloyds guy?
-Your new employer.
-Huh?
-And I would suggest you
go and pay him a visit.
-What?
Hang on a second.
What the hell is going on?
-Starting this next season, only
the seven biggest corporations
are going to be
sponsoring heroes.
Hate to say it, but our company
just dropped off the list.
-So you're gonna
disappear, just like that?
-Hey, business is business.
-Do all the other
heroes know about this?
I'm the last to know.
BEN: Sorry, old pal.
KOTETSU: What'll happen to you?
BEN: Oh, don't worry about me.
I'm going to relax,
collect my unemployment,
and look for work
in a few months.
-So I'll be alone
at this new place?
-You'll be fine.
-But Ben--
-Times are changing.
I'm really going to miss
being in your corner
and watching you fight.
Really.
But no matter what
happens, I'll always
be Wild Tiger's biggest fan.
-Hm?
Hmph.
-Oh!
-[humming to self] Hm?
This is the place.
Hm?
Hm.
I got it.
Unh!
[gasp]
-Here you go.
-Aw, thank you.
Um, I think you
dropped your cards.
-Ah!
Oh, those are just--
-It's OK, Mister.
I understand.
-Aha, darn.
You figured it out, huh, kid?
-You like Wild Tiger
'cause he's old like you.
-[laughs] Say what now?
KID: Here, you
can have this one.
-Uh, you should keep that.
I'm sure it means a lot to you.
-Actually, I'm a Sky High
fan, so I don't need it.
Take it.
-Heh.
Thanks.
Huh.
That's how it is.
-So you're Wild Tiger.
And I see your real name here,
but how do I pronounce it?
-It's Kotetsu.
Kotetsu Kaburagi.
-Hm.
Right.
You'll be briefed on your new
suit in the design department.
-Oh.
I hadn't planned
on starting today.
-Or you can just quit
if you don't like it.
-Today works.
Heh.
[alarm buzzing]
-Huh?
LLOYDS: The industrial district.
-The Steel Hammer statue?
-Why is it moving?
-I bet a NEXT is behind this.
-All right, you'd
better get going.
-Huh?
Oh, but I don't have
my suit with me.
-No need.
I have your new one right here.
-Uh--
-This is a perfect chance
to debut your new look.
-I don't think I
could do that, sir.
-Really?
And why is that?
-It's just-- I've worn the
same suit my entire career.
LLOYDS: Don't be nervous.
The tech on this
suit is far better
than that old one
you're used to.
KOTETSU: Yeah, that's
not the issue here.
That costume defines my life.
It's everything I am as a hero.
A symbol of hope and justice.
-Just wear the thing,
or you're fired.
[sirens blaring]
[tires squeal]
-Actually, this
thing is really cool.
[rumbling]
-There you are.
Let's do this.
LLOYDS: There is
one other thing.
We've decided to partner
you up with another hero.
-Huh?
-Apollon Media is
going to sell it
as the first ever superhero
duo to take the stage.
-Nobody asked me about that.
-That's because you don't
have a say in the matter.
-Where's my teammate, anyway?
And who the hell
are they giving me?
ROCK BISON: Aaaahhhhhh!
[thud]
-Unnh!
Damn, that hurt.
Guess I can't take
this guy alone.
-What?
It's you?
[MUSIC - AOBOZU, "HOSHI NO
SUMIKA"]
-Hold up.
They're pairing me
with you, Rock Bison?
-Unh.
Say what?
-Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Apollon wants you
to be my partner?
[tires squeal]
-You gonna talk
all day, old man?
Or are we gonna get to work?
-Gah!
No way.
Hey, I'm Kotetsu, the bearded
member of Tiger and Bunny.
Holy crap, a statue
has gone wild.
And a NEXT could be
pulling the strings.
Next time on "Tiger and
Bunny," a good beginning
makes a-- I can't read
this stupid thing.