[music playing]
-You know my ice is-- hm.
Ah!
My ice is a little
cold, but your crime
has been completely put on hold.
-Hm.
You didn't really try
on that one, did you?
Honey, the fans can see
when your heart's not in it.
They can sense a phony.
-Quit nagging me.
MRS. LYLE: Really?
That's how you speak
to your own mother?
I'm only telling you this
to help with your career.
It's your catchphrase, dear.
At least try to make it sound--
-Thanks for the advice, Mom.
-(QUIETLY) Look at him.
I'm sure your father doesn't
approve of that skimpy costume
you wear.
-Actually, the costume
doesn't bother me.
-Really?
-I'm much more
worried by the fact
that my daughter risks her life
fighting criminals every day.
-I can take care
of myself, Daddy.
Besides, I'm not planning
to be a hero forever.
[MUSIC - UNISON SQUARE GARDEN,
"ORION O NAZORU"]
ANNOUNCER (ON TV):
Breaking news!
Earlier today in the
Stern [inaudible] area,
a brazen criminal made
off with an armored car.
And the dangerous bandit
is still on the loose!
-OK, he's headed right for you.
Are the two of you
ready for action?
BARNABY: Ready and waiting.
-Wait, this guy's just
trying to shake the cops?
Why are we getting involved
in some dumb traffic stop?
[sirens]
-Fine.
Guess we'll get some
easy points and go home.
-Are you hard of
hearing, old man?
-Huh?
-If you were
listening, they said
the suspect's in an armored car.
[whistle blowing]
[crash]
-Yeah, I know, I
heard the report.
It's like a dumb bank
truck or something.
-They don't mean
that kind of armor.
-Huh?
-Never mind.
-Whatever.
Us heroes should be fighting
real bad guys, you know?
Like guys with machine guns.
Ba-da-da-da-da-da-da-da--
[boom]
-Huh?
That's a tank!
-That's what I was
trying to tell you.
-Ah!
ANNOUNCER (ON TV): Oh, boy!
Barnaby and Wild Tiger
are on the scene!
I wonder what Tiger's
gonna wreck today.
-What did he just say about me?
-Hm?
[crash]
-Hey!
Take it easy on the sidecar!
[bam]
-Well, guess I'll
start by wrecking this.
AGNES (ON COMM): Hey!
Be careful.
You need to avoid any
collateral damage.
-Hold up.
Am I supposed to be
wrecking stuff or not?
[crash]
-Morning, sunshine.
-Wah!
-[screaming] Ah!
[grunts] Oh!
Ow, that hurt.
-Honestly, do you
ever think about what
you're doing before you do it?
-Hey, I stopped the
thing, didn't I?
And I didn't even
break it-- I think.
-Ah!
[gunfire]
Hey, so where did this
guy get a tank, anyway?
AGNES (ON COMM):
You're the one who
wanted to fight "real bad
guys with machine guns."
-I know, but I wasn't
expecting a tank.
AGNES (ON COMM):
It only proves how
dangerous this city has become.
[yawn]
CAIN (ON COMM): Coming
your way, Blue Rose.
-What?
I'm going on the air?
CAIN (ON COMM): Not the
cameras, the suspect!
-Oh.
I was kinda hoping it would
be the other way around.
CAIN (ON COMM): Listen up.
The streets are wet from rain.
Freeze them to stop the suspect.
-All right.
[panting]
[siren]
-Huh?
-Hey.
My ice is a little
cold, but your crime
has been complete-- huh?
Oh no!
[machine gun fire]
-Stop!
Uh-oh.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
ANNOUNCER: Uh-oh!
Blue Rose is in trouble!
-Ah!
-Uh.
-[sigh]
-Ah!
Ha!
[crackling]
-Ah!
-Ha!
Huh!
Hah!
ANNOUNCER: Another
electrifying arrest
by the Lightning Bolt
Kung-Fu Master, Dragon Kid.
WILD TIGER: You kidding me?
We got the spotlight
stolen from us again.
BARNABY: Well, at least I
scored a few points rescuing
a damsel in distress,
so I'm good.
BLUE ROSE: Hey, newbie.
You're not referring
to me, are you?
-Who else would it be?
-This new partner of
yours, I don't like him.
WILD TIGER: Huh.
Welcome to the club.
But it was your fault
for getting distracted.
-I have a lot on my mind, OK?
-Oh, like what?
Your little side job?
-Uh?
Yeah, what's it matter to you?
-If your mind's not in
it 100%, then you've
got no business
trying to be a hero.
That's how people get hurt.
-Oh, please.
This from a guy who has
zero points this season?
-[gasp]
-You're so lame.
-Now hold on a sec.
We are not lame.
We were awesome
the other day when
we took care of that bomb scare.
BARNABY: Let's be honest,
that bomb thing was mainly me.
-Uh?
-Like I said-- lame.
-Hey!
I am not finished
talking to you.
-What I do in private is
none of your business.
(QUIETLY) Truth is, I don't
want to be a hero anyway.
Ugh, what a know-it-all.
That bearded idiot.
TEACHER: Ahem.
Do you have a problem
with my beard, Miss?
-No, I wasn't talking about you.
-Look, Karina, I understand it
can be stressful being a hero.
But a student should put her
education above everything.
You really must finish
your assignments if you--
KARINA: Actually, I just did.
-Huh?
-Does that mean I can go?
-No way!
I don't believe you.
-It's true!
I saw them walking
home together today.
-She's with that guy?
He's so weird!
Karina, what's wrong?
-Oh-- nothing.
Huh?
-So?
What do you guys want to do now?
Hey, what about that
new sushi place?
-Yeah!
I heard it was great.
What do you say, Karina?
Do you want to come with us?
-Huh?
Oh-- oh, uh, sorry, but I
really do anything today.
-More urgent business?
-That's right.
Kind of hard to explain.
-What?
But we waited through
your tutoring session.
-Sorry.
-We're kinda used to it
by now anyway, aren't we?
Bye, Karina.
-Yeah, see you later.
-Bye.
Why?
TITAN INDUSTRY SUIT:
Karina, sweetheart,
how many times have
I told you to follow
our instructions to the letter?
I know you're young, but you
can't act like an amateur.
When you ran away yesterday,
you missed the perfect chance
to make an arrest.
Not to mention
your little stumble
gave rescue points
to Apollon's hero.
[slaps desk]
This is unacceptable.
You're damaging our
company's image.
-Mmph!
-Well, according to the bigwigs.
KARINA: How was I
supposed to know
that guy had a submachine gun?
TITAN INDUSTRY SUIT:
Listen, I get it, OK?
It can be tough out there.
But risking your life to stop
criminals is part of this job.
I mean, you are a hero.
Besides, that's why you
have these powers, Karina,
to help you beat the bad guys.
[clears throat]
What I'm saying is you need
to realize how important it
is to keep our sponsors happy.
And right now, they're
not very pleased, 'K?
-So it's all the sponsors?
Every day, I'm risking
my life-- for what?
What's the point
of me being a hero?
-Well, there's lots of--
-Is it to make your
company look good?
Is it to keep the
sponsors happy?
-It's for the
citizens of Sternbild.
-Come on!
Do you really believe all that?
Honestly?
-Don't you dare question me!
Now I was starting
to have my doubts,
but now it's clear you don't
think of yourself as a hero.
Our company isn't
interested in a star singer.
We pay you to be a star hero.
You listen to me.
We are running a
business, Karina.
-No, you listen.
I never even wanted
to be a hero.
-Uh?
-The company said I had to if I
wanted to make it as a singer.
That's the only
reason I signed up.
Now if you'll excuse me.
[slams door]
[sigh]
KARINA: Grr!
I mean, how could he sit
there and berate me like that?
NATHAN: Easy, kitten.
You don't want to give
yourself wrinkles.
-I'm out there getting
shot at and they only
care about profits and sponsors.
-I'm sure your employers
have their reasons.
But there are some things
that can't be changed.
-Easy for you to
say, Fire Emblem.
After all, you own your company.
-But that doesn't mean I'm
free to do whatever I want.
-I can't even tell my
friends what I do every day.
I never expected this
job to be so frustrating.
I mean, how have you guys
done this for so long?
No one ever acknowledges you--
KOTETSU: Hey.
-Wow, look who it is.
What do you want?
-I think you've got the
wrong idea about us.
-Oh yeah?
How am I wrong?
-All us heroes.
We don't do this
job just because we
want people to appreciate us.
-Mm-hm.
-And?
-And nothing.
-That's supposed to move me?
-Well, I mean, uh--
I'm talking about--
-That's just it.
You're all talk, Zero Point Man.
-Hey, hold on!
I'm not finished yet.
-Yeah?
Well, I am!
-Honey, you are never going to
break through to a young girl
by lecturing her like that.
She's a teenager,
for crying out loud.
-Well, I don't think I
was really lecturing her.
What's with you?
-Oh, it's nothing.
-What, did I say something
to offend you, too?
Know,
-It's not like that.
Actually, you sort of echoed me.
-Echoed you?
What do you mean?
REPORTER (ON TV): But doesn't
it bother you that being a hero
is so unrewarding?
-I don't do this because I
want people to appreciate me.
I just want to help the city.
MRS. LYLE: That's
Barnaby for you.
He is so humble.
-Yeah, right.
-You know, you should really
start following his example.
-No need anymore.
I quit being a hero.
-Um, I don't think I
heard you correctly, dear.
Did you seriously quit your job?
-Sure did.
I never wanted that life anyway.
-But you have so many fans
out there who worship you.
And what about your dream
of becoming a singer?
-If I want to sing,
I'll do it at a club.
-Wait, Karina, don't go!
[singing and playing piano]
[applause]
KOTETSU: Not bad.
You're pretty serious
about this, aren't you?
-It's what I love to do.
What are you doing here, anyway?
-Huh?
Hm.
[sigh]
--[sigh] So why do you
keep bothering me?
Can't you leave me alone?
What's that for?
-It's a tip.
Not a lot, but look, you've
got a pretty nice voice.
If you really want to be
a singer, I say go for it.
Sorry I bothered you.
KARINA: Hey, hold on.
-Huh?
-I was just wondering
why you became a hero.
-It's funny, you seem
like a pretty honest kid.
I misjudged you.
-Uh?
You don't know what
you're talking about.
-Anyway, aren't you too
young to be drinking?
-This is just mineral water.
-Like I said, an honest kid.
-Don't pretend you know me.
-Say, you never told me why
you want to be a singer.
-I love singing.
And I want to share my
voice with the entire world.
-Same goes for me.
-Huh?
-The reason I became a hero was
because I enjoy helping people.
What other reason
could a guy need?
If people acknowledge
what I do-- well,
that doesn't really
matter to me.
[knock]
MR. LYLE: Karina?
Can we talk for a moment?
KARINA: I don't want
to talk to anyone.
-I understand that
you quit being a hero.
Your mother was quite concerned.
KARINA: Why do you care?
You were against it all along.
-The other day, you said being
a hero wasn't your goal in life.
Now I'm no fan of your
costume, but what really
bothered me that day
was your attitude.
If you don't believe
in what you're doing,
that's a recipe for disaster.
I'm saying if you want
to quit, then quit.
I think it's the right choice.
And think-- if
you do retire now,
this card may be worth
a lot in a few years.
-They don't get it.
[beeping]
-Huh?
[cell phone ringing]
Yes?
MANAGER (ON PHONE): Oh, Karina.
Hey, sorry for calling you
out of the blue like this.
Look, the singer we booked
for tonight just bailed on us.
I hate to ask, but can
you head over to the bar
and start warming up?
-Huh?
-All right.
Your mission for today is
a basic search-and-rescue
operation.
WILD TIGER: Right,
we know the drill.
AGNES (ON COMM): However, things
are still dangerous out there,
so stay on the boat
until I give the order.
Especially you, Wild Tiger.
Look before you leap.
-Yeah, I'll behave.
-Status check.
Where's Blue Rose?
Why isn't she
responding to our calls?
ANNOUNCER (ON TV): This just in!
There's been an
explosion on an oil rig
just offshore in Stern Bay.
According to reports,
most of the workers
have been evacuated
safely, but one of them
is still trapped inside.
We've been informed that several
fearless heroes are already
on their way.
However, the inferno shows
no signs of dying down
The situation is
spiraling out of control.
With the explosions,
smoke, and deadly blaze,
there may be nothing our
heroes can do at this point.
-Hey, Agnes.
I'm not waiting anymore.
We're moving in.
AGNES (ON COMM): Absolutely not.
It's too dangerous.
I'm not going to risk
losing two of my heroes.
Stand down.
That's a direct order.
-Sorry, can't hear you.
AGNES (ON COMM): Tiger,
this isn't a joke.
-Hey, I'm an old man.
My hearing's shot.
-Don't you disobey me!
WILD TIGER: If there's
even a glimmer of hope,
a hero cannot
abandon a human life.
Un!
-You have a million corny
catchphrases, don't you?
-Don't stop me.
-Whoever said anything
about stopping you?
-Huh?
-Here's what I say.
If there's even a
glimmer of hope,
a hero cannot abandon his point.
AGNES (ON COMM): Barnaby!
-Huh?
Showoff.
KARINA: [singing]
The smile that you
see is just my heart breaking.
Change the [inaudible]
behind your [inaudible].
Another day sleeping, my
soul kept from waking.
Not myself, not the
girl deep inside.
Now I walk alone down
a dark, shadowed path--
PATRON: (SLURRING) Come on!
They only gotta save
one fellow, right?
So what the hell's
taking 'em so long?
These punks call
themselves heroes?
You wimps don't seem
like heroes to me.
-Uh?
-We don't risk our
lives every single day--
-Simply to be
appreciated by people.
-No, they're not just doing
this to win your gratitude.
-These heroes are so pathetic.
Anybody want to make a bet?
$20 says they can't
save that guy.
Who's in.
[pounds notes]
Huh?
-Hey!
That's enough.
-Huh?
Who the hell are you?
You got a beef with
me or something, kid?
-Sure, you might
talk a big game,
but you have no idea how
much those heroes risk
to keep you safe.
-Huh?
-No one wants your money.
-Hey, what are you doing?
-Hah!
-[panting]
-This stuff's heavier
than it looked.
ROCK BISON: Found him.
Over here!
-Huh?
[grunting]
[panting]
[boom]
-Damn it!
WILD TIGER: What a joke.
-Huh?
-That big metal body
of yours just for show?
-Big talk coming from
a guy who runs out
of power in five minutes!
-Hey!
I train more than you.
Right, Bunny?
-Actually, I don't recall
ever seeing you train.
[boom]
-The whole thing's
about to collapse!
-Thank you, Captain Obvious!
[all grunting with effort]
-He's all yours, Sky High!
[explosions]
-Damn!
Huh?
ROCK BISON: Ice?
-Great.
There go my points.
-It's about time.
(SHOUTING) You're late.
-Just be grateful I even
came for you losers.
ANNOUNCER: And swooping in
at the last possible moment,
it's Blue Rose!
That vixen will whip your tail
and make you beg for more.
She's the Queen of Sadism.
-So, did you figure
out why you do it?
-I'm a hero because I
like helping people.
What other reason
could a girl need?
-Hmph.
-Hey, don't laugh.
Now fork over your $10.
-What are you talking about?
-Aw, come on.
You bet me that she
wasn't going to show up.
-Huh?
-Look, I said she wouldn't come,
but I don't remember anything
about money.
-What?
You two were actually
placing bets on me?
You suck.
-Wait, I said that you'd come!
-I wasn't really betting.
-So lame.
[giggles]
-My ice may be a little
cold, but your crime
has been completely put on hold!
[MUSIC - AOBOZU, "HOSHI NO
SUMIKA"]
KOTETSU (VOICEOVER):
Hey, this is
Kotetsu of "Tiger and Bunny."
You know, the one who brushes
his teeth in the bath?
Oh, it's Barnaby's
birthday, huh?
Well, we'd better
do something big.
Wait, what?
A robbery?
Now?
Ugh.
Next time on "Tiger and
Bunny," go for broke!
So, uh, what does
that even mean?