[music playing]
LLOYDS (VOICEOVER): You
want to take a vacation?
-Yeah.
I thought I'd better
go visit my daughter.
You know, before she
forgets what I look like.
-It's unusual for you
to request time off.
Not to mention you
wouldn't return any phone
calls the other day.
-Ah, yeah, well, it
was just a thought.
If it's not possible, that's OK.
I mean, after all, the safety
of the city has to come first.
-Relax.
I'm not saying the idea's
out of the question.
BARNABY: Just to let you
know, it's OK with me.
It shouldn't be a problem.
I think I can handle things
by myself for a while.
-Well, if you're sure
about that, then fine.
He can go.
-It would be good for
you to spend some quality
time with your daughter.
Hey, I have to look
out for my crew.
She's one of my biggest fans.
[awkward chuckling]
-"The Latest Invincible
Hero Legend?"
That's great.
JACKSON: You should
start thinking
about what to do with your life.
[music - novels, "missing link"]
[sigh]
-Hmm?
Hey, do you need some
help with your car, pal?
-No thanks.
I don't need a hero to
handle a job like this.
It's nothing I can't
take care of my own.
-Come on man, it's old.
How long you gonna keep
driving that clunker?
-It's not a clunker.
It happens to be
vintage, Kotetsu.
-Well, I guess that depends
on how you look at it.
You don't see anyone
driving secondhand junk
like this in Sternbild anymore.
-It runs just fine out
here in the boonies.
You coming or what?
-I'm kind of surprised
you picked me up
in the middle of the day.
Thought you were busy.
Slacking off?
-I came because Mom asked me to.
-Huh?
What, you're not even
gonna come inside?
-You said it yourself--
I'm busy right now.
I still have some
deliveries to make.
-Your little brother come home
for the first time in years.
Come on, at least
stay for a cup of tea.
-If you want to have a
talk, come by the store.
I'll keep the
place open tonight,
just for old time's sake.
-You always were the
serious one, weren't you?
Hm.
Well, the place looks
the same as always.
Hey, Mom!
I'm home!
Huh?
[running water]
Huh.
Mom!
Hey, I'm home.
-Oh, Kotetsu.
I didn't expect you till later.
-Ah, that's all right.
You seem to be doing
pretty well, Mom.
-I try to keep active.
How about you?
-Oh, I'm fine.
Everything's going
along perfectly.
-You sure about that?
Tell me, did something happen?
-Something happen?
No, not a thing.
-All right, if
that's what you say.
I was just surprised
when you said
you were coming
home, that's all.
-So, is Kaede still at school?
-Yes.
She should be coming
home pretty soon, though.
-Oh, great.
-I knew it.
You're not looking
very well to me.
-No!
It's not like that, Mom!
-You're all wilted.
-It was the plant.
[chuckling]
Ah, it's been a
long time since I've
seen this room and my old desk.
Uh?
Aah!
What is all this?
She's been collecting these?
Huh?
Ah.
KAEDE: Dad?
-Kaede!
Heh heh.
Hey, surprise!
Are you happy to see me?
I haven't been here
in a long time.
-What are you doing
snooping around my room?
-Eh?
-You came in without permission.
-Uh, well, that's true, but, uh,
this used to be daddy's room,
so I didn't think you mind.
KAEDE: You went
through my stuff?
-I, uh-- well.
I must say, you've
really been growing.
You're big now.
You must be 11 stories tall, hm?
[grumbling]
-Hmm.
I know!
Why don't we take
a bath together
like we did a few years--
-Pervert.
- --ago?
Pervert?
'Scuse me?
Where did you even
learn a word like that?
-Pervert!
Pervert!
Get out of here!
-Kaede, what's the matter?
-Hmph!
-Kotetsu, you need to
each more vegetables.
Come on.
You probably eat fried
rice all the time,
since it's the only thing
you know how to cook.
Am I right?
-So what's the problem
with fried rice?
It just happens to taste
really good, you know?
-Thanks for dinner.
-Hey, Kaede, are
you still mad at me?
-You expect her to
just forgive you?
Have you even tried
apologizing to the girl?
-Not exactly.
-I mean, going through your
daughter's things like that.
Wake up, she's
already 10 years old.
-Mm.
[sigh]
I'm so sorry, Kaede.
I realize I shouldn't have gone
into your room without asking.
Can you forgive me?
I promise I'll never go in
there again unless I'm invited.
Pretty please, with whipped
cream and a cherry on top?
KAEDE: Stop talking
to me like I'm a baby.
-Oh, wait!
Almost forgot.
Daddy got you an autograph
from Barnaby Brooks.
You can have it
if you forgive me.
[grunt]
-From Barnaby?
Really?
I don't believe it!
How did you get it?
-How did I-- well, I
stood in line all night
at a book signing and had
him autograph it for you.
See?
-Oh!
Thank you so much, Dad!
This is the best!
-Great!
Glad you like it.
Can I read you a bedtime story?
-That is not gonna happen.
-I can't believe my little
girl is already 10 years old.
She's practically a young woman.
No room for a dad, I guess.
-So what happened, Kotetsu?
Gonna tell me?
-What?
Nothing's happened, man.
-I thought you came here
to talk about something.
-Well, now that
I think about it,
it's not all that important.
It can wait.
-Oh yeah?
So why'd you come back home?
-Good question.
I'm not sure.
-Mom's really worried about you.
-Mm.
-Hey, you gonna
spill it or what?
A guy your age
isn't supposed to go
around getting his mother
all upset like this.
-Hey, what's your problem?
Are you saying I need
a reason to come home?
-That isn't what I said.
-Well, that's what it
sounded like to me.
Look, I'm sorry I barged
in on you like this,
but you're family.
Where else was I supposed to go?
-Why are you getting so upset?
I am not getting upset!
I just want you
to leave me alone.
-Then why did you
bother coming back?
-I've got things I'm
trying to deal with, OK?
Is that so hard to--
-I can't help unless you
tell me what's wrong!
Stop trying to act
so tough, Kotetsu.
Listen, back here, you're
not Wild Tiger, the hero.
You're Kotetsu Kaburagi,
my little brother, OK?
Your powers are getting weaker?
-Yeah.
The time limit that
I can use them in
is getting shorter and shorter.
At this rate, I'll
completely lose them.
When that happens, I won't
be able to be a hero anymore.
That's what scares me, and I
don't know what to do about it.
-Life would go on.
-I know there comes
a time when you just
have to accept your fate,
but-- dammit, not like this.
I've sacrificed a
lot to get where
I am-- a lot more
than I ever wanted to.
And for what?
So I can wake up one morning
and be put out to pasture?
-Why didn't you tell me
about this before now?
-I didn't want to
burden you with it.
-That's always been your way.
You've always tried to keep
everything to yourself,
even when you were a kid.
It's a bad habit.
Back when you first
discovered you had powers,
you did the same thing.
Agonizing over it won't
give you any answers.
Give yourself some time to rest.
That's why you came
home, isn't it?
-I suppose.
-Kotetsu-- that's $2.
-Huh?
-One more thing--
-Yeah, what's up?
-Even if you do end
up losing your powers,
your life isn't over.
You have a lot to live for.
ANNOUNCER (ON TV):
He's done it again!
Barnaby has saved yet
get another person
from this high rise fire.
He continues to top
the charts this week.
-I think I can handle things
by myself for a while.
My ranking is not
what's important.
Protecting people at all times,
that's what we heroes do.
TOMOE: A hero has to
protect people at all times,
isn't that right?
KOTETSU: Well, yes, but there
are more important things to--
-Then what are you waiting for?
You have to go.
-I can't just leave
you here like this.
[comm buzzing]
Fine, I'll go then.
Are you happy now?
TOMOE: Promise me, dear,
that no matter what happens,
you'll never stop being a hero.
I'm proud of you.
ANNOUNCER: And here
comes Wild Tiger!
The Crusher for Justice
has just saved two lives
by blasting through the
front of the building.
[phone ringing]
[gasp]
KOTETSU: Tomoe?
[footsteps running]
-I'm so sorry.
Her condition worsened
after you left.
-I guess this is it for me.
The end of the road.
Sorry, Tomoe.
I just don't think that I
can keep my promise to you.
KAEDE: Dad!
Dad, wake up!
Please!
Dad!
You have to help Grandma!
Something's happened to her!
-What?
Slow down a minute.
What are you saying
about Grandma?
Mom!
What happened?
Can you hear me?
What's wrong?
-Don't be so rough.
I'll be fine, I
just hurt my back.
I think it's because
the weather got colder.
[groan]
-What is it, Kotetsu?
What happened to Mom?
Is she all right?
-Uh.
-Sweetheart, you kind
of overreacted a bit,
don't you think?
-It's OK.
Don't be so hard on her.
She saw me on the floor and
got scared, like anybody would.
Sorry for that, Kaede.
-See?
Grandma's doing just fine.
You don't have to worry.
But you do have to
get ready for school.
-I want to stay.
-Not when you have school.
Now do as I say and get ready.
Don't be concerned, Kaede.
Like I said,
Grandma's just fine.
Besides, I can take care of her.
Are you even listening
to me, young lady?
-You're the one
who never listens!
Why'd you come here?
I hate you, Dad!
-What's happening?
[sigh]
-I'm so confused, Tomoe.
I'm really lost.
It's awful.
I don't know what I did
to bring all this on,
but Kaede absolutely hates me.
MURAMASA: Can't believe
it's already been six years.
-Huh?
-I was in the area,
so I stopped by.
-Sorry for all the fuss.
Kaede got a little
panicked this morning.
-First you, now her.
They say the apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
I guess they're right.
Let me ask you
something-- do you
know why Kaede got so upset?
-Uh, not really.
-'Cause she feels alone.
Mom is the only
one she has left.
Since you live in the city and
can't be around all the time,
she's afraid she's
gonna be abandoned
if she loses her grandmother.
She lives with that fear
every day of her life.
That's why she gets so
upset when even the smallest
thing goes wrong.
When you think about
it, Kaede was probably
never able to get over
the loss of her mother.
-That would explain a lot.
MURAMASA: I'm not trying to
blame you for the situation.
I mean, you have your
own life to live.
But Kaede is always
feeling lonely.
Just keep that in mind when
she acts the way she does.
-You're the one
who never listens!
-You're right, Kaede.
I guess Daddy never did try
to understand your feelings.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Stop that right now!
Mom, you should be lying down!
-Oh, I'm all right.
See?
-Come on, who cares about
those stupid cabbages?
It's too much stress!
This is what caused you to hurt
your back in the first place!
-I put so much effort
into raising these babies.
I can't just ignore them
when they're under stress
and not doing well.
It's the same way
I feel about you.
-I'm not a vegetable, mom.
-Please, if you can hear
me, please help Grandma,
I'm begging you.
I couldn't bear
it if I lost her.
I'd be alone.
-Mom, it's pouring outside.
Think we should go pick her up?
[thunder]
[whimpering]
[scream]
[gasp]
-Can somebody help me?
Is anyone out there?
-Yes.
Yes.
I see.
Well, thank you very much.
-What's up?
Do they know where she is?
-It looks like she left
school over an hour ago,
and she hasn't gone to any
of her friends' houses.
-That's bad.
And I still can't get through
to her on her cell phone.
I'm gonna go check out the area.
Kaede!
Where are you?
[car horn]
Kaede!
-Have you had any luck?
-No.
What about you?
-Not a trace.
The rain so heavy, nobody's
out, let alone Kaede.
I hope she was able to find
shelter inside somewhere,
[beep]
[thunder]
[whimper]
KOTETSU: Kaede!
It's Daddy!
-Kaede!
-Answer me, Kaede!
Kaede!
No time.
I'll have to take my chances.
-Wait.
Even if you use your
powers, it won't do any good
if you don't have any
idea where she is.
-I know that.
Now be quiet for just
a little bit, OK?
KOTETSU (VOICEOVER):
I'm almost out of time.
Kaede, please-- say something!
KAEDE: Dad.
Help me, please!
Dad!
-Kaede!
[sobbing]
KOTETSU: Kaede!
-Huh?
KOTETSU: Kaede,
are you in there?
-I'm here, Dad!
-I'm coming to get you!
I know you're scared, but I'm
gonna get you out of there.
Don't worry, everything's
gonna be fine!
[grunting]
What?
I need more time.
-Dad?
KOTETSU: It's OK, Kaede.
Your dad is Kotetsu Kaburagi.
It'll take more than a little
storm to make me give up!
[grunting]
What good is a hero if he
can't save his own daughter?
[grunt]
[thunder]
Kaede.
-(SOBBING) Oh, Daddy!
-It's OK, sweetheart.
You're safe now.
-(SOBBING) I'm sorry
I got in trouble.
I didn't mean to scare everyone.
-It's all right, Kaede.
I'm sorry as well, baby.
I'm sorry I wasn't
here for you more.
MOTHER: Heading back already?
You barely had time to rest.
KOTETSU: I know, Mom.
But, uh, I'll rest when I
get back here in a few days.
MOTHER: Huh?
KOTETSU: Well, I'll
be coming back just
as soon as I turn
in my resignation.
MOTHER: Resignation?
What brought all this on?
KOTETSU: Oh, nothing
in particular, really.
MOTHER: Hmm?
KOTETSU: Well, there is
something in particular.
I decided I wanted to
spend more time with Kaede,
and I made her a promise.
Right?
Right.
-Mm-hmm.
-I see.
But, Kotetsu--
-I'm starting to become
vintage, Mom, let's face it.
-Huh?
-I think it's time for me
to move on with my life.
[sigh]
Mm, there's my ride.
[honk]
-Dad, are you really
gonna come home soon?
-Yeah.
I'll be back very soon,
right after I quit my job.
-Do you swear?
Don't say it if you
don't really mean it!
-Oh, I mean it, sweetie.
Promise.
Watch out, you're
gonna hurt yourself.
Kaede!
-Kaede!
-Huh?
You mean--
-I'll be waiting for you!
Here!
This is so you don't forget!
-Uh, thanks, sweetheart.
She's-- she's becoming a NEXT.
-Kaede!
-Huh?
Oh!
[grunt]
[laughter]
-The apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
KOTETSU (VOICEOVER):
It's gonna be OK, Tomoe.
I promised you'd I'd
always be a hero.
But now, I'll be Kaede's hero,
and that's all I really need.
[music - tamaki, "mind game"]
BARNABY: Hi, I'm Barnaby,
the member of Tiger and Bunny
who starts showering by
washing his neck first.
What?
She woke up?
Great.
Now we can find out the
truth about Ouroboros.
Join us next time on "Tiger and
Bunny" for "Ignorance is Bliss.
See ya.