[music playing]
-This is a perfect chance
to debut your new look.
-Huh?
What?
It's you?
-You gonna talk
all day, old man?
-Gah!
No way.
[MUSIC - UNISON SQUARE GARDEN,
"ORION O NAZORU"]
-Hey!
How come I'm stuck
in the sidecar?
-I think it suits you well.
-Yeah, dream on.
BARNABY: Take it up
with our sponsor.
-You passed it.
Turn around.
Where are you going?
You blind?
[boom]
[glass shattering]
[screaming]
-Evacuate the area!
-Everybody, please,
just keep calm.
This way!
I'll handle this area.
You all go on ahead.
-So what are we gonna
do, sit here and watch?
-I'm still studying the area.
We don't want to just
rush in at the same time.
We've got to time our
entrance for maximum effect.
-Ugh, what a clown.
-Excuse me?
-That's a brilliant idea.
Why don't we wait till the
whole city's destroyed?
Ugh.
A real hero doesn't
time his entrance--
AGNES (ON COMM):
OK, it's showtime.
We are ready to go live,
everyone, so good luck.
-In three, two--
["hero tv live" theme music]
-OK, time to move.
-You sure?
Don't want to touch up
your makeup or go-- hah!
-Sorry.
-Hey, what the?
ANNOUNCER: And look
who's just arrived.
Now we can really get
this party started!
[music playing]
-My ice is a little
cold, but your crime
has been completely put on hold.
ANNOUNCER: It's Blue Rose,
that crime-fighting hottie.
Hold on to your hats.
It's not just her
body that's naughty.
-Yes!
I made it into the shot.
-This is ridiculous.
That's not how-- huh?
Hey!
I thought we were a team!
[boom]
I'll show you how to
bring this thing down.
-Yeah?
Good luck with that.
-I'm going to have to drop
a line on this little guy.
Unh!
Hah!
Huh?
What's wrong with
the damn thing?
Unh!
Aaah!
Oh!
See?
Watch and learn, kid.
Hey, where'd he go?
ANNOUNCER: Is that
who I think it is?
Yes!
It's our newest fan
favorite, Barnaby Brooks Jr.!
-Hah.
-Hnh.
Man, I hate that.
OK, big guy.
[digital beeping]
WILD TIGER: You're going down.
[weapon fires]
-Oh!
What the hell?
-Gotcha.
Unh!
-Aahh!
-Huh?
-Aaaahhhh!
Unh!
-Unh, ohhh ho ho!
[both crying out]
-Great plan.
Worked out real well.
-Well, maybe if you
hadn't gotten in the way.
Huh?
Guh!
-Just undo this thing
and let's get moving.
-Well, maybe-
-Now!
-Uh, look up there.
-Huh?
Oh, great.
[both shouting]
-I'm telling you, I
can't work with this guy.
-Well, I must admit your
debut as a team was hardly
a rousing success.
In fact, I thought
we'd seen the of you.
KOTETSU: [laughs sheepishly]
-It was just lucky for you
that that thing ran out of gas.
NEWSCASTER: It's a mystery why
the rampaging statue suddenly
stopped, or why, hours later,
it remains frozen in position.
-So do we have any idea who's
behind it or what they want?
LLOYDS: Forget that.
You've got bigger problems.
-Huh?
-You don't seem to understand
the situation you're in.
You are yesterday's news.
KOTETSU: Hey!
-Listen, this offer to
be Barnaby's sidekick
is your last chance to
remain relevant at all.
-What?
-That's right, sidekick.
Backup.
Second banana.
And you're lucky to get it.
-Sidekick to that showboat?
That guy's a costume clown who--
LLOYDS: Speaking
of costumes, you've
got some explaining to do.
-Hm?
[speech inaudible]
-What's that?
-Uh, suit?
Huh?
-Uh-huh, OK.
-Well, it was my first time.
-Hey, come on, that
suit isn't that bad.
-Hee!
-Uhhh--
-Nnnnhh!
Hey, whoa, whoa!
All right, that's enough!
I get it, I get it!
OK, OK, you proved your point.
-Heh heh.
-What a weird little guy.
-Yeah?
-You mean this?
-Oh!
ELECTRONIC FEMALE VOICE:
The current time is 3:28 PM.
-Is that the time?
Oh, man, I gotta go.
I-- I gotta go!
KOTETSU: I swear I'm on my way.
I'm just running a
little late, that's all.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): You said
you'd be here at 3:00.
-I know, honey.
I'm sorry.
KAEDE: Are you even coming?
KOTETSU (ON PHONE): What?
Of course I am.
-Yeah?
When are you gonna be here?
KOTETSU (ON PHONE):
Uh, well, um--
-[sighs]
KOTETSU (ON PHONE):
Don't worry, Kaede.
I'll be there.
When do you actually go on?
-You're not coming, are you?
KOTETSU: Op; I am coming.
When's it start?
-4:00.
-OK, plenty of time.
[alarm buzzing]
-Hang on a second, honey.
Calling Tiger and Barnaby.
It's showtime.
The statue has
started moving again.
We need you suited up and
on the scene right now.
-Ugh.
Uh, Kaede?
KAEDE (ON PHONE): Dad, you'll
never guess who's here.
-Hm?
-The reigning junior
champion, Isaac.
KOTETSU (ON PHONE): No kidding.
-He's, like, the best
in the whole world.
It's so cool.
I've always wanted to
meet him in person.
And now he's going to be
here, in the competition.
-Hey, that's great, honey.
Oh!
Huh?
Oh.
How long have you
been waiting here?
-Just 3 and 1/2
minutes of my life
that I'm never
going to get back.
But hey, don't worry about it.
-Oh, boy.
How'd I get stuck with you?
[screaming]
-Hang on.
-Huh?
[digital beeping]
-Ah-- hunh, ahh!
BARNABY: What are you doing?
-What do you think?
-Just wait a minute.
-That thing's got a little kid.
-Or maybe it's the
other way around.
-What are you--
get out of my way.
-Look, maybe it's not the
kid that needs saving.
You see where I'm
going with this?
-No.
-What if he's the NEXT
controlling the statue?
-Well, he's still in danger.
-Maybe the kid's a NEXT
with telekinetic powers.
-Well, while you're thinking
about it, I'm going in.
-I wouldn't be so hasty.
Remember what
happened last time.
-Hey, that was an accident.
-You know, I'm beginning
to seriously question
your judgment.
I never liked this idea.
If the sponsors weren't
insisting on it,
I'd quit this team right now.
-That makes two of us.
Uh-oh.
[gunfire]
[screaming]
-(SHOUTING) Don't move,
or you're all dead!
[people whimpering]
WOMAN: Don't hurt us!
[glass breaking]
-You!
-Drop the gun.
-Why, it's Mr. Legend.
[machine gun fire]
WOMAN: Oh, wow!
-Huunh!
RINGLEADER: One more
move and the kid gets it.
-Huh?
[screams]
-What the hell's
wrong with this kid?
Unnhh!
-What do you know?
-Keep away.
-Huh?
-You don't want to
come anywhere near me
when I start to
go off like this.
-And why's that?
-Because I hurt people.
MR. LEGEND: You've got it wrong.
-Huh?
-With those powers of
yours, you can save people.
-Uh?
-After all, you saved me.
That makes you a hero, too.
-Have a nice nap, old man?
-Funny.
You gonna tell me what happened?
-The statue grabbed us
and then he stopped again.
-And you're just sitting here?
Why don't you escape?
-Well, I can't.
-Huh?
-Without using my power, I mean.
-Then use it, you idiot.
What are you waiting for?
-We've only got five minutes.
I want to save it
till I really need it.
-Unbelievable.
Well, suit yourself,
Little Bunny.
I'm out of here.
BARNABY: Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa-- hold it.
-What?
-What did you call me?
Did you just call me Bunny?
-Yeah, why not?
You got those long pink ears and
you're always hopping around.
You're just like a
cute little bunny.
-I am not a bunny.
My name is Barnaby.
-(MOCKING VOICE)
I am not a bunny.
I'm a Barnaby.
BARNABY: I don't talk like that.
-(MOCKING VOICE) I
don't talk like that.
Nyah, nyah, nyah.
AGNES (ON COMM):
Heads up, you two.
Huh?
-We've got another statue
going on a rampage.
There's a giant stone lion
headed toward the New Morgan
district.
WILD TIGER: What?
That's where the ice rink is.
Hunnnhhhh!
Aahhh!
BARNABY: You mind
getting me out, too?
-Huh?
-Well, I mean, you're all
powered up and everything.
-You're right.
I am.
[phone ringing]
[laughter]
-Aah!
-Come on, Issac.
we've got to get ready.
ANNOUNCER (ON PA):
All participants,
please assemble backstage now.
[car alarm blaring]
-Daddy's coming, Kaede.
Huh?
Gotcha.
AGNES (ON COMM):
Tiger, you read me?
-You can't use your wire guns.
-What?
-The statue's a historical
cultural artifact.
The government doesn't
want it damaged.
-Well, tell them too bad.
Saving the lives of
innocent people comes first.
AGNES (ON COMM): You
break it, you buy it.
-Meaning?
-The statue's a
national treasure.
You have any idea
how much it's worth?
-Oh.
Got it.
Hey, kid, come on
down from there.
-Just stay!
Away!
[loud roar]
-Wait!
-Huh?
-Oh, no!
Hmmnnnnnngh!
[glass shattering]
[screams]
[loud roar]
[screaming]
[boom]
[whimpers]
-Oh no.
I can't stop it!
Aaahh!
-Unh!
Mmmnnnnnhhahh!
This way, folks!
[screaming]
WILD TIGER: Kaede!
Nooooooooooo!
[smash]
Kaede.
KAEDE: Thank you
so much, mister.
-Ah!
Huh?
-Now you get on out of here.
-I sure will.
-Hey, um, thanks.
-Huh?
Thanks for what?
I didn't save your life, did I?
-No, but, uh--
ISAAC: Help me!
Help!
Aaaaahhhh!
-Stay out of my way.
WILD TIGER: Why are
you doing this, kid?
-He knows why.
He and the others.
WILD TIGER: What do you mean?
-My whole life, they've
hated me and treated me
like I was some kind of freak.
-No, not your whole life.
Just since you started
to make things move.
Normal kids can't
do what you do.
I mean, it freaks us out.
We don't hate you.
We're scared of you.
-I didn't ask to be
given these powers.
It's not my fault!
-I don't want you around.
Just go away!
-You're going away.
[roar]
WILD TIGER: Slow down, kid.
I know just how you feel.
-No, you don't.
-I do.
Because it happened to me too.
I was about your age when
I found out I was a NEXT.
-Huh?
-My friends turned on
me, called me a freak.
I hated them for that.
Most of all, I hated my powers.
Then a hero called Mr.
legend came along and told
me something that
changed my life.
-With those powers of
yours, you can save people.
-My powers can't.
WILD TIGER: Why not?
-Because they're not like
a real hero's powers.
All I can do to make stuff move.
-Trust me, one day you will
find the right use for them.
I promise.
-You mean it?
-You could be one of the best.
-Really?
-Sure.
Now come on down and let's have
the police call your parents.
-What are you doing?
If we don't arrest him,
we don't score any points.
-Oh, shut up, will ya?
OK, kid, you want to be a hero?
This is your first step.
What do you say?
You gonna come down?
It's gonna be OK, Tony.
WOMAN: Oh, are you OK?
[scream]
BYSTANDER: Watch out!
The building's collapsing!
-Huh?
-I'm on it!
ROCK BISON: Let's go.
Go!
-Help me, somebody!
-I got it.
Save your power.
Unh!
ROCK BISON: Damn!
We're losing it!
[heroes grunting with effort]
ROCK BISON: Glad
to see you, buddy.
-Thanks.
And thanks again.
Uh-oh.
-What's wrong, Tiger?
-I'm out of time.
-Huh?
-Power's about to run out.
-Well, we gotta do something.
-(SHOUTING) Hey, Tony!
-Uh?
WILD TIGER: We can't hold it!
It's gonna fall!
[screaming]
-We need your help, Tony!
We need you now!
-I can't.
WILD TIGER: You can do it!
I know you can!
I'm down to five seconds.
Four, three, two--
[heroes grunting with effort]
-Huh?
[laughs]
[cheering]
TONY: Yay!
I did it!
-Hey, somebody give him a medal!
[cheering]
-Unless I'm mistaken, you
just saved the day, Tony.
Do you know what that means?
Means you're a hero.
-I'm a hero?
I
[siren]
ISAAC: Hey, Tony!
You were awesome back there.
-Come on.
You have plenty of power left.
-Huh?
Whoa!
Well, what do you
know about that?
-Tch.
The guy's a loose cannon.
I don't think this team
thing is gonna work.
MAVERICK: On the contrary,
it's working perfectly.
-Yes, but--
-The two of you have
captured people's attention.
Viewership is up
whenever you're on.
Now's your chance
to sell yourself.
There's a reason you
revealed your true identity
to the public.
You're not going to let all
your careful preparations
go to waste, are you, my boy?
-No, sir.
KOTETSU: I'm just
glad you're all right.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): I'm fine.
But it was so scary!
-I'm sorry, honey.
I should have been
there to protect you.
That's what a dad's for, right?
KAEDE (ON PHONE): Oh, I had
plenty of protection, Dad.
-Huh?
KAEDE (ON PHONE): This
guy Barnaby saved me.
He's one of those
heroes, you know?
Oh, and you should see him.
He's so cool!
And really cute.
He's my new favorite
hero on the show.
-Uh-- um-- [sigh]
[MUSIC - AOBOZU, "HOSHI NO
SUMIKA"]
-Ourobouros.
[glass cracks]
BARNABY (VOICEOVER): This is
Barnaby, the member of Tiger
and Bunny with the
glasses, and-- hey,
who went and planted the bomb?
I'm right in the middle of
a freaking interview here.
Next time on "Tiger and
Bunny," many a true word
is spoken in just.
See ya.