-Just what the hell are you?
[theme music]
-Wow, kiddo, you're doing great.
Hey, do some more.
KAEDE (ON PHONE):
2 times 7 is 14.
2 times 6 is 18.
And 2 times 9 is 18.
-That's amazing, Kaede.
So smart.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): 3 is 9.
-When did you get so good at
math all of a sudden, baby?
Huh?
-Um, a long time ago.
-You don't say.
Daddy's very proud
of you, sweetie.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): Yeah, Dad?
Maybe you shouldn't talk
to me like that anymore.
I mean, I'm not a baby.
-Huh?
GRANDMOTHER (ON PHONE)::
Kaeda, it's late.
You should get to bed.
-OK.
GRANDMOTHER (ON PHONE):: Why
do you sound so depressed?
-Oh, it just sucks
how kids grow up
even when their
parents aren't around.
-Oh, it's not that bad.
The truth is the reason Kaede's
acting so upset right now
is she lost her teddy bear.
-Her what?
Really?
-When she's sad like this,
she really needs her father.
Can't you come home more often?
-I'd love to, but
there's no way.
You know how it is, Mom.
Heroes just don't
get vacation days.
-That may be, but you still need
to take care of yourself, dear.
-I know.
Love ya.
TIGER: A paid vacation?
-You've put in the hours,
now's a good time to use them.
Starting tomorrow, why don't
you take two or three days off?
-But a hero's work
is never done.
-You can save the speeches.
The media will have a
field day if they find out
where violating labor laws.
-But this doesn't seem right.
-You know the deal, if you don't
like it, you can always quit.
-But what if you guys need me?
-Ah, I think we'll be just fine.
-Oh, yeah, Bunny's
the big number two.
[cell phone ringing]
-Kotetsu.
-Hey, it's me.
Where are ya?
You wanna come knock
back a few cold ones?
KOTETSU: I, uh,
don't feel up to it.
-Aw, what a buzz kill.
Everyone else is living
it up on their day off.
KOTETSU: Well, then
call one of them.
-Aw, come on.
-Oh, he's so cute.
Thank you for the
present, Daddy.
-Come one, come all, and
take a gander at this.
The super rated toy is going
to sell out in no time.
The ultra mega popular Mad Bear.
Just a few in stock.
This is the must have toy.
-Hm?
Kids really like this crap?
-Oh, sir, you
cannot even imagine.
Those fresh out of surgery
stitches, the dead fish
eyes with that blank stare.
Every kid goes crazy
for this little guy.
-Really?
Gee, I don't know.
-Buy this for your kids and
they'll love you forever.
-Wrap it up.
-Hello.
KOTETSU (ON PHONE):
Hey, Bunny, it's me.
Listen, uh, I'm taking
a few days off work.
Can you cover for
me while I'm out?
-Well, that's a surprise.
You don't really seem
like the vacation type.
KOTETSU (ON PHONE): Yeah, you
know what the best part is?
I won't have to see your
ugly mug for awhile.
Oh, boy, won't that be a relief.
-Hey, kid, how's it
feel to watch them die?
-Hey, Bunny?
Where'd you go, man?
Are you mad or something?
[phone hanging up]
-I was just kidding with ya.
-Mr. Maverick, sir, the man who
killed my parents, I found him.
-Sweetheart, I'm
heading home right now.
KAEDE (ON PHONE):
OK, drive safe.
-Oh, and Kaede.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): Yeah, dad?
-You're gonna love
the present I got ya.
Apparently, this stuffed
animal's all the rage.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): Um, it's
not a Mad Bear, is it?
Uck, I hope you didn't that.
Those are so hideous.
-Oh, those ugly things?
I would never get you that.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): So are you
really coming home or what?
-I promise I'll be
there in a jiff.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): Dad, you
always break your promises.
-This time, I promise I won't.
Damn it.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): Hello?
Dad, are you there?
What happened?
Dad, can you still hear me?
Dad.
-Sorry, Kaede, it looks like I'm
not going to keep that promise.
KAEDE (ON PHONE): I knew it.
-Ah!
[beeping]
MAVERICK (ON PHONE):
Wild Tiger, we're
getting word of a terrorist
bombing at Braux Bridge.
You're nearby, right?
Get to the scene quick.
-Oh, first you force
me to take a vacation,
now you want me to end it early.
Make up your mind.
MAVERICK (ON PHONE): Wild Tiger,
a hero's work is never done.
-Hey, that's exactly
what I said to.
MAVERICK (ON PHONE): I'll
send in the transporter ASAP.
-I should have known something
like this was going to happen.
Did you catch that, Bunny?
Some terrorist lit
up the Braux Bridge.
Where are you right now?
-Actually, I was
heading to Abas Prison.
KOTETSU (ON PHONE): What?
Why?
-I wanted to go see an inmate.
It's the man who
murdered my parents.
-Wait, you found him?
BARNABY (ON PHONE): I was
on my way to confirm it,
but I'll turn around and head
to the bridge right away.
-Naw, keep going.
Look, you've been searching
for this guy for like 20 years,
right?
I'm not going to make you turn
back when you're this close.
-But you'll have to deal with
these terrorists by yourself.
-What?
Are you saying I can't
handle things without you?
Don't you worry, bud.
I've been a hero a
lot longer than you.
I got this.
Now, get to that prison and
find out if he's your man.
NEWS ANNOUNCER: This
just in, everyone.
the Braux Bridge just
suffered a massive explosion
during heavy traffic,
and the Justice Bureau
is treating the incident as
a possible terrorist attack.
-All right, so who's the one
that needed some attention over
here?
What's that?
Oh boy.
Worst vacation ever.
-Hello, Heroes.
As you can see, we have
a bit of an incident.
You know what to do, arrest
every last one of them.
ALL: Yes, ma'am.
-That's it.
I'm going full power.
You want to dance?
Let's dance.
Knock, knock, who's there?
What the hell?
AGNES (ON HEADSET): What
did you find, Tiger?
-It's a Mad Bear.
They're like super rare.
AGNES (ON HEADSET): A what?
-Haven't you heard of them?
They have these fresh
out of surgery stitches
and dead fish eyes
with this blank stare.
Whoa.
Hey!
Get back here, you dumb doll.
Hey.
Come on.
Get back here.
A-ha, nowhere to run, Mr. Bear.
Ah, that smug little bastard.
Listen, pal, you are
so not worth 30 bucks.
Whoa.
-A teddy bear?
KOTETSU: That's
what I just said.
Look, there's got to be
a mastermind somewhere
with the power to control them.
-A NEXT must be behind this.
What happened?
-There was another explosion
at the North Gold heliport.
-So the plot thickens.
This show is getting exciting.
Sky High, Rock Bison, Fire
Emblem, Origami Cyclone
come in.
Forget the bridge.
Get to North Gold now.
ALL: Yes, ma'am.
-Well, is the army
containing the attack?
-Actually, Maverick has put
in a request with the mayor
to let the Heroes take
care of it from here on.
-Heroes have never dealt
with a terrorist attack
of this magnitude before.
It's outrageous, I tell ya.
What is he thinking?
-Well, Heroes, let's
see if you're up to it.
-Looks like the dolls
are at this location too.
-The same person is
responsible for both attacks?
-What?
Another one?
-Where is it now?
-Two more blasts now at
East Gold and West Bronze.
AGNES (ON HEADSET):
You're kidding.
-We're almost ready, Mr. Jake.
-Hey, Fire Emblem, Rock Bison,
leave this to the others.
Got to East Gold.
-Oh, come on.
-We just got here.
-Oh, she's such a tease.
-And Blue Rose, Dragon Kid, get
your asses to West Bronze Port.
-Ha, right.
-Will do.
But are you sure we should
leave Tiger by himself?
-What did she just say?
I can handle myself, lady,
and hey, if things get rough,
I'll just use your cutie escape.
Hey, come on, I
wasn't done talking.
Party time.
MECHANICAL VOICE: Powers
expire in five seconds.
Four, three--
-This always happens.
MECHANICAL VOICE: Zero.
-Damn it.
Why haven't you heard
back from Barnaby yet?
-I keep dialing his com, ma'am,
but he must be ignoring it.
-What could possibly be
more important than this?
[beeping]
-What?
Are you saying I can't
handle things without you?
NEWS ANNOUNCER: Yes, Dragon Kid
brought down one of the robots.
-Hey, don't go
stealing my targets.
-Oops.
Sorry.
NEWS ANNOUNCER: Fancy foot work.
They outwit another one
with a double escape.
-Fire!
NEWS ANNOUNCER: Now, Fire
Emblem's cranking up the heat.
-There you go.
NEWS ANNOUNCER: Oh, no.
Rock Bison and Fire
Emblem are surrounded.
-Sky High!
-And there he is.
The king of Heroes whoops in and
shows us why he's the champion.
-Thank you for saving me.
-This is my duty.
There's no need to thank me.
-Origami Cyclone actually
racking up the points
and he lands a nice close up.
Until he gets punched
off the screen.
-And stay down.
Man, how many of these walking
garbage cans are there?
-Help me!
Ahh!
-Oh, for-- it was
supposed to stop the car.
I got ya.
Just hang in there.
-This is really bad.
All the Heroes are starting
to get overwhelmed.
Everyone watching this
is going to panic.
Ma'am, I really think we
should go off the air.
-Don't be such a baby.
We're not letting
this chance slip away.
-You want to make the
same mistake as last time?
Don't you see?
The public will turn
against us if they
lose faith in the Heroes.
Just like they did
when Lunatic appeared.
-It's not worth the risk.
OK, stop the broadcast.
Kill the live feed
and switch to tape.
-You'll do nothing of the sort.
What kind of show is this
if we can't trust our stars?
We owe it to the Heroes
to have faith in them.
They'll pull
through like always.
-Look, even the king of
Heroes can't beat these guys.
-You can do it, Heroes.
NEWS ANNOUNCER: It appears
Wild Tiger is in real danger.
He's sacrificing himself to
protect an innocent woman.
-Good.
-Everything is ready now, ma'am.
-Excellent work.
-Bastards.
Think a few bullets can stop me?
Got it.
Just hold on.
I will get you out of there.
You know, I really hate
using these things,
but for them, I'll
make an exception.
Say hello to my little friend.
Ah!
-You all right?
-Bunny, what are you doing here?
-It's been awhile
since I carried you.
If feels like you've
packed on some pounds.
-Shut up and put
me down, will ya?
Hey, what about
your prison thing?
-His sentence is 250 years.
I don't think he's
going anywhere soon.
And besides, I owed
you one for saving me.
Now we're even.
-All righty then, let's
take out the trash
so we can pay your
friend here a visit.
-Sounds good.
Just try to stay out of my way.
-Your way?
Smart ass.
[high pitched noise]
-That noise.
-What is that?
-What the hell is all this?
-Business cards?
But why?
-That's weird.
-Hey, it's that symbol.
FEMALE VOICE: Attention
citizens of Sternbild.
Your resistance will
not be tolerated.
-Who's voice is that?
-Nothing works.
Somebody must be
jamming our signal.
KOTETSU (ON HEADSET): Agnus?
Want to tell us what's going on?
-The hell if I know.
-Now that we have
your attention,
let us introduce ourselves.
We're known as Ouroboros.
-It's them.
-We have seized control of
every major traffic point
across your entire city.
I'm afraid Sternbild
is now isolated
from the rest of the world.
Or, in lay mans terms,
your entire population
has become our hostage.
We only have one
single demand, there's
a comrade of ours being
held in a Voss prison
and we would like him to
be released immediately.
If you fail to
honor this demand,
we will destroy half
the pillars that
hold Sternbild above water,
thus sinking your whole city.
-You're insane.
-You have more than 20
million citizens here
and I doubt many of them can
tread water for eternity.
The clock is ticking.
If you want to save yourselves,
you know what to do.
Release one man.
His name's Jake Martinez.
-Damn!
-All done.
[theme music]
-Hi, I'm Barnaby, the member
of Tiger and Bunny that refers
rose wine.
Ouroborus, you've finally
come out of the shadows.
Good luck, Origami.
If this plan works, then
I will finally-- Next time
on "Tiger and Bunny,
The Die is Cast."
See ya.