[music playing]
[gunfire and shattering glass]
[digital beeping]
WILD TIGER: Well, this
is getting us nowhere.
I say we rush 'em.
What do you think?
You in?
Hello?
Ah, forget it.
You do what you want.
I'm going in.
-OK, on the count of three,
we'll rush them from the right.
WILD TIGER: Screw the counting.
Let's go!
Wait, why the right?
-There's less dirt on this
side, so there'll be less mud.
It's the logical
direction to attack from.
-Forget logic.
I go off my gut.
And my gut tells me we go left.
-No, right.
-Like it matters
which way we go.
-So we go right.
-No, left!
-Definitely right.
-Nnnnghh!
That does it!
Listen, Bunny, I've been around
the block a few times, OK?
I think I know what
I'm doing here.
Aaah!
[MUSIC - UNISON SQUARE GARDEN,
"ORION O NAZORU"]
BARNABY: Well, that shut you up.
And for the last time,
stop calling me Bunny.
-Huh?
-OK, we've had enough of this.
This simulation is over.
You just proved my point.
Your gut?
If that's what we're
supposed to rely on,
I don't want any part of it.
-It was just a simulation.
And I--
BARNABY: And you're
lucky that's all it was.
If it'd been real,
neither of us would
be walking out of here alive.
-Tch.
-Uh--
-Oh, don't mind us.
Just pretend we're not here.
Act natural.
-What a jerk.
Why I agreed to this,
I'll never know.
LLOYDS: Don't you get it?
You're supposed to be a team.
That's the whole point.
A team is about teamwork,
and yours is terrible.
Going off the
results so far, I'm
beginning to wonder why we
ever hired you, Kotetsu.
-What?
It's my fault?
-Well, I'll leave
you guys to it.
-Hey!
Where do you think you're--
-No, let him go.
Barnaby's not the problem.
In fact, our stock's been
up ever since we signed him.
As for you, well, we
expected much more.
And frankly, it's
make-or-break time.
-[sigh]
-We thought you'd
set a better example
while showing him the ropes.
You've been at this a lot
longer than he has, after all.
-Not that much longer.
-Well, we thought a training
simulation would give you
a chance to
demonstrate leadership,
to show us what you've got.
-A simulation?
-Yes.
It's never the same thing,
running around in a simulator.
There's no danger,
no risk involved.
I prefer the real thing.
-Really?
We could fire you.
Would that be real enough?
[sigh]
Ugh, when it rains, it pours.
Hey, turn it off, sill you?
I'm rusting here.
AGNES: Wild Tiger, got a moment?
Or maybe I should
call you Kotetsu,
since you're clearly off duty.
ROCK BISON: What do
I think of Barnaby?
Well, he's an opponent, but
he's an opponent I can respect.
It'll be an honor to
beat him this season.
FIRE EMBLEM: He's
going to be a big star.
I mean, come on, with
that face and that body?
Yes, he's going places.
I only hope my place
is one of them.
Talk about yummy.
SKY HIGH: You know, I
sense something special
from that man.
And so I say, thanks,
and thanks again.
-Uh, I got nothing.
AGNES: Cut!
Cut.
What the hell do you
mean, you've got nothing?
I thought you were
supposed to be his partner.
So that's it.
Are you trying to wreck my show?
-My mother taught me if you
can't say anything nice, then--
-This is the most idiotic,
unprofessional behavior
I've ever seen.
-Idiotic?
What about Sky
High's catch phrase?
-Huh?
-"Thanks, and thanks again."
How dumb is that?
-There is nothing
wrong with that.
The people love
that catch phrase.
They eat it up.
-What people?
-Look, I don't
have time for this.
I'll just write
your lines for you.
-What?
AGNES: I'll write them.
You read them.
[beeping]
-OK, I guess I don't
get any privacy.
-Nope.
We want an up close and personal
look at the real Barnaby.
-I'm afraid you won't find
my place very interesting.
-Oh, that's OK.
The fans just want a peek at
how you spend your downtime,
you know?
-Uh-- uh--
-[laughs]
-What's so funny?
-Hey, it's cool.
I totally understand.
I'm a single guy myself.
-Huh?
-Don't worry, I'm not
going to let anything
get on the air that
would ruin your image.
-Thanks.
-Just let me know if you
come across any sites
you'd recommend, because
I'm always looking, heh.
-Mmph.
-The ceremony was held before
a large crowd in the Stern
Medaille Area today
to mark the completion
of the spectacular
Fortress Tower Building.
The high points took
place in the lobby,
where a statue of Mr. Legend,
the first hero, was unveiled.
On hand was Albert
Maverick, president and CEO
of Apollon Media.
-By building the
Fortress Tower, we
think we've added
a bold new landmark
to the skyline of
this great city,
as well as a symbol
of peace and a beacon
showing the way to
a better tomorrow.
MAVERICK (VOICEOVER):
It's time to go, Barnaby.
It's all right.
You won't ever be alone, my boy.
-I'm as alone as ever, sir.
KOTETSU: Hi there,
Bunny, old pal.
-Uh?
-Uh, hey, homey, you
want to, like, hang out?
-Why are you talking like that?
It's creepy, man.
-Ugh, I agree.
AGNES: Cut!
That's going to be the
worst acting I've ever seen.
And just call him Barnaby, OK?
That's his name.
-I was improvising.
-All this scene's
about is you wanting
to spend some time with your
partner on your day off.
What's so hard about that?
Now let's try it
again from the top.
-Hey, I'm not being
paid to be an actor.
AGNES: You're lucky anyone's
paying you for anything.
-So what am I supposed to do?
-Oh, you're OK.
Just be yourself, that's all.
-Just be myself?
That I can do.
[sigh]
He's being himself all
right, and it's sickening.
KID: Go get it signed!
He's not gonna bite you.
-There.
-Thanks!
-Now me, now me!
-Some people just have
it-- and some don't.
-What are you talking
about, you don't want it?
I'm giving it to you.
It's a collector's item.
-No thanks.
Wild Tiger's lame!
-Hey, come on, take it.
It's free.
You can exchange it
for something else.
Oh, come on.
CAIN: OK, hold it.
-Huh?
Where'd he come from?
-I don't know.
-He really thrives
on this stuff.
So does Origami Cyclone.
Hey there.
Are we almost done here?
AGNES: Yeah, it's late.
We've got to move on
to the next location.
KOTETSU: What?
There's more?
-One more, the Fortress
Tower Building.
The sponsor wants to get
in some free publicity
for its new landmark.
-Ah!
Look at that!
AGNES: Come on,
let's keep moving.
-Hey, wait!
Don't you want to
get a shot of this?
Look, it's Mr. Legend!
-There's something
wrong with it.
-Hey, is it OK to get on?
-Yeah, I just fixed it.
-Fixed it?
I thought this
place was brand new.
-It wasn't anything big.
I was just greasing the cables.
AGNES: Well?
We're waiting.
Let's go.
-Uh, you sure it's safe?
-Would you just get on?
-I'm telling you, it's him.
It's Barnaby.
Oh my god, he's gorgeous.
WAITRESS: Shut up!
[women giggle]
-Uh, doesn't that
make your arm tired?
-What do you mean?
-Excuse me, I was just wondering
if I could shake your hand.
-Sure.
I'm pleased to meet you.
WAITRESS: Likewise.
Thank you!
-You're not sick of that?
-Not really.
Comes with the territory.
So then, nice view.
-Oh, yeah, it's breathtaking.
-What's that building there?
-Jeez, man, I don't know.
Where are you--
well now, let's see.
Which one?
-There.
KOTETSU: Oh, that's just
your standard building.
BARNABY: What about that one?
KOTETSU: That would
be another building.
And you see that
thing next to it?
That's a building, too.
And so is that little
one down there.
In fact, most of these
things you see sticking up
are buildings.
-Will you please knock it off?
-I thought it was going well.
[alarm sounding]
-Uh?
MAN (ON PA): Attention
all visitors.
The building's security
alarm has been activated.
Great.
MAN (ON PA): Remain calm
and await instructions
from our security personnel.
SECURITY: Follow me!
Please, everyone!
We need to evacuate this floor!
-What's this all about?
A fire?
-Uh, well--
AGNES: It's OK.
They're Barnaby and Wild Tiger.
You know, "Hero TV"?
-Oh.
Well, in that case, OK.
Just between you and me,
we got a bomb threat.
-What?
-Where's the bomb?
-They didn't say.
We're still searching for it.
-Hm.
-It could be some sort
of prank, I guess.
-Were there any demands
made by the perpetrator?
SECURITY: No, not
that I'm aware of.
-It might be a prank.
-I was just greasing the cables.
-Uh!
Be right back!
-Hey, where the
hell are you going?
-Just checking something out!
WOMAN: A bomb?
Did you hear?
-It's all right, everybody.
It's just a prank,
from the looks of it.
But they want us
out just to be safe.
Just think of it
as a fire drill.
[ding]
-Damn!
It's huge!
That thing could flatten
this whole building!
[beeping]
[alarm ringing]
-All right, people, this way.
This way.
Over here.
-It's all right.
No need to panic.
Everyone stay calm.
Single file down the
stairs, nice and easy.
AGNES (VOICEOVER):
A hero showing
he's a hero even when
he's out of costume.
This footage is golden.
CAIN: Uh, Ms. Joubert?
Don't you think we should
maybe get out of here, too?
-You crazy?
Something finally
happens and you want to--
-(QUIETLY) Hey.
-What?
MAN: Get out of the building.
Run!
-How much time we got?
AGNES: So it really is a bomb.
-Let's go.
-You!
you're both coming with me!
We stick to them like glue.
Don't just stand there, come on!
-You've got to leave
like everyone else.
-Huh?
No way.
Listen, buddy, I've
got a show to run here,
whether you like it or not.
-You're not running this show.
This isn't a game
anymore, Agnes.
It's the real deal.
Look, if you want
us to be heroes,
you've got to get out of the
way and let us do our job.
And that job's defending
the people of this city,
and that means everyone--
including you and your crew.
-Whoa, man, that was a
cool speech he made, right?
-Huh?
Whatever.
-You're forgetting we've
got a job to do, too.
-Hey, don't worry.
The old man can shoot
your footage for you.
-Huh?
-Jerk.
I'm gonna have to direct
issue from the van.
Bring it around front right now.
We now go to Fortress Tower,
where officials have confirmed
that a bomb threat was
received at 7:15 this evening,
forcing them to evacuate
hundreds of visitors
from the brand new building.
-The latest word from
here is that everyone
has been evacuated
safely, largely
through the efforts of the
world famous heroes who
arrived quickly on the scene.
Authorities don't yet know
who is behind the bomb threat
or why the Fortress Tower
Building has been targeted.
They don't even know yet
whether there really is a bomb.
But meanwhile, they're
taking every precaution.
-OK, let's guess
this party started.
REPORTER (ON TV): And this
is certainly not the way
Albert Maverick envisioned
the grand opening.
-Can't wait to see if they'll
pull this off. [laughs]
WILD TIGER: So,
any ideas, Bunny?
[beeping]
While we're waiting,
tell our viewers
what hair product you use.
-What made you think that
the bomb was here, anyway?
-Oh, it just seemed strange
that they were still
working on the elevator after
the building had opened.
-Is that all?
-You saw that guy.
That workman.
He was way too clean to have
been greasing cables all day.
His clothes were spotless.
-Years and years of honing your
skills have paid off, I see.
-Uh, hey, it hasn't been
that many years, OK?
So, seriously, you got a plan?
-Yeah, to be careful.
You're lucky you didn't set it
off when you barged in here.
-Heh.
-Fortunately, I've had some
experience with devices
like this.
-You're kidding me.
You have?
Really?
How is that?
-It's part of what I consider
to be basic training for a hero.
(MOCKING) It's part
of what I consider
to be basic training for a hero.
Hm.
Well, OK.
Fine.
Then I guess I'll just sit
back and watch the master work.
-What are you doing?
-Well, what do you think?
You were the one who
stuck me with the camera.
-Look, I can handle
this by myself.
Why don't you get out
of here while you can?
-Yeah, right, like I'd
just run off and ditch you.
What kind of a jerk
do you think I am?
Don't answer that.
-Anyway, that's touching,
but if I were in your place,
I'd ditch me.
-Well, I'm not you.
Look, don't go getting the
idea it's 'cause I like you
or trust you or anything.
It's just that I've got
standards too, you know?
And one thing a hero doesn't
do is run away when the going--
-OK, I got it.
Now can you just keep
quiet for a little while?
-Fine, fine.
Not a problem.
[beeping]
ANNOUNCER (ON TV): You can
feel the tension in the air.
Still no word from
inside the building,
where our heroes,
Barnaby and Wild Tiger,
are attempting to
defuse the bomb.
And keep in mind, they're
facing this danger
without the protection
of their hero suits.
Time's running out on this,
the first-- and hopefully not
the last-- real test of Apollon
Media's two-man team of crime
fighters.
While we wait--
It's such a shame we're
not getting any live feed
from that camera
inside the building.
We're just repeating the same
boring footage over and over.
I've been thinking--
wasn't it Wild Tiger
who supposedly found the bomb?
Well, we know he hasn't
been happy playing Barnaby's
sidekick, so what if he made up
the story for a publicity stunt
or something?
-Will you be quiet?
ROCK BISON (VOICEOVER): Don't
get yourself killed, Kotetsu.
[beeping]
-Hey, are you almost done?
You do realize we're
way past the point
where we could get
to safety, right?
-Yes.
-You did it?
-I've only disconnected
the conductor.
So now--
-What?
-I have to avoid the trap.
-Huh?
-There are two wires, one above
and one below the detonator.
-Oh.
Well, isn't that just wonderful?
-I've got a choice.
Cut the correct one and
the bomb will be diffused.
-Yeah, I know, I know.
Stop milking it.
And if you cut the wrong one,
we'll be blown to bits, right?
-Yeah, that's about it.
WILD TIGER: Go high or go low.
Oh, wow, this is such a cliche.
So which one is it?
-If I knew, I would
have cut it already!
-I say go high.
-Excuse me?
-Cut the top one.
-Oh, man, not your gut again.
-Hey, my gut's got a
pretty good record.
-So far, it's 0 and 1.
-OK then, Mr. Logic,
which one's the right one?
-I'm trying to figure that
out, if you'd just shut up.
-Well, cut one of them.
Hurry up!
[beep and buzz]
-Uh!
-Gah!
-The bottom or top?
[beeping and buzzing]
WILD TIGER: Go high, now!
[sirens]
So tell me, what was it that
made you finally listen to me?
BARNABY: I don't
know, a snap decision?
Seemed like the right
thing to do at the time.
-So, you went off your gut.
Put us in a
real-world situation,
and I say we make
a pretty good team.
BARNABY: Well, don't
go getting too excited.
-Huh?
-I'm still not
looking for a partner.
And if I were, it
wouldn't be you.
WILD TIGER: You know, for a
bunny, you're not so cute.
-What?
ANNOUNCER: We can
finally show you
footage of exactly what
happened inside the building.
-Go high!
Unh!
ANNOUNCER: Take Wild
Tiger's furious fists
and Barnaby's
explosive footwork--
-Haaahh!
Unh!
ANNOUNCER: And you have the
formula for a winning team!
[boom]
[cheering]
AGNES: Right, a winning team.
Except for the fact that
they hate each other.
MARY ROSE: Speaking
of which, what
do you want to do
with this footage?
-Well, we're sure as
hell not gonna air it.
BARNABY: Great idea, old
man, blowing the roof
off the whole building.
Couldn't just open a window?
-Shut up!
What took you so long?
That's what I can't figure out.
I was nearly caught
in the explosion.
BARNABY: Maybe
that was the idea.
-That's it!
[MUSIC - AOBOZU, "HOSHI NO
SUMIKA"]
[playing piano]
-I'll have what he's having.
-So you saw the bomber, right?
What'd he look like?
-He was just your average
bad guy, that's all.
-That's it?
-But that sure was
no average bomb.
It was C9.
-But that's the most
sophisticated explosive around.
How'd he get his hands on that?
-It's a mean and
ugly world out there.
-But I see you and
Barnaby are getting along.
-We are?
[chuckles]
-Barnaby?
He's a great guy and
a terrific partner.
We have a lot more in
common than people think.
[chuckles]
[applause]
-Huh?
EMCEE: For the first time on
our stage, ladies and gentlemen,
wasn't she great?
Ms. Karina Lyle!
[applause]
-Thank you.
Huh?
-Huh?
KOTETSU (VOICEOVER):
Hey, this is
Kotetsu, the member
of Tiger and Bunny
who puts mayonnaise
on everything.
OK, so Blue Rose has a
nice voice, but how come
she's hung up her uniform?
Is she really gonna
quit being a hero?
Next time on "Tiger and
Bunny," fear is often-- what?