[music playing]
-Apparently, he only
kills murderers.
-So I heard.
-From all appearances, Lunatic
will continue his killing
till every criminal
is wiped out.
-Man, with Lunatic
around, crime will soon
be a thing of the past.
-He seems to be more
effective than the heroes.
Don't you think?
-What a face.
[theme music]
-I must say, this is unexpected.
-We never thought something
like this would cause the public
to mistrust our city's heroes.
-If more and more people
question their abilities,
it could be disastrous.
-You're right.
It could put Hero
TV in jeopardy.
-We've got to do
everything we can
to prevent that from happening.
At this point, we've got too
much money invested in them.
-Let's focus.
We can't afford to have someone
operating above the law.
Lunatic may think
he's fixing the world,
but the Justice
Bureau doesn't approve
of the use of
capital punishment.
We should be putting
together a plan
to arrest him, and as soon
as possible, before there
are more victims.
-Wait a second.
How do we do that?
We have no idea when or
where he'll strike again.
MAVERICK: Everyone,
please, calm down.
The immediate problem
for us is that people
are beginning to support
Lunatic's actions.
Our top priority
should be to help
people regain their
trust in the heroes.
We need to convince our
citizens that the heroes are
the true representatives
of justice in this world.
[applause]
-Young ladies and gentleman,
today some currently active
heroes have come here to
address the Hero Academy.
-What a waste of time.
-Huh?
-We're not being effective here.
We should be out on patrol,
looking for Lunatic.
-But the higher ups want us
to regain the people's trust
first.
-Their trust in what?
Our pretty smiles?
-So we finally meet.
Pay attention, everyone.
I shall now teach you the
secrets to becoming a hero.
Schwing.
That's right, everyone.
Now, repeat after me.
Schwing.
-It's so hot.
-I'm tired.
-Don't tell me you
want to go home.
-Sounds good to me.
-What?
You're giving up?
-Why not?
-Hey, what happened to you?
You were so jazzed about
that ninja star thing.
-I was putting on a
show for all those kids.
I'm not really qualified
to teach anybody.
I mean all I ever do is
stay in the background.
Who am I kidding?
I'm the lowest ranking hero.
-You shouldn't worry about that.
-And I got bashed on
my blog last week.
-Seriously?
-It was full of
comments telling me
I wasn't really
made to be a hero,
and that I should just quit.
-That's pretty weird.
I wasn't aware you had a blog.
-If you're worried about
what's been bringing down
our reputation, I
think it's been me.
-Tell me something.
Were you always such a downer?
-Hello, boys.
Are you ready?
-Principal Massini.
How are you, sir?
-Ah, Barnaby.
Good to see you.
You've become such a fine hero.
-Well, it's all
because of this school.
-Thank you, my boy.
I'm happy to hear that.
Ivan, I've been following
your activities too.
-Please don't call me
by my real answer, sir.
-Yes, you're right.
I should be calling
you Origami Cyclone.
The both of you have
made me so very proud.
-Ah, Mr. Tiger.
So pleased to meet you.
-Right back at you.
I hope you don't mind I'm
here even though I'm not
a graduate of the school.
-Don't be silly.
The students will
be thrilled to meet
someone who's an ex-star hero.
-Maybe you could
leave out the ex
and just introduce
me as a star hero.
-Why, of course.
We're all looking forward
to hearing the lectures
from the three of you.
-(BOTH) Right.
-Sure.
-One of the most important
things a hero needs to do
is earn points.
Take before it is taken.
That's a well known
phrase in this industry.
-(ALL) Right.
-Protecting people is
your most important task.
You can't let anything
get in your way.
Destroy buildings
if you have to.
Don't worry about the damages.
All right.
-(ALL) Right.
-The most important
thing a hero needs to do
is to be able to
showcase his sponsors.
When you're being
interviewed on camera,
make sure your
logos are visible.
Does everyone understand?
-I'm not doing this
just for screen time.
-Can you give us any
tips on how to save
people who are in trouble?
-Let me think.
STUDENTS: Mr. Tiger--
Mr. Tiger-- Can
I show you my powers?
-Please, Mr. Tiger.
I just want to show
you what I can do.
-Take it easy, everyone.
Show me your powers
one at a time.
-Yes, sir.
My power's pretty unique.
-That's different.
-Nobody else can stretch
their skin this far.
-You've got a great smile.
-Me next.
Watch this, sir.
I can sweat buckets.
-Excuse me.
-Pretty impressive, huh?
-Sweet sweat.
-Hey, can you watch
my powers now?
-Can I be next?
-I'm ready.
STUDENT: Can we all
become heroes like you?
-Well, anything's possible.
-Can I actually become a hero?
I'm not sure I
have what it takes.
EDWARD: Come on.
That's not true.
-You're really lucky, Edward.
Everyone says you're bound to
be a hero once you graduate.
Not like me.
I'm just a big failure.
-Hey, why so down on yourself?
-Isn't it obvious?
Look at the power I've got.
I don't even know how to use it.
-You'll be fine.
There's got to be
something only you can do.
-There is, but for what purpose?
-You're over-thinking.
It'll become obvious
as you train.
-Thank you very much, Mr. Tiger.
-You're welcome.
It'll be tough for
them to become heroes
with those kinds of powers.
They're more like sideshow
attractions than NEXT.
IVAN: Hey Tiger.
-Hey, what's going on?
-Would you mind taking a
look at my powers as well?
-Huh?
Wow, amazing.
-Wow, amazing.
-That's OK.
You don't need to copy me.
-I'm serious.
You can stop now.
-I'm not kidding, Origami.
-Oh, sorry about that.
-You know that's
an amazing power.
You can actually shape-shift
into other people.
-The only thing
is it's not really
useful for saving people.
-You think so?
You could shape-shift into
me and use my hundred power.
-Not really.
You see I can copy a
person's appearance
but not their powers.
-That blows.
-I knew it.
I'm not fit for being in
the company of superheroes
with powers like these.
I should just quit
right now and get a job.
-Now, I'm starting
to feel depressed.
Could you stop crying
with my face there?
-Sorry.
-Maybe you shouldn't
obsess over it.
I'm sure there are
some situations
that your power
would be perfect for.
-Actually, someone once
told me the same thing.
That someone was
a friend of mine
who was a NEXT at
the top of our class,
but I didn't take
his word seriously.
-Really?
But the guy never went
on to become a hero.
The fact that you
became one is important.
It means that you were
better suited for this work
than he was.
-That's not true.
-Of course, it is.
-No.
Really.
You're mistaken.
-Don't be so modest.
-Believe me.
I'm telling the truth.
-What?
-He should have
become a hero, not me.
-I remember like it
was yesterday, Barnaby.
Everything you did when you
were a student was perfect.
I don't know if you realized
it, but the whole school
looked up to you.
-Aw.
-You even had a fan club.
That never happened before.
They all wore classes in
the same style as yours.
-Stop.
Please.
You're embarrassing me.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-Tell me, what was he
like way back then?
-Hey, enough already.
-Not you, Bunny.
I was talking about Ivan.
-Well, Ivan was interesting.
He was talented, no question.
But he was very quiet,
always hiding behind
his closest friend
at the Academy.
-Was that the student
he keeps talking
about who was at the
top of his class?
-I'm sure it is.
He was actually very gifted,
but while he was still
a student here, an
incident happened.
-Really?
-We haven't talked
about it much at school.
It's a very bitter memory.
-Where's the car I ordered?
-Have any heroes arrived?
-No, not yet.
-Let's go, Ivan.
Come on.
We have to take care of this.
-But using our powers off
campus is against Academy rules.
-You've got to be kidding.
Think about it.
The powers we have are
meant to help people.
What good are they if
we don't get involved?
-My powers are even useful.
-Don't worry.
You'll do fine.
I'll back you up.
Let's go.
-Wait a minute.
I'm not sure.
You want to become
a hero or not.
-What's taking so long.
I'll kill her.
I swear I will.
-All right, give it up.
It's over.
-Who the hell are you, kid?
You little punk.
-Let go of me, scumbags.
Ivan, help me.
What are you waiting for?
[gunshot]
-I heard about that
entire incident.
Even though it was an accident,
he was charged with murder.
-As a result, Edward
ended up in prison.
He was no longer eligible
to become a hero.
-That explains Ivan.
-He should have
become a hero, not me.
-Wait a minute, is
Edward still in prison?
-Not anymore.
-Long time, no see.
-Edward, I--
-This brings back memories.
It was at this spot that you
often asked me for advice.
-How did you get here?
I thought you were
still in prison.
-I came back for revenge.
-He broke out.
-Yes, I got the
call a few days ago.
IVAN: Help!
-Do you know how much I've
suffered because of you?
Huh?
I was this close to
becoming a certified hero.
You ruined everything.
Why didn't you try
and help me that day?
I went to save someone, so
why am I now the criminal
while you're the hero?
This is your fault, coward.
I lost everything, because
you were too scared to move.
KOTETSU: Oragami!
-Edward.
-What's he doing?
Leave the kid alone.
-Are you all right?
-Why did you guys
have to interfere?
-Huh?
-I'd be willing to die if
I thought it would somehow
make him feel better.
-Why would you say that?
-You have to understand.
I'm the one who ruined his life.
-Edward's just looking for
someone to blame, Ivan.
He should never have stepped in.
What happened back then
was not your fault.
-No.
He asked for my help, and
I was so afraid I froze.
I couldn't move.
All I could think about
was getting killed.
As it turns out, I
might as well have been.
If I had jumped
in, he would have
been a hero, a much
better hero than me.
-Listen.
You're coming at this all wrong.
Edward simply wasn't ready
to be a hero back then,
and he'll mess up again
if you don't stop him.
-What do you mean?
I can't do anything.
-Wouldn't that be the same
mistake you made before?
-Let go.
Ivan, help me.
What are you waiting for?
-Remember, you're a hero now.
I'm better than I thought I was.
-And so modest as well.
You're not supposed
to brag about it.
-It's no big deal.
Let's go.
-You have a good
partner, Barnaby.
-So he keeps telling me.
-Edward!
Edward!
-You were looking for me, right?
So what's with the scared face?
-I came here to ask you to stop.
Come on, Edward.
Please.
-Shut up.
-Sinful one.
Your time has come.
-It's Lunatic.
-Why did he shoot at me?
-You escaped from
prison without atoning
for the murder you committed.
You will pay for
that with your life.
Foolish man.
-You should stay here.
-Edward, are you all right?
-Remember, you're a hero now.
-Did you think you
could escape from me?
-Wait a second.
I'm the real Edward.
-What the--
-You said you were
after me, right?
So what are you waiting for?
-Senseless killing goes
against my principles.
Identify yourself sinner.
-I told you.
I'm the real Edward.
-You're prepared to
atone for your sins.
Very well--
-Dammit.
-Because sinner's
have to pay the price.
Accept your
punishment as justice.
-Go ahead.
I'm going to protect Edward.
Go on.
Shoot.
-I have no choice.
Those who defend
sinners are also evil.
-You're not getting away.
-Good job there, Origami.
-What is it you
want with Edward?
He doesn't have anything
to do with Ouroboros.
You're not attempting to silence
people for your organization?
-I've only come here
to make evil doers
atone for their sins.
-Are you trying to tell us
that you're not with Ouroboros?
-You talk too much.
-Don't play coy.
Because of you I lost
my lead to Ouroboros.
-That's too bad.
-Don't be stupid.
-How reckless.
Has hatred consumed you, hero?
Hear the voice of Thanatos.
-Are you all right?
-Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
Calm down.
Don't get crazy.
-But--
-I have no wish
to fight with you.
-What?
-Let me make myself clear.
I'm just giving murderers
what they deserve.
-Killing people?
That's what you call justice?
-The oldest form on
Earth, an eye for eye.
-Yeah, well, I have a
very different approach.
My idea of justice is
arresting idiots like you.
-Interesting.
We shall see where that
sense of justice leads you.
-Wait a minute.
Bastard.
-Sorry, no one can enter.
-I wish we could
start over again.
Wipe the slate clean.
I know this is partly my fault.
-Shut up, will you?
Thanks for saving me.
I appreciate it.
[sirens]
-I'll be waiting
here for you, Bunny?
-Hey, Bunny.
-Yeah.
-Aren't you glad that old
palm face isn't really related
to Ouroboros?
Or maybe you're not so glad.
[ambulance siren]
DISPATCHER (ON RADIO): Unit
three, this is Central.
We need an update.
What's your 20?
DESK ANCHOR (ON TELEVISION):
Today's hero campaign
was welcomed with a lot of
excitement across the city.
I'd particularly like to credit
the work of Origami Cyclone.
This boy is a true hero.
-I was just doing my job.
But I want to announce
that from now on, I
won't be staying in the
background any longer.
Schwing.
-Huh?
Well, what do you know?
[theme music]
-Are you trying to tell us
that you're not with Ouroboros?
-You talk too much.
[sirens]
BARNABY (VOICEOVER):
I don't get it.
Why do you bother with me?
I'm beginning to seriously
question your judgment.
I don't want anyone's
help on this one.
I never liked this idea.
Hi, I'm Barnaby, the
member of Tiger and Bunny
who's fussy about the design
of the indirect lighting
in his apartment.
Why do we have to
take care of a baby?
Hey, don't mess up my room.
Next time, on "Tiger
& Bunny," "Spare
the Rod and Spoil the Child."
See ya.