[music playing]
INMATE: Problem is when
you kidnap a child,
you're stuck with them.
You got to feed them.
Keep them quiet.
They're a pain in the ass.
-Yeah.
I guess he would have
been if we kept him alive.
-He was in the ground before
we even sent the ransom note.
Makes it a lot cleaner.
-Quiet.
The guard's coming this way.
-Keep it down.
All of you.
-I had a bad dream.
-Shut up and sleep.
INMATE: Someday, I'll put
him to sleep permanently.
[scream]
-What the hell.
I thought I told
you guys to shut up.
[theme music]
PHOTOGRAPHER: Yes.
Nice.
Now we're talking.
OK.
Do that thing with
your hair that you do.
Oh, fierce.
Whoa.
OK.
Now, look at me, but
don't look at me.
That's it.
Use that emotion.
Love it.
Good.
Ah, this issue is going
to sell like crazy.
You are a phenom.
My best work yet.
-He's so hot.
-We'll just be focusing
on Barnaby today.
Don't worry about the other one.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Right.
Got it.
BARNABY: Ah, don't
leave the old man out.
You'll hurt his feelings.
-That's it.
There go.
Oh yeah.
Very nice.
Very, very nice.
[chuckling]
-Yes.
Yes.
-What's so funny?
-Huh?
Oh, uh, I was just
reading the funny pages.
They kill me.
[laughing]
-Wait a minute.
I've seen these guys before.
-What guys?
-Hey, yeah, you're right.
I'm surprised you remember them.
-Most people would.
-Yeah, well, when you've busted
as many bad guys as I have,
they all start to
blend together.
-Yeah, or your memories going.
KOTETSU: Says here
they were burned alive.
-Gee, what a shame.
-That's all you can say?
-What else is there?
-That's a hell of an attitude.
Three men died.
It doesn't matter who they are.
I thought it was our job
to save people's lives.
That's what a hero does.
-Save the sermons for
someone who wants to listen.
MR. LLOYDS: No.
No problem at all.
I'll have Wild Tiger
head over right way.
-Hm.
-No.
Sorry.
I'm afraid Barnaby's
tied up at the moment.
You'll have to make
do with Wild Tiger.
Yes, yes.
He's quite resilient.
-Mr. Lloyds, what's going on?
[screaming]
-Make the flame hotter.
-If you insist.
-No.
We're still not there yet.
It should be
hotter, much hotter.
-What a sadist.
-He's going to melt the
whole prison in a minute.
-All right.
That's enough.
-Whatever you say.
-[gasp] Water.
-Hm.
Too hot for you, honey.
-Hey, man.
Did you have to
lay it on so heavy?
-Excuse me.
I'm just trying to clear
myself of a murder charge.
That's all.
-How's it look?
-Still don't have enough data.
-All right.
One more time.
-One more time?
-It's that or Fire
Emblem will have
to be suspended from the show.
-And you really think
all this will clear him
of any suspicion?
-It might see if we can reenact
the events of last night
and then compare the data.
-And my word's not
good enough for you?
Hmph.
TECHNICIAN: There's
nothing we know
that could have produced
flames of such intensity.
So it's natural to
suspect that whoever
produced them wasn't a
normal human but a NEXT.
-Yes, somebody a lot
like you in fact.
-I am really not enjoying this.
-Well, I'm not a big
fan of it either.
Why do I have to be
put through this?
Can't you just use a
dummy or something?
[whispering]
-Say what?
-Glad you're amused.
-Oh, so you're an opera fan.
Really?
-Yes, that's something I
picked up from my parents.
-Oh, it's sweet the way
you talk about them.
You must have loved
them very much.
Now, do you have any
particular dislikes?
Are there things you don't like?
-Flames.
I don't like fire.
INTERVIEWER: Are you OK?
Can we keep going?
-Sure.
INTERVIEWER: So what's your
favorite part of that outfit?
-The belt.
-Not enough data.
Unbelievable.
How much data do they need?
And meanwhile, I'm
suspended from Hero TV.
-Same time tomorrow.
You too.
-Huh.
-We continue the tests till
we get to the bottom of this.
-Ugh.
You gotta be kidding me.
-The sooner we clear
his name, the sooner
we get him back on the show.
Understand?
-But what do you need me for?
-Maybe we'll just hand
you over to the cops.
How's that?
-I almost think you'd do that.
-So do you think they're right
in that a NEXT is behind it?
Oh, It's scary to think that
there's someone out there
with even more
sizzle than I have.
[cheering]
PRISON GUARD: Quick.
We've got trouble in the yard.
-Get back.
I got you.
Hang in there, buddy.
Hey, hey, hey.
Come on, buddy.
No.
-So tell me, what
did you guys see?
-I don't know.
It all went down so fast.
-Anybody see what happened here?
-Damn
-Nope.
I've never seen
anything like that.
-And you've never heard
the name Ouroboros?
-Uh-uh.
Sorry.
-OK.
Thanks.
-This symbol.
Have you ever seen
one like it anywhere?
-Dear me, I'm afraid not.
No.
-So you're positive?
You're sure it doesn't
mean anything to you?
-Sorry.
-I finally found you.
I'm not letting you get away.
-Hey, get back, young man.
-Not until he tells me
what those symbols mean.
You know.
Please tell me.
-Ouroboros.
AGNES (ON PHONE): Well, at least
this second attack clears you
of any suspicion.
-So they're sure it's
the same perp who
fried the three others.
AGNES (ON PHONE): Same method.
Same location.
Who else could it be?
-Hm.
KOTETSU: Hey, can you pull
over and let me off here?
NATHAN: Really?
But we're not even
close to your place.
KOTETSU: Yeah, I know, but
I feel like taking a walk.
Thanks.
NATHAN: You going to
be all right, honey?
KOTETSU: Sure.
I'll be fine.
-Say there.
You sure you don't want
some company tonight?
-Huh?
NATHAN: A warm body
to snuggle up to?
Hm?
-Thanks, but you're
not exactly my type.
You're too tall.
NATHAN: Well, fine then.
Your loss.
[car horn honks]
[opera music playing]
-It's no good.
I can't remember.
-Mr. Saito, come in.
Where's that damn suit
when I really need it?
Why the hell doesn't he answer?
Mr. Saito!
BARNABY (ON PHONE): No, it's me.
-Huh?
-I don't appreciate you
messing around with my phone.
KOTETSU (ON PHONE): What?
-Don't ever do it again, OK.
It's not funny.
Goodbye.
-Hey, wait!
Wait!
-Skip the apologies.
KOTETSU (ON PHONE):
Who's apologizing.
I'm under attack by
some giant robot thingy.
-Yeah right.
KOTETSU (ON PHONE): It's true.
Dammit.
And I don't have my suit.
I really need--
-Look I'm not falling for
any more of your pranks, OK.
Bye.
-Wait!
Bunny!
Bunny?
Ah, crap.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ah!
OK.
That does it.
See ya.
-Huh?
Whoa!
-Hey, wait.
Hold on.
Come back.
-Well, well, you changed
your mind about my offer?
-Don't flatter yourself.
Take a look back there.
-What in the world?
-Hey, what the
hell are you doing?
This is my car.
-Go on.
Use your powers.
Fry that bastard.
-You have powers too, don't you?
-Yeah, I know, but I
don't want to waste them.
I may need them later.
The whole point of having
powers is to save people.
-Yes.
So use yours to save me.
Out of ammo?
-Let's find out.
Nope.
Definitely not.
-Well, I guess I have no choice.
Fire.
You've got to be kidding.
-Hit the deck.
-Whatever that thing is,
it just snuffed my flames
like they were nothing.
-So maybe we found the guy
responsible for the murders.
-Could be.
One way to find out.
Let's get him out
of that contraption.
-He's coming.
-I'll try and distract him.
-Huh?
-I'll draw his fire, while
you find his weak spot.
-Uh, OK.
-Get going.
-Ooh, you are so butch.
-All right.
Come on out of
there, you-- hold on.
I know you.
[horn honks]
-Reinforcements.
[sirens]
-Well, what do you know?
What the-- I was wondering
if you were going to show up.
Nice of you to fit me
into your schedule.
-Don't get too excited.
I didn't come here
for your sake.
-I know.
It was for my sake
you came, wasn't it?
-Nope.
Honestly, I didn't even
know you were here.
-Oh.
-So where's the culprit?
-He got away.
-Uh-uh.
-Damn.
I was hoping to
earn some points.
-Gee, I'm real sorry about that.
-What?
You've seen that man before?
-Yeah, I have.
NATHAN: When?
Where?
-I'm trying to remember.
I met him somewhere.
-We're wasting our time here.
It's hopeless.
-Huh?
-The old man's memory is going.
He can't even remember faces.
-Will you shut up?
-You know I think
Handsome has a point.
You're not much help, are you?
In fact, come to
think of it, I don't
know how he puts up with you.
-Weren't you the
one who just offered
to spend the night
snuggling with me?
-He's crazy.
I swear to you.
There's nothing
going on between us.
Nothing.
-Like I said, this
is a waste of time.
I'm leaving.
-Good.
-Wait.
I'm coming with.
[whispering]
-Say what?
-That's right.
Where the hell were you?
I almost got myself killed.
-Huh?
-You poor guy.
What the hell is going on with
all the elevators in this town
anyway?
-I just fixed it.
-Thank you, Mr. Saito.
I just remembered where
I've seen that guy.
-Oh.
-He's the worker who was coming
out of the elevator right
before the bomb scare.
-You lost me.
-And he came after
you, because--
-Mhm.
Let's go.
-Where?
What?
I can't stand being
kept in the dark.
-Come on, Bunny.
Would you step on it?
-What use are you going to be
anyway without your powers?
You've got an hour before
you get them back, don't you?
-Ah, who cares about that?
Look.
I'm going to nail
this creep, if I
have to do it with
my bare hands.
-Sorry to interrupt
this macho banter,
but will someone tell
me what is going on?
-The perp in question is trying
to silence any witnesses who
saw him at the scene
of the bomb scare.
-Ah.
Were there others?
Who else was there?
-Agnes and the camera man.
-All right, but I
need that final edit
on my desk first
thing in the morning.
Got it?
-What the hell?
What are you doing?
-You all right?
-Barnaby.
-Looks like we got
here just in time.
-You again.
-Safe and sound.
-Just who is this guy?
-Later, honey.
Right now, we've got
to get you out of here.
-I'll finish all of you.
-What's wrong?
That all you've got?
-Nice work, Handsome.
-Hey, how come you
always get the spotlight?
-Be my guest.
There aren't any
points involved.
-Huh?
Oh, OK.
The party's over,
you lowlife scumbag.
We're taking you in.
-Then stop showing off and
take me in, you jackass.
BARNABY (VOICEOVER): Ouroburos.
-You made a big mistake
tangling with me, punk.
I'm gonna-- hey,
what are you doing?
You said I could handle this.
-That tattoo on your neck.
It's an Ouroburos, isn't it?
What is it?
Some kind of crime syndicate?
-Where's the man who wears
that mark on his hand?
Answer me.
-Hey, hey, wait.
What are you going to do?
-Out of my way.
-All right.
Just calm down.
What's eating you?
-Stay out of it.
-They're at it again.
Honestly, you're like
an old married couple.
-Take off those masks and
put your hands in the air.
I'll blow her head off.
I swear.
-OK.
OK.
-The other guy too.
Now!
-Hey.
-Better do it.
-There we go.
-What's your game anyway?
Why'd you kill those
guys in the prison cell?
How the hell do they
fit into all this?
-What?
-And the one this morning?
Why?
-I don't know what
you're talking about?
-Don't play dumb with me.
Come on.
-I said I don't know.
I'm going to do you first.
-What on earth was that?
-Is it human?
[screaming]
[theme music]
KOTETSU: Hey, Kotetsu here,
the member of Tiger and Bunny
who prefers to bite
into his candy.
Oh, so it's you again.
Who are you anyway?
OK.
Fine.
I guess I'll just have
find out the hard way.
Next time on "Tiger & Bunny,"
"The Wolf Knows the Beast is--"
wait.