ANNOUNCER (ON TV): I don't know
what to make of this, folks.
Perhaps pushed to
desperation, the murderer,
Kotetsu T. Kaburagi,
has just shown up
wearing Wild Tiger's
old hero suit.
-What's he planning to do?
-Oh, that's just great.
He has to land on our roof.
This guy is a real
pain in the ass.
-Yes, sir, he sure is.
-This building isn't
safe right now.
We have to evacuate.
-Everyone, please
try to remain calm.
Proceed in a single file.
-All right, listen up, heroes.
I'm done with
running and hiding.
Let's do it.
[theme music]
-I'm going in, sir.
MAVERICK: Wait, let's see
what Kaburagi does first.
BARNABY: With all
due respect, sir,
it doesn't matter what he does.
I'll bring him in at any cost.
-If you've one flaw among
your admirable attributes,
it's your emotions, Barnaby.
You've got to be patient.
ANNOUNCER (ON TV): The murderous
NEXT has activated his powers.
But what can he expect
to do against six heroes?
-Don't worry.
I have a plan.
-Well, let's see what you've
got up your sleeve, Kotetsu.
-All right, pay attention.
ALL: Huh?
-You remember this pose, right?
And look at this suit.
It's not ringing
any bells for you?
Come on, I'm the
original Wild Tiger.
You know me.
We worked together on Hero TV.
-That's your brilliant plan?
-Seriously, you know
you guys recognize me.
Here, how about this?
Wild Roar!
You remember that at all, huh?
Come on.
-You actually have the gall
to dress up as Wild Tiger
after everything you've done?
-What?
-Don't think you can fool us
with that cheap imitation suit.
-I'm telling you it's not fake.
Guys, it's me.
-What are you waiting for?
Capture the suspect.
ALL: Yes ma'am.
-Playtime's over, pal.
Today's wind velocity
is off the charts.
-Just hold on a second.
Damn it, I said hold on.
-So annoying.
Stop dancing around, honey.
-Would you guys just ease
up and listen for a second?
-No one wants to hear
your excuses, lowlife.
-You're surrounded by heroes.
There's no escape.
-Calm down, will you?
Just give me a chance here
and I can prove to all of you
that I'm the real deal.
Starting with you, Dragon Kid.
Remember that time
you and I spent
babysitting the mayor's son?
Well, I know that ever
since then, you've
been wearing that cute
little flower hair pin
that your parents
gave you, right?
-I only wear it when
I'm out of uniform.
How do you know about that?
-And you, Blue Rose.
I haven't forgotten what your
first love was, that you always
dreamed of being a
singer, not a superhero.
-How could you know that?
-Origami.
Remember when we visited
the Hero Academy together?
You were doubting
if you were even
cut out for this
line of work, right?
-What?
-And you, Sky High, you
like sucking yolks out
of fried eggs like this.
[slurping] Am I right or wrong?
-Eh?
-Fire Emblem, you
shave your facial hair
and armpits three times a day.
-Oh.
ANNOUNCER (ON TV): It's not
quite clear what's unfolding,
but the suspects
seems to be exposing
each heroes most
personal secrets.
-What's with this guy?
How does he know so much?
-You don't think he could be?
-Yes, you remember
now, don't you?
-You're a stalker.
-What?
Are you kidding me?
These are all my
friggin memories
from all the time
we spent together.
You still don't believe
me after all I've said?
I mean seriously,
just look at me.
Do I really seem
like the kind of guy
who'd go and kill a person?
-Sort of.
-Yep.
-Uh huh.
-Sure do.
-Really?
-This is the end of
the road for you.
-No, he doesn't.
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Just look at him, you guys.
I don't think I can even
imagine him killing someone.
-Thanks, Blue Rose.
-It makes no sense.
I mean, if he really
is the murderer,
why stick his neck out like
this to prove his innocence?
-Don't be fooled.
He's trying to trick us
by gaining our sympathy,
but that's not going to work.
-Will you quit it, Bison?
I don't want to do something
I'll regret, especially
since you still owe me $20.
-Shut up, you lowlife.
-You have to believe me.
I'm innocent, I swear.
-This is the best
you can do, is it?
Have you managed to
calm down yet, Barnaby?
Yes.
ANNOUNCER (ON TV):
Well, it looks
like this coldblooded killer
is no match for our six heroes.
-Thanks for the
boost, Mr. Kaburagi.
Mr. Maverick?
MAVERICK (ON PHONE):
You'll have to forgive me.
I just sent out
my company's hero,
but it looks like he
won't make it in time.
-Oh, no complaints
from my end, sir.
Thanks to the other
heroes, our show
just hit its highest
ratings of the season.
-Well, I'm very glad to hear it.
We'll have to put our heads
together and figure out
what we can do in the future
to boost them even higher.
-All right.
So what happens now?
You going to arrest me?
-You just don't know
when to give up, do you?
-Oh, he will once he's in jail.
-What happened to all of you?
Why?
Why don't any of
you remember me?!
ANNOUNCER: And there
you have it, folks.
Kotetsu T. Kaburagi
has been arrested.
-Wait.
ALL: Huh?
-My dad never killed anybody.
-Kaede, why are you here?
-She's your kid?
ANNOUNCER (ON TV): What's this?
A young girl has
suddenly appeared
and is pleading that
the suspect is innocent.
-Young lady, this man has
done very, very bad things.
-Those are nothing but lies.
-I understand how
you feel, sweetie.
But we need to take him away.
-No, no.
You can't.
-Well, this is a pickle, huh?
-My dad.
Give me back my dad!
-Kaede.
-That girl.
-What the heck?
-Mr. Maverick?
-Miss Agnes, we've
got a problem.
Our signals been jammed.
Everything's down.
-What do you mean jammed?
What's causing it?
-I have no clue.
-Huh?
-Hey, wait a second
guys, what are we doing?
-What are we doing?
We're about to arrest
Tiger, of course.
-Yeah, but why would we do that?
-Well, because he killed
someone and-- huh?
-I'm not sure why,
but we were definitely
treating Wild Tiger
like a criminal.
I think.
-But why?
That would be
impossible, wouldn't it?
-And besides, why are
you dressed like that?
-Yeah, what's up with that?
You look weird.
-You know who I am?
Thank god.
You guys finally
remember me again.
-Dad, want to tell
me what's going on?
-Oh yeah, Kaede.
Um, what are you
even doing here?
-Why didn't you
tell me anything?
-Huh?
-You don't think you should've
told me that you were a hero?
-Oh, well, you see--
Look, sweetheart, I
wasn't trying to hide from you.
I just didn't want you to
have to worry about me.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
-You can't treat me like
a little kid anymore.
-Now wait, all of
that aside, Kaede,
what's going on with you?
What was that ball of
white light just now?
-I don't know, dad.
I didn't plan it.
It just happened.
-Well, you've got to be
replicating someone else's
power, but the question is who.
Do you think you've come
in contact with anyone new
recently?
-Let's see.
-I see.
You're one of Barnaby's
biggest fans, aren't you?
Well, thank you for
coming all this way.
-Oh, an old man on the first
floor of this building.
-Here?
Well, what did he look like?
-Um, he had glasses on.
Oh, and he was
wearing a bow tie.
-It was Maverick.
-Listen kids, I'm
sorry to interrupt,
but do you maybe want
to shed a little light
on what's going on around here?
-Albert Maverick is
behind this entire mess.
-Come again?
-Maverick used his powers
to manipulate your memories.
He was playing you against me.
[gasp]
-Our memories?
-Yeah.
But my kid here was able
to use her NEXT powers
to restore you all
back to normal.
-When did he manipulate
our memories though?
-Well, he did call
us all together.
Maybe it then?
-Was it just you guys or
was anyone else there?
-Miss Agnes was, and
people from your company.
-So he was trying to
frame me by changing
the memories of everyone
who knew my real identity.
-I'm so sorry.
This is our fault.
-I should have put
two and two together
when brought up the fried eggs.
-Don't worry about it.
I'm just glad that
you all remember now.
-Tiger, I--
-You're a good friend.
-Huh?
-Even with your
memories gone, you never
stopped believing in me.
Thanks Blue Rose.
You, on the other
hand, you treated me
like a commonplace criminal.
-Really?
My memory's still
a little spotty.
-I believe the word
you used was "lowlife."
Twice actually.
-Let bygones be bygones, right?
I mean, is-- is this the little
girl we've heard so much about?
Introduce her already.
-Oh, how stupid of me.
Sorry for the late intro, guys.
This is my daughter, Kaede.
-Hi, everybody.
Gosh, it really is an honor.
-Hey, sugar.
-It's great to meet you.
-Thanks for saving us.
We're in your debt.
-Oh, it's OK.
Thanks for always
helping out my dad.
-You've got a good
head on your shoulders.
I like your spirit.
-So where's Barnaby?
Is there any chance I
could meet him, dad?
-Oh, that's right.
I forgot about him.
-Were Barnaby's memories
altered as well.
-Most likely.
-I'll never forgive you.
You'll pay for killing Samantha.
-Hey, Barnaby.
-Barnaby?
-Easy now, handsome.
Just take a breath.
-It's a mistake.
Tiger didn't murder anyone.
-It's no use, you guys.
-Yeah, but--
-I need a repeat of
what you did earlier.
You think you can do it, kiddo?
-What?
-Barnaby's been brainwashed
by a very bad man, Kaede.
And right now, your power is the
only thing that can save him.
-You got it, dad.
-Just hang tight, Barnaby.
We're going to get your
memories unscrambled, OK?
-Whoa, uh, dad?
-The heck?
-Oh yeah, he
touched my shoulder.
-You've got a good
head on your shoulders.
I like your spirit.
-Idiot.
-Huh?
-That's just great.
Thanks to you, Kaede's
abilities have changed again.
-Me?
What did I do?
-She's a Mimic, a NEXT who
copies the powers of anyone
she comes in contact with.
[gasp]
-I'm so sorry.
I had no idea.
-Damn it.
She was the only
shot we had here.
-Fools, every last one of them.
-Everyone else out of the way.
My business is with him.
-Listen, Barnaby.
You're being
manipulated right now.
Maverick has been behind it all.
-I've heard enough!
-Calm down, Barnaby.
-Don't do this, handsome.
He's your partner.
-That's right.
Try to remember.
-What are you talking about?
That man is a murderer.
-Barnaby.
-Don't interfere.
-Come on, Barnaby.
You've got to snap out of it.
-Let go.
Kotetsu Kaburagi, why
did you kill Samantha?
Answer me.
-Take care of Kaede if
anything happens to me.
All right, if that's
the case, I'll
just have to make you remember
whether you want to or not.
Let's go, pal.
Come and get me.
-Dad, you can't.
-Oh , no, you don't.
-It's too dangerous.
-Yeah, but--
-It's all right.
Trust us, kid.
Your dad is a hero.
-Oh, uh, nothing to see here.
I'm nobody suspicious
or anything.
Uh, I know it looks bad, but--
-Wait, your memories.
Were you watching
that broadcast?
You remember me
again, don't you?
-Hey there, partner.
What took you so long?
-How did you get that
suit and that motorcycle?
-A black suit and
a red bike, huh?
No offense, but you looked
way better in the old suit.
You coming or what?
-Remember this?
You on the right,
me on the left,
chasing down all
those real bad guys?
-Shut up.
-Barnaby, relax, would you?
Hey, this is dangerous.
Eyes on the road.
-Hm?
What the?
[screaming]
-Wild Tiger.
-And Barnaby too.
-Hey, up ahead.
Aw crap.
This is where we first met.
Brings back some
memories, doesn't it?
You carried me in your arms
after saving me, remember?
-I would never do that.
-There's nothing to worry about.
Those two are going
to be just fine.
-Hey, stop.
I said stop.
Oh, would you cut
it out already?
Oops.
-You bastard.
So you're ready to fight?
-It's not like that.
-Is that Tiger?
-No, It's the person we were
persuaded to believe was him.
-Who are you?
-You aren't getting off
with a few minor burns
after what you pulled.
-Now show me your power.
Time to put our
cards on the table.
-All right, you impostor,
reveal yourself.
[gasp]
-Guess I have no choice.
Let's do this.
COMPUTER: Good Luck Mode.
Good Luck Mode.
[theme music]
KOTETSU (VOICEOVER):
Hi, I'm Kotetsu,
the member of
Tiger and Bunny who
has a mole on the
bottom of his foot.
Come on, Barnaby, hurry
up and remember me.
If you don't, I-- [sigh] Next
time on "Tiger and Bunny"--
Misfortunes Never Come Singe-ly.
What?