-Now that we have
your attention,
let us introduce ourselves.
We're known as Ouroboros.
The clock is ticking.
If you want to save yourselves,
you know what to do.
Release one man.
His name's Jake Martinez.
[gasp]
That's it for now.
We expect to receive an
affirmative response.
[theme music]
-This is crazy.
Isn't there some place safe
we could move everyone?
-Yes, what about downtown?
That area hasn't been hit yet.
-That's right
-Gentlemen, that option has
already been considered.
We have a much more
urgent concern.
This city is built on
three separate levels
with a stern medial
area at its center.
Should the foundation
collapse, everything
will go down with it.
-They're holding the
entire city hostage.
We must be careful not
to do anything reckless.
-Are you saying we should
give into terrorists?
-We can't do something
that irresponsible.
-How could we find
ourselves in this position?
You said the heroes
would handle this,
that they were on top of it.
-It's horrible Miss Agnes.
Isn't there anything
we can do to help out?
AGNES JOUBERT:
Sorry, not right now.
-So we have to sit
by and just let
these bastards do
as they please?
-With all our abilities,
I can't believe
there's nothing we can do.
-No.
I'm positive that there's
something we can do.
We just have to stand by and
wait until that time comes.
-I understand how
you feel, but don't
forget people's
lives are at stake.
-I happen to be aware of that!
-Come on you guys.
This is no time to fight.
-We need to pull together
as a group and stay focused.
-What's eating him today?
-Mm.
-Uh sorry guys.
I'm afraid I must of
gotten on his nerves.
-What did you say to him?
-Well I thought I'd tell
him how I got my code name.
It is kind of interesting.
-Huh?
-The ko in Kotetsu means tiger.
That's why I'm
called Wild Tiger.
Get it?
-What?
-Why would you bring
that stuff up now?
-Inappropriate.
No wonder the guy got so upset.
-Yeah.
I'm going to go
apologize to him.
-How could he be so oblivious
to what's happening right now?
-No, honey.
Something else is
going on there.
[sighs]
-Hey Bunny.
Wait up a minute.
Where ya going?
-Sorry about that.
I kind of lost it back there.
I know you were only
trying to help out.
[grunt]
Right when I found the bastard.
-We have an emergency.
-Can't make you
out, repeat that.
-The powered exosuits destroyed
one of the support columns
in East Bronx.
[yelling]
-Sky High and Blue Rose, you
have to head to the scene
immediately.
-We're responding.
What do you want us to focus on?
-Ignore the powered exosuits.
You need to save people and
prevent widespread panic.
-I'm going with them, Agnes.
-I'm ordering you to stay.
-Why would you do that?
-There could easily
be another attack.
Everyone else is on standby.
-We should be doing
something right now.
What's taking so long
to make a decision?
REPORTER: With Sternbild on
the brink of destruction,
everyone's asking, why aren't
the city leaders and the heroes
mobilizing to fight back?
-Tiger's right.
We can't just wait
for the next attack.
KRIEM: We've been waiting.
Waiting for someone in charge
to respond to our demands.
Perhaps you don't believe
that we're serious.
Our next attack will be
in an hour at 11 o'clock.
We'll decide on the location
by rolling a pair of dice.
-I'm not waiting til then.
Come on, Bunny.
AGNES JOUBERT: Don't do this.
You're disobeying
a direct order!
-They plan to destroy
another support column.
-How do we know that for sure?
They could be bluffing.
-What are you talking about?
The city's already
beginning to tilt.
We must take action now!
-We can't drag this
out any longer.
We're facing a
potential disaster.
You have to make a
decision, Mister Mayor.
-Huh?
-We have no choice.
You have to release Jake.
-What?
Wait just a minute here.
Don't put all of this on me.
-I'll accept full
responsibility if that's
what it takes to
get through this.
But you're the one who must
make the final decision.
-Yes, right.
But if by any chance
things go wrong.
-Ladies and gentlemen.
I've deployed Sky High and
Blue Rose as you requested,
but we have one little problem.
-Why the hell are you just
sitting on your asses?
Isn't your top priority to
save the lives of citizens?
-What?
What are you doing here?
-Listen, let us worry
about Jake and his gang.
We heroes always
come through for you.
-Usually.
-Then what the hell
are you waiting for?
You're not trying to protect
that thing of yours, are you?
-Thing?
-Can't think of the word.
Uh, self something or other.
-Self-interests.
-Yeah, that's it!
-Aha
-There's no point in
beating around the bush.
You all have friends
and family in the city.
Don't you want to protect them?
Then you need to make a
decision quickly and rise
above your own whatchamacallits.
-Self-interests.
-Thank you!
-I have to say, even though my
friend here wasn't very clear,
he does make a good point.
-Listen to the man.
He's absolutely right.
[gasp]
Except he's wrong
about capturing us.
We got tired of waiting for
an answer from you big shots.
I'm here to work out the
details of your surrender.
-You're one of the Ouroboros!
-You can call me Hans Chuckman.
I'm here to negotiate.
-You have some nerve,
barging into this place!
-Oh, really.
I don't suppose the same
could be said of you.
-Ugh, stop it, both of you.
People's lives are at stake.
-Sorry.
People's lives are
the top priority.
-I agree.
-Now that we've
settled that, tell me.
What have you big
shots decided to do?
-Well we thought,
in order to ensure
the safety of our
people, we'd like
you to withdraw your
powered exosuits.
-Ha, you've got
to be kidding me.
Apparently you don't
understand the situation.
-We were just hoping to reach
some kind of accommodation.
-We're not making any deals.
You've been offered one
final chance to surrender.
-Why, funny should say that.
We were just talking about that.
-It's no use trying to buy time.
If we don't hear from
you before the deadline,
the decision is simple.
Kaboom.
-Residents of Sternbild, this
is an important announcement.
Your safety is our top
priority and therefore we
have concluded the following.
We are unable to defend the city
and we cannot allow any more
casualties.
That being said we
have decided to give in
to the enemy's demands and
release Jake Martinez at once.
-Good, should have
done that earlier.
[humming]
-Hey Jake.
I thought you were in here
for the rest your life.
-Want to know why I'm
being released today?
There's a simple answer.
You see, I'm Jake.
And you my friend are not.
No big deal.
I mean, the next time you see
me, we'll still be friends.
Wait.
There won't be a next time.
I kind of figured this
was your doing, Kriem.
-I'm sorry you had to be in
there for so long, Mr. Jake.
We were trying.
-How did you finally do it?
-I think I'll leave that
one to your imagination.
-A secret, huh?
I love secrets.
And I love a woman with secrets.
-Jake Martinez has
now been released
and is leaving the
prison in a helicopter.
The question is, has
destruction been averted?
-I guess we're all just
going to have to be patient.
-Once they've withdrawn their
forces and the people are safe,
then we'll make our move.
-It's a daring plan.
I hope everything goes OK.
-It will, as long as they
don't know what we've done.
-This city's still a dump.
Nothing's changed, I see.
How about a toast?
-Better not, I'm
at the controls.
-You're so serious, my friend.
-What do you think you're
going to accomplish
by keeping me here?
The city's about to sink.
-We're well aware
of the problem.
That's where I come in.
-Sorry you have to
do this, but I'm
absolutely sure that you'll
be able to pull it off.
Of course, if things
go wrong, your life
will be in grave danger.
You can still--
-I'm fine.
After all, I am still a hero.
The fact is this is something
only I can do, right?
I'll do it.
-Hey, Origami.
You forgot this.
-Thank you.
If something goes
wrong, contact us.
We'll all be standing
by to back you up.
-Got it.
-Our future now depends
upon your abilities.
Good luck, Origami Cyclone.
-Thanks.
-I've been meaning to ask,
what's the name of our pilot?
-This is Hans Chuckman.
As you've probably figured
out, he's not a NEXT,
but he believes in our cause.
-A regular human being?
That explains why
he's so boring.
-He wants to help us create
a Utopian nation controlled
by NEXTs.
A world ruled by you.
-Ah.
I guess that means you aspire
to become a NEXT some day.
I'm afraid that's impossible.
Isn't that right Kriem?
-That's true.
It's too bad for you humans,
but NEXTs are God's chosen ones.
Chuckman.
-What is it ma'am?
-Since Mr. Jake has
been freed as planned,
you can now prepare to
release the hostages.
-Yes.
-Hold on.
Tell me about these hostages.
-Do you have any updates?
-No, sir.
There's been no
movement whatsoever.
-I see.
-What's happening?
When are they going to
pull back their forces?
-Easy.
Let's not panic gentleman.
It's only been a half hour since
Jame Martinez was released.
Maybe they're in the
process of mobilizing
their forces to pull out.
-I have to agree.
Our plan is right on track.
We at least need to wait until
Origami Cyclone has a chance
to contact us.
-He's the key to
the whole operation.
Do you think he's
all right out there?
-He's still alive.
We're able to monitor his
vital signs through sensors.
We only have to worry
if that green tracking
signal turns red.
-Hey, what's happening?
We kept up our end
of the bargain.
-Don't ask me.
I don't know how they think
or what they plan to do!
-Hey, calm down.
We need to trust Origami.
-I am calm!
Tell me what
Ouroboros is planning.
Answer me.
-Hey, you're going too far.
Cool it Bunny.
-I'm gonna go out
and take a break.
-They're not idiots.
They probably caught
onto your stupid plan.
-Please just leave me alone.
How long do you plan
on standing out here?
-(MOUTH FULL) That's
none of your business.
Just leave me alone.
-I know I must seem to
be acting irrationally.
-You really don't seem
much different than usual.
-When I finally see
Jake face to face,
I'm not sure I'll have
much self control.
-Quit worrying about it.
I got you covered.
I'm not going to let
you do anything stupid.
Relying on others for a little
help every now and then?
Not such a bad thing.
-Hey Kotetsu, Barnaby.
We've got some trouble.
-Citizens of Sternbild.
Thanks for releasing me.
I speak to you
now is a free man.
-It's Jake.
-I had no idea why I
was being released.
No one told me it was
negotiated in exchange
for sparing the lives of
useless human garbage.
As a result, I've
made a decision
not to release any
of the hostages.
-What?
Am I hearing this right?
-In other words for those of
you who are still confused,
your lives will remain
in the palm of my hand.
After all you'll
do anything I want.
Am I right about that?
I guess we're going to find out.
Bye-bye now.
-Well Origami's still safe.
Damn it, how much longer
is this all going to take?
-What's going on here?
Mr. Maverick?
-Actually we expected
this to happen.
Our plan is going just fine.
Now all we have to do is wait
for our spy, Origami Cyclone,
to tell us how the
powered exosuits work.
Then we'll know how
to attack the enemy.
-What?
How am I supposed
to explain this
to the people who
thought this was over?
This is crazy.
The population of the city
is going to be up in arms.
How am I supposed to--
-I have a plan to address that.
-Mr. Mayor!
What's your plan?
-You'll have to
hold your questions.
Mr. Maverick is handling
everything at the moment.
-Mr. Maverick is?
You're the mayor, aren't you?
-Of course I am.
We'll hold an interview
after everything's resolved.
That'll have to do for now.
-The people deserve a straight
answer from their mayor.
-We have questions.
Over here, sir.
-Yes, we're meeting with
the press at 2 o'clock.
We'll explain what
we can at that time.
Hopefully that will
satisfy everyone.
-You wanted to see us, sir?
-Mr. Maverick's about to speak.
-As you all know, Sternbild is
undergoing a terrorist attack.
The mayor decided that your
lives took top priority
and therefore acted accordingly.
Rather than put your
family's safety at risk,
he decided to take the
terrorists at their word
and release their leader.
However, it turned out that the
terrorists couldn't be trusted.
-Now everything's even worse.
[shouting]
-I'm sure you're angry
and dissatisfied.
So is the mayor, and
so are we, of course.
But shouldn't that
anger be directed
at Ouroboros, and its
leader, Jake Martinez?
There's a hero who's
been waiting patiently
to fight these terrorists.
I've talked to him about why
he chose to become a hero
and now he's ready
to reveal the reason.
-Barnaby?
-You might not have
noticed, but he's
the only hero whose chosen
to fight under his real name.
-Reveal my past?
-Yes and soon.
This isn't your problem
alone anymore, Barnaby.
Go public.
-But what about his
right to some privacy?
-I know how you
feel, but there's
a more pressing imperative.
The people need the
courage and spirit
to stand up to these
terrorists and Barnaby
can help them do that.
If you share your
thoughts with them,
I'm sure they'll be inspired.
Please reconsider.
We desperately need your help.
After a terrible
childhood tragedy
involving the death
of his parents,
this boy became
a hero, and chose
to go by the name of
Barnaby Brooks Junior.
Taking on his father's
name was this boy's way
of declaring war.
War against the man who killed
his parents 20 years ago.
-Is that for real?
-I never knew that
was his background.
-No wonder he's so
committed to justice.
-And now he's finally
found that man.
He's identified the
criminal he saw murder
his parents when he was
just a child of four.
An innocent child.
Forever scarred by
an unspeakable act.
That man is Jake Martinez.
Barnaby Brooks is just as
angry, perhaps more angry,
than any of you.
Everything he's
done in his life has
been in anticipation
of this very moment.
-Uh, Mr. Brooks.
Tell us, is all of this true?
-It is.
Every single word of it.
I've dedicated
myself to capturing
Jake and his compatriots
and saving this city
from the threat of terrorists.
[shouting]
-This should get
things back on track.
-That's heavy.
He had a tough past.
-So that's why he's
been so dedicated.
-We need to catch Jake
for our friend Barnaby,
if nothing else.
ORIGAMI CYCLONE: It's me.
-Origami?
ORIGAMI CYCLONE: Yes.
And I need to report.
I've finally gotten
inside Jake's hideout.
-Great job, Champ!
And great job again.
ORIGAMI CYCLONE: Thanks,
but now comes the hard part.
I've got to find the secret
behind those powered exosuits.
-Watch your back at
all times, Origami.
-Return safely and I'll
give you a big kiss.
ORIGAMI CYCLONE: Ye-- Yeah.
Well I gotta go.
-I wasn't through, ah!
-Guess it's time for us
to get ready for battle.
You set?
-Yeah.
This is where it all begins.
[theme music]
-Thanks, but now
comes the hard part.
I've got to find the secret
behind those powered exosuits.
BLUE ROSE: Watch your back
at all times, Origami.
FIRE EMBLEM: Return safely
and I'll give you a big kiss.
-Yeah, well I gotta go.
-Hey Chuckman,
tell me something.
What do you think
of my new haircut?
-Well I think it looks
very good on you, sir.
-I think so too.
Makes me look like
one of those heroes.
Heroes are great, aren't they?
They look so cool.
Hey Chuckman, what do
you think of heroes?
Right after Legend
died, all those NEXTs
sided with the humans.
It made no sense to
me back then and I
have to admit I don't fully
understand it even now.
But the bottom line
is it's awesome.
Awesome for them to
be such a nuisance.
Of course, that's not
what you and I want is it?
Ah!
Bingo!
Hey Chuckman.
What do you think of him?
I know no one's asked you, yet.
But if you become a NEXT
wouldn't you want this ability?
Wouldn't you?
-I suppose so.
I think.
-Well he looks silly,
but I think he's useful.
There's no way I would
waste a power like his.
But the question is,
when would I use the guy?
I mean think about it.
Someone who could
shape shift like that
would come in pretty handy.
He'd be the perfect
spy, wouldn't he?
Hey.
What's wrong?
You're sweating like a pig.
-Hi I'm Kotetsu.
The member of Tiger & Bunny who
squashes his burgers before he
eats them.
We finally come face to
face with the guy who
killed Barnaby's parents.
Next time on Tiger &Bunny, take
heed of the snake in the grass.
Snakes.
Why'd it have to be snakes?