[music playing]
[screaming]
-Dammit.
-Wait!
Who the hell was that guy?
BARNABY: This is your fault.
None of this would have happened
if you hadn't gotten in my way
back there.
I was this close to
uncovering the Ouroboros.
-Hey, just calm down.
-I can't calm down.
Those bastards
murdered my parents.
[theme music]
KOTETSU: Listen, Bunny.
I understand that this
is personal for you,
but you lost control.
And a suspect in our custody
got killed because it.
You know that, right?
Will you fill us in?
Why did you lose it on that
perp in the first place?
And what the hell
is this Ouroboros?
If you don't talk,
we can't help you.
Come on.
We've got no idea
what's going on.
-I don't know either, OK.
I think Ouroboros is
the crime syndicate that
murdered my parents.
And that perp had their
symbol tattooed on his neck.
-Tattoo?
Does that mean the bomber creep
was a member of Ouroboros?
-I'll never know
thanks to that NEXT.
-Who was he?
And how did he just show up
out of nowhere like that?
-Well, judging from that
insane power of his,
I bet he's the one
we're looking for,
the one behind those killings.
-Hold on.
You're saying that whack job
with the bombs was innocent.
-It's hard to believe,
but there really
is a NEXT with more
firepower than me.
-Wait.
What's he up to?
Tell us what you know, so
we can help take him down.
-Just leave me alone.
I don't want anyone's
help on this one.
BARNABY: Those bastards
murdered my parents.
NATHAN: Oh, forgive me, honey,
for keeping you waiting.
KOTETSU: So uh, did
you find out anything?
NATHAN: Handsome's back
story is quite the tragedy.
It's no wonder he let his
passion get the best of him.
The one person who could have
identified his parents' killer
was torched in front of him.
-You're saying the
witness was killed by--
-Ouroboros.
-Wait a sec, what
does that have to do
with that NEXT with
the blue fireballs?
Is that guy a member
of Ouroboros too?
-Well, you know what they
say, "Loose lips sink ships."
-Sink ships.
Hm.
Like a boat.
-Get a clue, dear.
Use that brain of yours, and
think about the fire victims.
What do they all have in common?
Hm?
-They were all known criminals.
-Bingo.
If Ouroboros is a
big crime syndicate,
the NEXT could plugging
leaks in the organization.
-Get off me.
Hold up, so everyone he killed
was a member of Ouroboros?
-Maybe.
Finding that tattoo on
their bodies would prove it,
but they're burned to a crisp.
-And Bunny, have you
told him this yet?
-He's a hard man to
get in touch with.
MR. LLOYDS: Oh, this is great.
Now, Barnaby's not
answering my calls anymore.
This is so unlike that boy.
Barnaby has been nothing but
a model employee up until now.
Why should I care if he
isn't feeling up to it?
I'm running a business.
Not a charity.
NATHAN: I'm worried about him.
Handsome lost his parents when
he was only four years old.
Can you imagine
how horrible it's
been to carry that kind
of pain his entire life?
-Well, you know
everybody's got something
they have to live with.
-I didn't peg you as
the heartless type.
KOTETSU: It's not like that.
I'm just saying this might
be part of Bunny's past
he doesn't want us to touch.
-I mean honestly, how dare
he pull this disappearing act
right before a big performance?
KOTETSU: Hey.
Take it easy.
It's no big deal.
Every big star's going
to act like a diva
every once in awhile.
When I was a young buck, I'd
pull shenanigans like this
all the time.
-I'm sure you did, but you were
never as big a star as him.
-What?
I was huge.
-You know sometimes, I wonder
what planet you live on.
-Got to love me.
That being said, couldn't you
have found a better understudy
than this guy?
-I had no choice.
He was the only one
who was available.
-Yeah.
But that poor kid is going
to get killed out there.
-This better be important.
I'm sick of these
last minute calls.
[scream]
-No.
-Hold it.
Let the girl go or else we'll--
KARINA: Oh good.
You're wearing black.
Then you won't have to
change for your funeral.
-Ow.
-Let's do this.
Filthy pig.
You can open up your eyes.
You're safe now, sweetie.
-You've got some nerve.
Who the hell are
you freaks anyway?
-Huh.
Who us?
We're the heroes--
-We are the heroes of this city.
That's who.
The name's Blue Rose.
Remember it.
When trash like
you comes around,
my friends and I
take out the garbage.
-Yeah.
What she said.
-My ice is a little bit cold.
Go on.
-Huh.
But your crime has been
completely put on hold.
[cheers]
-Thank you.
KOTETSU: You stole
my thunder out there.
KARINA: Hey, I did you a favor
filling in at the last minute.
So what happened?
You two have another
lover's quarrel?
-Oh, you mean Bunny?
This time, it has
nothing to do with me.
-Fine.
Don't tell me then.
-Hey, wait.
Do you have feelings for him?
-No.
Absolutely not.
-That's so cute.
ANNOUNCER: And now,
the main event.
A surprise live concert
by our superstar guest,
the Ice Queen
herself, Blue Rose.
-You heard him.
I'm on.
Now get off my stage.
-Anyway, I'm sure Bunny
would have thanked you.
-I didn't do it for him, dummy.
Now, beat it.
-Hey Tiger--
-Hm.
-Why didn't you kill them?
-Why didn't I kill who?
-Those bad guys.
Why didn't you take them
out when you had the chance?
-It's not that simple.
Hey, I made the arrest.
Doesn't that count
for something?
-The good guys are supposed
to kill the bad guys.
-Little punk got me
in the same spot.
[sigh]
MAVERICK: That charity
event raised a lot of money
for a good cause.
Nice work.
-What?
Oh.
-Show some respect.
That's not how
you greet our CEO,
or have you forgotten that
this is the person who
took a chance on you when
nobody else wanted to hire you?
-Oh, that's right.
He did, didn't he?
Thanks a bunch.
You rock.
-Were you raised by animals?
-Don't worry, Lloyds.
It's fine.
I'm the one who barged into the
man's dressing room unannounced
in order to thank him.
-I was just doing my job.
-I also wanted to ask if
you're busy later this evening.
-Me?
-Yes, I'd like to take
you somewhere special
as a sign of appreciation
for all the hard work you do.
-Oh.
OK.
So this is where
you're taking me?
-You're looking at a highly
concentrated oxygen chamber
that Dr. Saito
recently developed.
A prototype anyway.
It's supposed to
restore your health.
And I thought this would be a
good chance for the two of you
to test it out.
-The two of us?
Me and Doc Saito?
Bunny?
What are you doing here?
-I was invited, like you.
-By Mr. Maverick?
-Our young Barnaby has
been exhausted lately.
He needed to take a break.
I apologize that you had
to handle those criminals
without your partner today.
-Oh.
No problem.
Just another day at the office.
SAITO (OVER SPEAKER):
So how does it feel?
Your body seems
lighter doesn't it?
Like you're drifting
off to a blissful sleep.
-I just got in the damn tank.
SAITO (OVER SPEAKER): Are
you getting sleepy yet?
Well, how about now?
Are you sound asleep?
-Grr.
SAITO (OVER
SPEAKER): Hey, Tiger.
Are in dream land?
Is it relaxing?
Tell me.
-I can't sleep with you yelling.
MAVERICK (OVER SPEAKER):
Can you hear me, Barnaby.
I understand how
frustrated you must be.
But if you give up now,
your goal will elude you.
You won't have closure.
-Sir, the trouble I've
caused, I'm sorry.
MAVERICK (OVER SPEAKER): Just
close your eyes and rest.
You'll get another
chance soon enough.
-Thank you.
MAVERICK (OVER SPEAKER):
Good night, Barnaby.
[alarm sounding]
-I was so close.
ANNOUNCER: Calling
Tiger and Barnaby.
It's show time.
Report immediately to
the abandoned church
site located in
the downtown area.
I repeat.
Calling Tiger and Barnaby.
It's show time.
-Been waiting long?
-This time it's not a show.
We've got the real deal here.
-I figured.
-Apparently, the cops
are going to raid
the hideout of some
crime syndicate
they've been watching.
-Crime syndicate.
-We're going live.
No tape delay?
-It'll be a sensation.
Our ratings are going
to go through the roof.
-But ma'am, this is supposed
to be a surprise operation.
Isn't airing it live going
to tip off the criminals?
-Not if we get really creative.
Come on.
Let's live a little.
BARNABY: Standby?
KOTETSU: Yep.
BARNABY: Why is
she making us wait.
The hideout is right down there.
KOTETSU: The hell if I know.
She just said to sit
tight and wait for orders.
-The Justice Bureau
gave us approval.
We've set up a direct line
of contact to the police.
Once the heroes are
in position, they'll
all move in on my command.
At that instant, you roll the
cameras, and Hero TV goes live.
-I get it.
So they won't have
enough time to escape.
I got to admit, the audience
is going to eat it up.
-Are you getting excited?
-[gulp] No.
-Hello, heroes.
We know there are five criminals
hold up in that church.
They are heavily armed
and very dangerous.
There may also be NEXTs.
So watch out.
Just in case, the police
have set up roadblocks
and sealed all entry
points around the area.
Listen.
The police have spent months
tracking down this syndicate.
You cannot let them get away.
Hero TV's reputation
is at stake.
Or to put it another way,
do a good job and you'll
rack up a huge amount of points.
-Hey, you hear that?
I bet you're happy now.
Yeah, well, I guess
points aren't everything.
You know if those
guys in the hideout
are from Ouroboros, that
NEXT with the blue flames
might make an appearance.
He's been dropping criminals
one by one, keeping them quiet.
Almost like he's cleaning
house for his organization.
Don't you think?
-I'm surprised you figured
that all out on your own.
-Well, Fire Emblem kind
of helped, a little.
-Of course, he did.
-Look.
I get it, Bunny.
I know how bad you want to
go in and get your revenge,
but an order's an order.
-I don't need lessons on
professionalism from you,
but you can save the sympathy.
-Good talk.
Good talk.
AGNES: Right.
Then, we'll proceed.
Everyone's in position.
I'm going to change things up.
For this mission, open all
com channels to the heroes.
-On it.
AGNES: The second
this commercial ends,
we're on the air.
-Hey, Bunny.
If that NEXT does show up,
are you, uh-- you know.
-What?
-Hey, what the
hell just happened?
NATHAN (ON INTERCOM): Is
that who I think it is?
KOTETSU: It's him.
[shouting]
-He's egging us on.
ANTONIO: Where are
you going, Kotetsu?
-Where do you think?
I'm going to save people.
Hey, Bunny, we've got
the hideout covered.
You go after the NEXT.
NATHAN (ON INTERCOM): Teach
that wannabe a lesson for me.
-Whoa.
-You'll never take us
alive, you bastard.
-What are you, nuts?
We're here to protect you.
-OK.
We're back from commercial.
What do we do about
the broadcast?
Should we call it off?
-Not a chance.
-But, ma'am.
-Roll cameras.
I want those ratings.
Think about it.
Heroes trying to protect
the very criminals they
were sent to arrest.
You can't buy drama like that.
LUNATIC: My fellow heroes.
I do hope you can hear me.
-Hey, who was that?
-Ignore him.
Just stay on task.
LUNATIC: The justice
you seek is nothing
more than a hollow fallacy.
COMPUTER: Good Luck Mode.
LUNATIC: You call
yourselves heroes,
but you can neither
save nor punish anyone.
Your so called bravery
is all in vain,
why do you even bother trying?
-Come on.
LUNATIC: If you
want true justice,
only I can give it to you.
What a shame.
Is the show already over?
-Are you part of Ouroboros?
Tell me.
-And if I were, what
would you do to me?
Catch me and rip off my suit?
Tear my body limb from limb.
-Damn you.
-Ah.
There's the answer I expected.
I understand that the justice
you and your hero pals believe
in only takes you so far.
It's all a facade.
My name is Lunatic,
and you'll see,
I follow my own code of justice.
KOTETSU: Not today,
you psycho bastard.
You call what you do justice?
Well, I got another word for it.
Murder!
-Murder?
You have a peculiar way
of looking at things.
-Yeah.
Well, your face is peculiar.
What the hell's that
on your head, a glove?
-So you're Wild Tiger.
I'll be sure to remember you.
-Hey, get back here.
LUNATIC: Don't worry.
We'll meet again.
Where there is
darkness in the world,
I'll be there to snuff it out.
-Dammit.
I let him get away.
-Don't give up just yet, Bunny.
After all, we have a lead.
Rock Bison just called
in from the hideout.
He managed to capture one
of the criminals alive.
[theme music]
-So did he have one
of those tattoos?
Ah, dammit.
Then whatever that
crime syndicate was,
it wasn't part of Ouroboros.
-There's no point beating
ourselves up over it.
We'll just have to
wait till he wakes up,
and then ask more questions.
-Hey, you're taking this
better than I thought.
But if that NEXT wasn't
trying to silence him,
then what was he trying to do?
-The good guys are supposed
to kill the bad guys.
-I follow my own
code of justice.
-Lunatic.
-Sir, I apologize
for all the trouble.
I realize you're very busy.
-No.
It's fine.
This is just part of my job.
-Being a judge sounds
like a tough gig.
I mean you got to sit through
all those boring trials.
-Well, we judges
are here to serve
the Justice Bureau,
just like you.
If there's anything
else I can do for you,
please don't hesitate to ask.
I'm here to help.
BARNABY: Hi, I'm Barnaby,
the member of Tiger and Bunny
who owns five pairs
of the same glasses.
What?
A hero campaign?
Hold on.
With these people?
Next time on "Tiger & Bunny,"
"There is Always a Next Time."
See ya.