[opera]
[bells chiming]
[music playing]
-Dinner is served.
Eat it while it's hot, monsieur.
-What is this?
-Duh, fried rice.
If you recall the last
time I made this dish,
it got ruined before
you took a bite.
So I'm trying again.
-That's not what I meant.
-Hm?
-Why are you doting
on me all of a sudden?
-Uh, well, I-- you know
I'm worried about you.
[chuckle]
[sigh]
-Uh!
-It's so frustrating.
-Hm?
-My parents murderer,
in my memory,
his face keeps changing.
At one point, he
even looked like you.
-Uh, just for the record,
I wasn't the killer.
OK?
-The harder I try to remember
that day the less I know.
My memory is so vague.
It's driving me nuts.
I can't take it.
-Well, what if we retraced
your steps the day
your parents died?
-What's the point of that?
-It always seems
to help me when I
lose something really important.
Maybe it'll help you too.
Hey, you won't be the
Bunny we all know and love
until you get this figured out.
-OK.
[christmas music playing]
-On that day, this is where you
were right before it happened?
-Yeah.
The rink was just as
likely as it is today.
-Uh, was that kiosk
here back then?
-Huh?
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Mr. Maverick bought me a hat.
[laughter]
-Thank you.
Have a nice day.
[laughter]
-Do you really think this is
the best time to go shopping?
-Don't worry I got
something for you too.
See?
-Yeah, no thanks.
-(SHOCK) What?
I bought us a matching pair
because we're partners.
-That's not a selling point.
-(CHEERFULLY) Oh, come on now.
Don't be shy.
Hold still so I can
pin it on you here.
-I think you're
forgetting why we're here.
Plus, this is a leather jacket.
Don't go ruining it with
some cheap souvenir.
Why are you being so sappy?
We'll have plenty of
other opportunities
to hang out together.
-All right already.
I'll resign and get back
there just as soon as I can.
PHOTOGRAPHER (OFF
SCREEN): All right.
Say cheese.
-Wow!
That tree must be a
million feet high.
I had my picture
taken that day too.
BUNNY (VOICEOVER): I can't wait
to show this to mom and dad
when I get home.
[laughter]
-A cheesy holiday picture with
Maverick, that's hilarious!
-Why is that?
-Why?
I don't know.
It's just ridiculous to imagine.
-Not that.
I can clearly remember coming
here with Mr. Maverick.
But why can't I
picture the killer?
-Don't torment
yourself over this.
-(ANXIOUSLY) But what
if my memory is gone?
What if I never know the answer?
I can't!
-Huh?
Woah Barnaby!
-(SADLY) I can't!
-He uh He's just--
Take it easy Bunny.
-(SADLY) Kriem was
right after all.
I'm going to be tortured by the
past for the rest of my life.
[crying]
-That's it.
I've made up my mind.
I'm not leaving until we
solve this thing together.
Real partners stick
together no matter
how tough things may get.
-(WHISPER) You mean it?
-Yeah.
That sounded pretty badass, huh?
-What the-- Hey,
what's wrong with you?
Come on, Bunny, talk to me.
Thanks for all your help.
I guess he was just exhausted.
Poor guy.
[door closes]
[christmas music playing]
BUNNY: Thank you so
much Uncle Maverick.
I'll see you real soon, OK?
[laugh]
[gun shot]
[opera]
-Kotetsu?
-Oh, hey, mom.
It's me again.
How's Kaede doing?
-She's fine.
And I assume she told
you about her abilities.
-Yes, she can copy
other people's powers.
-From what I hear, it's
a pretty rare ability.
We still don't know all the
ins and outs of how it works.
-So how's she
handling everything?
-So far, she's dealing
with it extremely well.
-That's my girl!
-You're not out
of the woods yet.
Your daughter is
going to need a lot
of help getting through this.
So when can she expect
her father back home?
-Uh, yeah.
About that, actually, I've
run into a little hiccup
that might delay my return.
-How long of a delay?
-I'm not sure, but I'm
definitely quitting soon.
-Are you ever really
going to resign?
-I am honest!
There's just some
unfinished business
I got to take care
of first, you know?
If I throw in the towel
without settling this,
I know Ill regret it.
Sorry, but you'll just
have to be patient with me.
-(ANGRILY) Don't
bother coming home!
I'm not going to believe a
word you say as long as I live!
-Is that you, hon?
-You promised me you were
quitting, and it just a lie!
-No, wait!
I am coming home just not today.
-You care about your job
more than me, don't you?
-That's not true, sweetheart.
Of course, you're the most
important thing in my life.
It's just that now is not
exactly the best time for me
to be quitting my job.
Daddy is serious
about quitting, OK?
You just have to hang
on a little bit longer.
[phone clicks]
-Huh?
Not again.
BUNNY: What was that all about?
What did you mean
quitting your job?
So you're going to
quit being a hero
just like that, without
even telling your partner?
-Oh that.
I uh--
-But why right now?
Is this related to your
daughter's new powers?
Is there something
wrong with her?
-No, it has nothing to
do with that at all.
-Then why are you running away?
-Well, I just think
it's time for me
to settle down and
be a normal guy.
You know what I mean?
-No.
-Being a hero is unpredictable.
It's fine when
you're a young man,
but I'm getting too old
for this stuff, which
is why I decided to get
out of the hero game
and get myself a nice desk
job like everybody else.
-Do you honestly think
I'm going to believe that?
Why want you just tell me
what's really going on?
-Huh?
-You always told
me that partners
are supposed to be
there for each other.
The truth is you don't
trust me, do you?
-Hey, come on Bunny.
It's not like that.
Oh, I get it.
All day long, you've
been trying to help,
trying to stop me from quitting.
You were doing all
that so it would
make it easier when you quit.
-Well, I--
-The only reason
you wanted to help
was so you wouldn't feel guilty
for turning your back on me.
-No!
-I trusted you, and
you betrayed me.
Well, guess what?
You don't have to bother
pretending anymore.
Leave whenever you feel like
it, I'll be just fine on my own.
-Hey, hang on a second Bunny.
-I'm better off alone.
-Huh?
-I was doing fine
before I met you,
and I'll be relieved
when you're gone.
-You don't mean that.
-Letting you get some
arrests was one thing,
but I'm tired of carrying you.
-Hey!
-I'm better as a solo act.
In fact, I can't wait
till you're gone.
-Woah!
Sorry about that Bunny .
Don't you power up!
Hey, wait a minute!
Come on!
Uh.
-Sorry to drop in so suddenly.
-Did something happen.
Why don't you try
telling me about it?
I might be able to
help you out Barnaby.
-It's my parents.
Their murder isn't solved.
Whoever killed my mom
and dad, it wasn't Jake.
-What!
Impossible!
-Kriem let it slip
right before she died.
-I can vouch for his innocence.
I was with him the
entire day it happened.
We're just a small
faction of Ouroboros.
BUNNY: The real
murderer is probably
someone else who works
with Ouroboros, which
means Ouroboros might be a much
bigger organization than we
ever imagined.
-And you're just going
to believe everything
a dying criminal tells you?
-But what about that tattoo?
The murder had one on his
right hand, but Jake didn't.
-Then, I'm sorry Barnaby.
It appears we're
back to square one.
-That's not the only thing.
Ever since I found out that
Jake wasn't the real murderer,
my memory has been
a complete mess.
Without that lead, I
don't know anything.
-You should calm down my boy.
I can understand
your frustration,
but impatience won't help you
get any closer to the truth.
Perhaps, I should do some
digging into Ouroboros.
-Thank you.
-Was anyone else
in the room when
Kriem gave you that information?
-Huh?
-I think it would
be wise to keep
this just between the two of us.
-Kotetsu was with me.
That's it, but--
[phone ringing]
-I don't mind.
You can answer it.
-Sorry Samantha.
Would you mind if I
called you back later?
-Barnaby I remember the
day of your parents murder.
-Hey, can I leave my
car here overnight?
-Sure, buddy.
Of course you can.
-Great, Ill take
something stronger.
-Well, Barnaby, you've already
broken Mr. Legends record,
so is there any hero out
there you aspire to be?
-Well, no one comes to mind.
-Thanks, pal.
-But, you know, there is one
person with more heart than me.
REPORTER: Oh, more
heart, you say?
-He's clumsy and
does crazy things,
but he always gives it
110% and takes pride
in his work like no one else.
He impresses me
all the time, and I
hope that one day I can
be worthy of his trust.
Even so, I wouldn't want
to be exactly like him.
-Which hero is it?
-That's a secret.
(VOICEOVER) The truth is
you don't trust me, do you?
-On second thought,
I'm done for the night.
SAMANTHA (ON PHONE): What you
said yesterday got me thinking,
so I dug through some old
boxes, and I found a photograph.
-Photograph?
SAMANTHA (ON PHONE):
Yes, Barnaby.
It was taken the
day of the murder.
-What is going on?
SAMANTHA (ON PHONE):
I don't know,
but ever since I
found this picture,
I've been really confused
about what happened.
I still can't make head
or tails of any of this.
-Don't get too upset, OK?
Listen, I'll look into this
and give you a call later on.
-Everything OK Barnaby?
-Mr. Maverick, you
took me to the park
to see the Christmas tree the
day they died, didn't you?
-Barnaby, don't-- Yes,
it was 21 years ago.
You and I went to see
the Christmas tree
and spent the day together.
We've gone over this 100 times.
BUNNY (VOICEOVER): I can't wait
to show this to mom and dad
when I get home.
[laughter]
-I know!
I wasn't with you.
-Of course you were.
What on earth are
you talking about?
-I visited the
Christmas tree that day,
but you weren't the one with me.
-Yes, I was.
My boy, you seem to be a
bit confused and anxious.
Maybe you need some rest.
-I can remember it
perfectly now all
because of Samantha's
this picture.
SAMANTHA (VOICEOVER):
Yes, Barnaby.
It was taken the
day of the murder.
-What is going on?
You weren't there with me that
day at the Christmas tree.
So the real question
is, why have you
been lying about
it all these years?
And if you weren't with me,
then what were you really
doing that day?
-How dare you talk
to me like that?
If anything you should
be grateful to me.
You are the man you are because
of the way I raised you.
When you were young, I was
impressed by your powers.
I knew that I could make
you into a true hero,
and I was right.
You have far surpassed
my original expectations.
-What are you talking about?
-Barnaby, seeing you now I
know I made the right decision.
I'm glad I let you live.
-Let me live?
No, you don't mean--
-Your mother and father
had a strong sense
of justice and compassion
almost to a fault
It was rough when I
first launched Hero TV.
Your parents were about the only
people who supported my vision.
They were my closest friends.
They even provided me with
the earliest hero suits
using special metal
alloys they developed
through their extensive
robotics research.
But despite our best efforts,
Hero TV's ratings were abysmal.
The audience was against us.
People still had a strong
prejudice against the NEXT.
So I came up with
a plan that would
make the heroes of
vital necessity,
and at the same time,
boost my show's ratings.
I set up exciting crimes and
broadcast the arrests live.
I knew that by doing so,
the people of the city
would change how they
thought about heroes.
But I needed
perpetrators, so I had
to team up with a certain
crime organization.
-You mean Ouroboros?
-The plan worked perfectly,
but just as the show
began to pick up steam, your
parents asked to meet with me.
It was on Christmas Eve.
-Did you think we wouldn't
find out what you were doing?
We didn't develop
nanometals so they
could be used by criminals.
MR. MAVERICK (VOICEOVER):
They realized
that I had joined forces
with the organization
and had been using
their technology
to supply them with weapons.
They demanded that I come
clean, make everything public,
and atone for my crimes.
But when I refused
[sigh]
It turned out that your parents
were far too smart and too
naive for their own good.
[gun shots]
-It can't be.
You're lying.
I can still see that
moment, and you're not
the murder in my memories.
-There's one more thing
I've neglected to tell.
You see, I can plant memories
inside people's minds.
You're a NEXT.
-But now it's apparent that
the memory I implanted in you
has been compromised by
the tiniest contradiction.
This isn't good.
-You mean all this time you
were the one behind everything?
-There is really no point in
asking any more questions.
After all, when I'm
done, you're going
to forget this
entire conversation.
-Uh
-Don't worry my boy.
I will give you this
gift one more time.
[phone ringing]
-Have sweet dreams Barnaby.
[music playing]
BUNNY (VOICEOVER):
Hi, I'm Barnaby
the member of Tiger & Bunny who
uses an electric toothbrush.
Be careful Kotetsu!
It's been him all along.
Next time on Tiger & Bunny,
Full of Courtesy Full of Craft.
See you!