[sonar beeping]
[gasping]
[beeping continues]
[cell phone rings]
-Is it Kotetsu?
-No, it's Mister Lloyds.
Hello, this is Barnaby.
-Listen Barnaby, I just got a
call from the Justice Bureau.
That girl Kriem who
was helping Jake
just came out of
the coma she's been
in since the helicopter crash.
-What?
[chuckling]
-Check out how young I looked.
I hadn't decided what kind
of hero I wanted to be.
Ahh, this is really not
the time to be doing this.
-Here, this is so
you don't forget!
-All right.
[MUSIC -- NOVELS, "MISSING
LINK"]
-Bunny, there's something
I have to tell you.
Sorry, but due to events
beyond my control,
I've decided to retire.
Yes, that sounds pretty good.
Oh, wait.
I wonder if Bunny is going
to ask what those events are.
What do I say?
[laughter]
-Tiger, you're back.
It's great to see you.
-Uh, thanks.
-Oh, you took of so suddenly
we were worried about you.
-Yeah, sorry.
-It was only a few
days, but something
didn't feel right about it.
-I have to agree.
-But you're back now.
And that's a reason
to celebrate.
So welcome, uh,
and welcome again.
-It's good to be back.
-Oh, come on.
What's everybody getting
so excited about?
-Eh?
-I mean, you really
didn't have to come back
if you didn't want to.
Why doesn't everyone admit it?
It felt nice having
one less rival.
-What's the point
of lying like that?
-Huh?
-Well, if I'm not mistaken,
you missed Mister Wild
more than any of us.
-Uh, no I didn't.
-Yes she did.
(FEMALE VOICE) When
is Tiger going to come back?
She asked me that
like, every single day.
-Yep.
She asked me the same thing.
-Me too.
-Well, I-- I was worried.
Welcome back.
-Hmm.
-I can't imagine what's
making her act like that, hmm?
-Hmm.
-Well, the reaction does show
just how much we missed you.
Now that you're
back, everything's
going to be golden.
-Right.
Oh, by the way,
anybody seen Bunny?
-So what's happening?
Have you told everybody
you're going to be quitting?
-I haven't found the right
time to bring up the subject.
-Oh, good heavens, what
are you waiting for?
-Well, I wanted to
tell my partner first,
but he hasn't been around.
-Are you sure you
can do this, Kotetsu?
The longer you wait, the harder
it's going to be to tell--
-Eh, don't worry.
I'm sure the opportunity
will come up soon.
As a matter of fact, I heard
Bunny's in a pretty good mood.
A key suspect is
finally talking.
-Oh?
-That's right.
And after that, I'm
going to tell him,
-Well, whatever works.
But please son,
don't drag your feet.
We need you back here
as soon as possible.
We've been having a tough time.
Kaede's powers are running wild.
She's been breaking
everything in the house.
I'm telling you,
it's complete chaos.
KOTETSU: (ON PHONE) Oh yeah.
It takes a little bit
of time before you
learn to control
the Hundred Power.
-Yes, I remember.
You had the same problem.
[kaede gasps]
-OK, that's it.
I'm sick of this!
[glass shattering]
-Oh, my kitchen table!
If she keeps this
up, I'm afraid she's
going to bring the
whole house down.
So hurry up, will you?
-All right already.
I'll resign and get back
there just as soon as I can.
[footsteps]
-Hey.
Coffee, Bunny?
-Kotetsu.
You just get back?
-Yep.
What's up?
Have you been able to get
in to talk to Kriem yet?
-No, not yet.
After she heard about Jake's
death, her condition worsened.
-Not surprising.
-So what brings you here?
-No reason.
I just had something important
I wanted to talk to you about.
-Oh?
So what is it?
-Ah, never mind.
We'll talk about it later.
-Mr. Brooks, she says
she wants to talk to you.
-The doctor said
you have something
to tell me, Miss Kriem?
I need to know.
Why did Jake kill my parents?
-I guess you don't understand.
He was my savior.
Mister Jake meant
everything to me.
-Yeah right.
This is nonsense.
[kriem laughs]
-Ever since I was a
little girl, people
treated me as if I were
some kind of awful monster
just because I
happen to be a NEXT.
They would avoid me or
terrorize me wherever I went.
I was isolated,
persecuted by the world.
FEMALE VOICE: I heard
she's not a normal human.
Yeah, she's a NEXT.
MALE VOICE: She creeps me out.
KRIEM: No one had anything
kind to say to me.
They either ignored
me or abandoned me.
Even my own parents
didn't love me.
-I can't take it anymore.
-Quiet, she can hear you.
-I don't care if she can.
We're being treated like
monsters because of her.
It's driving me insane.
-Why couldn't we just have a
normal child, like everyone
else?
-If I'd known she
would be a NEXT,
I never would have had children.
-I was different from everyone.
I wasn't a normal human being.
I looked the same
as everyone else.
So why was this happening?
Why was I the only one
being treated like that?
Then, when everything
seemed so dark, I met him.
[kriem gasps]
-Now, don't make a fuss.
KRIEM: Later that day, he
demanded a large sum of money
from my father,
-So that means you were
Jake's victim at first.
-Then why the hell did you
end up joining that psycho?
-It was a simple decision.
Mister Jake saved me.
We waited in the
station for hours.
But in the end?
My parents didn't show
up with the money.
-They're not coming, are they.
They really don't want me.
It's because I'm a NEXT.
It's because I'm a freak.
-Hmm?
-Sorry.
My parents don't think
I'm worth the money.
There's no point in waiting.
You can kill me now.
Go ahead, get it over with.
It really doesn't matter.
No one's going to
miss me anyway.
You're doing everyone a
favor by getting rid of me.
So go ahead.
Kill me.
[kriem sobs]
-Tell me.
What's so great
about being normal?
Don't be ashamed of who you are.
Be proud.
Listen to me.
People consider us freaks.
But we're actually the ultimate
form of human evolution.
The reason we've been
given power is easy to see.
We are the chosen ones.
-What?
We're the chosen ones?
Really?
-I've never been more sure.
We NEXTs stand above
the human race.
Remember that.
The weak have always
been fearful beings.
In fact, they refuse to accept
the existence of anyone who's
superior to them.
You're a member of
that superior race.
The rest of the population
is afraid of your abilities,
and will always
try to destroy you.
So remember, don't be ashamed.
Be proud.
Go on.
You're free to leave.
-I couldn't believe
what I had heard.
His words released
me from my suffering.
He was the first
person to accept me
for what I was, and told
me to be proud of it.
Wait, please!
Will you take me with you?
-Hmm?
-I get it.
And I want to help you.
-Fine, whatever.
-When I look back on it, the
only happy time in my life
was with him.
It was when I truly
felt alive and free.
Mister Jake and I were
trying to build a world ruled
by NEXTs, where we'd be
free from persecution.
It was a dream he had for
a long time, something
we shared together.
[kriem gasps]
-Are you all right?
-If you and your friends hadn't
interfered with the plan,
we would have been saved.
We were on our way to
completing our ideal world.
And you heroes kill him!
-How would that have been ideal?
I mean just look at
what you've described.
In that world, normal
humans would just
experience what you did.
Everything would be
the same, but you'd
end up being the persecutors.
-It would be a
natural progression.
After all, humans are
inferior to NEXTs.
-So killing normal people
would then be acceptable?
That would be your
idea of justice?
Is that why Jake went out
and killed my parents?
-To defend Mister
Jake's honor, I'm
going to tell you something.
I know you think he was the
one who killed your parents.
But you see, he didn't.
I'm sure you remember
your parents were killed
21 years ago on Christmas Eve.
That also happened to be the day
when Mister Jake kidnapped me.
-What are you saying?
-I can vouch for his innocent.
I was with him the
entire day it happened.
-You're lying.
-Sorry, but he's
innocent of the crime.
That means your parents' murder
hasn't been solved, I guess.
-Liar!
-I hope the past tortures you
for the rest of your life!
This is your punishment
for killing Mister Jake!
-What are you doing?
Hey, we need some help in here!
-What's happened to her?
-We're just a small
faction of Ouroboros.
-Move out of the way!
[kriem gasping wildly]
-Ouroboros will never die!
-What are you talking about?
-Hold her steady!
-I'm trying!
-Mister Jake, I will
be with you forever.
[sirens in distance]
-By the way, what is it
you wanted to tell me?
-Huh?
-Earlier you said you had
something important to tell me.
-Oh, well.
I don't need to
tell you right now.
-OK.
-I'm really sorry, Bunny.
I know you were hoping
today's meeting would give you
some closure.
Looks to me like we're
back to square one.
But I'm sure the
answers are out there.
-Jake is the murderer.
I remember the whole thing.
It's burned into my memory
like it happened yesterday.
There's no way it
was someone else.
-Then you think Kriem was
saying all that just to bait us?
-Yes.
She obviously held
a grudge against us.
-Yeah, but there
really was a report
saying that Kriem had been
kidnapped 21 years ago.
On top of that, the
date was accurate.
According to the case file, she
went missing on Christmas Eve.
-So what?
It doesn't prove that Jake
was the one who kidnapped her.
-But still--
-Who are you going to believe?
I remember Jake is the murder.
His face is burned
into my memory.
I remember him
looking at me right
after he killed my parents.
He was holding a gun
in his right hand,
the one with the
Ouroboros tattoos on it.
What's the point in
looking through all
those old video files?
-I'm trying to see if
there's any footage of Jake
with his gloves off.
-What?
-Well, we don't really
know if he was with Kriem
on the day your
parents were murdered.
-Trust me, he wasn't.
-What if you're wrong?
You see, one thing
we can easily confirm
is whether or not Jake
was sporting a tattoo.
We should be able
to learn something
from these archived videos.
-What are you saying?
That my memory's not reliable?
Well, this is so stupid.
-Aha.
Here we go.
-Go ahead.
But I already know the answer.
-Were the heroes
too boring for you?
Well, here's some
titillating news.
After the NEXT match,
we're halfway done.
-He doesn't have a tattoo.
-Can't be.
Impossible.
Something's wrong.
Maybe he had surgery
to remove it.
-I can understand your feelings.
But there's no evidence
he ever had one.
-No way.
That tattoo is very
clear in my memory.
If it wasn't him, who's
the murderer I saw?
-What's wrong?
[barnaby pants]
-Hey, Bunny, you all right?
What's going on?
-I'm not really sure.
-The murderer's face changed?
-Yeah.
My memory of Jake's
face suddenly
morphed into all
sorts of other people.
-What does that mean?
-That's what I'm
trying figure out.
-Has something like this
ever happened to you before?
-There was a time when I
couldn't remember his face,
but nothing like this.
-Hmm.
[cell phone rings]
-Hello, Kotetsu?
How did it go?
Have you told them
you're quitting yet?
-Uh, not really,.
-What are you doing, son?
You promised me
earlier that you were
going to tell them before
the end of the day.
-And I was going to, believe me.
But it's been crazy,
things keep coming up.
-Oh, please.
Are you going to break your
promise to Kaede again?
-Huh?
-I won't go on making
excuses for you, Kotetsu.
-So how is Kaede?
Has she at least calmed down?
-Well, not exactly.
It seems as though her power is
turning out a little different
than yours.
-Huh?
-It's very strange.
Now her body is
acting like a magnet.
[kaede sighs]
-Wait a minute.
Are you saying she has
two separate powers?
-I really can't tell.
That's why I want you to hurry.
Get home, will you, so
you can look after her?
Who knows what powers she's
going to have tomorrow.
Get here before something
really bad happens.
-I'll do my best.
-Are you all right?
You sounded like
you were worried.
-Yeah.
My daughter's developed
some powers, that's all.
-Do you know what kind?
-Oh, not sure yet.
But there's something else I've
been meaning to talk about.
-Sorry.
But due to certain events
beyond my control--
-I understand.
You want to leave early, right?
-Leave early?
-It's fine.
You should hurry home
and go see your daughter.
-No, wait.
I, Wild Tiger--
-You don't have to explain.
I can handle
things, don't worry.
It'll be OK.
-Wait a minute, that's
not what I meant.
-Hello?
-Oh, hello.
I haven't heard
from you in a while.
I must say, it's kind of unusual
for you to give me a call.
Oh my, who's the
gentleman with you?
-Hello ma'am.
My name's Wild Tiger.
-Very nice to me you.
My name is Samantha.
I used to work as a
housekeeper for Master
Barnaby and his family.
-Nice to meet you.
-Samantha.
SAMANTHA: Yes?
-Sorry to bother you.
But there's something
I want to ask.
-What is it, my dear?
-21 years ago, can you tell
me where you were on the day
my parents were murdered?
-What?
-That day, you weren't there
at the house, were you?
-No.
I believe I was home ill.
I remember having
quite a serious cold.
-Is there anyone who
can prove you were sick?
-Prove it?
I'm afraid not.
That was quite a long time ago.
-So the fact is, we
have to take your word.
-Hey, hold on a minute.
-What is it?
-What's going on with you?
-I told you what was going on.
My memory of the murderer's
face started changing.
Her face was in the mix.
-So you think she
murdered your folks?
What the hell's wrong
with you, Bunny?
She seems like just a
nice, sweet old lady.
-Yeah, but she showed
up in my memory.
I don't have any other leads.
I have to follow up on the
ones that present themselves.
-How do you know you
can trust your memory
after all the things you're
starting to find out?
If you ask me,
you're acting nuts.
SAMANTHA: Um, Master Barnaby?
Are you still there?
-He's still here, he
just got interrupted.
He'll have to call you back.
-At this point, I just
don't know what to think.
The facts I've
believed all this time
have suddenly begun
to fall apart.
I feel like the ground's been
pulled out from under me.
-That's completely
understandable.
-Kotetsu?
-Hmm?
-Maybe it'd be best
if I just stepped
down and quit being a hero.
-Huh?
-I'm not really confident
I can do the job-- not
in this state of
confusion, anyway.
-What?
Now, let's not get hasty.
-I'm sorry.
I need to sorts some things out.
-But, hold on a minute!
-I'm so sorry, Kaede.
Daddy's been having
a really tough time.
Just when I was about to tell
my partner I was quitting,
he beat me to it and he
said he was quitting.
-Yeah, so?
-Well, the problem is,
I'm not sure what to do.
If we all quit, no one's going
to be around to do the job,
right?
-So that means you're
not coming home.
-Not immediately.
-I expected some excuse!
-No, it's just a
temporary delay.
Uh, so tell me
about your powers.
I hear you have two of them.
That's pretty amazing.
-No.
I just have one.
-Huh?
-I have one power, OK?
-Really?
But grandma said that you had
magnetic power plus the Hundred
Power.
-Looks like I have the
ability to copy powers.
KOTETSU: Copy?
-Uncle Muramasa told me he
thinks he figured it out.
I can copy the power
of any NEXT I touch.
He says I'm like a chameleon.
-Don't think I've ever
heard of a power like that.
So does the previous power go
away when you copy the new one?
-I don't really know.
And I don't really
want to talk about it.
-Oh, Kaede.
Come on, please tell daddy?
-I don't even know why
I'm talking to you.
What's the point?
You're not coming back.
-That's not true.
I'm definitely coming
home tomorr-- oh, brother.
[music -- tamaki, "mind game"]
[operatic chanting]
[barnaby screams]
KOTETSU: Hi, I'm Kotetsu,
the member of Tiger and Bunny
who develops crushes
on every actress.
The truth about Ouroboros
is a complete mystery again,
but I've already decided
to quit being a hero.
Next time on "Tiger and
Bunny," "There's No Way Out."
Hey, pretty good, huh?