[music playing]
JUDGE: We have
reached a verdict.
This court finds that the
structural damages caused
by the hero known as Wild Tiger
in the filming of "Hero TV"
did not result in saving
any civilian lives.
Therefore, Apollon Media
will be held liable
for the cost of all repairs.
-Yeah.
-This court is adjourned.
KOTETSU: Hey, why
are you pissed off?
This is my problem.
BARNABY: It's my problem, too.
We're a team.
That verdict takes points
away from both of us.
-Ah, who cares about points?
A real hero does it to
protect innocent lives--
-Would you just shut up?
I know we're a duo,
and I've really
tried to put up with you.
But I don't think
I can take much
more of your constant meddling.
-Meddling?
-You said you were
trying to save people,
but all you did was
destroy buildings.
How is that supposed
to save anyone?
-Jeez, it was just
this one time.
-It's every time!
And it's not just during work.
You stick your
nose in everything.
You even bug me about my diet.
-Oh, now I can't
give you advice?
-Not when it drives me crazy.
Listen, I know you mean well,
but every time you try to help,
it just causes more problems
for everyone around you.
-Mm.
WOMAN: Oh my god, Barnaby?
Oh, he's a huge fan of yours.
Can you please sign my baby?
BARNABY: Uh, your baby?
I-- guess so.
-Oh, and by the
way, happy birthday!
-Huh?
-Tomorrow is your
big day, isn't it?
-Yeah, that's right.
-Uh?
-I bet a megastar like
Barnaby Brooks Jr.
must have a most
extravagant birthday
party planned for tomorrow.
-Actually, I don't have plans.
Here.
-Oh, wow!
I'll treasure this pen forever!
Oh!
KOTETSU: Uh, let me
get that for you.
It's the least I can
do for a young mom.
Gah!
-My pen.
-Ugh.
-Ah, you gotta be
kidding, you dumb car!
Talk about awful timing.
[MUSIC - UNISON SQUARE GARDEN,
"ORION O NAZORU"]
KOTETSU: Good
morning, everybody.
Isn't the weather out
there beautiful today?
-Mm-hm.
I guess so.
-When you look at a
gorgeous blue sky,
it makes stuff like paying
government fines seems
so trivial, don't you think?
-Because you're
not the one paying.
-Oh, ha-ha, you're such
a kidder, Florence.
Hm?
What's wrong?
You sick or something?
-No, I feel fine.
It's just that seeing
your face is reminding me
of what happened yesterday.
-Gah!
[sigh]
-Uh, what do you
mean, what happened?
-Oh, never mind.
It bums me out just
thinking about it.
-Wait a minute.
Yesterday--
-Barnaby Brooks Jr. must have
the most extravagant birthday
party planned for tomorrow.
-Actually, I don't have plans.
-Oh, I get it.
-A birthday party?
-That's right.
We gotta throw
Bunny a big shindig.
-Fabulous idea.
-You're saying Pretty
Boy was really upset
about some stupid birthday?
-Yeah.
The poor guy was so depressed.
That was the first time I've
ever seen him like that.
The only way we can cheer him
up is with a kick-ass birthday
party.
-Sounds like you're
just meddling to me.
-Say what?
-I mean, your partner
doesn't strike me
as the type of guy
who enjoy surprises.
-You don't get it!
When Bunny finds out we went
to all this trouble for him,
he's gonna be like, thank you!
He's gonna hug all of us!
KARINA: Then count me out.
-Huh?
-I'm not interested
in hugging that guy.
Come on, look at us.
We're not his friends.
We're his competition.
-She makes a good point there.
-But Fire Emblem said
it was a fabulous idea.
-Huh, on second
thought, it sucks.
-Come on!
What's wrong with you people?
Aren't birthdays a
chance for everyone
to celebrate and be together?
KEITH: Absolutely.
I completely agree.
Birthdays are special days.
Yes, when one of a
celebrates a milestone,
we should all support him.
Right, Mr. Wild?
-Right, but these
guys don't want to--
-A surprise party it is.
-Huh?
-If the King of Heroes
says so, then I'm on board.
-Sky High, what you just
said was really moving.
-Hey, he just repeated the
same thing I said before!
-All right, people.
Let's work together to throw
Barnaby a one-of-a-kind party.
ALL: Yeah!
-This was my idea.
-Hey, so what kind of gift
are you getting Barnaby?
-Huh?
I kind of thought the
party was his present.
-Uh, no, dummy.
You have to give
him a real gift.
Something from the heart.
-I have no idea
what he even likes.
-You're so hopeless.
Do you want me to help
you find something?
-Uh, uh--
-You'd look snappy in
something like this.
-I would never wear that.
-Really?
So, uh, which one of
these do you like?
-Have you ever
seen me wear a hat?
-Guess not.
Hey, so what do you think
about this man apron?
-What is wrong with you today?
-Oh, I'm just doing research
on some of my friends.
Just want to keep up to
date on what they're into.
-And why would you
want to know that?
-No reason.
Come on, isn't there anything
that you really want?
-Up there.
-What?
You want a flat-screen?
-Not the TV, the diamond.
REPORTER (ON TV):
The rare diamond,
known as the Tears of
Hercules, is currently
on display at the
Sternbild Central Museum.
People have been
lining up all day
to get a glimpse
of the gem, which
is valued at roughly 6
million Stern Dollars.
-Out of my price range.
PAULY: I want that rock.
In fact, I've decided that's
what we're going to steal next.
-Yet another diamond, sir?
-Do you have a problem
with what I want?
-But sir, isn't your collection
already quite extensive?
-Don't you get it?
When it comes to
my desires, there's
no such thing as enough.
If I want something,
I will make it
mine-- that is, as long as I
have my wealth and my powers.
[laughs]
-You're wondering why
I called you down here.
Well, it's because
there's a dangerous gang
of thieves on the loose.
Are you up to catching
these guys, Bunny?
(FALSETTO VOICE) As
long as you're with me.
Let's do it, then.
[grunts] [groans] Look!
That must be one
of the thieves now.
Let's roll.
-(FALSETTO VOICE) OK!
[panting]
-Get back here!
-You're cornered!
-Boss, you gotta save
me from this guy.
-Stop right there.
So you're the thief in charge.
-Who are you guys, anyway?
--[laughs] We don't give
our names to scum like you.
You guys got one more chance.
Give up or you're going down.
-You are the one who
should be giving up.
-What?
KARINA: Freeze, tough guys.
-Uh?
-Oh, no!
We're surrounded!
-We heard that you've been
calling us scum behind
our backs.
Bit mistake, buddy.
-What should we do, Bunny?
(FALSETTO VOICE) I don't know.
I'm scared!
-[laughs] I am afraid it's over.
You'd better say your prayers.
-Save me, Bunny!
-Eat lead!
[bang]
ALL: Happy birthday!
-And that's a wrap.
-Good rehearsal.
-Yeah.
-I think I sounded
pretty cool, huh?
We don't give our names to scum
like you. [chuckles] Awesome.
-Yeah, yeah.
-What kind of feedback is that?
-Well, how do you think I did?
I threw in some brand new lines.
-You overdid it.
"I'm afraid it's over.
You'd better say your prayers."
You're laying it on too thick.
-Oh, sorry.
Next time I won't improvise.
-So did you decide
on a present yet?
-Nah, I took your
advice and asked him
what he likes wearing, but
he's kind of hard to read.
-I see.
Well, sorry.
-It's fine.
But thanks for the help.
-Huh?
-Maybe I'll just
give him this, hum?
-Oh, no you won't.
We chipped in for this.
It's from all of us.
Barnaby's your partner, so you
better get him something good.
-Hmm.
BARNABY: Thanks for
doing this every year.
OLDER WOMAN (ON
MONITOR): It's nothing.
I worked for your family
for so long, dear.
Baking you a pound cake
is the least I can do.
For as long as I
know you, I promise
I shall always send you
a cake on your birthday.
-Samantha, you're the best.
[chuckles]
SAMANTHA (ON MONITOR): Barnaby?
-Oh-- uh, sorry.
-I'm sure that your parents
would send you their warmest
blessings, if only they
were still with us.
Have a wonderful birthday.
-Thanks.
[beeping]
-What do you want?
-Get over here.
We've got a bad
situation on our hands.
-Uh?
GUARD: Nothing over here.
That thing is something.
6 million bucks, huh?
Mm, what I could do
with that kind of dough.
Nothing over there.
Nothing over here, either.
Huh?
-Good evening.
-Uh?
Ah.
Ah! [screams]
-Well, did you ever pick
out a birthday present?
-Sure did.
I gave it some thought
and realized just
hanging out with me
is present enough.
-Are you kidding me?
He hates hanging out with you.
-Yeah, that's a problem.
-You should really
go buy him something.
-I would, but we're
running out of time.
-Ooh, heads up!
He's coming.
-Get into position!
Hey.
-Hey.
So what's going on?
-You're wondering why
I called you down here.
Well, it's 'cause there's
a dangerous gang of thieves
on the loose.
Are you up to catching them?
-I think I'll pass.
-Huh?
-I thought it might be more
of your incessant meddling.
That's why I only respond
to calls from headquarters.
-[grunts]
-Pickpocket!
What are you doing?
-The stupid bag is stuck!
-Would you just go?
-I'm trying!
-That guy a friend of
yours or something?
-No, no, not at all!
Hey, that guy ran
off with my bag!
Come on, help me get him.
-No thanks.
-What are you waiting for?
Ah!
-Ah!
-Uh, sorry about that.
-What is he doing?
-Hey, I'm pretty sure that
pickpocket of yours got away.
-Uh?
[sigh]
[humming]
BARNABY: There's no way
we're going to find him.
-Just have faith.
Let's see, where was it again?
-What do you mean, where was it?
Do you know where the guy's
secret hideout is or something?
-How would I know that?
It's just a feeling.
Ah, there he is now.
Hey, you!
-Mm?
-Stop right there.
So you're the thief in charge.
-How did you know that?
-How did I-- um, lucky guess?
That dummy's
improvising lines again.
-Who are you guys, anyway?
-Yes!
Now we're back on track.
-Ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha ha!
We don't just give
out our names to--
-Barnaby.
My name is Barnaby Brooks
Jr. And this is Wild Tiger.
I assume that
you've heard of us?
-You mean the heroes?
-If you're smart,
you'll surrender now.
Well, looks like you
can take it from here.
-Uh?
What do you mean?
-He's not going to
run from a superhero.
I think you can handle
this one on your own.
KOTETSU: Wait!
Don't go yet.
-Stop wasting my time.
KARINA: Freeze, tough guys!
-Oh no.
We're surrounded.
-We heard you've been calling
us scum behind our backs.
Big mistake, buddy.
-What do you mean?
We never called you scum.
-What?
-They didn't?
-Ah, great.
This is a mess.
-Are you mocking me?
Better say your prayers!
-Ah, that's right.
Save me, Bunny!
-Too late.
Die!
[gunshot]
[gasp]
-What's going on?
-That's exactly
what I want to know.
Were you seriously just about
to use me as a human shield?
-Oh. [chuckles] Never mind that.
Hey, why did he use live rounds?
-Care to explain
to me why you're
talking to the criminals?
Wait, what are those?
BOTH: (WEAKLY)
They're our weapons.
-Over here!
-Finally!
Get me out of here!
-That guy was a real criminal.
-Come on.
-I feel like I'm
missing something.
-Well, that's the
understatement of the year.
Start talking.
What is the meaning of all this?
-Well, uh, truth
is, we were throwing
you a surprise birthday party.
-Again with your meddling.
How many times do I have to tell
you that you have to stop this?
You always cause more problems
for people you try to help.
[alarm buzzes]
-Hello there, heroes.
New orders from
the Justice Bureau.
This time it's a robbery.
Get on it right away.
-Hey!
ANNOUNCER: Time for another
episode of "Hero TV."
We're live with a brand
new crime in progress.
And there they are--
it's Pauly and his gang,
criminals wanted for stealing
the Tears of Hercules!
-He's a NEXT?
AGNES (ON COMM): That's right.
He's able to transform
his body into diamonds.
-Sounds like he's tough.
What's the big
plan, Little Bunny?
-I've had enough of you.
Don't bother me.
-Huh?
Nothing good happens
when you're involved.
From now on, I'm going solo.
We're no longer a team,
as far as I'm concerned.
SAITO (ON PA): Tiger and
Barnaby, you guys ready?
-You've got that mic
turned up pretty loud.
[zhoom]
-Ah.
SAITO (ON PA): A little
something extra for you.
I heard it was
Barnaby's birthday,
so I modified his suit a little.
Tiger's, too.
-You what?
Huh?
Where is it?
What the hell?
ANNOUNCER: Incredible!
The King of Heroes himself, Sky
High, is first on the scene!
-You criminals ruined
our entire skit,
and after I worked so
hard to learn my lines!
Aah!
Sky High!
-Aah!
-Let's go!
-Huh?
ANNOUNCER: Wild
Tiger and Barnaby
have activated their powers.
This means they have five
minutes before their Hundred
Power wears off.
-Spread out!
-[grunts] Oh!
Oh!
ANNOUNCER: Sky High has
captured one of the thieves.
-You crossed the line this time.
-I'm sorry.
-The next one's ours, Bunny.
Huh?
Bunny?
-Eh!
[screams]
-My ice is a little cold,
but your crime has--
-Oh, balls, I'm late.
-Huh?
Hey!
At least let me
finish my catchphrase.
SKY HIGH: I know the feeling.
I also wanted to say my lines.
There I was, waiting
the whole time,
alone in some dingy
back alley, like a dog.
-Oh, that just sounds awful.
Why don't we make it up to you?
Take the last guy.
-Thanks, but no thanks.
I think it's best if
we let them handle it.
-Huh?
-After all, it is
Barnaby's special day.
-[grunts] Ah!
Gotcha, punk.
Come to Papa.
[grunts] Huh?
-Bye-bye.
-Hah!
Ah!
-Hey, let go of me!
-You're not getting away.
FEMALE ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Powers expire in 30 seconds.
-Damn it!
This is good.
Our powers are almost out!
-I heard her, you idiot.
And thank you for sharing
that with the suspect.
-So, your powers are about
to run out, are they?
Then I think I'll
stick around and play.
-We've got a
different idea, Shiny.
[bam]
Damn, that's hard.
[mocking giggle]
[bam]
[boom]
[mocking chuckles]
I'm made of the hardest
substance known to man.
-What are you doing?
Shut him down!
ANNOUNCER: Uh-oh.
Not even Tiger and
Bunny's Super Strength
can penetrate the
crook's diamond skin!
--[laughs] You
heroes are pathetic.
I'm the strongest person
in the whole world!
FEMALE ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Five seconds remaining.
Four, three--
-[grunts] [grunts]
MALE ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Activating Good Luck Mode.
Good Luck Mode.
Three, two, one.
BOTH: Hah!
[boom]
MALE ELECTRONIC VOICE: Tiger
and Barnaby, over and out.
[diamond cracking]
[shards tinkle on ground]
-Oh!
-We did it.
SAITO (OVER COMM):
Great job, you two!
-That add-on is amazing!
It really boosted our power!
SAITO (OVER COMM): Ah, it
doesn't affect your power
at all.
-What?
SAITO (OVER COMM): Yep.
It's purely cosmetic.
Just makes your
suits look cooler.
-That's all it does?
-Then how did we
just beat that guy?
SAITO (OVER COMM):
You worked together!
It was perfect teamwork.
That's all!
-Huh?
SAITO (OVER COMM):
I had no idea you
could smash through diamonds
when you combined your powers.
-I wouldn't exactly
call that teamwork.
-Yeah, don't get the wrong idea.
It was just a lucky--
SAITO (OVER COMM):
What are you, nuts?
You knuckleheads
were totally in sync!
You're finally becoming a team!
-Why don't you take him?
-Uh--
-It's my birthday
present to you.
-Huh?
You honestly believed me when
I said I wanted that diamond?
I can't accept stolen property.
-Not that.
What I meant was I'll
give you the arrest.
-Huh?
-After all, I know how
much you love points.
Happy birthday.
[chuckles]
-There's nothing happy about it.
-Huh?
[sirens approaching]
-I told you, I hate
it when you meddle.
-But--
-And besides, only friends
give gifts, not us, right?
-[groans]
-Is that so?
-Hey, why are you smiling?
BARNABY: I'm not smiling.
-Is it gonna stay this big?
[MUSIC - AOBOZU, "HOSHI NO
SUMIKA"]
-Well, that was a
crazy turn of events.
-Who would've thought we'd
run into a real criminal gang?
-Yeah, and we never got to
throw him our surprise party.
--[gasp] What happened
to that bunny,
the one we bought for him?
-Oh, yeah.
If I'm not mistaken--
-I swear, I'm--
I'm not a criminal!
-Then what's this weird thing?
-Uh, that's just for
a friend of mine.
-Sounds criminal to me.
-No!
Wait, come on!
-Come on, pal.
[siren]
BARNABY (VOICEOVER):
Hi, this is Barnaby,
the member of
Tiger and Bunny who
saves the best bite for last.
What?
Fire Emblem is
suspected of murder?
That mark.
Next time on "Tiger
and Bunny," fire
is a good servant
but a bad master.
See ya!