ANNOUNCER: Today, we are
in pursuit of a new target,
a homicidal Next named
Kotetsu T Kaburagi.
He is suspected of killing
68-year-old Samantha
Taylor, a resident of Sternbild.
If you see this man, contact
the authorities immediately.
KAEDE: Dad!
ANNOUNCER: Which
hero will apprehend
this vicious criminal?
-I can't believe this.
[phone beeping]
-Damn it.
Is this phone broken?
Oh, boy.
Ah, what now.
Hey, wait a minute, folks.
There's been a big mistake.
I don't know how this
happened, but I'm not
the man you think that I am.
CROWD: It's the murderer!
Aaah!
Let's get out of here!
-Hello?
Urgh.
ASSISTANT: All personal data
regarding Kotetsu T Kaburagi's
association with Hero TV has
been deleted from the network
server, as you requested, sir.
-Good work, young man.
[opening theme song]
KOTETSU: Hey, Agnes,
can you tell me
what the hell is going on?
AGNES: Who is this?
KOTETSU: It's me, Kotetsu.
Don't you know my voice?
AGNES: Kotetsu?
Kotetsu Kaburagi?
KOTETSU: Is this
is supposed to be
some sort of special
event for Hero TV?
Because nobody told
me a thing about it!
AGNES: Are you really
Kotetsu Kaburagi?
-I just told you I was.
Look I'm real close to
the studio, right now.
Give me some guidance.
What should I do?
AGNES (TO OTHERS): Kotetsu
Kaburagi is near the studio.
Get everyone out
there, and find him!
-Huh?
AGNES (TO KOTETSU):
You've got some balls,
challenging us like this.
Do you really think
you can get away
once we deploy our resources?
-Huh?
What in the world
are you talk-- Aah!
SKY HIGH: Kotetsu Kaburagi,
suspected murderer
of Samantha Taylor, you
are completely surrounded.
Do not attempt to resist.
Turn yourself in!
KOTETSU: Ah, quit showing
off for the cameras.
I didn't do anything
and you know it.
SKY HIGH: That is
not for me to judge.
A jury will decide whether
or not you're innocent.
I shall capture you and let
justice take its course.
-Did you even hear one thing
I was trying to say to you?
SKY HIGH: Sky...
High!
-What the hell is
going on around here?
TELEPHONE: The number
you have reached
is no longer in
service at this time.
Please check your number
and try again later.
Thank you.
[sigh]
-Don't worry, Sweetheart.
It's all just a big
misunderstanding.
KAEDE: I'm sure
you're right, Grandma.
-Kaede.
KAEDE: I know Dad, and he would
never do something so awful.
He's a liar, and
he can be silly,
but my dad would never
hurt anyone on purpose.
Not ever!
-You're right, Kaede.
Your father's job is
to capture criminals.
He's one the heroes.
There's a reason why he hasn't
been able to be with you.
He's been living in the
city, working closely
with the other heroes
to keep everyone safe.
I'm sorry.
I should've told you sooner.
-You're kidding!
-No, it's the truth, Dear.
I'm sure you must know who
Wild Tiger is, don't you?
Well, believe it or
not, he's your father.
DETECTIVE 1: There
was a phone call
from the fugitive,
Kotetsu Kaburagi.
He's still hiding
within the city.
Set up road blocks at
all major access points.
DETECTIVE 2: Do we have
any more information on him
besides his photograph?
DETECTIVE 1: Aside from
the fact that he's a Next,
we haven't been able
to find out anything.
KOTETSU: I should've
known they'd be here.
Well, someone's all
pumped up and ready.
-Don't even try it.
There's nowhere to run!
-Origami!
DRAGON KID: So you
finally showed up, huh.
Haa!
-Uh, wait!
-Why would we do that?
Come along quietly
You're outmatched!
-Hold on guys.
A hero like myself would
never kill anybody.
This is clearly a case
of mistaken identity.
-You've got some nerve, Mister.
A criminal has no business
calling himself a hero!
-Huh?
-Eh?
-Wait a second.
It's me.
Don't you know who I am?
-Kotetsu Kaburagi.
-Right!
-Don't move!
-Ugh You guys are
driving me crazy!
Why are you treating
me like this?
Explain right now
what's going on--
ROCK BISON: We don't explain
ourselves to criminals.
As you'll discover,
it's very simple.
Earning points by capturing
bad guys like you is our job.
-You idiot, I'm
your best friend.
ROCK BISON: Best friend?
What kind of nonsense are
you talking, you low-life?
-Low-life?
All right, you've crossed
the line, you bastard!
-What do you know?
This guy's a power-type Next.
-Hold it!
ANNOUNCER: The murderer
showed up at his home moments
ago, but has
disappeared once again.
According to reports, the
suspect, Kotetsu Kaburagi,
may actually be a
power-type Next.
MAVERICK: How are
you feeling, Barnaby?
-Sorry for missing so
much work lately, sir.
But I'm feeling fine, now.
I'll head out to make
the arrest immediately.
The timing couldn't
be more perfect.
New versions of the hero suits
have been in development,
and I've received
word from the lab
that yours has just
been completed.
-You mean?
MAVERICK: That's right.
We have new suits for
both you and Tiger.
Everything is all set.
Go get them, my boy.
KOTETSU: Ugh.
That really hurt.
What a jerk.
That cow is as hard as a rock.
[shivering]
She's going to be a pain
in the ass, I know it.
Damn it.
I'm running around here
like some kind of sewer rat.
I'm Wild Tiger, for
crying out loud.
KAEDE: My dad is Wild Tiger?
MURAMASA: I'm not all that
worried about Kotetsu.
I'm sure it's just some
misunderstanding that'll
get cleared up.
Anyway, how's Kaede?
ANJU: She's taking it quite
well, all things considered.
She seems to be
a lot more mature
that we gave her credit for.
MURAMASA: I see.
Well, that's good.
ANJU: Kaede?
-Why don't you give up.
This is silly.
Do you really think you
can run away from me?
-I don't have much choice.
I wouldn't have to run
if you'd quit chasing me!
BLUE ROSE: Playtime's
over, loser.
There's no way for you
to escape, you murderer.
-I told you before, and
I'll tell you again,
I didn't kill anyone.
How many times do
I have to say it?
-There happens to be proof.
Really, it would be best
if you admitted your crime,
so we can wrap this up.
-Come on.
What the heck
happened to you guys?
Why don't any of
you recognize me?
All right, maybe this'll
help jog your memory.
Remember that time
when you weren't
sure about how your
career was going?
How I gave you a tip
at the bar because I
thought you were a good singer?
BLUE ROSE: What are
you talking about?
KOTETSU: Huh?
-Wild Tiger was the one
who gave me that tip.
How do you know so much about
my private life, anyway?
-How do I know?
Because I'm Wild Tiger!
How else would I
know that stuff?
-Come on.
Stop joking around.
KOTETSU: Huh?
-As you're probably
aware, nobody
knows Wild Tiger's
true identity.
It's pretty bold of
you to claim to be him,
just because we don't know
his real face or name.
-This is unbelievable.
What are you--
BLUE ROSE: Freeze right there!
I'm warning you,
I'll show no mercy
if you keep spouting
this nonsense.
KOTETSU: You're the one
who's spouting nonsense.
You're crazy.
And I suppose you've forgotten
about the time I gave you
that towel, as well.
How could you forget that?
At a rehearsal I spilled coffee
on your towel and ruined it.
And then, I gave you a really
cool towel to replace it.
Will you snap out of it?
I really am Wild Tiger.
Please believe me.
Wait, do remember now?
Wah!
Oh, man.
Who is it this time?
It's Wild Tiger?
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and
gentlemen, welcome back.
We are focusing on
Wild Tiger, who's
made a wild entrance
in his new suit.
Looks like this might be the
end of the line for the suspect.
-You have got to be kidding.
The real Wild Tiger is me.
So who the hell are you?
Are you serious?
In that case, see you.
Who the hell are you?
And that suit,
where'd you get that?
FIRE EMBLEM: Aww.
You already found him.
It's so frustrating.
You always steal the
show, little Tiger.
-Wait a minute.
Who exactly are you talking to?
-What do you mean?
You really don't know
who Wild Tiger is?
-Yeah, I'm Wild Tiger!
BLUE ROSE: You can
drop the act, now.
We all know it's a lie.
-What's happened to you guys?
Aren't we friends?
Colleagues who fought
alongside each other?
You have to believe me!
This is some kind of nightmare.
You've really
forgotten who I am.
FIRE EMBLEM: What is this
creepy old man talking about?
Take this nutcase
away and lock him up.
LUNATIC: Is this how it's
going to end for you?
KOTETSU: Lunatic?
Stop!
Let me explain.
I'm not the murderer.
-You need to reflect
carefully upon your actions.
-Why are you helping me?
LUNATIC: Passing judgment on
those who are truly sinful
is my idea of justice.
Therefore allowing
you to be captured
by the hands of
false justice would
be something that goes
against my beliefs.
Kotetsu Kaburagi,
is this how you're
going to let your
idea of justice end?
FIRE EMBLEM: What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Do you plan on
defending that murderer?
LUNATIC: I defend no one.
Nor do I follow your
code of justice.
I obey the voice of Thanatos.
ANNOUNCER: Kotetsu T
Kaburagi, the prime suspect
in this case--
-I don't understand.
Why did he help me?
HOBO: Hey.
This is my spot.
I'm trying to sleep.
Why don't you find
your own place.
-Yeah, like you pay rent.
-Bunny will find that bad guy.
HOBO: Maybe not, but
I was here before you.
As far as I'm concerned,
you're trespassing.
So go on.
Get out of here.
ANNOUNCER: We have a
scoop for you, folks.
Our cameras have caught up
with Hero TV's number one
star, Barnaby Brooks
Jr., who was reported
to be resting away from home.
KOTETSU: Bunny!
I'm so glad he's safe.
ANNOUNCER: This solves
one mystery for us.
During his time away,
it appears that Barnaby
was staying at the vacation
home of Mr. Albert Maverick.
-Please rest assured, everyone.
The criminal who is
terrorizing this city
will be brought to justice.
He will be captured
by Barnaby himself,
who is thirsting for vengeance.
The victim, Ms. Samantha
Taylor, was more than a friend
of Mr. Brooks.
She worked for his parents
for many years and, in fact,
helped raise him.
He though of her as family.
REPORTER: Over here, over here.
Just one question, sir.
-Mister Maverick was with Bunny?
All this time?
-Did anything unusual happen?
ASSISTANT: Ms. Samantha
Taylor is here,
and she has a photograph
she'd like to show you.
KOTETSU: Well that's weird.
-You need to reflect
carefully upon your actions.
-I understand it now.
-Hey, man.
You're that guy.
[screams]
-Hey!
Ben, it's Kotetsu.
-Get in.
-Good grief.
I knew I could
still count on you.
At this point I had no
one else to rely on.
I figured if I stayed in the
area, you'd pass by eventually.
Where are you going?
Hang on.
Ben, don't tell me you
forgot who I am, too.
BEN: Shut up, and stay put.
-Hey, you're not taking
me to the police, are you?
I'm telling you, I
didn't do anything.
I'm not a murderer!
Please, stop the car.
You've got to believe me, Ben.
I was set up!
BEN: Calm down, Kotetsu.
Really?
You call yourself a hero?
I don't know what
happened here, but I'm
willing to give you the
benefit of the doubt.
It's cold but at least
it'll fill you up.
When I heard you
were on the run,
I figured you might be hungry,
so I came out looking for you.
I can't believe you'd
thought I'd forgotten you.
-Sorry about that.
-BEN: I'd never stop
believing in you,
no matter what they say.
Hey, I'm one of
your biggest fans.
-Is this what I think?
-Oh yeah.
Brings back memories, huh?
This suit is filled
with the good old times
we spent together, my friend.
I always keep it with me.
-Ah, that's great.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
What happened?
How come it's all wrinkled?
-Hey, I'm a cab
driver, not your maid.
[laughing]
-You know, I have to say,
I was pretty shocked.
On TV they're talking about
you like you are the murderer.
No if, ands, or buts
-Somebody made
sure I was framed.
KAEDE: This is where Dad works.
Sorry grandma.
MAVERICK: Excuse me,
young lady, are you lost?
-No.
I just-- I came all the way
here so I could meet Barnaby.
-Barnaby you say.
-Yes.
You see I have a
problem, and I was
hoping it he be
able to help me out.
MAVERICK: I see.
You're one of Barnaby's
biggest fans, aren't you?
Well, thank you for
coming all this way.
Unfortunately, he's
pretty busy right now.
I'm afraid he won't
be able to help you
with your problem at the moment.
Sorry, my dear.
BEN: I see.
So this whole mess you're
in is Maverick's doing, huh?
Well, I guess that makes sense.
-He's even gone through the
trouble of finding someone
to go out and pretend to be me.
Who is that guy, anyway.
-I'll tell you.
You sure know how
to make enemies
with the wrong people, Kotetsu.
-Yeah, it seems like it's
always happening to me.
You think that Barnaby's
being influenced by this guy,
as well?
-Yeah.
I'm guessing he's probably not
going to remember me, either.
If I'm right, He'll be
just like everyone else.
BEN: And you figure Maverick
is the reason they've
forgotten about you?
KOTETSU: Well, I
can't be sure, Ben.
I don't know if
it's him, or a Next.
I'll tell you this, though.
A Next power is definitely
at the root of this.
-So what's going to
be your next move?
KOTETSU: The only thing I can
think to do at the moment,
is to try and make them remember
that I'm the real Wild Tiger.
Yeah, but how?
-Don't worry.
I have a plan.
-I'm listening.
-I know it'll work now,
thanks to you, Ben.
-What's going on?
-Not sure.
A man who resembles
Kotetsu Kaburagi
has appeared up on the
roof of Apollo Media.
-Did you contact him?
-Actually, he called us.
He says he's the
real Wild Tiger,
and he wants us to assemble all
the heroes at that location.
-What, are you kidding me?
What the hell's going on?
-Well, looks like
most of you are here.
All right.
It's time to let out a...
Wild Roar.
[ending theme music]
-Why do you suppose he's
wearing that costume?
KAEDE: Dad!
MAVERICK: That fool.
What's he planning to do?
KOTETSU: Hi.
I'm Kotetsu, the member
of Tiger and Bunny
who hits the want ads first
when he reads the newspaper.
All right, come
at me all at once!
Kaede, why are you here?
No!
Next time on Tiger and Bunny,
Bad Luck Often-- Often-- damn.