[music playing]
MAN 1: Sky High kinda
sucks lately, huh?
MAN 2: Yeah, he's
lost his touch.
-Totally.
These days, it's all
about Tiger and Barnaby.
[chuckling]
ANNOUNCER: Look at him soar!
The former King of Heroes and
current wind wizard, Sky High!
-If you don't get
your head straight,
it's only a matter
of time before you
fall into third place.
-Yes, sir.
[music - novels, "missing link"]
[grunting]
-Ooh, somebody's getting ripped.
KARINA: What's gotten into him?
[grunting]
-I don't even want to know.
And look at how
quiet that one is.
-OK, Kotetsu, let's head out.
-Almost done, Bunny.
-Are you doing another
one of those workouts?
At this rate, you won't
last the whole day.
-Don't worry about me, pal.
I been feeling like
a million bucks.
BARNABY: Well, hurry
up and get changed.
You're gonna make us
late for our interviews.
KOTETSU: You got it.
Let's rock.
[sigh]
-Those two are so busy lately.
Aren't they, Sky High?
[sigh]
-Wow, I've never seen
him so depressed.
-Can you blame him?
-Huh?
ANTONIO: Well, he's no
longer in first place.
That's gotta be hitting
him pretty hard.
ANNOUNCER: No criminal
can beat them!
They're the invincible
Tiger and Barnaby.
But against tough stains,
they use a secret weapon
to deliver a clean knockout.
Meet the new stain-fighting
hero, Super Dish!
Available now.
[sigh]
[bark]
-John!
Come back!
[bark]
[barking]
Hey, cut it out, John.
Uh, sorry about that, ma'am.
-I am fine.
-Oh, good.
Uh, do you mind if I join you?
-No.
-He's a pretty good
dog most of the time.
-All right.
-Uh-- sure is a
beautiful evening.
Hey, um, would, would
you like an apple?
-I am sorry.
-Hold on, are you a NEXT too?
-I don't know.
-I see.
Maybe your powers are
just new to you still.
It's OK.
Learning how to control them
will be pretty tough at first,
but you'll catch on.
I remember when my
powers first awakened.
It was summer.
I was 18.
[shutter click]
FEMALE INTERVIEWER:
So, Barnaby, when
did you first get your
abilities as a next?
-I must have had them as
early as two years old.
They tell me I gave my
mother a lot of headaches
because whenever
she put me down,
I'd start crying and
activate my powers.
-You must have been
one cute superbaby.
Don't you think so, Mr. Tiger?
-I agree.
Why the hell did we have to
do that interview half naked?
-Well, to save time, I had to
schedule the swimsuit photo
session and the
interview simultaneously.
-But we never wanted
this kind of attention.
Tell him, Bunny.
You hate this stuff, right?
-Actually, I don't
mind it at all.
-Huh?
-In fact, I'm
starting to have fun.
-You are?
Oh.
-My whole life used
to be about revenge,
but now everything feels so
different, like a new day.
-This is fascinating,
but we're running late.
You two mind finishing
this in the car?
-More publicity?
BARNABY: Didn't you even
look at the schedule?
LLOYDS: Next, there's an
appearance on a variety show.
Then you're doing guest voices
for a New Year's anime special.
-Now hold on a second!
Is this supposed to be
some kind of circus?
We're heroes!
-Don't be so dramatic.
It's not like you're being
called into action right now.
-Yeah, I guess.
-Wow, look who it is.
-Huh?
Sky High?
What's he doing out there?
NATHAN: Oh, don't tell
me you didn't know.
-(IN UNISON) What?
-Our hunky flyboy
likes to moonlight.
Ever since he became a hero,
he patrols the city at night.
-Wow, he's dedicated.
JACKSON: Thank you
sir, have a good one.
KOTETSU (ON RADIO):
Oh yeah, it's true.
Lately, I've been
feeling than ever.
-Huh?
-The other day, I went
flying like, "Whoosh!"
Then I was all like, "Boom!"
And then gave it a "Blammo!"
And then I went over to the--
BARNABY (ON RADIO):
Hey, hey, hey.
Nobody can see
what you're doing.
We're on the radio, remember?
KOTETSU (ON RADIO): Oh, yeah.
Uh, well, anyway-- I had
way more power than usual.
MAN: Hey!
Get out of the road!
KOTETSU (ON RADIO):
It's awesome.
Well, I guess you could say
Wild Tiger is still evolving.
FEMALE HOST: Well, I am
very excited for you.
KOTETSU (ON RADIO):
(FLIRTING) Well, I'm
very pleased that I
could get you so excited.
[chuckling]
-Ugh!
What an idiot!
-Man, it's like those guys
are on every single channel.
[sigh]
-There, there.
Don't beat yourself up.
You can still make a
comeback and be number one.
-What?
No.
I'm actually more worried
about my love life.
[gasps]
-(IN UNISON) What?
-Sky High, you're in love?
-Ooh.
Must be something in the air.
-Is that why you've been
acting so depressed?
-She's got a point.
Why didn't you tell us?
When do we get to meet her?
KEITH: Uh, she's--
-When did you meet?
KEITH: Maybe three days ago.
-Did you tell her you like her?
-No, not yet.
-You haven't?
Oh, you're such a prude.
Fine then.
We're gonna give you all the
love advice you'll ever need.
-(IN UNISON) Mm-hmm.
-OK.
I'm all yours.
[grunt]
Here goes.
-Start with a smile.
No girl can resist a winning
smile from a hot hunk.
-Hey.
How you doin'?
-Hi.
-Compliment her.
Girls like it if you
tell them they look nice.
-That's a nice hairband.
It's an interesting shade
of red, my favorite color.
Is it your favorite as well?
-It's not.
-OK.
-Girls need physical contact.
Just take her hand and
she'll be yours forever.
[gulp]
[belch]
-Well, see ya.
-Right here, please.
Can you face my camera?
-Over here, too.
Many of my readers
look up to you,
but who is the person
you admire most?
-Well, I'd have
to say Mr. Legend.
-Why?
KOTETSU: 'Cause he's
so rad and so awesome.
-(IN UNISON) Mm.
-And you, Mr. Barnaby?
Same question.
-I suppose that
would be my parents.
-Go on.
-Well, my mom and my
dad devoted their lives
to robotics research.
They had one dream--
to create a robot that
could protect people and bring
peace to the entire world.
They were partners at
work and partners at home.
I may wear a suit
and fight crime,
but my parents are my heroes.
BOY INTERVIEWER:
What a great answer.
GIRL INTERVIEWER: So sincere.
LLOYDS: Oh, I learned
something new today, Barnaby.
So, your parents really
worked in robotics?
-Yeah.
I have fond memories of them
bringing me along to their lab.
They always looked so cool
when they were at work.
I loved them both so much.
-I wish Kaede would feel
the same way about her dad.
-I'm sure she loves you too.
-Eh, I don't know.
Whenever I call her, all she
does is complain about me,
harping about how my stories
are boring or my jokes are dumb
or my beard is lame.
-She's right.
-Gee, thanks a lot, pal.
Huh?
Hey, check it out.
BARNABY: Hero TV?
NEWSCASTER: We are live
with a suspect on the run
and he's got hostages.
And who's that in pursuit?
It's Sky High!
Can he break out of his slump
and make an arrest today?
-Hey, why the hell weren't
we called in on this?
-Is the comm broken?
LLOYDS: No.
I told them not to bother you.
-(IN UNISON) Huh?
-You two have your hands full
with all these interviews.
Your time is just too valuable.
I thought all the second
tier heroes could handle--
KOTETSU: Are you
out of your mind?
-Eh?
-Our job isn't to smile
for your dumb cameras!
We're heroes, dammit,
and heroes are
supposed to be out there
saving people's lives.
-Kotetsu, take it easy.
NEWSCASTER: She did it!
Dragon Kid has
apprehended the criminal!
-Ha!
NEWSCASTER: And Origami
Cyclone racks up some points
for rescuing the hostages.
The young heroes are
really shining this season.
Meanwhile, Sky High suffered
a sudden crash right
at the end of the chase.
He'll finish scoreless again.
Sadly, his slump continues.
ANNOUNCER: They're the
invincible Tiger and Barnaby.
-I, uh-- I didn't expect
to find you here so late.
-Yes.
-Would you mind if I get
some things off my chest?
-No.
-You see, I used to be the
best at my job until recently.
Now, nothing seems to click.
It's not dropping in
rank that bothers me,
it's just-- everyone has
these expectations of me
and I don't want to
let them all down.
I failed them once, and
I learned the hard way
what it feels like
to be powerless.
And now, when it's time
to work, I-- freeze up.
I'm completely helpless.
I mean, the way things
have been going lately,
I'd be better off quitting.
WOMAN: Why?
-Because I'm worried that-- that
everyone will lose faith in me.
WOMAN: Why?
-Because I-- I can't--
-But why?
-You're forcing me to confront
a deeper truth, aren't you?
It's true.
I've just been
hiding behind excuses
and not doing anything to
change things for myself.
Thank you.
I-- it's late.
Let me walk you home.
-I am fine.
-Uh-- yeah.
Sorry for unloading like that.
I'll, uh, see you tomorrow.
Good night.
-Ah, Cis.
There you are.
I was worried about you.
-I am sorry.
-Here goes nothing.
[sigh]
-I can't believe we wasted
the whole friggin' day.
BARNABY: Giving interviews is
an important part of the job.
-But if all we do is talk,
we're gonna get out of shape.
-You know, maybe you
should stop whining
and try to follow
Sky High's example.
-Huh?
-He never complained
when he was on top.
And if you think about it, he
worked twice as hard as we did.
-Yeah, I know.
But still-- Whoa!
What the hell?
-Cis!
Stop!
[gasp]
-Are you all right, sir?
-Aren't you--
-She looks like a
power-type NEXT.
KOTETSU: That's
an understatement.
-Heroes.
Heroes.
-Yes!
It's about time I get to
do some real work today.
Hey, lady!
Waa!
[grunt]
-Heroes.
-Guess talking isn't an option.
-Plan B. What?
Whoa!
-She's powerful.
-What's wrong with her?
This is crazy!
-Perfect.
She's perfect.
-Yes.
No.
I am sorry.
I don't know.
I am fine.
Yes.
KOTETSU: That chick isn't human.
BARNABY: I had no idea such
an advanced android could even
exist.
-No, it couldn't until now.
I'm the one who brought
her into existence.
-You created her?
MAN: Yes, to show the
world that androids
have infinite capabilities,
that they could easily
surpass humans and soon could
even surpassed the NEXT.
My whole life, I've
worked to create
an all-powerful
cybernetic being,
one that will rise above us all.
I poured all of my data
into one prototype, Cis.
She is perfect.
Cis is my masterpiece.
-Hero.
-Knock it off!
And stop saying
"Heroes" already.
BARNABY: What do you want?
Why did you program
her to kill heroes?
MAN: No, she's not
programmed to kill you.
This is all just a
peculiar malfunction.
Her memory is loaded full of
data on every single hero.
After all, I wanted her
to become the strongest
being in the world, so I
gave her powerful examples
to draw from.
But then, a few days ago,
while transporting her,
our vehicle was
struck by lightning.
In the commotion that followed,
Cis jumped out of the car
and fled.
And by the time I was
able to track her down,
her system appeared
to be damaged
by the electrical shock.
Now, it seems whenever she sees
anything related to heroes,
she shifts into battle mode.
And that's what we
are witnessing here.
But this is far better
than I could have imagined.
I didn't think she could beat
your heroes this quickly.
And none of this would
have been possible
without your parents' research.
You still don't
recognize me, young man?
-You're--
-The name's Rotwang.
I worked for your mom and dad.
And yes, Cis is based
on their research.
It was passed on to me and
I took it to the next level.
They would have been so pleased.
-The hell they would!
My mother and father wanted
to invent a machine that
could save people's lives,
not some mindless weapon
of mass destruction
like that thing.
ROTWANG: Young man, I put
their theories into practice.
As scientists, that's exactly
what would have they wanted!
[scream]
CIS: I am sorry.
I don't know.
I am fine.
ROTWANG: Unfortunately,
Cis will continue
to destroy the city
unless she is shut down.
You see, Sternbild is plastered
with the faces of heroes.
BARNABY: Dammit.
KOTETSU: That-- really hurt.
It's payback time!
Hey, quit moving!
Whoa.
What the-- waa!
-Hold it!
-Aw, crap.
I, I thought I activated
my power when Bunny did.
How come his is still going?
-Dammit.
She can fly too?
KEITH: Hold it right there!
-Huh?
Sky High?
-I can handle this one.
What kind of robot is this?
[grunt]
Oh!
Gah!
[grunt]
[growling]
Yaa!
I won't let you endanger
the people of this city!
-In order to stop her, he's
going to have to destroy her.
-It's over!
Sky high!
[gasp]
-No.
-I did it.
I did it.
-Well, what a
difference a day makes.
KARINA: Yeah, glad he's
back to his old self.
Wish I could say the
same for that one.
NATHAN: Huh, I wonder
what's eating him?
-Do you think
it'll happen again?
-Huh?
-Another android attack like
the one we had last night?
-Hey, Bunny, are you all right?
-Well, I am still
shocked that my parents'
work was manipulated
like it was.
But at the same
time, I can't presume
to know whether they
would have objected
to Rotwang's ultimate goals.
If only they were still
alive, I could ask them.
KEITH: Buck up, you two.
Come on, guys.
Heroes aren't supposed
to be all depressed.
We've got to set an
example for the citizens.
-Yeah, you're right.
-For the good of the city, let's
try to keep our spirits high.
-All right.
-Now I must be off.
-Hey, where you going, sweetie?
KEITH: That girl from the park.
I have to thank her.
-Oh?
-Huh?
KARINA: You mean the one
you've got a crush on?
NATHAN: Oh!
I knew you could do it!
Oh, go get her, stud.
Rawr.
[music - tamaki, "mind game"]
-Hey.
-Hey, hey.
Long time, no see, buddy.
I was kind of surprised to
hear from you like this.
-There's something--
-One coffee, please.
- --I need to ask you, Kotetsu.
-Huh?
Yeah?
-Have you been feeling
different lately?
-Me?
No, not really.
Oh-- well, the
other day, my powers
did you get this sudden boost,
but, uh, that's about it.
-Right.
And did your Hundred Power
end before the five minute
limit was up?
-Huh?
-Stay calm and listen up.
Kotetsu, I get the feeling
that your NEXT powers
might be starting to fade.
-They're what?
JACKSON: It's very rare,
but some NEXTs gradually
lose their abilities over time.
And just before they disappear,
they become even stronger,
like a candle
before it goes out.
[gasp]
WOMAN: Here you go, sir.
KOTETSU: I'm Kotetsu, the
member of Tiger and Bunny
who puts on his left sock first.
So, you're back again, Lunatic.
Tell me who you are!
Wait, is he beating me?
Next time on "Tiger and Bunny,"
"Proof Lies at the Bottom
of a Well."
Can I do that again?