[music playing]
[grunt]
-Dad, please, stop it!
[groan]
MOTHER: Stop!
-Get away from her!
-Oh!
Oh my god!
[groaning]
ANNOUNCER: With
5,930 points, Barnaby
is dominating the ranks.
Currently in hot pursuit
of a suspect wanted
for robbery and
murder, Barnaby is
poised to make history tonight.
Can Legend's longstanding
record finally be
shattered by this
newly-crowned King of Heroes?
[music - novels, "missing link"]
-Heh heh.
-Damn Grasshopper.
Haa!
Huh?
[chuckling]
[gasp]
ANNOUNCER: Uh oh!
Lunatic has appeared once
again, ladies and gentlemen.
[gasps]
-All right.
-Ratings'll be through the roof.
-Repent, sinner.
Your judgment is at hand.
-No, please.
I'm begging you!
-Oh no you don't!
Almost out of time.
Hey, Bunny, I'll
lure this creep away.
You take care of
the Grasshopper.
-On it.
-Oh ho ho-- whoa!
ANNOUNCER: Lunatic is a
force to be reckoned with,
but if anyone can take him
on, it's Tiger and Barnaby!
-The stage is all
yours, Lunatic.
Give the people a show.
-What a joke.
ANNOUNCER: Wait a minute.
Is Lunatic bowing out?
-You're kidding me.
Is that it?
He's going to kill
the whole segment.
ANNOUNCER: And the
moment has finally
arrived-- Barnaby has scored the
most points in a single quarter
season.
Legend's record has been broken.
-Well, guess this'll do.
[chuckling]
-Thanks for saving my
skin back here, hero.
-That's enough out of you.
Come on.
[groan]
GRASSHOPPER: Aw.
-Ladies and gentlemen,
here to deliver
a congratulatory
speech, I present
to you Mr. Albert Maverick.
[applause]
-Well, what can I say?
I tip my hat to you, Barnaby.
Well done.
As we all know, Mr. Legend
held on to the top spot
for years, right up
until the day he died.
An entire generation has
been inspired by his legacy.
He truly was a hero
amongst heroes.
But today, we've witnessed
the birth of a new legend--
a young hero for a new age.
I'm sure it won't
be long before you
set a record for the season.
I can only hope that such
talent and grace will inspire
every hero to follow
your shining example.
[applause]
-Hmm.
BARNABY: What's the matter?
The room getting
too stuffy for you?
-Hm?
What about your party?
-It's not going anywhere.
Thanks, by the way.
-Huh?
-You let me make that
arrest tonight, didn't you?
-Uh-- heh heh.
I wasn't about to
ruin your moment.
-Well, I couldn't have done
this without your help, Kotetsu.
-Ah, come on.
That's not true.
And anyway, I'm happy for you.
So is Mr. Maverick,
by the looks of him.
You gotta love that guy.
He's like the patron
saint of heroes.
-Yeah.
He's been like a father to me
for as long as I can remember.
-What do you mean?
-Well, Mr. Maverick and my
parents were very good friends.
He would look after
me whenever they
were tied up with
their research.
He was always there for
me, whenever I needed him--
even on that fateful
Christmas Eve, 21 years ago.
-Thank you so much,
Uncle Maverick.
I'll see you real soon, OK?
BARNABY: Moments later,
my parents were killed.
[gunshot]
-It's time to go.
It's all right, you
won't ever be alone, son.
BARNABY: After that,
I was an orphan,
so Mr. Maverick took me in.
-Starting today, this is
going to be your home.
-He raised me like
I was his own son.
-Oh.
-Even when I was
at boarding school,
he was always
looking out for me.
-This bright young man has just
won the approval of the bureau,
so you'll all be seeing
a lot more of him.
Please welcome the city
of Sternbild's newest
hero, Barnaby Brooks, Junior.
BARNABY: And he knew
I was determined
to find my parents'
killer, so he encouraged
me to become a hero, then he
pulled all the right strings.
Without Mr. Maverick, I
wouldn't be here today.
-That's a hell of a story.
-Until now, my only goal in life
has been to avenge my parents.
But after all this time,
I finally have a new one.
-Huh?
-I want the hero
business Maverick
built to be bigger
and better than ever.
I'm going to make
it happen to show
my gratitude for everything
he's done for me over the years.
I guess that you could
say it's my dream.
[chuckling]
-Chasing the dream, huh?
-And what about
yourself, Kotetsu?
-Huh?
-You must have a dream too?
-Uh--
[gasp]
You know, I'm glad you asked,
'cause I do-- a big one.
I want my kid to think
her old man is cool.
-But that's so simple.
-Hey!
What exactly is it you're
trying to say, huh?
-Just that there's a difference
between having a dream
and sentimental pining.
-Aw, shut it.
I'm not gonna judge
myself by your standards.
As far as I'm concerned,
it's an awesome dream.
-I hope you're able to
get your wish someday.
-Uh, I don't think that'll
be happening anytime soon.
[sigh]
-It's very rare, but
some NEXT gradually
lose their abilities over time.
-Mm.
[sigh]
Hm.
NARRATOR (ON TV): Mr. Legend
has gone and set another record,
once again living
up to his name.
-Benoit Depardieu.
He has assaulted and murdered
nine women in the past two
years.
Due to the fact that
all of Benoit's targets
have been women, he has aptly
been dubbed the Lady Killer.
-Real charmer, huh?
And you mentioned it
was a civilian who
spotted him and
tipped off the police.
YURI: That's right.
We're currently
following up on the lead.
-Time is of the essence here.
We need to have the heroes deal
with this in proper fashion
before Lunatic kills him.
-Yes.
WOMAN 1: What?
You're the Lady Killer?
WOMAN 2: Oh, he's just joking.
[chuckling]
-Of course I'm joking.
Say, uh--
WOMAN 1: Whoa!
-Either of you ladies
up for a little fun?
[giggling]
-Trying to buy yourself a woman?
You're such a bad boy.
-Yeah, but you like
bad boys, don't you?
[groaning]
[grunting]
[scream]
[punching]
[groan]
[grunt]
[scream]
[punching]
-Don't you look at me like that.
I know what you're thinking,
that I'm some useless,
broke down old loser, huh?
[grunt]
-Dad, please stop it!
[groan]
[grunt]
[scream]
Get away from her!
[groaning]
-Oh!
Oh my god!
[groaning]
-You little shit!
Heh.
Huh?
[growling]
[screaming]
[grunt]
[panting]
MOTHER: How is it?
Is it good?
A little bland, you say?
Yes, of course.
Ah, Yuri, my dear.
Would you pass me the vinegar?
I can't quite reach it.
[chuckling]
Don't mind Yuri, dear,
he's just rebelling a bit.
You know, boys will be boys.
Oh--
[grunt]
YURI: Don't make me
repeat myself, mom.
Dad has been dead for years.
-And it is all because of you!
He was just going
through some hard times.
He would have
eventually gone back
to being the father
he once used to be.
But you!
It's all your fault!
You!
Why are you giving me that look?
Are you going to kill me too?
You're horrible!
[scream]
[grunt]
[phone ringing]
JACKSON: Over here.
-Ah.
-Hey.
-Funny to see you on
this side of town.
Heh heh.
Uh, hey, I'll have
a Legends Cola.
So, what'd you want
to talk to me about?
-Brace yourself.
I went ahead and
did some digging
to see what I could uncover
about NEXT that might have lost
their powers and I came
across something really big.
-What is it?
-Well, I hate to tell you
this, but as it turns out,
Legend also suffered a
decline in his powers.
-Say what?
-Uh.
-(HUSHED) Hey, come on.
Keep it down.
-Uh-- yeah, sorry.
Uh-- oh!
Hey, Legends Cola.
Thanks.
There's just no way
that can be true.
Do you have any proof?
-I recently spoke
with a guy that
was a hero during
Legend's time and he
had no reason to lie to me.
-That's crazy.
Legend set a record that no
one could touch for years, Ben.
A hero like that wouldn't be--
-Trust me, I know how you feel.
When I first found
out, I certainly
didn't want to
believe it either.
Apparently, when his
power started to go,
they began staging the
program on a regular basis.
They'd let the other heroes
do the work rounding up
the criminals and then
give to the actual credit
for making the arrest.
-Are you serious?
-Not only that, they
even went as far
as erasing any arrest records
that made him look bad.
-So that's why there
were no records on Jake.
-With his powers declining,
I guess he had no choice.
Otherwise, it would have
been impossible to remain
at the top.
I'm told that Legend
was torn up about it.
They say he drowned
himself in alcohol.
So, how are you holding up?
You notice any decline
in your powers?
-Yeah, sort of.
-I see.
Look, let me give
you some advice.
You should start thinking
about what to do with your life
before you end up like Legend.
-I don't want to
quit being a hero.
-Hey, come on.
I don't want you
to quit, either.
But you and I both
know you can't
continue this work forever.
Listen, I'm saying
this for your own good.
-I'm not done yet!
[sigh]
-That makes you a hero too.
[chuckling]
-Yuri, if you ever see people
doing wrong in this world,
you mustn't turn a blind eye.
You have to be strong someday
so you can punish evil.
-OK.
-You'll be a chip off
the old block, son.
[gasp]
Why?
Why are my powers slipping away?
-It's going to be
all right, dear.
You've done more than
enough for this city.
-Shut up!
You don't understand!
People are expecting
me to do this.
I can't let it end like this.
What do you know about my
pain, what I go through?
-I can't turn a
blind eye anymore.
I have to be strong,
no matter what.
-You again.
How long are you going
to torment me, father?
-Do you still honestly
believe that striking me down
was the right thing to do?
-Yes, and I continue to
bring evil to justice
every single day.
-Hmph.
WOMAN: Someone help me!
-Huh?
-Somebody, please!
[grunt]
-Now then, time for your
spanking, sweetheart.
-Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
-Eh?
-Please help me.
-And who might you be?
-Tiger, I want you
on the scene, pronto.
KOTETSU: Sorry,
little busy right now.
-Excuse me?
-You're one of them heroes, eh?
-So what if I am?
[chuckling]
[screaming]
[growl]
Uh.
-Hm?
-Uh, hey, folks.
Sorry to interrupt, heh heh.
-The time for your
judgment has arrived.
[sigh]
-Now you didn't
really think you'd
escape from a hero
of justice, did you?
-Ah!
[groan]
-Sorry, buddy.
You're gonna have to
do better than that.
Huh?
-What do you know?
Looks like I'm doing
better already, eh?
[screaming]
[chuckling]
Pathetic.
Don't they have any standards?
How did a weakling like you
become a hero of justice?
[grunt]
You ought to quit
the hero business.
You can't even stop
a normal human.
ANNOUNCER: Barnaby
has successfully
arrested the terrorists and
rescued countless civilians.
-We heroes fight for justice
and the hard-working people
of Sternbild.
[cheering]
-So, how would you
like a little spanking?
-Sounds like fun.
Do I look like I've been bad?
[chuckling]
DANCER: Oh!
Uh--
-Eh?
-Oh!
[screaming]
-What the hell is that?
-Repent, sinner.
Your judgment is at hand.
-You one of those heroes too?
All right, already, I surrender.
You happy?
Just kidding.
Yaa!
Eh, sorry about that.
G-guess my hands
must have slipped.
-The voice of Thanatos
shall release you
from your dark
curse and send you
down the path of
atonement and rebirth.
-Eh, well, I guess
the jig is up.
I know when I'm beat.
All right, pal, I'll
come along quietly.
You happy?
What, are you deaf?
I said I surrender.
Are you out of your mind?
This isn't what the heroes
of justice as supposed to do.
-You made two mistakes,
unfortunately.
First, I'm not a hero.
Second, this is my
idea of justice.
[music - tamaki, "mind game"]
NEWSCASTER: There's a chance
of possible thunderstorms
in the afternoon, so
please take precautions
when you are out and about.
We've just received breaking
news-- serial killer Benoit
Depardieu, also know
as the Lady Killer,
was murdered last night.
Judging from the
scene of the crime
and according to
eyewitness accounts,
he was killed by Lunatic.
At this point, it's
unclear how the heroes
will handle this turn of events.
-You should start thinking
about what to do with your life.
-You ought to quit
the hero business.
You can't even stop
a normal human.
BARNABY: Hi, I'm Barnaby,
the member of Tiger and Bunny
who goes to the
hairstylist twice a month.
Kotetsu went to
visit his family?
Well, I guess he
could use a break.
I hope you get some
good rest, old man.
Next time on "Tiger and Bunny,"
"Blood is Thicker than Water."
See ya.