[music playing]
-Hey, what's wrong?
You're sweating like a pig.
[grunting]
Hi.
[yelp]
[chuckling]
[grunt]
Heroes aren't supposed
to run away, right?
[chuckling]
[MUSIC - UNISON SQUARE GARDEN,
"ORION WO NAZORU"]
AGNES: Point 19 of North Bronx.
Thanks to Origami
Cyclone's undercover work,
we've pinpointed Jake's
current location.
-Mm.
-Ah.
Heroes, you've done great work.
I knew the people of
Sternbild could count on you.
-A ninja star?
Guess that goes with
your hero costume.
How cute.
[grunting]
(HUMMING) Hmm hm hmm, hmm hah.
Bang.
PAO-LIN: So we'll launch a
surprise attack on his hideout?
ANTONIO: Settle down.
If we go charging in, they
could demolish the city.
NATHAN: Good point, honey.
We should proceed
with caution until we
learn how they control
those powered exosuits.
KARINA: So we're waiting
for Origami to call in?
KOTETSU: Yep.
Let's stay on standby
near his location.
-Might I offer a suggestion?
Perhaps we should do
some reconnaissance on
is hideout to prepares us
for the battle ahead, right?
-Uh-huh.
-Sure.
-Then I volunteer to go.
-Huh?
-Alone?
-I need to do this.
I promised the people
I would catch Jake
and I'm going to do
everything in my power
to fulfill that pledge.
-All right then.
Barnaby will be our scout.
I have the utmost
confidence in him.
-Thank you.
-Bunny, I think I
should come with you.
-It's too much of a risk.
I'll go solo.
-Uh, but if you
see that guy Jake,
you might lose it like before.
-I'm asking you to trust me.
AGNES (ON COMMS): Barnaby, the
film crew can't follow you,
so make sure you get good
footage on your helmet cam.
-Copy that.
Did you learn anything
about Jake's powers?
AGNES (ON COMMS): The
Justice Bureau database
says he's a NEXT with deadly
force, but gives no details.
BARNABY: Nothing?
Shouldn't there be arrest
reports from 15 years ago
when Legend brought him in?
AGNES (ON COMMS):
For some reason,
those records have
been wiped clean.
-I see.
OK, I'm moving in.
-Mm.
-Please, let this work.
-Huh?
Where's Tiger?
-He was right behind
us a second ago.
-Is that?
What are you doing here?
-You can breathe easy, Bunny.
I got the jerk.
-No, you don't understand.
He's--
-What the--
[laughter]
-What'd I tell you?
They fell for it.
-You called it, Mr. Jake.
-Jake.
-Ah, you must be
Wild Tiger, huh?
Or as it says here, the
"idiotic one-man wrecking crew."
Which do you prefer?
-Shut your trap!
-Was it you?
Were you the one who
murdered my parents?
-Huh?
-Tell me!
-I kill lots of folks, tin man.
You expect me to
remember 'em all?
-You're dead.
-Cool it, Bunny.
-Listen to you friend.
If I have to kill
you now, it'll ruin
the surprise I have
in store for later.
[chuckling]
-What the hell was that?
-Heh.
-What do you mean
he just got away?
-Sorry.
We have no idea where he went.
-How would you people lose him?
I assured everyone
you could handle this.
You've made a liar out of me.
[monitor beeping]
-Why the hell did
you go in there?
-Well, when I saw you
activate your power,
I thought you were gonna
go nuts on the guy.
-But he was wearing one of
our comm units on his wrist.
-Huh?
Wait, you knew that
was Origami Cyclone?
-Do you have any
idea how long I've
been waiting for
this opportunity?
And now, because of you,
that bastard got away.
-Uh--
-And I specifically told
you I could handle it alone.
Why didn't you stay back,
like I asked you to?
-Well, I mean, I was
sort of worried that--
-Shut up.
I needed you to trust
me and you couldn't.
I was actually
starting to believe
I could rely on
you as a partner,
but I can't put my trust in a
partner who doesn't trust me.
OFFICER: Hey, who are you?
Get back!
-Mr. Jake?
[whistling]
-This is an absolute nightmare!
Locate Jake immediately!
That's an order!
-Um, sir?
What would you like us to do?
-We have to play the one
card we still have left.
Release Chuckman.
We can use him as a decoy to
flush out Jake, and then--
JAKE: I'm one step
ahead of you there.
[gasps]
-Huh?
[chuckling]
[snap]
-Jake.
Why are you here?
-Only cowards run away.
And it seems poor Chuckman
had an unfortunate accident.
Why did I kill him?
Well, let's just say that when
he let himself get captured
he lost all of my respect.
-You came all this way to gloat?
-That was just a prologue.
Mr. Jake would like to share
a much more important message
with you.
AGNES: What message?
-We can all agree that NEXTs
are the most advanced beings
in our world, but recently,
some have allowed themselves
to fall under the influence
of much lesser humans.
These aberrations wear costumes
and prance around calling
themselves heroes.
They're an embarrassment.
Which is why, on
behalf of all NEXTs,
I've decided to crush
them once and for all.
-Oh, and he would like to do so
on one of your live broadcasts.
Unless you want us
to sink your city,
you'll roll your cameras for us.
-What are we shooting?
-Mm, the greatest show ever.
-Are you a total moron?
Jake escaped because you
can defied Barnaby's request
and got in his way.
That's now how you
treat a teammate.
-You're right about that.
-Huh?
-I kept trying to convince him
we were a team, but in the end,
I was the one who
didn't trust him.
[music playing]
[comm buzzing]
KRIEM (ON TV):
Greetings, all you
hero-loving citizens
of Sternbild.
Today we'll be presenting
a special live broadcast
of Mr. Jake's seven
deadly matches.
-Seven what now?
KRIEM (ON TV): But first, a
word from the man of the hour.
-I know how much you love
your so-called heroes,
but I'm gonna show you
how worthless they are.
-The rules are simple.
Heroes will be picked
at random and Mr,
Jake will battle
them one on one.
-Say what?
JAKE (ON TV): If any hero
manages to defeat me in battle,
I'll shut down my exosuits and
leave your fair city in peace.
-Sounds great, but what
happens if all the heroes lose?
-Then I'll blow up
the support pillars
and destroy the whole place.
KRIEM (ON TV): You heard him.
The fate of the city now
lies with the heroes.
-Good luck, everybody.
KARINA: What is wrong with him?
NATHAN: This guy's
off his rocker.
First he kills his own
man and now this insanity.
-Actually, this could
work out perfectly.
NATHAN: Huh?
KARINA: What?
-As long as it's one on
one and nobody interferes,
I can beat this guy.
KRIEM (ON TV): And now
we'll spin the big wheel
to find out who's fighting
in match number one.
-You.
KRIEM: The honor of being the
first challenger goes to--
-Bingo.
The King of Heroes.
It's Sky High.
The best one's gonna die first?
Damn, that's gonna
ruin all my fun.
-As the King of Heroes, I
gladly accept his challenge.
I will show him the
honor of a champion.
-Careful when you're flying.
He might try to shoot you down.
-Shoot him?
-When we faced him
at the hideout,
he was firing laser beams
out of his fingertips.
And they were
strong enough to go
through thick concrete walls.
-I'm not worried in the least.
Despite his power, he can't
hurt me if he doesn't hit me.
I swear this to you,
Barnaby-- I will capture him
and bring him back to you alive.
-This sucks.
I can't believe we gotta follow
their orders and air this crap.
-What are you talking about?
This is television gold.
-Huh?
-Look, it's about to start.
-Hey, you change your recipe?
-Yeah.
Can you tell?
-Whatever you did, keep doing
it, 'cause this is great.
[laughter]
Huh?
ANNOUNCER: Here he
comes now, the daring
ace himself-- Sky High!
-Hear me, evildoer!
You have broken our city's laws
and placed lives in jeopardy.
Jake, I am here to
bring you to justice!
[slurping]
Huh?
-Where does he get
off ignoring Sky High?
-Hear me, evildoer!
You have broken
our city's laws--
-I heard you the first time.
Just get on with it.
-Very well.
But be warned, the day's wind
velocity is off the charts!
ANNOUNCER (ON TV): And so,
with the very fate of Sternbild
hanging in the balance--
-The battle royale
is about to begin.
ANNOUNCER (ON TV):
That's my line!
-So without further
ado, let's go!
[grunt]
-Yaa!
KRIEM (ON TV): And Jet
Head strikes first,
pummelling his opponent
with a flurry of attacks.
-I'll finish him before he
has a chance to fight back.
KRIEM (ON TV): Could
Mr. Jake be in trouble?
-Way to go, Sky High!
-Yeah!
Take him down!
-Come on, Sky High!
-Sky high!
-Waa!
KRIEM (ON TV): Oh no, Mr.
Jake's taken a direct hit!
-Yes!
-Kick his ass!
-Oh ho, he did it!
PAO-LIN: Nice!
-Looks like you
challenged the wrong hero.
Now surrender at once.
-I actually felt
that last one, champ.
-Aah!
[gasps]
[chuckling]
-How can you stand after
taking a hit like that?
-Huh?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You never hit me.
[grunt]
-Checkmate, flyboy.
-Jake doesn't shoot lasers.
He creates force fields.
-You've gotta be kidding.
-Yee haw!
-Yaa!
-That's the King of Heroes?
Kind of a let down.
-He beat Sky High?
-I don't believe it.
-This can't be happening.
-I, I thought he
shot laser beams.
-No.
He uses defensive force
fields and attacks with them.
I guess someone
jumped to conclusions.
ANTONIO: Hey, they're
drawing the next card.
-Eenie, meenie-- and mo.
Ugh, Bull Tank of
the West Coast?
Seriously?
He looks like a cow.
-I'm gonna rip
that guy a new one.
-Rock Bison, this man
is very dangerous.
Be careful.
ANTONIO: Don't worry.
Now that I've seen
his power, he's mine.
I'll bust through his force
field with brute strength.
AGNES (ON COMMS):
Good luck, Bison.
KRIEM (ON TV): It's time
for the second match.
How long will the
metal heifer last?
[growl]
Oh!
There he goes!
[chuckling]
ANTONIO (ON TV): Gaa!
-Aw, come on, heroes.
Is that all you've got?
-Nobody alive could
defeat you, Mr. Jake.
-Well, bring out the next loser.
-All right!
JAKE (ON TV): That
dumb ass who always
has to pay for breaking stuff?
I can waste him
with my eyes closed.
Might as well draw
the next guy too.
-Say that to my face!
JAKE (ON TV): Oops,
I picked a team.
Isn't that just adorable?
Be seeing you boys.
-I'm gonna go prep my suit.
-Eh, don't even bother
getting dressed.
I'm gonna end this
punk in no time.
Wait-- I know I was wrong
before and I'm sorry.
[monitor beeping]
[grunting]
-I have to tell them right away.
-Hey, ninja, I got a fun idea.
Turn into me.
-He was still holding hostages,
so I had to do what he told me.
-Forget about that.
Just tell us what you learned
about those powered exosuits.
-I'm getting to that, sir.
-Disguising yourself as
Chuckman to sneak in.
That'll teach those
morons what happens
when they don't
take us seriously.
Now blow up those support
columns, little teddy bears.
-Not yet.
There's more fun to be had.
-The stuffed animals
operate the exosuits,
and they only seem to
respond to her commands.
She was using some
kind of communicator
to relay her orders to them.
-You're saying that if we
can somehow jam that signal--
-We can take the exosuits
out of the equation.
[gasps]
-Good work, Origami.
We should start setting up
jamming systems across the city
immediately.
-Mm.
-Jamming the city?
MAVERICK (ON PHONE): Countless
lives could be spared.
It won't be up and running
until tomorrow morning, though.
You have to hold out till then.
-I understand.
-Look, it's the oaf who
trashes his own city.
They call you
Crusher for Justice?
You look like you couldn't
even crush a soda can.
-I'll be happy to show you.
-Mm.
AGNES (ON COMMS):
Remember, Tiger,
strength alone won't be enough
to get through his force
fields.
-That's why I'm gonna
beat him with speed.
-And now for the
third match, Mr. Jake
versus the scary Tiger Begin.
[chuckling]
-Hmm.
Yipe!
Ah.
Ooh hoo hoo!
[grunt]
[chuckling]
[groan]
Not fast enough.
[gasp]
-Oh no.
King Tiger, get up.
Get up!
-Hey, get me outta here.
-What for?
The city's locked down.
-Who cares?
I just want to go.
These lousy heroes
are blowin' it.
JACKSON: All the more reason
why you're not getting a ride.
You just insulted a
good friend of mine.
-Huh?
-Kotetsu.
[groan]
[grunt]
-(HUMMING) Mmm, mm mm mm mmm.
Mmm.
-Are you worried about Tiger?
-Not really.
I came here to study the fight,
to help me prepare for my turn.
-So you don't
believe your teammate
has any chance of winning this?
-What a wuss.
Too scared to come out
from behind your shields?
-You should talk.
You're the one
jumping around so you
don't have to face me head on.
-That's it!
MALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Good Luck Mode.
[grunt]
[groan]
MALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Ability timeout.
-That didn't work the first
10 times you tried it, either.
-Why can't I hit you?
-I can hear what you're
gonna do before you do it,
and that's why
you'll never beat me.
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Powers expire in 10 seconds.
-Dammit.
Already?
[grunt]
KOTETSU (VOICEOVER):
Come on, Kotetsu, focus.
He has to have some weakness.
[chuckling]
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Three, two, one.
-Oops, time's up.
Too bad.
-Waa!
-Well, you tried.
Wee hee hee!
Ha ha ha!
-Oh my goodness.
Without his Hundred
Power, he'll never
be able to survive
Jake's attack.
-Oh, this is ridiculous.
Bang.
-What's he doing?
This is suicide.
-A real hero never gives up.
I can't let this punk stop me.
-You don't know when
to quit, do you?
[grunt]
Huh?
-Oh!
-He hit him.
-Ow!
You slippery punk!
Now you're really in for it.
No one kicks me!
No one!
Grr!
-My god, we can't air this!
Cut to a commercial!
-Yes, ma'am.
-Grr!
I really don't like getting
kicked in the head, hear me?
You're so dead, Kotetsu!
Nobody kicks me
like that and lives!
Grr!
[groan]
[grunting]
-If the heroes keep
losing at this rate,
we're not gonna
last until morning.
-Hey, is the next
victim ready yet?
-Pardon me, Mr. Martinez.
-Hmm?
What now?
-Might I suggest
taking a little break?
-Huh?
Are you trying to
tell me what to do?
AGNES (ON SCREEN): Not at all.
I just don't think it's the best
idea to run the show all night.
-Eh?
-Ratings drop off when
people go to sleep.
It would be a shame to
waste this excitement.
-Hmm.
Yeah, like your thinking, woman.
Fine then.
It's intermission.
-Nice going, Miss
Agnes-- using ratings
as a ploy to buy us time
so we can jam the signal.
-I've never seen numbers
like this in my life!
[hesitant chuckling]
-That force field-- there's
nothing we can do to break it.
-Hmm?
Barnaby, your fight
isn't till tomorrow.
-He's right.
Jake almost killed Tiger and
you have the exact same Hundred
Power he does.
DOCTOR 1: He has
deep lacerations.
Pulse is dropping.
DOCTOR 2: We have to
stop the bleeding.
Prepare for a transfusion.
[MUSIC - AOBOUZU, "HOSHI NO
SUMIKA"]
-Good morning.
Rise and shine,
scum of Sternbild.
I hope you slept like babies.
-Hold on, Mr. Jake.
My makeup isn't on yet.
Oh!
-Let's pick up
where we left off.
Oh, were the heroes
too boring for you?
Well, here's some
titillating news.
After the next match,
we're halfway done,
so I decided that if he loses,
I'll destroy half your city.
That ought to gets
your juices flowing.
BARNABY: Hi, I'm Barnaby,
the member of Tiger and Bunny
who uses two pieces of
tissue to blow his nose.
The day is finally here.
Now is my chance to
get my revenge on Jake.
Next time on "Tiger
and Bunny," "Confidence
is a Plant of Slow Growth."
See you!