[HANAMARU]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[YOSHIKO] Would you like
to descend with me?
[HANAMARU] Yoshiko had
a hard time gettin' rid of
her Yohane persona!
[CHIKA]
I found it!
[HANAMARU]
Then Chika suggested that Aqours
become fallen angel idols
so we'd stand out.
[DIA]
It's disgusting!
[HANAMARU] We had to go
back to the drawing board.
[YOSHIKO] I should've
dropped this whole act.
[HANAMARU] But Chika and
Yoshiko had a little talk.
[CHIKA]
'Cause the most important thing
is to show your favorite self!
Your shining self!
Don't let it go!
[HANAMARU]
And then...
[DIA]
Explain yourself now!
There's nothing more I can say.
Uranohoshi High School
is gonna close down,
and the students will go
to a school in Numazu.
I thought you already knew.
I heard, but nothing
was certain.
[MARI]
That's right.
It's not exactly a done deal.
I keep pushing them to wait,
but there's only
so much I can do.
And why would you care?
I think you already
know that I have
my own personal reasons for
becoming the director here.
[DIA]
Uh...
I'm not going to
lose this school.
No matter what.
It's important to me.
More than any other
place in the world.
[DIA] I hope you have
a strategy in mind.
Did you realize that every year
we have fewer and fewer
applicants enrolling here?
And that's exactly why we
need the School Idol Club.
You're serious?
I said it back then, didn't I?
I never believed in giving up.
Even now.
I know there's a chance
to turn things around.
It'll be fine.
I'll find my own way to keep
the school from closing.
[door opens, closes]
So stubborn.
Always thinking of Kanan.
[bell chimes]
[YOSHIKO]
Can you believe it?
It was super annoying!
Don't you think?
We all agree! Right?
It so was!
Have a good day!
Bye-bye, new best friends!
[STUDENT 5A]
Yoshiko is so funny!
[STUDENT 5C]
I know!
Well, that was tiring.
Uh! It shouldn't be
this hard to be normal!
Like we've been sayin',
you don't gotta force yourself
to be ordinary, zura!
[YOSHIKO]
Sparkle!
From the darkness of
the infinite abyss...
...Yohane descends!
[grunts]
There's the beautiful fallen
angel we all know and love!
[door opens]
[BOTH]
Uh?
[RUBY]
Bad news! I have bad news!
[HANAMARU]
What's the matter?
It's terrible!
Our school is gonna be--
[ALL]
Combined and shut down?!
[RUBY]
Mm! That's what's going around.
We'll have to merge with
a school in Numazu.
So we might as well kiss
Uranohoshi goodbye.
It can't be!
When?
Well, that still depends on next
year's enrollment numbers.
If there aren't enough
new students,
they'll have no choice
but to close down.
Close down?
[RIKO, YOU gasp]
This is it!
Our time has finally come!
Sounds to me like Uranohoshi
is on its last leg!
I'd say our school's in
desperate need of saving!
Are you okay?
I think you need to sit down.
Yoo-hoo! Earth to Chika.
What are you so happy about?
[CHIKA] I can't believe
this is happening!
Our school is shutting down!
It's just like Otonokizaka!
Oh, yeah!
[CHIKA grunts] The stage
has been set perfectly!
We'll work together
and save our school!
And we're going to shine!
Like Mu's! They'll
be our guiding light.
You can't really think
it's going to be that easy.
How do you feel, Hanamaru?
[HANAMARU]
We'll be combined and shut down!
[RUBY]
Not you too!
You're tellin' me that if
this place has to close,
we'll go to school
in Numazu, zura?
We could officially call
ourselves city girls!
Right, yeah...
[HANAMARU sighs]
That's just like her.
Good grief.
Zuramaru has always
been like this.
No way.
[gasps] It's the future, zura!
[YOSHIKO]
Huh...?
I guess it makes sense.
Well, what about you, Yoshiko?
I, for one, think closing this
place down is a terrific idea!
In the big city there
will be tons of students
who are up to date with
the latest trends, like me!
Oh, that's wonderful to hear!
Think of all your old friends
from middle school!
You can reconnect!
[YOSHIKO] I meant to say I'm
completely against combining!
[ALL]
Uh?
[CHIKA]
Listen up!
We now know that our treasured
house of learning is in danger
of closing. So Aqours
will take swift action...
...to save the school!
[YOU]
Uh... Full speed ahead!
Let's perform a rescue mission!
Yeah, you have our attention,
so tell us your plan!
Huh?
[ALL]
What?
[yawns]
[CHIKA]
All righty!
I did some research,
and all Mu's had to do
was form their group
and register for their
ranking as school idols.
They performed together at Love
Live, and then got super famous.
Do all that and
the school is saved.
[YOU]
Oh, is that it?
[CHIKA]
I think so.
Except...
The number of students taking
the entry exam keeps decreasing.
[knocking]
Uh! Come in.
Hey Sis, got a sec?
[DIA]
Is something the matter?
Not really.
I wanted to let you know I might
be running a little late.
[DIA]
Again?
Yeah. Chika thinks
that if our club
made a promo video it might
inspire some new applicants
to come to our school next year.
[DIA]
Thank you for telling me.
[gasps]
I'll let mother and father know
that you won't be
home for dinner.
You don't mind?
Thank you so much!
[DIA]
It's fine.
Just make sure you're
home before dark.
Right! Gotta run, see ya later!
How is it?
Being a school idol.
It's a lot of hard work,
but I'm having fun.
Oh.
[RUBY] Where are the other
student council members?
[DIA]
Their schedules are full
because they're all
involved in other clubs.
Too bad.
Would you--
Well, you'd better get going.
Uh...
[DIA]
You wouldn't want to be late.
[RIKO]
Cool things about Uchiura?
That's right!
This town is so rinky-dink
most people probably don't
know anything about it!
So we'll make a video that
tells them all the great stuff
we have going on!
[YOSHIKO]
So we're filming a PV?
Yup! Mu's did something
like this, too.
We'll make it look awesome here
and post it for everyone to see!
The sea of knowledge, zura?
Well, whaddaya think?
Everybody's gonna love it!
[gasps] I don't know what to
say to that camera thingy!
I can't do it!
[RUBY whimpering]
[YOU]
Mm... Where'd she go?
[YOSHIKO]
I predict she's in the tree!
[ALL gasp]
[RUBY]
Crazy! I can't get up that tree!
[YOU]
Ha!
[RUBY shrieks]
Wow! That was amazing!
Can we see it again?
We don't have the time
for that right now!
Check out that view!
Mt. Fuji looks so
awesome from here!
And what do you think about
this shimmering ocean, huh?
Guess what else?
Our mandarin oranges are yummy!
If you walk into
town we have a--
In the town we have a lot of...
Uh... We have a lot
of nothing at all!
[YOU]
You can't tell them that.
[CHIKA sighs]
Okay.
You can even visit the big city!
Just a bus ride away!
While you're at it check out
some of the great stores!
And there's more... nearby!
[RIKO]
Have some money to spend?
If you bike ride over
the big hill you'll find
the exhilarating Izu shopping
arcade, a great time waster.
Good grief. Gettin' here
wasn't easy at all.
And it would take a person
500 yen to get to Numazu by bus!
[YOSHIKO groans]
This isn't working out!
[CHIKA]
Mm... You're up.
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
Greetings, little demons.
It is I, fallen angel Yohane.
Now then, allow me
to familiarize you
with the earth upon
which I have landed!
The first thrilling feature?
This dirt!
[laughs]
I just love it when Yoshiko
shares her true self
with the world!
Uh. Maybe we should think
about taking this whole video
in a different direction.
Aw! But this is funny!
[RIKO] But it's not
supposed to be funny!
[laughs]
[WAITRESS 6A]
Here you are, ladies!
Been a while since we've
had such a big group.
Let us know if there's
anything you need!
Why did we come to a café?
I hope your family
didn't get angry
'cause we got too loud
last time we were there.
[CHIKA] Not at all!
We came here 'cause Riko
doesn't wanna come in
if Shiitake's roaming around.
I never said I didn't
want to come in!
I just suggested you keep
your dog on a leash!
Do I have to?
That's how it is.
Most people think of their
pets as part of the family,
is that so weird?
I don't get it.
[DOG 6A barks]
All right, knock it off.
[RIKO gasping]
[RUBY gasping]
[yelps]
You're afraid of
little dogs, too?
[RIKO]
It's not the size!
It's the fangs
that freak me out!
Those things are razor sharp!
What are you doing?!
[CHIKA]
This one wouldn't hurt a fly!
Isn't that right, sweetie?
Will you please be careful?
You're gonna get your
whole face ripped off!
[CHIKA]
That's it!
This cutie-patootie can help get
you over your fear of dogs!
[whimpers]
[yelps]
[screaming]
[YOU]
Hey, come back!
[RIKO] I'm not leaving this room
until that thing is outside!
She didn't mean it,
little friend.
Are you done yet?
Well, I've done some simple
editing. This was tough.
But really we don't have
much to work with.
Only filming around here makes
things difficult, I guess.
As a last resort we could
always add a few shots
from Numazu into the mix.
Hello there and welcome
to our town!
[barks]
[RIKO]
No fibbing allowed!
[CHIKA]
It was just a thought!
I don't think Riko trusts those
bright ideas of yours anymore.
Hm?
What now?
[YOU gasps]
It's the last bus!
[YOSHIKO]
No way!
[horn honking]
[YOSHIKO laughs]
Farewell.
Onward, Yoshiko!
[BOTH gasping]
[panting]
Well, sure doesn't feel like
we got much done today.
[screams] It's almost seven?!
Come on, Hanamaru,
finish dessert on the way!
[CHIKA]
Can I admit something?
Showing people how great
it is around here
is harder than I thought.
[RIKO] The video was a nice
idea, but our small town
might be hard to appreciate
through a computer screen.
[CHIKA]
Yeah.
I want to try it though.
If we lose our school,
it would be a lot tougher for
all of us to hang out like this.
You're probably right.
[CHIKA] As school idols,
we really need to work hard.
[RIKO]
I thought we did.
You're right about that.
But you know what?
I just realized something.
This is important to me!
I love it.
I don't want to
let our school go!
[laughs] Me either!
[door opens]
You should totally tell me
the next time you visit.
The masters of the house tend
to get a little irritata
if someone comes
in without asking.
Our school's
being shut down?
No it's not. Well, not yet.
But there's work to be done.
We have to take action.
And that's why I need
you to fight again.
Do you?
You should never underestimate
a good stalker, bella . Heh.
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[RUBY]
Kay then!
That's all I've got. See ya!
I gotta go out there
and do my Rubesty!
What do you think?
Oh!
[ALL groan]
[CHIKA] Come on!
We're doing our best here!
The least you could do is watch!
This is your best?
Yes!
Yet it was like so
embarrassingly awful!
Is it that bad?
You're going a bit too
far, don't ya think?
[RIKO]
She's right! You have no idea
how hard we worked just
to make that little bit!
Putting in a lot of effort
isn't gonna be enough!
If you don't understand what
makes this place so special,
why even bother?
I think I get what she's saying.
What's the point of
makin' the video
if we don't know what
we're talkin' about?
That's kinda rude.
Do you know what makes
this place so great?
Absolutely.
Would you like me to tell you?
Ask me.
I don't get why you
didn't let her tell us.
I dunno.
I just felt like it was
the wrong thing to do.
So you were doing it
to be stubborn?
[CHIKA]
No, nothing like that.
[YOSHIKO]
Mm?
I understand why Mari
said those things to us.
If we don't know why our
school and town are special,
how can we make a PV about it?
[RIKO]
I think you're right.
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Let's set sail then!
There's a lot of planning to do
so why don't we all meet
up at Chika's house?
Using the café will
get expensive.
Riko, you just be strong
and do your Rubesty!
[RIKO sighs]
[CHIKA laughs]
[inhales] Right!
Let's go!
Uh. There's something I forgot.
[ALL groan]
I'll be right back!
It'll only take a sec!
[RIKO]
Seriously?
Uh?
[CHIKA gasping]
--[clapping]
--[DIA] Uh!
Amazing, Dia! Really neat.
That was so awesome!
Why-- Why were you watching?
[CHIKA] I already know that
you hate school idols,
but we need help.
This school means a lot to us,
and we'll do anything
to keep it open.
I think this is a cause
worth fighting for.
We'd really love you to join in.
Become a school idol!
Listen to her, Sis.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
However, I must say that
it's nice to see you
doing something worthwhile
with your time.
I wish you luck in your efforts.
[RUBY grunts]
I don't get it, Ruby.
Why doesn't she
like school idols?
Didn't she used to love them?
[RUBY]
Yes.
She was even a
bigger fan than me.
Uh!
We can't force her to join us!
Okay, Ruby.
[RUBY]
I'm sorry.
[CROWD cheering]
[MARI]
Well, well.
You're leaving so soon?
Running away won't
change anything.
It's best to move forward.
Don't you agree?
[DIA]
I'm not running away.
And I didn't back then.
Dia...
Shiitake's not here!
Isn't that right, Chika?
Can we move on?
What are we doing about
the promo video?
We've been scratchin' our
heads for a while, zura.
Any ideas?
I dunno, I might
have a few maybe.
[SHIMA]
Hello!
[ALL gasp]
Welcome back.
[SHIMA]
You ladies having a meeting?
[RIKO]
Yeah.
[SHIMA]
Sounds fun!
Remember, you all
have to get up early.
Try not to stay up too
late tonight, okay?
[ALL]
'Kay!
Why do we have to get up early?
Uhh. Ya know, I don't remember!
[CHIKA] It's the first day
of beach season!
[RIKO]
What the--? Chika!
[CHIKA laughs]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[SHIITAKE barks]
[RIKO whimpering]
[beeping]
[RIKO groans, yawns]
[CHIKA]
Riko! Over here!
Good morning, sunshine.
It's early.
We grabbed one of
the lanterns for you.
[YOU] So we start at
this end of the beach,
and pick up trash as we
walk towards the ocean!
I have a question.
[YOU]
Hm? What's up?
[RIKO]
Do you do this every year
on the first day
of beach season?
[YOU]
Yeah. Sure do!
[RIKO]
I had no idea.
And I didn't realize so many
people live in this town!
[YOU] Yep! Almost everyone
joins in to help!
It's kind of a community effort.
[RIKO]
Amazing.
I can't believe we
didn't see it before.
Maybe this is what makes our
school and town so special.
That's it!
[YOU]
Huh?
[ALL]
Hm?
Uh?
Everyone! Attention, please!
I wanna say something!
I'm from the new school idol
group at Uranohoshi.
We're Aqours!
Our school's in trouble and
we're on a mission to save it!
We're gonna do all we can
to bring in more students,
but we can't do it alone!
Will you help us?
With the support
of our community,
I know we can do it together!
[music plays]
[singing in Japanese]
[CHIKA] For so long, I'd been
searching for something,
for anything wonderful,
and thinking I would
never find it here.
But I was wrong about that!
[CHIKA]
I'm going to keep reaching.
There's no way I'll slow down!
This is the beginning
of everything!
I can do it!
[GIRLS]
Next time, "Tokyo!"