[HANAMARU]
Ever since I was a little girl,
I was always the quiet
one who played alone.
I wasn't all that
good at sports,
and I was cast as a tree
in the school play.
[HANAMARU]
It wasn't so bad.
I got kinda used to spendin'
time by myself.
I started to love readin' more
than anything else in the world.
Books were my happy place,
and the library was a paradise!
I loved being whisked away!
I felt my imagination growin'
with every story I read.
[clock chimes]
[HANAMARU]
Whenever I finished a book,
I'd always feel a
little lonely inside.
It was fine though, cause no
matter how many I got through,
I knew I'd never run out.
[pages rustling]
[gasps]
[RUBY sighs]
Heh. Uh?
[whimpering]
[HANAMARU laughs]
[HANAMARU]
That girl was Ruby Kurosawa,
and she became one of
my closest friends.
[CHIKA]
There we go!
Can you believe it?
After everything
we've been through
our club was finally approved!
[YOU] Especially since we
don't have enough members.
The director said okay so that
means we're in the clear!
Well, she didn't just say okay.
She could hardly
contain herself!
It seems a little strange
that she's this eager
to help us with this stuff.
Don't you think so?
Maybe she's just a huge
fan of school idols.
No, I think there might
be more to it than that.
Let's solve the mystery
in our new club room!
[ALL]
Uh...
[YOU]
Yuck!
She did say we'd have to clean
the room before using it.
We deserve so much
better than this!
[RIKO] We might as well stop
complaining and get to work.
[YOU]
Mm-hm.
[CHIKA whines]
Uh?
There's writing on this thing.
They look like song lyrics.
Why would they be in here?
I have no idea.
I guess we should start now.
[footsteps, door opens]
[RUBY] I knew it!
They have a club room now!
That must mean the School Idol
Club's actually been approved!
That's terrific!
Yep! Ahh, I can watch them
perform again! Yay!
--[door opens]
--[RUBY screams]
Anyone still in here?
[RUBY whimpers]
Oh! Hey, Hanamaru!
And... Ruby! There!
[RUBY yelps]
How'd you know she was hiding?
U-Uh... Uh.
[laughs]
[gasps] Hi. Nice to see you.
So adorable!
[YOU laughs]
So we found all these
books in the club room.
Did they come from the library?
[HANAMARU]
Yeah!
They belong right here.
Thank you for bringin' 'em ba--
[RUBY gasping]
Will you two please join
the School Idol Club?
Uh?!
Give it a rest.
It's official!
We're the real deal!
It's super exciting and we'd
love for you to join us!
You two would shine so bright
on stage if you sang with us!
You'd be perfect for it!
Uh. Well. I, uh...
Oh, golly.
Golly?
I meant to say...
It looks fun, but I don't think
I'd be any good, really.
Yeah. I agree. I...
wouldn't either.
Hey. You're being a little
pushy, don't you think?
C'mon, Chika.
That's a lot of pressure to put
on two first year students.
Sorry about that!
Heh, heh. You're just so cute!
We should probably
start practicing.
Oh! You're right.
See ya!
They want us to be school idols.
Isn't that somethin'
you'd really like?
[gasps]
I can't.
[HANAMARU]
Because of Dia?
We used to spend a lot of time
pretending to perform like them.
[DIA, RUBY laugh]
[RUBY] We'd act like we
were members of Mu's.
It was so much fun.
But... once Dia started high
school everything changed.
[RUBY humming]
[DIA]
Put that away.
[RUBY]
Uh?
I said get rid of it.
I had no idea.
And really,
I might as well stop liking
school idols the way she did.
But Ruby...
Because it isn't right of
me to keep liking things
Sis can't stand the sight of.
So I won't.
That's too bad.
[RUBY] If you're interested
in becoming a school idol,
you can tell me.
Oh, no! That's not my thing.
'Cause I'm not very athletic,
and my accent sneaks
out sometimes, too!
Then I feel better
about not doing it.
[CUSTOMER 4A]
I had such a great time!
[KANAN]
Thank you so much for coming!
Enjoy the rest of your vacation!
[gasps]
Oh, you are so snuggly I
could stay here forever
and we could all
four be besties.
What are you...? Stop that!
I can't help it!
You're so shiny!
To what do I owe the pleasure?
[MARI laughs]
I've come here to scout you.
What's that mean?
[MARI laughs]
I'd like you to join
the School Idol Club
at Uranohoshi.
Once you ritorno .
Would you?
Absolutely.
Why'd you think I came back?
Should've known that she'd
make things tough for me.
[RUBY gasping]
--[RUBY humming]
--[DIA laughs]
I'm pretty sure
Hanayo is my fav.
Great choice.
It's Elichika for me.
She's even student
council president.
Wow. She's the coolest of all!
So this is Mu's, huh?
I can't do that, zura. [gasps]
[gasps]
Wow.
[YOSHIKO]
The advent of Zuramaru!
What is she doing here?
[HANAMARU]
Hm?
[RIKO, YOU panting]
[RIKO]
I can't climb much longer!
[CHIKA] You gotta! I read
somewhere that Mu's
climbed stairs during
their training!
Yeah, but... did we have to
start out with so many?
We have to remember that we're
new to this kind of thing.
It would be better
to pace ourselves.
[KANAN]
Chika!
[ALL]
Uh?
[CHIKA]
Hey, Kanan!
You make it look easy!
Did you actually run
all the way to the top?
[KANAN] Yeah, I did.
I do it every day.
[ALL gasp]
Every day?
So, what's up? I've never
seen you here before.
Well, we're in training!
It's all a part of
being school idols!
Oh.
I see.
Well, keep up the good work!
Sorry I can't chat, I have
to open the store now!
She ran all the way up and
she's not even out of breath.
There's always someone
farther along than you are.
[sighs] Better catch
up then. Let's go!
[RIKO, YOU laugh]
[RUBY gasps]
You want to be a school idol?
Yup!
But why?
Looks like fun. I kinda
wanna see if I'd like it.
That silly?
No, not at all! But I could've
sworn you told me yesterday
that you weren't
interested in joining them.
Yeah, but then I remembered how
much fun we had watchin' 'em!
I think we'd have a great time.
What do ya say?
You wanna go be a
school idol with me?
You're asking me?!
Yeah, we could try it together.
[RUBY] But I'm worried
I might be too shy.
And I'm pretty sure
Sis wouldn't be okay
with me joining the
School Idol Club.
In that case,
I think I have an idea.
[inaudible]
Trial period.
Is that allowed?
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
Really?!
Yep!
Thank you so very much!
[squeals] Yay!
Awesome!
[CHIKA]
Awesome! [laughs]
We'll definitely win
Love Live now.
We'll be legends!
You weren't listening, were you?
They're joining
for a trial period.
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Okay, it's like this...
It means they're trying
out the School Idol Club
to see if they like it.
If they have a good time,
they might join, but if
it's not their thing,
they'll be free to go.
Is that right?
I'm afraid so.
Things are complicated.
Because of the student
council president, right?
Uh! Yeah.
So we'd be really grateful
if you kept us bein' here
under your hat.
[CHIKA]
There!
All done!
Chika... Let's work on
those listening skills.
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Now that it's all settled
why don't the two of you
join us for practice today?
[RUBY gasping]
I made this chart after
looking at a ton of blogs
from other school idols.
What about composing songs?
Guess we'll have to
squeeze that in
between everything
else on the schedule.
I feel like a real school idol
when we talk about
this kinda stuff!
Any idea where we're
actually going to practice?
Uh...
[PLAYERS chattering]
Fly ball! Pick it up!
Both the courtyard and
field are taken already,
and the club room is way
too small to dance in.
Why don't we just
practice at the beach?
If you think about
all the time we'd waste
travelling there, it
makes more sense
to figure out a place
here at school.
Maybe the rooftop would work!
I never thought of that.
There's a lot of room to dance,
and that's where Mu's
always practiced too!
Hey, that's true!
That's a great idea, Ruby!
To the roof we go!
Oh, wow!
It's awesome!
You can see Mt. Fuji
so well from up here!
The sun sure is bright
today, isn't it?
[CHIKA]
The roof is perfect for us!
We'll soak up all the sunlight,
and the ocean air will feel
really good in our lungs.
We couldn't ask
for a better place!
The ground is so warm.
[YOU]
It sure is.
[HANAMARU]
This feels amazing, zura!
Think we lost her...
I guess it's time
to get started!
[CHIKA]
All right, let's do it!
Aqours.
[ALL]
Sunshine!
[YOU]
One, two, three, four.
[panting] Did I do okay?
That was amazing, Ruby!
I finally remembered it all!
Oh! Sorry.
Let's go ahead and
take it from the top.
[RUBY laughs]
Didn't you say that you'd have
the lyrics done by today?
I couldn't really think
of anything though.
Uh? Hey, what's goin'
on with those two?
They're okay.
We've been stumped trying
to think of a new song.
Our brains have
been fried lately
so tell us if you've
got one, 'kay?
Sure thing.
[RUBY]
Wait a sec!
We're gonna climb
all the way up?
That's the plan!
I guess you forgot to mention
the long break we
take in the middle?
So I did.
If we want to be able to dance
multiple songs in a row,
we'll need the stamina it takes
to make it all the
way to the top.
Yep! That's right!
To the top like Mu's!
Ready, set, go!
[ALL panting]
[RUBY]
She's falling behind.
I don't think I can...
make it to the end...
Hey, Is something wrong?
I'm sorry. I need a second
to catch my breath.
I'll meet you at the top, okay?
No prob! Don't overdo it.
[HANAMARU panting]
You're still here?
Let's stay together.
[HANAMARU]
Go... on without me.
[gasps]
[HANAMARU] You need to keep
going no matter what.
What do you mean?
You gotta do it.
Go for what you want
even if there are other
people slowin' you down.
You deserve to be happy.
Tryna please everybody else
is just gonna drive you crazy.
I didn't even know
I was doing that.
[HANAMARU]
I know that deep down
you really wanna be a
school idol, don't you?
In that case, here's
your chance to shine!
Now, go on up!
But, I can't go alone.
Go.
[HANAMARU] The girl who spent
all her time in the library
with me always put others first.
It was nice of her, but she'd
often forget her own needs.
And be unfair to herself.
All the dreams she had...
All the high hopes
for her future...
...were locked away in the
deepest parts of her soul.
I wanted to figure out a way to
pry open the door to her heart,
and take away all her fears.
To let loose the light inside,
so it could come floodin' out.
[RUBY panting]
--[CHIKA] You're almost here!
--[RIKO] Go, Ruby!
[RUBY panting]
[HANAMARU] I knew it could make
every corner of the world shine.
It would brighten the sky.
She'd be happy, and
the universe would glow!
[RUBY gasping, laughing]
[HANAMARU]
Her joy... That was my dream.
[panting] I did it. I did it!
And on your first try, too!
Look, Ruby!
[gasping]
Yeah, we did it!
We made it to the very top!
[DIA]
Did you need something?
You must have called me
here for a reason.
I did. And I hope that
you'll hear me out.
Your sister has some
things on her mind
and she really needs
to talk to you.
What do you mean?
Oh, Ruby.
I already know.
[RUBY]
Sis?
[gasping]
[DIA]
Ruby?
Hey Dia.
What are you doing here?
Tell me why you're
here with them, now.
I, uh, I was trying, I mean...
Don't be upset!
It's just a trial!
I'll do it.
Okay...
Hear me out.
Don't you see?
I want this!
[bell chimes]
[door clicks]
[MARI]
That's wonderful.
Her dream finally came true.
[DIA]
What are you talking about?
Please let me join the club!
Without a doubt!
Thanks!
I'll do my best!
What about Hanamaru?
Is she not joining?
[HANAMARU] And so,
I guess my story ends here.
[HANAMARU]
The dream I had just came true.
So I'm comin' back
to the world of books.
I'm alone again.
That's okay.
[HANAMARU]
Bye-bye.
I saw, ya know!
[gasps]
What'd you say?
I noticed!
I saw it all when you
thought I wasn't looking!
All that time I thought
you were pretending
you wanted to be a school
idol, because of me!
I was worried you were
pushing yourself too hard,
for something you didn't
even care about!
[RUBY]
But then, when we were dancing,
and when we were on the rooftop,
and we were all
spending time together...
...I noticed that
you looked happy!
[HANAMARU]
Uh.
[RUBY]
And I realized,
you love school idols
as much as me!
You only thought it was
something you wouldn't
like to do, but you
don't have to be alone!
[gasps] It's not true.
I don't like them.
Then why spend so much
time reading that magazine?
[HANAMARU]
It's because...
[footsteps]
[RUBY]
Listen to me!
I've always thought it
would be so wonderful
to become a school idol
with you! Side by side!
We could help each
other work hard!
I wouldn't be able to
do anything like that.
I don't know how, zura.
I'd mess it up.
You know the girl you
keep looking at? Rin?
She didn't think
she would make
a good school idol either,
but look at her!
[RIKO] She loved it, so she
decided to give it a try.
I don't think there's
anything wrong
with starting out that way.
[gasps]
[RUBY]
Please!
Without you, this
doesn't feel right!
Be a school idol with me!
I'm scared. Can I even do it?
[CHIKA] I ask myself
the same question.
Uh?
Nobody really knows if they can
or can't do something they like.
Where's the fun if
you don't try though?
[RUBY laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[CHIKA laughs]
[CHIKA]
Okey-doke!
You ready?
Let's go!
4,999th place? No way.
So there are 4,998
groups above us?
That's so many!
[HANAMARU]
Hm. Well!
Better start running!
Zura!
[YOU, CHIKA, RIKO]
Yeah!
[RUBY laughs]
[YOSHIKO]
Next time, "Yohane Descends."