[KANAN]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
"Love Live! Sunshine!!"
[CHIKA]
Aqours!
[KANAN]
We managed to break through
the prelims of Love Live.
[CHIKA]
Zero.
[YOU]
Tokyo?
[KANAN] But with no new
applicants, we went to Tokyo
to find out how Mu's
saved their school.
[CHIKA] And they
were so wonderful,
'cause they did a
brand new thing.
They weren't afraid
to pave the way.
Mu's worked hard to make
their dreams a reality.
They were free,
and true to themselves.
[KANAN] So now, we'll work
hard toward our new goal
of turning that zero into a one!
Hello everybody!
Nice to meet you.
We're idols of Uranohoshi
Girl's High School!
[ALL]
We are Aqours!
[CHIKA] Today, we have something
very special to share with you.
And that is...
[KANAN]
One, two, three, four...
Try and speed up your movement
right there, Ruby.
[RUBY]
Uh, 'Kay!
[KANAN]
Oh, and Yoshiko.
[YOSHIKO]
Yohane!
[KANAN laughs]
You need to speed up a bit, too.
[YOSHIKO]
Understood! Teleportation mode!
[KANAN]
Good!
Let's take five everyone!
[ALL sigh]
It's too dang hot today, zura!
Feels like I'm melting
into a Ruby puddle!
[YOU]
Here!
On hot days like this, it's
important to stay hydrated!
Okay, got it!
Thank you!
[exhales] It's a gorgeous day!
Yes, but you should
take a break as well.
Too much time in the sun can
wreak havoc on your complexion.
Not Kanan! She loves the
sun and it loves her back!
[groaning]
[ALL gasp]
I tried to warn you that
wearing black in this heat
was a poor choice.
Foolish mortal! You
would never understand!
Black is a fundamental for
a fallen angel's identify!
[DIA]
As is heatstroke, apparently.
Heads up Chika!
Special delivery!
Nice catch!
Thanks ladies!
[CHIKA laughs] This is awesome;
things are starting to heat up.
Let's keep doing our best!
Aye aye ma'am!
Okay then! Who's ready
to get back to work?
Boop! Boop!
What?!
[DIA] Overworking ourselves
is against club rules!
Says Kanan! She's the
expert on exercise!
That's true,
and I guess the hottest part
of the day is coming up.
[DIA]
I understand you're worried
since the regional
qualifiers for Love Live
are right around the corner,
but it's equally important to
give your body a proper rest.
[RUBY]
You're so smart, Sis!
[KANAN]
Before we do anything else,
everyone needs to
pitch in some cash!
[YOSHIKO]
The time has come again.
It's the ultimate
daily challenge.
[chuckles] Today I will not
descend to Ragnarok.
I will... prevail!
[KANAN]
Get ready.
One... two...
[YOSHIKO]
How do I always lose?
I'm afraid you're
just few yen short.
Which one of you got the
expensive ice cream?!
Zura.
Ruby.
Yoha.
You know the rest of us would
enjoy some cold air as well.
I don't understand why the
classrooms don't have AC.
[RIKO] The school wouldn't
invest in something so expensive
when it's about to be shut down.
[CHIKA]
I guess so.
Oh yeah, that reminds me!
Would someone check and see
if there's any new applicants.
[MARI grunts]
[DIA]
Mari! That's so un ladylike!
According to the website...
According to the website?
[MARI]
According to the website...
According to the website...?
Zero!
[CHIKA groans] I don't get it,
why isn't anyone signing up?
Our school can't possibly
be that boring.
[door opens]
[YOU]
Mm?
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Hello?
[CHIKA]
Hi, Mutsu! What are you up to?
Oh. We were just here
to return some books
What about you?
More idol practice?
Yep! The regional
qualifiers are soon.
You work out in this heat?
It's not so bad. We practice
every day, so we're used to it.
Whoa, for real?
Every single day?
Even though it's
summer vacation?
[CHIKA]
Mm-hm!
[KANAN]
Hey, time to go back up, Chika!
'Kay! Bye girls!
See ya later.
That's crazy, they
practice every day?
It's pretty amazing that
they're doing all this
just to keep our school
from closing down.
Yeah.
[MUTSU]
You know what though?
They're really sparkling!
[ITSUKO]
They're inspiring!
[YOSHIMI]
For sure!
[sighs] Another day
of practice down!
Yeah, but I can tell we're
really improving!
Hey, Riko. Any updates
on the new song?
Hanamaru and are I
fine tuning the lyrics,
and Kanan is choreographing
the dance.
I can't wait to perform
it on stage,
we're going to be
totally brillante !
[KANAN]
We worked really hard today.
I say we reward ourselves
with a swimming break!
[splashing]
[DIA]
Not again!
[GIRLS chattering]
[KANAN]
Come on in, the water's great!
[gasps]
[MUTSU]
Ah, there they are!
Hey Chika!
[CHIKA] Oh, hi Mutsu!
I thought you went home already.
Well, not yet.
We actually wanted to
ask you a little question.
[CHIKA]
Yeah?
It's just that... You've
spent your whole summer
practicing for Love Live
regionals, right?
So we wondered if being a school
idol is as fun as it looks.
It sounds silly, but we kinda
thought maybe we could try
and become school idols too,
and help save the school.
[ITSUKO] And we're not the only
ones, there are tons of students
at our school who feel exactly
the same as we do!
We all just wanna help out!
You really feel that way?
Yes!
They're going to combine and
shut us down, aren't they?
We love this place too,
but we're just kids,
we never imagined we might
be able to save it.
Exactly! That's why seeing all
your hard work is so inspiring!
Let us help you!
We all want the same thing,
to save our school,
to sparkle and shine, the
same way that you girls do!
Uranohoshi is special to us,
and we'll do whatever it
takes to keep it open!
[CHIKA cries]
Well, Chika?
What do you say?
Okay! We'll do it together!
[YOSHIMI]
For real?!
[CHIKA]
Yeah!
[MUTSU]
Thank you!
[YOU] This is pretty
exciting stuff, huh?
[CHIKA laughs]
I can't wait for Love Live!
It's gonna rock!
[RIKO]
Just the song?
[CHIKA] Yeah! I know they don't
have time to learn the dance,
but I figure they could
at least learn the song
and maybe sing with
us up on stage.
Think they can do it?
Yep!
We're gonna sound so awesome,
all singing together!
We'll get super famous,
and then the school will get
a ton of new applicants.
They'll have no choice
but to keep us open!
It's possible, but still...
[CHIKA]
Right now,
I wanna turn that
zero into a one.
Today, when I was talking
to Mutsu and the others,
I thought about why our
school has zero applicants.
I mean, Uranohoshi
is so much fun
and everyone always
looks super happy.
It's not just the school either,
our town can also
be very charming.
I feel like that must mean that
this is a wonderful place,
you know?
We may have zero applicants,
but only 'cause they
don't understand
how awesome our school is yet!
It's not like I don't care about
Love Live, because I do.
I just want everyone to see
this place through our eyes.
And... And I think we
can totally do that!
[RIKO gasps]
Whoa, Chika!
Behind you!
There's like a ghost!
Or spirit! I'm not sure!
[gasps] Mom!
What are you doing here?
Did you say your mom?
Is she a ghost?!
Oh my! Yes, I'm Chika's mother,
but I'm not a ghost!
You must be our
new neighbor, then!
Right, of course!
I'm terribly sorry.
Nice to meet you!
No worries, dear!
Nice to meet you too,
and aren't you pretty?
Oh... Me? That's
kind of you to say!
And also true.
[CHIKA]
Mm...
Hold up, you never
answered me earlier!
Aren't you supposed
to be in Tokyo?
Yes, well I was,
until Shima told me you were
in the School Idols Club
and I should come back
to see you perform.
Something to that effect
anyway, so here I am!
Shima should mind
her own business!
But anyway, Mother,
I've got some important stuff
to talk about with Riko,
so can you please just
give us some space?
Fine, fine. I'll see myself out.
Ah, one question though.
Yeah, what?
Will you give up? Or stay true?
I won't give up!
Your mom is kinda cool.
[CHIKA]
What? That's just crazy!
But enough about her,
let's get back to Love Live!
Right!
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[CROWD chattering]
Future!
Is it?
My new domain awaits.
Yohane's arrived!
[CHIKA] They're asking where
we're supposed to meet?
Did we come from over there?
Or was it over there?
[ALL sigh]
[YOU] I wonder where Mutsu
and the others could be?
I'm positive I said to
meet us here. I think.
[MUTSU]
Chika!
[gasps]
Ah! There!
So glad you made it!
[MUTSU]
I'm so sorry!
We had a little
trouble finding you.
[YOU]
Where's everyone else?
--'Bout that...
--Yeah.
We wanted to tell you
before now, the thing is...
No problem!
We understand, it's okay.
It is summer vacation.
[MUTSU] We really did tell
everyone at school.
[CHIKA]
Huh, uh?
It's true, we tried our best.
Uh, what?
All right! Is everybody
ready to go?
[URANOHOSHI STUDENTS]
Yeah!
[AQOURS] They're all here!
Everyone's joining in!
Awesome.
Did we surprise you?
Yeah! If we all sing
on stage together,
I know that we'll
shine super bright!
We'll show how great
our school can be!
[RIKO]
Wait, I'm sorry!
[CHIKA]
Huh? What for?
[RIKO]
The thing is...
I looked it up and there's
a rule which states
the only people
allowed to sing
are those who
applied beforehand.
[CHIKA]
Oh, no.
[RIKO]
On top of that,
they're not even allowed
to be near the stage.
I should have said
something sooner.
[CHIKA]
I'm so sorry, everyone!
[MUTSU]
Hey, it's not your fault!
I mean, we didn't really
give you much warning.
[YOSHIMI] Yeah, it's fine!
Think of it this way,
you'll have a super huge
cheering section!
[MUTSU] And you can bet we're
gonna be loud and proud!
[ITSUKO] Go out there
and give it your best!
Do it for us, okay?
[RUBY] This is so weird. I
can't believe we're really here.
Me neither, zura.
I never imagined we'd
actually make it this far.
Feels like I'm dreamin'!
[YOSHIKO]
It's not that hard to believe!
This is real. This is happening.
Thank you both.
[HANAMARU, RUBY gasping]
Now! All that's left is
to become school idols,
and descend upon
the stage together!
[RUBY laughs]
I wouldn't wanna descend
with anyone else!
[YOSHIKO]
Let's do it!
Yohane and her demons will
rise up, and win... Love Live!
[KANAN] Wow, we finally made
it after all this time,
and as third years nonetheless.
[DIA]
It does seem surreal,
and it's all because of someone
who was very stubborn.
Yeah, true. We never
thank her, so thanks.
But I'm the one that should
be thanking you girls.
You're both the reason
I became a school idol
in the first place.
And we're here now because
you decided to wait for me.
I love you both so much.
[KANAN] We'll take back
what we left behind.
This time we'll succeed!
[DIA]
We'll do it together!
[RIKO]
It's sort of strange.
When I moved to Uchiura,
I never could have imagined
what kind of life
was waiting for me.
I guess you can thank
Captain Chika for that!
[CHIKA] It wasn't just because
of me, you also have to thank
Love Live, and thank
Mu's as well!
And school idols everywhere.
Besides, both of you
played a part too!
A lot of things are
going to come our way.
It won't always
be easy. In fact,
I'm sure there will be
a lot of obstacles.
But I'm going to enjoy
every single second of it.
I'll treasure this time,
and savor each special moment.
Because together... together
is how we'll truly shine!
[DIA]
Well said.
The nine of us will sparkle.
[CHIKA]
There's more than just nine.
Let's go!
[CHIKA] Today, we have
something very special to share
with you, and that is the story
of a little town called Uchiura,
and the school in it!
Here is where Aqours was born.
Here, the ocean's big,
and it kisses the shoreline.
Here the sun always
shines bright!
Our town's small, and
there aren't many people.
But there's plenty of fish
and tons of oranges,
probably more than you
could ever even eat!
Everyone who lives there
is super friendly.
In this town, there's also
what you might consider
a small high school.
All of its students are here!
Cheering us on!
Not too long ago,
we decided to start
a School Idol Club.
In Akiba, we saw Mu's
for the very first time.
We wanted shine like
they did, except...
[BOTH]
Wait, compose?
That's right!
You have to be able to
write your own songs!
It's in the Love Live rules.
Otherwise you'll fail!
[BOTH]
An obstacle!
Luckily enough, we got
a new transfer student.
Riko could play piano
and write songs!
It's a miracle!
[RIKO]
I'm so sorry!
[BOTH]
What?!
[STUDENTS laughing]
[CHIKA] Riko had just moved
to our little town from Tokyo,
and wasn't really
that interested
in school idols at first.
She had her own problems
to deal with.
[CHIKA, YOU]
But then...
I want to shine!
[YOU] That's how Riko
became the third member
of our budding
school idol group!
Next up!
Oh, hi there! I wanna join,
but I'm not very athletic, zura.
And me?
I'd love to be a school idol,
but I'm way too shy.
[STUDENTS gasp]
I am called Yohane!
I have descended
from the heavens!
I wish to spread my wings in a
place where I can be truly free!
After our numbers
had grown to six,
we decided to make a promo
video about our town,
and our wonderful community.
Before we knew it,
we'd been invited to perform
at an event in Tokyo!
The future, zura!
Look at all the people!
Some know it as the city of sin!
This is where we're singing!
Let's do this!
We lost? There's no way!
[CHIKA]
We came in last.
Wanna know how many
votes we received?
Zero.
[RIKO]
[YOU]
Zero.
[YOSHIKO]
[RUBY]
Zero.
[HANAMARU]
[CHIKA]
Zero...
Being a school idol
is really kinda tough.
It was definitely harder
than we thought it would be.
You give up?
Hey Chika? Should we give up?
[CHIKA]
It was frustrating!
It was really frustrating!
We had worked hard,
but it wasn't enough!
We got zero votes!
Why? We deserved more!
[RIKO] On that day, we all
decided on a new goal together.
Turn that zero into a one.
That's right! We can't
let it end with a zero.
So we'll just have
to keep trying.
If we work hard, I'm sure
that zero will become a one!
Together, we decided
to carry on!
[RIKO]
Then our group grew yet again,
as we found some new allies!
I'm Uranohoshi's student
council president, Dia!
I guess if you're joining
the idols, I will too!
Ciao bellas , I'm Mari!
These three former idols
joined hands again,
and became part of our group.
With all nine members,
Aqours was finally perfect!
And so we entered
the Love Live prelims
and passed with flying colors!
We were all really happy!
And yet...
We had no new applicants.
Our old foe was back again.
That pesky zero clung to us
like a wet towel, zura!
Why?!
[KANAN] We thought about
our problem a lot.
We thought about how
we could move forward.
We thought of ways to change
that zero into a one.
And together,
we made a decision.
What we decided...
...was with our town....
...and with our school.
And of course,
with all our friends.
At last, we would
follow our own path!
Accepting whatever came our way.
[DIA] We'd treasure
every precious moment.
[MARI] Because that's
what it means to shine!
We'll enjoy life,
and shine bright!
So one day, we can finally
turn that zero into a one!
[music plays]
[CHIKA]
Okay, here we go!
[inhales] One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
And six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
[URANOHOSHI STUDENTS]
Ten!
[URANOHOSHI STUDENTS cheer]
Ladies! Let's shine
brighter than ever!
From zero to one!
Aqours!
[ALL]
Sunshine!
[singing in Japanese]
Hey! All of you!
Let's shine together!
[singing in Japanese]
[CHIKA] You might be wondering
what exactly we managed
to make out of that zero.
We chased what seemed
like an impossible dream.
We got lost, got scared.
Cried a little...
Everything was to
outrun a number.
But when things seemed
their darkest,
we found a light
shining inside of us.
It was the belief
that the nine of us
could do something
truly amazing.
It ignited our passion.
That's how we came to be.
Aqours was born.
Born from our own light!
We're going to achieve our goal,
and shine brighter
than ever before!
Just look inside
yourself. [laughs]
[ALL]
Is your heart shining?