[DIA]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!
[ALL]
Combined and shut down?!
[DIA] Aqours attempted
to save our school
by making a promo video.
[CHIKA] We have a lot
of nothing at all!
[DIA] But they struggled
with highlighting our town
and school's best features.
[MARI] Putting in a lot of
effort isn't gonna be enough!
[DIA]
So they kept searching.
[RIKO] I can't believe
we didn't see it.
Maybe this is what makes our
school and town so special.
[CHIKA]
That's it!
[DIA]
With that realization,
Aqours took a big step
toward helping our school.
Did you just say our video
has 50 thousand views?
Whoa, for real?
Yeah, a lot of people
are talking about
how much they like the lanterns.
Look at our ranking.
Ninety-ninth place?!
Zura?!
[gasps] Awesome.
Awesome, this is awesome!
Those rankings are for
the entire country, right?
You're telling me that
out of over 5,000
school idol groups
we're in the top 100?
Normally I wouldn't want to
get excited over a temporary
boost in our position,
but it's pretty amazing!
And get this--in improved
ranking, we're first!
Really? That's so cool!
You know what? If things
keep going like this,
we could even be the
champions of Love Live!
You think so?
Somehow I get the feeling
it won't be that easy.
I didn't say it would be,
but at least we know
it's not a completely
impossible dream either!
[computer chimes]
[ALL]
Hm?
Hey, look.
It's an e-mail.
"To the members of Aqours."
Looks like it's from the
Tokyo School Idol Association.
I wonder what they could want?
What? Tokyo?
Yeah, that's what's it says.
The Tokyo?
As in like the capital of Japan?
No, the other Tokyo, seriously?
[ALL gasp]
Tokyo!
[gasps]
[DIA]
Tokyo?
[RUBY grunts]
There's an event.
And they'd like us
to come perform.
I understand. So this is
an official event, then?
[RUBY]
Mm-hm.
And I forgot to mention that...
well, a lot of last year's
champions are performing,
so it's a big deal.
We should go!
These kind of trips can
be expensive, you know?
I'll get an advance on
my allowance, okay?
[RUBY]
That's what Chika said, anyway.
[DIA]
But Tokyo?
So is that...
...a "no"?
[DIA]
What did Mari say about it?
She'd give us permission.
But only if everyone said okay.
Wait, Dia!
Uh?
Does this... stuff...
bother you a little?
You know like, the "me being
a school idol" thing.
Ruby. Tell me something.
Becoming a school idol is a
path you chose for yourself,
isn't that right?
[RUBY]
Mm-hm.
Okay then,
so you shouldn't worry about
what I or anybody else think,
got it?
But I--
[DIA]
I apologize.
I've been making things
difficult for you.
Don't let me stand in your way.
Do your best. But just...
Just what?
Well... Never mind.
You should get some sleep.
My, what a surprise.
[DIA]
What are you doing, Mari?
This isn't a game.
You know what it means
to allow these girls to go
to Tokyo for this event.
[MARI] You could totally
stop them and stuff.
Just bear in mind that
if you do keep them
from performing in Tokyo,
they just might quit
trying all together.
I mean, don't you want
them to succeed?
Want them to overcome the
obstacles that we could not?
Want them to be vittorioso ?
[laughs]
Sure, but what happens if
they aren't successful?
What if they all fail instead?
If that were to happen,
those girls would be haunted
by their inadequacy.
It's a possibility,
but not something they
can totally avoid.
If they're serious about
being school idols
and saving the school,
then they have to give
it their best shot.
You haven't changed
at all since then.
You're still the same.
[CHIKA]
A Tokyo top!
Tokyo skirt!
Tokyo shoes!
And this bag... with a panda!
[laughs]
Seriously, Chika?
What are you doing?
Isn't it adorable?!
[RIKO] You know you don't
actually have to dress that way
to go Tokyo, right?
[CHIKA]
Huh? Easy for you to say!
You're from there!
But for us small, city-folk,
going from Uchiura to Tokyo
is a big deal, you know?!
[footsteps]
[HANAMARU, RUBY]
Good morning everyone!
Ah!
...uh?!
[RUBY]
How's this?
Does my outfit look okay?
--[CHIKA gasping]
--[RIKO] U-Uh...
[HANAMARU]
Right, I'm ready!
Let's do this!
Bring on the treacherous
gorges of Shibuya, Zura!
Wow, you both look
absolutely ridiculous.
[RUBY, HANAMARU]
Aw...
And there are no
gorges in Shibuya.
Ha, ha, talk about a couple
of country girls!
Look who's talking!
What?!
[HANAMARU]
That's too bad,
we ended up changin'
into our normal clothes.
Well if you want my opinion, I
think you both look super cute.
You mean it, zura?
[RIKO] Yes! Oh, but
when you're talking,
you might want to be careful
with your "zuras."
[HANAMARU]
Zura!
[DIA]
Ruby?
[RUBY]
Uh?
Be strong. And do
your best, okay?
[RUBY]
What did she mean by that?
[HANAMARU]
Hey, Ruby?
[RUBY gasps]
Help me out if I start
sayin' "zura" on our trip.
Stop me, 'kay?
[RUBY]
Mm-hm!
Where are they?
[YOSHIKO laughs]
[YOSHIKO]
I, the esteemed fallen angel,
descend upon you from
the heavens above.
Now behold, you mortals,
as I summon my little demons
from their capital of sin!
[GIRL 7A] Mommy, what's
wrong with that girl?
[MOTHER 7A]
Shh. Don't look at her!
You're attracting a ginormous
boatload of attention.
[ALL chuckle]
[CHIKA]
Oh, Yoshiko.
[RUBY]
Your persona is showing!
[YOSHIKO]
Uh!
Zura, she's in full on
fallen angel mode.
You're all late, Chika!
Yoshiko's not here right now.
[ALL gasp]
--Yohane is!
--[CROWD screams]
This place is beyond perfect!
It's the kind of stage my
fallen angel character
can really thrive on,
know what I mean?
[ALL]
Um, sure.
Riko, wait.
Yes?
Those girls, well, they're
not exactly used to Tokyo.
So keep an eye on them.
'Kay!
[MUTSU]
Chika!
[CHIKA]
Hey, Mutsu!
Glad we caught you!
We wanted to wish you luck!
Ta-dah! This is from our class!
Wow, that's so sweet!
Knock 'em dead!
Show them city girls what
Uranohoshi is made of!
[CHIKA grunts]
We will!
[GIRLS]
Good luck out there!
[CHIKA]
Thanks a lot!
[CHIKA] Which train are we
supposed to take?
I don't know. Maybe that one?
[YOSHIKO]
The city of sin rejuvenates me!
[HANAMARU]
This is bread is delicious!
You ruined the moment!
Let's go!
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
Please come visit us!
[MOTHER 7B]
Say cheese!
I've heard stories
that in Tokyo demons
often run rampant
through the streets.
The promised land
of magic and evil.
Whoa, check it out!
I think I just saw a really cool
ad for school idols over there!
If you don't tone
it down a little,
everyone's gonna know
we're from the country.
Oh. You're probably right.
We should maybe try
to blend in somehow.
Of course.
Wow. Oh em gee,
Harajuku is like so
over the top crazy, you
know, just like always!
[laughs]
[WOMAN 7B]
How adorable!
[YOU]
Uh, Chika...
[RIKO]
This is Akiba.
Silly me!
[RUBY]
Huh?
[gasps] It's the future, zura!
The fu--
[RUBY]
Hey, where'd they go?
It's all so shiny! And check
out all the different pins!
Ah! I've never seen this
poster before, awesome!
Looky!
Come on, we're gonna
run out of time.
Hold up. Where's
Hanamaru and Ruby?
Hm?
Fallen Angel.
[YOU humming]
Uniforms? Over a hundred types?
'Kay! It's about time
we go pray at the shrine
for tomorrow's success.
Does that sound good to you?
Huh?
[CHIKA]
Yes. Yeah.
It's the big building.
The other one.
[RUBY]
Oh! There you are!
[HANAMARU]
We are so sorry!
We're still missing
Yoshiko and You.
Don't worry. They said they
know where we're going.
I'm sure they'll meet up
with us there soon.
[CHIKA]
When is "soon"?
[RIKO]
No idea...
[CHIKA grunts] Everyone is
off doing their own thing!
Yeah, these things happen.
[gasps] Romance books?
What was that?
Who, me?! Oh nothing!
What's nothing?
No... thing! Uh.
On second thought,
I need to use the restroom!
Wha?!
[RIKO panting]
[CHIKA] Man. I can't believe
we ran out of time.
I was hoping we
could look around
a bit more after
coming all this way.
Hey! What are you
looking at me for?!
I told you, this is
super important stuff
to use in our show
tomorrow, got it?
And why are you
dressed like that?
Come on! You did say we're
going to the shrine, right?
I'm ready for action, captain!
I'm pretty sure shrine
maidens don't salute.
[CHIKA]
This is it!
We're here! Mu's practiced
on these stairs! No way!
Are you ready for this?
Of course!
All right! Then, on your
marks, get set, go!
[ALL laughing, chattering]
[CHIKA] Mu's climbed
these exact same steps.
Right here.
[CHIKA]
All to win... Love Live!
[CHIKA panting]
[singing in Japanese]
[gasps]
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
Why, hello there.
Oh. Um, hello there!
Uh, Chika?
[YOSHIKO] It can't be...
heavenly servants?
Hang on! I recognize
you girls from somewhere.
Aren't you Aqours?
Wait. You know us?
Careful! She's a
probably a telepath!
S'cuse me. Are we
famous or somethin'?
[gasping]
We watched your promo video.
It was amazing.
[gasps] Thanks,
that means a lot!
So tell me, are you
by any chance
in tomorrow's school idol event?
Yeah.
[SARAH] Good to know.
I'm excited for it.
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasping]
[RUBY gasps]
See ya!
Amazing!
Do you think that's just
like a Tokyo school thing?
Because I was really
impressed, zura!
They're heavenly servants!
Of course you were impressed!
But still, I loved their song.
[sighs] This place
is so relaxin'!
I'm glad you're all having a
good time. It's nice, right?
It's super fun!
It almost feels like we're
on a field trip for school!
[YOSHIKO]
Yohane has... descended!
Ta-da! Now with cape!
Oh, so that's what you bought!
What of it, Zuramaru?
I haven't been judging
your food purchases!
Get off the table!
[YOSHIKO]
Uh...
I originally got these as gifts,
but there are a few
extra if I decide
to have a late night snack.
Wait.
These aren't treats
from the inn?
[HANAMARU]
I can't believe you'd go
and eat all my special
snacks like that!
[RIKO]
I'm so sorry! If you want...
Um, Hanamaru. it's bad
eat too late at night.
Can you keep it down?
I can't concentrate over here!
Whatever, zura!
Here goes!
[GIRLS chattering]
[RUBY] Okay then. I'm just gonna
start laying the futons.
[RUBY gasping]
[ALL scream]
[CHIKA] Hey! Listen, I talked to
the innkeeper and you... huh?
[YOU]
Otonokizaka. Mu's' school?
[CHIKA] Yeah, and it turns
out they're close by!
Hey, Riko!
[RIKO]
Uh?
What do you say?
Wanna go check it out?
[RIKO]
Uh...
All of us!
[ALL gasp]
Ah, come on!
It'll be so awesome!
It's something I've
always wanted to see!
This is the high school
Mu's kept alive!
Where they practiced
all their routines!
[RUBY]
Sounds fun, I wanna go too!
[YOU]
Aye aye, count me in!
[HANAMARU]
Isn't Tokyo dangerous at night?
[CHIKA] Dangerous how?
Are there ninjas?
[HANAMARU]
Yoshiko is shaking with fear!
[YOSHIKO]
I am not!
Sorry! I'll pass this time.
[ALL]
Why?
[RIKO] I'm going to bed.
But you girls have fun.
Okay then...
You know what? We should, too.
[RUBY] You're right. We have
a show tomorrow, after all.
[YOSHIKO grunting]
[RIKO]
Uh?
Yohane has descended.
[RIKO laughs]
[CHIKA]
Having trouble sleeping?
Yes, and you?
Yeah, a little.
I'm sorry.
You know, for bringing
the room down earlier.
[CHIKA] Mm-mm! It's not
your fault. It's mine.
Otonokizaka High. You could
say they're pretty famous
when it comes to their
musical programs.
Maybe it's because back when
I was in middle school
I had competed
nationally for piano.
But when I entered high school
there were some big
expectations for me.
[CHIKA]
Wow, really?
[RIKO] I don't hate my
old school or anything.
I just practiced constantly.
I felt like I had to live up
to those expectations.
And then I didn't do so hot
during the last competition.
[CHIKA]
Living up to expectations...
It's kind of nerve wracking.
[RIKO]
Huh?
When we left Numazu,
and all of our friends
came to wish us luck,
I was super happy they came,
but also kinds scared.
I know they're all
cheering for us.
I really don't want to
let any of them down.
I can't fail.
Oh, Chika...
[CHIKA]
I'm sorry!
Uh?
I didn't mean to just
ramble on and on.
[RIKO]
Mm-mm. I'm glad you did.
[gasps]
Now then, let's get some rest!
[birds chirping]
Heh!
[CHIKA]
Okay!
[panting]
[panting continues]
[CHIKA] I remember this
is where I first saw them!
School idols... Mu's.
[YOU]
Hey, Chika!
[ALL panting]
I knew it!
I thought you might be here.
[gasps] Yeah, I--
If you're going to
practice, let us know!
You better not be trying to
leave us behind or anything.
Hey, on the way back, let's stop
and pray at the shrine, zura!
[RUBY]
Sound good?
[music plays]
Uh?
[ALL gasp]
What the...? Love Live!
Oh, wow!
I can't believe it's time
for Love Live already!
They're taking entries.
[RIKO]
So, Chika?
What will we do?
We're entering, duh!
Just like when Mu's entered it!
Just like when Mu's
saved their school!
We'll shine with
everything we've got!
Are you ready?
Let's go!
[ALL]
Aqours...
...Sunshine!
The ranking?
[EVENT STAFF 7A]
Yes, that's correct.
This year, we decided to base
the ranking of the show's idols
off the votes we receive from
everyone in the audience.
So if you're near the top,
then I guess you have a chance
of getting famous even faster?
Yeah, I suppose.
Anyway, Aqours,
you ladies go on second.
Break a leg out there!
Second.
We're the warm up act.
I think it'll be okay.
You have to remember,
most of these other groups
have already performed
in previous Love Lives.
[HANAMARU]
I guess, zura.
It'll be awesome, just watch!
I know we can do it!
[RIKO gasping]
[YOU]
Are you nervous?
[RIKO]
Yeah, a little.
[YOU]
Okay then, give me a salute!
An Aqours aye aye!
Okay... An Aqours aye aye?
[laughs] That's perfect!
It's my magic spell for
calming your nerves.
[HANAMARU]
What's wrong, Ruby?
[RUBY]
I don't think I can do it!
[HANAMARU sighs]
Do your Rubesty,
and you'll be fine, zura!
[CHIKA] Oh, c'mon.
We gotta keep it together!
[EVENT STAFF 7A]
Excuse me, Aqours?
This way please!
[AUDIENCE chattering]
So many people!
Uh! Like, how many is so many?
[ALL laughing]
[gasps]
Hey, break a leg
out there today.
Wait a minute, so you ladies
are school idols too?
[SARAH] Oh, my.
Did I not mention that?
So sorry. My name's
Sarah Kazuno.
[SARAH]
Leah.
[SARAH] Saint Snow is
about to take the stage.
I hope you'll enjoy the show.
[GIRLS] Next time,
"Isn't it Frustrating?"