[YOU]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[YOU]
With Mu's as her guiding light,
Chika was inspired to start a
School Idol Club of her own!
Things didn't really
go as planned.
[DIA]
I refuse your application.
[YOU]
After that,
Chika met a piano player
visiting from Tokyo,
and shared her big dream
of becoming a School Idol!
[RIKO]
Let go of me! Get off!
[CHIKA] I wanted to do
this with my own friends.
[YOU] In order have a school
idol group, Chika has to find
a student who can compose
music for the group.
And wouldn't ya know it?
Riko, the girl she met by the
sea, transferred to our school!
[CHIKA]
It's a miracle!
[ANNOUNCER 2A] Presenting
Otonokizaka High first year,
Riko Sakurauchi.
Performing, "Those Who
Return to the Sea."
[applause]
[gasping]
[AUDIENCE murmuring]
[RIKO cries]
I'm sorry.
If you'd just hear me out,
I think you'd be a great
fit for our club!
[groans]
[RIKO]
I'm sorry.
When Otonokizaka High
was about to shut down,
the school idols saved it!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[CHIKA whines]
[YOU laughs]
[CHIKA panting]
What we're really looking for
is someone who can
compose music, ya know?
[RIKO]
I'm sorry!
[CHIKA]
Wait! Ah!
Jeez. That's sad.
[laughs sheepishly]
[CHIKA]
One, two! One, two!
One, two...
[YOU]
Did you break her yet?
[CHIKA]
Nope!
But although she said no,
I know that she knows
she wants to say yes.
[YOU]
Oh, yeah?
[YOU sighs]
In the beginning,
she was like...
[RIKO]
I'm sorry!
But now it's unsure,
kind of like a...
[RIKO]
Uh. I... I'm sorry.
It's only a matter of time!
Hate to break it to ya,
but she might just be annoyed.
I'm not too worried.
If worse comes to worse,
leave it to me!
I've got this!
Well... You can teach yourself,
but I'd like to do this
before we're old ladies.
So how's everything
going on your end?
[YOU]
Ah-ha! I'll show you!
I don't know...
Well...?
[CHIKA]
It's pretty neat.
But it looks more like a uniform
than a school idol costume.
Do you have any
designs with skirts?
[YOU]
Sure do! Here!
[CHIKA] Ah, well, okay, but it
doesn't look like a costume.
What about something super
cute and unique, you know?
[YOU]
Oh, then you'll love this!
Here!
[CHIKA]
Why do I have a gun?
[YOU]
It's adorable!
Uh, but it might be hard
to dance in combat boots.
[YOU]
Hm?
[CHIKA]
Uh... We want to shine
when people watch us perform,
so how about something bright?
[YOU] I thought you'd say that,
so I came up with this design.
Here!
[CHIKA gasps]
Oh my gosh, it's just perfect!
[YOU]
You like it?
[CHIKA]
Can you really make this?
[YOU] Mm-hm. It'll be
super easy to sew!
Really? You're the best!
Now there's nothing that
can stand in our way!
Once again I refuse
your application!
Are you for real?!
We spoke too soon.
[DIA] I've already said that you
need five people to form a club.
And enlighten me,
have you found a composer yet?
Well the thing is,
maybe, if we believe
with our hearts,
the perfect person will
sign up for sure!
I'm not worried. I bet Mousse
didn't have it easy either
when they were first
starting out. We got this.
Have you ever heard of them?
They were the underdog group
from Otonokizaka High
who won the second Love Live!
You know, Mousse!
You must be confused.
For a moment there,
I thought you were actually
talking about Mu's.
[CHIKA, YOU]
Hm...? Uh!
[CHIKA]
Ah! Silly me!
I didn't know it was
pronounced "Muse."
[DIA]
Be quiet, you!
So rude!
She acted like I didn't know
what I was talking about.
So... you give up?
Not a chance!
We got this!
[CHIKA yelps]
You have the audacity to
use them in your pitch,
and you don't even know how
to pronounce their name?!
[YOU]
Huh?
In the world of school idols,
Mu's are like gods!
Such a mistake is sacrilege!
They're record-breaking
geniuses,
masters of their craft!
They're everything!
True legends.
Thinking you could be
like them is ridiculous.
Um. Isn't this a little close?
[CHIKA]
Oh! It's Hanamaru!
Hi-ya!
Hi! Good to see y'all!
Oh my gosh, don't you think
she's super adorable?
[gasps, growls]
[HANAMARU]
Huh?
[RUBY gasps]
I see you hiding back
there, Ruby! Hey!
[DIA] Hmph. Let me guess
how all this started.
You stumbled upon
Mu's somewhere,
and with your limited
knowledge you assumed
that you might be able
to imitate them.
No, that's not true.
Tell me. What was the first song
Mu's sang together
as a group of nine?
Any clue at all?
I don't really...
[DIA growls]
Eh! Time's up!
C'mon, a little
closer. Just a bit.
You know want it. [laughs]
[gasps]
[CHIKA]
Whoops!
So close!
Aw. We're all friends here so
there's no need to be afraid!
All right!
[RUBY screams]
[CHIKA laughs]
Got ya! Give us a hug!
[DIA]
"Bokurano Live, Keemitono Life."
AKA "Borarara."
Next up. Do you happen to
have any idea which venue
Mu's and A-RISE chose for
the second Love Live prelims?
The venue? Um.
[DIA]
Eh! Eh! Time's up!
[CHIKA gasps]
The rooftop of Akihabara's
UTX High.
It's so simple to best you
that it's actually pathetic.
Moving on. Tell me
what Mu's sang
for their encore at the
second Love Live finals.
I know that!
"Bokurawaimano Nka de"!
I wasn't finished.
How long have we had
a School Idol Club?
Well, we're starting
it this year!
You wanna join us?
[HANAMARU] Uh. I signed
up to be a library helper,
but it sounds fun, zura.
I mean... it sounds fun.
[CHIKA] I gotcha.
What about you, Ruby?
[gasps] Well... I, uh...
I'm not too sure about it.
Gotta think about my sister.
Who's your sister?
Dia is.
It makes things a
little complicated.
Ah! You gotta be kidding me.
Yeah, she's against having
a School Idol Club.
We tried everything.
I know.
[DIA] Continuing. What are the
names of the four members
skipping in the opening
choreography?
[CHIKA whines]
[DIA]
Boop, boop, boop!
--Err! Time's up!
--[PA system screeching]
[STUDENTS gasping]
[DIA]
Eli Ayase, Nozomi Tojo,
Rin Hoshizora,
and Maki Nishikino.
The fact you don't know
that is embarrassing.
[CHIKA]
I... I guess it is.
Wow, so you're like a huge
Mu's fan, aren't you?
[DIA]
That should go without saying.
Obviously I know what I'm--
Uh! Uh... Th-This
kind of information
is general knowledge!
[BOTH chuckle]
Well, regardless!
I will never approve
a School Idol Club!
[YOU]
Okay.
We should change tactics and get
more of our materials together.
She'd have to take us seriously!
I'll try anything.
Wait a second, didn't
we just miss your stop?
No. I have to drop off a
notebook in Numazu today.
What for?
[HANAMARU]
Well,
it started on the
first day of school.
To those of you clinging
to your weak mortal coils,
Yohane offers the
deal of a lifetime.
As my demons... Heh, heh.
Crap!
[HANAMARU]
It was weird.
And I haven't seen her
at school since then!
Looks like you're stuck!
[CHIKA panting]
See you!
How are you doing, Riko?
[gasps]
[exhales]
[footsteps]
[CHIKA]
Let's see here.
You're not gonna try to
jump in again, are you?
No, I'm not!
That's a relief.
Well then... You need
to know that even though
you followed me here,
my answer won't change.
Huh? Oh, I know that!
I was just saying hiya!
So anyway, the ocean. Have
you figured the sound out yet?
[CHIKA] In that case,
are you free on Sunday?
Think so.
[CHIKA]
If you come here around noon,
you might hear it.
The special sound
you're looking for.
And if that happens you'll force
me to become a school idol?
[CHIKA]
Ah. I totally would if I could.
But it'd be better if
you wanted to join.
Ya know?
[RIKO]
Really?
Look, you don't know anything
about school idols,
but I'd love the
chance to show you.
And who knows?
Maybe you'd like it!
Is that okay?
[sighs] Remember back
when we first met,
I told you that I play piano?
[CHIKA]
Mm-hm.
[RIKO] I've loved music
since I was a little girl.
But lately, despite my attempts,
I'm not improving.
I haven't even had
the motivation to play.
I thought a change of
scenery would inspire me.
If I could hear the ocean,
I thought maybe
something would change.
[CHIKA]
Something is going to change.
How can you be so sure?
No idea! I can just
feel it in my heart.
You're really strange, but nice.
Thanks, Chika.
But I don't really have the
time to be a school idol.
I'm sorry.
Uh?
It's okay!
But, I still wanna help you find
the sound you're looking for.
I have a few ideas
that might help you out.
[RIKO]
Huh?
Would you be okay with that?
I've never met
someone like you.
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[KANAN] So, you transferred
from Otonokizaka High?
[CHIKA] Can you believe it?
The school Mu's is from!
[RIKO]
Is that a big deal?
[KANAN]
Well, to a lot of people!
[RIKO]
Imagine...
[KANAN] Human ears can't
hear well underwater,
but I think diving will give
you another perspective.
Pretend that your body is
an actual part of the ocean.
It's so peaceful down there,
it'll be like a completely
different world.
So, you're telling me
just to use my imagination?
Yup, that's exactly
what I'm saying.
Can you do it?
[RIKO]
I'll try.
[gasping]
[YOU]
Anything?
I haven't heard it yet.
It might take some time.
You're diving for inspiration.
[RIKO] True. I didn't expect
it to be so dark down there.
Tough to see?
Let's go!
We can all dive together
one more time.
[splashing]
[piano plays]
Did you hear it?
Yes.
Call me crazy, but I
think I heard it too.
[YOU]
So did I! It was beautiful!
[ALL laughing]
[bell tolls]
What?! No way!
Are you for real?
I am.
I can't believe
this is happening.
Thank you so much!
[CHIKA yelps]
Hold up.
I need to be clear about this.
What?
I'm saying that I can help
you write a few songs
if you need me to.
But I'm not signing up
to be a school idol.
Aw...
I don't have the time for it.
Okay.
We can't force her to, ya know.
Yeah, don't remind me.
Now just give me
the lines, please.
What lines?
[CHIKA]
Lines?
We have lines?
Lines...
Sorry, what lines?
[YOU] ♪ She'll provide
the music for us to sing ♪
♪ if we only give
her the lyrics! ♪
--So, lyrics.
--Oh. Lyrics.
This place?
I thought this was an inn!
Yep, it is!
[YOU]
This is a great place to relax!
Plus, there's a bus stop nearby,
so getting home is a cinch!
[SHIMA]
Welcome, girls! Come right in!
You, you get cuter everyday!
[YOU]
Aw! [laughs]
So, Is this the girl you
were telling me about?
[CHIKA]
Mm-hm! Say hello to Shima!
[gasps] I'm Riko Sakurauchi.
[SHIMA]
It's nice to meet you.
She's so pretty!
[CHIKA]
I think so, too! She looks like
one of those Tokyo fashion
models, doesn't she?
[SHIMA]
Absolutely.
There's not much here today,
but make yourselves at home.
[MITO]
Mm. Hey, Chika!
[CHIKA]
What's up, Mito?
Wait, is that my pudding?!
It totally is!
[SHIITAKE barks]
[RIKO shrieks]
[CHIKA]
Gimme back my pudding!
[SHIITAKE howling]
[CHIKA] How am I supposed
to focus on our work when
the special pudding Shima bought
just for me was devoured.
Is that even legal?
Why don't we start
on the lyrics?
We can't let food go to
waste! Ya snooze, ya lose!
Oh, shut up!
[gasps]
Okay, you asked for it!
Uh...
Guess I missed...
[ALL gasp]
[RIKO]
Excuse us.
Now, let's get started.
Oh my gosh, I can't believe
you got a smartphone, finally!
I know. I just got it!
So cool!
[CHIKA, YOU grunt]
[MITO]
Run, Shiitake!
[SHIITAKE barks]
[RIKO] We're going to start
working on lyrics right now.
[BOTH whimper]
Kay!
Maybe a love song is too
complicated to start with.
No, we just need something great
like Mu's "Snow halation".
It's hard to write about love
when you have no
experience with it.
I've totally been
in love before!
You have?
[CHIKA grumbles]
Well, not really.
I figured. We need
to write what we know.
You know what? I wonder
if that means that one
of the members of Mu's was in
love when they wrote that song.
I would've never
thought about it!
I have to look it up.
[RIKO] Isn't there another time
you could be doing that?
We're working here.
I'm sorry, but I have to know.
[RIKO]
Uh...
Oh, Chika.
She's absolutely in love
with school idols, isn't she?
Seems like it. [gasps]
[gasps]
What is it?
You have experience
with love after all.
Why don't you try
writing lyrics
using your special feelings
for school idols?
Your first passion isn't
for another person...
[RIKO]
...it's for Mu's!
[CHIKA gasps]
Yeah, you're so right!
I could write a million songs
about my love for them!
Okay! First, I'm gonna
write all about how
bright they shine
as a group!
[PIANO TEACHER] Riko,
you're such a good pianist!
[RIKO] Thank you!
I feel like I'm flying
through the air when my
hands are on the keys.
And I feel sparkly.
Like the stars!
I love it so much!
[CHIKA]
Here!
[RIKO gasps]
You're done already?
It's not mine, but... this song
touched my heart so much
I had to write it down.
[RIKO]
"Yume no Tobira."
[CHIKA] Yep! The second
I heard it, I was hooked!
Then and there I decided,
I had to help other people
feel the same joy I felt!
You really want to give joy?
Yep!
I hadn't ever been inspired to
work toward anything before.
But even I can make miracles!
I'm learning to work hard
and put in the effort.
It sounds crazy, but
this'll bring out my best.
So I can shine!
Mu's has done a lot for you.
[CHIKA]
Uh. Mm-hm! I really love them!
[CHIKA] They were just
average high schoolers.
But when they all worked
together on that stage,
they shined like the sun!
I realized school idols were...
Well, they were... they
were so incredibly radiant!
[RIKO whimpering]
[AUDIENCE murmuring]
[piano plays]
[singing in Japanese]
[singing continues]
[CHIKA gasping]
[RIKO]
Chika?
Well, hey there, neighbor!
I can't believe you
live right next door!
[RIKO]
Yeah, me neither.
We only just moved in,
so I had no idea!
Were you playing the
song, "Yume no Tobira"?
[RIKO]
Huh?
I could hear you singing
through the window.
No! Well, maybe.
[CHIKA]
Don't you love the words?
"I've been looking for
the door of dreams."
[RIKO]
Yes. They're nice.
It means so much to me I
could listen to it all night!
It's from the second Love Live--
[RIKO]
Listen...
[CHIKA]
Uh. Huh?
[RIKO]
I'm bored.
Nothing is fun anymore.
'Cause my passions
aren't making me happy.
And I've been trying so hard.
One more time.
Would you wanna...
become a school idol?
I can't.
There's no way I that I could
give up playing the piano.
You don't have to!
But try something fresh.
It could inspire you
in a whole new way.
Then you can go back
to what you love!
It's not fair.
Becoming a school
idol is your dream.
And I'd be using it just
for motivation, you know?
[CHIKA] If it helps you at all,
it'll be worth it.
That's why I'm doing this.
Listen. Find your joy!
That's what being a
school idol is all about!
[gasping]
Uh! Chika!
I have faith!
I know in my heart this
is the right thing to do!
[BOTH grunting]
Uh. That's far enough.
We aren't able to reach, so--
Riko! Don't quit!
[RIKO]
Uh.
[BOTH grunting]
[RIKO laughs]
[CHIKA laughs]
[CHIKA, YOU, RIKO]
Next time, "First step!"