[RUBY]
Previously on,
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[RUBY]
Chika invited me and Hanamaru
to join the newly approved
School Idol Club.
[CHIKA] I know you two would
shine so bright on stage!
[RUBY]
I really wanted to do it,
but I was worried about what
my sister would think.
Then Hanamaru told me...
[HANAMARU] Isn't that something
you'd really like?
In that case,
this is your chance to shine!
[RUBY] So I joined!
And Hanamaru did, too!
[CHIKA] Nobody really knows if
they can or can't do something
they like. Where's the fun
if you don't try though?
[RUBY]
And just like that,
Aqours had five members!
[YOSHIKO]
I feel it.
There's a rift in the spiritual
barriers between our worlds.
The magical balance
has been altered.
The fate of this humble
planet now depends on
a divine decision from
the heavens above.
Now behold the Fallen
Angel, Yohane,
descended to this dark world to
foresee all, the chosen vessel!
Come and join the
ranks of my demons!
Gain true power!
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
Yes, I did it, hooray!
What's with Yohane?!
Who is this fallen angel?!
What about her demon followers?!
Do those things really exist?!
Yeah, right!
[YOSHIKO panting]
Oh, get it together, Yoshiko!
You're in high school now!
You're way too old
for this nonsense.
But your only alternative
is facing reality.
Can you shoulder a
burden that heavy?
Yes, of course!
I can handle anything!
To those of you clinging
to your weak mortal coils,
Yohane offers the deal
of a lifetime.
As my demons. Heh, heh.
[YOSHIKO cries] I can't believe
I actually said that!
I'm never going back to school!
[YOU] Oh... We've barely
moved up at all!
[RIKO] Come on, it's
better than yesterday
when we were
in 4,856th place.
[YOU]
I guess.
At least we're not
dropping in rank.
From what I saw online, our
songs are getting good reviews.
Not to mention, people think
our two newest members
are beyond cute!
Does it really say that?!
You betcha!
And it seems Hanamaru
is especially popular.
[RIKO] Yeah, "I'll be
cheering for Hanamaru."
[YOU] "I hope she sings
as pretty as she looks.
Can't wait to hear!"
[CHIKA]
See? See?
You guys are a hit!
Wait! So this thing's
a computer?
For real?!
I read about this.
is it true you can connect
to the internet and then
gain access to an entire
sea of knowledge?
Yeah, it's true.
Except it's more like a sea
of adorable cat videos.
Wow!
[RUBY laughs]
Okay, has she seriously never
seen a computer before?
Actually, she lives in
this super ancient temple
and they're kinda lacking
in technological stuff.
That makes sense.
You should have seen her
at Numazu the other day.
Whoa.
How in the heck are you supposed
to turn on this faucet, zura?
[gasping]
It's the future!
Ruby, it's the future!
I love Numazu!
Yeah...
Can I please touch it?
[CHIKA]
Uh, sure.
[gasping]
Huh?
Zura!
[ALL gasping]
Wait. What button did
you press just now?
Oh, ah...
Well, there was one that
was glowin' really brightly
so I kinda sorta pushed it.
You, Is it okay?
[YOU] I hope I saved the file
for our costumes!
[HANAMARU]
Uh, sorry.
It was an accident! I didn't
mean to mess it all up.
[laughs] Don't worry,
it'll be okay.
[HANAMARU whimpers]
[HANAMARU] Wow! It really
is a sea of knowledge.
Everyone must know
everything now, huh?
Yeah!
And to switch to the other
window you just click here.
So cool, zura!
Hey. Aren't we supposed
to be practicing?
I think it can wait
a few more minutes.
Besides, I'm more worried
about how we're gonna
increase our ranking.
It'll be tough with so many
other school idols out there.
Especially with us living way
out here in the boonies!
We're plain and we're boring!
The Queens of Average!
All hail the Queens of Average.
I don't understand why we
have to stand out though.
'Cause it'll help
our popularity.
What can we do to set
ourselves apart?
Let's see...
Here's a thought. Maybe we could
try changing our group name
to something a little
more eccentric?
That "Something" being
"The Three Mermaids"?
Oh, wait it's five now!
"The Five Mermaids"
would be adorable!
[ALL giggling]
Come swimming with us!
[ALL]
For we are "The Five Mermaids"!
Would you please stop
bringing that up?!
But dancing in those
fins would be tough.
I know, I know!
We'll tell them to cheer for us
so our fins will turn into legs!
[CHIKA] Oh my gosh yes,
that's an awesome idea!
But in exchange for them, we'll
have to give up our voices.
But we need those!
Enough with the stupid
mermaid ideas, all right?
Truly, "The Little Mermaid"
is a tragic tale.
Don't you agree?
[CHIKA]
Yes.
[RIKO]
You're just being mean!
I don't recall any of your
original ideas being any better!
[CHIKA] Yeah well, I
don't recall them being
any worse either!
Curses! I was really hoping
nobody would be up here today.
[YOU]
Does it even really matter?
S'that Yoshiko?
[gasps] Zuramaru!
Uh! Stealth mode!
[HANAMARU]
Huh...
[STUDENT 5AA]
Wanna grab a bite to eat?
[STUDENT 5BB]
Sure thing!
[YOSHIKO] No one should
be able to locate me
while I'm using my
stealth mode powers.
Well, look-ee who
we have here.
[YOSHIKO screaming]
Yeah? Well, what of it?
I just happened to
accidentally descend
from the heavens inside
the school, like you do.
It happens.
[YOSHIKO] Don't act like
everything is normal! Spill it!
What have people in class
been saying about me?
Huh?
Come on, you know what I mean!
Tell me what they're saying!
Like, "Yoshiko's so weird!"
and then like,
"She called us demons,
tee-hee!" Tell me!
[HANAMARU]
Oh...
Crap, I knew it!
Your response has confirmed
my deepest fears!
Everyone probably thinks I'm
a complete and utter nut job!
You mortals will
never understand!
I retreat. To solitude!
To tell you the truth,
I haven't heard anyone
mention a word about it.
Really! I think you're
probably overreactin' a bit.
[YOSHIKO]
I'm not!
Wait, what?
[laughs] Actually most people
are wonderin' why
you aren't comin' to school.
Seems they're worried they
did or said somethin'
to make you stay home.
Wow, really?
[HANAMARU]
Yep.
[YOSHIKO]
Is that the truth?
Do you swear on it?
Cross your heart and hope to
fall from the heavens above?
Uh. I swear.
[YOSHIKO]
Okay! It's not too late!
I can still be normal!
This is my chance
for a fresh start!
Zuramaru!
[whimpering] Is that me, zura?
Yohane has a very
special mission for you.
[STUDENT 5CC]
Good morning.
[STUDENT 5DD]
Hey there.
[STUDENTS]
Ah...
[YOSHIKO laughs]
Excellent, they've noticed me.
Like Zuramaru said,
they don't seem to remember
my previous actions.
All right!
Good morning!
[ALL]
Oh. Uh, good morning!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 5A]
It's surprising,
you seem so different
from before!
And we were super
worried about you.
Since you stopped coming
to school and all that.
I'm so sorry!
I'm glad to be back and hope we
can be friends. Sound good?
Absolutely!
I was wondering... What
was your first name again?
You don't remember?
Oh wait, I don't either.
Help us out, here! Was it, Yo...
Yo... Yoha.
Yoshiko! You can just
call me Yoshiko, okay?
Oh, sure thing!
[STUDENTS laughing]
[RUBY] Looks like
Yoshiko's finally back.
Yep!
I accepted her
special mission, zura!
What mission is that?
Monitor you?
Please accept.
You see the fallen angel
Yohane only tends to emerge
when I'm being careless.
You can help me.
Basically I'm supposed to stop
her if things get weird!
[RUBY] Like if the fallen
angel comes out?
[STUDENT 5B] Hey, what kind
of hobbies do you have?
Hobbies?
Uh... None that I can think of.
[YOSHIKO] Hold up,
I can't waste my chance
to fit in with everyone!
I'll make the class
like me even more!
Uh. Except for fortune telling.
Whoa, for real?!
Can you please tell my fortune?
Well, sure!
Let's see...
Oh!
Why don't we do it
right here, okay?
[STUDENTS laughing, cheering]
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
'Kay, I'm ready!
Here! Will you please
light the candle?
Huh?!
[YOSHIKO] Oh. Hear
me spirits that sprawl
in the heavens and underworld,
I make a proclamation to you
who dwell in purgatory.
Lucifer, who baptized Azmodeus,
join the fallen angel Yohane.
Ha!
The time has come for
you all to descend!
[YOSHIKO]
I did it again!
[exhales]
[YOSHIKO]
You were supposed to monitor me!
Now everything is
ruined! [cries]
You realize I had no
possible way of knowin'
you were carryin' that
stuff around.
What exactly happened?
I only just heard about
this myself, but...
Apparently back when she
was in middle school,
Yoshiko was convinced
she was actually
a fallen angel from heaven.
Behold mortals!
A heavenly being
stands before you!
Fallen angel, Yohane!
Would you like to
descend with me?
As it turns out,
she hasn't managed
to really break the habit yet.
[YOSHIKO]
I understand.
I know I'm not a
real fallen angel.
How could I be?
They don't even really exist.
Seriously?
So why'd you bring that weird
stuff to school with you?
[YOSHIKO]
Well, I can explain!
That "weird stuff" is crucial
to Yohane's identity.
Without those things,
I would lack the ability to
descend from the heavens!
Guh!
I'm starting to understand
you're going through
a complicated phase right now.
I'm sure it's perfectly normal.
[RUBY]
Check this out!
I did a search for her online;
it looks like she does
do fortune telling.
[CHIKA]
Oh?
[RUBY]
Uh...
[YOSHIKO] Come, descend
with Yohane once again.
[YOSHIKO screams]
Turn it off!
Look, I just wanna be a
normal high school student!
More than anything!
You gotta help me!
Zura...
You're so cute.
[RUBY, HANAMARU]
Hm?
Huh?
I found it! What
we've been missing!
I don't follow.
Listen to me, Yoshiko!
I mean... listen to me, Yohane!
Would you like to join us?
And be a school idol?
Say what?
[CHIKA]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[RIKO]
We-We're going to sing in this?
They're even shorter
than the last ones!
People are sure to see our--!
I've got shorts!
[RIKO]
Stop it, pull your skirt down!
[sighs] I just don't
know about this idea.
Don't worry! I searched the web
for fallen angel idols, and
there weren't any! We're
gonna stand out for sure.
I suppose.
These costumes are
more unique anyway.
Really unique.
I'll say. It's a
little embarrassing.
I'm not comfortable in this.
Hey, should we really be
wearing these clothes?
Much less performing in them?
Right, 'cause they're adorable!
[RIKO]
That is not what I mean.
I don't know.
No way this is gonna work.
It's going to be super awesome!
We'll go out onstage and sing,
then everyone will see how
charming a fallen angel can be!
A fallen angel can be charming?
Uh? Absolutely not!
People are just gonna think
we're a bunch of weirdos!
No, they're going to love us!
Trust me!
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[YOSHIKO]
Discarded from the very heavens,
I'm the fallen angel Yohane!
Watch me descend!
They love me! [laughs]
She's laughing.
That's probably a
good sign, right?
I guess it's decided.
[MITO] There, there,
who's a good doggie?
Hey there. How's it going?
[RIKO whimpers]
[YOU]
Hm...
[MITO]
Shiitake, no!
--[SHIITAKE barking]
--[RIKO screaming]
[CHIKA]
What's going on?
[RIKO screaming]
Get down!
Just calm down!
Shiitake won't hurt you!
[screaming]
Ow, my face!
[RIKO]
Get away!
[ALL]
Whoa, perfect form!
[SHIITAKE barks]
[RIKO groaning]
[ALL]
Wow!
[RIKO groans]
Chika!
[RIKO'S MOM]
Welcome home.
Oh, hey, Mom...
[CHIKA] I'll leave the
costumes to you, then!
Aye, aye, Chika!
[HANAMARU]
We should go, too.
[RUBY]
Have a good one! Bye-bye!
[CHIKA]
'Kay, see ya!
Ow, it's still tender.
I bet!
I'm glad you think
it's so funny.
You'd better put that dog up
the next time I'm over there!
[CHIKA]
Yeah, yeah. [laughs]
Oh jeez. Do you always
laugh at your friends
when they're really distressed?
Well, no, not usually.
I was really just thinking about
how different we all are!
Uh?
I'm super happy that we started
the School Idol Club together.
It's hard to believe,
but I used to think we
were normal and boring.
Are you still obsessing
over that?
[CHIKA] I can't help it!
This whole thing was my idea,
so I feel I gotta
take responsibility.
But deep down, I know I lack
the necessary leadership skills
to run this group on my own.
Wow, Chika...
But the more I get
to know everyone,
the more I see how
unique we are!
Each of us has her own
personality and charm.
We're anything but ordinary,
and I think we're very special.
Together, I know we can
shine the brightest!
I always knew you were a weirdo.
[yelps]
I've thought that since the
day I met you at the harbor.
Wait a sec, are you
complimenting me
or insulting me?
Maybe both.
What?! You can't do
both at the same time!
Anyway, Chika, let's
continue to do our best.
We're going to show everybody
what a bunch of normal girls
like us are capable of, right?
[gasps] I still feel like you're
insulting me, but okay.
[RIKO]
Bet I can beat you back home!
[CHIKA] No fair, cheater!
Uh oh, watch out for Shiitake!
[RIKO]
Uh?!
[CHIKA]
Made ya look! [laughs]
Now... The prophesied angel has
fallen upon the beaches of Izu,
to say hello!
Join with Yohane, and descend!
[ALL]
Please join us!
[RIKO]
I can't believe I did that.
[CHIKA]
Well, You? Whaddya think?
We're about to see.
[computer chimes]
[CHIKA]
No way!
Our rank just jumped way up!
That crazy idea really worked?
Check out all the new
comments! Yay, us!
[YOU
"I'd fall for Ruby any day."
[HANAMARU]
"Ruby is adorable."
[RIKO] "Ruby looks so great in
her cute little mini-skirt."
[RUBY]
"I love Ruby's smile."
[gasping] Oh, I'm flattered!
Hi, I'm the fourth demon
under Lady Yohane.
I'm...
I'm Ruby Kurosawa.
As the littlest demon
of our group, it's...
...nice to meet ya!
Oh! What an adorable bella !
[DIA] Adorable?
It's far from adorable!
It's shameless! It's disgusting!
Come on, they're only
stage costumes, right?
We were just acting!
This is exactly why I was
opposed to this whole idea!
That's enough! The only
reason I even permitted
my sister to join this
ridiculous School Idol Club
was because I never knew
that the group would...
Well, dress her up in that
travesty of a costume!
But, I'm really sorry, Dia.
Besides... Doing demeaning
things to raise your rank
is insulting and I
will not allow it!
Those sorts of actions will not
be tolerated in the future!
But still, our goal was to
raise our rank and we did.
You may have raised it,
but only temporarily.
Such basic methods will never
yield long lasting results.
[gasping, sighs]
Huh?!
[DIA] If you're truly serious
about being idols,
you should rethink
your strategy.
[CHIKA]
Yes ma'am.
That was a bust.
The president really hit the
nail on the head, didn't she?
We insulted Mu's by
dressing up like that.
It's just plain rude of us.
You can't blame yourself
for this, Chika!
[YOSHIKO]
She's right.
[ALL]
Mm?
[YOSHIKO]
Blame Yohane.
It's her fault.
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Honestly, I should have dropped
this act a long time ago.
Yoshiko!
[YOSHIKO]
It's true!
And, it's okay.
Starting tomorrow, I can finally
be a normal high schooler.
[RUBY] But, what about
being a school idol?
[YOSHIKO]
Mm... I think I'll pass.
I don't want to cause
you guys trouble. Bye!
Even though it was only for a
little while, I appreciate you
playing along with the
fallen angel thing.
It was fun, really.
I wonder why she wanted
to be a fallen angel?
[HANAMARU] I know.
Or at least I can guess.
I think it's because she was
probably always normal...
...like the rest of us.
She never really
stood out before.
[HANAMARU] Have you ever asked
yourself that question?
"Is this the real me, or am I
meant to be somethin' more?
Maybe I was once
a sparkling angel,
but now I'm stuck on Earth."
I think Yoshiko just wanted
to feel like she was special.
I mean, don't we all?
I see.
I can understand that feeling;
it makes perfect sense.
When we were in
kindergarten together,
Yoshiko used to say...
[YOSHIKO] Did you know I'm
really an angel from heaven?
One day I'm gonna
grow some wings!
Then I'll soar through the sky!
Zura!
Yeah.
This is how it should be.
[CHIKA]
Hey, Fallen Angel Yohane.
[YOSHIKO]
Huh?
[ALL] Please, join our club
and become a school idol!
[YOSHIKO]
Uh...? Huh?
[CHIKA laughs]
Come on, you heard us!
Join our group!
We'd love to have
Yohane on board!
What are talking about?
Didn't you hear me yesterday?
I...
We don't care! Just be you!
Even if that means
being a fallen angel!
I'm sorry!
[ALL gasp]
Wait!
I made the student council
president mad at us!
[CHIKA]
No!
It was my fault for not
thinking things through!
You're fine the way
you are, Yoshiko!
Trust me!
[YOSHIKO]
What does that even mean?!
Excuse me, ma'am!
[YOSHIKO]
Go away!
[CHIKA]
You know what?
I think I understand how
Mu's became so legendary!
I get how they connected
school idols the way they did!
At least hear me out, please!
[YOSHIKO]
Stop! Just cut it out already!
[ALL panting]
[CHIKA] When they were on
stage, they showed everyone
exactly what they loved
without any hesitation.
[pants] It didn't matter what
others might think of them,
or how popular they
might become,
'cause the most important thing
is to show your favorite self!
Your shining self!
Don't let it go!
You have to love every single
part of yourself, Yoshiko!
Including Yohane,
the Fallen Angel!
You sure? I might say
weird stuff again.
That's okay.
And there might be some times
when I perform rituals.
I think we can probably
manage a few.
What if I order you
to become my demons?
Well, let's see...
I guess, If I don't like it,
I can always refuse.
Uh?
[gasps]
Come with us.
[CHIKA laughs]
[YOSHIKO laughs]
[DIA]
Mari!
That's me! Can I help you?
What is the meaning
of your e-mail?!
You don't know?
I like totally made
it crystal clear.
[DIA]
No way.
You have got to be kidding!
[GIRLS]
Next time, "Let's make a PV!"