[MARI]
Huh?
[KANAN]
I'm sorry.
But I quit.
I'm done being an idol.
[MARI]
Why?
Because of Tokyo?
Listen, it's no problema !
[KANAN] Mari, don't you have
the chance to study abroad?
You should really go.
No way. Are you
serious right now?
We've already talked about this,
and I decided to stay
here at Uranohoshi.
Come on, Dia, back me up!
Say something.
[KANAN]
She agrees with me.
There's no point in continuing.
[MARI]
Kanan! Dia!
It's time to move on.
Oh, boy. The festival!
[HANAMARU] I wanna visit
the yummy food stalls, zura!
Oh, what an amazing
bench this is!
In the name of Yohane I
claim thee as my perch!
What do we do with here?
We got back from Tokyo and she's
stuck in fallen angel mode.
[HANAMARU]
Just leave her alone.
Where's Shiitake?
Hopefully that crazy dog
is put up somewhere.
Hey Chika, what are we going
to do for the summer festival?
Excellent question
as always, You.
Let me think on it a bit.
Well, Numazu's fireworks
show's pretty cool.
I can't believe they want
us to perform there.
It could be a good opportunity.
Not to mention it's also a great
way to get our name out there.
That's true.
But it's so soon it doesn't
leave us much time to practice.
We should be fine.
We'll just have to focus
and make whatever practices
we do have count.
[YOU]
Whatcha think, Chika?
[footsteps]
[CHIKA]
'Kay!
Let's work hard to
be really awesome!
You got it!
Yeah, we're with you!
I say we go on that stage and
shine as bright as we can!
And if that's still not enough,
then we'll work even harder!
Rinse and repeat and
we're sure to succeed!
Aye-aye, Cap'n!
We promise to do our Rubesty!
I'm proud of her, aren't you?
Yes.
[RUBY shrieks]
[YOSHIKO] You can't outrun
your divine fate...
[HANAMARU] No thanks,
I just wanna eat, zura!
[RUBY]
Don't leave me!
[KANAN]
Hm? Oh, hey.
Keep up the good work!
Hold on, tell me something!
Were you a school idol?
[KANAN]
Talk about nosy.
I used to be.
[YOU]
What's wrong?
It's Kanan.
I just don't understand why she
quit being a school idol.
I thought the president
already explained it.
She froze up and couldn't sing
when they were in
Tokyo or something.
[CHIKA]
That's what she said,
but it's not like Kanan
to give up so easily.
[RIKO]
Oh, really?
Yeah. I've known her
since we were kids
and she was always
super strong.
[KANAN] Come on,
don't be chicken, Chika!
You gotta be brave
or you'll regret it.
Listen, I know you can do it!
[CHIKA whimpers]
Jump!
--[CHIKA yelps]
--[splash]
[RIKO]
So that's how she is.
But looking at her now, she
seems so distant and stuff.
Oopsie! How rude of me.
[YOSHIKO]
I've got it!
She's been possessed
by a powerful demon!
Talk about a head scratcher.
It'd be so much easier
if I knew more about when
she was a school idol.
Maybe, but we'll never know
since she won't talk about it.
[ALL]
Huh?
[RUBY yelps]
Hey, Ruby. Did you hear
anything from Dia about Kanan?
Have you ever overhead
them talking?
She's your sister and
you live together.
You've got to know something.
[whimpering]
[RUBY]
Sorry!
Uh-oh, there she goes!
[YOSHIKO]
I'm on it!
Check out Yohane's
secret technique!
Fallen Dragon Phoenix Hold!
[YOSHIKO grunts]
No weird holds, zura.
Right.
Whoa, no kidding?
I don't know all the details,
but I'm pretty sure
the Tokyo performance
is what started this whole mess.
Because when Dia got
back from their trip,
she suddenly didn't wanna
talk about school idols.
There's more.
[ALL]
Like what?
[laughs nervously]
[DIA] Are you insinuating
that I'm running away?
Because I'm not.
And don't you even dare try to
say that about Kanan, either.
[RUBY]
So, yeah.
She thought they
were running away?
Why?
[KANAN grunting]
Okay!
[yawns] I'm so sleepy.
[RUBY] Why would anyone
wanna get up so early?
[RIKO]
I don't know about this.
I'm pretty sure she's gonna
notice us if we all follow her!
[YOU] Maybe, but everyone
wanted to come along.
[CHIKA]
Wow, she runs kinda fast!
[YOSHIKO] Ow! My legs
are starting to cramp up!
[YOU]
Girl's got some major stamina.
[HANAMARU]
Please, go on without me, zura!
[RUBY]
Eek, idol down!
[CHIKA] Is it just me, or does
it look like she's having fun?
[RIKO]
I guess.
[ALL panting]
How beautiful!
[clapping]
I saw your re-enrollment letter
for school, welcome back.
Thank you.
[MARI] So are you finally
done running away, then?
Let me be perfectly clear.
I took a break from school
so I could help run the shop
while dad's leg healed.
But just because I'm back
doesn't mean I'll become
a school idol again.
Failure never used
to hold you back.
The Kanan I knew would never
run from her feelings,
she'd keep going and
fight for her dreams.
And she'd do it with a
big smile on her face.
[KANAN] Is that a fact?
We graduate in less than a year.
We'll have to make
the most of our time!
Plus, we have a bunch
of new members now.
[ALL gasp]
That's great, you should
let them handle things.
Seriously?
Why did even you
even come back?
Know what? I wish that you
would have stayed overseas.
Kanan...
Heh. Some things never change,
you're still so stubborn.
[KANAN]
That's enough.
[gasps]
Stop it. You're such a nuisance.
Just leave me alone.
Uh...
[GIRLS panting]
[RUBY]
How mean.
[HANAMARU]
I know, poor her, zura.
[YOU] Seems like there's
a lot more going on there.
[CHIKA]
Yeah.
She asked if she was
"finally done running away".
[CHIKA]
Huh?
Oh. It's probably nothing!
[bell chimes]
[CHIKA]
Kanan's back today?
[YOU] Yep! At least that's
what I heard anyway.
I wonder how that
makes Mari feel.
Dunno, I hope they're
okay though.
[ALL sigh]
Welcome back!
Uh?
[YOU]
No way. A uniform!
[BOTH]
Girl overboard!
[YOU gasping]
[CHIKA, RIKO sigh]
[CHIKA]
Whoa, is that...
[YOU]
...a school idol costume.
[RUBY, HANAMARU gasping]
[KANAN grunting]
Let go!
You're being ridiculous!
[MARI] I'm not letting go
until you say yes!
Besides, you're the one
that's being ridiculous!
I mean you're totally
freaking out
over one teensy little failure!
I am not! Why can't
you just drop it?!
It's been two whole
years, already!
Get it through your thick skull
that we can't be idols anymore!
Like I keep saying,
we're third years now!
Both of you, cut it out!
You're acting like children!
Come on Dia, whose
side are you on?
No one's side!
But you can't force Kanan to
change her mind and go back to
being a school idol, no matter
how much you wish she would!
[MARI]
Why not?!
Why are you both so eager to
give up your school idol dreams?
Chika-chi and Aqours didn't!
They didn't give up when they
failed, so why are you?!
[KANAN]
Don't compare me to Chika!
Wait, come back!
[KANAN] Why don't you quit being
so pushy all the time?
I'm tired of your games!
Chika?
[CHIKA grunts]
Stop fighting!
Now!
[CHIKA] We get it! You guys
had a fight or whatever!
But the way you're acting's
so... so... dumb!
Mm! It's so dumb!
Just talk it out already!
It's none of your business!
[CHIKA]
Yes, it is!
I beg your pardon?
[CHIKA] This affects all of us!
I want all three of you
to report to the clubroom
after school today!
Well, but we--
It wasn't a request.
[KANAN, MARI, DIA]
Okay.
Chika's officially the coolest.
She really put them
in their place!
[CHIKA]
Uh...
Look, we froze up in Tokyo and
couldn't sing, end of story!
Yeah, Dia already told us
about what happened there.
But you've never
been one to give up
just because of a
little set back.
[MARI]
Sì ! That's right!
Which is what I've
said all along!
This whole thing is
totally suspicious!
You wanna tell us what's
really going on?
Kanan...?
I already told you.
We couldn't perform.
Sorry, but there's nothing
else to tell, okay?
[groans] So annoying!
I could not agree more!
This stupid attitude of yours
is totally ticking me off!
I wouldn't let it bother you too
much, the feeling's mutual.
What's strange is I could
swear I saw her dancing
at Benten Island the other day.
[KANAN grunts]
[HANAMARU]
Zura!
Uh-oh! You're like, way rosso !
No, I am not!
[MARI]
You know what I think?
I think you miss it!
[gasps]
All right, enough.
You're wrong about me.
I was tired of being a school
idol, that's why I quit!
I'm not joining you.
Stop hounding me.
[YOU]
Good grief...
[RIKO]
Dia.
[DIA gasps]
Is there something
you're not telling us?
Me? No, why on earth
would you think that?
For one, the look on your face.
And two, the look that's
still on your face.
Oh well, you must be mistaken.
[screams]
Go, Yoshiko!
[YOSHIKO]
On it!
--[YOSHIKO grunts]
--[DIA screaming]
Where do you think
you're going?
[RUBY]
Dia...
[HANAMARU]
Must run in the family, zura.
[DIA groans]
[ALL]
It was on purpose?
[DIA] Yes. It wasn't that
Kanan couldn't sing
and she didn't freeze up either.
Her acts were intentional.
[MARI]
But why?
Obviously a curse--
[HANAMARU grunting]
The truth is,
she did it for you.
What do you mean?
You can't really
be that forgetful.
You accidentally hurt your ankle
right before our show, remember?
[AUDIENCE chattering]
[MARI groaning]
Are you sure you're all right?
Yep, I'm good!
[grunts]
Kanan, let's do this thing!
Uh? Are you okay?
But I don't understand
what my ankle has to do
with her faking stage fright.
Because what exactly do you
think would have happened
if we had gone on stage?
It could've gotten worse.
You could have done
permanent damage.
That can't be.
[RUBY] So she didn't
run away after all.
What happened afterwards?
I mean yeah, it seems like you
could have just picked back up
after Mari's injury
had time to heal.
[MARI]
Chika's right.
We could have prepared
for the fireworks show.
We could have made a new song,
perfected our routine.
There's so much more
we could have done!
But we didn't.
We were worried
about your future.
Every time talk of
transferring schools
or studying abroad popped up,
you would turn down
the opportunity.
Of course I turned it down!
[ALL gasp]
[DIA] Kanan felt like we
were holding you back.
Try to look at it from
her point of view.
What kind of friends would
continue to let you waste
opportunities like those?
She... just wanted
the best for you.
[TEACHER 9A]
You should at least consider it.
Your parents and the school are
both in agreement on the matter.
If you were to
graduate overseas,
getting into college
would be a cinch.
Nah, I'll pass.
And besides, I can't since
I'm a school idol now!
We want to save this place!
[MARI]
You're kidding?
So that's why.
[DIA]
Where are you going?
I'm gonna slug her!
Because she just... 'cause she
should have told me the truth!
You're so selfish.
All Kanan has ever done is worry
about you and your well-being.
[DIA]
About how you fit in.
About your feelings.
[DIA]
And...
...about your future.
[DIA]
She cares more than anyone.
[MARI]
How would I know that?!
She never bothered to tell me!
[DIA]
She showed you all the time.
You just never
bothered to see it.
[MARI grunting]
She did.
[MARI]
Huh?
[KANAN] Were you listening
to anything I said?
Even if you had to move again,
I'd never forget about you.
Kanan...
Stupid.
[KANAN]
Mari?
[MARI] It's time we settled
this once and for all.
[splash]
[MARI]
Why didn't tell me back then?
You should have told me
what you were feeling!
I wanted to look out for
you like you did for me,
because that's what friends
are supposed to do!
[MARI] I didn't care about
my future back then.
Studying abroad?
Why would I care about
such a silly thing?
You couldn't sing.
You couldn't sing, Kanan,
and I couldn't let that go!
I thought you needed me!
[gasps]
Listen.
I care about you
more than anything!
Don't forget that.
If that's true...
If that's honestly how
you feel deep inside,
then say it!
Stop making it all
about winning Love Live!
Be real with me!
[MARI]
You're right.
[KANAN]
Uh?
So, go ahead.
[MARI whimpers]
[DIA] We'll be in so much
trouble if we get caught!
[KANAN]
Don't worry!
Huh?
[DIA shrieks]
[laughs]
[MARI]
Who are you?
Um, hug!
Uh?
Hug me!
Hug me.
[cries]
[BOTH crying]
[CHIKA laughs]
You care for them a lot.
I think I might be starting
to figure you out!
That may be,
but you're going to have to
take care of them from now on.
Oh and fair warning, they're
a pretty sensitive pair.
Maybe I should keep you
around since you're the expert.
Wait, what?
I don't have time
to be in any clubs.
I'm far too busy with
the student council.
Oh, stop making up excuses!
Now that we have Mari and Kanan,
we only need one more person
to make Aqours perfect.
[DIA]
Ruby?
We made this especially
for you, Sis!
Consider it your
welcome present!
[music plays]
[singing in Japanese]
[KANAN laughs]
So Aqours, huh?
[YOU]
Hm? Yeah, what's so funny?
When we had our
school idol group,
it happened to also
be called Aqours.
Whoa! That's super crazy.
[RIKO]
Yes, what a coincidence.
[KANAN] Well, I suppose it
could be a coincidence.
[YOU]
Wait...
[ALL]
Mm?
[KANAN] But I think... It's more
likely that a certain someone
was playing us like fiddles.
[RIKO] Oh my gosh,
I said to forget about it!
[CHIKA]
Okay!
[KANAN]
But I won't name names.
[YOU]
Aqours?
[ALL] Next time,
"We've got Stewshine!"