[CHIKA gasping]
[SARAH] Saint Snow is
about to take the stage.
I hope you'll enjoy the show.
[EVENT STAFF 7A]
All righty!
Time to jam with our
first school idol group!
It's Saint Snow!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[CHIKA grunts]
[music plays]
[singing in Japanese]
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[EVENT STAFF 7A]
Give it up for Saint Snow!
Now this next group has
really made a splash
in the school idol world.
Everyone say hello to Aqours!
You ready?
[gasps]
[CROWD chattering]
[RIKO] You know, there are
more than 13 million people
living in this city.
[YOU]
Wow. That's a lot.
It can be overwhelming.
I can't wrap my mind around
the thought of so many.
It seems huge compared
to where we're from.
Can't believe you lived
in a place like this.
[HANAMARU] Buildings as
far as the eye can see.
[RUBY]
Is that Mt. Fuji back there?
[HANAMARU]
Zura.
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
[ALL]
Mm?
[YOSHIKO]
Finally, the time has come.
I shall summon the underworld,
and release an ancient evil unto
an unsuspecting metropolis!
So cool!
It looks like you're having
a lot of fun, Yoshiko.
Right now I'm Yohane! Yo-ha-ne!
[HANAMARU]
You wanna keep bein' Yohane
even though the
show's over, zura?
[CHIKA]
Looky what I've got!
Well? Better grab 'em
while they're cold!
Which one would ya like?
Are you okay?
Everybody gets their own flavor!
Here! Give it a try!
Uh... Um, sure.
[CHIKA]
Yum! This one's yours, Ruby!
Uh? Thank you, Chika!
[CHIKA]
You were amazing today, ladies.
We should be proud.
And know what?
That show was like
the best we've done!
Our voices were really strong
and we didn't even make
that many mistakes!
We're new to this, ya know?
It's crazy to see how far
we've come! I'm happy!
I mean, think about it!
All those other groups have
been at Love Live before!
It's no wonder we didn't
win the competition!
That's true.
But if we want to qualify
for Love Live,
then we have to
push even harder.
We need to be as good as
those other groups were.
Well, I guess you
have a point there.
[YOU]
Riko is right.
I realized it when we
watched Saint Snow.
That's what top level
school idols are like.
We're not there yet.
Not even close.
They're great, and they
didn't win the competition.
If we were as good as they are,
it still wouldn't be enough.
[RUBY]
Yeah. I think I agree.
[HANAMARU]
Me, too.
Well, I think you're wrong.
An evil power
distorted our talents
so we'd seem lackluster
next to everyone else!
Why didn't you stop
it from happening?
Yeah, you didn't
even us warn us!
I didn't foresee it, okay?
Sweet of you to say all
that just to cheer us up!
I wasn't!
I was just t distracting
you! It worked!
[CHIKA]
She's right!
[ALL]
Uh?
We don't need to be so negative.
Let's stop worrying about it!
Look at us! We're in Tokyo!
We should be out exploring
and having fun!
--[phone rings]
--[BOTH] Huh?
This is Chika.
Huh? No. We haven't
left the area yet.
Sorry about having to call you
ladies all the way back here.
I didn't know you were leaving
or I would've given
this to you sooner.
Wonder what's in it.
Could it be... paychecks?
[HANAMARU]
You wish.
Huh?
Take it. Remember the winners
were all picked based
on the audience's votes.
These are the results.
[CHIKA]
Oh, thanks a lot!
[EVENT STAFF 7A]
No problem.
You know, to be honest,
I wasn't sure what
to do with them.
But in the end,
we decided to hand them out
to all the participants.
'Kay...
See ya!
You gonna look?
[CHIKA]
Mm.
I think they're in order.
The results show the
number of audience votes
each group got.
[HANAMARU]
So where is Aqours, zura?
[CHIKA] Let's see here. Oh!
Look, there's Saint Snow!
They got ninth place.
They almost made it
into the winners group.
Yea, but where are we?
[ALL gasping]
[CHIKA gasps]
We came in 30th.
30th out of 30 groups.
That's crazy.
So then we came in last?
[HANAMARU] You didn't have
to put it like that, zura!
How many votes from
the audience did we get?
Looks like...
[CHIKA]
...zero.
No way.
We worked so hard to get here.
Not even one person
voted for us.
[YOU]
Chika?
[SARAH]
Hello again, ladies.
[CHIKA gasps]
Saint Snow?
You were fun to watch!
Your song was lovely and the
whole group performed well.
But... I want to be
honest with you,
if you're trying to get into
Love Live or be like Mu's,
save yourself the trouble
and give it up.
[ALL gasp]
Love Live is serious.
Uh!
Don't take it lightly.
This isn't a game!
I think she was crying.
That's sad.
I bet it was really frustrating,
not making the winners' group.
Yeah...
[YOSHIKO]
Who does that girl think she is
telling us not to
take it lightly?!
[RUBY, HANAMARU sigh]
Maybe it seemed like we
didn't care that much.
For what it's worth, I think
we were pretty amazing.
You do?
We've come a long way
since we started.
Every day we give it our all,
and we even got
invited to Tokyo!
We've done well for a
few small-town girls!
Don't ya think?
I guess so.
[CHIKA]
There ya have it!
We need to be proud
of ourselves.
Taking everything
into consideration,
we couldn't have done better!
Come on now.
[CHIKA]
Hm?
Does it not frustrate
you at all?
Huh?
[ALL]
Uh?
[gasps]
Isn't it frustrating?
Yeah, it is, I mean,
a little bit.
But we really did our best,
so I'd say I'm pretty
darn satisfied.
It was fun. Just... fun.
All right.
[RUBY sighs]
We're finally home!
[HANAMARU] That means I
can say zura again, zura!
[YOSHIKO]
It's not like you ever stopped.
[HANAMARU]
Zura!
[STUDENTS]
Hey!
[CHIKA]
Wow, look, everyone's here!
[STUDENTS]
Welcome home!
How did you like Tokyo,
was it fun?
Well, yeah!
There were all kinds
of cool places to shop
and a ton of delicious
foods to try!
Did you sing well?
Tell us! You didn't get
nervous, did ya?
A bit! We survived
it all though.
Right?
Yeah, we sure did. And
the routine went well.
You know, it's funny
you  brought it up
'cause we were just
talking about how
it was the best performance
we've ever done and
it all went awesome.
That's great to hear!
Guess I got all worried
for nothing. Yay!
I knew it! So that
means the rumors
about you aiming to win
Love Live are true!
Huh?
Of course they're all true!
I mean, you don't get invited
to a big event in
Tokyo for nothing!
Yeah, you got it! Well,
we'll do what we can!
[BOTH exhale]
[DIA]
Welcome back.
[RUBY gasps]
[RUBY]
Dia.
[RUBY whimpers]
[cries]
You did the best
you could, Ruby.
[RUBY cries]
[MARI]
It's been quite a while
since you called me
out here like this.
[KANAN] Well, Dia reached out.
She told me about the girls.
[MARI]
Oh?
[KANAN]
What are you going to do?
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[DIA] So no one in the
audience voted for you?
That's right.
Considering how intense school
idol competitions can be,
I wish I could say I was
surprised to hear that.
I want you to understand this...
Despite the outcome not being
ideal, this wasn't a failure.
You have so much dedication!
You practice for hours on end,
and you gave the audience one of
your best performances to date.
However, that alone
won't be enough.
Every year, expectations grow.
[YOU]
What do you mean by that?
[DIA]
7,236.
Does that number mean
anything to you?
--Yohane counts her--
--No, zura.
You didn't let me finish!
That was the final
number of entrants
for Love Live last year.
And, it will only
continue to rise.
It's ten times the amount
of the first competition.
So many...
School idols have
always been popular,
and that won't change
any time soon.
The truth is that ever
since Love Live began,
more and more girls are deciding
to become school idols.
Groups like A-RISE and
Mu's are so famous
the trend is sure to continue.
And now they're even holding
the championships in Akiba Dome.
You see, That's the reality
of being a school idol.
[RIKO]
Wow.
[DIA]
Yes.
You didn't get any audience
votes, and we couldn't perform.
Nothing more can be done
about those things now.
That's just how it is.
[gasps] Wait, you
didn't perform?
What do you mean?
Two years ago there was a
similar rumor circulating
about our school
being shut down.
School idol? Who, me?
Of course you!
We're forming a group and if
it becomes popular enough
we might be able
to save the school!
You're so stylish!
Mari, if you join our team would
hit the top ranks in no time!
[MARI]
Scusa .
I'm not interested in
that type of thing.
Hug! [laughs]
Hey, what are you doing?!
I won't let go! Say yes!
This is peer pressure, yunno?!
[KANAN]
No way!
[MARI]
Come on already! Quit it!
[KANAN] Say you'll join us
or I'll hold out forever!
[MARI] I don't know where
things went wrong.
Everyone in the town supported
what we were doing,
and we all seemed to be
having a wonderful time!
Yes, and the one show we
did went well too. But...
Perform in Tokyo?
Yes, perform in Tokyo!
We've been invited to
participate in the competition!
Keep yelling like that and
you'll blow your voice out
before we even get there.
[DIA] This is our one chance
to change everything!
If we can make everyone
fall in love with us there,
we'll qualify for
Love Live easy!
But then, we couldn't
even sing a note.
We were blown away by the
talent of the other groups.
The stage seemed so big
and the lights so bright.
We were terrified to perform.
Count yourselves lucky
that you managed to get
as far as you did.
I see now. That's why you
were against us, huh?
[DIA] I figured something like
this would happen to you.
[DIA]
That's enough!
This farce was only successful
because of the efforts of
previous school idols,
and the good will
of this community!
And don't you dare forget it!
Becoming a school idol?
Winning Love Live?
Even if you're trying
to save Uranohoshi,
who are you kidding? Why bother.
Those things are impossible.
So you're saying that it's
better to just give up?
I think that's exactly
what needs to happen.
[KANAN gasps]
Kanan...
[laughs]
It needs to stop before
someone gets hurt.
I'm never going to give up.
I won't stop fighting
for you and Dia!
There has to be a way to
get our friendship back!
I can't stop trying.
You two mean more
to me than anything.
[MARI cries]
[MITO] I went ahead and ran
some bath water for you!
[CHIKA]
Thanks.
You take it easy
too, okay, Riko?
I will. Thanks again
for the ride.
Chika?
--[CHIKA] Huh?
--[RIKO] You okay?
[CHIKA] Eh. I'll think
everything over.
I need to get my
act together, right?
Or it'll make things
harder for the others.
Chika...
[YOSHIKO]
That's all for now.
[RUBY]
One and two. One and--
[RUBY yelps]
[DIA] Yes. I gave
it to her straight.
[KANAN]
Okay.
[DIA]
This is what you wanted, right?
What you wanted.
[YOU]
Hold on.
We giving up?
Tell us. Are we giving up?
It's a little chilly out there.
[RIKO]
Mm.
[CHIKA gasps]
[birds chirping]
[gasps] Where's she going?
[CHIKA grunts]
[RIKO panting]
Chika!
Chika! Chika!
[inhales] Huh? What's wrong?
[sighs] What on earth
are you doing?!
Um... I thought I might be
able to find something out here.
[RIKO]
What?
Remember?
We all dove in together to help
you find the sound of the ocean.
I decided to give
it a try to see
if I could find something too.
[RIKO]
Oh yeah?
[CHIKA]
Mm-hm!
Well, have you found anything?
Still looking. Nothing yet.
You sure?
[CHIKA] Mm-hm. I'm gonna
keep looking though.
It's okay. I don't
mind the search.
Just gotta continue.
It's tough.
Most of the time I can't
see what's up ahead.
But I try to keep
swimming along.
It's a zero right now,
but one day,
it might turn into a one or a
ten, that's why I can't stop.
If I give it all up, I'll never
know how much we can grow.
Chika...
[CHIKA] How could I stop
being a school idol now?
We have so far to go!
Our score was a zero!
A zero.
We worked so hard.
And it should've counted
for something more.
We practiced so much together,
we made our costumes, our songs,
and even that video.
We pushed ourselves every day
and I can't understand
why that wasn't enough.
The only thing we wanted to do
was go out there and shine!
[gasps]
I can't believe we
ended up with a zero!
A zero? No!
[gasps]
This is so frustrating!
I don't care if
it's different now
than it used to be back then!
It's not fair.
We deserved so much more.
[cries] I just can't stand it.
[RIKO]
I'm so relieved.
It's not good for you
to hold it all inside.
I'm supposed to be the one
who cheers you all up!
I don't wanna upset you more!
I was the one who talked
you all into this!
We put ourselves out there
and we don't have
anything to show for it!
That's why I've
gotta keep going!
That's why... I have to try!
Listen to me.
You didn't make us join.
All of us wanted to
try something new.
We wanted to do this.
I did.
[gasps]
[RIKO]
You did. Ruby did.
Hanamaru did.
And even Yoshiko did!
[YOU]
Ahoy!
[CHIKA]
But...
We're here for you.
You can always
share your feelings
because all of us are
in this together now!
[YOU]
Chika!
[HANAMARU]
Zura!
[GIRLS laughing]
[RIKO] Win or lose we'll never
leave you. We're friends!
[CHIKA cries]
[GIRLS laugh]
I'm not sure we'll be
able to go from zeros
to the winners' circle just yet.
It's okay.
I think we might be able to
work our way to a one though.
I want to see if we
can make that happen.
We all feel that way.
Uh?
[ALL gasping]
Yeah!
[KANAN, DIA, MARI] Next time,
"Young Dreamer!"