[CHIKA] It was the miracle
that I desperately needed.
[CHIKA] It could only
be one thing... fate.
[YOU, CHIKA gasping]
Look! Come on, Chika!
[CHIKA] I wanted to be
captivated by something.
Take one!
[CHIKA] I wanted to do
my best in something.
[BOTH gasping]
I'll help you!
[CHIKA] I just wanted to put
my best foot forward, but...
...my feet didn't exactly know
where they were going yet.
[CHIKA] Luckily, destiny
stepped in and took charge.
It gave me a push,
and there it was!
[CHIKA laughs]
[CHIKA gasping]
[CHIKA]
The something!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[CHIKA]
Join the School Idol Club!
Starting this Spring!
School Idol Club!
[CHIKA]
Sign up today and don't delay!
You! You!
Come on, embrace
your inner idol!
The School Idol Club wants you!
Don't you want
the Idol Club too?!
[YOU]
Uh, Chika?
[CHIKA whines]
They all just ignored me.
[YOU]
Uh...
[CHIKA] Why doesn't
anyone wanna sign up?
We're so... cool!
[CHIKA groans]
What was that?
If I had to guess,
I would say Chika.
Is this about that
idol nonsense again?
The noise is gonna
bother our customers.
I asked her to keep it down.
She's living in a dream world!
Things work too differently
way out here in the country!
Aw, man, that one hurt.
Is anything injured?
Nah, only my pride!
Whatcha think?
Tell me!
[YOU]
Mm... Well...
[CHIKA laughs]
Looks good to me!
Hooray!
So are you really serious
about this club?
[CHIKA]
Yep!
What the...?
Check it out, I plan
on setting it all up
right after we start
the new term!
Heh. Okay. Any members? Oh!
As of right now, nobody, unless
of course you count
me, myself, and I.
You're already in swim club.
No offense, but this school idol
thing seems kind of sudden.
It does?
Well, yeah. I mean, it's not
like you've ever taken
any sort of interest in club
activities before, so...
...what's the deal?
[CHIKA laughs]
[YOU]
Mm...
[BOTH gasp] If we don't hurry,
we'll miss the bus!
[SHIMA]
Chika! You! Hey, hey!
What have I told you girls about
using the guest entrance?
[CHIKA, YOU]
It's an emergency!
[horn honks]
[YOU gasps]
There it goes!
[CHIKA]
We want on!
[CHIKA, YOU]
Stop that bus!
[YOU, CHIKA sigh]
Thank goodness they
stopped for us!
We'd be super late if we had to
wait for the next one.
[YOU] Whoa, you've already made
a flyer?
Yep! Nothing wrong
with being prepared.
Ah... Plus I'm super excited!
Well, yeah. It's just...
Is something wrong?
No! I'm excited, too!
I'll do my very best
to help you out, Chika!
The School Idol Club
needs people like you.
[wind blows]
They're like, crazy popular,
and too good to be true.
[sighs]
Well don't rush in all at once.
[gasps]
[gasping]
[BOTH laughing]
Whoa, she's gorgeous--
[yelps]
Hiya!
Ever thought of becoming
a school idol?
Zura?
Zura...?
[HANAMARU]
Forget I said it!
Anyway, I promise our
club will be tons of fun!
I'm sure you'd both be very
popular!
So, what do you think?
[HANAMARU]
Huh? You want us to be idols?
[CHIKA]
Whoa.
Here, down here!
Are you interested?
It sounds cool!
Do you put on concerts?
[CHIKA] Mm-mm. Well, I mean,
not as of right now.
I'm still putting
everything together,
that's why I need
a cutie like you!
[RUBY]
Huh?
Zura!
[CHIKA laughs]
[screams]
I'm so sorry.
Ruby runs on the shy side.
[CHIKA]
Uh?
[YOSHIKO screaming]
[GIRLS gasping]
[YOSHIKO]
Ow, my legs!
[YOSHIKO grunts]
[GIRLS gasp]
Hey, um... are you
gonna be okay?
[YOSHIKO gasps]
[YOSHIKO chuckles]
Where hast I landed?
It's so lowly!
[ALL gasp]
Oh no, she's brain damaged!
No, not at all!
Ordinary humans
such as yourselves
could never comprehend the
greatness standing before you!
[YOU]
Whoa.
Okay, I'm more worried
about your legs though.
[groans] Pain is just
a state of mind!
For this fragile meat vessel
is only too temporary!
You might assume that I
am one of your own kind,
but in fact I am Yohane,
the fallen angel!
Oops, I probably shouldn't have
revealed my true identity!
Guess there's no...
Hold up, Yoshiko?
Oh my gosh, it is you!
It's me Hanamaru!
From kindergarten, remember?
Ha-na-ma-ru-ru?
I know not of whom you speak,
you insolent girl!
Rock... Paper...
[HANAMARU, YOSHIKO]
....Scissors!
Look at those scissors;
you're definitely Yoshiko!
That is a human name!
I'm Yohane, the fallen
angel, got it?!
Yohane!
Hang on!
[RUBY]
Hey!
[YOSHIKO]
Ah! Get lost!
[HANAMARU]
Yoshiko, Don't run away!
[RUBY]
Slow down!
[YOSHIKO]
Beat it, mortal!
[CHIKA]
That was strange.
Oh well, I'm gonna recruit
those girls later!
[laughs]
Are these flyers yours?
Were you the ones
passing them out earlier?
[BOTH]
Huh?
I wasn't aware we had
a School Idol Club here
at Uranohoshi
Girls' High School,
so perhaps you could
enlighten me?
Are you a new
student at this school?
No, she's not a new
student, stupid!
She's actually one
of the third years!
And more importantly, she is...
No way!
[CHIKA]
The Student Council President?
[DIA] Basically, you were
recruiting new members
for a club you've
yet to apply for,
further more you have
not received permission
to start said club.
Is that against the rules?
I wasn't trying to cause
trouble or anything!
I'm just really excited
about this club,
so I might have jumped
the gun a bit.
Ah-ha. And how many
members do you have?
There's only one name written on
the form you've provided me.
Well, if you count
me, uh, just me.
[DIA]
I see.
Need I remind you
that you actually need five
members to start a new club?
That's exactly why I was
trying to recruit people, silly!
[yelps]
[DIA groaning]
[DIA growls] You're in no
position to be laughing!
[CHIKA]
I'm sorry, ma'am!
Anyway, as it is, I simply
cannot accept this application.
It's far from complete.
Wha...?
C'mon Chika, let's just
come back later.
Fine! I'll submit it again
when I have five members!
[DIA] Well, you're free
to do whatever you wish.
But don't get your hopes up
in regards to getting
your club approved.
[CHIKA]
Why wouldn't it be?
Because as long as I'm the
student council president,
I will never allow a School
Idol Club to form here!
[CHIKA, YOU grunting]
That's... not fair!
[CHIKA]
Well, that was a complete bust.
I mean, what does
President Grumpy Pants
have against School Idol
Clubs anyway?
I don't think she's like them.
Okay, a while back, one
of the girls in my class
tried to start an Idol Club too
but she also got rejected.
What?! Did you know
that this whole time?!
Sorry!
[groans] Why didn't you say
something earlier then?
[YOU]
You were so excited.
I didn't want to ruin it for
you.
I heard a rumor...
Supposedly, the president comes
from a really old fishing family
or something like that.
Anyway, some of the
other students say
that's why she's so serious.
And why she thinks school
idol clubs are ridiculous.
There's nothing
ridiculous about them.
[CHIKA]
Ta-dah! We arrived!
You guys are late.
I thought today you
had early release?
[YOU] Yeah, we did, but we
got a little sidetracked.
[CHIKA]
Here!
Straight from my mom
with tender love and care.
Her love usually
involves oranges.
[CHIKA] If you don't want Mom's
love, tell her yourself!
[KANAN laughs]
[KANAN grunts]
So Kanan, I don't suppose
there's any chance
you'll come back to
school this term?
Well, it's hard to know
for sure at this point.
There's a lot to do here.
And Dad's bone is still healing
up, so I can't really say.
That's too bad.
I was gonna see if you
wanted to sign up as well.
Sign up for what?
Since you asked, I've decided
to become a school idol!
[KANAN]
Oh yeah?
Just remember that while you
guys may be second years,
I'm a third year student, so...
I remember!
But you'd be amazing!
[KANAN]
From Mom, with love.
--[YOU laughs]
--[CHIKA] Aw, dried fish again?
If you don't want Mom's
love, tell her yourself.
But yeah, that's how things are.
I'll be back at school
just as soon as I can.
In the meantime, keep me
in the loop, okay?
Oh, okay.
[helicopter blades whirling]
Huh?
Hey, what's that noise?
Probably the Oharas.
Two years already.
[CHIKA grunting]
[CHIKA] I have to figure out
a way to make this work.
I can't give up
when I'm so close.
[CHIKA gasping]
Huh?
Wha--?
Nah. She's not gonna
swim in April.
[RIKO panting]
[yelling]
[CHIKA grunting]
Wait!
That water is freezing!
You'll get sick!
Let go of me! Get off!
I have to do this!
[BOTH grunting]
[CHIKA]
Uh!
[RIKO]
Ah!
[RIKO, CHIKA scream]
[GIRLS]
Love Live! Sunshine!!
[RIKO sneezes]
[CHIKA] Are you okay?
The water's not very warm yet.
There are dive shops around
if you really want to go
swimming that badly.
I wanted to hear the
sound of the ocean.
Like, inside the ocean?
But, what for?
Never mind, I guess it's
none of my business,
but seriously, why do
you wanna hear it?!
[RIKO]
Heh. The thing is,
I'm composing a song for piano,
but no matter how hard I try
I just can't seem to capture
the sounds of the water.
Wow! That's so cool!
It's amazing that you
can write your own music!
So do you go to
school around here?
Tokyo.
[CHIKA] No way. You came here
all the way from Tokyo?
Well, I guess it's complicated.
[CHIKA]
Nah, I think that's awesome!
Oh! Do you know any of
the school idols there?
Did you say school idols?
Yep! Tokyo's supposed to have
a ton of famous groups.
Which one is your favorite?
I'm not following.
Huh?
[yawns]
[CHIKA]
You mean you don't know?
School idols are girls
who, well, go to school!
And perform in live competitions
and stuff like that!
They're not famous, are they?
Oh my gosh, they're
totally famous!
And sometimes if a
group is good enough,
they could even get to
perform at the Dome.
If it makes you feel any better,
I only learned about
all this recently.
Wow, really?
I've been so involved
in my piano playing
so I guess I never even
knew they existed.
Hey, you wanna see 'em?
They're so cool!
Trust me on this!
Like, you mean watch
them right now?
[CHIKA]
Yep, on my phone!
[RIKO]
Hm. They're, uh--
[CHIKA]
Awesome?
I was gonna say, well,
they look kinda... average.
I mean! You know, like
normal in the best way!
I just thought they'd look
more like celebrities
since they're famous
idols and all.
[CHIKA] I agree.
What?
I admit, it really
surprised me, too.
[gasps]
[CHIKA]
When you talk about piano,
I can tell you're super
passionate about it,
to the point where you'd
jump into freezing waters
just to write a song better.
To be consumed by
your very passion,
to have a special dream.
I've never had that kind
of feeling before.
You know something?
I'm normal, too.
[CHIKA] If you look up 'normal'
in the dictionary,
you'd probably see a picture
of me next to it.
No matter what I did,
I never stood out.
To be fair, it never
even really bothered me.
'Cause if everyone is special,
then nobody's special, right?
Time flew by.
Before I knew it, I was in my
second year of high school.
Not cool!
I had to act before I became
permanently normal!
I needed to evolve
into Chika-chi,
an awesomely normal
monster, and do it soon!
So, roar!
[CHIKA laughs]
Pew! Pew-pew! Bang!
Hi-yah!
Ka-blam! [laughs]
[RIKO laughs]
Then I saw them. On that
day, everything changed.
[CHIKA] They were just
average high schoolers,
but when they all worked
together on that stage,
they shined like the sun!
♪♪♪
And then I began to wonder,
is this something
that I could do, too?
How cool would it be
to stand on that stage
and move as one person?
I wanted to be like them.
They captivated me.
They inspired me!
I realized school idols were,
well, they were...
They were so... They were so...
They were so incredibly radiant!
[CHIKA] I immediately listened
to all of their songs.
I watched every
single video online.
I memorized their lyrics.
I knew I wanted to do this
with my own friends.
I wanted to inspire
others like me.
I felt passionate!
But mostly, I learned
that I want to shine!
Thanks a lot.
Because your story
is seriously amazing,
I'll work hard too.
Wow, really?
Really!
I'm rooting for you.
Chase your dreams!
Thanks! Oh, my name's
Chika Takami!
I'm a second year
student at that place:
Ooranohoshi Girl's High School.
[RIKO]
We're in the same grade!
I'm Riko Sakurauchi.
And my school is...
[RIKO]
...Otonokizaka.
Seriously?
[CHIKA]
Yes.
It sounds crazy,
but I wanna try asking Dia
to approve the club again.
Chika...
"That day will definitely come!"
That's what they sang about
in their song, right?
So there's no way I'm
gonna give up now.
Since you're so determined...
Huh?
[YOU]
Yoink!
Hey! Come on!
[YOU]
You know what?
Ever since you and I were
in elementary school,
I've always wondered
what it would be like
if we did something
really crazy together.
What are you talking about?
I've got swimming.
But I can split my time!
[CHIKA gasps]
[YOU laughs]
Here!
You, do you mean it?
[cries] Thank you!
You're crushing me.
All right! We're gonna
be the most awesome
school idols the world
has ever seen!
[YOU]
Mm-hm!
[splash]
[BOTH]
Uh? [scream]
[DIA sighs] I can't believe
you have the audacity
to turn in such a water
logged application.
Additionally, you've
only managed to recruit
one other person.
[CHIKA] I won't apologize!
I'm committed to this club
and I'll do whatever
it takes to start it!
I know you're just
testing my resolve,
'cause deep down you
want me to succeed!
[DIA]
You're delusional!
I told you before that I will
never approve your application!
[CHIKA growls]
And why is that?
Because I'm the student
council president
and I say we don't need
school idols here!
And why is that?!
[DIA, CHIKA growling]
[YOU]
Please stop!
I don't have to
explain myself to you!
Even if you do start
the school idol club,
can you compose your own music?
Say what?
[DIA]
In order to enter Love Live,
you can only compete if you're
using original material,
and that's only one of
the multiple obstacles
you would have to
overcome as a school idol.
There may be students
in Tokyo who compose,
but you won't find anyone
here who can do the same.
[CHIKA]
Not one person.
I can't believe the
student council president
was actually right.
[YOU] Yeah, starting
a school idol club
is a lot tougher than I thought.
[CHIKA grunts]
Okay!
[CHIKA] I'll just have to
learn how to write music!
By the time you're good at it,
we'll have graduated, sorry.
[CHIKA]
It's true though.
[TEACHER 1A]
Listen up, ladies!
[BOTH gasp]
We have a new student
joining our school today.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[TEACHER 1A]
I want you all to do your best
to help her feel welcome, okay?
[RIKO sneezes]
Excuse me!
Hello, I just transferred from
Tokyo's Otonokizaka High School.
Huh?
[RIKO sneezes]
[gasping]
I'm Riko Sakurauchi.
It's a pleasure to meet you!
[CHIKA]
Ahh! It's a miracle!
[gasping] Chika, it's you!
[CHIKA] That moment was
the start of everything!
Hey, Riko!
Let's be school idols!
We'll have so much fun together!
[RIKO]
Heh.
[gasping]
[RIKO]
I'm so sorry!
What?
Wha...?! Ah!
[CHIKA, YOU] Next time,
"Catch the Transfer Student!"