-( theme song playing )
♪ LET'S ROLL ♪
-♪ LET'S ROLL ♪
- ♪ REMEMBER ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, CHECK IT OUT ♪
♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
- ♪ NAKED MIND ♪
♪ NAKED DESIRE ♪
♪ NAKED MIND ♪
♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
♪ MOVE, MOVE ♪
♪ IT'S THE TIME! ♪
- THAT SUCKED.
I BARELY SLEPT A WINK
LAST NIGHT.
NO EIGHT-SIX.
MAN, THIS IS WEIRD.
FEELS LIKE I'VE LOST
SOMETHING IMPORTANT,
LIKE A FAMILY MEMBER'S DIED.
- ( bell tolling )
- ( grunts )
- YOU LOOK LIKE THE WALKING DEAD
AS USUAL MY FRIEND.
HOW YOU FEELIN'?
- COME ON.
IT IS WAY TOO EARLY
FOR YOU TO BE ACTING
LIKE A HYPERACTIVE FREAK.
WHY ARE YOU SO
WORKED UP ANYWAY?
- WHY ELSE WOULD I BE?
TODAY'S THE DAY OF THE BIG RACE.
THE RED SUNS AND THE EMPERORS
ARE GONNA GO TOE TO TOE!
I'M ALREADY SO FREAKING EXCITED,
YOU KNOW I CAN'T
EVEN TAKE A LEAK?
I KNOW. WHY DON'T WE CARPOOL UP
THERE LIKE THE TWO OF US DID
THAT TIME WE WENT UP
TO RACE IN MYOGI.
AND CAN WE TAKE YOUR EIGHT-SIX?
MAYBE SHOW IT OFF?
TO THE ADORING FANS?
UH...
DO YOU HAVE WAX IN YOUR EARS
OR SOMETHING?
I SAID, WHY DON'T WE TAKE
YOUR EIGHT-SIX UP THERE?
HOLD UP! TAKUMI,
WHERE YOU GOING, MAN!
I CAN'T WAIT TO CHECK
THIS RACE OUT TONIGHT.
IT'S GONNA BE A HELLUVA TIME.
ANY THOUGHTS ON WHO'S GONNA WIN?
'CAUSE I THINK IT'S
GONNA BE RYOSUKE.
HE'S CLEARLY THE BETTER DRIVER
OF THE TWO.
THAT SUDO GUY FROM
THE EMPERORS ISN'T THAT GOOD.
FORGET WHAT I THINK
ABOUT HIM PERSONALLY.
HE JUST HAPPENS TO
DRIVE A BETTER CAR.
- YOU KNOW WHAT, DUDE.
YOU DON'T KNOW CRAP ABOUT CARS.
SO JUST SHUT UP, ALRIGHT?
- WHAT ARE YOU SO
PISSED OFF ABOUT?
- LOOK, MAN. IT'S NOT THAT
I'M MAD OR ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST THAT SOMETHING CAME UP
WITH THE CAR
SO I CAN'T GO WITH YOU
TO WATCH THE RACE TONIGHT.
- HUH, WHY NOT?
- I JUST CAN'T.
GO WITH IKETANI AND KENJI, OKAY?
YOU'LL BE FINE.
- WHAT THE HELL?
TAKUMI ACTUALLY LOST?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- SO, HE REALLY DID GO
TO AKAGI LAST NIGHT.
THAT'S JUST PERFECT.
I HEARD SOMETHIN' ABOUT HIS CAR
STOPPING DURING THE RACE.
I WAS HOPING IT WAS JUST RUMOR,
BUT I GUESS IT'S 'NOT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN IT STOPPED?
DID HE BLOW THE ENGINE
OR DID HE SLAM IT INTO A
GUARDRAIL OR WHAT?
- NO ONE KNOWS EXACTLY
WHAT HAPPENED.
WE'RE JUST HEARING
BITS AND PIECES.
WE'RE BASICALLY PANICKING OVER
EVERY LITTLE THING WE HEAR.
- WELL, BOSS,
WE ACTUALLY FIGURED
YOU MIGHT HAVE HEARD SOMETHIN'
ABOUT IT FROM HIS DAD.
THE TWO OF YOU BEING
OLD FRIENDS AND ALL.
- SORRY, GUYS, BUT THIS IS THE
FIRST I'M HEARING ABOUT IT.
HANG ON. I'M GONNA GIVE HIM
A CALL REAL QUICK.
- ( phone ringing )
- ( ringing continues )
- HE'S NOT ANSWERING.
DAMN THE LUCK.
TAKUMI'S PROBABLY AT SCHOOL
RIGHT NOW ANYWAY.
IT'S BUGGING THE HELL OUT OF ME
THAT THEY NEVER EVEN BOTHERED
TO TELL US ABOUT THIS.
- ( car approaching )
- LOOK.
THAT'S KEISUKE TAKAHASHI.
- IS TAKUMI HERE?
- NO. TODAY'S HIS DAY OFF.
HE'S BACK ON SHIFT TOMORROW.
- ALRIGHT. I WAS HOPING TO
TALK TO HIM DIRECTLY.
I DON'T WANNA LEAVE A MESSAGE
WITH YOU GUYS.
BUT IT'S LOOKING LIKE THAT'S
WHAT I'M GONNA HAVE TO DO.
TELL HIM I SAID LAST NIGHT'S
RACE DOESN'T COUNT.
THAT I WON'T ACCEPT THE WIN.
IT WAS TOO STRANGE TO
COUNT FOR ANYTHING.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT
ANYONE ELSE THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
I CAN ONLY SPEAK FOR ME.
THING IS, I JUST CAN'T STAND UP
AND SAY TAKUMI FUJUWARA
WAS DEFEATED LAST NIGHT.
AND ONE MORE THING.
HE NEEDS TO KNOW.
WE'RE ALL PLANNING TO
AVENGE HIS EIGHT-SIX.
SHOW THE EMPERORS WHO'S BOSS.
THAT'S THE TRUTH.
WE ARE GONNA WIPE THE PAVEMENT
WITH THOSE WANNABES. LATER.
- HOLD UP!
WE'LL GIVE HIM THE MESSAGE.
AND I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
GOOD LUCK WITH TONIGHT'S BATTLE.
WE'RE ALL GONNA BE
PULLING FOR YOU, MAN.
- ( engine accelerating )
- ( crashing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ( thudding )
- ( screaming )
- ( crashing )
- ( whimpering ) BAD IDEA!
- Takumi: WHAT THE HELL?
ARE YOU NUTS?
YOU THINK MAYBE THIS
ROCK'S A LITTLE TOO BIG
TO BE THROWIN' AT MY WINDOW?
YOU COULD'VE SHATTERED THE THING
OR GIVEN ME A CONCUSSION
FOR THAT MATTER.
- I LOOKED FOR SMALLER ONES,
BUT 'THERE WEREN'T ANY.
BESIDES IT ISN'T LIKE YOU
GOT HURT OR ANYTHING, RIGHT?
AND I MADE SURE TO
THROW IT LIGHTLY.
I WAS ACTUALLY PRETTY
AWESOME IN BASEBALL.
- LOOK, I DON'T CARE HOW GOOD
YOU THINK YOU WERE.
YOU DON'T THROW FREAKIN'
BOULDERS AT MY WINDOW.
- ( screaming )
- I AM SO SORRY!
I DIDN'T MEAN TO HIT YOUR CAR!
- ( sobbing ) I DON'T DESERVE
NICE THINGS ANYWAY!
- I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU THAT
I WASN'T GONNA GO WITH YOU
TO AKAGI TODAY.
- I KNOW. AND I DECIDED THAT
I'M NOT GONNA GO EITHER.
INSTEAD OF THAT, WHY DON'T
YOU AND I GO ON UP TO AKINA PASS
FOR A LITTLE JOY RIDE.
WHATTYA SAY?
COULD BE SOME FUN.
- HEY. TAKUMI?
ONE THING.
I JUST WANNA SAY I'M SORRY
ABOUT THIS MORNING.
I 'KNOW I HAVE A KILLER ARM,
BUT THE ROCK WAS BIGGER
THAN I THOUGHT.
- DUDE, I DON'T
CARE ANYTHING ABOUT THAT.
I WAS CURIOUS TO SEE IF YOU'D
MAYBE HEARD ANYTHING
ABOUT LAST NIGHT'S RACE THOUGH.
- YEAH. IKETANI FILLED ME IN
ON IT AFTER SCHOOL.
- SO I GUESS EVERYONE AT THE
STATION ALREADY KNOWS, TOO.
- SEEMS LIKE EVERYONE IN TOWN
IS ALREADY TALKIN' ABOUT IT.
IT'S PRETTY BIG NEWS.
THEY ALL KEEP THEIR EYES ON YOU.
BY THE WAY, IKETANI SAID
HE HAD A MESSAGE
I WAS SUPPOSED TO GIVE TO
YOU WHEN I SAW YOU.
- WHAT THE HECK? GOT SOME
DUDE RIDIN' RIGHT UP ON MY TAIL.
- WELL, HE'S PROBABLY JUST AS
EXCITED TO GET UP THERE
AND SEE TONIGHT'S
RACE AS WE ARE.
- YEAH, SURE, MAN. I GUESS SO.
BUT THE GUY'S JUST RUBBING ON
MY NERVES A LITTLE BIT,
LOOK AT HOW DAMN CLOSE HE'S
RIDING TO MY FREAKING BUMPER.
I'LL JUST SPEED UP.
- NAH, LOOKS LIKE
HE'S TRYING TO PASS.
PULL OVER SOME AND
LET HIM GET BY.
- YEAH. LET'S SEE WHAT
KINDA CAR HE'S 'DRIVING.
- DUDE THAT'S A FREAKIN'
EIGHT-SIX LEVIN!
- AND IT'S GOT A TURBO!
I COULD HEAR THE WASTE GATE PASS
THE EXHAUST OUT THE TAILPIPE!
DAMN, THAT GUY FLEW BY
MY SR-TWENTY TURBO
LIKE I WAS PARKED IN
A DRIVE-THROUGH.
HOW'D HE DO THAT?
I MEAN, WERE ON AN UPHILL!
- WHERE DID THAT GUY COME FROM?
HAVE I EVER EVEN SEEN HIM
AROUND HERE BEFORE?
- Itsuki: THAT'S WHAT THEY SAID.
KEISUKE CAME TO THE GAS STATION
AND SAID AS FAR AS
HE WAS CONCERNED,
HE DOESN'T THINK YOU LOST
LAST NIGHT'S RACE.
- I HONESTLY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HE MEANS.
I MEAN I DID LOSE.
I WAS COMPLETELY OUTMATCHED.
IF YOU'D SEEN IT, YOU'D AGREE...
- SO SUDO WAS THAT GOOD, HUH?
THOSE EMPEROR'S KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE DOING.
- YEAH, THEY DO.
I WOULD'VE LOST TO THEM
EVEN IF WE RACED IN AKINA.
- Itsuki: MAKES SENSE.
- SO DUDE, HOW IS THE
OLD EIGHT-SIX, ANYWAY?
CAN YOU FIX HER UP?
- MY DAD THINKS SHE
NEEDS A NEW ENGINE,
BUT I DUNNO, MAYBE IT DOES.
- ( gasps )
- I SHOULD NEVER HAVE
GONE TO AKAGI.
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
ONE I'LL PROBABLY REGRET
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
- ( people chattering )
- DAMN, THE AIR'S SO TENSE
AROUND HERE, YOU COULD PUNCH IT.
- YOU HEAR ABOUT THAT CRAZY RACE
WENT DOWN LAST NIGHT?
- YEAH. AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX LOST.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
BUT SUDO'S TECHNIQUE IS
NOTHING TO SCOFF AT.
I HEAR IT'S FREAKIN'
OUT OF THIS 'WORLD.
- I GUESS
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI REALLY IS
GOONMA'S ONE LAST
HOPE OF REDEMPTION.
I WANT THAT GUY TO WIN
NO MATTER WHAT.
- Takeshi: SHINGO, YOU CAME TO
SEE THIS THING PLAY OUT, TOO?
- TAKESHI.
I FIGURED COMING OUT AND
ROOTING FOR THE RED SUNS
IS THE LEAST I CAN DO.
- THERE'S NOT A CHANCE IN HELL
RYOSUKE'S GONNA LOSE THIS ONE.
WE CAN'T JUST LET THESE LAN-EVO
IDIOTS LOOK DOWN ON GOONMA
FOR THE REST OF ETERNITY.
- YEAH.
LOOK AT HOW CLOSE YOU ARE.
WHATTYA SAY YOU BACK
THE HELL UP A BIT?
- ( tires screeching )
- WOAH. DUDE, AN EIGHT-SIX!
- WAIT, IS THAT AKINA'S
EIGHT-SIX?
- NO, IT'S GOT SAITAMA PLATES.
- WHATTYA THINK?
THIS GONNA WORK, KAZUMI?
- IT'S FINE.
- ( crowd gasping )
- THERE THEY ARE.
IT'S THE LAN-EVO'S.
- COME ON, RED SUNS!
YOU CAN DO IT!
- GOT ANYTHING TO SAY BEFORE
WE CRANK THIS UP, RYOSUKE?
- NOT REALLY.
JUST THAT IT'S ONLY GONNA BE
YOU AND ME OUT THERE TONIGHT.
- ( scoffs )
YEAH, THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
NOW WHATTYA SAY YOU AND I
START A REAL RACE, HUH?
- INITIAL D.
- REMEMBER HOW YOU TOLD ME
YOU WEREN'T GONNA RACE
IN AKINA ANYMORE?
MAN, WHEN I HEARD THAT,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE THE
BRAVEST DRIVER I'D EVER MET.
AND I REALLY MEAN THAT.
YOU WANTING' TO RACE ANYPLACE
BUT AT HOME IMPRESSED
ME, BIG TIME.
- LOOK MAN, YOU'VE GOT IT
ALL WRONG.
THERE WASN'T ANYTHING IMPRESSIVE
ABOUT WHAT WENT DOWN LAST NIGHT.
EVERYTHING ABOUT IT WAS AWFUL
AND 'WHEN IT WAS OVER,
I WAS MADDER
THAN I'VE EVER BEEN.
BECAUSE OF THAT, I STARTED
MAKING REALLY STUPID DECISIONS.
I COULDN'T CONTROL MY EMOTIONS
AND I ENDED UP WRECKING THE CAR.
SERVES ME RIGHT, I GUESS.
I WAS SO PISSED OFF
I COULDN'T SEE STRAIGHT.
I DIDN'T HAVE ANY BUSINESS
BEING BEHIND THE WHEEL.
I'M JUST LUCKY I WALKED AWAY
IN ONE PIECE.
I CAN ACCEPT THE LOSS,
BECAUSE DEEP DOWN
I KNOW I WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
WHAT I CAN'T GET
OVER IS THE FACT
MY EIGHT-SIX
ENDED UP TRASHED.
AND MY DAD, HE TRUSTED ME.
SORRY, DUDE.
- ( engines revving )
- THIS IS IT. SO WHAT PLAN
ARE YOU RUNNIN' WITH?
- SIMULATION X.
- SERIOUSLY?
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WE HAD AN X.
- RYOSUKE IS AN EXCEPTION TO
ALL OF OUR OTHER RULES.
AND I DEVELOPED A SPECIAL
STRATEGY JUST FOR THIS BATTLE.
IT'S ONE THAT'S GONNA WIN THIS
THING FOR ME. COUNT ON IT.
- EYES FRONT!
I'M STARTIN' THE COUNTDOWN!
FIVE, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE. GO!
- ( tires screeching )
- AS LONG AS MY BROTHER
RUNS HIS NORMAL RACE,
THERE'S NO WAY HE'LL LOSE
TO THAT LAN-EVO.
- ♪ I WONDER WHAT YOU DO,
THIS IS MY TIME ♪
♪ TALKING YOU THE
RIGHT PLACE BABE ♪
♪ I'M GIVING ALL TO YOU,
I'M READY TO GET THROUGH ♪
♪ DON'T YOU WANNA LET ME IN,
I'M SINGING AGAIN ♪
♪ THERE'S A PRESENT
JUST FOR YOU ♪
♪ AND TONIGHT IS
THE RIGHT TIME ♪
♪ IT'S SO GOOD TO ME ♪
- RYOSUKE CORNERS SHARPER THAN
ANYONE ELSE ON THE CIRCUIT!
- WELL, THAT'S DIFFERENT.
I'VE SEEN RYOSUKE RACE
DOZENS OF TIMES
AND HE USUALLY LETS HIS
OPPONENT TAKE THE LEAD.
WONDER WHAT HE'LL DO NEXT?
- THIS IS AWESOME!
I MEAN, BOTH OF THOSE CARS
ARE SO INTENSE OUT THERE!
- YOU'RE RIGHT SIS,
IT IS A PRETTY AWESOME RACE.
BUT HEY, ARE YOU ABLE TO SEE
ALL OF THE LITTLE SUBTLETIES
IN THEIR STRATEGIES?
LIKE THAT THE EVO THREE
HAD A QUICK START
BUT IT NEVER FULLY ACCELERATED
COMING OFF THE LINE.
AND WHEN THEY DOVE INTO THE
FIRST CORNER ALL TANGLED UP,
IF YOU WATCHED CLOSELY YOU COULD
SEE HE RETREATED A LITTLE BIT.
THAT KINDA THING'S OUT OF FORM,
FOR HIM.
- OH.
- MAYBE HE WAS CHOOSING TO STAY
BEHIND AS SOME KIND OF STRATEGY.
THERE'S REALLY
NO WAY OF KNOWING.
WHAT I DO KNOW IS THAT IT
WAS WORTH COMING OUT
TO SEE THIS RACE.
- ( tires screeching )
- I CAN DO THIS.
THIS IS A RACE I CAN WIN.
BY HANGIN' BACK, I CAN
SEE EVERYTHING
THAT RYOSUKE IS TRYING TO DO.
I'VE GOT THIS GUY.
ALL OF THE UNCERTAINTIES
THAT HAVE BEEN SWIRLING
AROUND IN MY HEAD,
THEY'RE GONE.
- ( tires screeching )
- I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN, RYOSUKE,
WHAT YOU TOLD ME A YEAR AGO,
AFTER I LOST TO YOU.
- Kyoichi: DON'T LET THIS GO
TO YOUR HEAD, MAN.
I STILL THINK YOU STREET RACERS
ARE THE LOWEST OF THE LOW.
THE BEST ANY OF YOU COULD HOPE
TO BE IS MEDIOCRE.
THERE'S NO WAY THE MOTOR
SPORT TECHNIQUE IS INFERIOR
TO PRIMITIVE STREET TECHNIQUE.
IT WAS DEVELOPED TO
ACHIEVE MAXIMUM SPEED!
EVERYBODY KNOWS IT!
GOT THAT? THAT'S WHAT
I'M ALWAYS GONNA THINK.
- BELIEVE WHAT YOU WANT,
BUT THE MOUNTAIN PASS REQUIRES
ITS OWN TECHNIQUE.
YOU WON'T SUCCEED UP THERE
WITH WHAT YOU'VE LEARNED SO FAR.
THAT STUFF YOU PICKED
UP AT GYMKHANA
AND THOSE OTHER CIRCUITS.
- THAT'S TOTAL BS.
NO FREAKIN' WAY!
- KYOICHI!
I'M GETTING THE FEELING
THAT THIS CONVERSATION
ISN'T GOING ANYWHERE.
AT LEAST NOT ANYWHERE
THAT'S GOING TO RESULT
IN ANY ANSWERS FOR YOU.
BECAUSE IF YOU REALLY BELIEVE
THAT YOUR THEORY IS CORRECT,
THEN GO AHEAD AND DEFEAT ME.
BUT IF YOU CAN'T BEAT ME,
THEN ALL YOU'RE LEFT
WITH IS A THEORY.
- ( scoffs )
I WON'T FORGET THIS, RYOSUKE.
I WILL DEFEAT YOU SOMEDAY.
THEN YOU'LL TASTE THE SAME
BITTER ANGUISH THAT I DO.
AND I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
IT SINCE THEN.
I KNOW YOU REMEMBER, TOO.
ALL OF OUR RACING THEORIES
AND PERSONAL BELIEFS,
THEY'RE ALL RIDING ON
OUR TIRES TONIGHT, PAL.
- ( tires screeching )
RYOSUKE, YOU TOLD ME
THE MOUNTAIN PASS
REQUIRES ITS OWN TECHNIQUE.
THE BOLDNESS TO TAKE
THE SHORTEST LINE.
HEEL AND TOE,
THE ALL-WHEEL DRIFT WITH
ZERO COUNTER-STEERING.
YOU MAY BE FAST OUT HERE,
BUT WHAT'S SO SPECIAL
ABOUT YOUR TECHNIQUE?
YOU'RE JUST SPITTIN' OUT
TEXTBOOK CIRCUIT
RACING BULLCRAP!
IF YOU WANT SPEED, YOU'LL END UP
HAVING TO RELY ON
MOTOR SPORT TECHNIQUE!
MY THEORY IS THE RIGHT ONE!
- ( tires screeching )
RYOSUKE'S FC IS KICKIN'
DOWN THE PASS!
IT'S LIKE A DAMN JET ENGINE!
THE EVO THREE IS RIGHT
THERE ALONG WITH HIM!
- ( engines accelerating )
- HERE THEY COME.
WONDER WHO'S IN FRONT.
- THIS PART ALWAYS
MAKES ME NERVOUS.
- CHECK IT OUT, GUYS!
IT'S THE FC!
- I'LL SHOW YOU JUST
HOW MUCH I'VE GROWN
SINCE I FACED YOU
LAST YEAR, RYOSUKE!
- ( crowd cheering )
THIS IS WHERE MY
FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE
AND THE MISFIRING SYSTEM
REALLY KNOCK IT OUT!
- WHAT? THE EVO THREE
JUST PASSED RYOSUKE'S FC!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Announcer: WHAT? THE EIGHT-SIX
WAS SEEN IN AKINA!.
SO IT'S RUNNING AGAIN!
NEXT ON INITIAL D SECOND STAGE.
"DANGEROUS CAR."
DON'T MISS IT!