- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ LET'S ROLL! ♪
♪ LET'S ROLL! ♪
- ♪ REMEMBER? ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, CHECK IT OUT! ♪
- ♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
- ♪ LET'S ROLL! ♪
♪ NAKED MIND ♪
- ♪ NAKED MIND ♪
- ♪ DESIRE ♪
- ♪ NAKED DESIRE ♪
♪ NAKED MIND ♪
♪ NAKED LOVE ♪
♪ BLAZIN' BEAT! YO! ♪
♪ M.O.V.E MOVE ♪
♪ IT'S THE TIME! ♪
- I CAN'T LOSE THIS RACE.
CERTAINLY NOT TO ANY PUNKS
THAT BLAST INTO MY TURF
WITH THEIR BAD ATTITUDES.
- TIME TO KNOCK THIS GUY OUT.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- CRAZY DUDE! HE BLEW PAST
TAKESHI LIKE IT WAS NOTHIN'!
- BADASS. THAT GUY'S A BEAST.
- THE EVO FOUR PASSED
TAKESHI'S R-THIRTY TWO
AND IT'S PULLIN' AWAY FAST.
- WHAT? HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
- WONDER WHAT DESPERATE THOUGHTS
IN THE SMALL BRAIN OF THAT GUY.
SURE, HE'S IN A LAN-EVO
BUT HE JUMPED IN FRONT OF
A SKILLED MYOGI RACER.
THAT'S THE WORST POSITION
YOU CAN BE IN.
IS IT REAL CONFIDENCE?
OR IS THE GUY JUST AS
DUMB AS I THINK HE IS?
- HE BETTER NOT THINK
THIS IS OVER YET!
- Keisuke: HEY, BRO,
YOU IN THERE?
- I'M HERE. COME ON IN.
- THE LAN-EVO TEAM. THEY'RE
RACING TONIGHT ON MOUNT MYOGI.
I JUST HEARD IT FROM A FRIEND.
- AGAINST TAKESHI
OF THE NIGHT KIDS, RIGHT?
- YEAH, I SUPPOSE SO.
WHO'S YOUR BEST GUESS?
ANYBODY RIDING TO THE TOP?
BECAUSE FOR ME, THIS HAS
GOTTA BE THE FIRST TIME
I'M HOPIN' TAKESHI
ACTUALLY WINS.
AND THAT LAN-EVO'S
BIGASS SPOILER IS ENOUGH
TO MAKE ME WANNA THROW UP
IN MY OWN MOUTH.
- TAKESHI'S POWER
LIES IN HIS BOLDNESS,
HIS OFFENSIVE
DRIVING STRATEGY.
THE THINGS THAT MAKE YOU DISLIKE
HIM SO MUCH IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WHEN HE'S ON,
THE BOY'S QUITE FAST.
BUT UNDER PRESSURE, HE TENDS
TO CRACK LIKE DRYING MUD.
I JUST HOPE HE WAS ABLE
TO RECOVER FROM THE LOSS
HE SUFFERED WHEN HE
WENT UP AGAINST YOU.
'CAUSE IF HE WASN'T,
IT COULD BE A REALLY BAD NIGHT.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
BUT WE STILL GOT A LONG WAY
TO GO BEFORE THE FINISH LINE.
IF I DON'T STOP THESE GUYS,
WHO THE HELL WILL?
( screams )
DAMN IT!
- NOW YOU HAND OVER YOUR TEAM
STICKER. THAT'S THE DEAL.
- IN NO TIME MY ENTIRE SPOILER'S
GONNA BE PLASTERED
WITH THE SLASHED UP STICKERS
FROM EVERY TEAM IN THIS REGION
THAT I CHEWED UP AND SPIT OUT.
- DON'T START PLANNING
YOUR PARADE YET, YOU PRICK.
THERE ARE MORE RACERS IN GUNMA
THAN YOU 'KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH.
- THAT SOUNDS TO ME LIKE THE CRY
OF A GUY WHO'S ALREADY A LOSER.
- HA! LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
- YEAH.
ONE MORE THING.
FROM NOW ON
WHENEVER YOU SEE A CAR
WITH A TEAM EMPEROR
STICKER ON IT,
I WANT YOU TO PULL OVER
TO THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.
- TAKESHI, I HAVE A HARD TIME
WRAPPIN' MY HEAD AROUND THE FACT
THAT HE WAS FASTER THAN YOU
IN AN UPHILL BATTLE.
- Kenji: SO, THAT LAN-EVO TEAM
DEFEATED THE NIGHT KIDS.
- Itsuki: NO!
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDIN' ME!
- THAT'S ALL ANYONE I'VE RUN
INTO HAS BEEN TALKIN' ABOUT
ALL MORNING LONG.
TAKESHI CRASHED HIS R-THIRTY
TWO INTO THE WALL
AND JACKED IT UP PRETTY BADLY.
- WHOA. THAT SUCKS.
I GUESS THINGS HAVE BEEN
PRETTY ROUGH FOR THE NIGHT KIDS.
I GOTTA ADMIT I FEEL
KINDA SORRY FOR THEM.
- REMEMBER, I HEARD
THE LAN-EVO TEAM
IS PLANNIN' TO CONQUER GUNMA?
WELL, THEY WANNA DO IT
WITHIN THE MONTH.
THAT MEANS AKINA'S GONNA BE
ON THEIR LIST REAL SOON.
- Itsuki: WHAT DO WE DO
WHEN THAT HAPPENS?
- WE'RE NOT GONNA HAVE MUCH OF
A CHOICE BUT TO FACE 'EM DOWN.
WE'RE AKINA'S TEAM,
SO IF THEY TRY AND CHALLENGE US,
I DON'T HAVE ANY INTENTION
OF RUNNING AWAY NOW.
I'VE ALREADY SWITCHED OUT THE
TIRES ON MY S-THIRTEEN
TO ONES THAT GOT BETTER GRIP.
AND I TOLD ALL OF
THE OTHER TEAM MEMBERS
ABOUT WHAT MIGHT BE GOIN' DOWN.
- TAKUMI, COME HERE.
THEY MIGHT CHALLENGE
YOU SPECIFICALLY
TO A DOWNHILL BATTLE,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO ACCEPT IT
IF YOU DON'T WANT.
YOUR UNDEFEATED STREAK IS A BIG
SOURCE OF PRIDE AMONG ALL OF US.
I'D REALLY HATE TO RUIN IT
AGAINST THEIR LAN-EVO.
NOT TO MENTION THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE NOT
OFFICIALLY A TRUE MEMBER
OF THE SPEED STARS
YET, YOU KNOW.
AND I WANT YOU TO KEEP YOUR
WINNING STREAK ROLLIN', TOO.
THIS LAN-EVO BUSINESS
IS NO JOKE.
I MEAN, YOU MIGHT AS WELL BE
GOIN' UP AGAINST A CAR
FROM THE WORLD RALLY
CHAMPIONSHIP.
ITS BODY IS LIGHT AS HELL
AND EQUIPPED WITH TURBO
AND FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE.
IT'S GOT NO REAL WEAKNESSES.
FREAKIN' CAR SHOULDN'T
BE ALLOWED ON ANY PASS
IN MY OPINION.
- LISTEN GUYS,
I'D HATE TO, UH...
- I'D HATE TO AVOID A RACE.
I WANNA RACE THEM
AS MUCH AS YOU.
I'M READY.
- OH, TAKUMI. YOU SOUND LIKE A
REAL RACER NOW! YOU'RE THE MAN!
YOU'RE MY TRUE FRIEND.
I LOVE YOU, MAN! I DO.
I KNOW YOU'LL WIN.
THERE'S NOT A DOUBT IN MY MIND.
YOU'RE GONNA MOP UP THE FLOOR
WITH THOSE GUYS!
- THINK THIS IS
THE SMARTEST THING?
- RIGHT NOW I'D PUT OUR CHANCES
OF WINNING AT ABOUT,
RIGHT AT ZERO PERCENT, GUYS.
- UPGRADING THE EIGHT-SIX, HUH?
THAT CAME OUT OF NOWHERE.
SO WHAT'RE YOU GETTIN' AT?
- COME ON. IT HAD TO
HAVE CROSSED YOUR MIND
AT SOME POINT, BUNTA.
TAKUMI'S EVOLVING INTO A MUCH
BETTER RACER THAN HE USED TO BE.
JUST SEEMS LIKE IT'S TIME
TO UPGRADE.
YOU KNOW, TRY TO BRING
THE EIGHT-SIX'S CAPABILITIES
UP TO THE SAME LEVEL
AS THE KID'S.
HEY, DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I'M NOT TELLING YOU WHAT TO DO.
I CERTAINLY KNOW
BETTER THAN THAT.
JUST CURIOUS AS TO
WHAT YOUR PLANS ARE.
- I GUESS, UH, THIS ENGINE IS
GETTING A LITTLE RUN DOWN,
ISN'T IT?
MAYBE IT IS ABOUT TIME TO
FINALLY GIVE THE OLD GAL
AN OVERHAUL.
- YEAH.
- ACTUALLY,
I KIND OF ALREADY GOT ONE.
- ( gasps ) YOU SCREWIN' AROUND
WITH ME, MAN?
- NO. BUT I JUST HAPPENED UPON
THE MOST INCREDIBLE LITTLE THING
FROM THE MOST UNLIKELY SOURCE.
- WHAT'S INCREDIBLE?
- ALRIGHT. I'LL SHOW YOU.
JUST GET IN THE CAR.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE YOUR EYES.
- ( gasps ) UNREAL!
WHOA, IT'S LIKE HAVING GOLD!
- TOLD YA YOU'D BE IMPRESSED,
DIDN'T I?
- NO, IT GOES WAY BEYOND THAT.
THIS BLOWS ME AWAY.
HOW'D YOU MANAGE TO GET A HOLD
OF SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
I JUST HOW'D YOU CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GOT THIS FOR THE EIGHT-SIX.
THAT'S AMAZING!
- YEAH, ME EITHER. HAVEN'T FELT
THIS EXCITED IN A WHILE.
ALMOST SEEMS TOO GOOD TO
WASTE ON A KID LIKE TAKUMI,
DOESN'T IT?
- WELL. WHEN ARE YOU GONNA
PUT IT IN THERE?
- WE'LL SEE.
A BETTER ENGINE ISN'T
AUTOMATICALLY GONNA MAKE
THE CAR A BETTER MACHINE.
I'LL NEED TO ADJUST A WHOLE
LOT OF OTHER STUFF
AND FINE-TUNE THE
FOOTWORK FIRST.
- AND WITH THE PROPER BALANCE,
I THINK THIS ONE WILL BE
THE MONSTER TO BEAT.
- Bunta: I'LL TEST HER MYSELF
AND WORK OUT THE
BEST CONFIGURATION.
ONCE I'M FINISHED WITH THAT,
MASASHI, I'LL NEED YOUR HELP.
- SURE, WHATEVER YOU NEED.
I'VE LEARNED NOT TO ASK
QUESTIONS BY THIS POINT.
YOU'RE TOO STUBBORN TO LISTEN
TO MY SUGGESTIONS, ANYWAY.
- JUST LIKE THE OLD DAYS,
HUH, GUYS?
- BUT, UH, THERE IS ONE MORE
THING TAKUMI HASN'T BEEN ABLE
TO ACCOMPLISH IN THAT CAR.
- YEAH? YOU GONNA TELL US
WHAT THAT IS?
- NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
- WOULD You STOP BEING
SUCH A PAIN IN THE ASS
AND JUST TELL US?
- FINE. BUT YOU HAVE
TO SWEAR TO ME
THAT YOU WON'T TELL
TAKUMI ANYTHING
ABOUT WHAT I'M GONNA
SAY TO YOU.
- I PROMISE WE WON'T
SAY A THING TO HIM.
- THEN I'M HAPPY TO TELL YOU.
THAT SINGLE THING IS
HE HASN'T LOST A RACE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
HE'S TRIED SO HARD TO
REMAIN UNDEFEATED!
HE'S THE TOP GUY IN
THIS WHOLE REGION!
- AND THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I DON'T LIKE.
LONG AS HE KEEPS SUCCEEDING,
HE'LL NEVER HAVE THE KIND OF
APPRECIATION FOR WINNING
THAT HE'D NEED FOR THIS UPGRADE.
TAKUMI HAS TO PUSH THE CAR'S
CAPABILITIES TO ITS VERY LIMITS.
THEN HE'LL REALIZE THAT IT'S
STILL NOT GOOD ENOUGH
TO SIMPLY WIN.
BECAUSE THE LESSON OF
HUMILITY CAN ONLY BE LEARNED
FROM FAILING.
SO UNTIL HE LOSES,
I CAN'T IN GOOD CONSCIENCE
UPGRADE THE EIGHT-SIX.
- Narrator: INITIAL D!
- Kyoichi: AT THIS RATE,
THE SIDE OF THAT SPOILER'S
GONNA BE WALLPAPERED IN NO TIME.
- YEAH, THE WHOLE THING'S
KINDA FUN FOR ME
THE MORE I THINK
OF IT AS A GAME.
BUT I REALLY WISH I WAS
RACING DRIVERS
WITH A LITTLE MORE EXPERIENCE.
ANYWAY, WHERE'S OUR NEXT TARGET?
HAVE YOU DECIDED YET?
- YEAH, IT'S GONNA BE TOMORROW
NIGHT. WE'RE HEADING INTO AKINA.
- ( gasps ) WE'RE GONNA DO
THE EIGHT-SIX?
HOW FREAKIN' BORING.
- I WOULDN'T MIND RACIN' HIM
MYSELF IF YOU DON'T WANNA.
- KYOICHI'S RACIN' THE DUDE?
WHY WOULD HE PUT HIS
REPUTATION ON THE LINE?
- I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
- OUR ULTIMATE TARGET,
OUR MAIN OBJECTIVE,
IS RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI OF
THE AKAGI RED SUNS.
- BUT BEFORE HIM WE GOTTA
TAKE DOWN AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX.
LOOK, I CHECKED OUT
THE COURSE YESTERDAY.
THE SLOPES ARE WAY MORE SEVERE
THAN WE'RE USED TO.
MY EVO THREE IS LIGHTER
AND BETTER SUITED TO IT.
- DUDE, WHATEVER.
LET ME DO THIS.
YOU KNOW I'M GOOD FOR IT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHERE
I RACE, OR WHO IT IS,
I'M NOT GONNA LOSE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE CAR ON THE ROAD
THAT MY CAR CAN'T BEAT
AND YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHICH ONE
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT, KYOICHI.
IT'S YOUR EVO THREE.
IT'S A BETTER VEHICLE THAN MINE,
AND YOU'RE A BETTER DRIVER.
WE DON'T NEED OUR NUMBER ONE
TO GO UP AGAINST SOME
WEAK-ASS EIGHT-SIX.
YOU GOT NOTHIN' TO PROVE.
I'LL DO IT. OKAY?
- ( clock tolling )
- WHO'S LEAVING ME NOTES?
DID YOU KNOW THAT NATSUKI MOGI
IS TAKING MONEY TO DATE AN OLDER
MAN WHO DRIVES A MERCEDES?
- Itsuki: TAKUMI!
SO, ARE YOU READY TO GO YET?
- YEAH, SURE.
- WHATCHA GOT
IN YOUR HAND THERE?
- IT'S, UH, NOTHING.
- I ALMOST FORGOT.
THIS CAR MAG THAT I BOUGHT THE
OTHER DAY HAD A FEATURED ARTICLE
ON THE EVO FOUR
THAT YOU MIGHT WANNA READ.
COULD HELP YOU UNDERSTAND HER
A BIT BETTER.
AND YOU NEED ALL THE HELP
YOU CAN GET.
I MEAN, YOU MIGHT BE GOING UP
AGAINST ONE, RIGHT?
- THANKS, MAN, BUT NO THANKS.
- WHY NOT? IF THE
ARTICLE ISN'T HELPFUL,
IT SURE AS HECK ISN'T GONNA
HURT YOU, DUDE.
- YEAH, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I PROBABLY 'WOULDN'T
KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH ANY OF THE INFORMATION
THE ARTICLE HAS ANYWAY.
IT MIGHT JUST CONFUSE ME.
- HUH?
- LOOK, I ONLY GOT ONE THING
ON MY MIND RIGHT NOW.
HOW CAN I DRIVE THE EIGHT-SIX
FASTER? THAT'S IT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHICH CAR I'M UP AGAINST.
- HAVEN'T YOU PUT ANY THOUGHT
INTO FINDING A MORE
POWERFUL ENGINE
AND STICKING THAT SUCKER
UNDER THE HOOD OF YOUR CAR?
THAT'D DO IT FOR SURE.
- I NEVER CONSIDERED IT.
- ( Itsuki exclaims )
SERIOUSLY? I'M DYING FOR MORE
POWER FROM MY EIGHT-FIVE.
IT'S LIKE ALL I THINK ABOUT!
- A MORE POWERFUL ENGINE.
I WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE TO START.
- ( brakes screeching )
- TAKUMI!
- HEY, IKETANI. YOU LOOK KINDA
WORRIED. WHAT'S GOING ON?
- YOU DIDN'T HEAR?
THEY'RE COMING TO AKINA.
TONIGHT.
- boy: HERE COMES
THE LAN-EVO CREW.
THIS IS GONNA BE ONE OF THOSE
BATTLES FOR THE RECORD BOOKS.
- THE LAN-EVO'S ARE
FILIN' IN, GUYS!
THIS NIGHT'S
GONNA BE CRAZY!
- THAT WHITE EVO FOUR IN
FRONT MUST BE THE ONE
THAT BEAT TAKESHI IN MYOGI.
AND BEAT HIM PRETTY BAD, TOO.
ALL I'VE HEARD ABOUT HIM IS THAT
HE'S RIDICULOUSLY FAST.
- DUDE! I KNEW IT!
THOSE'RE THE SAME GUYS
I MET OUT AT AKINA LAKE!
- SO YOU'RE THE SPEED STARS.
I'M KYOICHI SUDO, THE LEADER
OF TEAM EMPEROR.
I'M SURE YOU ALREADY KNOW THIS,
BUT WE ONLY HAVE ONE DEMAND.
WE JUST WANNA RACE YOUR
EIGHT-SIX ON THE DOWNHILL.
THAT'S IT.
WE'LL ACCEPT
WHATEVER STIPULATIONS
YOU WANNA PLACE ON THIS THING.
ANY NUMBER OF RACES,
ANY KIND, AND ANY CONDITIONS.
BUT IF YOU FAIL TO WIN
EVEN ONE RACE, JUST ONE,
THEN YOU PEEL OFF YOUR TEAM
STICKER AND HAND IT OVER.
GOT THAT?
- OUR STICKER?
- WHAT ARE THEY GONNA DO
WITH A STICKER? WEIRD...
- YEAH. BUT WHO CARES?
THEY WON'T WIN.
- WE ACCEPT THE CHALLENGE.
- THEN WHAT DO YOU SAY WE
STOP FLAPPIN' OUR JAWS
AND JUMP RIGHT INTO THIS RACE?
IT'S NOT LIKE EVERY HOUR
IN THE WORLD WAITS ON US.
THE FIRST RACE WILL BE
THE MAIN DOWNHILL. GOT IT?
SO, GET YOUR EIGHT-SIX READY.
- WHO IS IT YOU GOT RACIN'
FROM YOUR TEAM?
- THAT'D BE ME. AND I'LL BE
DRIVIN' MY EVO FOUR.
- OKAY, MAN, THEY SAID THAT
THEY WERE READY TO GO
FOR MORE THAN ONE RACE WITH US.
SO WHEN TAKUMI'S DONE,
WHICH ONE OF US IS UP NEXT?
- IF TAKUMI LOSES,
THEN I'LL RACE NEXT.
BUT IF HE CAN BEAT TAKUMI
THEN I SURE AS HELL
WON'T BE ABLE TO DO ANY
DAMAGE OUT THERE.
BUT THERE'S JUST NO WAY
WE'LL BE ABLE TO ACCEPT DEFEAT
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
- THEN AFTER YOU GET YOUR ASS
KICKED, IT'S MY TURN.
- MM-HMM.
- I THINK WE'VE BEEN LEANING ON
TAKUMI A LITTLE TOO MUCH LATELY.
WE NEED TO SHOW HIM THAT
WE'RE CAPABLE OF DOIN' THIS
AS MUCH AS HE IS.
- YEAH!
I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
YOU'RE THE LEAD-OFF MAN.
GO GET HIM!
- ( crowd chattering excitedly )
- HERE COMES THE EIGHT-SIX
FROM THE FUJIWARA TOFU SHOP,
YOU GUYS!
IT'S THE EIGHT-SIX
VERSUS THE EVO FOUR!
GOOD LUCK, MAN!
YOU'RE GUNMA'S DOWNHILL HERO!
- LISTEN, SEIJI, BE CAREFUL.
I WANT YOU TO APPROACH THIS RACE
WITH "SIMULATION THREE".
- COME ON, MAN,
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
"SIMULATION THREE" AGAINST
AN EIGHT-SIX? THAT'S OVERKILL.
- NO, MAN, I'M SERIOUS. DO IT.
I CAN TELL.
I FELT THIS KID'S ENERGY.
THIS EIGHT-SIX IS THE REAL DEAL.
HE'S NOT FAKIN' IT.
HE'S GOT SOMETHIN' THAT
ALLOWED HIM TO BEAT RYOSUKE.
UNTIL WE KNOW WHAT THE
HELL THAT SOMETHIN' IS,
WE CAN'T LET OUR GUARD DOWN.
- I'LL GO AHEAD
AND START THE COUNTDOWN.
- Kyoichi: HOLD UP.
NO NEED FOR THAT.
THIS IS JUST A REGULAR RACE.
NO KIND OF TIME TRIAL HERE.
WE LET THE CAR WITH
LESS ENGINE POWER START
WHENEVER HE FEELS LIKE
AND THE OTHER CAR
CAN START AFTER THAT.
SURE, IT MIGHT NOT BE
WHAT YOU'RE USED TO,
BUT IT'S A FAIR WAY TO ROLL OFF.
THAT LEAVES US STARTIN' LATE,
BUT WE DON'T MIND.
THAT'S THE HANDICAP
WE'RE USED TO
FOR HAVING THE
HORSEPOWER WE GOT.
IT MIGHT NOT BE
COMMON AROUND HERE,
BUT WE CALL IT THE
'HANDICAP METHOD'.
HOW 'BOUT IT?
THAT WORK FOR YOU?
- WORKS FOR ME
IF YOU'RE COOL WITH IT TAKUMI.
- Seiji: I REMEMBER HIM NOW.
THAT'S THE KID WE
SAW AT AKINA LAKE.
NEVER OCCURRED TO ME THAT A PUNK
LIKE HIM COULD BE THE DRIVER
OF THE EIGHT-SIX
EVERYONE'S TALKIN' UP.
KYOICHI'S DEVELOPED
THREE STRATEGIES
TO WIN ON AN OPPONENTS COURSE.
"SIMULATION THREE" IS ONLY USED
ON THE TOUGHEST DRIVERS.
SO WHY THE HELL DOES HE
HAVE ME BUSTING IT OUT
AGAINST THIS EIGHT-SIX?
WHAT A WASTE.
- TAKUMI BLASTED OUTTA THERE!
- YES! GO FOR IT, MAN!
- I'M NOT JUST GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW KILLER THE EVO FOUR IS,
YOU'RE GONNA SEE
HOW GREAT I AM.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Announcer: THE RACE
HAS BEGUN!
WILL SEIJI UNDERSTAND THE REASON
HE'S USING SIMULATION THREE
AGAINST THE EIGHT-SIX?
NEXT ON INITIAL D
SECOND STAGE.
- Kyoichi: "PREMONITION
OF DEFEAT!"
- Announcer: DON'T MISS IT!