-( theme song playing )
- ♪ LET'S ROLL ♪
♪ LET'S ROLL ♪
- ♪ REMEMBER ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, CHECK IT OUT ♪
♪ PUMP THE JAM ♪
- ♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
♪ NAKED MIND ♪
♪ NAKED DESIRE ♪
♪ MOVE, MOVE ♪
♪ IT'S THE TIME! ♪
- SO, YOU'RE THINKING TAKUMI
TOOK HIS SHOW ON THE ROAD
TO AKAGI?
- OH. THERE YOU ARE, BOSS. YEAH,
I MEAN, THAT'S WHAT WE THINK
BUT WE'RE NOT SURE.
- HE WAS ACTIN' ALL KINDS OF
LOONY TODAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HIS
MALFUNCTION WAS.
- DIDN'T WE HAVE SOMEBODY ELSE
FROM OUR TEAM WHO HEADED OUT
TO AKAGI THIS AFTERNOON?
WE COULD ALWAYS TRY
GIVING THAT GUY A CALL.
- NO, IF TAKUMI WENT
THERE TO BATTLE IT OUT
WITH THE EVO THREE,
THEN IT'S TOO LATE, THE
RACE WOULD ALREADY BE A GO.
- ( grunting )
I THOUGHT HE WAS OUT ON A
HOT DATE WITH YOU, NATSUKI,
JUST LIVIN' THE HIGH LIFE.
WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU DOIN'?
- I'M SORRY, GUYS.
- NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE,
YOUNG LADY.
NOTHING THAT'S HAPPENED
IS YOUR FAULT.
BESIDES, WE DON'T KNOW
FOR SURE YET
IF HE'S EVEN ACTUALLY
RACING IN AKAGI.
HE COULD BE OFF DOING
WHO KNOWS WHAT ELSE.
- TAKUMI.
- ( tires screeching )
- I HAVEN'T LOST THIS THING YET.
- HE PASSED THE EIGHT-SIX!
THIS RACE IS OVER.
- NO WORRIES NOW, BRO.
KYOICHI IS WAY TOO
CAREFUL TO LOSE HIS LEAD
ONCE HE'S GOT IT LOCKED IN.
- JUST 'CAUSE HE TOOK THE LEAD
DOESN'T MEAN IT'S LOCKED.
YOU CAN'T RELAX YET, KYOICHI.
THE EIGHT-SIX COULD TURN SOUTH
ON YOU REAL QUICK.
THIS RACE IS FAR
FROM OVER, MY MAN.
- I SEE 'EM!
HERE THEY COME, DUDES!
- THE EVO THREE.
- IT'S THE EMPEROR!
- WHERE'S THE EIGHT-SIX?
- RIGHT THERE!
- ( both gasping )
- HE'S STARTIN' TO MOVE
FASTER AGAIN.
I GET IT NOW.
SINCE HE DOESN'T KNOW
THIS COURSE,
THERE WAS NO WAY HE COULD
ATTACK IT AT FULL SPEED
WHEN HE WAS LEADING.
BUT WHEN HE'S TAILIN' ME,
THE GUY CAN PREDICT WHAT'S AHEAD
BASED ON MY MOVEMENTS.
WITH THAT PIECE OF
CRAP UNDER HIM,
I'M AMAZED HE'S
PULLIN' THIS OFF.
CONSIDERING THE ACCELERATION
GAP BETWEEN US,
HE'S GOTTA BE TURNIN' THESE
CORNERS WAY FASTER THAN I AM.
- ( engine accelerating )
- ( tires screeching )
- GOTTA GIVE IT TO HIM.
HIS CONTROL'S SOMETHIN'
OF A MIRACLE.
I KNOW IT'LL PUT A
HELLUVA STRAIN ON THE TIRES,
BUT I WONDER IF I SHOULD
SPEED UP NOW.
OR MAYBE I SHOULD WAIT
UNTIL THE NEXT STRAIGHTAWAY
TO KICK IT ON UP.
( scoffs ) THAT'S STUPID OF ME!
I ALREADY KNOW THE ANSWER.
I'M NOT GONNA CHANGE
THE PACE AT ALL.
IT'D BE THE CROWNING ACHIEVEMENT
OF DUMB MOVES FOR ME TO DO THAT.
AS FAR AS I KNOW, THAT MIGHT
HAVE EVEN BEEN HOW SEIJI LOST.
A RACER AT THE TOP OF HIS GAME
CONTROLS TIRE STRAIN.
HE DOESN'T ENCOURAGE IT.
I'LL JUST STICK TO THE BASICS.
THAT'S HOW I'LL WIN THIS!
- THE GAP ISN'T
WIDENING ANYMORE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE IT'S ACTUALLY
STARTING TO GET SMALLER.
- IT'S AMAZING. THE EIGHT-SIX
IS MOVING EVEN FASTER
THAN HE DOES IN AKINA.
- WHICH MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
- YEAH? AND WHAT DO YOU
MEAN BY THAT?
- IT'S ALL ABOUT THE MID-SECTION
OF THIS COURSE.
IT CONSISTS SOLELY OF
MID-SPEED S-SHAPED CORNERS.
IN THAT SECTION, THE DRIVER HAS
ONLY A FRACTION OF A SECOND
TO ACCELERATE FROM
ONE CORNER TO THE NEXT.
THEY HAVE TO BE CONSOLIDATED
IN THEIR MOVEMENTS.
- RIGHT.
- THE REST OF THE TIME ON THE
COURSE IS SPENT STRUGGLING
WITH THE CONSTANT G-FORCE
COMING IN FROM THE SIDE.
IT'S NOT AN EASY THING TO DO.
AND WITH THE MISFIRING SYSTEM
THAT KYOICHI HAS INSTALLED
ON HIS SOUPED UP EVO THREE,
HE'S GOT UNBEATABLE ACCELERATION
COMING OUT OF THE CORNERS.
SO THE EIGHT-SIX HAS TO
COMPENSATE FOR THIS ADVANCEMENT
BY ENTERING CORNERS AT A MUCH A
HIGHER RATE OF VELOCITY.
UTILIZING ITS LIGHTWEIGHT BODY
WHICH IS HIS ONLY
REAL ADVANTAGE,
HE WAITS UNTIL THE
LAST POSSIBLE MOMENT
BEFORE BRAKING ON EACH CORNER.
THIS GIVES HIM THE USE OF THE
GRIP ON ALL FOUR TIRES
TO ACHIEVE MAXIMUM
CORNERING SPEED.
IF THE EIGHT-SIX DIDN'T ALREADY
TAKE ON THE QUALITIES
OF BEING AN EXTENSION OF
TAKUMI'S BODY
DUE TO ALL THE HOURS OF
PRACTICE HE'S PUT INTO IT,
WELL, THERE'S NO WAY HE COULD
HAVE POSSIBLY ACHIEVED
A MIRACULOUS PERFORMANCE
LIKE THIS ONE.
- THEN IT SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
HE HASN'T GIVEN UP YET.
- WITH THE FRAME OF MIND
HE'S IN,
HE MIGHT NOT EVEN BE ABLE TO
GRASP THE CONCEPT OF GIVING UP.
HIS VERY BEING IS BUSY
BECOMING ONE WITH THE MACHINE.
THAT'S JUST HIS WAY.
- EVEN IF I CAN MANAGE TO
SHORTEN THE GAP AT THE CORNER,
HE WIDENS THE DAMN THING
ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS.
THAT'S THE POWER DIFFERENTIAL.
- ( phone ringing )
- HELLO, FUJIWARA TOFU SHOP.
OH. YUUICHI, IT'S YOU.
NO, TAKUMI ISN'T BACK YET.
HE'S STILL OUT.
SO WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON HERE?
EVERYONE SEEMS TO BE
LOOKING FOR HIM
LIKE HE'S THE MISSING
LINK OR SOMETHIN'.
HE WENT TO AKAGI?
I SEE.
- I GOTTA GIVE IT TO YOU FOR
EVEN MAKING IT THIS FAR.
IT'S A REAL FEAT FOR ANYONE.
- SEE YA LATER.
- ♪ I'LL BE LIKE AN ANGEL ♪
♪ I WILL BE YOUR SHINING STAR ♪
♪ NOTHING HAS CHANGED AND ♪
♪ I CAN SAY ANOTHER TIME ♪
♪ TRY TO REMEMBER ♪
- THIS IS THE MOMENT,
THE END OF THE S-TURN SECTION.
I CAN KICK IT UP TO FULL SPEED
AFTER THE NEXT CORNER.
THIS IS WHEN THE
SERIOUS RACING STARTS.
AND IT'LL END THIS THING FAST.
- HIS STYLE CHANGED.
- FOR THE FIRST TIME TONIGHT
I'M GONNA USE THIS FEINT,
AND FOLLOW IT UP WITH
AN AGGRESSIVE DRIFT.
THAT'LL SHOW HIM THAT
I'M SERIOUS AS HELL
ABOUT WINNING THIS RACE.
IT'S NOT A LONG STRAIGHTAWAY
BY ANY MEANS.
BUT IT SHOULD BE LONG ENOUGH
TO SHAKE HIM OFF MY TAIL.
- INITIAL D!
- HE'S TOO FAST,
I CAN'T KEEP UP WITH HIM.
MAYBE THIS IS IT.
THIS IS WHERE I LOSE IT.
IS IT EVEN POSSIBLE
TO CATCH HIM?
I'M NOT SURE I CAN DO IT.
- ( crashing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ( engine hissing )
- ( liquid dripping )
- ( sighs )
- HERE IN THE RACIN' WORLD
A BLOWN ENGINE MEANS ONE THING,
THAT YOU LOST.
BUT LIKE I WAS
TELLIN' YOU EARLIER,
I NEVER CONSIDERED THIS
THING A REAL RACE.
NOW YOU CAN ACCEPT THE REALITY
OF WHAT YOU'RE UP AGAINST.
I MEAN, JUST LOOK AT
HOW DEAD YOUR CAR IS.
THE ENGINE'S SMOKIN' LIKE IT'S
BEEN COOKED ON A BAR-B-QUE.
I THINK IT MIGHT BE ABOUT TIME
TO SEND YOUR EIGHT-SIX
OUT TO PASTURE, BRO.
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW FAST
YOU CAN TURN A CORNER,
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A
FAST CAR AND A SLOW CAR
IS JUST TOO MUCH.
WE'LL RACE AGAIN SOMETIME
WHEN YOU HAVE A MACHINE
THAT'S CAPABLE.
ONE THAT ACTUALLY DOES THE JOB.
- ( car approaching )
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, DUDE. I'M GOOD.
I DID WHAT I CAME HERE TO DO.
THE WHOLE THING WAS JUST
FOR FUN ANYWAY.
- FOR FUN?
THAT RACE SEEMED
A LITTLE TOO BREAK-NECK
FOR SOMETHING THAT WAS
JUST A GOOD TIME.
- TRUE ENOUGH. I T WASN'T
EVEN REALLY THAT MUCH FUN.
CONSIDERING THAT THE EIGHT-SIX'S
ENGINE BLEW UP
BEFORE ANY OF THE GOOD TIMES
COULD REALLY GET ROLLIN'.
- HE BLEW OUT HIS ENGINE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
- WHOA, DUDE, I THINK
THE EIGHT-SIX LOST.
- SERIOUSLY?
- THE RED SUNS, MAN,
THEY'RE IN SHOCK.
- HE BLEW HIS FREAKIN' ENGINE.
- THAT EVO THREE WAS JUST
TOO MUCH FOR HIM TO TAKE ON.
- GUESS IT WAS THAT
DIFFERENCE IN POWER.
- AND HE WAS UNDEFEATED
BEFORE TONIGHT.
- NEVER WOULD'VE SEEN
THIS COMIN'.
- I JUST KNEW OUR BOY
WOULD WIN THIS!
- GOIN' UP AGAINST KYOICHI
WITH AN EIGHT-SIX
WAS A SUICIDE MISSION
TO BEGIN WITH.
- EVERYTHING HAPPENED
LIKE WE EXPECTED IT TO,
BUT SOMETHING'S OFF.
I DON'T GET IT.
SOMEHOW, I'M UNSATISFIED
WITH HOW IT TURNED OUT.
MAYBE I EXPECTED ANOTHER ENDING,
OR SOMETHING MORE
FROM THAT EIGHT-SIX.
- Ryosuke: WE'LL SAVE OUR RACE
UNTIL NEXT WEEKEND.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
- Kyoichi: ENJOY YOUR
CONFIDENCE WHILE IT LASTS, MAN.
'CAUSE I'M GONNA CRUSH YOU.
AND WHEN THE DUSTS
FINALLY SETTLES,
YOU'RE GONNA FIND THE EMPERORS
HAVING CONQUERED ALL OF GUNMA.
- ( wind blowing )
- MY BABY.
MY EIGHT-SIX.
- HEY, SON.
- OH. HEY, THERE, DAD.
DAD, I... I JUST...
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT LATER,
ALRIGHT? FIRST THINGS FIRST.
WE GOTTA TOW IT.
- SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING, SON?
STOP GAWKIN' AT HER AND
GET IN THE CAB ALREADY.
- YEAH.
SO, HOW'D YOU FIND OUT?
I MEAN, HOW'D YOU FIND OUT
ABOUT THE WRECK?
- I JUST HAD A FEELING.
- YOU HAD A FEELING?
- YEAH.
- HEY, DAD. I GOT A QUESTION.
- YEAH, WHAT?
- I'VE BEEN SAVIN' UP SOME CASH
FOR A LITTLE WHILE NOW
AND I SHOULD HAVE ABOUT
TWO GRAND IN THE BANK.
MAYBE IT'S NOT ENOUGH BUT I
WANNA TRY AND USE THAT MONEY
TO HELP REPAIR THE ENGINE,
IF THAT'S COOL.
- WELL, YOU'VE GOT A LOT MORE
THAN THAT, BUDDY.
AND, YOU'RE A HELLUVA LOT
RICHER THAN YOU THINK.
- WHAT?
- YOU'VE BEEN
DELIVERING THAT TOFU
EVER SINCE YOU WERE IN
JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL.
I STARTED A SAVINGS ACCOUNT
IN YOUR NAME BACK THEN.
I MEAN, YEAH, I BORROW
A LITTLE BIT FROM IT
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
- GOOD. THEN I CAN USE
THAT MONEY FOR THE REPAIRS TOO.
- I CAN'T LET YOU DO THAT.
- YOU THINK IT'LL JUST BE
TOO EXPENSIVE.
HOW MUCH WOULD THIS
KINDA THING COST, ANYWAY?
- IT'S NOT A MONETARY
ISSUE, TAKUMI.
'CAUSE THAT ENGINE
CAN'T BE REPAIRED,
NO MATTER WHAT YOU TRY.
SEE, THERE'S A SMALL PIN
THAT CONNECTS THE CRANKSHAFT
AND THE CON-ROD.
WELL, THAT PIN SNAPPED AND THAT
CON-ROD PUNCHED A BIG HOLE
IN THE ENGINE BLOCK
FROM THE INSIDE OUT.
LIKE SOME KINDA MINI-EXPLOSION.
- IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
IF I HADN'T ACTED LIKE
AN IRRATIONAL IDIOT
THIS WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED.
- THAT ENGINE IS HISTORY.
WE NEED TO PUT IN ANOTHER ONE.
- WHAT? ANOTHER ONE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- ARE YOU GONNA USE AN ENGINE
FROM ANOTHER CAR
OR ARE WE GONNA HAVE TO
BUILD ONE FROM SCRATCH?
EVEN IF THE THING COULD
RUN AGAIN, WITH A NEW ENGINE,
THE CAR WOULD FEEL
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
AND ISN'T THAT BLOWN ENGINE
SOMETHING SPECIAL TO YOU?
I MEAN, YOU PUT SO MUCH TIME
AND EFFORT INTO BUILDING IT
OVER ALL THESE THE YEARS.
WE SHOULD REALLY TRY
TO FIX IT, I THINK.
LET'S BORROW THE MONEY IF
WE HAVE TO. I DON'T CARE.
I'LL DONATE EVERY DIME I MAKE
TO REPAIRING IT.
- ( chuckles ) COME ON, KID,
WE AREN'T THAT POOR, YA KNOW?
- YEAH, THEN WHY WOULD WE
HAVE TO USE THE ENGINE
FROM SOME OTHER CAR?
- LOOK, IF I COULD I WOULD...
TRUST ME, IF THERE WERE ANY
WAY TO FIX IT, I'D TRY,
BUT THAT SUCKER'S BEYOND REPAIR.
THAT ENGINE IS USELESS.
IT'S SCRAP.
AND THAT'S THE END
OF THAT STORY.
- ( phone ringing )
- TAKUMI STILL HASN'T
GOTTEN HOME YET.
I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM.
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
I JUST KNOW IT.
- TAKUMI, LISTEN.
YOU THINK YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED, DON'T YOU?
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
BEATING YOURSELF UP.
YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT.
YOU JUST HAPPENED TO BE
THE ONE DRIVING IT WHEN IT BLEW.
I PROMISE YOU, SON,
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
- ( crying )
- ( theme song playing )
- Announcer: GOODBYE, EIGHT-SIX.
NOW WE GOT THE EVO THREE
AND THE FC RACING IN AKAGI!
NEXT TIME ON
INITIAL D SECOND STAGE.
"BATTLE AT AKAGI!"
THE BLACK AND WHITE FLASH!
DON'T MISS IT!