- ( theme song playing )
♪ LET'S ROLL ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YEAH, YEAH, CHECK IT OUT ♪
♪ PUMP THE JAM ♪
- ♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
- ♪ LET'S ROLL ♪
♪ NAKED MIND ♪
♪ NAKED DESIRE ♪
♪ NAKED LOVE ♪
♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
♪ MOVE, MOVE ♪
♪ IT'S THE TIME ♪
- Takumi: MAN, IT'S COLD.
HEY, DAD. MIND IF I PULL OUT
THE HEATER? IT'S FREEZING.
- LAZINESS IS WHAT'S
MAKING YOU COLD.
YOU SHOULD TRY STAYING BUSY.
- YEAH, RIGHT. YOU SOUND JUST
LIKE MY PE TEACHER AT SCHOOL.
- ( car engine running )
- HUH?
NO WAY. YOU FIXED IT UP
ALREADY?
DOES IT RUN OR DID YOU
JUST CLEAN IT UP?
- 'COURSE IT RUNS.
BETTER THAN IT HAS IN A WHILE.
AND I PUT IN A NEW ENGINE, TOO.
YOU CAN START USING IT
FOR YOUR DELIVERIES AGAIN.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
I NEED TO TELL YOU, TAKUMI.
I HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO USE SOME
OF YOUR OWN HARD-EARNED MONEY
TO FIX UP THE CAR THIS TIME.
SO FROM NOW ON,
YOU AND I BOTH
OWN IT, FIFTY-FIFTY.
- BUT, IT WAS ME WHO BROKE
THE CAR IN THE FIRST PLACE.
ARE YOU SURE?
- YEAH BUT YOU DIDN'T BLOW
THE ENGINE ON PURPOSE.
IT'S OKAY, I KNOW
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
I HAD TO SPEND EVERYTHING YOU'VE
SAVED UP FROM YOUR PART-TIME JOB
AS WELL AS YOUR
MORNING DELIVERIES
IN ORDER TO PAY FOR THE REPAIRS.
YOU'RE ENTITLED TO FEEL
ATTACHED TO IT IF YOU WANT,
NOW THAT IT'S HALF YOURS.
ANYWAY, I'VE ALREADY
MADE UP MY MIND.
THIS IS HOW IT'S GOING
TO BE FROM NOW ON.
YOU'D BETTER GET GOING, OKAY?
FINISH UP THOSE DELIVERIES
BEFORE THEY GET COLD.
- OH. RIGHT.
SOMETHING ABOUT
THIS FEELS WEIRD.
- I INSTALLED A BUCKET SEAT,
SO YOUR EYE LEVEL'S GOING
TO BE A LITTLE LOWER
THAN YOU'RE USED TO.
WATCH, IN A FEW DAYS YOU WON'T
EVEN NOTICE THE DIFFERENCE.
- THE STEERING'S HEAVIER
THAN BEFORE.
SAME WITH THE CLUTCH.
- ( engine revs )
- ( gasps )
- WHEN YOU FIRST PUSH IN
THE CLUTCH THAT'S THE MOMENT.
THAT'S WHEN YOU
REALLY NOTICE IT.
JUST HOW DIFFERENT IT FEELS.
- ( clock ticking )
- ( ticking echoes )
- GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR BUDDY
IN THE MERCEDES.
LUCK WITH YOUR BUDDY
WITH YOUR BUDDY IN THE MERCEDES.
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR BUDDY
IN THE MERCEDES.
- HOW DID HE FIND OUT?
OF ALL THE PEOPLE TO KNOW.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
I'M SUCH A HORRIBLE PERSON.
IF THIS IS A DREAM,
PLEASE LET ME WAKE UP.
- ( tires screeching )
- MAN, THIS IS REALLY TOUGH
TO CONTROL. WHAT THE HELL?
- Kenji: WHAT?
- Iketani: WHAT?
- THE EIGHT-SIX
IS FIXED ALREADY?
- SERIOUSLY? HAVE YOU TAKEN IT
FOR A TEST DRIVE YET?
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
- HOW'D IT FEEL?
- I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS IT
PRETTY MUCH DROVE
LIKE ANY OTHER CAR DOES.
- ( both gasping )
- VERY FUNNY.
- WE KNOW THAT, DUDE. BUT THAT,
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE MEANT.
NOW STOP PLAYING DUMB WITH US.
- I BET ONCE THEY FIND OUT
HOW AMAZING THE NEW ENGINE IS,
THOSE TWO ARE GOING
TO GO ABSOLUTELY BANANAS.
- SO WHAT'S THE NEW ENGINE LIKE?
IS IT A BEAST?
- IS IT FAST?
- YEAH, ABOUT THAT.
I THINK THE TWO OF YOU ARE GOING
TO BE A LITTLE DISAPPOINTED
ONCE I TELL YOU THIS.
I GET THE FEELING THE NEW ENGINE
IS SLOWER THAN THE OLD ONE.
LIKE IT ISN'T QUITE AS POWERFUL.
- ( gasps )
- ( Itsuki singing )
♪ I'M A LONELY DRIVER,
THE KING OF THE MOUNTAIN PASS ♪
WHOA. THAT IS AN
AWESOME EIGHT-SIX.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'VE NEVER
SEEN THIS ONE BEFORE.
- Yuuichi: HEY, TAKUMI.
I HEARD WHAT YOU SAID JUST NOW.
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT YOUR
NEW ENGINE LACKS POWER?
- OH, I DON'T KNOW. IT JUST
FEELS A LITTLE SLOWER TO ME.
- BUT HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
SEE, YOUR DAD TOLD ME
THAT ENGINE'S PREMIUM.
BEST OF IT'S CLASS.
- UH, MY DAD
REALLY TOLD YOU THAT?
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO DISAGREE
WITH HIM ON THAT ONE.
'CAUSE IT'S KINDA,
WELL, HARD TO CONTROL.
- SURE, I DON'T DOUBT THAT.
BUT ISN'T THAT BECAUSE
IT HAS MORE POWER
THAN YOU WERE USED TO
BEFOREHAND WITH THE OLD ENGINE?
SEE THE NEW ENGINE
SHOULD INCREASE YOUR POWER.
- HEY BOSS, DID YOU
GET A LOOK AT IT?
YOU KNOW WHAT KIND
OF ENGINE IT IS?
- HUH?
- HAVE YOU DRIVEN IT?
- ME? NO.
I HAVEN'T BEEN NEAR IT.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING
ON. I'M JUST GUESSING HERE.
WHAT IS GOING ON, BUNTA?
HOW CAN THE NEW ENGINE WE
PUT IN HAVE LESS POWER?
- Itsuki: WOW, IT'S GOT
A ROLL BAR AND A BUCKET SEAT.
THAT IS SO COOL.
IF I HAD AN EIGHT-SIX
OF MY OWN,
I'D DO IT UP JUST LIKE THIS.
WHOA. OH, AND IT'S GOT
A BOOST METER TOO?
THAT MEANS, THIS EIGHT-SIX
IS A FREAKING TURBO.
THIS IS THE BEST CAR
I'VE EVER SEEN.
I WANT THIS LEVIN
SO BAD. I WANT IT.
( exclaiming in excitement )
- Kazumi: HEY.
WHY ARE YOU SCREAMING?
AND WHAT ARE YOU DOING
ALL OVER MY CAR?
- WELL, YOU KNOW.
I WAS JUST ADMIRING IT.
IT'S A SWEET-ASS RIDE.
- SWEET-ASS RIDE? WHAT THE
HECK ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THIS THING'S ONLY
A DOMESTIC. WEIRDO.
BE HONEST WITH ME. I SAW YOU
MESSING AROUND WITH IT.
IS IT 'CAUSE IT DOESN'T
HAVE GUNMA PLATES?
- YOU OUT OF YOUR
FREAKING MIND?
YOU REALLY THINK
I'D DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- HEY, TAKE IT EASY.
STOP YELLING. CHILL OUT.
- FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
I LOVE EIGHT-SIXES. OKAY?
SO, GO AHEAD AND SUE ME.
AND WATCH WHAT YOU SAY.
US GUNMA PEEPS DON'T MESS
WITH OTHER PEOPLE'S CARS.
YOU GOT THAT? GOOD.
HOW RUDE.
- Wataru: KAZUMI.
IT'S OUR LUCKY DAY. I FOUND THE
HOTEL OUR AUNT'S WORKING AT.
OH, HEY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL. BY THE
WAY, GUNMA IS FULL OF JERKS.
- WHAT? HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
YOU JUST GOT HERE TODAY, SIS.
AND LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE HERE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
SO PLEASE TRY TO HAVE A
LITTLE PATIENCE FOR ME, OKAY?
THIS ATTITUDE OF YOURS
WORRIES ME.
YOU'RE REALLY GOING TO HAVE TO
LEARN HOW TO CHILL OUT MORE.
THE WORK IS ONLY TEMPORARY,
BUT YOU'LL BE DEALING WITH
CUSTOMERS ALL DAY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MAKE
OUR AUNT LOOK BAD, DO YOU?
- I'LL BE FINE.
- LIKE, IF A
CUSTOMER'S BEING RUDE,
YOU CAN'T YELL OR ANYTHING.
- OKAY, I PROMISE. I'LL BE ON
MY BEST BEHAVIOR AT WORK.
BUT ONLY IF YOU PROMISE NOT
TO GO TO AKAGI FOR A SPIN
ON YOUR WAY HOME.
- ALL RIGHT, IT'S A DEAL.
I WOULDN'T WANNA GO UP THERE
ON A CROWDED SUNDAY ANYWAY.
- THINK I'LL FALL FOR THAT?
I CAN ALWAYS SEE
THROUGH YOUR LIES.
I KNOW YOU CAME HERE TO RACE.
AKAGI'S FC, AM I RIGHT?
- THE FC?
I REALLY CAN'T SAY.
- Yuuichi: HEY, ABOUT
THAT NEW ENGINE.
I OVERHEARD TAKUMI
TELLING THE BOYS
IT WAS SLOWER THAN THE OLD ONE.
- YEAH.
- SO WHAT?
DID YOU SET IT UP THAT
WAY ON PURPOSE?
- WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH WORK
THAT WOULD TAKE.
- I DON'T GET IT. WHAT DO
YOU HAVE UP YOUR SLEEVE?
- TAKUMI'S BASICALLY RIGHT.
AND WHAT HE SAID MAKES
PERFECT SENSE.
- HUH?
- OH, COME ON, YUUICHI.
GIVE ME A BREAK HERE.
THE ANSWER'S RIGHT
IN FRONT OF YOUR BIG UGLY MUG.
- IT IS?
- FIGURE IT OUT FOR YOURSELF.
I'M GOING TO HANG UP.
TOO MUCH TO DO.
- BUNTA, WAIT. DON'T HANG
UP YET. I STILL HAVE TO...
- ( phone dialtone )
- WHAT IS WITH HIM?
- ( engine revving )
- MAN, IT'S BEEN DAYS.
DAMN IT. I STILL
CAN'T CONTROL IT.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( panting )
- CRAP. I'M GOING TO BE LATE
FOR WORK AGAIN.
WELL, LOOK WHO IT IS. IT'S THAT
GIRL WHO FREAKED OUT ON ME.
- INITIAL D.
- I'LL TAKE SIX TO GO.
FIVE IN THE BAG AND I THINK
I'LL EAT ONE NOW.
- ALL RIGHT. THAT'S SIX-SIXTY
YEN. CAREFUL, IT'S HOT.
- MMM.
UH-OH. I'M TEN SHORT.
I'M SO SORRY, BUT IS THERE ANY
WAY YOU COULD BREAK A 10,000?
- I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH
CHANGE TO COVER THAT.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO TELL YOU.
- REALLY?
OH, NO.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- HEY, THANKS FOR DOING THAT.
I PROMISE I'LL PAY YOU BACK.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
- BUT I WANT TO.
I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO SLEEP
AT NIGHT IF I DIDN'T.
LET ME KNOW WHERE TO FIND YOU
SO I CAN MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
- OKAY. WELL, DO YOU SEE
THAT GAS STATION?
THAT'S WHERE I WORK.
I'M THERE MOST DAYS.
- I JUST STARTED A TEMP JOB
AT THE HOTEL IN TOWN
WHERE I'M STAYING.
MY AUNT WORKS THERE.
I'M RUNNING AN ERRAND
FOR HER RIGHT NOW.
- I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT THE
OTHER DAY. YOU'RE A NICE GUY.
- YEAH?
- I KNOW YOU'RE MAD
AND SORRY I WAS MEAN
BUT I WAS ACTUALLY HAPPY.
PEOPLE RARELY COMPLEMENT
MY BROTHER'S LEVIN.
- OH, SO IT'S YOUR
BROTHER'S CAR.
- I REALLY DON'T KNOW
ANYONE HERE IN GUNMA YET.
SO, I WAS STARTING TO GET KINDA
BORED AND A LITTLE LONELY TOO.
YOU AND I SHOULD HANG OUT
SOMETIME. I'M KAZUMI AKIYAMA.
- ITSUKI. ITSUKI TAKEUCHI.
- SEE YOU AROUND. BYE.
- ( heartbeat resonating )
- THIS FEELING. COULD IT BE?
AW, CRAP.
- SO, AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX
IS BACK, HUH?
- KENTA WAS TELLING ME HE SAW IT
DRIVE BY JUST THE OTHER NIGHT.
HE SAID IT HAD
THE FUJIWARA TOFU SIGN
RIGHT ON THE DOOR
AND EVERYTHING.
- IT KINDA MAKES ME WONDER.
THINK MAYBE HE PUT
IN A NEW ENGINE?
- I THINK WE SHOULD DO
A LITTLE SCOUTING.
- YEAH.
- ( car approaching )
- HEAR THAT?
- ( engine revving )
- I KNOW THAT SOUND.
- tires screeching )
- HEY BRO.
IS THAT HIM?
- YEAH. SOUNDS TO ME,
LIKE HE ISN'T FULLY ACCUSTOMED
TO THE NEW ENGINE YET.
LOOKS LIKE THE EIGHT-SIX
HAS BEEN REBORN AS A MONSTER.
- WELL, YOU WERE GONE
LONGER THAN I EXPECTED.
SO, DID ANYTHING HAPPEN?
- NOT MUCH.
I FINISHED MY DELIVERIES,
DROVE A FEW LAPS
AROUND THE PASS.
I GUESS I MUST'VE USED A LITTLE
MORE GAS THAN I MEANT TO,
'CAUSE THE TANK'S SITTING JUST
ABOVE EMPTY. SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- UH. I DON'T CARE.
- HEY, DAD?
- HMM?
- CORNERING IN THE NEW CAR IS
TOUGHER THAN I THOUGHT IT'D BE.
IT CAME SO EASY
TO ME BEFOREHAND
BUT NOW I FEEL LIKE
I'M STRUGGLING
JUST TO GET THROUGH
A WHOLE TURN.
IT'S REALLY FRUSTRATING.
I'VE BEEN TRYING A FEW
DIFFERENT THINGS,
BUT SO FAR IT'S NOT
GOING SO WELL.
- THAT'S THE ATTITUDE, SON.
RATHER THAN MESSING AROUND
WITH THE SUSPENSION SETTINGS,
YOU'RE CHANGING
UP YOUR TECHNIQUE
TO MAKE UP FOR THE GAP.
GO AHEAD AND STRUGGLE
WITH IT FOR A WHILE.
TRIAL AND ERROR IS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF THE LEARNING PROCESS.
GIVEN TIME, THIS CAR WILL
ACTUALLY IMPROVE YOUR TECHNIQUE
AND BEST OF ALL
YOU WON'T EVEN KNOW IT.
YOU'RE STILL GROWING AS A DRIVER
AND THIS CAR IS
GOING TO BE A BIG HELP
IN YOUR JUMP TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
- ( Itsuki humming )
- HEY, ITSUKI.
- KAZUMI?
- I'M HERE TO PAY YOU BACK,
JUST LIKE I SAID I WOULD.
HERE. AND THAT SHOULD
MAKE US EVEN, OKAY?
- YOU REALLY SAVED ME YESTERDAY.
- YEAH?
- OH, GREAT.
WHO'S THAT?
- SEE YOU TONIGHT.
- ( laughs )
- SO, WHO'S THE CHICK?
EH, BUD?
- OH, SHE'S JUST
A FRIEND OF MINE.
- A FRIEND?
I THOUGHT YOUR MANTRA WAS
THAT RACERS DON'T NEED GIRLS.
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO
MISTER LONELY BOY RACE CAR
DRIVER ITSUKI, HUH?
ANSWER ME WHEN
I AM TALKING TO YOU.
- ( car honks )
- NO WAY. HE DRIVES A LEVIN TOO.
ITSUKI. OH MY GOSH,
IS THIS YOUR CAR?
- SURE IS.
- Kazumi: OH, ME?
WELL, I ACTUALLY GRADUATED
FROM HIGH SCHOOL
JUST THIS LAST SPRING
SO, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
I'M A YEAR OLDER THAN YOU.
- WHAT DID YOU DO
AFTER YOU GRADUATED?
- I WENT STRAIGHT OUT AND GOT
A JOB. WELL, SORT OF.
BUT I DIDN'T LIKE IT VERY MUCH.
MY BROTHER'S ALWAYS
TELLING ME HOW IMPATIENT I AM
AND DON'T TELL HIM I SAID SO,
BUT HE'S RIGHT.
- YOUR BROTHER? YOU MEAN
THE ONE WITH THE EIGHT-SIX?
- MMM-HMM.
YOU MAY THINK IT'S WEIRD
BUT HE AND I HAVE BEEN
ATTACHED AT THE HIP FOREVER.
EVEN WHEN HE'D GO RACING.
HE'S GOOD. THEY SAY
HE'S THE FASTEST
DOWNHILL RACER IN SAITAMA.
WATARU'S DOWNHILL IS...
OH, SORRY. I DIDN'T TELL YOU.
MY BROTHER'S NAME IS WATARU.
HIS DOWNHILL IS PRETTY AMAZING.
MY DUMB BROTHER.
HE'S STARTING TO USE
ME AS AN EXCUSE,
TO COME UP TO GUNMA
AND RACE CARS.
IN FACT, HE'S PROBABLY
RACING A PASS EVEN AS WE SPEAK.
- Keisuke: SORRY, MAN.
YOU SEE, THE RED SUNS
HAVE A STRICT POLICY
AGAINST RACING IN AKAGI.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND. IS IT
BECAUSE I DRIVE AN EIGHT-SIX?
- NO. IT'S BECAUSE
IT'S TOO EASY.
EVERY SINGLE RACER IN GUNMA
KNOWS THAT THE RED SUNS
DO NOT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
RACE ON THEIR OWN TURF.
SO IT'S REALLY NOTHING PERSONAL.
THERE IS ONE THING
I WANT TO BE CLEAR ABOUT THOUGH.
WE TAKE OUR EIGHT-SIXES
VERY SERIOUSLY.
IN FACT. GUNMA'S OWN EIGHT-SIX
IS A DOWNHILL SPECIALIST.
YEAH, OUR BOY HAS NEVER
LOST A SINGLE BATTLE.
- REALLY?
- HE BEAT EVERY CAR
HE'S OFFICIALLY RACED.
- HE HAS? EVEN MORE
POWERFUL CARS?
- YEAH.
- SO WHEN I BEAT YOU,
YOU CAN TELL ME
WHETHER OR NOT I'M BETTER
THAN THIS GOLDEN BOY OF YOURS.
- WATCH IT.
-IT'S OKAY, KENTA. WE DON'T
RACE HERE, SO FORGET IT.
- LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU THINK YOU ARE
BUT TRY COMING BACK IN TEN YEARS
IF YOU WANNA TALK
TRASH TO KEISUKE.
YOU GOT THAT, DOUCHEBAG?
- FINE THEN.
- ( engine revs )
- I HATE TO DO THIS TO YOU
BUT YOU'VE LEFT ME WITH
NO OTHER CHOICE.
- IF YOU'RE THAT DESPERATE FOR
A RACE, WHY NOT, I'VE GOT TIME.
- YEAH. THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
LET'S TEACH THIS JERK A LESSON
OR TWO IN REAL STREET RACING.
THAT SOUND.
HE'S GOT A TURBO.
- HE WAS ABLE TO FOLLOW ME
OUT OF THE CORNER.
HIS CAR'S POWER
IS EXTRAORDINARY.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
IS IT REALLY AN EIGHT-SIX?
- I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY HOW
MUCH HORSEPOWER HE'S CARRYING
BUT THAT MUCH JUICE WOULD
USUALLY HURT HIS CONTROL
ESPECIALLY IN THE TURNS.
A TURBO IN THAT CAR
IS A LOOSE CANNON
BUT SOMEHOW HE'S FINDING
A WAY TO CONTROL IT.
DAMN IT. I CAN'T KEEP UP
ANYMORE. THIS SUCKS.
- ( engine revs )
- I MAY NOT KNOW AS MUCH AS MY
BROTHER WHEN IT COMES TO RACING.
BUT I KNOW ENOUGH TO RECOGNIZE
WHEN I'M UP AGAINST
A REAL THREAT.
- YOU BETTER GET SERIOUS DUDE
OR I'LL LEAVE YOU IN THE DUST.
- Man: OH MAN,
THAT DOES NOT LOOK GOOD.
WE'RE REALLY LUCKY WE WEREN'T
GOING TOO FAST, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH.
- MAY NOT BE A BAD IDEA
TO PUT UP A WARNING REFLECTOR.
A CAR COULD EASILY CRASH
INTO US IN THIS BLIND CORNER.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( screams )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Announcer: WATARU HAS
HEARD THE RUMORS
AND WANTS TO RACE GUNMA'S
OTHER EIGHT-SIX.
BUT WHAT WILL HAPPEN NEXT?
ON THE NEXT
INITIAL D, SECOND STAGE.
- THE EIGHT-SIX TURBO.
- Announcer: DON'T MISS IT.