- ( theme song playing )
♪ LET'S ROLL ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, CHECK IT OUT ♪
♪ PUMP THE JAM ♪
- ♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
♪ LET'S ROLL ♪
- ♪ NAKED MIND ♪
♪ NAKED DESIRE ♪
♪ NAKED MIND ♪
♪ NAKED LOVE ♪
♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
♪ M-O-V-E, MOVE ♪
♪ IT'S THE TIME ♪
- ( engine revving )
- ( screams )
- ( tires screeching )
- DIDN'T SEE THAT ONE COMING.
- IT WAS JUST GETTING
INTERESTING.
SHAME WE COULDN'T FINISH.
- (engine revving )
- WE'LL HAVE TO TRY
THAT AGAIN SOON. UNTIL THEN.
DON'T ACT SO COOL, BUDDY.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY
RACER OUT THERE.
I'VE JUST GOT ONE MORE THING
TO LOOK FORWARD TO NOW.
- THEY DIDN'T NEED YOU
TO WORK ON A SUNDAY AFTERNOON?
OH WELL. I GUESS YOU'RE NOT THAT
USEFUL AFTER ALL THEN, HUH?
- YOU'RE SO RUDE.
I GOT UP EARLY
AND WORKED THIS MORNING WHEN
THEY WERE SUPER BUSY.
PLUS, IT'S BEEN LIKE TWO WEEKS
SINCE I'VE HAD A DAY OFF
SO THEY LET ME GO
FOR THE AFTERNOON.
- OH YEAH?
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S OKAY.
- WHAT'D YOU COME HERE FOR
ANYWAY? I WASN'T EXPECTING YOU.
- HUH? WELL, I JUST WANTED TO
SEE HOW YOU WERE DOING,
THAT'S ALL.
MOM AND DAD HAVE BEEN REALLY
WORRIED ABOUT YOU LATELY.
- JUST TELL THEM
I'M DOING FINE
AND THAT I'VE BEEN WORKING
REALLY, REALLY HARD.
- IS THAT THE TRUTH?
UH OH, THE TANK'S
ALMOST ON EMPTY.
BETTER STOP AND FILL HER UP.
- HEY, I KNOW OF A GAS STATION
NEARBY. MY FRIEND WORKS THERE.
LET'S GO TO THAT ONE.
- ( humming )
- JUST PULL HER FORWARD.
HEY.
- THAT'S ITSUKI. HE'S THE FRIEND
OF MINE I TOLD YOU ABOUT.
- WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
- TWENTY LITERS. HIGH OCTANE.
- SURE.
- MAN, HER BROTHER'S
A GOOD LOOKING GUY.
- HMM. I'VE SEEN
THAT EIGHT-SIX TURBO BEFORE.
- SO, MY SISTER TELLS ME
YOU AND HER ARE FRIENDS.
DON'T YOU THINK SHE'S JUST A
LITTLE BIT TOO STRONG-WILLED?
- UH. NO, I WOULDN'T SAY
SHE'S TOO STRONG-WILLED.
- ENOUGH THIRD DEGREE.
GIVE HIM A BREAK AND DON'T
ASK HIM STUPID QUESTIONS.
- MY SISTER'S A GOOD GIRL, SO BE
NICE TO HER. CAN YOU DO THAT?
- OF COURSE.
- NOW I KNOW THIS IS KIND
OF A CHANGE OF SUBJECT,
BUT I'VE HEARD THAT GUNMA HAS
ONE OF THE FASTEST EIGHT-SIXES
TO RUN THE PASSES IN YEARS.
- HUH?
- FROM EVERYTHING THAT I'VE
HEARD ABOUT HIM HE'S GOOD.
AS IN UNDEFEATED GOOD.
- NOW I KNOW GUNMA'S A
PRETTY BIG PLACE AND ALL
BUT IT'S WORTH A SHOT.
SO, I WAS WONDERING IF YOU
MIGHT BE ABLE TO GIVE ME
ANY INFORMATION ABOUT THIS GUY.
- OF COURSE I DO.
HE'S LIKE MY BEST FRIEND.
- WAIT, SERIOUSLY?
- OH, YEAH.
- YOUR NAME'S ITSUKI, RIGHT?
LOOK, I KNOW WE LITERALLY
JUST MET AND EVERYTHING,
BUT IS THERE ANY POSSIBLE WAY
YOU COULD SET UP A MEETING
WITH HIM FOR ME?
I SURE WOULD APPRECIATE IT.
I'D JUST REALLY LOVE
TO PICK HIS BRAIN.
YOU KNOW, WE COULD SIT AROUND,
TALK SHOP ABOUT OUR EIGHT-SIXES.
- SURE, I CAN SET THAT UP.
HE'S A BIT SLOW,
BUT HE'S A REALLY NICE GUY.
YOU'LL LIKE HIM
ARE YOU FREE TONIGHT?
'CAUSE I'M PRETTY SURE HE IS.
- REALLY?
- NO PROBLEM.
I'LL HOOK YOU UP.
- I WAS PLANNING TO SEE HIM
TONIGHT ANYWAY,
SO THIS SHOULD WORK
OUT PERFECTLY.
- WOW. THAT'D BE GREAT.
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR BUSINESS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOUR FRIEND
ACTUALLY KNOWS THAT GUY.
I MEAN, TALK ABOUT
A STROKE OF LUCK, RIGHT?
I'M GLAD YOU AND ITSUKI
ARE BUDDIES NOW.
- LOOK, I DON'T LIKE THIS.
IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE YOU'RE ONLY
INTERESTED IN ITSUKI'S FRIEND
INSTEAD OF ITSUKI HIMSELF,
LIKE YOU'RE GOING TO USE
HIM OR SOMETHING.
- OH, COME ON, THAT ISN'T TRUE.
HE SEEMS LIKE A NICE ENOUGH KID.
- THEN WHAT ARE YOU MEETING
HIS FRIEND FOR, HUH?
- THERE'S NO REAL REASON.
I'M JUST INTERESTED IN
MEETING HIM, THAT'S ALL.
HE MUST BE PRETTY GOOD
TO HAVE WON ALL HIS RACES.
GUNMA'S A REALLY
COMPETITIVE AREA.
- WELL, I HOPE YOU DON'T DO
ANYTHING STUPID.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU ARE
WHEN IT COMES TO STREET RACING.
YOU END UP LOSING YOUR COOL
OVER NOTHING. IT'S EMBARRASSING.
- Itsuki: COME ON, TAKUMI,
BE A PAL, PLEASE.
ALL I WANT IS FOR KAZUMI'S
BROTHER TO LIKE ME, THAT'S IT.
THIS IS LIKE THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY FOR ME
TO SCORE SOME SERIOUS
POINTS WITH HER.
IT MAY BE MY ONLY SHOT.
- YEAH OKAY. I'LL BE
THERE. BUT HERE'S THE DEAL.
- I'M NOT INTERESTED IN RACING
THIS GUY, NO MATTER WHAT.
THAT NEW ENGINE I'VE GOT
JUST ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
- DUDE, DON'T EVEN
WORRY ABOUT IT.
- I LEARNED MY LESSON AFTER
THAT WHOLE FIASCO
WITH TAKESHI AND THE NIGHT KIDS.
YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE KAZUMI'S
BROTHER. HE'S A SUPER NICE GUY.
I THINK THE TWO OF YOU
ARE REALLY GOING TO GET ALONG.
THREE BEAUTIFUL EIGHT-SIXES
SIDE BY SIDE.
EVEN THOUGH MINE'S
TECHNICALLY AN EIGHT-FIVE.
- DAMN, HE'S YOUNG.
- HEY, YOU KNOW THAT
EIGHT-SIX TURBO
THAT FILLED UP THIS AFTERNOON?
I'M PRETTY SURE
I'VE SEEN IT BEFORE.
IT MUST'VE BEEN BACK WHEN
I WENT TO SEE THE RED SUNS
RACE AGAINST TEAM EMPEROR.
- OH, YEAH?
- YEAH, IT HAD SOME
AMAZING UPHILL ACCELERATION.
GOT ME THINKING THAT SINCE
HER BROTHER'S OBVIOUSLY
A TALENTED DRIVER
WITH A SWEET CAR.
I DON'T KNOW, HE MAY NOT
BE TOO IMPRESSED WITH ITSUKI.
- OH AND THERE YOU
GO AGAIN, DUMMY.
YOU KNOW IT'S NOT GOING TO
DO YOUR SOCIAL LIFE MUCH GOOD
THINKING LIKE THAT.
- HUH?
- YOU DON'T SEE ITSUKI WORRYING
ABOUT SUCH INSIGNIFICANT THINGS.
A GUY WHO'S CLUMSY
BUT HAS A POSITIVE ATTITUDE
HAS THE UPPER HAND ON ANY GUY
WHO WORRIES ALL THE TIME.
YOU ARE TOO YOUNG TO WORRY.
- Wataru: I HEAR YOU JUST
GOT A NEW ENGINE?
- OH YEAH DUDE, BUT GET THIS.
IT'S LIKE A CRAP-TON SLOWER
THAN THE OLD ONE USED TO BE.
- RIGHT, TAKUMI?
- MMM-HMM.
THAT'S WHY HE WON'T
BE RACING FOR A LITTLE WHILE,
AT LEAST UNTIL HE FIGURES OUT
HOW TO SQUEEZE SOME MORE POWER
OUT OF IT. I'M RIGHT, RIGHT?
- YEAH. SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- IS IT JUST A REGULAR
OLD FOUR-A-G OR WHAT?
- UH. HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW
ALL THAT MUCH ABOUT ENGINES.
I MEAN THE POWER'S
PRETTY DECENT, I GUESS.
BUT IT'S REALLY HARD TO CONTROL.
SO YEAH, WHATEVER KIND
IT IS, IT'S WEIRD.
- WELL, WOULD YOU MIND IF I
TOOK A LOOK AT IT FOR MYSELF?
- UH. NO.
GO AHEAD.
- WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- HUH?
- THIS IS BIZARRE.
IT'S LIKE A FOUR-A-G ENGINE,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
IT'S TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
IF THIS IS SOME KIND OF
AN ELABORATE JOKE?
I'M SURE AS HELL NOT LAUGHING.
- WHAT?
- LOOK GUYS, I DON'T KNOW WHERE
IT IS YOU GOT THIS ENGINE FROM.
BUT TELLING ME IT'S SLOW
AND THINKING I WON'T NOTICE
IS FREAKING INSULTING.
- WAIT, I DON'T...
WHY'S HE SO MAD?
- WHO KNOWS?
- I THOUGHT SINCE
WE BOTH DRIVE EIGHT-SIXES
YOU'D BE STRAIGHT WITH ME.
SO, WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
IS MY CHEAP TURBO NOT
GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU?
- I DESERVE AN EXPLANATION,
SO SOMEBODY START TALKING.
- WOULD YOU JUST STOP IT? I KNEW
YOU WERE GOING TO BE LIKE THIS.
- STAY OUT OF IT, KAZUMI.
THIS DOESN'T CONCERN YOU.
I'VE BEEN AROUND CARS
FOR A LONG TIME
AND I'VE NEVER SEEN
AN ENGINE LIKE THIS
USED FOR STREET RACING.
THIS IS AN ENGINE
DESIGNED FOR THE PROS.
- ( both gasp )
- I COULD SAVE UP FOR YEARS
AND I COULD NEVER EVEN DREAM
OF OWNING AN ENGINE LIKE THIS.
HELL, ANY STREET RACER I KNOW
WOULD SELL THEIR OWN MOTHER
IN A HEARTBEAT
TO HAVE AN ENGINE LIKE THAT
IN THEIR RIDE, MYSELF INCLUDED.
- SO WHAT?
BIG DEAL.
- I DON'T REALLY CARE
WHAT KIND OF ENGINE YOU HAVE,
BUT WHAT I DON'T GET IS WHY YOU
FELT THE NEED TO LIE ABOUT IT.
WHY NOT JUST ADMIT
YOU'RE FAST?
ALL I CAME HERE TO DO
WAS TALK AND TRADE CAR STORIES,
AND YOU LIED RIGHT TO MY FACE?
- HOLD ON.
WE'RE NOT LYING TO YOU.
- DUDE, DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
I DON'T CARE ENOUGH ABOUT
YOUR OPINION TO LIE TO YOU.
COME ON, LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE, ITSUKI.
I'VE GOT NOTHING ELSE
TO SAY TO THIS GUY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- FINE, RUN AWAY. JUST KNOW
I'M NOT DONE WITH YOU YET.
- UH, OH. TAKUMI'S STARTING
TO LOSE IT. THIS IS BAD NEWS.
- KAZUMI?
- WATARU, I...
- INITIAL D.
- WHAT THE HELL'S
THE MATTER WITH YOU?
ITSUKI INTRODUCED YOU TO HIS
FRIEND OUT OF THE KINDNESS
OF HIS OWN HEART,
SO YOU NEED TO APOLOGIZE
TO THEM, RIGHT NOW. DO IT.
IF YOU'RE NOT MAN ENOUGH
TO SAY YOU'RE SORRY
THEN GET OUT OF HERE
AND DON'T EVER COME BACK.
- WHOA, SHE'S INTENSE.
- YOU JERK. HOW DARE YOU TALK
TO MY FRIENDS LIKE THAT.
I'M DOING THE BEST I CAN
TO MAKE A LIFE FOR MYSELF
IN A PLACE WHERE
I BARELY KNOW ANYONE.
AND IT SEEMS LIKE EVERY TIME
YOU SHOW UP IN MY LIFE,
YOU RUIN IT WITH
YOUR CHILDISH ISSUES.
- I UNDERSTAND. WELL, I GUESS
I BETTER GET GOING, THEN.
- ( engine starts )
- HEY BUD. I'M GOING
TO GET GOING TOO.
WHAT? DON'T DO THAT.
PLEASE, MAN.
YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE ME
HERE ALL BY MYSELF.
- SORRY. GOOD LUCK.
- WAIT, NO.
TAKUMI. TAKUMI.
WAIT, COME BACK.
- OH MAN.
I REALLY DIDN'T SEE
THAT ONE COMING.
I GUESS MOVING TO GUNMA
WASN'T SUCH A BAD THING
FOR KAZUMI AFTER ALL.
BUT FOR ME...
( sighs )
I'M NOT SO SURE.
- ( car approaching )
- I'M SORRY.
MY BROTHER HAS A TENDENCY
TO ACT LIKE A REAL JERK
WHEN IT COMES TO RACING CARS.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO APOLOGIZE.
- WHEN I SAW THE LOOK ON YOUR
FACES AFTER HE CHEWED YOU OUT,
I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS
SOMETHING JUST CAME OVER ME.
MY ARM MOVED BEFORE
I KNEW WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
I HAVE A TEMPER. YOU CAN
PROBABLY TELL.
BUT HE DID DESERVE IT.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT MAD OR ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW TO BE HONEST,
I WAS ACTUALLY KIND
OF GLAD WHEN YOU DID IT.
LOOK, YOU GOT UPSET. BUT YOU
WERE ONLY TRYING TO DEFEND US
AND I THINK THAT'S REALLY
AWESOME OF YOU.
- WHY DID YOU STOP?
I WOULDN'T HAVE
CHASED AFTER YOU,
JUST IN CASE YOU WERE WONDERING.
BUT SEEING THAT WE'RE
BOTH HERE NOW,
I WOULDN'T MIND PICKING UP
RIGHT WHERE WE LEFT OFF.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH ME. I GET IT, OKAY?
BUT THERE IS ONE
THING I NEED TO KNOW
AND I COULD REALLY USE
YOUR EXPERTISE.
I NEED TO KNOW THE TRUTH
ABOUT THIS ENGINE.
I NEED TO KNOW IF IT'S REALLY
ALL THAT YOU SAY IT IS.
I CAN TELL IT'S NOT
A NORMAL ENGINE
BY THE WAY IT LOOKS AND FEELS
BUT IF WHAT YOU SAY
IS REALLY TRUE,
THAT IT HAS ENOUGH POWER TO BE
WORTHY OF THE PROFESSIONALS.
THEN I WANT TO KNOW
WHY I CAN'T REACH THAT POWER.
I DON'T KNOW ENGINES. YOU DO
AND I REALLY NEED SOME ADVICE.
- SORRY, MAN, BUT I'M HAVING
A HARD TIME BELIEVING YOU.
HOW CAN A RACER NOT KNOW EVERY
SINGLE INCH OF HIS OWN CAR
LIKE THE BACK OF HIS HAND?
IF YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT,
WHERE THE HELL DID YOU
GET IT FROM ANYWAY?
- TECHNICALLY, THIS IS MY
DAD'S CAR AND HE'S THE ONE
WHO BOUGHT THE ENGINE NOT ME.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING HE
DOESN'T WANT TO TELL ME.
AND THAT'S A LOT.
- I GUESS YOUR DAD MUST HAVE
A JOB IN THE RACING INDUSTRY
IF HE WAS ABLE TO GET HIS HANDS
ON A BLOCK THIS ADVANCED.
- NO, HE OWNS A TOFU SHOP.
- ( gasps )
HOW CAN A GUY MAKING TOFU GET
A PROFESSIONAL QUALITY ENGINE?
IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU JUST
UP AND BUY FROM THE STORE
ON A WEEKEND.
YOU KNOW WHAT, FINE.
YOU SHOULD BE GETTING
PLENTY OF POWER OUT OF IT,
SO I'M JUST AS
CURIOUS AS YOU ARE.
DO YOU MIND DRIVING ME
AROUND FOR A LITTLE WHILE
SO I CAN TAKE A LISTEN?
IT'S THE ONLY WAY I CAN GET
A GOOD FEELING FOR IT.
- ( music playing )
- SO? WHAT'S THE BIG PLAN?
HAVE ONE?
WELL, I FIGURED IT'D TAKE
AT LEAST A FEW WEEKS TO A MONTH
FOR HIM TO FIGURE IT
OUT ON HIS OWN.
THE BOY'S HAD MORE THAN
ENOUGH PRACTICE WITH IT.
- THOSE PARTS YOU ORDERED
ARRIVED AT MY SHOP
JUST THE OTHER DAY.
DON'T YOU THINK
WE SHOULD INSTALL THEM?
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT YET.
I WAS HOPING TO HOLD
OFF ON THOSE
UNTIL I GOT SOME SORT OF
REACTION FROM TAKUMI.
-HUH?
- IT'S GOOD HE'S TRYING TO
COMPENSATE WITH HIS TECHNIQUE
RATHER THAN GOING
FOR SOME EASY FIX.
BUT TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
I FIGURED HE WOULD HAVE
NOTICED BY NOW.
I GUESS WE'LL JUST
HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE.
- SOMETHING'S OFF.
THE SHIFTING SEEMS TO BE
STALLING OUT THE ACCELERATION.
IT HAS PLENTY OF POWER
WHEN HE REACHES THE REV LIMIT,
BUT EVERY TIME HE UPSHIFTS,
HE LOSES A LOT OF TORQUE.
THIS ENGINE MUST BE
DEFECTIVE. IT'S A DUD.
THERE'S NO COMPARING IT
TO MY TURBO. BUT WHY?
THIS CAN'T BE
IT'S FULL POTENTIAL.
- ( tires screeching )
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
AGAIN? WHY?
OF COURSE. NOW I GET IT.
IT'S SO SIMPLE.
- ( sighs )
- WELL, GOOD NEWS.
I CAN TELL YOU WHY
YOU AREN'T GETTING
VERY MUCH POWER.
THE PROBLEM'S PRETTY SIMPLE
AND YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO FIX IT YOURSELF.
THERE, YOU SEE THAT?
THE ISSUE IS WITH
YOUR TACHOMETER.
- TACHOMETER?
- IT'S NO GOOD. NOT
FOR THAT ENGINE.
IT DOESN'T GO HIGH ENOUGH.
THIS IS AN ENGINE THAT
GENERATES IT'S MOST POWER
AT A VERY HIGH RPM,
WHICH IS WHY THEY CALL IT
A HIGH-REV ENGINE.
PROFESSIONAL NATURALLY ASPIRATED
ENGINES ARE ALL LIKE THIS,
THAT'S WHY PROS
USE THEM EXCLUSIVELY.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE GETTING
A SURGE OF POWER
RIGHT BEFORE YOU SHIFT?
YOU'RE NOT REVVING IT
HIGH ENOUGH.
THAT RED LINE'S
A COUPLE THOUSAND REV'S SHORT.
I'M PRETTY SURE YOU'VE
ONLY BEEN PUSHING IT
TO AROUND SEVENTY PERCENT
OF IT'S FULL CAPACITY.
IF I HAD TO GUESS WHAT
THIS ENGINE'S CAPABLE OF,
I'D SAY AT LEAST 10,000 RPM'S
EASY, IF NOT MORE THAN THAT.
A TACHOMETER THAT
ONLY READS UP TO 8000
IS CRIPPLING
THE CAR'S ABILITY.
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT EVEN COMING
CLOSE TO THE SWEET SPOT.
THIS PUPPY'S A CERTIFIED BEAST
COMPARED TO THE
EIGHT-SIX'S STOCK ENGINE.
IT'S CALLED A FOUR AG BUT IT
ACTUALLY HAS A FIVE-VALVE HEAD
THAT WAS ADAPTED FROM
THE NEWER ONE-OH-ONE SERIES
THEY JUST RELEASED.
THERE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
A V-V-T DEVICE THAT SWITCHES
THE VALVE TIMING AT BOTH
LOWER AND HIGHER RPM'S.
THE FACT THAT YOURS DOESN'T HAVE
ONE CAN ONLY MEAN ONE THING.
THAT THIS BABY IS IN A
WHOLE OTHER CLASS
CALLED A SUPER HIGH-REV ENGINE.
WHILE WE WERE DRIVING,
I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
SOMETHING ELSE I THOUGHT
WAS WORTH MENTIONING.
THE INSTRUMENT PANEL YOU HAVE
IS NOT ONLY CHEAP,
IT'S MISSING SOME IMPORTANT READ
OUTS YOU'LL DEFINITELY NEED.
AT THE VERY LEAST,
YOU'LL WANT THE WATER TEMP
AND OIL PRESSURE GAUGES.
WHOEVER IT WAS THAT DID
THE INSTALLATION ON THIS ENGINE
HAS AN IMPECCABLE KNOWLEDGE
OF ADVANCED AUTO MECHANICS.
BOTH THE TIRES AND THE BRAKES
ARE PERFECTLY BALANCED.
SAME GOES FOR THE BODY.
IT MAKES YOU WONDER WHY
WOULD THE INSTALLER
WANT TO LEAVE OUT
ESSENTIAL GAUGES?
AND THERE'S ONLY ONE
ANSWER I CAN THINK OF.
I CAN'T TELL YOU WHY,
BUT THE ENGINES TRUE POWER
HAS BEEN SEALED
OFF ON PURPOSE.
- SEALED OFF ON PURPOSE?
- IT'S A PRETTY RELIABLE ALBEIT
SIMPLE WAY OF DOING IT.
WITHOUT A PROPER TACHOMETER,
A GOOD DRIVER WOULD NEVER MAKE
THE MISTAKE OF OVER-REVVING,
WHICH ELIMINATES THE POSSIBILITY
YOU'LL BURN IT OUT
BY GOING PAST THE RED ZONE.
IN ALL MY YEARS
OF BEING INTO CARS,
I'VE ALWAYS FELT A KINSHIP
WITH OTHER EIGHT-SIX DRIVERS,
BUT NEVER ONCE
HAVE I FELT ANY HOSTILITY.
WELL, I'M NOT SURE
I CAN SAY THAT ANYMORE.
ALL I CAN SAY IS, I REALLY WANT
TO BE THE ONE TO BEAT YOU.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT YOU'RE
HIDING UNDER YOUR HOOD.
THE FACT IS YOU'RE LACKING
THE BASIC ELEMENTS
ANY RACER WORTH HIS
SALT SHOULD HAVE.
WE'LL SETTLE THIS FEUD
SOON ENOUGH AND WHEN WE DO,
YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO BRAG
ABOUT BEING UNDEFEATED AGAIN.
- ( engine revs )
- WHAT THE HECK DOES THAT MEAN?
I'M LACKING SOME
OF THE BASIC ELEMENTS.
- ( tires screeching )
- I THINK I'M IN SHOCK. I
ACTUALLY GOT SCARED BACK THERE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THE WAY
HE ENTERED THOSE CORNERS.
I'M SHOWING MY AGE.
IT'S OBVIOUS HIS BODY CAN HANDLE
A HECK OF A LOT MORE STRESS
THAN MINE CAN.
HE MAY BE IGNORANT
WHEN IT COMES TO CARS,
BUT HIS TECHNIQUE IS AMAZING.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
IF I LOSE TO HIM,
THE REPUTATION I'VE WORKED
SO HARD FOR WILL BE SHOT.
MY ENTIRE EXISTENCE
DEPENDS ON THIS CHALLENGE.
- ( theme song playing )
- Announcer:
WATARU CHALLENGED TAKUMI.
AND THE BIG RACE
IS ABOUT TO START.
NEXT ON INITIAL D,
SECOND STAGE.
- Takumi: THE SEAL IS BROKEN.
- Announcer: DON'T MISS IT.