-( theme song playing )
♪ LET'S GO ♪
- ♪ REMEMBER? ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, CHECK IT OUT ♪
♪ PUMP THE JAM ♪
- ♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
- ♪ LET'S GO ♪
♪ NAKED MIND ♪
♪ NAKED DESIRE ♪
♪ BLAZIN' BEAT ♪
♪ MOVE, MOVE ♪
♪ IT'S THE TIME ♪
- MAN, HE PULLED OFF THAT
COUNTERATTACK WITHOUT A HITCH.
AND HE DID IT LIKE IT WAS THE
MOST NATURAL THING IN THE WORLD.
- THAT LAN-EVO CAN DO THINGS
WE'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND.
IT'S GOT EXTRA BOOST AND
TRACTION THAT NO FR CAN IMITATE.
DON'T MATTER HOW FAR THAT
FR MIGHT BE TWEAKED OUT,
THE EVO'LL WIN ON EVERY LEVEL.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
YOU JUST CAN'T DENY
THE MECHANICAL SUPERIORITY
OF A CAR THAT HAS
FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE.
THIS RACE JUST BECAME A
REAL TOUGH ONE FOR RYOSUKE.
I WONDER IF HE'S EVEN GONNA
HAVE THE CHANCE
TO REGAIN THE LEAD AFTER THAT.
- I REALLY DOUBT IT, MAN.
- COME ON, RYOSUKE!
YOU CARRY THE PRIDE AND HOPE
OF ALL GUNMA RACERS WITH YOU.
WIN THIS FOR US!
- ALL THOSE ISSUES I'VE HAD
ABOUT MOUNTAIN PASSES
HAVE VANISHED.
AFTER DOING THIS,
I DON'T BUY INTO THE IDEA
OF HAVING SOME KIND OF CHARISMA
OR CHARM WITH THE PASS.
AND NOW THAT I'VE ANALYZED
THIS SUPERSTITIOUS ILLUSION,
I CAN SEE IT ALL COMES
DOWN TO EXPERIENCE.
THAT AND REFINED TECHNIQUE.
NOW THAT I UNDERSTAND THAT,
I'M NOT AFRAID OF
RYOSUKE ANYMORE.
BECAUSE WHEN IT COMES
TO REFINED TECHNIQUE,
THAT'S ONE AREA WHERE I'VE
GOT HIM BEAT.
- SO, TAKUMI,
WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENED?
IN AKAGI I MEAN.
IT SHOULD BE OVER BY NOW.
WHO DO YOU THINK WON?
- I HONESTLY DON'T HAVE
THE SLIGHTEST IDEA.
AND HOW COULD I TELL?
I LOST TO THAT LAN-EVO
EVEN BEFORE I SAW
WHAT HE WAS FULLY CAPABLE OF.
JUST TALKING TO YOU ABOUT IT,
PISSING ME OFF ALL OVER AGAIN.
- SORRY, MAN.
- ABOUT WHAT?
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S YOUR FAULT.
AND TALKING TO YOU IS
AT LEAST HELPING ME
TO GET IT OFF MY CHEST, Y'KNOW?
I WAS FEELING SO DEPRESSED
ALL DAY TODAY,
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO WITH MYSELF.
AFTER THE ENGINE BLEW ON ME,
THE GUY DRIVING THE
LAN-EVO TOLD ME
THAT HE DIDN'T
CONSIDER IT A RACE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
HE SAID THAT WE'D BATTLE
FOR REAL SOME OTHER TIME,
WHENEVER I HAD A BETTER CAR
TO DO IT WITH.
- HE SAID THAT?
- AND IT WAS THE WAY
HE SAID IT TO ME.
HE ACTED LIKE HE WAS ALREADY
SURE I WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND IT.
LIKE A TEACHER EXPLAINING
SCHOOL WORK TO THE DUMB KID.
NOT SOME GUY BRAGGING
ABOUT A VICTORY.
THAT PART HURT MY PRIDE
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
I'M PRETTY SURE THOSE WORDS
ARE GONNA STICK WITH ME
FOR A LONG TIME.
- WHATTYA SAY. LET'S GET
THIS OPERATION STARTED.
- MMM-HMM.
- BY TOMORROW NIGHT,
THERE'S GONNA BE A NEW RUMOR
STIRRING AROUND AKINA.
EVERYBODY IN TOWN'S
GONNA' BE TALKIN' ABOUT
THE RESURRECTION
OF THE EIGHT-SIX.
- YOU'VE GOT A FINELY TUNED CAR
THERE, KYOICHI.
SURPRISINGLY FINE
CORNERING ABILITIES.
IT CAN ACCELERATE AT ANY RPM.
IT TURNS 'EASILY AND
EXITS CORNERS FASTER
THAN MOST OTHER
DRIVERS COULD DREAM.
AND THE ACCELERATION...
WATCHING THIS THING PERFORM
SO UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL,
IT'S TERRIFYING.
OF COURSE, IT'S NOT LIKE
I JUST NOW HAD THIS EPIPHANY.
I KNEW ALL THIS YESTERDAY.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( crowd exclaiming )
- WHOA! YOU SEE THAT?
RYOSUKE SMACKED HIS FENDER
INTO THE GUARDRAIL!
- YEAH, HE HAD TO DO THAT.
I THINK IT WAS THE ONLY WAY
HE COULD KEEP UP
WITH THE EVO THREE.
- LOOK AT THIS TIME.
- ( gasps )
THAT'S NUTS!
IF THE EVO THREE KEEPS THIS UP,
HE'LL BLOW THE COURSE RECORD
OFF THE RAILS.
I 'NEVER THOUGHT I'D LIVE
TO SEE THIS.
- YEAH, AND RYOSUKE'S
NOT A SLOW DRIVER.
IT'S JUST THE EVO THREE
IS REALLY GOING
THAT FAST OUT THERE.
- YO. THIS IS CORNER THIRTY FIVE
CALLIN' TO CHECK IN. LISTEN.
THE EVO THREE IS
STILL IN THE LEAD.
- GOT IT.
- HEY, KEISUKE.
DO YOU THINK HE'S GONNA BE OKAY?
- IF THE LAN-EVO CAN
JUST KEEP UP THIS PACE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
I HATE TO SAY IT, YOU GUYS,
BUT YOU KNOW,
HE COULD WALK AWAY
WITH THE VICTORY.
- DON'T SWEAT IT, OKAY?
MY BROTHER'LL GET AROUND THIS.
HE'S STRONGER THAN YOU THINK.
I MEAN, THERE'S NO DOUBT
SUDO'S FAST.
YEAH, I DON'T THINK ANY OF US
HERE SAW THIS ONE COMIN'.
WATCHING THOSE TIRES IS LIKE
WATCHING LIGHTNING STRIKE,
I'M NOT EVEN KIDDING.
YOU DON'T SEE IT
'TIL IT'S TOO LATE.
BUT MY BROTHER CERTAINLY DID.
USING ALL THE DATA HE COLLECTED
AT VARIOUS CHECKPOINTS
THROUGHOUT THE RACE LAST NIGHT,
HE LEARNED A HELLUVA LOT
FROM WHAT SUDO DID
AGAINST THE EIGHT-SIX.
HE CALCULATED EVERY ONE
OF SUDO'S ABILITIES
MORE PRECISELY THAN
I EVER COULD.
SO I CAN TELL YOU
WHAT I TRULY BELIEVE.
MY BROTHER'S WALKING AWAY
WITH THE TROPHY TONIGHT.
- THE MISFIRING AND
THAT FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE
MAKE FOR A KILLER COMBO.
FULL ACCELERATION IN LOW
GEARS ISN'T GONNA CUT IT
AGAINST THIS GUY.
BUT I MAY GET MY CHANCE
TO OVERTAKE HIM
AT A HIGH-SPEED CORNER.
I KNEW IT!
- HE ISN'T COMIN' IN TO ATTACK
ME FROM ANOTHER ANGLE.
WHY NOT? WHAT'S HIS DEAL?
THIS PASSIVE DRIVING THING
IS STARTIN' TO PSYCH ME OUT.
HAS HE THROWN IN THE TOWEL?
( scoffs ) NO. THAT'S STUPID.
I KNOW BETTER.
HE'S GONNA ATTACK.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF WHEN.
LOGICALLY, I KNOW I'M IN
THE BETTER POSITION.
BUT I CAN'T SHAKE THE FEELING
THAT I'M BEING HUNTED HERE.
MAYBE I HAVEN'T GOTTEN
PAST MY WHOLE ISSUE
ABOUT RYOSUKE AND HIS CHARISMA.
BEATING THE HELL OUT OF HIM
WILL GET RID OF THAT.
I'M READY FOR YOU, PAL.
ALL MY TIRES HAVE STILL
GOT FULL TRACTION.
- THIS IS ONE INCREDIBLE BATTLE.
I ONLY HAVE ONE CHANCE HERE.
AND I NEED TO MAKE
MY ATTACK PRECISE.
IT'S TIME TO THREAD THAT NEEDLE.
- Man on radio:
RYOSUKE'S RIGHT ON TOP OF HIM.
BUT THE EVO THREE
IS REALLY COOKING.
HE'S NOT SLOWIN' DOWN AT ALL.
LOOKS LIKE THIS IS GONNA BE
A CLOSE ONE, GUYS!
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
I REALLY DON'T THINK
RYOSUKE CAN PULL THIS OFF.
THEY GOT ONE MORE CORNER TO HIT
BEFORE THEY GET TO
THE FINISH LINE.
- I KNOW. GUESS RYOSUKE GETTIN'
KNOCKED OFF THE THRONE
IS A LOCK AT THIS POINT.
- ( tires screeching )
- HERE THEY ARE!
- CRAP! THE EVO THREE IS
STILL IN THE LEAD!
- THIS TURN IS MY CHANCE
TO TAKE HIM OUT.
YOUR WEAKNESS IS YOUR FEAR
OF TURNING RIGHT.
IT'S SOMETHING YOU NEVER
BOTHERED TO CONQUER,
AND FRANKLY, YOU
REALLY SUCK AT IT.
- ( crowd gasping )
- RYOSUKE JUST TOOK HIM
ON THE OUTSIDE!
- AMAZING!
HE'S GOT THE EVO THREE BOXED IN!
- ( tires screeching )
- DAMMIT! HE'S GOT ME STUCK!
I CAN'T USE MY FOUR-WHEEL
DRIVE'S TRACTION
OR THE MISFIRING SYSTEM!
- INCREDIBLE! THE FC
IS CORNERING
WHILE IT'S BLOCKING
THE EVO THREE!
- THAT'S IT! YOU CAN DO THIS,
RYOSUKE! COME ON!
LET'S GO!
- YOU'RE ALMOST THERE, MAN!
- HE'S GONNA WIN THIS!
ALRIGHT! HE'S IN FRONT!
- THAT'S IT, RYOSUKE! JUST A
LITTLE FARTHER AND YOU GOT IT!
KEEP IT UP!
YES! HE REALLY DID IT!
UNBELIEVABLE.
THAT WAS A COURSE RECORD.
SUCK ON THAT, EMPERORS.
THE RED SUNS JUST SAVED GOONMA!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THEM APPLES!
- INITIAL D.
- ( people cheering )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
EVEN KYOICHI COULDN'T BEAT HIM.
THE HELL HAPPENED OUT THERE?
- THAT'S A CRAZY COURSE RECORD.
I MEAN, I'VE WATCHED YOUR
BROTHER RACE FOR YEARS
AND I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM
MOVE LIKE THAT.
WHY WAS HE SO MUCH FASTER HERE
THAN HE USUALLY IS AT HOME?
- MY BROTHER'S PRETTY GOOD
ABOUT LEAVING A BIG ENOUGH
MARGIN OF ERROR.
YOU KNOW, IT KEEPS HIMSELF
OR ANYONE ELSE FROM CRASHING
DURING THE TIME TRIALS
THAT WE RUN.
WHEN HE'S PUT INTO THE
KIND OF SITUATION
WHERE HE'S FORCED
TO RAISE THE BAR,
THEN I SUPPOSE THIS
IS THE KIND OF THING
THAT'S JUST GONNA HAPPEN.
THAT EVO THREE WAS A REALLY
TOUGH OPPONENT TO GO UP AGAINST.
SO I GUESS HE GOT REALLY
SERIOUS OUT THERE TONIGHT.
- NOW THAT WAS A KILLER WIN!
- THE WAY YOU TOOK THAT
CORNER WAS UNREAL!
- HEY, RYOSUKE.
LOOK, I GOT SOMETHING
THAT I WANNA ASK YOU.
WE BOTH BEEN RACIN' A LONG TIME,
SO WHAT THE HELL IS THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN US?
WHY CAN'T I BEAT YOU?
I JUST DON'T GET THIS, MAN.
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT AM I DOING WRONG?
- IN MY OPINION,
YOUR TECHNIQUE IS SOLID.
IN FACT, IT'S ALMOST
AS GOOD AS MINE.
- DON'T STAND THERE AND
PATRONIZE ME! JUST TELL ME WHY!
- THAT'S WHAT I'M
TRYING TO DO, KYOICHI.
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU THAT IT
ISN'T BECAUSE OF YOUR TECHNIQUE.
YOUR WEAKNESS IS IN
YOUR RIGHT TURN. THAT'S IT.
AND IT DOESN'T NECESSARILY
HAPPEN EVERY TIME, EITHER.
BUT I'VE NOTICED THERE ARE
A HANDFUL OF TURNS
WHERE YOUR WEAKNESS RISES TO THE
SURFACE AND IT CAN BE EXPLOITED.
- MY RIGHT TURNS?
- JUST TO THE RIGHT OF THE
CENTER LINE IS A DEAD ZONE
WHICH IS USUALLY OCCUPIED
BY OPPOSING TRAFFIC.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE USED TO.
YOU CAN'T ATTACK A
RIGHT-HAND CORNER
WITHOUT WORRYING ABOUT A
HEAD-ON COLLISION.
IT'S COMMON, AND NO ONE CAN GIVE
IT A HUNDRED PERCENT.
BUT WITH ENOUGH EXPERIENCE
AND COURSE KNOWLEDGE,
YOU CAN COME ABOUT AS CLOSE
TO A 100% AS ANYONE CAN HOPE.
IS THAT CLEAR ENOUGH, KYOICHI?
DO YOU GET THE DIFFERENCE NOW?
THEN HOW ABOUT THIS?
IN MOTORSPORTS, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT OPPOSING TRAFFIC.
THE GYMKHANA CIRCUIT DOESN'T
HAVE TWO-WAY TRAFFIC.
AND ON YOUR HOME COURSE, NIKKO
IROHAZAKA, IT'S ALL ONE WAY,
WHICH YOU KNOW
BECAUSE IT'S THE COURSE
YOU'RE MOST FAMILIAR WITH.
YOU NEVER GET THE CHANCE
TO PRACTICE.
I PAY ATTENTION TO YOU
ALL OF THE TIME.
AND IN YOUR COUNTERATTACK,
YOU ALWAYS STAY OUTSIDE AT
THE RIGHT-HAND CORNERS.
I READ THAT AS AN INDICATION
YOU'RE AFRAID OF THE INSIDE.
IN THE RACE YOU HAD
AGAINST THE EIGHT-SIX,
YOU SHOWED ME TOO MUCH, KYOICHI.
THAT'S WHY YOU LOST.
- ( car door closing )
- ( engine starting )
- ( tires screeching )
- YOU BEAT ME, RYOSUKE.
THE REAL ILLUSION WAS ME
THINKING I'D CAUGHT UP WITH YOU.
I GUESS THIS STREET CHARISMA
IS SOMETHING YOU DO HAVE.
- Iketani: IT WAS TOTALLY
FREAKIN' INCREDIBLE!
I GOT TO SEE FIRST HAND HOW
GREAT A RACER RYOSUKE TRULY IS.
IT OPENED MY EYES.
- SO I GUESS THAT VICIOUS
STORM OF LAN-EVO'S
THAT THREATENED OUR FAIR GUNMA,
IT'S STARTING TO LOOK LIKE
IT BLEW ITSELF OUT
AND PEACE HAS BEEN RESTORED
TO THE VALLEY.
-MMM-HMM. YEAH. I REALLY SHOULD
HAVE GONE TO THAT RACE.
BY THE WAY, DID ITSUKI AND
TAKUMI HAPPEN TO BE OUT
WITH YOU GUYS LAST NIGHT?
NO, THEY WEREN'T WITH US AND I
DIDN'T SEE THEM UP THERE EITHER.
MAYBE TAKUMI DIDN'T FEEL LIKE IT
AFTER LOSING TO KYOICHI THE
NIGHT BEFORE. I WOULDN'T.
- YEAH I'M SURE THAT WAS IT.
I MEAN IF WE'RE STILL IN SHOCK,
HE'S GOTTA BE FREAKED OUT
ABOUT IT TOO
- BUT HE SPECIFICALLY TOLD ME
HE WASN'T GONNA GO TO AKAGI.
I WONDER WHAT IT WAS THAT
GOT INTO HIS HEAD
AND CHANGED HIS MIND.
- ( bell tolling )
- I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW EXCITED I AM
THAT RYOSUKE WON LAST NIGHT!
NOW IT'S OFFICIALLY,
100 PER CENT PROVEN
THAT GUNMA'S GOT THE HIGHEST
STANDARDS OF RACING ANYWHERE.
ALRIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU
IN CLASS BROTHER!
- ( chuckling excitedly )
- HEY, TAKUMI!
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE WHAT JUST
HAPPENED. THERE WAS THIS KID...
HEY, WHERE DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE GOING?
- I'M SORRY, NATSUKI,
BUT I DON'T FEEL LIKE TALKING
TO YOU RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT?
- Takumi: FOR REAL? YOU'RE SURE
IT WAS MY DAD'S EIGHT-SIX?
NO, NO WAY, THAT'S GOTTA BE
SOME KIND OF MISTAKE.
HE WOULD'VE TOLD ME
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
- BUT IT WAS JUST
A FEW DAYS AGO.
ONE OF OUR TEAM
MEMBERS SAID HE SAW IT
OUT TOOLIN' AROUND AKINA PASS.
- SAID IT WAS A THREE DOOR PANDA
TRUENO JUST LIKE YOUR FATHER'S.
- MAYBE SO, BUT I DON'T THINK
IT WAS OURS.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHERE
YOUR DAD'S CAR IS THESE DAYS?
- NO, I'VE GOT NO CLUE.
WE HAD IT TOWED BACK FROM AKAGI.
AFTER THAT, MY DAD TOOK
IT SOMEPLACE,
I COULDN'T REALLY
TELL YOU WHERE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING ABOUT
ALL YOUR MORNING DELIVERIES?
- I'VE GOT THIS CHEAP OLD
PICKUP TRUCK I'VE BEEN USING.
IT'S PRETTY CRAPPY,
BUT AT LEAST IT RUNS...
- THAT EIGHT-SIX IS LIKE
AN AKINA LEGEND.
DON'T TELL ME IT'S BEING PICKED
APART FOR SCRAP AT SOME JUNKYARD
IN THE COUNTRYSIDE RIGHT NOW.
I MIGHT JUST CRY!
- NO, DUDE.
I DOUBT THAT'S WHERE IT IS.
MY DAD WAS TELLING
ME HE WAS GONNA TRY
TO PUT ANOTHER ENGINE IN IT.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS? WHAT KIND OF
ENGINE DID HE SAY IT WAS?
- NO WAY HE'S JUST GONNA CRAM
ANOTHER NORMAL FOUR AG ENGINE
IN THAT SUCKER.
THAT'S LIKE BACKTRACKING.
MAYBE HE'S PUTTING IN A TURBO.
- I HAVE NO INTEREST IN HIM
PUTTING IN A TURBO.
I REALLY COULDN'T CARE LESS.
- WELL, WHY NOT MAN?
- OF EVERYTHING INSIDE A CAR,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY THAT THE ENGINE
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT PART?
WITHOUT IT, YOU GOT NOTHING,
IT'S JUST A SHELL.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- SO IF YOU COMPARE
A CAR TO A PERSON,
THEN THE ENGINE IS LIKE
A PERSON'S BRAIN.
- UH, TAKUMI, WHEN
PEOPLE MAKE COMPARISONS
THEY USUALLY COMPARE THE
ENGINE TO A HEART.
- WAIT, WHO DOES?
WELL, THEN IT'S THE HEART.
WHATEVER. THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
THE POINT IS I DON'T WANT
ANOTHER ENGINE.
I'M USED TO WHAT I'VE GOT.
I DON'T WANT IT TO
FEEL LIKE I'M DRIVING
AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT CAR.
- OKAY.
I GUESS I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY REALLY
ATTACHED TO THAT THING.
- I DIG HOW YOU'RE FEELIN' MAN.
MAKES PERFECT SENSE TO ME, TOO.
WE JUST CAN'T HELP BUT WONDER
WHAT KIND OF AN
ENGINE IT'LL HAVE,
WHEN YOUR DAD'S DONE WITH ALL
HIS TINKERIN' AROUND WITH IT.
COULD BE SWEET.
- ( engines accelerating )
- ( tires screeching )
- SO BUNTA, WHAT'S THE VERDICT?
- I FEEL IT GETTING BETTER
EACH TIME I DRIVE IT.
ONLY PROBLEM IS,
THE ENGINE'S SO GOOD THE
SUSPENSION CAN'T CATCH UP.
- IT'S THAT GOOD OF AN ENGINE.
PRETTY NICE.
- GOTTA SAY, I'M IN LOVE.
- STOP IT, BUNTA,
YOU'RE REALLY TEMPTING ME HERE.
I MAY NEED TO JUMP
IN THERE WITH YOU
NEXT TIME YOU TAKE
HER FOR A SPIN.
- WHADDYA SAY?
- ( exhales )
I DUNNO, SHE'S SCARY.
- HUH? OH, COME ON,
GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOU'RE PREACHING
TO THE CHOIR HERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME
HOW SCARY YOUR DRIVING CAN BE.
I'VE BEEN THERE.
- WANT ME TO PROVE IT TO YOU?
TAKE A LOOK.
- WHOA. WHAT HAPPENED?
- HOW DID YOU GET THAT?
- LEANING ON MY SHIN.
IT HURT LIKE HELL, BUT I HAD TO.
IT WAS EVERYTHING I COULD DO
TO KEEP UPRIGHT.
I USED TO THINK THAT THE SIDE
G-FORCE IN PASS RACING
WASN'T WORTHY OF A BUCKET SEAT.
I DO NOW.
THIS BRUISING'LL GO ALL THE WAY
DOWN TO MY BONES
IF WE DON'T PUT ONE IN BEFORE
I GO OUT AGAIN.
NEEDLESS TO SAY,
I'VE HAD ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
THIS NEW ENGINE IS
ONE TOUGH CUSTOMER.
BUT I WILL ADMIT, IT DOES MAKE
IT ALL THE MORE EXCITING.
STILL HAVEN'T DECIDED HOW
I'M GONNA SET HER UP THOUGH.
I MIGHT TAKE MY TIME
AND ENJOY IT SOME.
SHE'S A SWEET LADY,
IF A LITTLE ROUGH.
COURSE, I GOTTA
CONSIDER TAKUMI'S GONNA BE
DRIVING HER TOO, AND HE CAN BE
A LITTLE INEPT.
- HE CALLED TAKUMI INEPT?
HE'S JOKING, RIGHT?
TAKUMI'S A GENIUS.
- I CAN'T WAIT TILL WE GRADUATE.
ANYTHING IS BETTER
THAN HIGH SCHOOL.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- I DO. I CAN'T WAIT TO START
WORKING A REAL JOB.
UNTIL YOU GOT A JOB,
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT ANOTHER KID
WHO'S STILL LIVING
WITH HIS PARENTS.
I WANNA MAKE MY OWN MONEY,
BE SELF-SUFFICIENT.
WITH A GOOD JOB, I COULD FINALLY
AFFORD MY OWN CAR
AND DO WHATEVER I WANTED TO DO.
I CAN'T BUY ANYTHING ON MY OWN
NOW. IT'S BORDERLINE PATHETIC.
- I THINK MAYBE YOU NEED TO HAVE
A LITTLE MORE PATIENCE.
WE'RE GRADUATING NEXT SPRING.
AFTER THAT YOU CAN DO ANYTHING
YOU WANT. JUST WAIT 'TIL THEN.
- I DON'T FEEL LIKE
I CAN WAIT ANYMORE.
THERE'S NOTHING FOR ME AT SCHOOL
THAT'S WORTH ANY OF MY TIME.
KINDA SEEMS TO ME LIKE
SOMETHING'S BUGGIN YOU, MAN.
WHAT'S UP?
- WAIT!
TAKUMI, WHY HAVE YOU BEEN
AVOIDING ME SO MUCH LATELY?
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG OR
WAS IT MAYBE SOMETHING I SAID?
I'M GOING CRAZY
THINKING ABOUT IT.
JUST TELL ME WHAT I DID
AND I'LL APOLOGIZE.
- YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
- THEN, WHAT'S WRONG?
- NOTHING IS WRONG.
- SOMETHING'S OBVIOUSLY
BOTHERING YOU.
WE WERE FINE UNTIL RECENTLY,
THEN YOU, LIKE, TURNED OFF.
SUDDENLY YOU'RE MR. DISTANT.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU, TAKUMI?
- I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU'RE SO WORKED UP
ABOUT SOME IDIOT LIKE ME.
I'M NOTHING SPECIAL.
AND NONE OF IT SHOULD REALLY
MATTER ANYWAY, RIGHT?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT
LIKE WE WERE EVEN
OFFICIALLY DATING OR ANYTHING.
- I'M TRYING TO UNDERSTAND,
BUT YOU'RE NOT MAKING SENSE!
YOU'RE LIKE A DIFFERENT PERSON!
- JUST STOP FOLLOWING ME.
OH, AND GOOD LUCK WITH
YOUR BUDDY IN THE MERCEDES.
NOW LEAVE ME THE HELL ALONE.
- NO. HOW DID HE FIND OUT?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Announcer: THE EIGHT-SIX IS
BACK AND THE BIG QUESTION IS,
HOW POWERFUL IS IT NOW?
NEXT ON INITIAL D, SECOND STAGE.
"THE NEW EIGHT-SIX."
DON'T MISS IT!