- [ENERGETIC ROCK MUSIC]
- [FAINT POLICE SIREN]
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
- Girl: [YELPS]
Shogo: Eh... Sorry.
Did I scare you?
I did, huh? Well, I'm glad I didn't
hit ya! I was in a hurry.
Oh, um... let me...
Yui: Hey! Get your hands off that!
How insensitive can you be? Driving
down the sidewalk is bad enough...
but a girl's handbag is-
well, it's private!
Oh, man, there's no way I'm
going to make it in time now.
Yeah, my bad.
Ah, you have no idea.
Why don't you grow up!
- Hey! Taxi!
- Uh, hey! No! Wait up!
- I need to get to the Piazza building in
Harajuku. How fast can you get there? - Hey!
Meiji Street's bumper-to-bumper.
Walking'll be faster than that taxi.
But... you're going to that building
in front of Kiddy Land, right?
I can get you there, in seconds.
C'mon, you wanted fast, right?
- 'Bout time.
- Yeah, well, just doin' it right.
- So, what's your name?
- WHAT?
- YOUR NAME!
- Yui. Yui Takanaka.
Shogo Yahagi, nice to meet'cha.
So, you work at the Piazza?
I wish! I part-time there
and work in Roppongi.
- See, in record time. - Well, thanks, I
guess. But you still drive like a lunatic.
- So where's this that you work?
- Oh, I dance at the Hard Rock.
Eh? Hey, I've been there. Maybe I can take
you for a spin on the bike sometime, huh?
Can I get your number?
Hey, wait! Have a heart, Yui!
Eight. That's when I start.
Drive carefully.
Huh? Eight? Which rhymes
with date, right?
Hmm... [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
408-7018... That's the Hard Rock's
private number!
Bye-bye!
[SATISFIED CHUCKLE] Yeah...
And he scores!
Hey, good morning.
- Oh, hi. Everyone's in Office 4.
- Banner: \"Always surprise with something new.\"
- Hey, doll.
- Good morning, sir.
We're heading over
to the studio. Ready?
[MOTORCYCLE SHUTTING DOWN]
Morley: Yahagi's going
for the gold. He jumps!
He nails it!
A double back-flip!
- Yeah, it's a ten! - Mai: I'll
give him a ten! - Tomomi: Me too!
Hey, you guys. Sorry I'm late.
- It's cool.
- Are you hot to trot?
Yeah, are you, big spender?
Well, yeah. Sure!
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
- Shogo: Hey, check this out, dude.
- Mai: Wow, I can't believe it.
Waa! This is the second
time I've seen him.
- That you've seen who?
- Man, that Eve is hot!
Yeah, and this new song rocks.
I snagged this video on my Beta.
- Let me copy it?
- Ummm... Nope!
- C'mon, Morley. Let me copy it! That's
what buds do. - Hey, cut it out!
~b~Eve: ~i~Your gaze is so icy that I think
your heart may be on fire.
I catch a glimpse of your
profile as you smile.
Love me do! Love me do! Love me do!
My skin tingles as I see the bright red
lights flow through the city.
Oh! Oh!
Isn't that strange?
When my heart races, it's like a carnival.
Love always starts so suddenly,
like a torrent of rain.
Falling in love...
the sentimental journey begins.
The tears I had yesterday
fly away with wings.
Fly away! Soar away!
At the horizon...
the sentimental journey begins.
In the moment... when we met...
I had already fallen in love with you.
That... night...
There were shooting
stars; it must be destiny.
Falling in love...
the sentimental journey begins.
If the sky sparkles like
a Chagall painting...
Fly away! Soar away!
Behind our backs...
the sentimental journey begins.
Your eyes flash green with energy.
That... night...
There were shooting
stars; it must be destiny.
[URBAN TRAFFIC, DISTANT TRAIN]
- Shogo, it's me.
- Hey, Shinji-Oh, what is that?
[STRUM OF REVELATION]
It's huge. So whose prototype is it?
It's not a Suzuki.
Or a Honda either.
Or a Yamaha, or Kawasaki.
15,000 rpms, 200 miles per hour.
That's Formula One speed, but this
thing wasn't built as a sports bike.
You're kidding, right?
Man, oh man. Where'd
you pick this baby up?
I borrowed it from my
company's hangar.
I was supposed to test drive it,
but do you know what this bike means?
- So what does \"Bahamood\" mean?
- \"From Bahamut.\"
- B.D.: Why, Mr. Nakagawa.
- [GASPS]
You know that the company frowns on
the borrowing of classified materials.
I trust you'll come quietly.
Since when did the company start
sending out goons with handguns?
- Shinji! - Don't move! - These guys are GS!
- Shogo, Plan E! - Yeah, got it!
- B.D.: Don't be stupid, Nakagawa!
- [MOTORCYCLE STARTS]
Don't force our hand!
[SHINJI SCREAMS IN PAIN]
- Damn! Go around back.
- Shinji!
[GOONS SCREAM]
Stop that kid! Call for roadblocks!
Don't let him leave this district!
The bastard's pulled a fast one.
What the hell is going on?!
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
- Hey look, I told you everything I saw!
- Morley: Dude, chill.
Chombo: I don't know, maybe you
should just give it back to 'em.
Don't be stupid! Who knows what those
guys would do if they caught us?
It's not your fault,
you were just there.
But if you don't get rid of this thing
soon, they'll find you for sure.
When they may have killed
Shinji for this thing?
- There's no way I'm not gonna make them pay.
- Coco: Cool it, hothead.
Getting all worked up and flying off the
handle's not gonna do anyone any good.
We'll check out the news
in the morning, OK?
If you're right, and he's dead,
you can bet you're next on their list.
He's right. If these guys are as bad as you
think they are, you'd better lay low.
Yeah, dude. And if they want this thing, just
leave it somewhere and let them find it.
Look, I've got an idea,
but I'll need your help.
Radio: The target's name is Shogo Yahagi.
We tracked him to Meguro,
but lost him in Aobadai.
- It's just a few hours before sunrise.
I want him found before then! - Yes, sir!
\"No Entry / Under Construction\"
\"Please pardon the intrusion due
to water pipe construction.\"
[SIGHS]
Paint's done. I assume you
want it on your tab, right?
I don't get it, old man. There's
nothing in the paper anywhere.
- It's not even on the TV.
- [PHONE RINGS]
Hey, Chombo?
So, what'd they say? Yeah...
What?! They said he went to America?
For three months, huh?
[MOTORCYCLE ARRIVING]
This ain't good.
- Put a tail on that one.
- Closed for water main repair?
And someone's in my room? These
guys are trying to hide something.
So what we've gotta do is,
go public with it.
Woah! Eve's television show?
I see... That's brilliant!
[MOTORCYCLE]
Mai: [HUMMING ALONG AS SHE PLAYS]
[CONTINUES TO HUM AND PLAY]
[YET MORE HUMMING]
[SOFT MOANS]
[EVEN MORE ANNOYING HUMMING]
[SLEEPY GROAN]
[ANNOYED YAWN]
[TIRED SIGH]
Hey, keep it down, huh? Some
of us had a late night, y'know.
That's no excuse for sleeping
past noon, you naughty girl.
Bppppf!
- She is naughty, isn't she.
- Meow...
- Yo! - Yo mamma! - Owww...!
Mai: [STARTS PLAYING AGAIN]
Umm... and...
- Oh, BooBoo ate it all.
- [PHONE RINGS]
- Huh? - Hey, Mai, who was supposed to have
cooking duty today? - Tomomi: Hello. - Me!
- Tomomi: Wait a second! I know this voice.
- Man! Frozen dinners again.
Is that you, Shogo?
Yeah, it's me, Tomomi.
And Mai's here too.
I know. Ain't it freaky?
- Is that Shogo?
- Tomomi: yeah...
- Shogo, huh? Who's that?
- Tomomi: I mean, what're the odds?
Tomomi: So, what's the
scoop on you and Yui?
- Mai: [SNICKERS]
- [CHUCKLES] All right, keep your pants on.
- Yui, it's Shogo.
- Shogo?
- Tomomi: Cute, motorcycle, drove you someplace.
- Oh, yeah...
Hey, I called the number you gave me,
and they gave me your number. Is that cool?
Yui: And you know my roommates
too, huh? Is this all you do?
No, it's all just a coincidence.
We just hooked up in
Shinjuku. Weird, huh?
And you were calling because-?
Shogo: Oh, just to say that if you want
to see something interesting...
check out Eve's show today.
I'm, well, check it out, OK? [HANGS UP]
Hey, wait! [SIGHS]
He said to watch Eve's show.
The show! Oh my god,
we're missing it!
Has anyone seen the remote?
Ah! Where it it?!
- It's on the VCR!
- I'm baffled.
That was hilarious.
He was so freaked.
Well, yeah, but fate can
be odd, you know.
- Shhh! Shut up, you two, it's starting!
- [\"Sentimental Behind Our Backs\" INTRO]
And coming up next,
Eve's \"Town Scoop.\"
Got a story to tell? Lost loves, cats
laying eggs, or whatever, it's all OK.
If you've got the scoop, give us the poop
via the vision-phone system.
[PING]
Hey, we've got our
first call. Talk to me.
[GULPS]
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry, but could you please
step back from the camera?
Er... Umm-Hi! Bahamut Six.
- Umm, Babamucho?
- No, I said Bahamut Six.
\"Please Stand By\"
- That was him, right? - Yeah, but where'd he go?
- Maybe he lost his nerve. - [ALL LAUGH]
- Calling up program T2R-B3. Rolling!
- Right... Good... Locked...
Three, two, one, cue!
Rerouting video feed.
- What a weird kid, he hung up. Oh well, lets hear
from our next caller. - Yui: Well, that was weird.
- He, like, just vanished.
- Tomomi: Maybe he's camera-shy?
- Ready, Major.
- Good.
All units, target has been located at the
phone booth in the 6th block of Aoyama.
And I need you to find out what's
going on. I'll show you the bike.
All right then. And I'll see
if I can find your friend.
And by the way, I guess I forgot to say
that you can put the receiver down.
Oh, I can, huh?
[EMBARRASSED CHUCKLE]
Well then, can your video see this?
- That's the bike, right there.
- Eve: Yes, I see it.
Shogo: And no one else ever has.
It'll do 200! And it even survived
a head-on collision with a Beemer.
Right... but what's a \"Beemer\"?
It's a foreign brick with wheels.
Any normal bike would've been trashed.
Oh, I see.
Actually, I don't know much
about motorcycles...
but I've never seen
one this big before.
So what I was hoping was that I could bring
this bike into your station for safekeeping.
And maybe you can someone
come and take a look at it.
To see if it's some kind
of weapon, or what.
So, did everyone see that?
I'm off to the station! Bye!
- B.D.: And here he thought he was slick.
- [LONG BEEP]
- Radio: Unit 11. Target confirmed. Standing by.
- B.D.: Don't let him escape.
Thanks. And that's it for today's call-ins.
Now, let's see my new video...
- So I wonder what happened to Shogo?
- \"Sentimental Behind My Back.\"
I guess he never called back in.
- That's freaky.
- And how. What'd he say, \"Bahamut?\"
Like, that's so bogus. I wonder
what he wanted to say?
And why did he even bother telling us to
watch in the first place? Uhh! What a freak!
Maybe he likes you,
and was going to confess it.
- Shut up, dork.
- Mai: Shhh! This song's...
been on top of the charts
for three weeks now!
Let me listen!
Lieutenant: All cars standing by.
Mobile Unit Two to all units.
Target is passing A-33.
Engage at the next intersection.
Center-Forward, we confirm.
This is Quarterback, confirm.
Van Driver: Hold on.
Target's trying to pass.
[HORN BLARES]
- [RELIEVED SIGH]
- Hey! Watch where you're going, you moron!
Say what?! Watch where I'm going?! You're
the one that ran into me, you jackass!
- Oooh! Just get out of the way, you jerks!
I'm in a hurry! - Holy cow!
- You're not injured, are you, buddy?
- Now! Take him down.
- Hold on! Get on back here!
- Thought you could pull a fast one, did ya?
Hey, fight fair! Owwww!
- Stop him! Pull out the key!
- What the hell?!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Lieutenant: I'm sorry, sir.
Target scored the touchdown.
He's currently fleeing on Gaien,
towards Highway 246.
Unit Two! You will force
the target onto Highway 3.
We'll have a transport unit ready.
You're ours, kid.
[SQUEAL]
Lieutenant: Target acquired.
We're in pursuit.
Moving from the highway
toward the Yoyogi interchange.
Sorry, guys! You may think
you're sticky, but watch this!
- Soldier B: We've closed off Gaien Street East.
- Soldier A: Understood.
Oooooh SHIT!
Where the hell are the other cars?
They tricked me!
They've got me surrounded!
You bastards!
So that's it! They're canning me!
Lieutenant: Just hold the ramp steady!
Eyaaah!
Desperate times call for-Yaaaaah!
Lieutenant: Don't let him get away!
Initiate transformation!
Corporal: Roger.
Sergeant: Unit One,
transformation complete.
Lieutenant: Understood.
Initiate capture.
Sergeant: Target acquired!
Wait! No! [SCREAMS]
What the hell is that?!
- Strikers, use the capture nets.
- Roger.
I'm screwed!
Geez! It is a robot!
Shogo: [SCREAMS]
Truck Drivers: [SCREAM]
[PANICKED CRIES]
Uh...? Huh...?
I'm not dead? SCORE!
[SOFT GRUNTS]
[PHONE RINGS]
- Yeah. What?
- Hi, Yui... It's Shogo Yahagi.
Look, I need a big favor. Could I store something
in the parking garage at your apartment?
- Right now.
- Right now? But why?
- Can I explain when I get there?
I'm kinda in a hurry. - Well, sure.
Do you know where it's at?
Right... Yeah...
- It's a New York style, and I'll be
waiting out front. - Thanks.
I watched that show...
and they cut you off.
They cut me off?
But that makes no sense!
Well that's what it looked like. You
were babbling a bunch of nonsense...
and then the screen went blank.
Just a caption that said \"Please stand by.\"
What's going on here? I was
talking with Eve the whole time.
Yui: What's wrong?
Look, I can't leave this
bike in the open.
- The garage is in the basement.
- Thanks.
Uhh... Sorry, the apartment
is kind of a mess.
Nice place! But the rent
must be killer, huh?
Yeah, for a girl on her own.
Oh yeah, right. I totally forgot
that you had two roommates.
- I spazzed.
- Obviously.
- Well, have a seat and I'll make some tea.
- Great.
- Huh...?
- Meow.
So I guess you know what both of
my roommates are into already?
Yeah! Tomomi wants to become
a movie director...
and she's working on
some scripts right now.
Mai's a singer, and she's working fill-in
at one of the Hard Rocks, right?
Actually, she works at the
same one that I do.
In fact, you oughta come by
and hear her sing sometime.
If I could find the time, I would,
but my job keeps me on my feet.
- Meow.
- Mmm-hmm.
At McDonald's. You know,
the one on Aoyama Street.
Really? And we're in that one,
like, all the time.
I guess our schedules
haven't matched.
Yui: Yeah, I guess so...
- Myew.
- Hmmm... Hmmm...
- So, hey, you dating anybody?
- Um, why? - Um... Just asking.
[GETTING TO KNOW EACH OTHER MUSIC]
But, it is cool for me to
park overnight, isn't it?
Well, I'm not saying no.
They're trying to kill you?
- Are you sure?
- There's something weird about that bike.
And that bit with the TV station proves it.
It was strange how they cut away.
But if it's the bike, then why
don't you just get rid of it?
Too late now. And, to be
perfectly honest...
even though it's scary, I just can't let
whatever happened to Shinji go unanswered.
So now it's personal.
But it's more than that.
It just wouldn't be right.
Yeah, know what you mean.
And there's more.
There's a kind of rush that you feel when
you're putting everything on the line.
- You get it.
- I've been around.
Still, there's never been a better
place or time to be alive.
Yui: Sometimes I think it's
the best it'll ever be.
It... feels good.
- Better than sex?
- Oh, please!
So what's your blood type?
[SCOFFS] You gonna ask my sign next?
It helps me understand you.
- I'm a B. - B? I see. Well,
I don't normally hate type B...
especially ones who get
too worked up about silly things.
- Was I just zinged?
- [LAUGHS]
- Shogo: I was! You! Hey, come back here!
- Yui: See, you're getting all worked up!
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey! What's up?
Uh, just hangin'. And I was thinkin'
that if you didn't have to work...
maybe you'd like to go somewhere.
Yui: Oh, um, sorry, I'm on my way
to a gig at the TV station.
- Shogo: Do you have to?
- Yui: Yeah.
It's not much,
but a girl's got to eat.
And it's my chance to make
some real connections.
You may laugh at this, but it's my dream
to stand on a Broadway stage.
Shogo: Oh, no. I think that's great.
- Yui: Hey, if you wanted to come...
- Shogo: To the TV station?
Yeah, I've always wanted
to see inside one of those.
Sure, I'll come.
[DANCE BEAT]
Hmm...?
Director: Cut!
Awesome, girls, that's fabulous!
Now that's a wrap!
- Yes, that's workin', people! Absolutely
fabulous! - [YUI LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
- [SLOW CLAPPING BY ONE PERSON]
- Huh...?
- Hey!
- Umm, I'm afraid something came up.
- What?!
- I can't go out, not tonight.
- Uh... - Sorry.
- Hey, wait up!
Later, 'kay?
- Hi... - So, see you at the Central
Hotel in an hour, right, Toots?
Yui: Uh huh. I've got to change.
That bastard!
[SUSPENSEFUL BASS LINE]
- Producer: So, Yui...
- Yes, sir.
- Why don't you take a shower first?
- Umm... OK, sure.
That's the hotel that old
letch mentioned.
The question... is what
room they're in.
[DISTORTED CONVERSATION]
Not there...
Maybe up higher...
[CRUNCH!]
[DISTORTED] So whad'ya think of what
Princess Di wore last night, huh?
[DISTORTED] Oh! Ahh!
Oh, Oh, right there! Oh!
Producer: Oh yeah, Yui. Very hot.
- [DISTORTED] Check out the hair, dude. - Dude,
do you like it? It's a Flock of Seagulls haircut.
- Where are you?
- [DISTORTED] Everybody's gonna want one!
[DISTORTED] I think I'd look
a lot better in that dress.
- [DISTORTED] Man, will you shut up and
pass that shit?! - Call me your Queen!
Producer: Oh, yeah.
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTS]
- Yui: No. - Producer: Come on, baby.
- Yui: No, you're too rough.
Producer: But I wanna make you
the lead in my next production.
Got you, you bastard!
[LOUD CRASH]
[CONFUSED WHIMPERING]
[TERRIFIED SCREAMS]
No! No!
[INCREDULOUS MOAN]
Woah! Damn!
[INCOHERENT GIBBERING]
You big jerk!
[LAUGHS HAPPILY]
I can't believe it.
You said that it was weird, but who would
have thought it would do that! [LAUGHS]
But what were you thinking?
- What was that for? - What were you
thinking about with that... sleazeball?!
That's not any of your
business, now is it?!
And you! Let's talk about
what you did to me!
What were you thinking?! Coming in
and grabbing me like you own me?!
You screwed it all up!
Just when... when I... I...
was about to get the lead role.
That's all ruined now.
I can't believe you'd've slept
with him just to get a part!
That's just between me and him!
Just... leave me alone!
\"McDonald's Hamburgers\"
Shogo: Yes, ma'am. That'll
be 2,350 yen, from 10,000.
And your change is 7,650.
Thanks, and have a McNice McDay.
- Tomomi: Hey, Shogo!
- Huh?
Hi. I've got a proposal for you.
- A movie?
- Yeah, using that bike of yours.
- I heard that it's rad. - She blabbed.
- Yup, us roomies talk.
That motorcycle is way too
dangerous. Look, I-
Yeah, but it looks so cool,
and there'd be no special effects.
And you'd be the hero.
Opposite Yui, of course.
And she's... OK with that, huh?
Uh... Yeah...
- I'll think about it.
- That'd be awesome!
Tomomi: I'm sorry about this.
But we need to scout locations,
and you can cover a lot of ground quickly.
And time is something we don't have.
It's weird. I didn't think
he'd say yes.
Mai: Say yes to what?
Nothing. I was just
thinking out loud.
About Shogo, right?
You can't hide it from me!
[GIGGLES AND SQUEALS]
Oh oh... Smokey on
a bike. See him?
For a while. He's been
there following us.
[POLICE SIREN]
Sign: \"Slow Down\"
- Shogo, over there.
- Right! - Eyaah!
- Looks like we lost him.
- What's the deal with this empty tunnel?
- [RUMBLING]
- [YELPS OF SURPRISE]
Hey! What's happening?!
Huh...?
Hey wait, it's going up now.
But how...?
Well, at least we lost the cop, huh?
[GRUNTS] Ow!
What'd you stop for?
Huh?
[SUSPENSEFUL, MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
Hey... there's a town
up on the ceiling, too.
It's like the world's biggest
ghost town, inside a funhouse.
There's some lights over there.
That must be where the people are.
B.D.: We've cleared through Bahamut 6. Currently
we're in the process of cracking level 7G.
- Hey, that's his voice! - Fortunately,
I don't think the man who stole the bike...
understood its connection
with Bahamut.
Superior Officer: Good.
If it becomes known that...
Bahamut is a computer that
oversees this time period...
the military's plans will
be severely impaired.
So Bahamut is the name of
some kind of computer?
B.D.: And even if those street punks did learn
that the bike is a terminal for Bahamut...
- they could never understand it.
- Oh, wow!
So Bahamut's a big computer?
This is getting heavy.
You should go.
Hmm... Well, I got the whole thing on film,
so maybe I should leave. What about you?
After I've scoped this
place out. See ya.
Looks like some of the elevators
go all the way up.
Why is it getting so cold?
[GASPS]
I don't get it. How can the gravity here be
pulling up and down at the same time?
Rogue Garland sighted in Block A3.
Send Hargan Unit to A2.
Oh shit!
Robot bike, don't fail me now!
Damn, they're cutting me off!
Soldier: Come on out and surrender!
[SCREAMS]
- God dammit!
- I'm not dead yet!
What the hell?
Now I'm in space?!
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
I can't believe that punk
has come this far!
Stop rotating so I can get a shot!
What the?!
Why don't you just give up on
the damn grappling lines?!
Wait! How about if we just
stand down and talk, OK?
Then lose the gun! And don't
go trying any funny shit!
I'm ready for some answers here.
[RAPID PANTING]
A secret metropolis buried
beneath the Earth?
Or a movie set just
waiting to be filmed?
Can a girl ask for a better place to shoot
her feature debut? [CHORTLES]
Wow!
It's time to start talking.
Why have you been chasing me?
Why did you just help me?
You already knew the
truth, didn't you?
That our whole city's actually
inside a giant spaceship.
That's correct. The military
has known for quite a while.
- But...? - But it's not the military
that's been hiding all of this.
Bahamut is the one who
didn't want us to know!
Yeah, Bahamut...
What the hell is that thing?
A computer. One that's been secretly controlling
everything the human race sees and hears...
since before we were born.
It's manipulated us so skillfully
that we'd never realize the truth.
Which is that the city we live in is
actually part of a giant spaceship.
All of this so that except
for an elite few...
the populus would be blissfully living
in an illusion of the perfect world.
Or rather, the perfect prison.
So everything else, the rest of the world,
exists only in the computer?
And the time we think we live
in is five centuries past.
Five centuries...?
No! That's totally crazy!
And I don't remember giving
you permission to move!
Lemme show you something.
- Follow me.
- I said stop!
Oh, don't be afraid.
[INTRIGUESQUE MUSIC]
This base is our frontline against
any alien infiltrations.
What?
Our radar's detected an enormous artificial
construct approaching this ship's position.
And that means this false peace
we live in is going to end.
- My god...
- [SCOFFS] Welcome to reality.
But how do you know
they're our enemy?
You saw that molten wasteland?
That's the reality of the impending danger
that we are all now exposed to.
Which is why we've secretly
expanded our military...
and developed new
weapons projects...
here, underground, where
Bahamut's influence can't reach us.
That's why we've been trying to find the key
to overriding Bahamut's core directives.
Thus far, we've managed to clear
six levels of programming.
That left just level seven. However,
before we could clear it...
the Garland interface unit that we had
secretly been developing was stolen.
That bike that you've been joy-riding on.
It wasn't supposed to be revealed until we were
on the verge of cracking the seventh level.
So that's how it is. And the second
Bahamut falls into your grimy hands...
you'll be able to do whatever
you want without challenge!
No one in the city will even know
until the war breaks out!
And you are going to let us
take advantage of that.
[SCOFFS]
I'm giving you the choice of becoming one
of my right-hand men, or death at my hands.
Yeah, right.
I'd like to see you try it!
[ECHOING GUNSHOT]
[MOTORCYCLE STARTS]
[SCOFFS]
[ENERGETIC DANCE MUSIC]
Yui: Hey, Tomomi. What's up?
Tomomi: Would you stop acting so
mopey and just call him yourself?
Yui: That's why you called?
Tomomi: You know, when I said I wanted
to make a movie, I was serious.
Un-huh... And so?
Tomomi: And, I really am going to use him
for the lead. Is that all right with you?
[SIGHS] Hey look, you're the director.
You do what you want.
Tomomi: Awesome! In that case, I wanna have a
story meeting tonight! Will you call him for me?
Me call him?!
Tomomi: So, this is the idea.
- There's this guy, see, who likes
motorcycles and stuff. - Meow!
But then, one day, he and his
girlfriend discover that...
everything in their world has been
fabricated by a giant computer.
And the next part is the
real hilight of the film.
The two of them have their lives
threatened by unknown assailants...
and unbeknownst to
the rest of the world...
they smash a secret organization
that's trying to create a military state!
Or something like that.
- How's that?
- Hmm...
The thing is that I can barely afford
the film stock, so I need your help.
Are you guys with me?
Sure. I'll do what I can.
So, how about you, Shogo?
You'd be the perfect leading man.
You don't want to play
opposite me, do you?
You don't want anything
to do with me.
You won't even tell me where
you're working now.
You won't speak.
It's like I'm not there.
I never should have bothered
calling you, should I?
Actually, I wanted to call you too.
[SOFT GASP]
And my problem's not with
you being in the movie.
I've just... got a bad
feeling about this.
[DOOR OPENING]
- Mai: Tadah Tum Tadah! Yeah!
- Tomomi: Oh, hi Mai! Holy cow, what's that?
I'm so freaked!
You won't believe this!
My agent just got me my first recording
gig, and I'm singing backup for Eve!
- No shit!
- That's wonderful, Mai!
- I've been scouted. - That's awesome.
It's your chance to hit it big.
- Mai: Yeah!
- [JOYFUL SQUEALS]
And the best part is that
Eve's your favorite singer.
- Thank you, god!
- [SIGHS] Later, OK?
- Huh? Oh wow, was I interrupting something?
- You're leaving?
Hey wait, why don't we go out
and party? My treat!
Tomomi: Yeah, and I wanna talk some
more about the movie, too. C'mon!
Shogo: Oh, yeah? Well,
how 'bout this one?
Huh?
What if the entire world that we live in
was being controlled from outside.
What if everything was an illusion,
run by a computer...
that also controls
a giant spaceship.
- A spaceship?
- Umm, did I miss something here?
In other words, what if this city was inside
some gigantic ship, floating in space?
Hmm... Sci-fi is hot...
Yeah, it's just something
I thought of.
- Interesting, huh?
- [MYSTERIOUS, CONSPIRATORIAL MUSIC]
General: We can't fight a war
with these relics.
What's the status on
Airgrain FX production?
The fact that we can't work on the surface
is hindering construction.
We're making progress,
but we're losing time.
It's always Bahamut.
We have currently cleared
seventy percent of level seven.
The rest is just a matter of time.
General: Time that we don't have.
That unidentified object is approaching.
- I understand, sir.
- Just get it done!
[CAR STARTS, DEPARTS]
All talk and no backbone. When it comes down to
the wire, I know which way they'll be running.
My men feel exactly the same way.
After all, how can we trust a leadership corps
who only cares about saving their own skins?
Too bad we're not in charge.
Oh, our time will come-
if we have to make it ourselves!
[ADVENTUROUS MUSIC]
It's OK, I won't ask you any
more questions about it.
- Look, I'd like to tell you, but-
- No, really, it's cool.
Fantastic, this is awesome!
This is going to be great!
- Is that story for real?
- That's what Mai told me.
But that doesn't make sense! Why wouldn't a big
star like Eve show up for her own session?
Yeah, Mai was really bummed out.
And how will they do
the video with only Mai?
They said that they'd cut them
together, but there's more.
- Something odd.
- What's that?
No one's ever seen Eve except on TV.
No concerts or anything.
[POP MUSIC (FAINT)]
~b~Eve: ~i~Those who are dreaming...
Lips...
Hesitant hearts... Fingertips...
Chase the wind...
and seize hold of love...
before this blue city crumbles to dust.
The sky, reflected in building windows...
Technician A: Hold on! Stop recording!
[STATIC]
We're supposed to rewind by
three seconds, seven frames.
Technician B: Yeah, yeah, all right.
Technician B: Man, this
computer is just amazing!
Technician A: Yeah, generating the melody
and the lyrics simultaneously.
Technician A: Then we have to redo it because
they screwed up the choreography. Figures!
[BOTH LAUGH]
Technician A: It doesn't matter. This song
will be a hit too. They always are.
~b~Eve: ~i~The sky,
reflected in building windows...
wants to...
[DRAMATIC GUITAR LINE]
Everyone... they've been
fooling everyone!
Lousy kid!
- Hey Todd, you wanna check out my VCR?
- Sure. - [BOTH SCREAM]
I don't think so, coppers!
[SCREAMS]
Ahhh!
[PHONE BEEPS]
[GROANS SLEEPILY]
Yeah, B.D.
What?! He drop-kicked a cop car?
Subordinate: That's right;
in the middle of town.
He's on the other line, and
demanding to speak with you.
What the hell.
Put him through.
Subordinate: Yes, sir. Connecting.
- Shogo: Hey, it's me.
- Well. Causing a little commotion, are we?
Maybe. Do you know that singer,
Eve? Interesting woman.
- In fact, I just met her.
- B.D.: And...?
And I think it's time you stopped
making fools of everyone!
That's all very nice, kid, but you're
barking up the wrong tree.
B.D.: Eve isn't our creation,
she's Bahamut's.
I'm goin' public anyway!
B.D.: [CHUCKLES]
Oh, we'll see about that.
Remember what happened when
you called the TV station?
- So that was you...
- [POLICE SIREN]
[GRUNTS]
Well just because you've got the media
locked up in the palm of your hand...
doesn't mean you're
gonna be safe!
[HANGUP TONE]
[DRAMATIC, SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
I want a full status update.
Distance?
Reading 400 as of the
last capture count.
There's no doubt; the target code-named
Dezalg is definitely on an intercept vector.
That fast. And where do we stand on
the Bahamut decryption process?
According to the latest report, the data technicians
are still examining the control codes for level seven.
- Well, tell them to work faster!
- Yes, sir.
Supervisor: Voice command and statement
from level seven has been changed to E.V.E.
Please confirm your memory maps.
There it is! I've finally
found it, sir.
The EVE interpreter is recorded
in the slave ROM; area AD3 to 9F3!
All right, all we have to do now use the
machine language and convert it to our own.
[WARNING SIRENS]
[DIGITAL SCREECHING]
Do you hear that?
Bahamut's screaming.
Attention: Operator, Level 7G.
- Operator, Level 7G. Program backup is requested.
- [ALERT TONES]
That's Eve!
Level 7G Operator, please open the file on
the RAM cartridge. Backup is requested.
I am EVE, a program created
by humankind, for humankind.
Based on data 5930, I must
proceed with code 86.
Based on data 5930, I must proceed
with code 86. Please authorize.
Uh, yeah. Go ahead, then.
[GASPS]
Eve: 5930. As the conflict which occurred
on Biosphere Prime neared completion...
the human race rendered the planet
incapable of supporting life.
As a result, the survivors were forced to
journey into space in search of another planet.
However, once in space,
the conflict reignited.
In the ensuing destruction,
the spaceships designated...
for the purpose of evacuation
were severely damaged.
As a result, half of the
biospheres were abandoned.
- Abandoned...
- Eve: 4,321,260 standard time units...
500 years have passed
since 5930 was encoded.
And now, the same error
is in progress.
The same calamity that took
Biosphere Prime will claim this ship.
Biosphere Prime? What is that?
Biosphere Prime is Earth,
the human homeworld.
- Hold on! Are you telling me that the
enemy are humans, just like us? - Correct.
But if Bahamut's seventh-level program,
E.V.E., was online...
it would be able to protect you.
That is the purpose for which
it... I... was designed.
However, this program
is about to be disabled.
If this happens, the peace you-
Wait, just tell me something first.
I can see why you'd make
this ship look like a city.
But why did you make everyone think
it's still the late 20th century?
Because that particular period in time was
one of the most peaceful for all of mankind.
Oh...
~b~Yui: ~i~\"There's never been a better
place or time to be alive.\"
Please help me! This program
is going to be disabled!
[FILM PROJECTOR]
Mai: Oh wow! Radical!
Yeah, and wait'll you see
Yui's performance!
[PHONE RINGS]
Yes, studio!
Yeah! We were just watching
the new rushes!
Uh-huh... and you look very studly!
Hold on, I'll transfer your call now.
Yui, it's your hero.
Hello. Huh? You mean, now?
- Oh! I detect a date! - Oh,
um... what about... You know you want him!
- Tomomi: What do we have to do, shove you?
- Well, what do you want me to do?
- Soldier: Distance countdown to 200, sir.
- And Bahamut?
We're currently converting the EVE
program using machine language.
Estimated completion: three hours.
So, what's going on?
You're looking so serious.
Hey, just tell me, OK?
I've... been wanting you.
- Well, that's kind of sudden!
- Hey, you knew it.
Uh, I mean, couldn't you phrase
it a little more romantically?
- So that's no, huh?
- Uh, Shogo...?
Uh, hey Shogo! Wait!
Yui: What is it with you?
Why are you acting like this?
Shogo: Hey, if you don't
want to, that's fine.
Yui: No, no. You brought this up.
So let's talk about it.
I'm sorry, Yui. My mind's
all messed up.
I don't know where to turn!
What should I do?!
All I know is, I'm runnin' out of time.
[CHOKED SOBS]
Supervisor: The conversion to
machine language is complete, sir.
We're saving the converted program now. Just
a little more and it'll be all wrapped up.
Good, I'll report this to the top brass
myself. And you'd better deliver.
It's time to implement our plan.
[SIGHS]
~b~Eve: ~i~At morning's first light...
- Hey, I've never heard this song before.
- No music, OK?
I want...
Just what is with you? [GASPS]
The wind's lullaby-I'll let you listen.
The wind's lullaby-I'll sing-
[STATIC] You must help me!
They're attempting to kill-
[STATIC]
\"Please Stand By\"
Huh? Again? What now?
It's done. We've just
cleared Bahamut, sir.
Good! Now transfer all of Bahamut's
remaining functions...
every single one,
to our internal systems.
And double-check everything.
Let's do it.
\"Please Stand By\"
We're interrupting regular programming
for a breaking news bulletin.
According to foreign sources,
a 35,000 ton Japanese tanker...
the Akebono-maru, appears to have
exploded after being struck by a missile...
launched from an orbiting
weapons satellite.
At this very moment, the tanker is aflame
and adrift in middle of the Pacific Ocean.
Asked for comment just now, government
officials stated that space-based warfare...
now seems to be a grim reality.
This station will keep you updated
as this story unfolds.
Please forget...
[SOFT SIGH]
Ah... Shogo...
[ENERGETIC ROCK MUSIC]
[LAUGHTER] ...Huh?
What is the meaning of this?
Isn't it obvious? We're here
to claim your lives.
Are you mad?!
[SCREAMS]
[MORE SCREAMS]
Objective A completed.
Status report, please.
Soldier: The TV station's secure.
We're on our way to the Diet Building.
Understood.
Yui, I want to tell you the truth.
Will you believe me?
- I'm listening.
- This movie we're making with Tomomi...
I didn't make that story up.
It's all real.
- That's... not possible! - But it is.
And I'm gonna tell you what I know.
Starting from the beginning.
[DISTANT SIRENS AND EXPLOSIONS]
[LIVELY MUSIC]
- [PHONE RINGS]
- Hmm...
- Yumekano here.
- Hello, sir. It's B.D.
- And the plan?
- Quite successful.
However, as you no doubt know, we will be relying
upon your assistance during the transition.
And the financial community
will support you, sir.
And now that Bahamut's
finally fallen...
the arms industry will rise to
levels never before dreamed.
Ah, Mr. Prime Minister,
do not be concerned.
We merely wish to remove
some of your burdens.
In fact, we will take responsibility for
everything from this point forward.
But we will need a public face.
Do as we say, and everything
should work out fine.
[GROAN OF RESIGNATION]
- \"Explosion! NNS News\"
- For those of you just tuning in...
approximately one hour ago,
in a separate incident...
another in our nation's fleet
of supertankers has been sunk...
by an attack from a military satellite.
No one knows why.
- Hey, old man! - Turn on the TV! - Shhh!
- TV: this can't be an accident, can it?
No, it must be deliberate.
And therefore, the government...
has no choice but to take retaliatory
measures against whoever it is!
Huh? We've got a new update. According
to information we've just received...
the government has stated that this is definitely
an act of aggression by a foreign country.
Within an hour, the Prime
Minister will make an...
- Bogus, man. So that's why. - ...emergency
announcement and hold a press conference.
- So, what's up?
- What?! \"What's up\"?!
Cheez, dude, haven't you looked out the
damn window?! There's a tank out there!
A tank?! The TV hadn't said
anything about tanks yet!
Oh yeah, man. A great big one.
It was awesome!
And that thing was hauling ass!
- Yui: So you're saying that our world is inside
a spaceship? - [EVE SONG BEGINS (SOFTLY)]
Shogo: That's right.
We're living inside a false reality...
maintained by an enormous
computer called Bahamut.
- Yui: But, all the other countries?
- Shogo: They don't exist.
Yui: But how can that be?
I have friends who've been to America...
and Europe. Mai's been there.
Shogo: No, they only think they've gone.
Bahamut uses some kind of hypnosis on them.
- Yui: Hypnosis?
- Shogo: That's right.
Even the people seeing other people off
at the airport get the same treatment.
What better way to keep us
from discovering the truth?
Yui: So, these people only think
their friends went somewhere else?
Shogo: Uh-huh. It's all a sham.
Our world really is just a stage.
Officer: UFO course still tracking.
Estimated time to contact: 180 seconds.
Sir, District 3D reports
a Rimarl will intercept.
We've got to take it out!
Shogo: Even as we're lying here, a battle between
spaceships is about to begin beneath our feet.
And if I'da said yes to that big shot,
I might be fighting with them right now.
But you're not buying
any of this, are you?
If you say it's so,
I believe it.
Yui... you're the only one
I can trust. I...
Rimarl group reports contact with U2.
Inform Rockwell group,
stand by for scramble.
Rimarl has engaged U2.
Launch all fighters!
- Rockwell, all units scramble!
- Scorpion standing by. All clear. Launch!
- We've lost the Rimarl?
- Yes, sir. We believe it's been shot down.
- Target confirmed!
- All units, Formation A!
Damn it! Die, already!
Rockwell to Michael... U2 disabled.
Requesting retrieval.
[GASPS] My entire unit
has been destroyed.
[APPROACHING HELICOPTER]
[SOFT POP MUSIC]
Hmm...?
- What's wrong? - Something's outside.
Could you turn on the television?
Announcer: Traffic in the nearby
area has been blocked off...
so there's not
a single car to be seen.
Ah, here they come! Following the
armored motorcycle in front...
is the newest weapon in our country's
arsenal, the MT1 \"Hell Peacock\"...
an armored missile launcher that is being revealed
for the first time to our general population.
Even the workingmen on their morning commute
have to be impressed by this spectacle.
All I can do is stand and stare at these amazing
vehicles built with our well-spent tax dollars.
- Passing by now is...
- What is this? It's like we're at war.
Announcer: What a tremendous
display of military might!
- And now, this elite team, Unit 803...
- The seventh level... it fell.
Last night, our military encountered, engaged,
and destroyed an attacking enemy force.
Thus we will always respond to those who
attempt to violate our nation's sovereignty.
We cannot yet disclose
the identity of this enemy.
However, events which we
would not have dreamed of...
in the peace we had until just yesterday
are transpiring as we speak.
- Therefore, to the people of our country, we ask
for your cooperation and your strength. - [GASPS]
- The threat draws closer moment by moment.
- Yikes! I think that we're at war!
Hey, I'm in a war of my own!
I have to wrap up all this filming today.
Oh, and I need you to get changed and pick
up the rushes from the camera shop for me.
Right...
Hmm... Yeah, that looks good.
This'll be the last scene, OK?
[CHORTLES] All right, guys,
it's time to get it on!
Ready, start!
If we go to war, there's no way
to know if we'll come back.
- Are you cool with that?
- Not really, but... I'll wait.
- That's good, just stick with... - [FEEDBACK]
- Eve: Everyone! Let's stand up...
- to defend our peace and freedom
from the invaders! - [LOUD ROCK MUSIC]
~b~Eve: ~i~Worrying about today,
dreaming of tomorrow...
We are drifting away.
- Is that Eve?
~i~- You are alone in town.~b~
All I can do is stand and watch.
You believe there will
always be a tomorrow...
but remember it was your choice.
They're gonna make all of us
soldiers before this is over.
[GASPS] But I can't lose you!
Oh yeah, great faces!
One more take with that feeling!
- Coco: Here... What the...? What the...!
- [SIGHS] That thing's hopeless.
Well, with all these tanks
out on the streets...
not even the craziest bikers are goin' out,
so what the hell else have I got to do?
- SIGN: Opening Day: Army Recruitment.
- Over 1200 youths gathered at the...
War Department this morning for a hectic
first day of volunteer recruitment.
This reporter was there to report.
I'm standing here with a group of patriotic
young volunteers. So, how does all this feel?
Umm... Well... I don't like being
called a private, y'know...
but I'll get a stylin' uniform,
and a gun! That'll be cool!
And, it's for our country!
Whatever! [LAUGHS]
- Morley... - And that's Chombo behind him.
- Newslady: Thank you very much, and good luck.
- Newslady: how about you? - I was wondering
where those two knuckleheads were.
Damn! What the hell
were they thinking?!
So, the last I heard, you were
singing with Eve. Is that still a go?
Uh-huh. But it's actually pretty boring. All we've
been recording is that military propaganda.
- Where's Tomomi?
- Yui: [SIGHS]
When she's editing a film, I don't
think Tomomi even sleeps.
She asked if we could bring her
some burgers and beer.
Man, if she keeps this up,
she'll look like a keg!
[DOG BARKS]
Oh, yeah... cool... cool!
Mmmm... And the composite
images turned out great, too!
Perfect! Nobody's gonna
believe this film!
- [CHORTLE] - [CLATTER]
- Huh...? Mai?
[GASPS]
- Who are you?! What're you-
- [SILENCED GUNSHOT] - [CHOKED YELP]
But... why?
[DRAMATIC STRUMS]
[CONSPIRATORIAL PIANO]
Loose end eliminated.
Excellent. Make sure you retrieve the
negatives and any incriminating evidence.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[SHOCKED WAIL]
[DRAMATIC NOTE]
- [ANGUISHED GASPS]
- T-Tomomi...
- Oh my god! Is she...?
- [MELANCHOLY PIANO]
- No! [WAILS] No! No!
- Mai!
Him!
Where are you going?!
I can't tell you.
But I'll be back, I promise.
Shogo...
[WEEPING]
Mai...
We've got to hold it together, Mai.
We need to call the police.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yes? Yes, sir, I...
She's here, but I-
Yes, sir, I'll put her on now.
Mai! Your father wants
to speak to you.
- [SOBS] Yes, Papa? - Yumekano: Mai!
- That's right, it's me, Papa...
Yumekano: Thank god. We've been looking
everywhere for you. Are you all right?
- Your mother's very worried.
- Uh-huh.
Mai, I think it's time
you came home.
The world's going to be changing,
and things will become... difficult.
You can't go on living
day-to-day anymore.
- I won't insist, but I really wish you'd
come back where you belong. - [LOUD WEEPING]
Oh, Papa!
[ACTIVE, DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I'm coming for you, you bastard!
We've made a thorough examination of
the captured enemy patrol ship...
and from the data we've collected, it seems that
their weaponry is fifty years ahead of ours.
True, but at this point we have
no option left but to fight.
With luck, we should be able to reverse-
engineer some of their weapons fairly quickly.
But their full capabilities are still
unknown. How can we plan for that?
Our records show that five hundred years
ago, our forces were evenly matched.
However, with a fifty-year technological
lag in armaments, and...
a probable numerical disadvantage
as well, I believe that we need...
to seriously reconsider our current strategy
if there is to be any chance of winning.
We've chosen our course,
and there's no turning back!
Therefore, think only of what
will lead us to victory!
I'm sorry, sir.
- Destroying Bahamut oughta piss him off!
- Headband: \"Victory at Any Cost\"
Turkey One to Full House.
Intruder is in B1.
Advancing towards Bahamut.
Requesting Hargan backup.
Full House: Roger.
- Watch this!
- [ACTION MUSIC]
Turkey Two: Yeah! All right!
He's dead; nothing on the sensors.
I'm going down to confirm.
Hey, wait! It's still dangerous.
Get back up here!
[SCREAMS]
Uhh! Turkey One to Balbrun!
The target is using sensor reduction.
We lost visual contact just short
of Highway 28 in Block A5.
Lawson: Balbrun Leader to all units.
The target is headed our way.
Set down and assume Formation One.
Shoot to kill on sight.
Soldier A: Roger.
Energy reading at 12 o'clock.
Soldier B: Thermal signature approaching.
Get out of its trajectory, now!
- Lawson: That was him. - Soldier A: Full speed
along the trajectory? I don't believe it!
- Lawson: You'd better believe it!
- Soldier A: I'm sorry, sir...
but he's managed to break
through to Bahamut.
- B.D.: This is ridiculous! - Lawson: Request
permission to use weapons inside Bahamut.
At a time like this,
that pathetic little-
- Permission for Energy Swords only. And
don't let him get away! - Officer: Yes, sir!
OK, so this screwed-up world
is all your fault, huh?
What?! Out of ammo?!
Ah, geez! And here they come!
Huh...? What is this?
[SCREAMS]
Oh, shit! [CHOKED SCREAM]
- There he is! - Mackie's down.
- Don't let him get away!
Damn! Where is that bastard?
[GRUNTS]
Can't take much more!
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Aha! There you are!
B.D.: I see you recognize me, Yahagi.
I can't trust you to those incompetents.
Care for a piece of me?
You have no idea what this
world's really fighting!
Damn, he's good.
This won't be easy.
But I'm too damn stubborn to lose!
- Don't get too cocky, kid!
- Screw you!
B.D.: You'd better learn to aim first!
Aww, what's wrong,
no more bullets?
- I'm not the pushover you think I am!
- B.D.: Oh, yeah? Well, how's this?!
B.D.: Where's your
cocky attitude now, kid?
[GASPS]
What happened to all that fire
you just had? Get on your feet!
Now you know how tough
you really are.
And by the way,
I owe ya something!
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
This fight is over. All units,
return to the line.
Major, a second enemy
wave is approaching.
Roger. I'm on my way.
[GRANDFATHER CLOCK CHIMES 4AM]
[SOFT SOBS]
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Yui!
I'm so sorry. [SOBS]
I won't forget about you...
Or about...
We all have to go where
our hearts take us.
The place that's best for you.
But what about you, Yui?
You're going to be all alone.
I can't think that.
- I know he'll be back.
- He will come back.
And I know you'll both
be so happy.
Yeah, we all will.
[SOFT SOB]
It's been wonderful. [SOBS]
I've gotta go! [WEEPS]
[SOFT GASP]
- [MELANCHOLY POP MUSIC]
- [DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[SOFT GASP]
[CAR STARTS]
Remember... every moment
that we live is a blessing.
[SOBS] Goodbye, Mai... Tomomi...
~i~ \"The Wind's Lullaby,\" ~b~ a new song.
[GROANS]
~b~Eve: ~i~Those who are dreaming...
Lips...
Hesitant hearts... Fingertips...
Chase the wind...
and seize hold of love...
before this blue city crumbles to dust.
The sky, reflected in building windows...
wants to bring me to you.
It's my first morning.
I want to deliver my heart to you.
The wind's lullaby-I'll let you listen.
The wind's lullaby-I'll sing it for you.
Don't show me...
- Shogo...
- that sad profile again.
[GRUNTS AND GROANS]
[WISTFUL POP MUSIC BEGINS]
~b~Eve: ~i~I met the city
girl in the \"heart town.\"
She acted cheerful, but she kept...
her loneliness inside somewhere.
I haven't seen her for a while...
and I heard rumors about her
which bother me.
[MUSIC BECOMES DYNAMIC]
I might have another broken heart, again.
I saw her walking with him.
When this song plays ever so gently...
I wonder if we'll
ever be romantic again.
The smell of a gimlet reminds me of you.
The cafe bar where you once
whispered lovingly.
I haven't been there for a while...
but give me a call right now.
Loneliness has given me sleepless nights.
We broke up because of a fight, but...
when I hear this ever-so-tender song...
I wonder if you'll return to me smiling.
When this song plays ever so gently...
I wonder if we'll
ever be romantic again.
When I hear this ever-so-tender song...
I wonder if you'll return to me smiling.