You know what I just remembered?
Valentine's Day is soon.
Why...?
Now I have to give
chocolate to someone!
It's sad what being so average
makes you worry about...
I'm glad I don't have to
stress out over that anymore.
My priorities have
changed since he kissed me.
Whose memory did
you steal this from...?
Because this is
what yours looked like!
I've French kissed!
Yamada Two Point 'Oh!'
Heave--ho!
Heave--ho! Heave--ho!
Hey, Yamada...
Would you like to go see
a movie with me later?
I don't know.
I'll have to think about it.
She said she'll think about it!
Yay!
See that...?
It's called strength...!
It's what happens when you
become an experienced woman!
What happens when you
become an experienced jerk?
Did you remember that
Valentine's Day is coming up...?
And did you happen to
get Kosuda anything...?
Chocolates or a card?
Huh?
Translation: No, I'm a jerk.
Why do I have to
give him a gift...?!
He's the boy in the story!
He's supposed to give me stuff!
Fine.
At least I'll be getting my
pipes cleaned soon and won't
have to deal with
this crap anymore...
...and then...
I'll become Yamada
Three Point 'Oh!'
Seriously...
No one else in
the world obsesses
over the nasty like she does.
A Valentine's Day filled
with sweat and tears!
From Yamada with... Love...?
Weird.
"Pick good ones?"
Great mom, that helps.
What does that even mean?
How do I know
which "ones" are good?
Look at the color.
You want a bright
blue one with white eyes.
Thanks for the help random lady!
Did you learn that
in house wife school?
Go home and roll something
in your fancy kelp!
Oh hi...
I didn't know that was you.
Thanks a lot Miyano...
I appreciate
your fish expertise.
Anytime!
I wonder if she knows that
Yamada kissed Kosuda.
I doubt she'd be this
nice to me if she did...
Maybe I should hang out
with her a little longer
and find some
way to bring it up.
So you really like
cooking, don't you?
Yeah...
You should've seen the huge
spread I made for New Years!
That's it...!
You're teaching me
how to cook tonight!
This is an easy soup with
sautéed burdock root,
ginger--stewed sardines, and
kidney beans in a sesame sauce.
Holy crap.
Will you stay and
have some with me?
Oh that's okay.
It's totally cool
if you want to.
It's not as fun
cooking for just me...
Plus, I'd love
to have your opinion.
She's like, freakishly nice.
Omigah!
Emergency!
I just read that I should
be doing squats every
day so that my
legs won't get sore!
Do your legs get sore?!
Are you doing squats
and not telling me?!
Sorry, I'm busy.
Takeshita...
Can I ask you something...?
You have a boyfriend, right?
You don't have
to answer, of course...
...but what does it feel like?
Aww...
She's so sweet about it...
Unlike some people I know.
Fine then I'll shake
it out of you...!
Tell me what it's like!
We're supposed to
be friends, damn it!
The reason I'm asking is...
there's kinda someone I'm into.
"Someone" meaning Kosuda?
Ohmigosh how did you know...?!
Did Yamada tell
you or something?!
I don't remember...
you gonna tell him how you feel?
Oh no...
I can't do that ...
We've been friends
for so long that--
I can't tell Kosuda I like him.
He doesn't need a klutz who
can't cook a meal
without spilling it!
I never thought I'd see the day,
but you're actually starting
to make sense to me.
Besides that,
it doesn't really bother
me that he's not interested...
I just want him to be happy,
and if that's with someone else
then I wouldn't want to
take that away from him.
Does it suck that I think Kosuda
might be better off with Miyano?
Wanna hear something silly?
I make him Valentine's Day
chocolates every year...
But I'm always too afraid
to give them to him.
That's kinda tragic.
The practice ones for this year
are in there if you
want to see them.
No frikkin way!
What is this chocolate
amusement park I'm staring at?
It's called a cake and
Miyano made it for Kosuda.
Yeah, she cares about
him so she does things like
that all the time, and she
never complains about it.
Sorry girl...
but if you want this to work
you have got to step it up!
Is there a way to just
ditch Valentine's Day?
It won't be that bad.
I'm sure we'll all
get something.
I wonder if she'll remember...
Of course she will...
but what if she doesn't...?
What'll I do...?
I'll have to quit school!
What's with the drama?
Didn't he make
out with her already?
You know I'll even
take a pity gift.
It's better than nothing.
Works for me.
You say that like
you've got someone
on reserve to
give you pity gifts!
It's just my mom, dude.
That cake is gonna
be pretty tough to beat.
Get ready!
I'm about to throw down
with some serious chocolate!
Really all you have
to do is melt it down
and let it get hard again...?
Guys are so freakin'
easy to figure out.
Yamada is great 'cause she
makes chocolate cake for me~!
Yay Yamada~!
He doesn't know that
the chocolate is just
the appetizer to
the yummy main dish...
...which is me.
Evacuate for gas leak...
Evacuate for gas leak ...
Are we about to die?
It's a good thing the main
dish is so amazing...
...because the
appetizer is screwed.
"Avoid burning chocolate by
heating in a double boiler,
between eighty--two and
eighty six degrees."What?
That's like four degrees apart!
This is stupid!
I shouldn't have to
risk my life to get laid!
Yeah, that'll help.
It's done!
That was easier than
I thought it was gonna be...
I'm just that awesome!
I do hope it works out for ya...
It shows you tried
if nothing else.
Please...
I don't know what
you meant by 'tried,'
but I don't try for any guy.
Sorry but the dark circles under
your eyes tell a
different story.
And so, Valentine's Day
reared its ugly head!
Nothing.
So, I um...
Made this.
Is that for me?
Still nothing.
Thought you might like this.
Wow, thank you so much!
Hope this isn't awkward.
No, I was hoping you would!
Good morning, everyone!
So glad you like it.
More than like it!
That's a box...!
Please be for me...!
No way, there's more...?!
Yamada...!
I made this for you!
Happy Valentine's Day!
I got you something too, lady!
Thanks so much you guys!
No fair!
Even the girls
are giving her gifts?!
That was the last bell.
I'm officially a loser.
Are you free today?
What?
Cool.
Was she taking a survey...?
What was that all about?!
All right!
So tonight's the
night it's going down...
I'd rather give it to
him at his house
than with all these
people watching.
So that's it.
She didn't do
anything for me today.
I can't freak out anymore.
I've got to give him
something this year.
I still want him to know how
I feel even if I can't say it.
I wonder which one
he'd like the most.
Wow, that's not
obsessive at all.
What if he's studying
or something?
I should do this later...
No! I can't keep
running away!
Here...!
I made these...!
For you...!
Please take 'em!
Rock; that's so sweet!
Kazuki!
What?
I didn't think about
what would happen
if someone else
answered the door!
I don't have a plan--B!
Sorry to bother you!
These are for--
Right...!
I remember now.
For the apples...?
You didn't have to...!
My grandmother actually grows
them so we get them for free!
I'm sorry--I should've
told you when you
picked them up the other day.
This smells wonderful...!
I failed...
I messed up Valentine's Day.
What...?!
You didn't get anything?
Are you that lame?
I'm kinda surprised.
I got like four
things this year.
This is for you, sweetheart.
Don't give me that
pouty look, Takashi.
You're in high school now.
So I don't get chocolates?!
Dude, just go to the store.
I guess it doesn't
make sense for me to be
bringing him Valentine's
Day presents this late.
In other words, you're wussing
out and staying a virgin?
But I can't leave damn it!
He'll never know what a
thoughtful, perfect person I am!
He has to think
I really care and
am not just out to
ride his disco stick!
Plus you want him to have them.
I'm too pretty to
be stressing about this!
All the way in!
It's stuck!
Come back!
I can't believe I just did that!
So there wasn't a card or
anything just creepy
random chocolates
in the mailbox?
Creepy is right.
Aw look!
Someone
remembered you after all!
You're really enjoying
this, aren't you?
Whatever. I'm sure
those were left for you.
Oh, like it matters!
We got free chocolate!
That looks disgusting.
Sorry...!
That gross, huh...?
Man I bet someone
must hate your insides
if they left you that crap!
I wonder if she's right.
Finally...
I wonder if he figured out
that box was from me.
Hey, Yamada...
Did you come by my house
last night for any reason?
No!
Why would I do that?!
You got a point!
Like... really...
Why'd you even ask that?
I know it seems weird,
but we got a box of chocolates
in the mail and don't
know who it's from.
Oh...
How thoughtful...
Well, did you try them?
Did they taste good?
Um...
Why do you care
what they tasted like?
No way!
Was it you?
Why didn't you
want me to find out?!
Please...!
Do you really think I'd
waste my time giving you
anything homemade
for Valentine's Day!
I don't think anyone mentioned
they were homemade.
I bet you didn't even
like them anyway.
No I liked them...
I mean, they did
taste a little funky...
...but I ate every single one.
It was obvious that
a lot of thought went
into them even
if they weren't for me.
I bet that wasn't it; you got
gifts from other people...
You probably liked those better.
Uh, no...
I didn't get anything.
Not even from Miyano?
Miyano...?
No, of course not...
I mean she brought
us a cake yesterday,
but that was
for the whole family...
She said it was a trade for
some apples we gave her.
No way...
Does he seriously believe that?
That sucks...
I feel sorry for her.
It's okay...
I've always got next year.
B Gata H Kei!
Yamada...
Yamada!
Hello?
Wake up!
What's going on?!
Who are you?!
Glad you asked...
It's about time...
I'm your Eros Deity
and I'm here to help you
on your sexual journey...
I've gotta say,
so far I am not impressed.
I'm totes being stalked
by a clone with a mustache?
And you're totes
the luckiest girl alive!
This new 'shy' thing you're
trying is giving me gas!
Don't make me hate my job okay!
What?!
Seriously...
Are you just trying
to drive me crazy?
Why are you having
so much trouble
getting that pansy
up in your pansy?
Hey...!
You don't know what
you're talking about!
We already kissed
each other with tongue!
A kiss is a kiss.
It doesn't count.
Listen...!
The reason you're
not getting laid
is cause you're denying
your sexual power!
No I'm not...!
You're talking crazy!
Check with your lady lumps
if you don't believe me.
Yeah... You're right...
It makes sense now!
I mean why are we doing
an episode all about
Valentine's Day and
giving gifts and crap...?
This is a story about me
getting it on and putting
out for one hundred guys--not
some stupid teen romance!
Good to have you back.
Now where were we?
You must unleash
the powers of naughtiness!
If he doesn't know what you're
after, he can't give it to you.
Kosuda...!
Hold on tight 'cause this
ride just got humpier!
Is she seriously just screaming
out the window at no one?
Work on your naughty power!
I've never felt a
sensation like this before...
Trying to be smooth and creative
is not working on Kosuda...
He's too slow for all that...
I've gotta enlist the
powers of naughtiness.
I have to just grab him by
the balls and tell him what I
want so that there are no
more misunderstandings...
...and I have to make
sure it happens quickly
so he doesn't freak
out and run away.
Maybe I should
hatch this plan inside.
That doesn't sound very good...
Catch a cold?
Maybe.
I tried something new
that I read in a magazine.
"Men find women sexier when
they don't wear any underwear...
Okay!"
So I figured,
"why stop at underwear?"
and I spent the entire
day completely naked!
I love you, Mr. Bear!
And then caught a cold.
You may have
read too much into it.
I know, right?
And ditching just the panties
would've been
so much easier, too!
No panties?!
That's genius!
Good~ bye~ panties~!
Coming on to him with
the vents open will
let him know
exactly what I'm after!
That's uh...
That's very inspiring.
So much better than
the time I showed
him my bra and
he totally didn't get it.
He'll finally know this
muffin is baked and ready!
I just have to
remember to pounce
when it's up and get it done!
Our time has come, Kosuda!
I guess I could've waited 'til I
got to school to
lose the skivvies.
It's kinda cold today.
What's up, Yamada?!
Hey, good morning!
Why does it feel like
they're all staring at me--
like they know or something...?!
So awkward!
Oh gross.
I hope the teacher can't tell...
Ugh, this chair feels sticky.
Stay down.
Please stay down!
I keep thinking my skirt
is going to fly up
and everyone here
will see my miracle!
Which I thought was our
long--term goal, so way to go!
It's just a small
piece of cloth.
Why does it feel like such
a big deal that it's gone...?
And what is with all the shaking
and sweating and
being nervous crap?
This is so not me...
Am I shy?
Am I going to have
to wear glasses now?
Omigosh!
What if it became a law that
women couldn't wear panties?
Then all the shy nerds would
become sexy vixens...!
We could do it where and
whenever we wanted,
which would stimulate
the population,
and then no one
would hate the government!
Hey do you guys know
how I could make a law?
What?
Uh...
I guess your first step would
be becoming a politician.
Wow is this what smart
people think about...?
Passing laws 'n stuff?
That's so awesome.
What is going on with her...?
She's acting weird again
and it's freaking me out.
Ugh...
I really have to go...
But I don't want to get up and
walk in the middle of class.
What did I do to deserve
a bag whacking?
What'd I do to deserve
a crazy friend...?!
Did you forget to
stop by the modesty
store on your way
out of the womb?
Seriously!
I have modesty...
look I'm blushing.
Who comes to school
without any panties on?
You're wearing a skirt!
Don't you get it this is an
important step in
the process...?!
I don't know when
he's going to be around
or interested so I've
gotta be prepared!
He'll be interested when
you act like you give a crap
and stop treating him
like a frikkin sex toy!
You're ridiculous!
Guys want to see it!
They'd probably jump for joy
if my skirt flew up
in front of them!
Yeah, that's what you think.
Why not...?!
Are you saying Cha Cha
looks weird or something?
Number one,
you named her Cha Cha...?
And second,
how were you planning
to let him know
you're free balling?
I don't know.
I was just gonna
show him, I guess.
Don't do that.
It'll turn him off...
Remember what happened when
you showed him your breasts...?
He's gonna think
you're a flasher.
No...?
Like the creepy old guys?
Those freaks get off on
seeing a bunch of people's
reactions and
have to search for
crowded parks and
malls and stuff.
My mission is simpler.
I just wanna screw.
Then go to a park and find some
old pervert,
get flashed and elope!
What would you do if this
started to get more extreme?
More extreme?
On your back...!
I'm sticking it in!
You're still gonna do it?!
Crap, what if she's right?
Would it really be
a turn off to him...?
I guess there's only
one way to find out.
Hey Kosuda!
Yeah?
Um...
Well...
I, uh...
Do...
Do you like it when
girls don't wear panties?!
Like it...?
You mean...
...like I like soda?
Why the hell is she asking me
such a random awkward question?!
Uh...
I...
...haven't really
thought about it I guess.
He just compared me to soda...
He must not be
that into it after all.
This sucks...
I guess guys are way more
complicated than I thought.
Now I have to try
to not show it to him.
Okay I think I'm
gonna go home now.
This is just stupid...
He seriously said
he didn't want to see
my muffin and
compared it to soda.
Whatever.
I'm glad he didn't see it...
I'll catch you guys later!
Yamada...!
Why did you ask me
that question earlier?!
It all makes sense now,
doesn't it, buddy?
I gotta walk the cat!
Why does he get to run away?!
That makes no sense~!
I'm the one who was standing
there with my gooch out!
I deserve the dramatic exit!
Acceptance has set in...
Yes, that really happened...
But how does someone forget
to put their underwear on?
Wait a minute...
Did she actually
want me to see?!
I'm gonna go for another jog!
Really?
You had like four
chocolates a week ago.
I don't know if she did
it on purpose or not...
...but it was beautiful!
I'm so happy I could die...!
Which is a good thing
because I'm pretty sure
Yamada's going to
kill me tomorrow!
Question one...
When was the last time
you didn't wear panties?
Well let me think.
It had to have been
in the third grade...
I used to like to go
swimming before class...
I wore my suit to the pool
and forgot to pack them
with my change of
clothes for the day.
Oh Miyano...
You're so cute
♪ closing song ♪
Guess who's started their
second year in high school!
I can feel the lustful eyes of
the first year boys all over me!
They want it bad!
Wait, who's this skank?!
A return student?
I feel like I've
seen her before.
Um...
Kanejou!
Don't you dare look
at any other girls!
That's what I want to say,
but I won't 'cause it's crazy!
Ugh, this sucks!
Anyway, see you next time!