So um...
It's been awhile...
...since we went out I mean...
Would you ever give
me another chance?
Sure, whatever.
I don't care.
And so, they're gonna
give it another go...!
This time, you better
get the goods
while the goods
are good to be got!
So you know...
H is for humpin'!
We've already kissed.
Do I have to do the deed next?
What if I'm not good at it?
Actually...
I've been trying hard not to
think about this, but what if...
Yamada...
Already has 'experience'?
You're kidding me, right...?
I bet Yamada and Kanejo
have tons of experience.
They probably know techniques
we haven't even heard of before.
Yeah, they've gotta be right.
What about Misato?
What?!
You are freaking
kidding me right now?!!
No way in hell...
Absolutely not.
Come on, I know
you're a boob guy, but still...
You guys all know she's
going to get nailed by someone.
True, oh, and right
in the middle of it...
Premature ejaculator much?
She's not gonna be able to
help that loud mouth of hers.
Whatever; like that
would ever happen.
What if...
Wow... Hopeless and a
minuteman, fantastic.
Die!
I bet Yamada would be
way worse than Misato.
Are you kidding me...?!
You don't have
a problem with that?!
You're so hard-core!
A hard-core masochist.
A two-pump chump is okay.
What are you doing?
I'm practicing what I'd say
in case Kosuda fails miserably.
You are seriously messed up.
Wow, you finished
before we even got started...
That's okay...
it happens all the time.
No way!
You can't blow before
you cross the threshold!
Poor guy...
He has no clue what
he signed up for.
The Kanejo Family.
Richy brother's
sparkling secret!
This time, I'll get
there really early...
Maybe Yamada will
be there early, too...!
Who am I kidding?
I wish we were
that much in synch.
Actually...
Guess who's already there!
Who the hell does
he think he is?!
This is unforgiveable.
I shouldn't have to wait!
I guess it could be my fault
for getting here an hour early.
Might as well lip gloss back up.
How you doin'?
You're late!
Let's go!
Awesome!
Note to self, start using that
how you doin' line all the time!
It's not easy being
me and by myself.
I always get hit on...
Being pretty is harder
than you might think.
Keiichi...!
Keiichi!
Where is he...?
How could he just disappear?
Oh, he went out for a bit, Miss.
Why...?
Oh, I swear...
I need to lock him up to
keep him from wandering off.
Well, now...
Let's not get carried away...
I brought tea; is there
anything specific you'd like?
Yes, a dungeon.
Ow. My back
went out again.
Are you okay, ma'am...?
Let me help you.
Mommy...!
Where are you?!
Mommy!
Come back!
Help...!
My water broke!
Sorry to trouble you...
...but could you tell me
where Jinbou-cho is...?
Did I say that right?
Or is it Jinbou-cho?
Jinbou-choo?
I'm supposed...
to be somewhere...
It's official!
That loser's late!
You're still five minutes early.
What an insensitive jerk!
He obviously should
have come here early
because he should
want to see me sooner!
Well, fine!
He's dead to me!
Dead!
Yamada!
You are dead to me!
Dead Mister Late-Face. Now
let's get to a hotel already!
I did it!
I finally asked him!
Yeah, keep on rolling, girl!
Get it while the getting's good!
A hotel?
Kanejo's big brother?
Yamada...!
I'm so sorry!
You thought I was him...?
Bummer.
That's Kanejo's
brother, isn't it?
About the other day...
I wanted to apologize.
A token of our new friendship.
What the hell do
you think you're doing?!
I was hoping I could make
it up to you somehow.
Look at that table.
That's like the
cutest couple ever!
They have to be models!
Yeah, they're gorgeous...
And I hate them.
Wait a minute...
Is someone else at their table?
I didn't even notice that guy.
I bet he gets that all the time.
What is happening right now?
I don't get it...!
Is this karmic punishment
for being late?
Why did I have to agree to this?
I hate it when
I'm overly nice to
make up for feeling awkward...
Well, I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm Keiichi Kanejo...
Good to meet you.
I'm Kosuda...
Nice meeting you too.
Is he in to Yamada?
Hey... so...
So what's the story
with you and Yamada?
Should I tell him
I'm dating her...?
There's no way I can
compete with a guy like that!
I'm... well...
I'm kinda...
Uh, we...
I just like her a lot!
Oh man...
Unrequited love...
That sucks.
It's not unrequited...
is it?
The important thing is you're
not 'dating her' or anything...
In that case,
I'm gonna ask her out.
You're cool with that, right?
I don't care how hot he is,
Kosuda is my priority...
He's my little cherry boy!
He's just a spoiled,
rich kid anyway;
like I need that drama...
He probably got deflowered
by one of his trampy maids.
And I'm sure he's
been practicing on
everything that's
looked at him funny.
Gah!
It's not fair!
Why can't I have his
awesome sex filled life?!
Kosuda? What's wrong
with your face?
Nothing...
I was just telling
him that I hoped you
were as into me
as I am into you.
Yeah, well, I'm not.
Did you hear
what she just said?!
I don't understand...
Is this what rejection is like?
I'm sorry, I must not
have made myself clear...
Would you like
to go out with me?
No!
No way...
Are you telling me
no because of Kosuda?
What?
Try making some sense!
It has nothing to
do with Kosuda, okay?
The point is I
can't go out with you.
Why not?
Because, obviously...
You're not rocking your v-card.
That girl just called him out.
And she did it so loud, too.
Yeah, I don't understand
why it's an issue.
You want a
guy who's a virgin...
Or else it's a deal breaker?
That's right.
Is that all she sees in me?
Sorry to disappoint you...
...but I'm actually
still carrying my...
..."v--card."
You've never done
the nasty before?
Why not?!
I'm curious as to why
you're so fixated on sex...
It's not necessarily
something that has to be done.
Don't act so pretentious!
FYI, this lady plans on getting
busy and staying that way!
I probably shouldn't say that...
What about if you're in love?
It should be okay then, right?
I like where
she's going with this.
No, I don't disagree...
It's just...
Believe me, I've had thousands
of women come on to me...
I've just never felt 'that way'
about any of them before.
I've eliminated every
single woman who
had even the slightest
chance of being the one...
I wanted to keep him pure.
The truth of the matter is...
I want my first
time to be special.
So he could have gotten his
freak on a million
times already,
but he chose not to because
he wants it to be "special"?
Can I shoot him, please?
Of course, all that's changed...
...now.
You're the first girl I've
ever asked out, Yamada.
If you wanna know the truth,
you're different from
all those other girls...
You're special.
What's he doing...?
Is he trying to change my mind?
Well, I'm not havin' it!
I don't believe him anyway...
He's popular.
There's no way he hasn't climbed
Mount Pork--o--lay--la yet.
You're no mountain
climber yourself.
A super, wicked
hot cherry boy...?
I didn't even think
such a thing existed.
If that's true, then
he's like perfect for me.
He's gotta be the finest piece
of virgin in the whole world.
Suppose he's telling the truth.
That means he's
the guy I've been
looking for my entire
high school career.
Crap, I think I'm late...
I forgot I'm supposed to
meet up with my sister.
I'm sorry, but I
have to be going now...
I hope you'll reconsider...
I really do.
I just totally blew him off,
and he still wants
me to reconsider
going out with him...?
There is something
not right about that guy.
Although, I guess
he wouldn't really
know how to play
a girl, would he?
I guess that was all kind
of unexpected, wasn't it?
Why am I
smiling like an idiot...?
This qualifies as
the worst date ever!
So he let his
girlfriend get hit on by
someone way
better looking than him?
I can't tell if he's confident
or really pathetic.
He's a virgin...?
--Yamada!
--I can't believe it.
Where do you wanna go next?
I can totally smell hot guy!
Hey!
Hi Yamada...!
What's goin' on?
Misato!
Was there or was there
not a hottie right here...?
Kosuda, where'd you come from?
I've been here this whole time.
Why are you two hanging out?
Are you on a date?
No!
Not at all!
We just ran into
each other, that's all.
So...
I'll get going, now.
See ya later!
All that thinking about
sex for nothing.
Misato...
I'm going to kill you one day.
Maybe we should do it now.
There you are!
I was starting to get worried.
We still have plenty of time to
make it to
the concert, don't we?
Where were you, anyway?
I was having tea with Yamada.
I sorta confessed my love
to her, which was a first.
Oh, thank heavens...
It was just a bad dream.
You've been moaning
for the past three days.
Oh good, Kyoka,
you're finally awake...!
I'm not quite sure why,
but Yamada hasn't
responded to my
confession of love yet.
No!
Miss, please!
Is she okay?
Bonus!
It's time for Dirty Talk with
"Those High School Boys"!
How do you guys
feel about Miss Akai?
I think she's totally hot...
I mean she
teaches PE, but yeah...
Do you think
she's still a virgin?
I do.
No I'm not
comfortable discussing
things of this nature!
Dude, maybe it's
our turn to teach her!
Yeah, I could go for that.
Me too!
She's a TILF!
Totally.
Scene...!
That concludes Dirty Talk!
B Gata H Kei!
You are beyond rude!
Calm down, Judgie...
Don't sit there and
pretend that you didn't
think Hottie McHotterson
wasn't a virgin, either.
It doesn't matter, you can't
just tell someone you won't
go out with them unless they've
bumped uglies before...!
What's Kosuda
supposed to think, now?
That you're only after his
man hymen, which is true?!
Man hymen.
I don't understand...
Is she just after my
untapped resources?
Extraordinarily untapped.
There's no way...
But then again, what about
that first time I met her?
You're still a cherry
boy, am I right?
What does that mean?
Does she have a
weird fetish for virgins?!
All right...
I should clear up
this misunderstanding.
Kosuda...
I'm not just
into virgins; I mean,
yes you happen to
be one... but I...
Wait a minute, that's not
a misunderstanding.
That's why I picked him...!
I was looking for a virgin,
don't you remember?!
Well, yeah, at first that
might have been true,
but things are
kinda different now!
No they're not!
Shut up; you don't know!
I like cherry boys!
Then, Kanejo's brother should
work just fine for you, right?
You know, if you
really wanted to get laid...
you wouldn't be trying
to hunt down a cherry boy.
Seriously...
be honest with yourself.
What do you mean?
I mean, it doesn't matter
to you whether the
guy's penetrated
anything or not anymore...
You only care whether
the guy is Kosuda.
That was strange.
Let me explain...
See, when Yamada
has gone over the
limit to her mental
load capacity...
...her Yamada breaker,
located in the back
of her mind, gets thrown...
Restore!
No way, lady!
I like cherry boys!
OMG, she just went back
to her last save point!
On my way to love?
Don't hit on my Kosuda!
Look!
Kanejo's come back...!
Hey girl!
You've been gone
for a whole week...
Colds are the worst, yeah?
So...
Maybe she's still feeling sick?
Wow...
That's random.
I can't believe my brother
confessed his love to Yamadog.
On top of that,
it happened while she
was out on a date
with Komatsubara...
His name is Kosuda!
Please, you can't blame her...
The shock has given Miss a
few short--term memory issues.
She better get ready
because like I said from
the very beginning, I'm gonna
steal her boyfriend...!
And then...
I'll throw him away
like a piece of trash!
Welcome back, lady...
How are you feeling?
Wait a minute...
Miyano is a childhood
friend of Koitabashi...
Or Kosuda, whatever.
But I don't know...
He seems inappropriate to me.
Hey, Miyano!
So... what kind
of a guy is Kosuda?
What...?
Now even Kanejo
is interested in him?!
I thought I'd be able to
stay by his side forever...
Just being near him
would've made me happy.
But I wasn't paying attention...
And now he's beyond my reach.
Don't give up on me, girl...!
You can do it!
No, it's fine.
Yamada and Kanejo
are wonderful people,
and I'm sure they have Kosuda's
best interests at heart.
Kosuda...?
He's a really cool guy...
and super kind...
...he's a man's man, too.
I think you misunderstood...
I'm asking about Kosuda.
Absolutism in France
was established under
the Bourbon Dynasty
that started with Henry IV.
I wonder what she really wants.
I think I need to get
advice from someone...
But who do I know that would
actually take me seriously.
Miyano?
I brought some food for you...
I wasn't spying or anything.
Thanks, I think.
Hey, um...
Would you maybe help
me out with something?
Relationship advice?
Yeah, but if not...
...that's cool.
No, um, whatever
I can do to help...
When we were kids I talked to
you about that boy
stuff, remember.
I'm sorry...
I know we don't talk
as much as we should,
what with being friends
for such a long time.
Stabbed!
Yeah...
no big deal.
Oh...
...so you and Yamada have
gone out several times, then.
Yeah.
But... the two of
you don't get along
at school like at all.
Stabbed!
You think so, too...?
I'm afraid she's
just being mean to me.
No. I don't think Yamada
could be mean to anyone...
She's such a sweet person.
You think she's sweet?!
I know how much you
care about her, Kosuda.
Everyone does...
You told her how you felt in
front of the whole class...
And...
I thought it was real cute.
Thanks...
I'm glad I did it.
I'm sure eventually Yamada
will tell you how she feels...
How could she not?
Thanks, Miyano...
I'm starting to feel
better already.
You're an awesome girl,
you know that?
Is it cool if I ask your
advice again sometime?
What happened?!
Why are you
supporting the love life
of someone you should be lovin'?
It's okay.
You know,
they say the best couples
are the ones who
started off as friends!
Stop it!
Go away devil whispers!
The next day!
Kosuda, you belong to the
photography club, right...?
What kind of
pictures do you take?
Yeah, that's right!
I wonder what this is about.
Normally, she barely
says hi to me.
It doesn't even matter
that I don't know you...
if I just keep talking to you
and looking at you like this,
you won't be able
to contain yourself...
I can taste Yamada's
bitterness already.
How does she make
her face sparkle like that?!
What's skankosaurus doing now?
She better not
be hitting on Kosuda!
You thieving little harpy!
Oh...
Yeah I didn't realize there were
so many ways to
take pictures of scenery.
This crap is taking forever.
Why hasn't he
fallen for me yet...?
This is my
best stare, he should be
a puddle of love goo by now!
Looks like you and Yamada
are after the same thing.
Oh no!
What if Yamada used
her body on him already!
I can't compete
with a devil of the flesh!
Don't say that...!
It's not very ladylike!
Not very ladylike,
but very true.
Man...!
What the heck
are they talking about...
Fine...
I'm all over this.
It's time for a Yamada Style
Secret Technique called...
Yamada knows how
to read lips, fool!
My brother enjoys
photography, too...
You should come over sometime...
We could talk about
pictures and hang.
You should come over sometime...
We could talk about...
We... could... take... some...
...hot... pictures... and...
...bang.
What the hell?!
You're not reading
her lips right!
Come on, there's no way she
would say anything like that.
She's not you, okay...?
It's all just your
wild imagination.
It is so not my
wild imagination...!
It was my lip reading technique,
and that's never
wrong, thank you!
Trust me you're only
saying that because
you don't know
deceptiskank's true colors!
You're right, Yamada.
She's finally lost her
will to argue back.
It was nice of Kanejo
to invite me over,
but I can't realistically go
to another girl's house
without saying anything
about it to Yamada.
Mister Kosuda!
Welcome, sir...
Please get in.
Let's go!
I promise I won't bite!
Please sir!
Get in!
How in the heck am I
supposed to say no to that.
Isn't that Kanejo's
annoying limo?
Isn't that Kosuda inside...?!
I can't believe it.
She kidnapped him.
Seriously?!
Welcome home, Miss Kanejo!
I'm sorry...
I didn't realize my
brother wasn't home.
Whoa!
She's wearing a dress...
and looks amazing and proper...
She's like the
perfect good girl.
So, it seems you and Yamada
have gotten pretty close...
That's great, but are you
interested in any other girls?
For example...
What about...
...me?
About you...?
What do you mean?
What's she doing?
I'm so confused.
What on Earth is going on?!
Wait...
I'm gonna be okay, right...?
He's not gonna attack me out of
the blue or anything, is he?
Yes!
I shall have you now!
No!
I can't go any
further with him than this!
You realize that attitude
is how Yamada will win?
Oh, right...
I'm not really sure what
I should do at this point.
You seduce him,
that's what, you ninny!
Seduce him?
I've never seduced anyone
before, so I don't know how...
Oh wait!
I could expose myself!
Here goes nothing...
Expose!
Kanejo...
What are you~
It's working, he's almost mine!
This is it!
It's a matter of time before
Kosuda becomes that love goo!
Afternoon, Miss...
I brought you some tea.
You've got it wrong,
Ms. Ichihara...
You don't understand...
I was trying to seduce him...!
Y'know what...
...he's extraordinarily
resistant to my feminine charms.
Can I ask you something?
Yes, Miss.
You wouldn't, by chance
know of any secret way I
could make him fall for
me instantly, would you?
Holy...
My brain won't stop hurting.
Kosuda...
Yamada!
The words that crossed Kosuda's
mind at that
particular moment...
They were neither,
"Why is she here?"
nor "It's not what
it looks like,
I swear to all things holy!"
Instead, Kosuda was
far more concerned
with the following words,
"She's going to kill me!"
I never dreamed Ms. Ichihara
would be so experienced
and know that many
ways to capture a man!
She's the epitome
of good service!
Using one of her techniques,
Kosuda will fall in no time!
I'm back!
I don't understand
why you went to
Kanejo's house
in the first place.
What's your deal?
I thought you liked me?!
I do; I'm sorry.
So...
what did she say?
She asked if I was
interested in any other girls...
...besides you, I mean.
I don't have time for
you to flake out on me, now!
I've worked really hard,
and I'm almost there!
You're almost there...?
Almost where?
Nowhere!
Yeah...
Okay.
I'm almost ready
to admit I like you...
You got a problem with that?
Nope...
We're good.
To be continued!
♪ closing song ♪
Christmas Eve take 2!
I'm ready, I've got protection,
and I'm so gonna
score this time!
Skanky's eyes
in that picture are
freaking me out,
but it could just be her face.
Naked, naked, naked Yamada!
We've finally reached the final,
climactic episodes!
Please don't let us get stopped
before we get started again!
Naked, naked,
naked, Naaakeeeeed!
See you next time!