Looks like the
Christmas party is going
to be quite
a success this year...
What do you think brother?
Sure.
Oh by the way...?
Yeah?
Make sure you don't
forget to invite Yamada.
That reminds me...
Ichihara said you had
Kosuda over the other day,
you should invite him, too...
This could be your chance!
But if not...
at least you have a new friend?!
Yeah...
that's a great idea.
How does he not know...?
I would think it's
painfully obvious by now.
Poor thing.
Oh, I'll invite both of those
disgusting love maggots.
Then Keiichi can watch them
paw at each other all night.
Hopefully that'll be enough
to make him realize
he has absolutely no
chance with that twat!
Year 2 Class H's Christmas Eve.
Take me to bed.
What's up guys?!
No way?!
Seriously?
Omigod thank you so much!
Here ya go.
Great!
Score!
I get to go!
Hey what's that?
It's called an
invitation and it's to
Kanejo's uber
fabulous Christmas party!
Oh great...
Joy to the world.
Can you imagine all
the hot, single rich guys
that are gonna be
there--including her brother?
Awesome.
And their house has so many
private rooms we can sneak into!
Wait...!
What do you mean?!
Rich hotties I can climb, duh...
I'm not sharing with anyone!
Okay...
how does it work exactly?
Yamada!
I just can't...
Just relax and trust me.
Sold...!
Tell me everything!
Like how does it work?!
Look for the butler
and give him the sign!
Got it...!
Wow, you know a
lot about this stuff!
I knew reading all
those trashy sex
mags would come
in handy one day!
Here's the deal...
...the party will
be on Christmas eve...
Make sure you tell
everyone you know!
We want it to be fabulous!
'Kay!
What if no one tells
Yamada because they know
she and I aren't
exactly bed buddies?
How do I make sure she comes...?
I could always
take her there by force.
Or maybe kidnap Kosuda
and hold him for ransom.
Invite me to your stupid party!
Okay!
Did she just come over here and
demand that I invite
her to my party...?
What a freak.
Kosuda, darling...
You are coming, right?
Coming where?!
What?
It's going to be so much fun...
and if you don't
go I'll kill you.
Kill...?
As in 'death'?
Um...
Just say yes!
No frickin' way!
She wants to go?!
This means my first
time getting laid will be
on Christmas Eve
in a rich skank's house!
Oh holy night!
Oh hell yeah!
Miss Kanejo...
Someone told me
you'll be serving alcohol ?
Of course.
But it's for my parents
and their friends...
I certainly don't support under
age drinking in my house.
Will there be students
from other schools?
Yes, and lots of them
are bringing their wealthy
parents who are presidents of
their own companies and stuff.
I guess I'll have to
be a chaperone then.
I mean, I do have
a responsibility here.
Right.
Wow... Your sacrifice
is truly inspiring.
She hates her.
Why would she want to
be anywhere with Kanejo?
I guess because
she likes her brother
and doesn't want to admit it.
Oh, I like totally forgot
she even had a brother...!
I just really wanted to be
around friends for the holidays!
OMG I don't think
he's cute at all!
I didn't even notice his
six-pack abs and porn star hair!
I knew you were depressed but
I didn't know you were a schizo.
What?! No!
I was just trying
to cheer myself up!
Sometimes doing girl
voices makes me laugh!
Now it's Christmas.
Time sure flies.
That means...
...holiday...
...banging!
Hello ...!
Merry Christmas!
Welcome to the annual fabulous
Kanejo Christmas party...!
So she lives there?
It's just like a castle!
I think it is a castle!
That is wicked sweet.
You've gotta be kidding...
That electric bill must be
a beating every year.
Oh no question.
I bet they could
pay my entire salary
with what it costs to
light those things.
Why are there like eight
different buildings here?
There's just one annex...
And that's our doghouse.
My dog needs a
house we're moving in!
You're so lying.
That's what
rich people look like...
They're beautiful...
...look how they hold their
glasses with only four fingers!
How are we supposed
to talk to them?
They'll probably beat us
up for not having cufflinks.
Hi there...!
I'm Kobayashi!
She's talking to them!
She's armed and ready!
She's the man!
I love Tokyo in June.
How 'bout you?
That's great.
If you'll excuse me...
My math teacher just walked in.
I don't want to be rude.
You understand?
Shoot me.
Kobayashi needs
a hug like bad...
I guess rich people
don't want to talk to us.
Nope that's not it Look!
They're totally talking
to Yamada!
Guess why.
You look lovely tonight...
Can I get you a glass of wine?
So you can get me drunk and
drag me off to some closet?
Please.
I don't have time for this.
I gotta go Get My Freak On!
Having a good time...?
It's really a shame that someone
like you is here alone tonight.
Oh no...
It's totally cool.
What!
Why does she get
to talk to them...?!
--Hey~!
--It's her rack.
She has a boyfriend,
stupid head!
--Bad idea.
--Talk to me!
I'm single and gorgeous,
not to mention a
freak in the sheets...
...well, I would be
if given a chance!
Miyano...
Whatcha staring at?
I can't get over how hot
Kosuda looks tonight...
...wow.
There are like, five hundred
hot, rich guys floating
around here and she's still
lusting after Boris McBoring?
Hey, what's that look for?
Man... she looks
so beautiful tonight.
I'm so getting
laid on Christmas!
A butler!
Hell yeah...!
Just give him the secret
wink then it's time to bone!
Is she hitting on
that guy in front of me?
I think it's about time
to make things a little
more romantic in
here for those two.
Keiichi should be coming
out any second now.
What's going on?
Is there a storm or something?
Is that Santa?
Dude!
No way!
Merry~!
Christmas~...!
And welcome...!
Good to see you!
That's totally Keiichi!
My darling, wonderful slice
of man meat I've missed you!
That was an amazing entrance.
There she is.
Please no.
Beautiful Yamada,
I must say no holida--
Darling...!
I've missed your sexy eyebrows!
Get him, Misato!
I forgot to put on
a bra this evening.
Because you don't need one?
Yamada, wait!
Kanejo!
Take us to the secret room...!
Yeah I know everything!
The room?
No way...
She has to be lying...
No one knows about my
secret vaulted sexy
brother tribute room!
Found you!
What's this room?
There is no room.
He doesn't know about the
private sex room
at his own party?
You should check it out.
It'll blow at least your mind!
Me specifically?
Why?
Don't listen to her!
She's drunk!
Shouldn't you be
doing it right now?
Right...
Let's go!
Okay.
Where are you going?!
Why did I send them away?!
Now Keiichi won't get to
see how disgustingly in love
with each other they are...
This was so not the plan.
This looks like a library.
Yeah it does...
Are you looking for something?
Uh...
Somewhere we could be alone.
I like that idea.
I was looking
for the same thing.
I've wanted to do
this for a long time.
Wait!
No don't!
I'm sorry...!
I don't want to do it
in there it looks like school!
There's gotta be a better room
to do it somewhere
in this house.
I just believe that
children are our future...
Teach them well and
let them lead the way;
show them the
beauty they possess.
Not only gorgeous but
a sense of family too.
Huh...?
The only family she
has is a cat and a DVR.
What do you think of
those two over there?
Too uptight.
They'll never put out.
I like the short squatty one.
I can't tell if this
is hilarious or sad.
Don't you just love opera?
I do.
Uh...
yeah.
Oh man, he's gonna
try to talk art...?
She's so going down...
What's this?
Someone like you
is usually never alone...
...but I can see
pain in your eyes.
Wow he's good.
Well played, Therapist Boy.
I can't find Yamada...
She probably went
home with someone.
Yamada's a sneaky little
troll but there's no way
she'd be able to find out
about the tribute room.
All right.
Where'd they go?
I need every camera activated.
I'm sure having a
portrait of me in every
room just looks like
I'm the favorite child...
...and that's true...
...but they'll never suspect
that my eyes are on
them no matter
where they run off to...
...especially in my
Keiichi Tribute room.
I don't even want to think
about what goes on in there.
Where are they?
Uh, I'm lost I need help!
Whoa?!
Holy moly!
I thought beds with curtains
were only in picture books!
Curtains...
I bet those are so you can
shut out the other couples
that come in while
you're getting it on...
...that means we found it!
This is the special
sexy time room!
Um...
I'm thinking this might
be somebody's bedroom.
No it's not...
I mean look how
frickin huge this thing is...!
It's a party room!
You think so?
Of course not.
But who cares!
I'm all about some
sweet sweet sexy time!
You're not gonna
need that entire box.
Alright...!
It's time for
some "Christmas Sex"!
Hi...
What's going on?
Everything...
Now close your eyes.
Everything?!
Like everything--everything?!
Meaning every thing...?!
Holy crap!
Ohmigod ohmigod he's on the
bed and I'm on him on the bed!
Don't freak out!
Calm the eff down
and just get naked!
Okay maybe not.
I read somewhere
that it's better
to take our clothes off slowly.
I can't move!
He's not moving...
I can do anything
I want to him right now!
I still can't find them ...
They must be wandering
around outside or something...
The only other place
I haven't checked is my
room but that
would be impossible.
What the hell are they doing on
my bed and why--that's gross?!!
Clothes off.
That's the first step...
But where do I start?
What makes the most sense?!
Wait...!
Yamada!
Aw yeah...!
We have lift off!
Right after this short break.
That's my line!
B GATA H KEI!
The day has arrived people...!
She's finally gonna
feed the trouser snake...!
The finish line is within reach!
Go Yamada!
Kanejo is watching?!
A live broadcast
that pushes the limits!
I can't believe they're
actually touching my bed
with their filthy parts
and skin cells!
This is not okay!
I've got to get
them out of there!
My zipper is down.
Yamada undid my zipper.
That means it's out.
He's out...!
If she's already gone this far,
I can't leave her hanging.
We're gonna do this.
I've never seen
that look on his face.
Kinda scary...
but sexy too.
Ohmigod it's happening.
Okay just calm down,
we can do this.
We're just kissing.
I've kissed with tongue
before so I'm totes pro at this.
It feels different though.
Holy crap I'm nervous.
Why am I freaking out?!
This isn't too weird is it...?
What the crap am I doing?
I don't want to
watch her get laid in
my room by the
most boring guy ever.
And yet you're
still sitting there.
Whatever you're doing
with your tongue is weird...
You should nibble
my lip a little bit...
...and grab my hair
like in the movies.
Don't you research
this stuff online?
I'm sure there's
an app for that.
No I didn't!
I totally just moaned!
I'm so embarrassed and
so frikkin turned on!
Gotcha!
Zoom damn it!
Zoom in!
Whoa I think that
painting just moved.
And what's with the eyes?
Something's weird.
Mother grabber!
It's okay...
I can at least show
that first part to Keiichi.
He'll get the point!
Crap, I can't do that.
If I do I'll have to tell him
I've installed
cameras everywhere.
I can't handle this.
This makes my hair hurt!
I'm totally calm now...
They're making this very
difficult and leave me no choice
but to bring Keiichi
to my room and
show him exactly
what's going on there...
I'm so glad.
I can't find a zipper.
How do I get her clothes off.
This awkward what do I do?
Where are you...?
You're missing everything.
I'm running out of time.
I need to make sure we
get there before it's done.
Knowing them it's not
going to last very long.
I guess if I don't find him
soon I'll have to go by myself!
Somehow I don't think
that will bother you much.
I know.
But I'm afraid
to watch by myself.
I don't know how I'll react.
I'd much rather have
my brother there with me.
Why are Yamada and
Kosuda randomly MIA?
I can't find them anywhere.
Now that I think about it,
Miyano hasn't
come back from
the bathroom either.
There's no cameras!
I mean, hey Takeshita.
Kanejo, what's up?
Do you think you could
come with me for a sec?
Huh?
I think so.
Wait, why?
Where are we going and why
does your face look all red?
Ohmigod, just come with me.
Tell me where we're going first!
At least this way,
they can't accuse me of lying.
Hi hi hi hi hi sexy boy!
I think we should get married!
What do you think?!
Sure.
Don't you think I should
meet your parents soon?
Sure.
Let's register and get
a license this week!
Sure.
Yay~!
I'm marrying a sexy sexy sexy
hot hot hot rich
rich rich rich rich rich
I just wish I knew whether
or not she was still here.
If she left who unwraps that
gorgeous Christmas gift?
She didn't leave and
she's giving her gift to
some other dude
on your sister's bed.
Holy crap it's off...!
Now for the bra.
Oh great...
how does this work...
...maybe like...
...no...
...there we go!
Turn around.
I want him to see my perfect
flawless bod and
be utterly turned on.
I believe in you!
Her breasts are right there.
And they're real!
They're real!
Totes real!
You got 'em!
I got 'em!
Hurry...!
I'm still wearing
heels over here!
We've gotta hurry or we
won't be able to see it live!
See what?
Boobs!
I'm touching boobs!
Real ones!
Not just my own shoulders when I
pretend I'm grabbing
real ones...!
They feel a little different
from when I first
grabbed them through
her clothes at the park...
...and what are those
things poking my palms?
I changed my mind!
I'm just not ready.
Almost there...
come on...
Who are you talking to?
Should I call
someone about this?
They're not as big
as I thought they'd be...
...but they're so soft...
...like my baby blanket...!
I can't take it!
Lose the crying.
He's touching me!
Why can't I control that?
He must think I'm crazy
or in pain or something.
I have to hold back.
But I can't for some reason...
I just...
I just can't.
I know you're in here!
Um...
Come out now...!
If not...
I'll, open the curtains...
...and I'll drag you out!
I'm not even kidding...!
Watch!
I'll give you till
the count of three...
...and one~!
There's no one in here.
There's not?
Are you sure?
Check it out for yourself.
Oh man that was a close one!
Was that Kanejo?!
What the heck was
she doing in here?!
This is the sex room!
Was she trying to get
all lezzie and watch...?!
And P.S...
Is that thing supposed to
shrink up in times of stress?
It's like a turtle.
Okay, awkward.
What room is this?
This is my bedroom.
And why did you bring me here?
We almost did
it on Kanejo's bed?!
Oh gross I wonder what kind
of things she's done in there?!
We were about to
have sex in her room.
On her bed.
Is that what Yamada wanted?!
Holy frogs, that hurts...
It's like someone put a giant
binder clip down there!
I guess we could finish here.
But it's so dark he might
go in the wrong way.
Hey, maybe that would
make me more advanced!
Like skipping a level?!
They're ruining everything.
I just wanted to film
it and watch it live.
That's not too much to ask!
Where are they?!
What is she doing?!
She's so weird...
I guess not as
weird as that one...
I'm sure I can
guess where she is.
I want sex!
The walk--in closet...
It's the perfect place to hide.
Especially in a panic.
This is perfect.
I mean, it's all going to
lead to this eventually.
I should just
kill them now while
they're both trapped
in the same place...
Once she's gone,
Keiichi won't be
tempted to cheat on me anymore.
It's show time!
What's wrong with you?
I am actually not feeling well,
thank you for asking...
I should probably stay
and lie down for awhile...
Please just go back to
the party and enjoy yourself.
Don't worry about me.
Yeah...
Uh, okay...
So this has nothing to do
with trying to find Yamada?
No, of course not.
No!
She found us!
We're gonna die in here!
Meow~
What an idiot!
It's a cat.
Weird...
Well, go on back to the party.
I'll see you in a bit.
It came from inside the closet!
I know it's strange...
...but we've always kept the
cats in closets at our house.
But that wasn't a cat!
Didn't you hear it meow, silly?
Uh, that was Yamada!
Get out of here!
Finally...
There's no one
here to interrupt us.
There are so many options now.
I can chop them up
and feed them to the dog...
Or maybe the fish in the ocean
might enjoy a nice snack.
Someone's entering the
Temple of Brotherly Love!
Hey Kanejo!
Uh...
Hi Miyano, what were you doing
in that room all by yourself?
I'm so sorry.
This house is so big and I
have no sense of direction...
I just wandered around
until I ended up here.
How is it possible to just
'end up' in that room?!
When you're a klutz that
kind of stuff just happens.
Oh my gosh she had to have
seen everything in there!
Kanejo wake up...
Speak to us!
Emergency...!
Someone help~!
I don't know
what just happened...
...but I'm pretty sure
Miyano saved our lives.
Let's run while we can!
Not again...!
They were so close!
Someone hold me!
I have to say this
comes as a shock.
Yeah, I know.
I never knew my own sister
would feel this way about me.
I'm so sorry...
I just...
I love you too...
sweet sister.
My dear brother...
you've made me so happy.
Kanejo...? Are you awake...?!
Can you hear me?
Why are you here?!
Oh thank goodness...
You passed out so quickly
I didn't know what happened.
By the way...
...that room I got
locked in was amazing.
Where'd you get all those
photos and figures of Keiichi?
I want one just like it!
But I'd want to fill it with
pictures and statues of Kosuda!
Looks like you've found yourself
an unexpected ally, huh?
I'm getting
all feverish again...
...and like my heart is about
to pound out of my chest.
Wait a minute, could I
be getting more turned on
because I have to
wait to have sex again?
Maybe this is going
to help me have the
most exciting
first experience ever!
How 'bout...
...no.
Maybe I was trying to rush this
whole sex thing too much.
Being friends is cool.
Maybe waiting's not so bad.
Let's go!
We have ten minutes
to finish what we started!
Ow.
Stop trying to pressure me!
I wanna wait...
'Kay?
She's right...
I've been so
wrapped up in it all I
didn't know she
was feeling pressured.
So um...
...how 'bout tomorrow?
It'll be Christmas!
Doing it the next
day counts as waiting?
You freaking bet it does!
Sure...
I'll see you tomorrow then.
As weird as this is,
I'm happy for her.
It's a message from Daisuke...!
Peace!
That girl is always so
obnoxiously happy.
Well...
...guess we'll try
again tomorrow, Yamada...
Don't screw it up.
Same to you, Kosuda.
In case you're wondering...
Nothing much
changes for these guys.
At least it didn't get worse!
Not for all of us.
I can't believe you did this!
I totally did!
He was too busy
being dreamy to sign our
marriage license
so I signed it for him!
You can't just
forge someone else's
signature on
documents like this!
It's a serious offense...!
You could go to jail!
The end.
♪ closing song ♪
Kosuda, it's been a year and
nine months since I met you.
Time flies when
you're having so much fun.
I feel like we only
met a few months ago.
Yeah, I wanted to tell you...
We don't have
time to get all mushy!
There's only one
episode left and there
are three segments
instead of two!
We're so getting
overtime for this!
Anyway, that means
it's time to say goodbye!
See you next time!
For the last time.