They've been on my bed...
What happened in here?
Ohhhhh, Kosuda!
Yamada!
Oh, gross.
Maybe it was just a...
...you show me yours,
I'll show you mine thing.
Hey, sis!
So, I hope
you're feeling better.
I am; thank you!
I had a good
time at the party...
...but I didn't get to
hang out with Yamada...
Darn...
It's gonna be hard to ask her to
marry me if she
won't talk to me...
She'll come around though.
Please let this go...
There's no point in falling
in love with someone
you'll never get
the chance to be with.
How many times have
I said that to her?
The world revolves for us.
Goodbye...
B Gata H Kei.
I'm home!
The program you're
watching was brought
to you by the global
Ogre Brand Group...
Hold the phone!
Aha!
Well, you're not there yet,
but it's a matter of time.
My helpless and adorable sheep
of a little brother is changing!
I can faintly detect the
scent of a full-fledged man!
Please...
stop!
Don't say that.
Please...
stop!!
You need to
calm down, like stat.
Remember who's been
the one been telling you
everything you need to know
to win over Yamada...?
I got your back, okay?
What do you need me to do?
I need to find out
how to stop screwing
up having sex,
and I need details!
Not that I don't
appreciate it, but is that
really something you
should be asking me?
Chika...
I need your help!
Please, help...!
It's life and death!
It'll affect my
life until I die!
This is weird.
I'm like surrounded by gifts,
and she didn't even notice...
She must be
freaking out for real.
I need to know how
to stop screwing up
having sex with Kosuda... and
I need to know some details!
Are you serious...?
I mean I'm flattered,
but why are you asking me?
Please, I'm begging you!
I'll owe you big time...!
When I start getting
busy with all those guys,
I'll throw one your way!
She sounds so desperate...
I guess this
isn't easy for her...
Which is...
well, that's pretty ironic.
I wish I could tell
you but I just don't know.
I think I should be
direct with him and say,
"let's shag, baby."
I'm gonna message
him to meet me,
and then we're gonna do it.
Yes!
I got a message from Yamada!
What...?
Six AM?
That's only four hours away.
I want to pick up where we left
off yesterday like yesterday!
The early bird blah blah worm!.
Strike while the iron
is hot and horny, girl!
Yamada!
Hey...
Uh... hey.
Don't be afraid, Yamada!.
Tell him you're ready
for some grinding!
I don't get why I'm so
freakin' embarrassed.
I have to say this now,
or we'll end up on a
normal no sex date,
which will just piss me off!
That does sound a
little familiar, does it not?
Maybe I should try
to be subtle about it.
I would like to...
I wanna ride!
Uh...
Ride what?
Ride, uh...
Something that's small and hard!
You mean a carousel?
Damn it!
Why can't I just say it?!
God, I'm such a girl!
Yamada?
Hey, it's kinda cold here,
so why don't we
walk for a little bit?
I can do this!
I want to have sex!
I can't believe it...!
I said it!
Yamada?.
I... Did I hear
her right?
Anyway, there's this TV show
I've been wanting to watch.
No...!Please wait!
It's called the Broken
Telephone or something...
If you receive their message,
you're supposed
to tell it to ten
of your friends.
How can she act like
she didn't say anything?
Um...
I do, too...! I want
to have sex with you!
Well, I feel better,
how about you?
Yeah...
Maybe next time we can try
for more than five minutes.
Long as there's a next time.
Long as you behave
yourself, there will be.
Gah, this is so awkward!
Wow, this is so awkward.
I know I'm just freaking
out a little, but we're only
three blocks away
from our station.
What if we see someone we know?
It's Miss Akai?!
Well, that was strange...
who'd've thunk?
What kind of a freak jogs this
early on Christmas morning?
At least we're inside!
That's true; I guess
we owe her one now.
I can't believe it!
We're finally here!
Okay, going around
and checking everything out
would be such an amateur move...
A pro would simply
get ready for business...
Okay, I should probably
turn off my phone.
Who am I kidding?
I am an amateur!
That's a big tub!
Do I need to shower again...?
Where do I start?!
I just want to get diddled,
is that too much to ask for?
Maybe you should
start with Kosuda...
Huh...?
The guy?!
I wonder how he's doing...?
I taught him what
I could in detail, but...
If he doesn't report back to me
with good news,
I'm gonna kill him!
I'm not sure if I want things
to go well for her tonight.
If they do what'll entertain me?
Oh, man; this is intense!
Oh, man.
Oh! Yes!
You're making me so hot, baby!
They're not wasting
any time, are they?
I don't think I've ever
felt more awkward
than I do right now.
I'm a genius.
He's gotta be loving this!
Kosuda's a guy,
and they're visual, right?
He's gotta be thinking
about boning now...
I should get an
award for sex planning!
Oh...!
Don't stop!
We're just
gettin' started, baby!
Hey, I know that move!
That's the same position
we were in yesterday.
Oh, yeah!
Tell me again how
much you want it!
I want it.
From here it doesn't look
as awkward as it felt...
I wonder if, maybe,
he'd mind doing it again.
Oh, don't stop.
I started this video
to turn him on,
but I think it's
working better on me...
My body is freaking
me out right now!
Why is she moving
around like that...?!
She's freaking me out right now.
I think Yamada turns me on more
than a dirty movie ever could...
She's way sexier
than those two...
How'd they get in that position?
I think I'm gonna explode...
I can't take it anymore!
Yamada!
What am I supposed to do now?
Take her clothes off?
Should I start making
out with her first...?
I need to focus.
Remember what Kazuki said.
Once you're in the
room start with talking...
You don't want to look
like all your after is sex.
Because, even if that's true,
you don't want to act
like a douchebag!
Damn it!
I've already screwed up!
Now...
I can't believe
I'm saying this but...
...while you're kissing her...
...you should gently lay her
down on top of the bed...
And...
...make sure that you're
kissing her nice and slow...
Don't be rude, either...
She's more than just
boobs and a nice butt...
Then...
...mix it up and do things
like stroke her hair!
And bite her
lightly on the ear...!
Those kinds of things'll
probably get her in the mood!
What are you looking at?!
If you don't stop pissing
me off, your body is
going to be too
damaged for any action!
Kiss her nice and slow...
What's wrong?
What did I tell you...?
You're acting like a douche!
Ugh, what's
taking him so long...
It's just a freakin' bra.
No...
Hold on let me do it.
Those are her breasts...
I know I've touched them,
but I've never actually
seen them before.
Ever since I saw her
that day in her bra...
I've wondered
what they looked like...
They're beautiful...!
They're better than
I could have imagined!
She's the most
gorgeous person I know...
And she's here with me.
This is so embarrassing!
Wow...
he's really close...
Too close...
They're so soft and warm,
and they smell so good!.
I wanna stay here forever.
He must really like this...
I'm sure eventually
I'll like it, too.
Oh, I don't think I
wanna do this anymore...
I can't tell him now, though!
Yamada...
What's he doing?
What am I doing?.
I'm totally not
ready for this yet!
Why is he so stupid?!
How can he not know
what I'm thinking?!
I dreamed about what
she'd look like before,
but I never thought
she'd be this perfect.
This is so not fair, Kosuda...!
You should have
to get all naked too!
This is awesome...
I can't believe
I'm here right now...
I'm about to
make love to Yamada,
and I think it might
actually happen this time!.
Oh, God, please make
me a natural at this!
I'm sorry; did I hurt you?
How could he hurt me
he hasn't done anything yet!
This is the worst!
'Kay, I think that I'm ready...
You ready?
Totally ready...
Let's do this thing!
Where is it?
Down a little, angle up a touch.
Is that right?
What?
What happened...?
Kosuda?!
Kosuda!!
B Gata H Kei!
You have a fracture
on your left ankle...
And, since you hit
your head so hard,
I want to run a few tests...
We'll need you to stay in
the hospital for three days.
What?!
I'll be back later.
Are you kidding me?
This is torture!
It's like the universe is trying
to punish me for nothing!
Come on everybody wants some!
Yeah...
hands off, Universe!
I'm so sorry, Kosuda.
Huh?
Why?
You didn't do anything.
This isn't your fault.
I hear someone
broke his little ankle.
Hi, Kazuki...
Hey, Yamada!
I haven't seen you in a while!
So...
Was it before...
or after?
Before.
Just tell mom and dad you fell
skating or something like that.
They'll never know.
Okay...
I want to do something nice for
him, but I'm not sure what...
I could make him some food...
But I can't cook.
I feel like such a jerk.
You know, my favorite
part about being
stuck at the hospital
is the nurses, I mean...
...they're great!
True...
Who doesn't want to be helped
out by an angel in white?
An angel in white?!
That's perfect!
Yamada turns into an angel.
Farewell...
B Gata H Kei!
Dude, why can't all
nurses look like that?
Agreed.
But what's with the hat?
This is brilliant!
I'm a nurse!
All men fantasize about nurses!
I'll be ready and waiting
with a tissue for Kosuda,
in case he gets a nosebleed!
I brought you some of my
"get well soon" food.
Cool, thank you...
You're so sweet.
Freakin' Miyano?!
So, Kosuda,
is this your girlfriend?
No! No, I'm not, no!
Really?
That's surprising.
You two would
be so cute together.
Thanks...
but um...
...we're just friends.
Tell your mom
and dad I said hello.
I will...
You try to get some rest, okay?
Yamada?!
Why is she dressed
up like a nurse?
He's on crutches, but he just
had to walk her to the door?
I guess I can't get mad;
it is my fault he's here.
Are you wearing that for me?
Please say that you are.
What?
Someone's got an ego;
I'm wearing this because
I wanted to,
is that all right with you?
I'll never understand her,
but I'm getting used to it.
You look really cute...
Will you take care of me?
Kosuda?
It's time for your medication.
A real nurse is here!!
I'm gonna go ahead and
give you a painkiller now...
You can take it whenever the
pain starts getting really bad.
Cool... thanks!
I'm finally this close to it!.
I should be excited...
but all I feel is awkward...
...again!
I don't know how everything
ended up like this...
...but I'm pretty
sure I like it...
Your girlfriend who was here
earlier is super shy, isn't she?
Yeah...
...but she really
isn't my girlfriend.
Oh, well, then, does that
mean you're single...?
Because to be honest,
you are like totally my type.
Morning!
I'm into nerds--what can I say?
What...?
You are?!
This is so not good.
A rather homely,
real nurse flirts
with you,
and you're ready to go?
There's no reason to
get that excited!
Foul on the play!
Wow, are you okay?.
You must be in a lot of pain...
You should take that medication
I gave you immediately.
Oh, your little nurse left!
Do you miss her already...?
Say something you
cheating piece of idiot!
He can't...
Yeah...
She doesn't know
what she did to him.
Excited...
Yamada I got excited...
because of you...
I got excited because of you.
You got excited cause of me...?
Oh, sorry; my whoopsie.
Your face was
just so close to it!
I'm sorry;
I couldn't help myself!
Ohmigod, What have I done??!!
I'm so sorry.
And...
I'm back!
Ow!
It hurts so bad!
Is there something
wrong with it?
I hope I didn't make
it hurt that time...
More importantly,
I almost touched it...!
I've never done that!
At the hotel, I barely
even saw the thing...
I really wanna touch it now.
Um, Yamada...
Don't take this the wrong way,
but could you please go home?
Does it hurt?
Would you like me to
have a closer look at it?
I'm a sexy nurse so I can find
out where the
pain's coming from.
Nothing's coming!
This is a medical
treatment, silly...
There's no reason to be so shy.
Hello, Doctor.
Three...
Two...
One...
Alive and kicking!
I love teenage boys!
That thing really is excited.
It's pushing
the stethoscope back!
Oh, crap!
What do I do next!
Damn you spontaneity!
Tell me what to do, Takeshita!
No!
What's that about, Takeshita?
Yeah, sorry.
I had this feeling
Yamada was asking me
another one of her
super crazy questions.
Uh, Yamada...
Will you please stop...
To be honest...
You're kinda hurting me.
Well... you wanna
do it to me, then?
This is kinda like
playing doctor.
Well, it's exactly
like playing doctor...!
And on top of that,
we're in a hospital...!
What if someone comes in?
Why do I even care?!
Do I wanna do it to you...?
Yes, please!
This is almost more intimate
that actually touching her...
Wow, I can hear how
fast her heart is beating...
Maybe that's just me?
I don't understand
why every time we start
getting a little dirty,
I get so embarrassed...
I wish I could get over
this weirdness already!
Doctor, would you mind
checking a little farther down?
Down there?
Yes!
Down there?!
Down there!!
Kosuda, are you hungry at all?
It's time for dinner!
Great.
Man!
I hate that lady!
What up, bro...?!
Hey!
Look who came to see
my little brother again!
Rumor has it you're coming
home before New Year's,
but you won't be able
to make it to the shrine visit.
What shrine visit?
We have a family
tradition that every year
we all go visit the
New Year's shrine...
Unfortunately
I can't go like this.
Then I guess you'll be home
alone on New Year's Eve.
Bummer.
That's so sad.
He's gonna be all by himself...
Happy New Year!
Last chance of the year...
Get on it, girl,
and make it count!
This is just great...
I'm finally out of the hospital
in time to be by myself.
Hey guys!
How's it hangin', Kosuda?!
We decided to check up on you!
Yeah, we heard you like
fell while you were skating.
Which is like,
so like you, too...
You've always been a klutz.
No need to be rude!
Yamada's here!
We're actually on
our way to see the shrine.
Wish you could go, man.
But we wanted to stop by and
wish you a Happy New Year first.
Yeah, I was hoping you'd
be able to come with us...
Why would you?
Obviously he can't come with us!
Do any of you guys
want some hot tea?
Walking around for a little
bit isn't really the problem...
I just can't risk a
crowd with this cast.
I've never had a cast...
I've never even been
this close to one either.
Can I draw something on it!
It looks like Miss Akai!
Well, we should go.
Yeah, check you later, man!
Happy New Year, bro!
Happy New Year!
Yeah, see ya next year!
Hold on...
Where's Yamada;
she was just with them.
Hey guys, where's Yamada?
She's, like, disappeared.
Oh she decided
to go back home...
She said something
about not feeling well.
What...?
We only came
with you guys because
Yamada was supposed to be here.
So you have a problem
with it just being us?
No, that's so not
what he was saying!
Yeah, I'm pretty
sure that's exactly...
Good luck, Yamada!
Ah--h, Bee--ee
Gata H--chee Kei...!
Yamada, you scared me!
How did you manage
to get in here...
And why the heck are
you only wearing a towel.
Since you're injured and stuff,
you can't exactly
wash yourself, can you?
I guess not, but still...
You sure you wanna do this?
I'll be able to see everything.
Stop being so shy!
Get in that tub, already;
he's seen your naughty
bits so get over yourself...!
Go!
She's totally naked
in this tub with me...
Man, she's doing
that knee up sitting thing.
Not that I'm complaining,
but I can't see anything.
I did it!
Go me; I'm totally naked in
this tub with Kosuda...!
Why am I sitting like this;
he can't see anything...
Whatever, it's not
like he's complaining!
I bet he feels
awesome right now!
I'm starting to feel dizzy.
Here, let me wash
your back for you.
Seriously?!
It's cool that
she's so devoted...
I knew she was really
nice underneath all that hot.
This is the lamest
thing I've ever done...
What do I say now,
"you ever been here before?"
Learn to make a freakin' plan!
Um if you want, I don't
mind washing your back too.
Just wash!
I mean, we don't
have to do anything...
Unless you really wanted to...
...just sayin'.
I can return the favor.
This is the best
New Year's Eve ever.
Who knew a back could be so...
...wow...
She's so beautiful,
I'm freaking out.
This is for real...
We're not playing doctor or
any kind of confusing games...
She's right in front of me...
...waiting for me to touch her.
Kosuda...
Please.
Yamada...
Yamada, Yamada,
Yamada, Yamada, Yamada!
Yamada!!!
Kosuda!!
That's not fair!
Yeah, that can happen ladies.
He didn't even
penetrate anything!
Please bring him back to life!
Please, God, please!.
We can't go out like this!!
Bring him back to me!
Please, God!
B Gata H Kei forever!
Please let me find a
wicked hot girlfriend this year.
Please let me be
able to talk to a girl.
Please let me find
an easy chick to date.
Please let me find a
cool boyfriend this year!
boyfriend with a shoe fetish.
Please let me get married
to my sexy true love!
Please let me find a boyfriend
who won't have
other girlfriends.
Since when is
this couples night?
Yeah way to rub it in Takeshita!
You should have told us you were
meeting up with your boyfriend.
Please let me have another
wonderful year with Daisuke!.
Also...
if you could keep
Yamada from asking me
anymore weird
questions, that'd be great.
Please let Takeshita
not have to deal
with any more of
Yamada's weird questions.
Please God, let me break my
lifelong sex fast with Yamada.
What he's praying for,
but with me.
Please, what that
girl is praying for,
don't give it to her.
O...
God...
and...
Buddha...
Please let Kosuda be
happy forever and ever.
Amen!
You are so pathetic,
you know that...?!
How about asking for
something for you for once?!
And, um, PS...
...please let Kosuda only be
happy when he's with me!
Nice.
I didn't even know there was
a shrine on this side of town.
That's because no
one ever comes here.
I only know about it 'cause
it's close to my house.
Do you mind if I ask
what you wished for?
What...?
That's stupid!
Come on...
Think about it!
I asked for the same
thing that you did!
Well, well...
It seems like they still
have a long way to go.
But I'm not ready
to give up just yet...!
It may not be today and
it may not be tomorrow,
but sooner or later
she is gonna get laid!
And believe me, I'll be there
to support her the whole way!
I'll do what I can.
♪ closing song ♪
The end!