Next in line please!
Hello there...!
What can I get for ya?
I can't even call the progress
I'm making with Kosuda progress.
I'm too freaked too out
by this whole Kanejo thing.
It's throwing me off...
...and so...
I welcome you to the
first ever meeting of the
Take Down Kanejo
and Conquer Kosuda Club!
Yeah, that's not a
club I ever signed up for.
Wait...!
Help me, Takeshita!
You're my only hope and stuff!
Just tell me what you
would do in my sitch.
How would you fight her?
I wouldn't fight her.
Well I would, so what should
I do to intimidate her?
I can play instruments!
I bet she can't!
I'm like a genius
at playing the recorder.
I practice all the time.
Something tells me you're
not using it to learn music.
And P.S.
I don't think Kosuda's
into that right now.
Into what?
Never mind.
Look, everyone has something
about them that
stands out, right?
So does Kanejo.
She's hot, smart and
doesn't rub it in your face.
Miyano's a sweetheart,
feminine, and a great cook...
It's okay for Kosuda
to notice that stuff.
And~...
What about me?!
Oh right...
You, um...
Make it up!
Your strong points are all
hidden under
a big pile of awful,
but I know they're
there and you'll find them!
That was way harsh...
But I think I get it.
Listen up, losers!
Next week we're gonna
be starting swimming class.
Swimming?
Crap, I have to drop ten
pounds by next week!
Which is impossible.
Except I don't want my
boobs to get any smaller.
I've got it!
Major duel in school swimsuits!
I'm not gonna lose against you!
Swim class means swimsuits.
Since we all have to wear
the same one it's gonna
be so obvious whose
bod rocks the most...
Wait, maybe that won't
be such a good thing.
That's so bleeping annoying!
Right!
I wasn't born with
a perfect face and
a body that won't
quit for nothing...!
I've gotta show these boys what
I was put on this planet to do!
The saddest part is
she actually believes that.
Legs, check...!
Armpits, check!
And what am I supposed
to do about all that?
I guess I could
just trim it a bit.
Argh!
No she di'n't!
I'm like so over
Kosuda for a while.
What happened...?
Is the world ending?
Dear god I love swim class...
I can't wait to see Yamada
in her swimsuit again.
Kosuda...!
What do you think...?
I picked it just for you!
Takashi!
This is hilariously tragic.
You're not gonna get a
six pack by next week.
Wow~ I don't
know how you do it,
but you look great in that!
Yeah~
I gotta change.
I'm running so late!
Alright, let's see
what sorry sacks
you've got hiding under there.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I just fell
asleep for a sec!
Weird, huh?!
That is the fakest
laugh I've ever heard.
Yes, Just in time!
Let's see what
we're working with here.
They're not very big
but their shape is good
and she's got great legs too...
I hate her.
Sweet!
That's a great swimsuit, Kanejo!
It's a competition suit...
I don't have a school swimsuit.
They don't wear them in America.
Wow that's so cool!
Like you couldn't just buy one!
Whatever, just wait
until I'm looking
hot stretched out by the pool!
I'm finally gonna get to see
Kanejo in a swimsuit today!
She's hot,
but I'm more interested
in seeing what Yamada's got.
Gross...
I don't want these tools
drooling over Yamada.
There they are!
Oh man, look at Kanejo!
Absolutely perfect...!
You think those are Cs or Ds?
Takeshita is lookin' good
and stacked from the back!
And I don't think I've ever
seen Miyano without glasses!
She's actually pretty cute!
Yay!
It's pool time~!
Yeah...
and then there's that one.
Hello~ Katase,
Kobayashi and Sakai!
Do you have any idea how
much I love swim class?
Yep...
Sure do!
It gets better...
'Cause now you get to stare at
the hottest bod all day ...!
Yamada's arrived and the
troll--girls can go home!
I know you're not including
me in that 'troll' statement.
Check me out!
I researched sexy
poolside poses online
for hours last night
just for the occasion!
Whoa!
Yamada!
What are you doing?!
You are not in a French window!
She's so...
so hot.
Boing.
Eat it up, Kosuda...
Eat... it... up.
What is wrong
with you, you jerk?!
Why aren't you looking at me?!
Because that's not
what this is about!
What?!
No way!
You can't swim...?
I had no idea.
It's not that I can't...
I'm just not very good at it.
Hey Yamada!
Miss Akai told me that
you were number one in
the crawl stroke the first year
we were in class together.
Do you remember?
I do...!
Because unlike Takeshita, I'm
actually a very good swimmer...
Wait!
Omigod! Is it because
of my breast size?!
Of course not!
Don't be ridiculous!
Hot damn...!
That was so incredible!
What happened?
Kanejo's being awesome.
Oh please!
She's just doing
it to get attention!
Wow...
and she's fast.
Misato doesn't stand
a chance against her!
That was fantastic, Kanejo!
Thanks...
I had a lot of practice during
my middle school tournament
while I was in the U.S.
Yeah!
She's the coolest
girl in school!
I call foul!
And I call 'shut up.'
This is a swimming class not
a competition for horny
male attention, geez.
All right...
I'll be clocking
your speed this time.
'Kay I'm ready.
No way.
Yamada's racing Kanejo?
Man, that girl's brave.
I hope their swimsuits fall off!
Yamada...
Bring it!
Let me know when
the parade is over.
Okay girls, ready?
This could get ugly.
She's good, but can
she beat someone
who competed in a
U.S. tournament?
Get set!
Look!
A U.F.O.!
No way! Where?!
Later!
Snooze, ya lose, beyotch!
Seriously...?!
Weren't you the one
calling fouls earlier?!
Oh that was smooth...
I guess you are
more than just pretty...
I may actually enjoy this race.
Yamada's pretty fast isn't she?
Yeah, but look,
Kanejo's catching up!
She's gonna win!
So who won?
I don't know.
The winner is...
Kanejo!
That was a good race...
Exactly what
I expected from you.
Just so you know...
It'll be a long time before you
ever stand a chance against me.
Congratulations, Kanejo!
You're amazing!
Oh thanks...
...but Yamada was just
going easy on me!
She's so sweet.
Everything okay?
You need help?
I hate her!
She's...
got it...
...coming...
just...
...wait.
I'll be better at school work,
social life, and at playing
the freakin' recorder!
But she still has that
extra something I don't...
She's so annoyingly charming...
And feminine...!
That's it! I need to become
so feminine and charming
that I can
take over countries!
Okay calm down.
Why don't we start with the
people in your class first?
Like the boys who
sit next to you?
I know!
I'll get Chika to coach me!
Which means I'll have
to ask her for something,
which makes me want
to hurl, but this is war!
Chika...!
I'm gonna ask you for help!
Make me charming
so I can beat Kanejo!
What are you
making that face for?!
Uh, because it's lame to
pick fights with people?
Omigod!
Stop yelling at me...!
She started it!
It's the next day now.
Your first assignment
is to meet Kane-ho
so you can figure out the
best way to take her down!
Why do you hate me?
Look it's Chika!
Hey Chika!
Look, Yamada's
sister Chika is here!
She's very pretty.
Is that her baby sister?
Yep!
She's awesome!
Oh that girl...
She's usually walking with the
hot guys whenever
I've seen her...
She must be popular.
Whoa...
She's beautiful.
And I can tell she's
not a fake, too.
She's actually that cool...
How did she end up
competing with my sister...?
I feel so sorry for her.
If she's anyone worth knowing
she's got to have a boyfriend...
Ew...
Why is she just standing there
like some possessed zombie?
I can't get a good
read on her at all...
It's kind of impressive, though.
That's it read her, Chika!
Take good mental
notes so you can
tell me how to crush
this skankatron!
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
No way...
All right, listen up.
I don't want you lazy
jerks slacking off
just because it's
summer break...
That goes double
for you, Misato!
What~?!
I'm not a slacker, am I?
That's it.
That's how I'm
gonna make this work.
I'll become more sexually
attractive and charming
if I just do it with Kosuda.
I don't know why you
ever stop focusing on that.
It never works out for you.
And it's summer!
Everyone wants to hang out more
and it's okay to wear less...
Kosuda might
even be hot at night
and leave the windows open.
You're not even joking are you?!
Last summer I let Takeshita
plan everything we did ...
Not this year.
This year I am a man and
I will ask her out myself!
Yamada!
Hey Kosuda.
Hey...
I wanna talk to you
about summer break...
I want to take you out sometime!
Flutter!
Did I really just 'flutter'?!
Next in line please!
Hello there...!
What can I get for ya?!
This sucks.
Our schedules
don't match at all...
I should've known you'd
pull something like this!
You're never going to
get laid at this rate!
B Gata H Kei!
I'm bored.
This sucks.
I can't believe I
don't have any plans
at all with Kosuda this summer.
I can't go anywhere
without guys staring at me.
What if one of
them bags me first?
A special glimpse into
Kosuda's summer break.
I can't believe I'm spending
the summer running errands!
If we look like slobs, no one
will ever want to visit us!
It's important to get to
know your ancestors!
Yamada, is that you?
Oh, hi Kazuki, how
are you doing today?
Well this is a strange
coincidence, isn't it?
Or is it?
I'm sorry...
He's not coming home today...
He already left
for our family trip...
I'm on my way out
there to meet them now.
So it's not just me...
He's out of town.
Have you ever heard of
Makinohara Camping Grounds?
We go every year...
We stay in one of the
bungalows there and fish,
have barbeques, make
s'mores and stuff like that.
It's pretty fun.
So cute that he still goes on
family trips during the summer.
It's like he's nine again!
We usually go out there with
our neighbors Miyano's family.
Say what?!
This is so not cute anymore!
Memories of a summer day...
Yamada returns to the wild!
This sucks...
He never told me
any of that crap!
Why would he leave out the
fact that Miyano was going?!
He didn't tell me because
he feels guilty...!
What are you hiding, Kosuda?!
That's good,
just a little bit higher...
Lift...!
I can't believe
I'm being told what
to do by a freaking
twelve year old...!
I'm taking this to my grave.
Mahiro... Stop!
I wonder what they're
doing right now.
I made it just the
way you like it!
All right!
I'm wearing a swimsuit now.
And I like it!
If you're ready...
I brought
you--know--what with me.
Winning!
No way I'm letting him bang her!
Death finds all traitors.
Make sure you get
yours before you kill him.
Great job!
Now that you're done with that,
go get us some water, okay?
Why are you such
a slave driver?!
I guess it was kinda
stupid to start walking
there when it was only a
thirty-minute car trip...
Ew it's hot.
It's time to put this gift
of a hot package
to work and hitchhike
all the way there!
You're too beautiful,
I can't help myself!
Hitchhiking is the best idea
I've ever had in my life!
Where're the cars...?
This sucks.
What am I doing...?
This is dumb...
What am I supposed
to say when I get there?
I know exactly
what I'm gonna do...!
I'll make him drop to
his knees and apologize!
Hello, young lady...
You look like you
could use a ride.
What the crap...?!
Who are these people?!
Omigod are those guns...?!
Are they criminals?!
Am I gonna die?!
I don't wanna!
Why can't I ever say no...?
Help!
I'm too pretty for this!
So what's the story, Kazuki?
Is there a husband
in your future?
Yeah, of course
there is eventually.
She's marrying me...!
Tell them!
I know I'm not very big now,
but I'm a good man!
Aren't you cute!
Look, I'll give you my number...
Okay this is kinda fun...
...but is it worth not having a
date with Yamada this summer?
I've decided I don't want
to come back here next year!
Okay how about this...
If only I could say it out loud.
Then I guess we'll just have to
have Takashi marry Mayu,
won't we?
I think that's
a great idea, dear.
I don't want to depress them.
Keep your head down low!
Right!
What is going on?!
Is this really what's
happening right now?
Listen up!
Take down whoever's in your way!
Annihilate the enemy!
Aye aye, sir!
Take that, and that,
and that, and that, and that!
And that and that and
that and that and that!
I call!
Four of a kind!
Crap...
You beat me again.
How do you do
that every single time?
Would anyone like
some watermelon?
Yes!
Excellent work Miss Yamada...
I don't think there's
anything left for
me to teach you out here today.
Thanks Captain.
You're welcome and
you can keep the gun.
Don't forget...
If you want something
bad enough, take it.
Yes sir...!
I appreciate all
you've done for me!
Power is justice...!
Just you wait, Kosuda!
Are you taking
pictures of the stars?
Yeah.
I don't know why I asked that.
Something told me
I'd find you here.
It's just like old
times when I used to go
to your house to
use the telescope...
I've always been
in love with the stars.
I'd give my life to be one of
those beautiful
lights in the sky.
Why?
Just hang in there!
It gets better, I promise!
According to this
I'm almost there.
You're almost there, Yamada.
You'll get to see Kosuda soon.
Wait a minute,
do I miss him or something?
No! Of course not,
I'm totally fine!
I know I came out here to tell
him how much he sucks...
...but now I don't care anymore.
Forest porn!
The pages are too wet
from all the rain to turn.
Thata girl.
Blame the rain.
Make it easier
for the kids at home.
There it is!
Kosuda...
I'm almost there!
Kosuda!
What was that?!
I don't know...
A bear?
Caw-caw-cacadoodle-doo!
Interesting, was that a chicken?
I don't think so.
Dammit.
Hold on! Why am
I the one who's hiding?!
They're the ones
who should be worried!
What's with all the hugging
and close-talking?!
I'm, sorry!
I didn't mean to!
Um...
I'm gonna go back.
Yeah... Cool.
Is that an air gun?!
And it makes
noise and lights up...
Very impressive!
And now I'm gonna show you what
actually happened
during this scene.
You stupid player~!
Just shut up and sit down!
Okay!
Why were you standing
so close to her earlier?!
Wait...
Yamada...?
Why are you here--
That is what the guiltiest
face in the world looks like!
What are you hiding?!
It's just a surprised face!
I didn't expect you!
Why didn't you want
me to know you went
camping with Miyano
and her family?!
What?
Don't 'what' me!
Kazuki told me everything!
And don't try to pretend like
it's some fuzzy innocent vacay!
You're not kids!
You're in high school
sleeping together in tents!
Well say something, damn it!
Okay.
I'm sorry, but I still want to
know what you're doing here.
How did you find it?
Oh... right...
I actually heard
there were a lot of
wild boars out here and I like,
really wanted to
make a stew tonight.
And you were gonna shoot
them with an air gun?
You know, it's okay if
you just came to see me!
What are you trying to say...?!
Do you know how to
cook stew or something?!
No.
Oh then, maybe you
came here to see Miyano?
Yeah! I just wanted
her to cook for me...
I don't even know what stew is.
Oh...
You should come
to the bungalow...
Couple of really nice families
who'd love to see you?
No, forget it.
I gotta roll.
No, don't leave...!
Is there something wrong?!
Can't we talk about it...!
Please?
I saw you standing there earlier
looking at Miyano's breasts.
I think that
means you're busted.
Bummer.
And you took your camera out so
you could take pictures of
them, didn't you?
What...?
Of course not.
I was taking
pictures of the stars!
Stars?
I see...
Yeah I guess that sounds more
like something he would do.
Not that I don't think
stars are very pretty...
But wouldn't you rather
take pictures of the
celestial being
standing in front of you?
Are you saying you don't
want to take my picture?!
I am a star!
I didn't say anything!
Unfortunately this
camera is already set up
to take pictures of the sky.
So we'll have to
use the digital one...
This'll be my first time,
I've never taken a
picture of you before.
Oh...
Well I hope it's good for you.
Wow...
She looks beautiful...!
I can't screw these up!
Maybe I should try it now...
I could say it's just
for the picture.
Kosuda, look!
Oh man, the battery
ran out on this thing.
Come on, let's go back.
It's getting kinda chilly.
'Kay...
You don't want to take pictures
of the stars anymore?
No, I was taking them so
I could show them to you...
...but you're here, so...
That's so sweet.
Look!
♪ closing song ♪
Finally!
The school field trip is here!
The best part is I'll be staying
in the same room as Kosuda!
They can look at temples.
I'm more interested
in the bath house
or the storage close--where
ever we can be alone!
Uhm...
Yamada!
I Lo...
Omigod!
Just spit it out!
What are you saying?!
And what is "Lo"?
He keeps stopping after 'Lo'!
Oh well, guess
we'll find out next time!