Coming!
Hey!
What's up, Mayu?
I brought the bulletin for you.
Oh, cool, thanks.
Are Kosuda and Miyano
just childhood friends...?
I gotta know!
So, do you like
a guy or anything?
Actually, what I
really want to know
is how you
feel about my brother!
You wanna know
how I feel about~?
I don't know.
I mean Kosuda's
nice and all, but still.
I wouldn't say I have
special feelings for him~
That's what I thought.
Okay...
Sounds good.
It's been so long.
Like...
ten years ago...
Run!
Dang it!
You'll pay for this!
Just you wait!
Thanks...
that was really nice of you.
He's so cool.
He's a prince...!
My very own prince!
Really...?
You found a prince?
I don't know who he is yet,
but he's way cute
and super cool.
I'm home!
Oh, hey sis, how was your day?
You're his sister!
Yeah...
How's it going?
For the last time...!
Will you please quit
walking around naked?!
How come?
I don't understand
what your problem is...
Ever since that day...
I've been too
afraid to fall in love.
Suddenly so close
in the darkroom!
Kinda dangerous
club activities?!
Okay...
The school
festival's coming up...
Any ideas on what
our class can contribute?
I dunno.
Something awesome?
Maybe we could sell food?
I wonder how Kosuda
really feels about Miyano...
Yo Miss Akai what if we
put together a little café?
A camera...? Why does
Kosuda have a camera?
It can't be!
Thank you for coming...
I can't wait to immortalize
your womanly body on film.
Oh...!
I can't wait either!
If we're gonna do a café we
should make it a maid café!
No...! No way!
I don't want that at all!
I'm with Yamada...
I don't want to
do a maid café either...
How about something
more appropriate?
I know! We should
do a butler café!
Right...
Does anyone besides
Misato have any ideas?
Later that day, after school...
Where's Kosuda going with
that stupid camera of his...?
Is he really gonna
take pictures of her!
I'm bouncy!
Yamada?.
What are you doing there?
Nothing!
I was just randomly passing by a
door and peeked in, that's all!
You were passing by a door
at the end of a hallway?
That's what I said...!
I should be asking what
you're doing here...!
And... Where's...
Miyano?
What...? Miyano?
I heard...
You two have been
friends since you were kids.
Yeah, that's true.
No way!
Is she jealous?
But...
Don't worry...!
We're just friends...
I mean...
Back when we were little kids,
she even asked me for advice
about some guy she thought was
her perfect prince or something.
Let me think about this...
that would mean she hasn't
liked him for like the past
ten years, which is good news...
Kosuda is free and clear!
So...
What are you doing
in here anyway?
What do you mean...?
This room is for my club.
It is?
Yeah, I belong to the
photography club.
I didn't know you belong
to the photography club!
I can't believe
she hasn't noticed.
Don't be offended.
She only notices
the naughty stuff.
See? I took this when
I was in middle school.
Uh,...
I have a question!
I need to go take pictures for
the school festival later!
Do you wanna come with me?
A trip to take pictures?!
A plateau...
A guesthouse...
And the grand finale,
a passionate night...
Oh yeah!
Get it girl!
The local nature park?
She must be bored...
I am just taking
pictures though...
But, you know what...
I'll take 'em like I mean it!
If he's gonna take pictures,
he might as
well take some of me...
I don't even mind doing
a few in the nude!
Do you not like
taking pictures of people?
Oh, not really...
They're okay I guess, I'd just
rather take pictures of nature.
It may not be like humans or
animals, but even scenery moves.
Crap!
I said what I meant...!
This is probably
pretty boring for you, huh?
No...
not at all.
Guys have it easy...
It's so not fair.
Huh?
Hey...
Good morning.
Yeah, morning.
After school...
I was gonna develop those
pictures from yesterday.
I was wondering...
if you'd want to come with me.
Where is it?
The photography
club has a darkroom.
A darkroom?
Yes, I'll go with you!
I'll definitely go!
I didn't expect her
to be so interested,
but I'm glad she's coming.
The darkroom...!
In other words,
a room that is dark!
That's right...
And you know what
you do in a dark room?
Have sex, that's what...!
I may have failed in the past...
But not anymore...
In the dark I should
be able to calmly
pounce on him and
tear him apart!
It's on this time Kosuda...
Get ready!
Would you please
stop making plans to
have sex while we're
eating; I mean, seriously.
Cool...
So is the photo club
not having a meeting today?
Nope.
All right!.
No interruptions!
If you have questions about
anything, feel free to ask me.
This is where the darkroom is.
Oh... Nice...
It's so dark...
and kinda tight.
I guess so, yeah.
We're all alone.
A little exciting,
don't you think?
What does she mean by that...?
Maybe it doesn't'
mean anything...
Damn it, this is confusing!
Why can't I figure chicks out!
Hey...
Don't feel so bad;
I can't ever figure out
what she's thinking either.
All right...
I'm calm...
I'm collected...
Let's do this!
I gotta calm down...
I gotta get out of my head...
Yamada did not come here
just to satisfy my dirty mind!
Actually...
yes she did...
...trust me.
This is it...
Here I come...
What sort of fate awaits
our dear hero Kosuda?!
Oh...
oops.
My hand is shaking like crazy...
I am alone in the darkroom with
the prettiest girl in
school, though.
What are you scared of now...?
Do you have any idea how long it
took me to get ready
for this moment?!
No holding back...
I'm going all the way!
Why's this room open?
Someone's here!
Is anyone in there?
Yeah!.
Hey, it's Kosuda...!
Please don't open the door;
I'm developing some pictures.
Oh, cool...
How's it going?
Going well; how's
it going with you?
Good.
Just forgot something.
Try to keep quiet...
He'll leave in a second.
What's happening?
I feel like I'm
caught in an affair!
I'm gonna turn on
the light really quick...
I can't see anything...
The light switch is...
How could I
screw this up again?!
Please, can we just do it?
Just a little bit?
Oh my God!
I thought this was gonna
be the most perfect plan...
...like ever...
Maybe it's not in
the cards for us.
Maybe Kosuda and I are
fated to never have sex...
This is awful. What if
I never know his touch?
What is this?
This is...
...second base...
also known as B!
It's so warm and squishy.
See ya later, man.
Make sure you lock the
room when you leave, kay?
Yeah, okay.
Cool!
Well that was a close one...
Uh...
I should've told you...
Only club members
are supposed to be in here.
Where are you going?
It's almost like I can still
feel him touching me...
Yamada!
You don't have to walk...
I can take you home.
Fine... I suppose
that'd be okay.
I wonder what I
felt in the darkroom...
It seemed a lot like...
No, that's stupid.
I can't believe he didn't notice
he was touching my boob...
This guy has
a talent for flushing
good luck down the toilet...
It's weird, though...
...because I still feel good
about the whole thing.
It kinda feels like
I'm flying in the sky.
B Gata H Kei.
My breasts have never
been this sensitive before...
My body will be cultivated
by the hands of a man.
Yamada's level
has now increased...
She is awarded with
sensitive boobies.
I'm climbing the
proverbial stairway to
adulthood and makin'
the beast with two backs!
Good grief...
Why does she always
have to be so loud?
This is weird...
The only thing I can think
about are Kosuda's hands.
Hey, Yamada, what's wrong...?
You sick?
I heard big boobs
aren't usually sensitive.
So...
...you won't understand
what I'm going through!
Yeah, I don't ever understand
what you're going through,
but best of luck with your
newest bout of insanity.
Passionate School Festival!
I, Yamada, will
be the school's queen!
We know what we're
doing for the festival...
The votes have
been counted, so it's official.
We're gonna put on
the haunted house, guys.
Aww... man.
That actually sounds like
it could be pretty fun.
Okay! We're gonna
decide on roles now.
Who wants to be a ghost?
Me! I do! I do! I do!
Thanks Yamada.
Anyone else!
I'll do it.
Yeah, why not?
I'll use the dark again and
go after Kosuda's face!
B is like second base,
and since A is kissing,
I'll be headed to
first base next.
Well, she might
have the order of
things mixed up, but,
we'll take what we can get.
We need someone
to take pictures, too.
Don't we have a member of
the photography club in here?
That's right...!
I'm in the photography club!
Oh, good...
We'll leave that to you then.
Kobayakawa...
Um...
I'm Kosuda.
He only got one character right.
We've been here for six months,
and he didn't know?
Whaddaya think?
I like it.
Yeah, it looks good.
Here's the next one.
Hey, Kosuda!
Would you mind
taking a picture of us.
Okay!
Kosuda!
Take ours too!
Okay!
Kosuda!
What's the deal?
Why isn't he trying to
take my picture?
Hey, Yamada...?
You wanna try
out the makeup now?
Yeah, sure.
Why am I not surprised...?
Your skin's taking
really well to the makeup.
Aww, thanks!
Say "cheese"!
Back off!
What's his problem?
He's just Kosuda!
I think all the
attention he's getting
is going straight
to his head...!
I don't want him to be a total
nobody, but I don't want
him being more
popular than me, either.
This one's rather
selfish, isn't she?
What's that...?
Did you take it the other day?
Yamada.
It looks like it developed okay.
Yeah.
I think so.
I don't remember it being
that peaceful and relaxing...
It's like we weren't even
looking at the same thing...
But he saw it as beautiful...
and captured it that way, too.
Uh...
so what do you think?
It seems tranquil...
I think it's totally the sort
of picture you'd take.
Is that a compliment...
or an insult?
Okay guys...!
You can do it!
Yeah!
Hurry up, Kosuda...
My lips are starting to
get impatient for you!
I can do it!
That's a very
self--motivated ghost.
I'm gonna get you...
Nice job, Yamada.
Oh, hey, you guys...
What are you doing here?
Looking for trouble...
We are in a haunted
house, aren't we?
True...!
Speaking of
looking for trouble...
I'm not sure how it works...
...but have you guys ever tried
using Konnyaku to get off?
Don't you think it's
wrong to take advantage
of the dark to steal a kiss?
No I don't, cause...
He's probably never even
kissed anyone before...
...which means...
Once.
I.
Kiss.
Him, he'll be hooked
on me for sure!
How can you know that?
You haven't kissed
anyone either...
Where do you come
up with this stuff?
Don't worry, though...
I'll go find Kosuda for you.
Thank you!
I bet he's at the reception desk
in the photography club room!
It's really dark in here...
So dark we might be
able to move past kissing!
Yes!
From B to A, or second
to first, and then C or third,
and finally home,
or D, which is sex!!
This is all very confusing.
Kosuda...!
He's here!
Here I come!
It's me, stupid!
Holy, what the hell...?
Damn it why are
you here, Takeshita?
I don't want my very
first kiss to be with you!
Quit yelling!
I didn't do anything!
Yeah, I know, and I'm sorry.
I just didn't want to have to
start calling you my girlfriend.
That doesn't make sense.
Start talking, girlfriend.
Where's Kosuda at?
Don't call me that...
I couldn't find him
in the clubroom.
Oh no...
He was supposed to be there!
Where did he go...?
This sucks bad!
His timing almost
physically hurts me.
I can't believe Kosuda
didn't bother to come see me...!
Yamada...!
What?
There you are!
We've been looking for you.
How come?
Wanna enter the beauty pageant?
Pageant?
Yeah, and the winner
gets to have an entire
year of free drinks from
the school store...!
So if you win you don't
mind giving me half do you?
If I do win, it might
be a nice reminder
to Kosuda about how lucky he is.
You can count me in!
This'll be a piece of cake!
Yeah it will!
We believe in you, Yamada!
It doesn't hurt that guys are
only interested in
a girl's looks, too.
Ladies and Gentlemen, let's give
a big hand to our contestants!
These are your finalists
for the seventeenth annual
Miss Takizawa High contest!.
Give it up!
Let's start counting
the votes immediately!
She's a shoe--in.
No one else up there comes close
to being as pretty as Yamada.
No one else is as dirty either.
This is great!
I can feel all those
dirty looks coming
from the guys in the audience...
And I love it!
Look!
I'm getting more votes...!
I'm totally gonna win!
It looks like Yamada
might win in a landslide!
It doesn't matter who wins this
because you're number one to me.
The votes are
still being counted!
Yamada, Yamada, Suzuki,
Yamada, Yamada, Yamada...!
You're going to regret
leaving me all alone in
that haunted house now,
aren't you Kosuda?
Uh oh... it looks like Kanejo is
closing in on first place.
It's anyone's game now!
Who will be the beauty victor!
I'm still number one,
though, aren't I...?
Who the hell is this
stupid Kanejo chick?
Whoa...!
She's really pretty!
I didn't know we had a
girl like that in our school!
Kanejo, seems like
you're closing in;
tell us
about yourself?
I just transferred here
yesterday from the US...
I'm Kyoka Kanejo...
Wow...
You're all so sweet;
it's nice to meet you.
Why didn't she
transfer tomorrow?!
So, she's back from overseas?
Cool.
Looks like she's
pretty rich too.
Yamada may not be
the "it" girl for much longer.
Yamada?
What are you worried about?
You're not like...
...that close to Yamada
or anything are you?
Can I tell him that
I think she likes me?
I mean come on dude...
You guys sit next to each other
but you barely even talk...
Plus look at her;
why would she be in to you?
Or maybe she doesn't
like me after all!
It's a dead heat between
Yamada and Kanejo!
Who will win the big title?
Who is the fairest of them all?!
The official results are in...!
The winner of
Miss Takizawa High is...
By a nose, the beautiful Yamada!
Did you see that, Kosuda...?
There's no denying
I'm amazing now!
And now she's won
a beauty contest...
He's right.
Why would she
waste her time with me.
A folk dance will be
held in the schoolyard.
All students, please make your
way to the schoolyard
immediately.
There she is!
Miss Takizawa High!
Will you please dance with me?
No, dance with me!
Where's Kosuda?!.
He should have been here first!!
What a jerk...!
He didn't come see me at the
haunted house or
the beauty contest!
A picture from the other day...
It's blurry, but at
least I got her in one.
Yamada...
I don't care if she's
too good or not...!
I'm gonna go ask
her to dance with me!
It's okay...
I don't really care.
Yamada...!
I'm coming!
I don't care.
Not one bit.
I don't care about
Kosuda anymore!
Yamada!
What are you here for...?
I'm kind of busy right now.
I wanted...
...to say congratulations
on winning the pageant.
Thanks...
Although I figured I'd win.
There's one more thing...
Will you dance with me?
Sure, but you'll have
to get in line first.
Oh...
That's gonna be a long wait.
It's not like I'm
happy he came...
Every guy in school is
in line to dance with me...
69 more people!
She was kinda rude,
but she waited for me...
48 more people.
10 more people.
One more person!
Finally!
The song ended.
You spent all that
time in line waiting...
We might as well dance.
♪ closing song ♪
In the next episode,
it's already Christmas!!
Once I get a gift
and eat some cake,
we'll be headed to the
hotel for my real present!
Oooh, fancy.
It looks like a castle...!
Gah, there're so many to choose
from, how will I ever decide?
Um...
Yamada?
Say tah--tah to your
cherry tonight, Kosuda!
I'm coming to get you...!
See you next time!