This has become
so freakin stupid.
I just wanted to get laid...
I didn't expect to feel
like this, or any way...
It wasn't about liking
someone or not liking someone...
What does that even mean?!
Why am I feeling things now...?
And on top of that...
Why does it suck?
Shouldn't love
make you happy...?
So why...
Why does this hurt?
Emo much?
I mean, get over it...
Everybody hurts sometimes.
Oh no!
In front of everyone...!
I never said I don't like you...
Autumn...
That's what I get for
telling her how I feel, I guess.
I know, right?
That's what I was saying--and
I wasn't even there!
Kosuda!
You ready to do this yet?
I think you're
the last one to vote.
For what?
For what?!
For hottest tail of course...
Only the guys
are voting, though...
It's a secret ballot...
so don't tell the girls.
Maybe you should
have whispered that.
Here, I'll make
it easier for you.
It's pretty much turned
into a race between
Yamada and Kanejo at this point.
That's hard!
I know, right...?!
Don't worry the
votes are anonymous.
Right now both of them
are tied for first place.
Which means, you get
to select the winner!
So much for it being
an anonymous vote, then.
Riddle me this...
Why are guys stupid?
Kanejo or Yamada...?
Well that's a no brainer.
Yamada, of course...
...but what if it weirds her
out that I picked her...?
I don't want her
to think I'm desperate.
That wouldn't help.
You better pick
me and then stick me!
What the...?!
Does she want me to pick her?!
It's just a vote, man...
C'mon!
Hurry up!
It's not rocket science!
I know it's just a vote...
...but I don't
want to upset anyone.
What if Kanejo starts hating me
because I voted for Yamada...?
Nah, she's really
not the type to
give a crap
about things like this.
What the what?
How'd she do that?
Hey, Don't be a tampon...
Man up and cast
your vote already!
That was harsh...
But he's right.
I kinda have been acting like
a tampon this whole time.
I'm so over that!
He was getting stung like
a hundred times but...
What's going on?
Yo!
Guess what time it is?!
Time for you to stop stalling!
I... I pick...
Her...!
I mean...
I'm in love with...
Yamada~!
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Whoa.
Dude, we weren't asking you
to propose or anything.
It was just a
popularity contest.
I can't believe
he just did that!
Oh, what a freak.
Yamada!
You're so lucky!
What the hell
is wrong with you...?!
All you had to
do was vote for me...!
Damn it, Kosuda!
Ohmigod...
I can't breathe...
Oh gross what's happening?
Am I crying?
Ew...!
Why does it feel like my
heart's about to explode?
Screw that!
I don't give a crap if he
has feelings for me or not!
That's his problem!
Who does he think he is?
Does he expect me
to care or something?!
You're so annoying!
Oh man, you just got shot down!
That's gotta suck.
What just happened?
Shock!
He didn't mean it, ya know...
It was just a stupid
popularity contest.
Yeah I know.
I wish that were true.
But I could see
on his face it's not.
Even with his face
scrunched up he looks adorable.
What an idiot!
Why'd he pick today...?!
And why'd he do it in
class in front of everybody?!
Did he seriously think
I'd be happy about that?!
'cause I'm totally not.
This is good...
You have his heart,
now go forth and get laid!
I did it!
I know she heard me that time.
The whole class did.
Yeah but, just because
you told her doesn't
necessarily mean she has
to like you back, you know.
How long have you
been standing there?
And what do you mean...?
And whose freakin'
side are you on?
Oh Kanejo~!
Wasn't that funny?
You lost to Yamada
again--just like last year!
Damn it, Yamada...!
How dare you...!
I'm so over you
humiliating me like this!
Miss Kanejo, I made you some
tea and honey if you'd like.
Yes I would!
Thank you so much!
Stupid tramp...!
Ugh...!
You're gonna get it!
I'm sorry Miss...
I completely forgot to
ask if you'd like some sugar.
I'd love some!
Or maybe not.
We don't want you to
have trouble sleeping.
I gotta hand it to you, Kosuda--
that was pretty
smooth yesterday.
Chicks dig when you
confess your love in public.
You are so the man, man.
She'll never forget it.
Seriously?
You're not gonna
say anything to him?
This shy guy summons
up the courage
to confess his love to you...
...and you have nothing
to say about it?!
You're terrible!
You make him sound like a
helpless puppy or something.
I'm just saying
you could be a little
more considerate
of his feelings...
Think of how hard
that must've been for him!
I guess you're right.
That day on the train...
I guess that's what
he was trying to say.
It's not that I don't
care about his feelings,
but I'm only interested
in sex right now.
You know, I knew that
but hearing you verbalize
it makes me feel that
much sorrier for Kosuda.
Why don't you just
tell him that you like him?!
Oh and lie?
I can't do that even if
it will get me laid!
It's not a lie!
Just do the deed already!
Fine, don't.
But the least you could do is
apologize for being
such a jerk about it.
Let's practice...!
Tell me what you're
gonna say to him!
Sorry you're such an idiot!
That's not gonna pass
as an apology...
...seriously.
I can't even find
a way to be alone
with him when
I want to apologize.
Field Day's coming up...
Now's your chance
to redeem yourselves.
I wanna see tears and blood!
It doesn't matter how you play
the game as long as you win!
I'm scared...
Is this P.E. or jail?
We need to figure
out who our planning
committee is
going to be, all right...
raise your paws if
you'd like to volunteer.
Oh, geez, calm down...
You know I'm just gonna
pick volunteers anyway.
You two.
Kosuda and Yamada...
Or should I call you Kosamada?
I get it!
'Cause they're like
a couple and stuff?
How did she even
find out about that?
It's kind of creepy.
Gosh that was awkward...
There's no way she's gonna
want to work with me now.
Awkward...!
Doesn't look
like we have a choice...
I guess I'll do it!
Don't do me any favors.
I'm just trying
to embarrass you.
Any objections to doing the
same events we do every year?
Alright...
Any ideas on events
to add this year?
Co-ed three--legged--race!
Co-ed mud wrestling!
Co-ed Twister!
Wow...
She seems pretty
excited about that.
Anyone interested in
being the event recorder...?
This person will be in
charge of taking pictures.
Oh!
I can do that!
Great...
Use a good lens.
Go to the media room
and check out
photos from last
year for reference.
Okay I will...
Can you remind me where that is?
Oh please...
You know exactly where it is.
You've been there
at least one other time!
Oh...
I didn't know
what it was called.
Don't just stand there...
Do your research.
This could be promising.
It's such a small room.
And we're alone!
--Yamada!
--Kosuda!
Sorry.
You go ahead.
I insist.
Okay...
Here's what...
If you haven't noticed I've
been avoiding you for a while...
...and uh...
Why is this so hard?!
Great, let me guess--
it would be so much easier
if I'd just go the 'H' away?!
And I wanted to
say I'm sorry, okay?!
I did it, crap that was painful!
Am I hearing things?
Sorry, could you repeat that?
Don't push it!
Okay...
It's all good...
...and yeah, it didn't
even bother me...
I'm totally fine.
What do you mean
it didn't bother you?!
I'm lying!
It bothered me!
I've gone completely
emo over the whole thing!
Okay. So what were
you going to say?
Um...
It's about what happened
with the popularity poll.
That was...
That was how I feel!
And?!
And I...
I was wondering if you...
If you felt the same?
He cannot be serious.
Is he that stupid?!
Remember when I apologized?
That might have been
an answer--I dunno!
What's happening...?!
Is she upset?
Thinking of something to say?
If you don't like me,
just tell me okay?!
I'll leave you alone!
Are you seriously crying?!
Look, I never said...
...that I didn't like you.
So she doesn't dislike me?
That means something...
I'll accept even a slim
chance at this point!
You make my brain hurt!
You actually said that...?
Omigosh saying you don't dislike
him means that you do like him!
If I said I hated him,
he wouldn't have sex with me...!
That's all this is!
Why're you always trying to
make it into something more?!
Because I know you...
and I know you don't have
the balls to admit
it's what you really want.
That's what 'busted' looks like!
It's okay to admit you
actually like him, ya know.
It's so exhausting
being right all the time.
Don't do it!
It gets better!
This isn't fair...
It shouldn't be so hard.
I thought if you're in love,
you're supposed to be happy
all the time and annoy
everyone around you?
So why does it hurt?
I just want it to be over.
Are we still here?
Things'll change if you
hold on for one more day.
She is confusing the
crap outta me right now.
B Gata H Kei!
Thank you sir!
Have a great day!
I hope you'll fly
with us again soon.
It was a pleasure
flying with the
most beautiful
women in the world.
Who is that?
Damn he's beautiful!
Is he someone famous?
Marry me!
Let's run away!
Princess, no!
I'm sorry,
I know that's sudden...
If marriage is out of the
question, perhaps coffee first?
If nothing else,
I'd love to know your name...
When I return home,
I'll tell everyone
that Japan was
my favorite stop...
Please, tell me your name!
Keiichi...
Kanejo
Are you all right?!
Keiichi Kanejo...
Keiichi Kanejo.
Put your hopes in Field Day!
Suit yourself...
Autumn.
Hold onto your poms poms...
It's field day
Cheese wiz!
What's going on?!
Second year,
Class H is competing
in the cheerleading competition.
Aren't we so sexy?!
Hey...! Kanejo...
watch where you're going.
Say no more...
It's totally fine.
What the crap...?
That was weird.
Weird because she handled it
better than you would've, right?
Today not even
Yama--dumb can get to me...
I finally get to
see my brother again!
But...
I should make a
note to remind myself
to punish her
later for touching me.
So...
Wanna tell me
what you're looking for?
I just want to make
sure I don't run into Kosuda.
You're still playing that game?
No but...
I don't want
to deal with it now.
I need to focus.
Picture time!
That's a very
focused pose there.
Oh yeah...
go on ahead.
I'll be right here!
I guess she's
still avoiding me...
I knew it was
too good to be true.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Hey...
What's up Kosuda.
Matsuo...!
You're just the
guy I wanted to see!
Thanks, I guess.
And that's
where I am right now...
I'm sorry...
I hope I didn't bore you.
You didn't bore me at all.
I was worried about you two.
Should I have said all that...?
I mean, he doesn't even know
Yamada and I
told him everything...
I wonder if he thinks
I'm a dramatic mess.
I didn't mean to look bored.
It's just that I already heard
the whole story from Takeshita.
My guess is that
with everything happening
the way it did Yamada just
needs some time to process it.
So she's not mad?
No, if that were the case
you wouldn't see her at all.
I mean, she's still popping
up here and there, right...?
So relax...
You laid a lot on her.
Give her some
time to think about it.
You're so right!
Thank you so much!
You know...
...sometimes I worry
that I'm gonna wake up
and find out it
was all just a dream.
I think you worry too much.
Yamada~!
What--a--ya?!
You have realized you can't
avoid Kosuda forever, right?
At some point you're
gonna have to face him
and decide
what you want to do...
Either be with him
or leave him alone.
What I want is
for him to lay back
and let me take the lead.
Whatever.
What you want is to lay back and
let a hundred Kosudas take ...
Oh nevermind.
You are such a waste of skinny!
Have I mentioned
how pretty you are?
You look so hot in that uniform.
That's very sweet.
Fine, I'll say it.
We all want to know if you
have a boyfriend or not.
I don't want a boyfriend...!
The only commitment I'll
ever make is to my brother!
Not that I can
say that out loud...
Plus, there's her.
Look who doesn't
have a boyfriend!
Pretty Miss 'I went to school
in the U.S. but no one cares!'
Yes, I do.
My boyfriend's the hottest,
smartest guy in the world!
No way!
That sucks so hard...
I hate you!
I wonder why that bothers
you so much, Yamada?
Why are you sinking
so low because
I have a boyfriend, hmm,
could it be because
you don't have one?
I knew it...!
You're such a fake!
Screw you...!
You don't know me!
I guess I don't...
Tell me then...
Do you have one or not?
I...
I uh...
Next up is second year
girl's Shoulder Wars!
What?!
Where's she going?!
Did she just make
a 'tsk' sound at her?
The next event will be
second year
girl's shoulder wars!
Good luck!
How'd she figure out I
don't have a boyfriend...?!
She must've been stalking me.
Well now she's gonna pay!
Don't get used to that headband!
'Cause you won't be wearing
it by the end of the game!
Bring it, hotpants!
Seriously?!
You're both on the
same freaking team!
It's so about to be on!
Dammit!
Go over to where Kanejo is!
Um, we're the legs so
we decide where to go!
No, you guys are
supposed to be the horse...
I'm the rider.
I'm in charge!
Did you call me a horse?!
Why'd you take
off your headband?!
What's going on?
Holy crap!
You really don't care
that you look like a freak...
That's the reason you
can't get a boyfriend isn't it?
How can someone like you...
be so damn pathetic?!
I never said I didn't have one!
But if I were you,
I would hope that I do...
...because if I don't then I'm
gonna have to steal yours!
I'll kill her before I let
her hit on my brother...
...skeezer!
No you didn't!
I don't know what came over me!
What were you thinking Yamada?
That hurt!
At this point I have to consider
that I may have been adopted.
Who's that?
He's so hot~!
The next event will be the
second year girl's
scavenger hunt race.
Kyoka?
Are you ready...?
I think you're up next.
I'm all over
this scavenger hunt!
I can find anything...!
Plus I'm sure there
are hot guys around here!
This is so not
the time for that.
One of these
envelopes has to have
"hottie" or "sexy guy"
written in it...
But which one...?
Misato Eyes...
activate!
There it is!
Tadaa~!
It's the wrong one!
What...?!
But... how?
Ohmigod!
There it is!
Here!
Switch me tickets!
What did you see
in the envelopes?
Hot guy!
I'm looking for you!
Come on out!
Where's my brother?
Why isn't he here yet?
Hi!
What's going on?
Kyoka?
Is that you?
Yes, darling brother...
How long are you going to keep
me waiting out here all alone?
I'm so sorry sweetie!
I'm kind of busy right now!
I found a hottie!
Yay!
--What are you doing?!
--Run, Hottie, run~!
He's so hot~!
I'm impressed.
But who is that guy?
Congratulations, you won...!
Can you tell me
what your name is, sir?
I'm Keiichi Kanejo...
My baby sister, Kyoka,
is second year, Class H...
It's good to see everyone today!
Can I keep you...?
You're so cute!
Hey little sis, how's it going?
You're looking well.
I am now that you're here.
It was you!
You're the one who
was fighting Kyoka
in the shoulder wars, right?
Where are you going?
I'm Keiichi...
Keiichi Kanejo.
Nice to meet you...
What's your name?
Yamada.
Such a beautiful name...
for a beautiful girl.
Oh no...
What's going on...?
That random hot guy just told
Yamada she was beautiful.
And look at the size
of his camera.
That's a high--end
single lens reflex digital!
There's no way I
can compete with that...
Mine is just a
used film camera...
There's only so much
you can do with it...
They're in totally
different leagues...!
Someone just kill me now!
It's such a treat to
see someone like you
after being away from
Japan for so long.
A token of our new friendship.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
All right!
She showed him!
That rules!
Oh wow.
That was so cool!
Douche repellant!
Now they just want
to bang her more!
I'll kill you for this...!
No one humiliates
my brother like that!
It's okay, it's more fun
when there's a challenge.
So you know her?
What's she like...?
You two are friends aren't you?
No...!
He can't be into her!
This whole sneaking around and
running away thing
is really getting old.
But I don't know
what else to do.
This sucks so much!
Hi...
Yamada?
So uh...
I wanted to ask...
...about what happened with
Kanejo's brother earlier.
Did you blow him off
because you like me...?
Okay that sounds so pathetic...
I can't ask her that--who
would ever ask her that?
Why does he do that?!
If you have
something to ask, ask...!
Besides, if you don't,
I can't tell you I dissed
that guy for you.
Yamada... I know
Kanejo's brother is hot.
Finally!
They both are, actually...
and that's not the point...
...but it is rare that both
siblings are so hot.
So?!
And who the hell
are you talking to?!
I'm sorry!
Don't kill me!
You've never
told me I was hot.
You never tell me
how pretty or sexy I am...
But you can just throw
it around about Kane--slut?!
Crap, it's getting awkward...
I should say something.
Yamada...
I want you to know that you look
very cute in your
cheerleading outfit!
I don't want to talk
to you right now!
And 'Most Dramatic' goes to~
You suck...
I'm leaving.
Yamada wait!
So um...
It's been awhile...
...since we went out I mean...
Would you ever give
me another chance?
Sure. Whatever.
I don't care.
All right!
Alright, you better not
screw this up for us...!
I want this date
to end in a banging!
Go forth, young virgin!
Spread 'em wide
and create a love-slide!
Oh man, I love
our class so much!
Not gonna lie,
this is where you want
to be for the
bangin' body buffet.
My eyes are so hungry.
What the heck?
Hey, Yamada!
There you are!
Way to keep us
all waiting... Jerk!
I'm sorry.
But guess what...?!
I'm here now and we're
gonna bring it down!
Yeah!
Yamada.
You better watch
yourself, Yamada.
I just wish...
I wish I knew more about you.
Ohmigod he's looking!
Hey, I brought you something!
♪ closing song ♪
Okay, something
weird is going on with
Kanejo and her brother,
but I can't figure it out.
Whatever, it's my
first date in like,
forever and I'm not gonna
let that creep stop me.
No way!
Kanejo's brother is what?!
No Kanejo!
Stop! Please!
Oh no you don't, Skank-Nasty!
Get your paws off of Kosuda...!
See ya next time!