Autumn, yo!
Okay, slackers, listen up.
Our school field
trip is next week...
This year, we're going
to spend four days
and three nights in Kyoto.
I bet the chicks in Kyoto
are so hot they're sick.
Like you'd have
a chance, anyway.
Shut up, dude.
Like these punks ever listen.
What if I get hit on by
guys from other schools?
How, when guys from your own
school won't hit on you?
This is exciting;
I've never actually been
on a school trip like this.
Oh, these are a blast.
You're gonna love it.
At night, we always
talk about whatever
guys we're crushing
on at the moment.
It's true!
Who we're crushing on...?
My only crush is
on my big brother...
But... I can't tell
them the truth...!
I can't!
So... are you
a Kyoto virgin too?
Shut up!
But yeah, I've never
been there either.
A city that old...
...the hotels have to
be loaded with history.
Let's go inside, right now.
Hold on... Isn't there
a jinx that couples
who start dating on a school
trip are doomed to fail?
Well... all I want
from Kosuda is a
one--time thing, so I'm
not really worried about it.
You do realize you're
sucking on a pencil, right?
She's practicing for later,
if ya know what I mean.
Yay!
It's a school trip!
No chance to be alone...
Hey...!
Back when you were in school,
what were your
out--of--town trips like?
I hate to say it, but you'll be
in groups most of the time,
so you won't get the chance
to be alone with Yamada...
Although you
should totally try to
kiss her again if you
get the opportunity!
Well yeah, I mean, obviously...
That's kinda my goal.
What, are you
a freaking mind reader?
How do you know we kissed?
I never said anything
to you about it!
Now you know...
before you kiss her again...
...you have something
you need to take care of.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm just talking about telling
her how you feel about her.
Tell her the truth...
Every girl wants to hear a guy
say those three little words.
They do--really?
She's right...
That is how I feel...
maybe I should say something.
And once she falls for that BS,
you can kiss her
wherever you want.
I can?
Yeah.
Does she mean
wherever like wherever
or like wherever wherever?
Toothbrush...
toothpaste...
towel and some lotion.
What's up?
Are you getting ready
for the big trip?
Cool...!
A Kyoto Guidebook!
Well, you know me,
preparationess
is second to godliness.
Yeah, I get that.
The 7:40 Negai 101 is leaving
for Hiroshima from
Platform number fourteen--
Morning.
I don't like this early.
Oh, Kosuda, celebrate your
adorable innocence
while you still can...
Because within
the next three days...
...that lonely cherry of
yours is gonna be mine!
I won't have to listen to
slutty stories anymore...
Finally, I'll be able to
tell the good stuff myself!
He'll be talking about you, too.
You do get that, don't you?
Ladies and Gentlemen,
thank you for
riding the Negai,
number 101 today.
Let's get this show on the road!
To Kyoto!
We're already on
the road, genius.
I got a bunch
of snacks you guys...!
Check this out...
vinaigrette kelp chocolate!
Ewie!
Would anyone care to purchase
a cup of nice, hot coffee?
No way!
Gimme a beer!
Don't make me expel
you from this trip
before we even get started.
We're all thinking the
same thing:
Miss Akai sounds really hot
when she gets pissed.
Look, it's Kosuda!
Kosuda!
Will you take our picture!
Yeah, sure!
If I give you my email,
will you send it to me later?
Well, I would, but this
isn't a digital camera.
Kosuda!
Take our picture too!
Okay.
Yet again everybody wants
him to take their picture,
and he thinks
he's Mister Popular.
Kosuda, will you buy me a soda?
Yeah, okay!
Kosuda would you
mind putting my bag up?
Sure, no problem.
Yo, Kosuda...
You wanna massage
my shoulders next?
Well, he may not
think he's popular,
but he's still pissing me off
being so damn nice to everyone.
"The Ladies" are so
complicated, aren't they?
Is that for the movie studio?
Yeah my mom
went there last year...
She gave it to me.
Really?
Did she love it or what?
Totally. She talked
about it for weeks.
This is gonna
the best trip ever!
So true...
It shall be, epic.
This is awesome!
We're completely
surrounded by lady lumps!
I need to tell her how I feel...
...but how can I do that if we
don't get the chance
to be alone?
Kosuda, over here!
Don't forget to
take our picture, too!
But you better make
sure we all look cute!
No worries, there!
Thou art false to
thy would be hook up!
Maybe this isn't the time
to tell her how I feel.
Traitorous rout-face!
Kosuda!
Come over here!
You need to at least be in
a few of the pictures too...
Why don't I take a picture
of you and Yamada together?
No...!
I don't wanna be in the same
picture with a jerky traitor!
Bring it down, Drama.
Everybody's taking pictures.
Yeah... Okay!
I'd like that...
I wanna be in a
picture with Yamada.
--What?
--Wonderful...!
Hey,
Inside--the--Actor's--Studio,
go stand by him.
Fine, let's get it over with...
I don't have all day...
I'm only doing this
'cause it's for school.
Sure you are...
Say cheese...!
--Cheese!
Now was that so hard?
Cheese!
We're in Kyoto!
Time to head back to the hotel!
Everyone still alive?
We've been here one day,
and we've had
to do everything
in a stupid group.
I couldn't break
away to save my life.
I thought that last temple was
gonna be a lot
higher than it was.
Yeah, but I bet back when it
was made it seemed pretty high.
Why does this jerk keep
talking about sightseeing?
He's supposed to be boning me!
A thousand years of culture,
and all you can think
of is bumpin uglies?
I'm so excited
about taking a bath.
Yeah, but before that, I could
go for some food, ya know?
I wonder what they're gonna
feed us for dinner tonight.
Typically, it would be a
special course dinner...
Kyoto special course dinner!
Side dishes!
Dessert things!
All of this looks amazing!
I've never been so happy...
Thanks but I don't really
need you anymore.
Imagination, you will not
get the better of me...
Kosuda's not a
slave to good food...
Not even a little...
Otherwise, he might
actually know I'm alive.
Miyano?
You okay?
The girls' side
of the bathhouse.
I swear your breasts get
bigger every time I touch them.
They do!
But those tickle parties
and pillow fights help too.
Heck yeah...
Can you imagine what those girls
are getting away
with right now...
Am I right?
Bulge.
No, down boy!
Way to grow, Kosuda...
Damn; that big boy is scary.
I know!
Let's all whip em out
and have a size off...
Yeah!
Can you imagine what those guys
are getting away with in there?
You're such a perv!
Seriously, this entire bathhouse
fantasy has been all you!
Lights out!
Everyone get some sleep;
we've got a big day ahead of us!
Lights out is when all
the good gossip happens!
Time for dirty talk!
So, Takeshita
we'd all like for you to
tell us what your
first time was like.
Why are you asking me that?
Nice, Misato!
She hasn't even
told me the details
of blasting her cherry bomb yet.
Oh, come on,
you have been dating your
boyfriend for
like ever, haven't you?
There's no escaping now.
Even the shyest
girl in the world
would spill her guts here!
This is what overnight
school trips are all about!
How's it fair that
I'm the only one
who has to tell their story?
I would but I don't
have a story yet.
Well, that's not my problem!
Okay, if you want
I can tell you about
Katase's tragic first time!
You shut your fat mouth!
Didn't you tell me that
you lost it at some hotel?
What're you talking about?
I never told you where it was!
Where was it?
Were you wearing
your school uniform
when you went to the hotel?!
It wasn't at a hotel...!
Damn it, you're
doing this on purpose!
Fine I'll tell you...
...but only because I don't
want you guys making up lies.
Sweet!
It's about time!
Misato...!
Yamada...!
I'm seriously gonna kill you.
Gah, I hate this...
but let's start from the top.
Shut the hell up
and go to bed already!
Takeshita did it in
her boyfriend's room
after ninth grade graduation.
Shut up!
Go to sleep!
How'd Katase get
her Vagistan occupied?
Shut up!
Go to sleep!
I wanna know more about her...
Like, anything really.
I do want to tell
her my feelings, but...
...on the other hand...
I think going to places with
each other is kinda cool, too...
We're seeing things
we've never seen before,
which means we get
to experience it together.
I like that.
Okay...
This is the main
part of the temple...
Which means...
She seems to be
really into temples.
Quiet... like... a... ninja.
This is perfectly deserted
and out of the tourist zone!
Now, I just have to get
cherry stump back here...
How do I manage that...?
Duh!
I'll send him an email...!
Weird...
I wonder why I can
message my feelings
better than just
talking in person.
What's that...?
D'ya get an email?
Weird...
It must be spam.
Online dating site or something.
I wonder what he's thinking.
I can't wait to
hear back from him!
You're gonna be waiting a while.
Dem's the breaks, sistah.
Now, we will all sit
and practice meditation...
Renounce all
your earthy desires...
And do not be trapped
in worldly thoughts...
If I see you relax your focus,
I will then strike you...
If you are struck...
please bow.
I gotta be grateful
for getting hit?
Thank you, Mistress Yamada!
I've been very naughty!
You'll be doing that a lot.
What if I don't
get the opportunity
to tell her how I feel...?
And just think...
...If I did, that could
change everything...
You're right...
Make love to me...
Like that would happen.
Is he having
Earthly desires or not?
He could at least
make up his mind.
Her thoughts are
in perfect order.
This girl is a
genuine inspiration.
She has already
mastered the way of Zen.
Keiichi...
Oh, brother,
oh brother where art thou?
I'll tear Yamada
into trashy little pieces!
Earthly desires are
swirling around in her mind,
but she shows
no trace of it at all.
What formidable
willpower this girl possesses!
There are
one hundred eight
Earthly desires in
one's heart...
One hundred eight...
By casting them
aside, you'll then be able
to clearly see the
path you seek.
Cast them aside,
and see the path I seek...
I wanna get laid...!
Oh, yeah!
I seek fornicating
with Kosuda...!
Bow chicka bow wow!
She's impressively decisive!
This PYT has already
achieved enlightenment!
B Gata H Kei.
On your left,
you can see Ogre Brand Tour's
Kyoto branch office building.
This building has
a thirty--year history.
It started out as
a main warehouse--
Wake up you
insensitive jerks and listen
to what the boring
lady has to say!
Yamada...
I haven't even been able to
spend a second alone with him!
Favorite non--frog?
The sales guy alien
was my favorite.
Move faster, you lazy freaks!
Once the boat tour is over,
we've just got the
trip back home...
I bet I'm not gonna get the
chance to tell her at all now.
What's she doing?
What the crap?
We haven't moved on to any other
bases this entire freaking trip!
However...
if I work on him while
we're riding the boat,
maybe we can find a spot
on the train for copulation!
Yamada...!
I have to have you...!
I have to have you now!
Agh!
Rock out!
Cock out!
Yamada, what are you doing?!
Yamada, we better get on
the boat now or we'll miss it...
Huh?
What the hell...?
You two have literally
just missed the boat!
They left us.
What are we gonna do?
I have to tell you that I lo~
The trip causes a great fuss.
You guys are lucky!
You got a whole boat chartered
for just the two of you!
I'm finally sort of
alone with him...
I hope he's ready to have
the hell seduced out of him!
I see Mister Happy
is happy to see me.
Who am I kidding?
Holding his hand will
probably make him blow.
I'm so excited I feel like
I'm gonna explode.
I'm finally alone with her...
...sort of.
We're surrounded by all
this amazing scenery...
...it's the perfect time
to say something.
If I don't take
this opportunity,
I might not be able to tell
her 'til after we graduate...
Then, we probably won't see each
other again for,
like, ten whole years.
Yamada?
Hey, Yamada!
Do you know that loser?
No, never seen him before.
Hey, limp dick!
Quit your slacking!
No!
I don't want things to
end up like that with her!
Ohmigah! Hands...!
We can totally hold hands!
Gently...
Bulging.
It knows what
I'm thinking before I do!
So, we're going to sit here
like two frogs on a rock.
Is it gonna end like this
without anything happening?
Bummer.
We came this far
and we're finally alone,
but we're still about to
go back without a single
new base being covered...!
Is that really okay
with you, Kosuda...?
A high school trip is
a once in a lifetime thing...!
Once in a sexy,
super hot lifetime!
I can do it...
Just say the words...
I'm in...
I'm in lo...
This sucks...
Um...
Yamada...
I want to tell you something.
--I think you should know I'm in
--Jerk overboard!
You jack wagon!
After the way you've treated me,
you deserve
to fall in the river!
What did I do?
Man I can't believe
the trip is already over...
That was way too fast.
We never got the chance to
talk to Kyoto chicks, either.
We are not cool, my friends...
Even girls from our
school won't talk to us.
Yamada...
Nothing happened...
--Three entire days...
--Uh oh, I think we've lost her.
Three. Entire. Days...
...and nada.
Hey, Yamada...!
I heard that you
and Kosuda got to
ride on a boat tour
all by yourselves...
Did anything happen?
What?
Why don't you try looking
at him and then looking
at me and not
asking that again?!
Yeah...
It's cool...
I'm sorry...
And a bit relieved.
Get away from me!
Why are you so angry?!
Kosuda, don't
let that bum you out.
You got to spend time
with her alone, right?
Sounds awesome if you ask me.
Yeah, you two are
in different leagues.
This meat is
really good, you guys.
I guess...
Yeah, you're right.
Different leagues?
Is that why she got so upset...?
It makes sense though.
But then, why~
I dunno...
she's really confusing.
Are you feeling all
right Kosuda you look
kinda sick and
you're not eating at all...
In that case...
Can I have your meat?
Wow, way to
be sensitive, dude.
You are such a good
friend it's not even funny.
When we get back to Tokyo,
can I stop by your
house for a bit?
Yeah, sure.
I don't see why not.
Whatever!
You don't own me,
school trip couple!
You're gonna break
up tomorrow anyway!
Not that I blame you
or that that made sense,
but turn down
the bitterness, lady.
Wonderful news.
Nothing at all good
happened to Yamada.
I had fun, though.
I got the chance to meet
students from other schools.
I bought a special
souvenir for Keiichi, too!
Wow, Miyano!
You bought a lot of
crap to take home, huh?
Yeah...
They're for my family, Kazuki,
and accidentally for Kosuda too.
That's nice,
but you can't actually give
it to him because
that would be weird.
Misato!
Do tell, did anything
exciting happen?
As a matter of fact it did!
A group of guys from
another school totally
talked to me,
and it was awesome!
I don't think asking
for directions counts...
...like at all.
Tokyo...!
Arriving at Tokyo!
Everyone's dismissed.
You're to go home
immediately, okay?
No exceptions!
The trip's not over until
you get home, understood?!
Can we go drown my
sorrows in sugary soda!
Can't...
Sorry. I promised to
meet someone after this.
No way! You are not
meeting your boyfriend!
Hey there...
Remember me?
The next stop is Oosedo...
After Oosedo,
this train will not make its
next stop until Igarashi...
I can't believe
nothing happened...
What's the deal, anyway?
Doesn't Kosuda like me anymore?
This is starting
to get ridiculous...
I dunno; maybe I just
need to find a different guy.
Yamada, wait!
What the~?
What are you doing?
Catching up!
Catching up with what?
I've been trying
to catch up with you
ever since we switched trains...
...but I ended up
helping a little kid
that was all
alone during rush hour.
Then, someone thought I was
a pervert, which wasn't fun.
He followed me all this way...
That's not a
"nothing happened" at all.
That is totally a
"something happened"!
There's nothing to
discuss, Kosuda.
Please!
You have to listen to me!
No, it doesn't matter...
Look, I'm not even
into you, okay?
Listen to me!!!
It does matter...
I have something to say to you.
It matters...
because I...
It matters because I...
lo...
Lo...
Looooo...
You...
I did it!
I finally told her how I feel
and it wasn't even a lie...!
I might not have
looked the coolest...
But I'm still glad
that I did it...
No matter how she responds,
I know I'll be okay...
That's not true.
What did he say?
I couldn't hear him at all!
Lo...
Like wearing
see--through lingerie?
Live for streaking?
Maybe I heard him wrong...
but I swear he said love...
I mean, if he followed
me home just to tell me,
it would have to be good, right?
What an idiot!
Talk about living
in a dream world...!
I mean, as if!
Who does that photo
fan boy think he is?
Someone seems to
be overcompensating,
It's not like I'm happy
about it or anything...
But at least this will guarantee
I'll get to have sex with him.
Although, what if I'm wrong...?
He might not have said
what I think he probably said.
I like you better
with makeup on.
You have bad skin.
That stupid virgin photographer!
If that's what he really thinks,
wait till he gets a
load of me all naked!
No matter how angry she gets,
she's always ready to go.
Lo... Lo...
Huh?
Well, let me think...
He could have meant lecher.
No surely that's not it...
Maybe lewd.
I don't even know you...
Like there could be a guy who
wouldn't fall in love with me?
Right...
So what are you gonna tell him.
Huh?
What do you mean?
He confessed
his feelings to you,
now you have to
tell him yours...
That's kind of how
these things work.
No way, that's dumb!
Why would I do that?
She is unbelievable...
Let's try this slower.
Do you like him, or would
you rather just be friends?
A... sex...
...friend.
A sex friend is
not a friend, okay?
So you gonna tell him
you don't like him, then?
I might have
been too hard on her.
No!
If I say I don't like him,
how will we have sex?
Seriously?
I'm still glad I told her...
...but I wonder if she
didn't understand me...
I should talk to her.
Yamada!
Yamada?!
Damn it!
Why do I always run away just
when it starts getting good?!
The flowing river
never stops and
yet the water
never stays the same.
Foam floats upon
the pools scattering,
reforming,
never lingering too long...
So it is with man and all his
dwelling places here on Earth.
Hey, it's Kosuda, can we talk?
I'll be in the photography
club room during lunch...
Yamada!
Talk to me!
I guess that must be her answer.
A big fat no.
How am I supposed
to know what it
means to like
someone or not...?!
I just want to get deflowered!
He makes me feel stupid,
but he's stupid!
Stupid!
♪ closing song ♪
That stupid Kosuda...
I don't understand what it means
to like someone or not, hello!
Do you know me?!
Wait, Kosuda!
We're in the classroom!
Everyone's here!
Hold on a sec!
I'm in love with you, Yamada!
You idiot!
Next time, I'll show
you how bold I can be!
The other story
is about field day!
See you next time!