Eros Deity here...
Today's the 18th of December.
Go!
I can't believe it's
almost Christmas Eve!
That will be the day!
I'm gonna get Kosuda's heart!
I already know what
kind of lingerie I'll wear!
Ogre Brand will
provide the protection!
And I've researched
several sexy positions!
It must be hard
for you to be that pretty and
perfect and yet still
be so painfully not a lady.
Chika...!
What do you think of this?!
I'm the present!
Merry Christmas!
Yet again.
Still not a lady.
Romantic Christmas Eve!
What does the
first kiss taste like?
Yamada!
Hey, I'm home!
I see that.
She brought a boy with her.
Hey.
He's super hot, too.
Well, hello there.
I'm so stupid!
I can't believe I hit on
my own sister's boyfriend!
What's with your sister?
Is she gonna be okay?
Don't worry about it.
That's kind of her thing.
So who's your
favorite character?
I like the girl the best.
I don't understand how
she got such a cute guy...?
Her last boy was cute too...
And the one before that...
And the one before that!
Noo.
She can't be more
popular than me!
She's way short,
and I'm so much prettier.
Don't forget about boobs.
Mine are huge compared to hers!
By the way, Chika, your
sister's like really pretty.
Did I upset you?
I'm fine!
I'm just proud of
my sister, that's all!
Don't worry!
Because she's nothing
compared to you!
Thank you.
Well, bye then.
Yeah, I'll see you later.
So, it turns out you're
pretty popular, huh...?
You ever gonna narrow
it down to one guy?
Yeah, eventually...
I'm not in any rush though.
After all when I think
about it, I'm still a child...
I've never known
true love, not really...
Don't get me wrong I adore
being lavished with all
the attention...
I love it when
boys say they like me
or that I'm pretty
or buy me name--
brand merchandise
for no reason...
All this and still a child, too.
Only three more days
left until Christmas Eve!
What am I gonna do...?
It's almost Christmas,
and I don't have
a boyfriend, yet!
I don't know...
Come watch DVDs
with me as usual?
No way...!
That's something only a
pathetic loser would do!
Yes, I know.
That's why I'm
asking you to do it.
They're so funny.
I'm jealous of them.
I mean, they get to have
such an easy Christmas Eve...
You and I will be busy.
What are you talking about?
Taking care of
unwanted hair and stuff.
The constitution says couples
have to have sex that night.
You're kidding, right?
But couples still
do do it, don't they?
Yes.
So...
I'm guessing you have
a date set up with Kosuda?
No, he hasn't asked me out yet.
What?
I can't help it.
I like the show.
A kid detective?
Really?
I want to ask her out
for Christmas Eve...
I think she might
even say yes...
Man, I don't know...
She could just be
waiting for me to ask her...
I'm gonna do it!
Yamada...?
Are you free Christmas Eve?
Wanna go out with me?
--No, go out with me!
--No, go with me!
Oh...
I can't ask her out now.
Okay...
I'm finally alone with her.
What's he waiting for?
Ask me out already?!
Hey!
Wait a minute...
Am I ready to ask her out?
I don't even know
what we do on a date.
On top of that,
it's Christmas Eve!
Am I supposed to
get her a present...?
What about dinner?
If I pay will that insult her?
Whoopsie! Someone's
not used to asking girls out!
Gah...
What is his freakin' deal...?
Fine, I'll make this as
easy for him as possible.
So, Christmas is just
a few more days away.
I bet the hotel district
is gonna register
on the Richter scale that night.
Oh yeah!
Right there!
Oh, God!
That's nice!
I think I freaked him out!
Yamada!
Are you Christmas Eve on free?
Please?!
Well, if you insist, I guess you
can spend time with me...
Just don't take me
to someplace lame, okay?
Okay.
Yay!
V-Card, I just wanted
to say goodbye.
It's been great knowing you!
I wonder where Kosuda
is planning on taking me...
I'm sure we'll start
with a romantic dinner...
...then head on over
to a nice hotel suite.
Man it's pricey...
I should've picked
up some part time work.
She really is sweet...
Just weird.
Hi--yah...!
Two more days to go!
Takeshita!
Um, hey...
So I'm going out with
Yamada on Christmas Eve...
...and I'm not exactly
sure what I should
do about getting her a present.
Easy. It's the
thought that counts!
That's what they say...
Could you give me some advice
on what she'd like, though...?
I mean, I...
I want her to like it, but I
don't even know where to go.
Oh, okay...
If you want to know the truth,
she just wants to
go to a hotel...
Seriously.
This is good...
I've got the present
taken care of.
Now where to?
Takashi...!
Hey, is that a present?!
Tell me who it's for.
Are you going on a date?
Is it with Yamada?
Stop.
Nice!
Well played, sir...
Ooh, let me plan
out the date for you...!
I'm awesome at
that kind of thing.
So you say...
Have you ever gone
on a date before?
First of all, you two need to go
see a wrestling match together.
Hey...!
I asked if you've
ever been on a date!
Then you'll have to go get
some barbeque to
build up your stamina.
Quit ignoring me!
I asked you a question!
And then tell her how you feel!
That'll make her ready for
some serious wrestling!
You're just trying to
torture me, aren't you?!
I'm kidding!
Hi--yah...!
Finally, the holy of
Holy Nights has arrived.
Gorgeous!
Okay, I'm ready!
Looks good.
Now get changed,
or you're gonna be late.
Here.
Put this on.
Now for accessories.
Jeez, Kazuki...
Your handwriting is awful.
Hey, stranger.
I'm here.
Hey.
Incredible...
Every guy out here
is checking her out!
I bet they're all wondering
why she's with me.
Soak it all in, Kosuda!
I bet you're thanking
your lucky stars for running
into me that day
at the bookstore!
Normally I'd freak
out and run off just
when things started
getting interesting!
But not tonight!
I'm not letting you get away!
Hey, come back here!
Let go of him!
This girl's ready
to go, big time!
I feel like such an idiot!
Whatever. This is
all Kosuda's fault anyway.
What is taking so long?!
I'm tired of waiting...
Luckily I have
a technique I've been
mastering for
years that should work...
No one can resist falling
for me after a direct hit!
Special trick...
Yamada eyes.
Crap, my fork fell.
Oopsie!
Watch where you
point that thing!
Come on...
He's really starting
to piss me off!
Yamada seems mad at me.
Thanks a lot, Kazuki, your
date plan completely failed...
What am I supposed to do now?
What...?
A kiss?
How am I supposed to do that?
She looks like she'll kill me
if I go anywhere near her!
If he doesn't get over here and
kiss me soon,
I'm gonna kill him.
Oh wait...
I almost forgot.
I, uh, Yamada?
What do you want?
I wanted...
to give you this.
Wow...
Thank you...
Can I open it now?
Yeah.
Pierced earrings...
Yamada, wait!
Great.
She hated it.
He got me pierced
earrings as a gift.
In other words...
I'd like to pierce
your hole too!
That's gotta be it!
Good job, Kosuda!
I was starting
to lose faith in you!
All right!
Let's go!
Okay, but, where
are we going exactly?
Here we go!
Why are we here?
Hotels by the hour?
We...
We shouldn't be here.
Unless that's what she wants...?
Yamada eyes...
Search mode!
I wish I could figure her out.
I have no idea
what she's thinking!
Believe me...
it's not all that complicated.
I just need to
find the right hotel.
Yes!
This place seems perfect!
That was so great.
How embarrassing!
They totally just had sex!
Eeahhh!
Oh...
We're out of the hotel district.
I think I can kiss her here!
This is the right mood...
isn't it?
It doesn't matter...!
I'm doing it...!
Here I go!
Sorry, we went too far.
Yamada!
Yamada...
I...
I think I...
I think I'm...
in...
Love...?
Am I...?
Am I in love with her?
I mean, she's pretty,
so I wasn't thinking
about it too much.
But all those things I don't get
about her make me wonder...
I feel like I want to kiss
her now more than ever.
Kosuda?
I don't know what to do!
He's finally making a move...
I'm so happy...!
Why am I scared though...?
And why do I want
to run again...?
No...
Not this time!
Here I go!
I plan on celebrating tomorrow!
Damn it!
I messed things up again!
We're totally kissing!
On top of that,
I think the momentum
forced my tongue in
his mouth, too!
I, kissed her...
Yamada...
I kissed Yamada.
I don't care about
all that stupid crap...!
I'll follow Yamada to
the ends of the Earth...!
I kissed Yamada!
Yes!
Oh good.
He's finally into it...
Way to go, Yamada!
Sex should be right
around the corner now!
Yamada...?
Where did you go?
Hellooooo?!
Yamada!
Oh, what am I gonna do...?
This is getting way too intense
and I don't have a
clue what's going on at all...
I'm so confused; I don't
know what to do anymore!
Snap out of it!
Now!
You sound like a silly
girl who doesn't even
want to sleep
with a hundred guys!
This is bad!
What's happened to Yamada?
And what's going to happen
to her sexual future?
B Gata H Kei.
I thought kissing was
going to be so easy.
I don't know~
What am I gonna do...?
I don't think I can
handle any more of this.
You need to get it together!
You've come too far
to run away this time!
My chest...
It hurts...
Ow ...
I can't face Kosuda, now...
I can't.
Come on!
I can't go back empty handed!
Let's go to the make out park!
Screw this stupid date plan...
The only thing that matters
to me is being with Yamada.
I just...
...don't know how to make
that happen at the moment.
Yamada!
Please wait for me!
I'll go with you anywhere!
Except there...
I can't really...
do that...
Can I...
I'm sorry, I've gotta take this.
Who is it?
Yamada?
Yeah...
Hey, what's up?
Is everything okay...?
Really?
Look at you go!
Thanks, I'm feeling
pretty good about it so far...
I just, I don't know what
I'm supposed to do next.
Help!
Try to breathe and remember
not to force anything.
What's important is how you guys
feel about each other, okay...?
I'm so excited for you;
I bet Kosuda's happy too, huh?
Uhh, well yeah!
It's not every day he gets to
kiss a wicked hot girl like me.
I mean, I'm way better
than what he deserves.
Yeah, you'll be fine.
First kiss, huh...
Now that I'm thinking clearly,
it's not that big of a deal.
Everyone kisses eventually...
What's more,
I bet they're doing a lot
more exciting stuff
than kissing...!
You guys will be, right...?
Later on tonight
you'll totally get it
on like donkey kong, won't you~?
Everything okay?
That's right...!
I can't abandon my
lifelong dream of getting it
on with a hundred
different guys!
That would be silly!
I don't have time to pout in the
stall of a public bathroom!
Right...!
And don't forget to wash your
hands before you leave.
Come on, we're going!
Okay!
I think.
Where are we going?
A park?
It's so stuffy
I can literally see it...
It must be pretty hot in there.
Oh, yeah!
Where the heck are we?!
Hello everybody,
and thanks for joining us
in Tokyo's most popular
make--out park!
The rumors were all right...
They say it gets
so hot in this park
you don't even know
it's winter...
I did so awesome!
Yamada must have
brought us here by accident.
She must be so
embarrassed right now!
Oh, yeah.
Wow...
this place is so cool...!
I'll have to bring
Takeshita some time.
She'd love it here.
Yeah, no thanks!
This is it!
Is this what she wants...?
For real...?
It has to be...
...which is awesome,
because I'm dying over here.
Excuse me...
But this is backwards isn't it?
I've come so far...!
Now I'm gonna go for it
with everything I've got!
That is what I'm talkin' about!
Listen to your instinct,
also known as what your
body is telling you to do!
Don't hold back,
and let her rip!!!
I'm so hot...
My body...
it's starting to
feel really warm...
You're pathetic.
Geez, if I keep
waiting for Kosuda,
we'll be here until morning...
Whatever...
I can do it!
Uh...
Yamada?
Crap!
What do I do now...?
Damn it, why don't I ever think
before I do stuff like this...?
I need to calm down,
I'm freaking out like I
always do when
I'm afraid I'm not ready...
But I'm pretty
sure I'm ready now...
Whoa!
She's on my lap!
I'm on his lap!
I'm not even sure
how it happened...
But who cares?
This is perfect!
I wonder how Yamada's doing...
I'd like to think she ended
up just going home, but...
Time for me to feast!
She might be crazy,
but there's no way...
Presenting the 'no way' thing
she was talking about.
She's looking at me...
...and I think it's
like a good thing.
She's so gorgeous...
I'm the luckiest guy
in the world!
I wonder...
Would she get upset...
if I just touched
them a little bit?
What?
Is he trying to
touch my breasts?
Oh no!
What if he thinks
they're too small?!
What if he's into big melons...!
I need to snap out of it.
They're boobs.
And they're mine.
He's gonna love them!
What is taking you so long?!
Touch them already!
Wow, they're intense,
aren't they?
Hey, boobies...
What's up...?
Yamada says it's all good.
I should've worn a super
push--up double padded bra
and thrown some chicken cutlets
in there for good measure...!
That would have been a terrible
idea because if I end up
taking the bra off, he would
have found out the truth anyway!
Kay...? Does that
mean she likes this?
I hope he likes this.
Well...
They're definitely round shaped.
That's pretty obvious.
They're kind of hard, though.
Honestly, I can't really
feel them all that well
through her bra
and clothes and stuff.
He's gotta be totally
infatuated with me by now!
How long is he gonna keep
holding them like that?
It's been forever!
Try...
moving them!
I mean what you were
doing was perfectly fine!
Yamada!
Kosuda...
I'm so confused...
I've known her all this time,
and I still can't figure
out what she's thinking.
I want to have sex!
I don't think there's anyone
easier to figure out than her.
I wanna go all
the way with her...
But is that what
you want, Yamada?
Whoa, they're
having like, for real sex...
And it's really explicit...
I don't wanna see any more!
They need to put all of
that back where it belongs!
Um... what are
they doing out here?
No, I can't!
I can't have sex
in a place like this!
Ugh... why are
you such a prude...?
It's usually better
when people are watching.
Yes!
Go for it, dude!
Come on, man!
It could be our only chance...!
It's unacceptable...
No.
We can't let them
take pictures of Yamada!
Well, this blows.
They're not gonna have
sex this year at all!
♪ closing song ♪
Agh, I feel a breeze, and it's
making me totally nervous...!
I'm holding my skirt down,
but I still think my heart is
gonna thump out of my
chest, because today,
I'm not wearing--Oh crap!
Thanks a lot breeze!
Um...
Yamada?
Yamada is going to criticize
the world of politics?!
And, an unexpected
Valentine's adventure.
These two stories next time...!