What's up, viewers?
Spring has sprung, and that
means it's a new school year!
Wow, she's like beyond pretty.
Hey guys...
Check her out.
Is she a model or something?
She's way too hot
to be a freshman.
I wonder if she's a sophomore.
Take it all in, freshmen.
Take it all in...
The girls want to be me
and the guys want to do me.
A hundred friends with benefits!
This is your year!
So says Lady Still a Virgin.
She gets an A for
effort but an F in ing.
So I've decided to do
an instant smackdown on
Kosuda and move to
the next guy like now.
Oh...! Wait...!
By instant, I didn't
mean prematurely instant.
Like you'd know?!
And who are you
talking to, anyway?!
You're right...
I bet Kosuda
will go super quick.
But...
Who's to say...?
Oh hey, it's Chika.
I didn't know she
was going to our school.
I hope she's not shocked when
she sees how popular I am.
She's gonna be devastated.
Oh my gah, you're so pretty...
Do you wanna go out with me?
Don't go out with him,
go out with me!
Or you could
just be my girlfriend!
See...?
Way devastated.
Yeah, I can see that.
I wonder how
she'll ever survive.
Kanejo is coming!
I can't stand that sparkle!
Dude, she's in our class?
Awesome.
We're in the same
class with her again.
Hey, Yamada!
Hey...
So how's it going?
I have no idea what
that meant, as usual.
Where are we sitting...?
Back here?
The very front row?
I can't see from that
far back anymore
for no reason in particular.
Whose camera is that...
Of course!
It's Kosuda's.
She's so stupid.
Why won't she just admit it?
Hey Yamada!
Hey Takeshita!
We're in the same
class this year!
Isn't that great?
That's so cool!
Yeah...
It's the best
news I've heard all day.
Right...?
I can't believe Kosuda
is this class too...
And this year I swear, I~
What?
Oh! Nothing!
Just being silly!
She was not being silly...
She doesn't do silly.
What if she's planning to
burst Kosuda's cherry?
That's not exactly
how it works, but...
I'm still gonna
go with I doubt it.
We're still in the
same class together!
This year will totes rock!
What's up girls...?
How's it going?
It's going great because
I know this year is my
year to get a tall, dark
and handsome boyfriend!
Right...
totally gonna happen.
Well, they do say sophomore
year is like the best year!
All the freshmen girls will
be so freakin' scared of us!
No way...
She's sitting
next to me again...!
This year, I'm gonna get closer
to her no matter what!
Well, we may be in a new class,
but at least my status
as queen remains secure.
Tell me you did
not just seriously
refer to yourself as royalty.
I love her.
Who is she?
I don't know but
she's literally sparkling.
Good morning...
How is everyone doing?
Uh oh, so...
...looks like there's a problem
in court, your queenship.
No...!
Off with her head!
Being in the same
class with you is an honor!
What's your name, anyway?
I'm Kyoka Kanejo...
So nice to meet you!
Hi!
Wait, I remember her now...
She's the one who almost
beat you in that stupid
school beauty pageant
thing last year.
Exactly, we're talking
about a loser, okay?
That girl is so
not a threat to me.
You've come back here
from America, right?
Yeah. You transferred the day
before the school festival.
During the pageant, I couldn't
see your face that well.
If I'd known you then, Kanejo,
I would have voted for you.
Same here!
And here!
Why aren't teenagers allowed
to buy shotguns online?!
C'mon!
I bet that's
because it's illegal.
Kosuda...
...why are you looking at
her instead of me?
You can buy an Atlantis Tantric
Buddhism kit for cursing--
Seriously?
Okay everybody.
Time to take your seats.
Welcome to my classroom.
My name is Akai and
I'm your homeroom teacher.
Let's have a
great year, all right?
Okay!
Holy jeez...
School just started.
What's she doing now?
Who does he think he is?
Why don't you tell
him you don't want
him looking at any
girl other than you?
I'd die before I'd say that...!
And I shouldn't have to; looking
shouldn't even be an option!
Someone doesn't
like sharing her throne.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah...
blah.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Blah, blah--blah,
blah--blah--blah---blah, blah.
Excellent, Miss Kanejo...
Your lovely pronunciations put
native speakers to shame!
Thank you, sir.
She's amazing...
Kanejo is the best!
That was beautiful...
Just what we'd
expect from Kanejo!
No one is as talented
as you, Kanejo!
She's pretty popular, huh?
Well, they say Americans
have no morals...
So, you know, she probably
has sex like all the time.
I'm so jealous of her!
I resent your dirty prejudices.
What the hell is that?
Well, I cooked it so it's gonna
taste good, no matter what...
Tastegasm starts now!
OMG, Kanejo...
That looks so good!
Like, wow!
They're totally shining!
Can I try some?
Really?
Kanejo made all this?
Let me try.
Yep...
It is delicious.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to have a bite too?
Wow...
That's delicious!
Yes...!
It's like I wandered into a
mythical forest where even
the deepest of fried foods still
taste refreshingly like the
forest and the sun combined
in heavenly wonder!
Kanejo, please...
Will you share
your recipe with me?
Even Miyano
is falling for that skank!
I thought you were a member
of my faction, you traitor face!
Seriously?
The following day at school!
Good morning, Yamada...
How are you?
Way to act like you're
in middle school...
Why does she even matter
to you in the first place?
Isn't it obvious...?
I can't let that hooker get off
thinking she's better than me!
Someone's acting
like she's in love.
What...?
In Love...?
No way!
Not with a jerky jerk like
him who thinks he can
just change his mind
whenever he wants to?
Today we vote for
our new class rep.
Who's up for the job, kids?
What about any recommendations?
Why's he keep looking at her?!
I think we should choose Kanejo!
Yeah, good idea!
She'd be perfect for it!
You guys are sweet...!
I would be honored.
Since you're all insisting...
I guess I have
no other choice...
I'd simply love to.
So, basically all
the super pretty girls,
are kind of the
same person, right?
Good...
We have our new class rep.
But only if you
all are really sure.
We are!
What the crap?
I turn away for two seconds
and she's the new class rep?
Why is she standing
like that, too?
I mean, who stands at an
angle and puts her weight
ever so slightly on
her right foot while tilting
her stupid head and
making that cheesy face?
Does she think she's
a model or something?!
I can't let her have this!
I gotta get attention
back pronto!
Okay, moving on.
Let's decide who'll
be class secretary.
I'll do it! Me!
I will! I will! Me!
Up next!
School disciplinary member.
Damn it!
No one can see my face this way!
Here, Kanejo, let me help you.
No, no, I can do it!
Oh no...
I wouldn't want
to bother anyone.
You're not a bother.
Well played...
Seriously.
What?
Are you okay?
I can pick them up for you.
You are all such gentlemen.
No!
What the hell?!
I hate her!
Maybe you should stop
trying to sabotage her.
But Takeshita...!
I want to be popular and
pretty, not just pretty!
Do you seriously expect
me to sympathize?
Anyway why don't you try
a more positive approach?
A positive approach?
Oh yeah...!
I could become a famous actress
or model to win their love back!
You could...
I could be like a pinup girl
or something sexy like that!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Stop right there, Kosuda...!
What the hell is in your hand?
Is that who I think it is?!
--Sonofabitch!
--Look, it's Kanejo!
I buy this camera
magazine every month.
I knew I'd seen
her somewhere before,
but I couldn't quite
put my finger on it...
This issue is from last year.
When I saw her, I figured
I'd take it to school with me.
Oh, man...!
It's not fair!
How cool!
I've never met anyone who's
been in a magazine before!
Me either!
Love her!
You must be an
actress or a model
or something like that, right?
No, no!
I'm so embarrassed!
My brother took this picture.
So whose magazine is this?
Uhh, it's mine.
Koishikawa!
Don't tell me you're
a photographer!
I'm in the photography club...
...so I guess I am.
Why is he acting
like such a weirdo...?!
You can tell her what
your actual name is, idiot!
The magazine holds a
contest every month and the
winner gets to have their
picture featured on the cover.
Winning that cover shot
is a pretty big deal.
Oh...?
You must have
a talented brother.
Well, he has a ton of hobbies...
For whatever reason,
he wins every contest he enters.
Oh, that's different then.
It's not like she's a
famous actress or anything.
It was just a contest.
He could have taken
a picture of a stupid,
really fat tree and still won.
You're thinking out loud again.
Selection of the subject
is evaluated as well.
Yamada!
Behind you!
Look behind you!
So, Kosuda was only
looking at Kanejo
because he remembered her from
some random magazine cover...?
I'm glad that you were wrong,
and he didn't have
a change of heart.
Well, duh--why would he?
Think about it...
My charms are like
freaking hypnotic, okay...?
I mean, I am a potential
friend with benefits, hello!
True!
I think it's finally time to
allow him to have sex with me...
Loyal servitude should
always be rewarded
with a giving spirit,
don't you think?
I think you really piss
me off sometimes.
Friends with
bennies for the win!
Wonderful you're home.
Welcome back, Miss.
Yes, thank you, Ms. Ichihara.
You must be exhausted, my dear.
Shall I bring you
something to drink.
Tea, perhaps?
Yes, please.
Green Earl Grey
sounds delightful.
Whatever I can do, Miss.
I can't believe
what a graceful and
humble young
lady Kanejo has become.
She is a darling girl and most
certainly defines 'well--bred.'
There's no doubt; I'm
the prettiest girl in school...
If anybody should be
pageant queen, it's me.
Stupid Yamada...
I was horrified when I lost
that beauty contest to you.
Horrified!
I've never been so
humiliated in my life!
How can I forgive
such disrespect?
I can't, so I'll take
everything away from you!
Your popularity.
Your friends.
I can't wait to see
you cry your eyes out
after your life
has been shattered!
Miss Kanejo I have your
Green Earl Grey Tea.
Oh, thank you, Ms. Ichihara.
B Gata H Kei!
Hey, that's my line!
Good morning!
Morning!
Hey guys, what's up?
Look, the gorgeous Kanejo girl.
She always looks
so perfect and pretty.
It's weird because I
really want her to like me
but I also kinda want
her to die a little.
Excuse me!
We... just wanted
to say hi, that's all.
Oh, well hello!
Hi!
Her smile is perfect, too!
She's totally got to have
like a way hot boyfriend!
He must be awesome!
Behind that rosy smile is...
Kanejo's dark secret.
I don't care what it takes,
I am going to be
first in everything...!
That's what being a member of
the Kanejo family is all about!
I have to do something
about that gross Yamada...
She needs to suck it up
and admit I should
have been the winner
of that pageant...
...not her.
More importantly,
I have to destroy her
before he comes back.
I've worked too
hard to just allow a
B--Cup--at--Best
Freak--of--Nature
ruin everything for me.
But what can I do...?
Of course...
It's so obvious;
I can steal her boyfriend!
That poseur has to have a man,
and I bet he's really
good looking too!
Yeah, no, not really.
By stealing Yamada's
boyfriend and ripping him
from her desperate
and disgusting arms,
she'll learn how much more
powerful I am than her!
I am the real queen, so kneel
in fear you little amateur!
Stalking is just not
my style, so spying is
simply not an option
at this juncture...
Oh no!
I suppose there's nothing wrong
with asking her
directly, is there...?
Plus, watching her crumble in
person is too
delectable to pass up.
Oh, Yamada...
Enjoy your boyfriend while you
can for he's about to be mine!
Miss, dinner is ready.
I do hope you're hungry.
Oh, yes, I am.
Thank you so much!
I wonder if Yamada is
doing anything after school.
I should ask her out...
I can totally ask her out.
We are kind of dating...
You can do this!
Yamada...!
--Yamada!
--Will you go~
What the?
What do you want?!
Excuse me...
I think we should get
better acquainted.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
Uh...
excuse me?
Why don't you come on over
to my place after school?
We can have tea
and bond and stuff.
Tea?
Is she planning to
poison me or something?
I can't die at
that hooker's house!
Not while I have a
really nice collection
of smutty books hiding
under my bed.
Come on, you're not scared
of anything are you?
What?!
No!
I'll totally come over!
Oh that's wonderful!
'Scuse...
me.
Jeez, your house is in BFE.
Are we, like,
ever gonna get there?
Technically we are there;
we've been on the grounds
for a little while now.
Who has a house
that obnoxiously huge?!
Hello, ladies...
Welcome home!
And welcome to
the Kanejo residence.
She is like, way super rich.
Well...
isn't that crude.
And awesome!
She hightailed
it to the corner fast.
I bet she was intimidated
by my family's obvious
wealth and went to
hide where she felt safe.
It's your own fault; you
entered the enemy's lair.
And get used to hiding
in the background,
'cause that's
where you're staying!
This room is crazy huge!
And it's just for you;
that doesn't make any sense!
No, don't be ridiculous.
This is just the
living room area...
My bedroom and personal
study are separate...
You're so adorable for
thinking that though.
Your panties are made of silk!
You got money!
Don't be intimidated.
It's a lot to take in.
Ooh, what's in the there?
Get your hands off my box.
Uhh, why?
There you are ladies.
Enjoy your tea.
What are you waiting for?
Go ahead and drink...
It's not like it's
poisoned or anything.
I wonder what's in
that stupid box of hers...
She did not want me
looking in there at all.
I get it...
Oh, she dirty.
What is she thinking about?
By the way, Yamada...
I...
Well, to be perfectly honest,
I would love to
be friends with you,
but for some strange reason you
keep objecting to
every single thing I say.
What?!
What are you talking about?
I do not!
You just did it.
It's quite revealing,
you know...
You must be
very worried about me.
And, don't get me wrong,
I completely understand...
Look at you.
You're so pretty
and used to being
the most popular
girl at school...
Well, until I showed up...
But...
Our school only has room for one
pageant queen, isn't that right?
I knew you'd draw
your claws eventually...
By the way they're not as
scary as you think they are.
Nice try, though.
Competition makes me hotter,
so I say we find out who
is the ultimate queen!
Are you in or out?
I suppose this path
must be our fate.
Now we can find out which
one gets to be on top!
Yeah, we will!
Let's get it on, girlie!
Which one gets to be on top...?
Is she talking about what I
think she's talking about?
I don't think I can
do this, Yamada.
There's nothing at all
to be frightened of...
Now just lie back and relax.
Ew!
I can't do other girls!
Not that there's anything
wrong with that, but no.
Are you okay?
Yep!
So, how are we gonna
solve this thing?
Another beauty pageant?
No, but I have a question...
Who's your boyfriend?
My whofriend?
I was hoping I'd get to
come here with Yamada.
Naps...!
Hey...!
What did I miss?
Anything good?
Boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend!
Then what do you call Kosuda?
Um, well what's it to ya?
I might as well
tell you the truth.
In one month...
Mark my words,
I am going to make your
boyfriend leave you
and fall in love with me!
That's how I'm gonna win...
Now be a dear
and tell me about him...
I'm guessing he
goes to our school.
No way I'm telling her
I don't have boyfriend!
Hey...!
Again, what do
you think Kosuda is?!
You can find that
answer yourself...
It's basic info even a pretty
princess can figure out.
Fine. I don't need
your help anyway.
I can't believe
I just got out of that.
I hope everything is going well.
Would you like more tea, ladies?
Oh, yes...!
That sounds perfect,
Ms. Ichihara!
Jeez.
Bi--polar much?
Damn it!
I wanna take her down...!
Richie Bitch needs
a reality check, but,
she can't find out that I
don't have a boyfriend, either.
Kosuda!
What about Kosuda?!
Oh no!
I ruined my lens!
Yamada.
Prepare to lose your title.
It shall soon be mine, and then
he will return home to me...!
I wonder...
How much longer will
we be forced to be apart?
Even I have no control
over this painful distance...
Why does Harvard have
to be so far away?
I can't take this loneliness.
Our separation has
broken my heart...
...and there's only one cure.
Fingerprint verified.
Verifying voiceprint.
I love you.
Palm and
fingerprints validated...
Retina scan verified...
Welcome, Miss Kyoka.
My love...!
My love!!!
You love him too much...
Please, Miss,
this isn't healthy behavior.
Tell me what you
think of my idea...
I'm thinking about
setting up cameras in a
hundred different places
all around his school.
I think that's a crime!
My dear...
You're going to have to give
up on this foolishness...
Your love for him is not right.
No!
Don't say that!
Of all people,
you should understand
how I feel the most...
How dare you...?!
I've loved him ever
since I was a little girl.
Please Miss, I'm only telling
you this because I care.
But you're not making any sense!
I love him!
It's an improper love, Miss!
No.
Please...
That's not true!
What is wrong with being madly
in love with my own brother?!
So, so many things.
blah--blah--blah, Keiichi.
Blah blah...
blah--blah--blah, blah.
Blah, blah, blah...
It's from Kyoka.
Hey, big brother...
It's been so long.
How are you doing?
This is the 101st
message today...
She's gotta be bored!
I know my feelings will
be reciprocated one day...!
I'm never gonna give
up on my big brother!
Never!
If my first time isn't with you,
it won't be with anyone at all!!
Dear Lord...
I beg you...
Please, please...
keep that girl a virgin.
Oh, just you wait, Yamada!
I'll be the one to win
my brother's love,
and I if I have to
destroy you and become
the school queen to
make it happen, so be it!
♪ closing song ♪
What up, my peeps?!
It's me Yamada!
The summer is coming,
which means swimsuit season!
Enjoy my perfect body
that I've conditioned
just for this time of year!
Takeshita and Miyano...
Can you guys just watch today?
Um...
Yamada?
Then, my wild side is awakened!
Rawr!!
I'll get that cherry boy
if it's the last thing I do!
See ya next time!!!