[TOJI] Fine.
If you don't believe me,
I'll prove it!
[KAIRI, MOMO gasp]
[SAE]
Uh...
[KAIRI, MOMO gasp]
Now you know,
so leave us alone.
[SAE laughing]
At first I said no, I mean,
Momo was so in love with him,
it just didn't seem right.
But Toji kept begging,
so finally I agreed.
He's so persistent!
[SAE]
Uh. Hey!
You're late! I've
missed you so much!!
[laughs] Where are
we going after school?
[TOJI]
Wherever you wanna go, Sae.
Aren't you sweet?
Always putting my needs
before your own.
[KAKO]
Loser.
Poor girl.
She's so jealous of us.
[TEACHER]
On this next section,
I need you to choose the word
that best completes the sentence
listed in your book.
Notice that there are two words
that are similar. I'm looking
for the best answer...
[MOMO] I don't understand.
How could you do this to me?
Now you know, so leave us alone.
[MOMO]
Do you really love Sae?
No. I don't believe it.
[MOMO sighs]
[STUDENTS chatting]
[MOMO]
Wait!
Look, get it through
your head already,
I don't have any intention of
getting back together with you.
Toji how could we
get back together
when we never really broke
up in the first place?
It doesn't make sense.
And I'm not ready for it
to be over between us.
[TOJI]
You're being pathetic.
Please stop following me around.
You'll upset Sae.
[KAIRI] That jerk!
How could he?!
We were so in love!
How could he suddenly fall
for Sae? I don't understand.
[MOMO]
Uh?
[KAIRI] It's bad enough that
he left me, but for Sae?!
Not Sae!
Anyone but Sae!
I won't believe it! No!
No! No! No! No! No!
[MOMO]
What are you doing?
Nothing. That was
the voice of your heart.
Don't get mad at me!
[MOMO sighs]
I'm assuming your
emotions are so fried
that you can even
yell at me. Right?
It was all true, Kairi.
Every single thing you said.
Well then dump the worthless
piece of, trash!
You're too classy
for that loser anyway!
Don't talk about him like that!
I know he would never break
up with me willingly!
This is Sae's fault.
She must have threatened him.
Wow, you really do believe
in him, don't you, Momo?
Of course I do!
What we've built together
isn't something
you can just decide to
throw away one day.
I've had about
enough of this!
[MOMO]
Uh?
I still believe in you, Toji.
[SAE]
Waiting for him again?
[MOMO]
Uh?
It needs to stop.
Besides, all you're
doing is bothering him.
Oh. Am I? Well I'm sure
it's no bother that you're
probably blackmailing
him into going out with you.
What are you talking about?
Are you really that dumb?
I mean honestly, if you guys
were actually in love,
then why would Toji even listen
to anything I had to say?
This has nothing to do with me.
Toji's simply over you.
I think it's about time you
opened your eyes to that fact.
He mentioned to me that he even
felt a little sorry for you.
You became so clingy with him,
it kinda freaked him out.
Yeah. I think the word
that he used was 'stalker'.
Aw, come on pouty eyes.
Look, I'll be nice.
I'll help you find him.
Toji left through the back gate
about two minutes ago.
[MOMO gasps]
But it's not the brightest
move to go chasing
after a guy who's
trying to avoid you.
Uh? Fine.
Don't listen.
[MOMO]
She's lying!
Toji would never say
those horrible things.
[door bell rings]
[MOMO]
Or would he?
What now?
Oh, um...
Well, I...
I have a lot of homework to do.
Wait! Toji!
I don't know what
Sae said to you
that made you feel like you
had to break up with me but,
we can get through this.
Please say you
at least wanna try.
We can get through
anything together, Toji.
Right?
Toji! Toji!
[exhales]
[TOJI grunts]
[TOJI whimpers]
[MOMO]
It's so cold out here.
But I have to make
him understand.
He has to see that
I'll do anything for him.
Please, Toji, talk to me.
[sighs]
Go home.
The neighbors are gonna
start talking if you stay.
[TOJI] Here, take these
with you, throw them away.
But Toji, these are the pictures
we took at my birthday.
Yeah, I don't need
them anymore.
[MOMO gasps]
[TOJI]
Oh, throw this out, too.
[MOMO gasps]
[cracks]
[TOJI] Sorry.
Guess it slipped.
[MOMO]
Toji, why?
How do you pronounce the name?
It's Amour de Patou.
Huh, Amour de Patou.
[TOJI]
Mm-hm.
[gasps]
But this was the first
present you ever gave to me.
This was supposed to be
a special memory for us!
Forget about us.
It's over.
[MOMO]
Uh...
Wait!
Please, Toji!
I don't wanna break up
with you! I need you!
I... I can't live
without you, please.
No! Toji!
[door slams]
[MOMO]
Don't do this! Toji!
Toji!
Come on.
Just talk to me!
--[MOMO] Please! Toji! Toji!
--[TOJI gasps]
Please, Toji.
[MOMO sobs]
--[STUDENTS chatter]
--[birds chirping]
[KAIRI]
Momo's absent today.
Apparently, she was outside
in the snow crying
all night long in front
of somebody's house
and she caught a cold.
Hey! Wait.
What the hell is going
on with you lately?
Mind your own business.
[KAIRI grunts]
[KAIRI] All Momo ever
did was believe in you!
And this is how you treat her?!
You're such a freakin'
loser, man!
Shut your trap, Kairi.
Don't say another damn word!
--[TOJI grunts]
--[KAIRI groans]
[KAIRI groaning]
You bastard!
[BOTH grunting]
[MISAO]
My goodness!
What on earth happened
to the two of you?
Too much testosterone?
[KAIRI yelps]
That's it. I'm done with you.
Now get out of my office.
[KAIRI]
Hmph.
[MISAO]
So let me guess,
Kairi was hitting on Momo again
and you had to teach
him a lesson?
Although it looks like you took
quite a beating yourself.
Hey, wait, isn't she
absent today?
I thought I saw her name
on the list this morning.
Did she catch a cold?
It was pretty nasty
out last night.
[TOJI]
It's my fault she's sick.
[MISAO]
Uh?!
[TOJI]
She wanted to talk,
but I ignored her and left her
outside in the snow for hours.
Well no wonder she's sick today!
Why would you do that to her?
[TOJI grunts]
She's such an idiot.
It doesn't matter how hard
I try to push her away,
she keeps coming back
like a lost dog.
You know how you can beat
dogs and throw things
at them to make them go away,
and they still won't?
That's how she is.
She still believes in me,
and I don't know why.
I'm such a jerk.
I didn't wanna
hurt her like that.
[TOJI cries] I wish we'd
never had to break up!
[MISAO sighs]
But it...
[MOMO coughs]
[TOJI]
It was the only way...
It was the only way I knew
she'd be safe from everything.
I had no choice.
[TOJI cries]
[MOMO coughing]
[MOMO]
Toji? Why?
Forget about us.
It's over.
[MOMO]
What did I do wrong?
Is it really over?
I don't understand.
--[MOMO cries]
--[dog barking]
[MOMO]
Stupid dog, shut up!
Would you shut up?
[MOMO, TOJI gasp]
[MOMO]
How long have you been here?
[TOJI]
Not long.
I happened to be walking
through the neighborhood.
[MOMO gasps]
[foot steps]
[panting]
[dog barking]
[MOMO'S MOTHER] Momo, get back
inside. You have a fever!
[MOMO]
Of course he's not here.
I'm so stupid.
--[bell rings]
--[SAE]  Aw, man!
[SAE] I hate PE.
I wish I didn't have to go.
[SAE]
Hm...
Miss Misao! I have
the nastiest headache.
Is it okay if I lay down
in here this period?
Do we need take
your temperature?
[SAE]
Oh, yes!
[MISAO]
Sae...
There's something I wanted
to ask you about.
Yeah, what's on your mind?
Where are the photos?
[SAE]
Mm?
The ones you took of Momo Adachi
and that model together.
Do you still have them?
I don't know what pictures
you're talking about, ma'am.
Toji told me the
whole story Sae.
You threatened to send
those pictures to the press
and get her expelled if he
didn't break up with with Momo.
No I didn't.
I would never do that.
--[beeping]
--Uh? That's just not like me.
You took advantage of his
feelings for her
to satisfy your own jealous
desires, didn't you?
Do you have any idea how
traumatizing it was
for him to break up
with her like that?
He doesn't want to be with you.
What's the point of all this?
But, I didn't...
Do you honestly believe I would
do something like that
to such a good friend?
You're taking Toji's side
without even listening to mine!
But it's...
It's not fair!!
[SAE cries]
You know, I can tell
you're faking it.
[SAE]
You can't prove it.
So there's no way to know
for sure, is there?
[SAE] Ugh!
I hate that old hag!
Okay, Do you want me to take
those pictures to the press?
I mean why else would
you have told her.
And don't think for a
second that I won't do it.
It doesn't take a whole
lot to piss me off.
So remember sweetie,
you belong to me.
[phone rings]
[MOMO'S MOTHER]
Thank you for calling.
We can't come to
the phone right now.
Please leave us a message
after the beep.
[beep]
[KAKO] Hi, Momo.
This is Kako.
I just wanted to check and
see if you're coming back
to school anytime soon.
We're all worried about you.
Take care, okay?
[MOMO] I've been absent from
school for a week now.
My fever's gone down.
But why can't I stop crying?
Toji...
I'm such an idiot.
Even after all this,
I still have hope.
Because you've
never let me down.
Because you've always been
the one to cheer me up.
[door bell rings]
[KAIRI]
Rise and shine, Momo!
We're going on a date now!
Let's go already.
[MOMO moans]
Hey! Look at you.
[MOMO]
You're here again?
I told you I would come every
day until you're feeling better!
Hey, that face!
You've been crying again.
You can't stay in this house
crying all the time.
I bet your fever's
gone down by now.
[MOMO]
Well...
[KAIRI]
Come on, let's go.
A beautiful girl needs
fun and fresh air!
[MOMO]
Kairi, I can't go!
I'm still in my pajamas!
[KAIRI]
I know, they're cute!
What a glorious day!
Don't you think so?
Hey! What do you say
we rent a boat?
[MOMO]
Mm-mm.
[KAIRI]
Heh.
[MOMO groans]
[KAIRI]
Yum! Food stands!
Are ya hungry?
They have fried octopus!
[MOMO]
Mm-mm.
[KAIRI] Oh come on,
it's good for you! My treat!
[MOMO]
Mm-mm.
All right then.
How 'bout a sweet potato,
it'll keep you nice and warm?
[MOMO]
Mm-mm.
[KAIRI]
Maybe I'll just give you a kiss?
Don't you even try it!
[KAIRI]
Uh.
[MOMO]
Mm.
There it is. Yeah, I
definitely think being angry
and shouting is more
your style than crying.
So, uh, how 'bout that boat?
[MOMO]
Why did Toji break up with me?
It just deosn't make sense.
Would actually rather be
with Sae instead of me?
I don't know.
Toji's the only one who
knows the answer to that.
I guess he just wanted
to be with someone
who was more attractive than me.
Are you kidding me?
You're the most beautiful girl
I've ever laid eyes on.
Whatever.
You're just saying that.
[KAIRI] What?
You really don't think you are?
[MOMO]
No. I really don't.
[KAIRI]
Well!
I guess I'll just
have to prove it you.
[MOMO]
W-What?!
[KAIRI]
Hey! This store looks cool!
You'd look great
in any of these!
[MOMO]
Wait, Kairi...
[KAIRI]
Or maybe this store?
[MOMO]
Uh, either one, but...
[KAIRI]
Now this is really hot.
[MOMO]
You think so?
[KAIRI]
Let's see, not this one.
[MOMO]
What about this?
[KAIRI] Oh, wow!
That's perfect for you!
Excuse me!
Can my friend please
try this dress on?
Kairi, no!
Don't worry about it!
[MOMO]
Cut it out!
You shouldn't have
brought me here!
[KAIRI chuckles]
Relax, you don't have to buy it;
you're just trying
it on so have fun!
[MOMO]
Mm.
Well, how's it fit?
[MOMO]
Well...
[KAIRI]
Whoa!! Bravo! Woo hoo!!
[SALES WOMAN]
It looks fantastic!
[KAIRI] Great! Where are we
going next? This is fun!
Stop! Kairi!
We can't just leave!
I have to take
the dress off first!
[KAIRI] No you don't.
It's yours, I paid for it.
[MOMO]
What?!
[KAIRI]
Hey look at this!
This would look great
with your dress.
What did you mean?
When you said you
already paid for it?
I meant that today, we don't
have to worry about money.
[MOMO]
Uh?
[KAIRI]
Check it out!
My brother made some
extra cash on a project.
So he gave me this for the day,
and told me to use
it however I wanted.
[MOMO] This is too much.
You don't have to do all this.
Of course I don't.
That's why they call it a gift.
I want to do it for you.
Try it on!
[MOMO]
Well. I guess...
I guess it's okay.
[MOMO]
Just this once.
Oh, wow!
You look amazing!
Just stunning!
Foxy lady!
You're the hottest
thing I've ever seen!
Okay, that's enough.
[KAIRI]
Okay, you're right.
You're not hot,
you're beautiful!
Radiant!
Brilliant!
A box-office hit!
[MOMO laughs]
You're a dork.
Hey, I'll take 'dork' anyday,
as long as it comes
with that smile.
See? Everyone's
checkin' you out.
It's because you're
so drop-dead gorgeous.
When are you gonna
start believing that,
and stop putting yourself
down all the time, Momo?
Hey, Kairi, with all
you've done today.
I feel I should pay you back.
[KAIRI]
I told you, they're gifts.
You're not supposed to.
[MOMO] That's sweet,
but I can't accept it.
I'll pay you back with the money
I'm getting for New Year's,
please? I insist.
Of course you do.
You're so stubborn.
Yeah, well.
All right, all right!
But only if it'll
make you happy.
[MOMO]
Mom! I'm home!
[KAIRI] You're beautiful!
Radiant! Brilliant!
[MOMO] If one of my other
friends had said those things,
I don't think it would've
made me feel this way.
It was really sweet of him
to take me out today.
I guess I'm glad he did.
I didn't think I was
ready to laugh again.
[dog barking]
[MOMO]
Uh?!
[foot steps]
[MOMO gasping]
[dog barking]
[MOMO sighs]
Hey, what are you doing
out here, Momo?
I was just coming to see you.
There was something
I forgot to ask you
while we were out today.
Will you please come back
to school tomorrow?
I know it's hard,
but I think you'll be all right.
[MOMO] Toji's never
coming back again, is he?
[KAIRI]
Huh?
Uh.
[MOMO]
I didn't wanna believe it,
but I guess it's true.
He's not going to
change his mind.
[MOMO]
It's really over.
It just isn't fair.
It seems like everytime
I'm feeling low,
he shows up just in time
to make me smile.
Am I falling for Kairi?
What should I do?
Next time on Peach Girl:
The Peach Flower, Blossomed?