[MOMO] I'm sorry, Kairi.
I just don't believe it
can work out between us.
Is that your final decision?
[MOMO] Yes.
So...
You're saying you
want to be with me.
[TOJI] Did you hear that, Kairi?
She said yes.
Now let us live
our lives in peace.
Let's go.
[KAIRI yelling]
Toji!
[TOJI] Kairi!
What did you teach that girl
when she was living with you
for all those years?
There you go again.
Blaming me for anything bad
that happens in this family.
Don't act so innocent.
[KAIRI] Taxi!
Just start driving!
[MOMO]
Where are you taking me?
Kids...
They don't even know how
to apologize these days.
[TOJI] Kairi!
Wait, Kairi!
Son of a bitch.
[SAE'S MOTHER]
Excuse me.
Are you the one who called us?
Huh?
It was about Sae.
We're her parents.
How come you don't
wanna be with me?
There's plenty of reasons.
Most of all, being with
you gives me anxiety.
I'm tired of looking
forward to being with you,
waiting around, and then
being totally disappointed
when you flake on me.
Toji... He's not like that.
He's good to me, ya know?
And he really knows
how to treat a girl.
It's relaxing to
spend time with him.
While I was with you,
I cheated myself
by staying with you when
I wasn't your first choice.
I told myself
I was okay with it,
but in my heart
I knew it was wrong.
Kairi, I need someone
who's going to love
and treasure me
unconditionally.
That's why it'll
never work out between us.
But you're wrong, Momo...
I know I've made mistakes
but I won't make them again.
If you just give me another
chance I'll prove it to you.
You're such a liar!
How can you say that when
you're still in love with Misao?
No... That's not true!
She and I are only friends!
[cell phone ringing]
Hi.
Momo! You okay?
[MOMO] Yeah, I'm fine...
Right now we're
on Commerce Street
near the 4th Street bridge.
Where are you?
--Well... I'm--
--[MOMO] Oh, my batteries are--
Listen, Momo.
Misao is no more
than a friend to me.
I don't have feelings for her.
You're the only girl in
my life now, and I love you!
You have to believe me!
Sorry, Kairi,
but I can't do that.
Come on... Why not?
I...
I love you so much, Momo.
So much it actually hurts!
[MOMO] I'm sorry,
but that's just not enough!
Then what...
What can I do to make it enough?
Well...
At this point you
can't change my mind.
'Cause this is the
way I feel about you.
[MOMO] I can't live my life
as a nervous wreck,
and I know that if I
gave you another chance,
I'd be making a mistake.
[TOJI] Momo!
[MOMO] My love.
[MOMO] Toji's the one.
[MOMO] Oh no...
My grades are in trouble.
At this rate,
I'm gonna have a hard time
getting into a decent college.
[TOJI] Don't worry.
You still have a whole
year to get your grades up.
I guess so.
Do you wanna go to
the same college as me?
[MOMO] Are you crazy?
I mean, sure, that'd be great,
but I'll never be able to make
the kind of grades you do.
[TOJI]
Don't decide you can't do it
when you haven't even tried.
[MOMO] Some kids
are already prepared
for their entrance exams,
which means I need to
study constantly this year
to catch up.
I won't have any
free time, ya know?
Say, there's a three day
weekend coming up.
Do ya wanna go somewhere?
Uh, what?
A vacation!
With Toji?
No way!
Well...
Pretty soon, it'll be time
to start thinking about
getting into college
and all that,
so we wanted to get away
before things got too busy.
Oh...
I see where you're
going with this.
You want us to help you
figure out an alibi, don't you?
No, I don't think I'll need one.
We'll only be gone two days.
Three at the max.
[MOMO] But if another
typhoon were to hit
and we were stuck there,
then I guess I would need one.
[NAMI] That's true, Momo.
You have to be careful
and protect yourself
because you never really
know what's gonna happen
when you're on vacation.
So if I need one,
just in case...
Yeah, yeah. Don't worry.
We'll cover for ya.
So when are you going?
[MOMO]
Two weekends from now.
[KAKO]
And where are you going?
[MOMO]
We're not sure yet.
[SAE] You guys should
totally go to the beach!
That way you'd be able
to check out Toji
in his swim suit, right?
Sae?
[SAE laughs]
[MOMO] You seem to be
doing pretty well.
I'm so glad.
Now that I know
I'm not pregnant,
I can finally get
on with my life
and try to have some fun...
It's like a tremendous
weight's off my shoulders.
What's up with you
and Kairi's idiot brother?
[SAE]
I know I did the best I could
and now I've put it behind me.
I wasn't able to
get Ryo to love me,
but that's okay 'cause it was my
first time to ever be in love.
Looking back,
I have no regrets about it...
It's a good experience.
[MOMO] I've never seen you
be this open before.
Well I guess I learned something
about myself, didn't I?
[laughing]
[MOMO] She went through
so much pain recently
and yet she seems fine.
But it's not like
she's putting up a front,
like she used to.
See ya later!
[MOMO] I gotta admit...
I'm a little envious of her
being so in touch
with how she feels.
[SAE] Look at you moping around
feeling sorry for yourself!
What's wrong with you?
[KAIRI] What's up, Sae?
So how have you been?
Pretty good.
Except when I'm home
and my parents are there.
Oh, right...
You've had a lot of
crazy stuff happen to you.
[SAE] Gross!
Wh-What's your problem?
Why are you acting like this?
[KAIRI] Leave me alone.
I'm just a no good,
useless, dead battery.
Huh? What do you mean?
[SAE] A dead battery, huh?
I didn't know Momo
could be so harsh.
And you're giving up on her
because you guys
had one measly fight?
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
She won't believe a word I say.
Listen, you big baby!
A dead battery can be recharged
and brought back to life,
just like new!
So don't try to use that
as your lame-o excuse!
You never ever
take a girl seriously
when she's emotional,
especially when it comes to
someone as stubborn as Momo!
You're an idiot if you give up
because she probably didn't
even mean what she said!
Dumbass!
Thank you, Sae.
I never thought
being verbally abused
would ever cheer me up.
No problem.
[MOMO] There. I'm all packed up.
[MOMO'S MOTHER] Momo!
Your friend is here
to pick you up!
Hey Momo!
You ready to have
the best weekend ever?!
You don't really think
you're going with us, do you?
Oh, stop.
I just thought I'd give you
an alibi with your mom.
Plus, I wanted to
give you a farewell gift.
Farewell gift?
So tell me, Momo...
Are you happy now?
[MOMO] Yes, of course I am.
Oh really...?
I think you regret
kicking aside Kairi
'cause deep down you know
you made a mistake.
How dare you!
Come on, Momo,
you can be honest with me.
I bet it freaked you out when
Kairi told you he loved you.
But then you had Toji
and you couldn't
just toss him aside.
If you had, it would have made
you look like an evil witch.
You know, with Toji
going out of his way
to protect you and all.
So even if you wanted
to be with Kairi,
you'd still look like a jerk.
For the last time,
I don't want to be with Kairi!
I'm in love with Toji, okay?
And I'm happy.
So stop trying to ruin a good
thing and leave us alone!
Poor Kairi.
Going all the way to Shiranami
in the middle of a
typhoon just to see you.
He risked everything
and look where it got him.
[MOMO] Huh?
[MOMO] What did you just say?
[SAE] You and Kairi
were supposed to go
on a little beach
vacation together, right?
You see, after you left,
Kairi followed you and Toji
all the way to Shiranami beach.
[MOMO] How?
How do you know all this?
Because I was with him
to help him look for you.
Which, by the way,
was no easy task.
We went as far
as we could on train,
but because of the
typhoon we had to stop.
At that point Kairi took a taxi
by himself towards Shiranami.
On the way there,
the road was blocked by
some boulders that had fallen,
so he got out and walked
the rest of the way,
which must have been
at least twenty miles.
He knew he could have given up,
but he didn't because he thought
you were alone and crying,
and he wanted to comfort you
and be by your side.
But then, turns out
you weren't alone.
You were with Toji.
Kairi said he saw you.
You were standing
there with Toji,
waiting for the train at
the station the next day.
[MOMO] That can't be...
Kairi was there?
I don't know why
you were with Toji,
but I think it was
quite a blow to Kairi
to see you two together.
After all,
when you walk twenty miles
through mountains in a typhoon,
the last thing you want to see
is your girl with another guy.
Look, Momo,
I'm not trying to force you
to get back together
with Kairi or anything.
It's your life
and I respect that.
But I thought you'd want to know
the truth about what happened.
Even though you
never actually saw him,
he really went out of his way
to be there for you.
Oh! Gotta go!
Have fun on your trip.
[MOMO] No... That can't be true.
He acted like
nothing had happened,
even after I came back
from the beach.
[KAIRI] Morning!
Sorry I missed you
the other day.
I heard that you and
Toji got back together.
Congratulations.
[MOMO] He knew what
had happened, and yet...
...he didn't want me
to feel bad about it.
[KAIRI] I'm sorry.
I'm just emotional.
Sorry.
Come on... Why not?
I... I love you
so much, Momo.
So much it actually hurts!
[quiet sobbing]
[MOMO] What have I done?
[MISAO'S MOTHER] Oh, Misao.
You look so gorgeous, honey.
I'm just meeting him.
Nothing more, right?
Please, you're gonna love him.
We're about a half hour early.
You wanna sit down
and have some tea?
Kill me.
Is that Momo?
Really?
Yes, really.
They're going on a
quick trip together.
Just the two of them.
And you'll never believe
the weather forecast.
Another typhoon is
expected to hit the coast
right where they're
staying again.
They may be stuck there tonight!
[SAE] Aren't you
gonna go save the day?
[KAIRI] That's impossible.
It's too late to do anything.
That's disappointing to hear
after I went to the
trouble of telling Momo
the truth about last time.
When?!
Just now.
You should have seen
the look on her face
when I told her you saw
them at the train station.
She may even get cold feet
and decide not to go
on this trip with Toji.
Where do you get off
telling her that?!
[SAE] From you, idiot!
You told me to tell her!
[KAIRI] I'm dead.
Misao...
I honestly had no idea Kairi
had followed me there.
I feel so awful.
I can't imagine how he
must have felt, seeing us...
I broke his heart and
I didn't even mean to.
So that's how it happened, huh?
What I don't understand is...
...why Kairi neglected
to tell you the reason
why he was late
meeting you that day.
What are you
talking about? Misao?
We were in the park
where you two were meeting
when Ryo was attacked.
He wasn't badly hurt,
but he left in an ambulance.
I was crying and hysterical
and a total mess.
So Kairi decided to go
with me to the hospital.
That's why he was late
meeting you for your trip.
Oh no...
[MOMO] What's wrong with him?
If he would have
just told me the truth,
I would have waited for him.
How was I supposed to know
if he didn't tell me?
Maybe he was hesitant
to tell you the truth
because he didn't want you
to take it the wrong way
and assume something worse...
He never even got a
chance to give you the rose.
Huh? What rose?
Earlier that day,
I ran into him at the
flower shop near the park.
He was there to buy you a rose,
and when I told him
that a red rose
symbolizes true love
and passion, he said...
[KAIRI]
When I give this rose to Momo,
she'll know how I
truly feel about her.
Then she can be confident that
she's the only one in my life
and number one on my list.
[MOMO]
I've done a... horrible thing.
Oh no...
I'm meeting with Toji soon.
[MOMO] But I can't see him
when I feel like this.
I know you're probably
feeling a lot of guilt right now
when it comes to Kairi,
but it's important for you
to focus on how you feel.
We've only been talking
about Kairi up to now,
but don't forget that Toji
has been very loyal to you.
He's a strong, patient person
who has really
looked out for you.
That's why you're
seeing him, right?
Both Kairi and Toji
love you very much, Momo,
and I think what they
want more than anything
is to see you happy.
Right now you need to
look deep into your heart,
and even deeper into your soul,
and find out what is
most important to you.
There's Toji, who's a smart,
mature, good-looking guy.
Then there's Kairi, who's
a bit more juvenile, but fun.
This is probably
the toughest decision
you've ever had to make, Momo,
but you're incredibly lucky.
You have two amazing guys
to choose from.
I wish I had that opportunity.
Don't be afraid.
As long as you stay true
to your heart, you'll be fine.
It's so hard.
[MISAO'S MOTHER] Misao.
We should get going soon.
[MISAO] Okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
take up all your time.
Are you and your mom
going to a wedding today?
[MISAO]
Actually, it's a meeting...
For an... arranged marriage.
My parents set it up
without asking me first,
so I told them I'd go to
be nice and not rock the boat.
I just hope to get
a good meal out of it.
What about...
Kairi's brother Ryo?
Oh, him.
I came to a conclusion.
I can't be with someone who
lacks a soul as much as he does.
So I said goodbye.
He's still adorable, though.
[laughs]
[MISAO, MOMO laughing]
Ryo, what are you doing
looking at that?
[RYO] They're from a
parenting website I found.
[RYO] In a way,
parenting is almost like
the ultimate video game.
If you do poorly,
you end up with a bad child,
and you can't reset your game.
But, you could end up
with something very special.
[RYO]
I think I was wrong.
Maybe I do want to be a dad.
[SAE] Looks like Momo
isn't here yet.
[KAIRI] And when did she say?
Ten o'clock.
I hope she didn't
change her mind.
[giggles]
Maybe I shook her up
a little bit, huh?
You lucky stud!
You may still have
a chance with her!
Oh come on!
You can at least
try to be happy.
[MOMO gasps]
Oh no!
I'm over a half-hour late!
Toji's waiting for me
at the park.
[MISAO] Huh?
[MOMO] I'm sorry, Misao.
I have to go.
[MISAO] Well good luck!
Geez...
She must be having some déjà vu.
[MOMO] What am I going to do?!
By the time I get there,
Toji will have been waiting
over an hour for me!
How inconsiderate of me!
I, of all people,
should know what's it like
to be left waiting.
I'm so sorry, Toji.
Just hold on.
She's an hour late...
Maybe she did get cold feet.
Kairi!
Wow... Toji left.
I thought he would've waited
around much longer than that.
Maybe with all the crap
you've put him through
having to fight for Momo
drove him to leave.
I know!
I should call up Momo
and tell her
that Toji just walked
away in a big huff!
--Give that back!
--That's enough already!
What good would it do
to call her at this point?
You're only gonna
make things worse.
[SAE] Get real!
I'm helping you out
more than you deserve!
Stop acting so righteous
and give me my phone!
Now!
No way!
[SAE] Don't make me
hurt you, 'cause I will!
It's Momo!
[sobbing quietly]
[TOJI] Momo!
Haha, hey there!
Right on time.
Uh... yeah.
I'm just kidding.
You know this is exactly
how I imagined you'd look
when I knew you were
running late. Here.
I'm sorry.
[TOJI] Don't worry.
I knew you wouldn't
just bail on me.
You're not that type of person.
[MISAO] Right now you need
to look deep into your heart,
and even deeper into your soul,
and find out what is
most important to you.
This is probably
the toughest decision
you've ever had to make, Momo.
Don't be afraid.
As long as you stay true
to your heart, you'll be fine.
[MOMO] Thank you.
[TOJI] Let's have some fun.
[MOMO] Kairi...
Was I just running
away from you,
or was I afraid
of losing you again?
Either way, I'm done running.
This time I'll face you, Kairi,
no matter how it turns out.
Next time on Peach Girl,
it's the final episode.
The Last Typhoon!