[crying]
What are you lookin' at?
Did you plan this whole thing?
You're insane.
It was you. I can see in your
eyes that you're lying to me.
Momo...
I ruined everything.
It's all over.
No it isn't, don't say that!
But... what about Jigoro?
You know what, Sae?
You're gonna get it!
Movie?
Cool, huh?
One of my older brother's
friends is a director.
And he's having
a really hard time
finding the right
leading lady for his film.
I thought you'd be
interested in meeting him.
Maybe. But why're you asking me?
Well, mostly because you happen
to fit the description
he gave perfectly.
Plus, he helped me out once
and I owe him a favor.
He's looking for a sweet,
kind-hearted girl
who makes men feel
protective of her.
But she also has to be
smart and beautiful.
Wow! That does
sound like me.
I guess I should give him a
call, but only to help you.
If it sucks, I'm gone.
Thank you.
And no one's here because...?
I'll see what's up.
My phone works better outside.
[KAIRI chuckles]
[BARNEY]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Uh.
Are you the director?
[BARNEY] Welcome to the set
of "The Fly Man Strikes Back."
Uhh...
[BARNEY grunts]
Help me!
Naughty Firefly Scene, take one!
--I'm your motivation!
--[SAE screams]
Why is Kairi so late?
This was all his idea.
Momo, can we talk about Sae?
I only kissed her
because she tricked me.
She had put together
this costume.
And she looked exactly like you.
Same clothes, same hair.
Even the perfume I gave
you for your birthday.
So you thought that she was me.
[MOMO]
What's wrong with her?
Why won't she just
mind her own business
and leave Toji and me alone?!
[KAIRI]
Yo, lovebirds!
Uhh.
What's goin' on here?
Nothing. We're just talking.
Well, it's time to cheer up
because I'm teaching Sae a
lesson she's never gonna forget.
[BOTH gasp]
What's that s'posed to mean?
It means that right now Sae
is experiencing a little bit
of what you went through
the other day with Jigoro.
[BARNEY laughs]
Please stop! Don't touch me.
Get away from me, you fat creep!
[SAE screams]
What a naughty little
firefly you are
to use such dirty, dirty
language. Time for a swatting!
--[SAE screams]
--[BARNEY] Papa's gonna get you!
--You can't run from me!
--[SAE screams]
--Such a naughty flea-fly!
[MOMO]
Uhh...
So right now Sae could be dead?
Nah, she's just getting
a little scare that's all.
She should be just fine.
[MOMO]
But--
Trust me, Momo, this is nothing
compared to what she did to you.
There's really no other
way to teach her.
How do you know this guy
isn't going to do anything
more than scare her, Kairi?
Did you ever think about
what might happen?
It'll be all right. Unless Sae
starts running her mouth,
then I can't imagine anyone
not wanting to harm her.
What's wrong?
[MOMO]
I can't believe you, Kairi!
Huh?
[TOJI gasps]
I have to go find Sae before
something awful happens.
What for?
If this was happening to you,
Sae wouldn't even lift a finger
Well, it did happen to me
and I wanted to die.
Besides, it doesn't
matter what she's done,
no woman deserves this.
Hey, wait!
Momo! Wait for me!
Hang on! I'm coming with you!
[MOMO]
I hope she's all right.
[SAE yelps]
Stop! You're hurting me!
[SAE cries]
They didn't tell me
how cute you were.
I might fall in love.
[SAE yelps]
[SAE screams]
It sounds like she
really is being attacked!
Sae!
Sae, are you in
there?! Answer me!
[grunts]
Momo...? I'm in here,
Momo! Help me, please!
[gasps]
Open the door right now!
We've already called the police!
They'll be here any minute!
[SAE yowls]
[BARNEY screams]
What the heck
is going on in there?!
Hang on!
[MOMO]
Out of the way!
[MOMO grunts]
[KAIRI, TOJI gasp]
[BARNEY whimpers]
[BARNEY screams]
[BARNEY coughs]
What the...?!
[MOMO grunts]
[BARNEY yelps]
[BARNEY whimpers]
[panting]
[SAE whimpers]
I hate to say it, but
I'm glad you're not dead.
Do you see now how
Momo must've felt?
[SAE gasps]
This is exactly the
same kind of helpless
and frightening position you put
her in with Jigoro, you psycho.
Are you saying that the three
of you planned this to happen?
Momo and Toji have
nothing to do with this.
It was all me!
[KAIRI, TOJI gasp]
[SAE grunts]
Calm down.
This is nowhere near the
same thing, you freaks!
Nothing ever happened
between Jigoro and Momo!
[ALL gasp]
Tell me, how would
you three have felt
if that fat sack of nasty
had had his way with me?!
And that's the only thing that
matters to you, isn't it, Sae?
Nothing that happened today
made you think of the
nightmare you put me through.
Kairi thought that
if you experienced
your own hateful pranks, you
might actually want to stop
doing these things to people.
But I guess he
overestimated you.
You are incapable of caring
about anyone but yourself.
This is the last kind thing
I'll ever do for you, Sae.
And I will never forgive you
for this as long as I live.
Stay away from me.
[KAIRI]
That was intense.
[SAE grunts]
It's not like I don't understand
why you did it in
the first place.
I mean, seeing Toji and
Momo so happy together
does make me a bit jealous.
Do you ever get
feelings like that?
Knock it off.
You wanna be as
happy as she is.
And you think the
only way you will be
is if you have Toji to yourself.
Well, Sae, you know what?
Here's the truth.
Even if you were somehow able
to break the two of them up,
you're not her.
What is it that makes you think
she's so much better than me?!
I'm only saying that you two
are very different people.
So you wouldn't have the
same kind of relationship.
I mean, think about it,
they've overcome a lot of
obstacles thrown their way.
That does tends to create
a pretty strong bond.
Good luck, though.
How dare he speak
to me that way!
[SAE grunts]
You think I can't have Toji?
We'll see about that.
[MOMO] Nothing actually happened
between me and Jigoro.
[MOMO]
What a relief.
And I'm finally free of Sae.
Forever.
I think I'm free all day Sunday.
Then how about we go
to an amusement park
so we can finish
celebrating your birthday.
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
An amusement park!
[SAE]
Hi, guys.
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO grumbles]
[MOMO] What time were
you thinking of meeting up?
[TOJI] The earlier
the better. Less crowds.
[SAE growls]
[bell ringing]
Toji!
[TOJI]
Hm?
There's something we need
to discuss about Momo,
do you have a few minutes?
[TOJI]
Uh.
What's this about?
You need to break up
with her. Now.
[TOJI grunts]
Yeah, right.
Well then, you leave
me no other option.
Sur-prise! Look.
Tomorrow at five o'clock
there's a press conference
for Jigoro's new TV show.
I bet the reporters would kill
someone for a picture like this.
[TOJI gasps]
Well, you're not going to
have the chance to find out.
I won't let you destroy
Momo with your lies.
That's so sweet!
Too bad I made all these copies.
And I have more at home.
What's ironic is that
this kind of publicity
will be good for Jigoro.
Thanks to me, he'll just
become more desirable
when he's on the cover
of every magazine.
And seeing how my
timing is so excellent,
I wonder if I should charge
the network for all this PR.
Then there's Momo.
She'll go from being
School Slut to
International Whore overnight.
And I imagine she'll
probably be expelled, too.
You wouldn't.
[SAE snickers]
You know something, Sae.
I just realized how evil
you actually are.
Honey, insulting me is not
going to protect Momo.
But breaking up with her will!
So do it!
You just don't know
when to quit do you?!
Nothing you say or do
could ever break us up.
So leave us alone!
[SAE]
Hmph.
[MOMO]
Toji!
[MOMO giggles]
Thank you so much for
bringing me out here today!
Ready?
[MOMO]
You bet!
We're gonna have so much fun!
[ALL screaming]
Do you not like it?
[TOJI grunts]
Uh... I haven't tried it yet.
I noticed. Is everything okay,
Toji? You're acting distant.
Everything's fine.
Hey, can you tell me
what time it is?
Uh...
It's twelve-fifty.
[SAE]
Tomorrow at five o'clock
there's a press conference
for Jigoro's new TV show.
[phone ringing]
[TOJI gasps]
Hello?
[SAE]
Having fun on your date, Momo?
[MOMO gasps]
Sae.
[TOJI grunts]
Sae wants to talk to you.
What do you want?
[SAE]
Just a friendly reminder
that you have a little
over four hours.
You should eat the sandwich,
Toji. It's your last date.
[TOJI gasps]
Sae, wait!
Toji! What is it? Hey! Hold on!
[TOJI]
Come back here!
[TOJI panting]
[MOMO]
Toji!
[MOMO grunts]
[TOJI gasps]
What's going on?
[TOJI]
Uh... It's nothing.
Don't shut me out like this!
I want you to tell me why Sae
is calling my phone
looking for you.
And why are you
running after her?
What is she doing here anyway?!
She must've told you
something that upset you!
[SAE] Then there's Momo,
she'll go from being
School Slut to
International Whore overnight.
Yeah, but don't worry about it.
She's just trying to get under
my skin and I overreacted.
Well, I'm glad
that's all it was.
[TOJI]
Are you ready to go?
[MOMO grunts]
It's getting kinda late.
Okay.
[MOMO]
What's bothering him?
He looks like he having
the worst time of his life.
I thought this was supposed
to be a good day for us.
[SAE] Honey, insulting me
is not going to protect Momo,
but breaking up with her will!
[MAN B] Jigoro's appearances
are always like this.
[MAN C] If looks are all it
takes to be famous, sign me up!
Just a minute there, miss,
do you have a press pass?!
[GUARD screams]
--[GUARD] S-She disappeared
--[SAE] Sneak. Sneak. Sneak.
--Help! Help!
[TOJI] There might still be time
to get to the press conference
and stop Sae from
releasing those photos
but we've got
to get out of here.
[TOJI gasps]
Hey, let's go.
[MOMO]
No... not until we ride that.
[TOJI]
Look at that line!
We'll come back.
Soon, I promise.
[MOMO] We haven't even
been at the park that long.
It's my birthday, Toji,
and I don't wanna leave yet.
[EMCEE] We'd like to start by
announcing our new soap opera,
"Open Your Eyes."
[SAE grunts]
[MOMO]
Why isn't he talking to me?
This silent treatment doesn't do
anything but make me nervous.
Just say something.
[EMCEE] Making his debut as our
supporting lead will be...
...Jigoro Oji!
[EMCEE]
Tell us a little bit
about your character,
if you will.
I found this role
to be both challenging
--and rather pleasurable.
--[FEMALES sigh, giggle]
[FEMALES sighing]
[EMCEE]
Oh no!
It looks like we have
to cancel the press conference!
[phone ringing]
[SAE]
Uh.
Yeah?
Anyone there? Uh...
Toji, look at the sunset!
Isn't it beautiful?!
[MOMO]
Uhh...
What is it?
[TOJI gasps]
We need to break up.
[MOMO gasps]
[SAE snickers]
But why? What for?
What did I do wrong?
I don't understand why
you're saying this.
It's just...
I'm not that into you anymore.
I'm sorry.
[SAE]
Hey, nice save!
A deal's a deal.
Now give me the photos.
It's a good thing you
called when you did.
Momo was about to become
a household name.
[paper crumpling]
What about your phone?
[SAE] Here, why don't
you delete it yourself.
Oh, look! It's our first date!
So, where shall
we go for dinner?
You can forget it.
[SAE]
Uh.
Going out with you was
never part of the deal, Sae.
If you try to force me, it'll
be a very short relationship.
I'll dump you five seconds
after we start, you ready?
Look. What a beautiful
evening it is.
It makes me want to break up
with you, you rotten scab.
I thought you might pull
something like this.
It's a good thing I always
have a back up plan.
See I figured you would
only play along
until you got what you wanted.
And then you'd run back to Momo
as soon as the deal was done.
You're so dumb.
Did you really think
that I'd give you
every copy of that photo?
Where is it?!
It's at my house, baby!
Saved on my laptop!
Come 'n get it!
[TOJI grunts]
Why you...!
Use your words, Toji.
I think we need to learn how to
communicate better, don't you?
[TOJI grunts]
Don't worry, boyfriend.
I'll give you the last copy
of the picture as soon as
I'm done with you.
[SAE snickers]
[phone ringing]
[TOJI] It's just....
I'm not that into you anymore.
[MOMO]
Something's going on.
I can't imagine that Toji
would ever say that to me.
[RECORDING] Your call is
being transferred to voicemail.
[GIRL A]
Yeah, I know.
--Can you believe it?!
--[GIRL B giggles]
Hi, It's me. Listen,
I'm not trying to be annoying
I just really need
to talk to you.
I know there's more going on
than what you're telling me.
You and I were doing fine.
It doesn't make any sense.
Toji, If you ever
cared for me at all,
you'll meet me on the bench
behind the school before class.
[KAKO]
What is he doing?!
[SAE giggles]
Oh, Toji, you're so funny! Uh...
[SAE snickers]
Let go of him, Sae!
Who do you think you are anyway?
How dare you come to school
with another girl's boyfriend!
[KAKO, NAMI, RITSUKO]
You just wait
until Momo hears about this!
Actually, she already knows.
Toji broke up with her
to be with me. Right?
[ALL sceam]
[school bell ringing]
[MOMO] Sounds like I'm gonna
miss the first class of the day.
I wonder if Toji
even got my message.
[KAIRI]
Momo!
[MOMO]
Uhh...
Kairi?
Come with me!
She's doing it again!
Who is?
Sae's telling everyone
that Toji's her boyfriend!
[MOMO gasps]
[KAIRI]
They came to school together.
She was holding onto his arm
and causing a scene!
She what?!
[STUDENTS chatter]
[MOMO]
Momo, is it true?
Did you break up with Toji?
No. We never broke up.
It's all a bunch of lies.
[MOMO]
Toji... Where are you?
...care for me at all
you'll meet me on the bench
behind the school before class.
[MOMO panting]
[TOJI grunts]
[KAIRI] There you are!
--[KAIRI laughs]
--[TOJI grunts, yelps]
Hey, Momo! Come quick!
I got him!
Get off me!
Right. So you can run
away and hide from her?
You're not going anywhere
until you tell Momo
what's going on with you!
Stop being such a wuss!
Toji, please talk to me.
Why are you doing this?
Everything was going
great between us
and we were finally having fun.
I can't believe you'd wanna
break up with me for no reason.
Yeah, well, that's just
the way I am, I guess.
Stop that!
This is not who you
are at all, Toji!
This has something to do with
Sae. Now tell me the truth!
The truth, Momo?
[ALL gasp]
You're making this more
complicated than it is.
He just likes me more than you.
Right, sweetie?
You're so pathetic!
Somehow you've tricked Toji.
No one in their right mind
would ever want to
date someone like you.
[SAE gasps]
Did you hear what
she said to me?
You can't be dating her,
this is just another lie.
She's behind all of this. You
don't want to break up with me.
Right?
I told you.
Something changed and I don't
care for you the way I used to.
Now you're just lying to me!
You still love me,
I'm positive you do!
[TOJI] Fine. If you
don't believe me...
I'll prove it.
[MOMO gasps]
[KAIRI gasps]
[MOMO]
Is Toji really in love with Sae?
I know he still loves me
so how is that possible?
I have to get him back!
The question is how.
Next time on Peach Girl
"The Unbearable Breakup."