I understand if you're
still in love with Toji.
I'm just glad I'm with you.
[MOMO] Thank you, Kairi,
but isn't it weird
that we planted a peach seed
and got a quince flower?
Huh?
Quince flower.
This looks absolutely nothing
like a peach blossom.
Uh?! Ah!
What?! That man lied to me!
He said it was a peach blossom!
[KAIRI yelps]
[MOMO] Peach Blossom, huh?
I don't think so!
[MOMO laughs]
[KAIRI] I don't need to
plant a peach blossom.
I've got one right here.
Did you know that peach blossoms
have a very special meaning?
They mean "I am your captive."
[MOMO]
I am your captive.
[NORI] Look at those two.
They're never apart.
You think they're dating now?
[AKI] Last time I talked to Momo
she said they were just friends.
[SANGO]
Ah, but guess what I heard?
Someone saw them
kissing the other day.
[NORI]
No way!
[AKI, SANGO, NORI growl]
[MOMO]
Uh!
Stay away from Kairi.
[MOMO] Whatever's going
on between me and Kairi
is none of your business.
Everyone at school knows you're
still in love with Toji.
So until you get that out of
your system, leave Kairi alone.
Yeah, he's much
too good of a guy
to be a rebound for
someone like you.
I'm sure anyone would
be good enough for you,
as long as they're
cute and popular.
You better do as we say. Never
talk to Kairi again. You got it?
You poor things.
Kairi would never go out with
someone as shallow as you.
How dare you!
[MOMO gasps]
You have no idea what you're
talking about, you slut!
You don't even love Kairi,
and yet you keep
stringing him along!
Shut up!
[NORI, AKI]
Uh!
Do you honestly believe
that I would kiss someone
I didn't like? Of course
I'm in love with Kairi!
[NORI growls]
You bitch!
[MOMO gasps]
[KAIRI]
All right, that's enough!
[NORI gasps]
You weren't actually gonna
hit my girl were you?
Kairi!
[MOMO sighs]
Just because you're not
getting the attention you want,
you treat her like this?
We were just trying to
help you out, I swear.
Go on and get out of here. I'm
disgusted with all three of you.
[SANGO, NORI, AKI whimper]
[SANGO, NORI, AKI cry]
I don't understand
why girls do that.
They smell blood in
the water and attack.
I knew this would happen.
It was just a matter of time
before they started something.
You saved me.
Everything's okay! I'm here!
[KAIRI groans]
[splash]
[MOMO laughs]
[MOMO]
It feels so good!
You should come over
and join me, Kairi.
Not gonna happen.
[MOMO]
Aw come on!
You won't even get
your feet wet?
Are you really that
scared of the water?
[KAIRI]
Yup.
That's cool. I guess
that makes sense,
since you almost drowned
in the ocean, right?
[KAIRI]
I don't really remember it,
but from what people have told
me it was a really close call.
[MOMO]
It sure was.
Everyone thought you were
dead when I pulled you out.
I know we've been
over this before,
but are you positive you weren't
the one to give me CPR?
Yes, I'm positive.
But I'm curious, how did you
find out that I'm the one
that pulled you
out of the water?
Right after I started going to
school here, I heard your name
mentioned in the hallway,
and it sounded familiar.
I remembered that the girl who
saved me had a name like yours,
and since you're the only girl
I've ever known named Momo,
it just made sense
that it was you.
Well if that's the case,
then how come you never
approached me back then?
You'll probably have a hard
time believing this,
but I'm actually
a very shy person
when it comes to
approaching cute girls.
You are such a liar.
It is strange though,
if you think about it.
If you hadn't almost
drowned that day,
we wouldn't be sitting
here right now.
In fact, we probably wouldn't
even know each other.
[KAIRI]
It's pretty weird.
[MOMO] So before you
developed this fear of water,
would you have called
yourself a strong swimmer?
Not by a long shot.
Then what in the world
were you thinking,
swimming so far away
from the shore, Kairi?
It was just a couple of
days after the typhoon.
The water was
still pretty rough.
I was trying to kill myself.
[MOMO gasps]
Ha! I totally got you! I was
kidding! I wasn't suicidal!
It was a joke!
[MOMO] A joke? That was
way too serious for a joke.
Maybe this is another side
to Kairi I haven't seen yet.
I mean, it is possible since
I'm always blabbing
about myself to him.
In fact, the more
I think about it,
I barely know anything
intimate about him.
--[KAIRI]  You ready?
--[MOMO] Uh?
--[crash]
--[MOMO, KAIRI] Uh?
Ah! Oh thank God!
It still works!
[MOMO] Whoa, Looks like it's
time to get a new case, huh?
I'm a little short on cash right
now, but it's cool though,
I'll just put some tape on it,
and it'll be as good as new.
[MOMO]
That's perfect!
Crap! I have to start over!
What's wrong with me? Even my
little cousin can knit straight!
I'm gonna run out of yarn soon.
I can't wait to see his face
light up when I
give this to him.
[MOMO]
No! Not again!
[MOMO] I can't believe I
worked on that all night.
I'm so tired.
Is anyone in here?
Nurse Misao won't mind if I
take a quick nap before class.
[door opens, foot steps]
[MOMO]
Mm? Mm. What time is it?
[MISAO groans]
Sixty-three kilos.
[MOMO] Oh no! Whatever
you do, don't laugh!
Damn it! I might as well be
pregnant with this belly!
[MOMO giggles]
[MISAO gasps]
Hi. I didn't know
you were here, Momo.
[MOMO] Uh! I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to laugh at you.
[MOMO]
Uh?
Here's some tea.
Just promise you won't utter
a word of this to anyone.
[MOMO]
That's nice of her.
If I were in her shoes and heard
some kid laughing at my weight,
I'd probably end up
punching their lights out.
Hey Momo! Heard you cut class!
No I was just napping in here.
I didn't get much
sleep last night.
What are you drinking?
It looks good.
Come on, give me a sip. Please!
Quit it!
Don't you have a class
to go to or something?
[KAIRI]
This is way more important.
I'm spending quality
time with my girl.
[MISAO]
Oh yeah?
Get back here!
Before I give you a valid reason
to be at the nurses' office!
[MOMO laughs]
--[KAIRI] Come on, stop!
--[MISAO growls]
[KAIRI]
Momo, help!
Uh. I can't believe
you're still wearing that.
[MISAO gasps]
[KAIRI] Especially after
what he did to you.
[MOMO]
Uh...
Kairi!
Kairi, tell me what
happened with Nurse Misao.
Whatever you said back there
seemed to really
hurt her feelings.
Do you know something about
her that no one else does?
Kairi, wait!
My brother, Ryo,
broke her heart. Okay?
Wait a second. Nurse Misao used
to go out with your brother?
When was this?
They went out together
while they were in college.
I needed some help with school,
so she became my tutor
in junior high.
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Your brother and the nurse?
Why didn't you ever tell me?
It never came up.
[MOMO] Then why keep
it a secret from me?
It wasn't like I was
keeping it from you.
It's just that when we talk,
it's usually all about you.
See ya around.
[MISAO] He always acts like that
when it comes to his brother.
I think he has a complex.
You should've seen
him when I first met him.
He's an angel now compared
to how he used to be.
Maybe it was his way
of rebelling against an
over-achieving brother.
He ran away from
home a few times,
and would skip class constantly.
I think his brother grew
concerned about him
as time went on,
so that's when he asked
me to start tutoring him.
[MOMO]
Tell me about his brother.
You know, what's he like?
He was wonderful.
He has an amazing spirit, and
being with him makes you ask
how anyone could
be born so blessed.
[foot steps]
[STUDENT]
Nurse! Come quick.
Someone just got hit in
the face with the softball!
[MISAO] Be right there! I gotta
go. I'll talk to you later.
[foot steps]
[MOMO]
I guess I was right.
I barely know anything
personal about him.
[MOMO]
That's Kairi's.
He looks so happy.
Who's this girl next to him?
The picture's so faded,
I can't tell how old it is.
[KAIRI]
Uh?
[MOMO]
So, who's that girl?
I take it you looked
at the photo inside.
[MOMO] There's something
I need to ask you.
Are you seeing someone that
you haven't told me about?
Don't worry about it Momo.
It was a long time ago.
Look I'm throwing
it away right now.
You see? You satisfied now?
[tires squeal]
[GIRL]
Kairi?
[KAIRI]
Uh?
[MOMO]
Uh! Its that necklace!
I don't believe it! It is you!
You look so handsome.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Morika?
--[MORIKA]  Come on!
--[KAIRI] Ah!
[MORIKA] Don't tell me
you don't remember
your long, lost girlfriend.
How could you forget me,
with all the crazy things
we've been through?
You know I still have two feet.
I didn't need a ride.
Don't worry about it.
It's my pleasure.
[MOMO seething]
[MOMO] Why is Kairi
sitting next to her?
[KAIRI] Is it hot in here,
or is it just me?
So you've changed.
I barely even recognized
you back there.
Well, ya know. I have lost a lot
of weight since I last saw you.
[MOMO]
She's the one in the photo.
Hm.
[MOMO]
What a cow.
Thanks for the ride.
[KAIRI]
I'll get out here, too.
[MORIKA chuckles]
[engine revs]
I was almost out the door, Mo!
What do you think you're doing?!
[MORIKA]
Calm down.
[KAIRI]
I can't calm down!
[MOMO]
Uh!
[MORIKA]
You're not mad at me, are you?
Turn around and take
me back to Momo.
Oh, so I see you for the first
time in years and you already
want out of my sight.
That's how you treat me?
[KAIRI] Don't you have
somewhere to be right now?
[MORIKA]
Uh. You really have matured.
If I had known you
would end up like this,
I never would have
broken up with you.
Isn't that nice.
I've really missed you.
I came back 'cause
I wanted to see you.
[KAIRI]
Uh?
I've been thinking
about us a lot lately,
and how you used to
be so sweet to me.
I know it's been a long time
since we broke up,
but of all the guys I've
been with since then,
none of them have
been a nice as you.
It makes me wonder why
I even broke up with you
in the first place.
It's nice hearin'
you say all this,
but what are you doing still
wearing that necklace?
My brother gave
that to you, didn't he?
[KAIRI gasps]
Kairi.
--[phone rings]
--[KAIRI] Hold on.
[MORIKA] Nice cell phone case.
It's about to fall apart.
Well it'll have to do
because I don't have enough
money to buy a new one.
[KAIRI sighs]
I'm in trouble.
[MORIKA]
Kairi! Where you going?!
[KAIRI]
I am so sorry about that, Momo.
Was that her? From the picture?
Figures. Lemme guess,
you're into that whole blonde
haired bimbo look too, huh?
You must be feeling pretty
good about yourself right now.
Seeing how happy
she was to see you
it's clear that
she's missed you.
Maybe you two could even
get back together again.
No, Momo.
Sorry. That was
really uncalled for.
Momo. You're the only one.
And if it makes
any difference,
Morika and I were never
really that close, anyway.
It's just that she and I
had a really ugly breakup,
and I still have some
baggage left over from it.
An ugly breakup?
Yeah, my brother
stole her from me.
But after seeing her
today, I realized that...
The baggage isn't really
about feeling like a loser
because she dumped me.
It's just the resentment I
have towards my brother.
So there's no
need to worry
about me running off
with my ex, okay?
Really?
[KAIRI]
Yes, really.
You wouldn't lie to me.
Would you?
[KAIRI chuckles]
[MOMO] When did I start
loving Kairi so much?
I don't mind. Kairi won't
hurt me. He never has.
I'm going to trust
him unconditionally.
I'm the one he's with now.
[KAKO]
Wow! That looks great!
I love the color you went with.
So when are you
gonna give it to him?
Probably tomorrow.
He has no idea he's getting it.
It's so cute. Great job Momo!
You could make a fortune
selling those at school,
if you wanted to.
[horn honks]
[ALL]
Uh?
[MOMO]
[KAKO, RITSUKO, NAMI panting]
We need Kairi!
I think he went to
the teacher's office.
That's right! He's the
school monitor today!
Oh, no! Right when
Momo's in trouble!
[RITSUKO]
Let's hurry!
So, is that your
natural skin color?
No I'm on the swim team.
Really? That's pretty cool. You
don't know how lucky you are.
Every time I try to get a tan,
I just end up looking
like a lobster,
I guess that's the just
price I have to pay
for having such
delicate skin.
It's okay though, I hear
that if you tan too much,
you'll look like a catchers
mitt by the time you're forty.
Speaking of, you might
wanna consider
rolling up your window
before your face starts to burn.
[MOMO]
Gimme a break.
I'm used to dealing with much
better insults from Sae.
[MORIKA]
Hey. You know that scar
near Kairi's belly button
that looks like a pumpkin?
Yeah that was me
who gave it to him.
I accidentally used his
stomach as an ashtray.
We must have laughed
about that for hours.
[MOMO]
Kairi has a scar?
No way! Don't tell me that
pervert hasn't shown you
his scar yet!
I can't believe it!
Come on girl.
How long have you two
been going out anyway?
About two months.
[MOMO]
That jerk.
I can't believe he said
they weren't close.
He obviously slept with this
bimbo! Oh, he's gonna get it.
[MORIKA gasps] You guys have
been going out for two months,
and he hasn't even taken his
shirt off in front of you?
No way!
[MOMO]
So what?
If I wanna look at his
belly button then I can
do that whenever I want.
'Cause he's my boyfriend.
Which means that he and I
have no secrets between us.
Morika! What are you doing here?
I'm actually looking for you. We
never finished our conversation.
As far as I'm concerned, we have
nothing else to talk about.
Now get outta here.
Wait, hang on, Kairi.
Let's go Momo.
[KAKO, NAMI, RITSUKO cheer]
[MOMO]
Mm.
[MOMO] I'm done! I'm done!
I'm finally done!
Now, I just have to wrap it. Ah.
I can't wait to give it to him.
[MOMO]
Yes!
[PHONE VOICE]
We're sorry.
The number you have dialed
is out of service or no longer
a working number. Please check
the number and try again.
Man. I guess I can try
his home number instead.
[MAN]
Hello?
[MOMO]
Kairi!
I wanted to give you something
tonight, so could you
meet me outside your
house in twenty?
[MAN]
I'm sorry, did you say Kairi?
[MOMO]
Uh.
[MAN]
This is his older brother.
[MOMO gasps]
Whoops!
Oh, sorry about that!
You sound just like him on
the phone. Sorry, sorry!
[RYO chuckles]
Don't worry about it.
He actually just
stepped out.
I think he's at that bookstore
he always goes to.
Okay, well. Thanks a lot.
Uh! How embarrassing.
[MOMO]
I gotta say though.
Kairi's brother
sounded really nice.
There he is.
[MOMO laughs]
I think I'll surprise him.
[MOMO]
Uh!
What's she doing here?
I'm in love. Please
do this for me, Kairi.
I promise I won't ask you
for anything again.
If you're willing to do it,
I'll be at the Blossom
hotel tomorrow.
[MOMO growls] What is this?
Is she toying with him again?
Come on Kairi,
tell her to get lost already!
[sighs] Okay I'll do it.
[MOMO]
Uh?!
[MORIKA]
Thank you.
I brought you a little present.
Just a little something
for being so sweet to me.
Your old one was
looking pretty beat up.
No thank you.
No really, take it.
[KAIRI gasps]
Uh! What are you doing here?
[KAIRI grunts]
Screw you!
[KAIRI]
Uh.
[MOMO] I can't believe how
stupid Kairi's been lately.
And his brother seemed
really nice on the phone.
So I don't know what
he's talking about.
But Kairi's all I
ever think about,
why can't things be normal?
Next time on Peach Girl:
The man who creates a storm!