[KAIRI]
What good is it to go on a diet
if all it's gonna do
is make you anemic?
[MOMO]
Hey Kairi, guess wha--!
I can explain.
[STORE MANAGER]
Uh!
[MOMO groans]
[STORE MANAGER]
I'm so sorry!
The door opened so fast,
I didn't see you!
Oh, great.
I... I'm sorry.
--[MOMO cries]
--[STORE MANAGER] Ah!
No, please don't.
It's not that bad!
This stuff is almost
expired anyway!
[MOMO] It's pointless.
This isn't going to work out.
[MISAO]
I'm so sorry about that.
I didn't mean to
pass out on you.
Hey, as long as you
don't sleep n' drive!
Hey, Momo, you don't look
like yourself today.
Is everything okay?
No, it's not.
Oh. Okay. Wow, it's
really stuffy in here!
[KAIRI chuckles]
[KAIRI gasps]
I'm sorry. 'Kay?
[MOMO] It's okay. I never
expected you to apologize.
You told me when we started
dating that you were into Misao.
I accept that.
And I know it's only natural
that you would want to
kiss the one you love.
I was just surprised
that you tried to do it
while she was sleeping,
I mean that was a
pretty smooth move.
Personally, I would've
slapped you across the face!
[laughing]
[MOMO] Oh well, there's
nothing I can do about it.
I'm his second choice.
[MOMO] I wonder if we
should've broken up then?
[MOMO]
I'm back!
[MOMO'S MOTHER] Hi sweetie. Your
friend is here to visit you.
Which friend?
Hi!
[MOMO groans]
What the...?!
Aw, c'mon Mo,
don't be mad.
I thought it might be fun to
have some girl talk, please?
[MOMO]
Mm. I don't know about that.
[phone rings]
[SAE] Oh! It's Kairi!
You should answer it!
This is Sae,
what do you want?!
Uh! Sae...?! But...
Look, Kairi. I heard about
what you did to Momo,
and I'm absolutely shocked
who, does that? C'mon!
[KAIRI]
Uh-um... But... Wha-?
So, what exactly happened
between you two?
I'll just ask Kairi if
you don't wanna tell me.
[dial tone]
[SAE]
What?!
Wow. So Kairi's got two girls.
Are you like his favorite?
I mean, who does he like more?
I don't know, Sae.
Please stop asking.
Come on! You've told me
this much already, so...
I get it. You're making all
this up so I'll start a rumor
about Kairi and turn
everyone against him.
Sure.
You would never do that.
School's out.
It would be pointless.
[MOMO] I would never do it
because I'm not like that!
[MOMO]
Besides, if we break up,
they'll be plenty of rumors
already without your help.
[SAE] You really think you
guys might break up?
I hope not, but it's possible.
Just because I love him
doesn't mean he feels
the same way about me.
I can't believe it. If he had
done something like this
to me a year ago,
I would've killed him, but...
Now I just let it go because I'd
rather feel this kind of pain
then the pain of losing him.
It's sick.
I'm not myself anymore.
Everything I do is for him.
I love him so much. I want to
be with him more than anything.
Why does it hurt like this?
You seem to have forgotten
that you're still together.
Uh?
[SAE] Listen Momo.
Love isn't always easy.
There are going to be
challenges like this.
You can't assume every time
your relationship is tested
that it's over, or even
something's wrong.
It's not easy to find someone
you can fall in love with,
and it's even harder to find
someone who loves you back.
You're taking it
all for granted.
He hasn't left you for this
girl so the fight isn't over.
I mean, If I haven't
given up on Ryo,
then you can hang in
there for Kairi.
[MOMO]
Uh...
This is weird. I never thought
you would cheer me up.
[BOTH laugh]
[MOMO]
Sae made me feel better.
I guess stranger things
have happened.
How are you doing today?
Great! What a lovely smile!
Thank you! That's very sweet!
Would you like me to heat
up your lunch for you?
[MALE CUSTOMER]
Sure! Thanks!
[MOMO]
Sae was right. There's no reason
to be depressed when the
fight isn't even over yet.
I'm not giving up on Kairi.
[KAIRI]
Sae? What the...
So, how do you really
feel about Momo, Kairi?
Listen.
Listening.
Did Momo really confide in you,
or are you just making that up?
Of course she did. But I
had to push her a little.
Great. I can't believe
she's that depressed.
She's so hurt by me that
she can be consoled by you.
And what, exactly,
does that mean?!
[KAIRI] She used to say I was
the only one she could talk to.
I feel sick. I...
I've really messed
things up between us.
So here's a
question for ya:
Does this mystery woman know
she's Momo's competition?
No, she has no idea...
I've never told her how I
feel, but I'm with Momo,
it doesn't matter.
[SAE] Oh my gosh, that's it!
You need to tell this girl
how you feel about her!
Until you can get
your feelings out,
you're just gonna keep
obsessing over this girl,
and you'll never be able to
focus completely on Momo.
Thanks Sae, You're right.
I can't believe I'm taking
advice from you.
Everyone's doing it now!
But this was too easy.
Anyone could see what was wrong
with a jerk like you. [laughs]
[SAE]
This was so much fun!
I'm gonna have to hang
out with Momo more often!
[MOMO]
What?
Sae came by here?
[KAIRI] Yep. She gave
me advice and then left.
[MOMO] She did? Do you
think she's trying to help us?
Possibly.
What's really going on?
[KAIRI]
I don't know,
but all of these changes seem
a little too good to be true.
When she starts giving good
advice and being nice,
it just makes me suspicious.
[MOMO] Yeah! I know
exactly what you mean!
You do?
[BOTH laugh]
I'm really sorry Kairi. I didn't
mean to become so possessive.
It's just that,
I keep forgetting I'm not
the only girl in
your life right now.
You must've thought I
was some kind of psycho
with the way I
reacted to the kiss.
And by the way,
it's your responsibility
to tell me if I'm crazy.
Since you're the sane one.
[gasps] "The sane one," huh?
Well, don't forget,
confusion's my middle name!
[MOMO]
I'll wait, Kairi.
I'll wait for you to
make your choice,
but be honest, do you think
you'll ever love me back?
Have a good night.
See you tomorrow, 'kay?
[KAIRI]
Yeah. Okay.
[MOMO] I'll wait for you
to make your choice,
but be honest, do you think
you'll ever love me back?
[door bell rings]
Kairi!
[screams]
What are you doing here?
It's really late.
[KAIRI] What's all
over your face?
Oh, this? It's a mask.
Now, what do you want?
Well...
I, um...
[KAIRI] I wanted to know
how you're feeling.
Oh, I'm feeling great, actually.
I mean, I just took
some iron pills.
[KAIRI] Iron pills,
that's great. Bye.
[MISAO]
Kairi, wait!!
[KAIRI]
Uh?
What are you doing running
outside like this?
[MISAO]
You didn't come by
just to find out if I was
taking iron pills.
[COUPLE laughs]
I should take this mask
off, just give me a minute.
Oh, don't be silly.
[MISAO]
Huh?
That's what's so great
about you. You're so carefree.
Yet you take care of everyone.
And you... you have a big heart.
That's why...
I'm in love with you.
[laughs] Oh Stop! You're joking!
I'm not joking.
[MISAO] What on earth
are you talking about?!
You're dating Momo!
I know that, but I'm in
love with you, okay?!
I've kept this secret
long enough.
[MISAO gasps]
[KAIRI]
Please, say something.
[MISAO] I'm sorry...
I'm just in shock.
I never would have guessed
in a million years
that you felt this way about me.
Well, it's 'cause I used to
constantly hide my feelings
from everyone, but now...
Momo's helped me to see
that I can't keep shutting
the ones I love out or...
or they will never love me back.
I realized that I had to tell
you how I felt about you,
or else there might never
be an opportunity for us.
Misao, would you ever
consider going out with me?
Sorry. No.
It's just that, I love you
like a little brother, Kairi.
And I always will.
Thank you. I actually
feel a lot better now
that I've gotten that
off my chest.
[phone ringing]
Yeah?
[KAIRI]
Hey, are you asleep?
Kairi? Uh.
[KAIRI] So I just told Misao
that I was in love with her.
[MOMO]
Oh.
She turned me down! And, uh,
I actually feel okay about it.
You know I always thought
that being rejected by her
might feel like it was the
end of the world, but...
But we ended up talking
for a long time.
I actually think we're gonna
be really good friends!
[KAIRI]
So that's it.
Nothing's ever gonna
happen with me and her.
I'm sorry for drivin' you
crazy all this time.
Kairi.
[KAIRI]
Hm?
[MOMO]
Are you okay?
Yeah. Ya know, the
truth always hurts,
but I'm sure I'll be
over it soon, I mean,
I'm alive, and mostly that's
because you're here to talk to.
[KAIRI] Knowing that there's
someone who does love me
helps a lot. Thanks.
[KAIRI] But I'm not gonna be
a jerk and come running back
to you just because
Misao doesn't want me.
That's not right.
Yeah, thanks.
[KAIRI] Momo, remember
when we first started dating
and you were confused
about how you felt?
Yeah.
Well, that's where I'm at now.
I've learned some things about
myself that I need to consider.
I think we should take a break
until I know exactly how I feel.
I don't want there to
be anymore confusion.
Until then, will you wait?
[KAIRI] What am I saying? If you
find someone else, go for it.
But don't get your hopes up.
You're not going to find
anyone better than me!
Ha, ha! I know.
[MOMO] I'll wait for you,
as long as it takes.
Even if that means forever.
I trust you, Kairi.
[SAE] I can't believe
Kairi's not here today!
That really sucks!
I had so much I wanted
to tease him about! Hm!
You're quite a
piece of work, Sae.
So what's the latest?
There any new drama?
Um, no.
So, did he ever
tell that other girl
that he was in love with her?
Wow! He actually told her.
Well, what'd she say?
He said that she
turned him down.
[laughs] That's great!
Wait just a minute!
That means he's gonna try
and get back together with you!
That's not fair! I won't let it
happen! You're too good for him!
Listen to you.
[SAE]
Momo! You liar!
You told me he wasn't
working today!
Hi Sae. Why are you here?
Is that how you greet all
of your customers?!
So, how did the meeting go?
What did he decide?
[KAIRI]
Can I talk to you for a second?
The boss said we
could take a break.
[MOMO] You don't have
to follow us everywhere!
[MOMO] You were in there
a long time talking to him.
[KAIRI] Yeah he was
tryin' to change my mind.
[MOMO] Change your
mind about what?
Today's my last day.
I don't work here anymore.
I see.
So, what are you going to
do over summer break?
[KAIRI] Well, as of right now,
I plan to thoroughly think
things over while walking.
[MOMO]
While walking?
[KAIRI]
Oh yeah.
They say you do your best
thinking while walking.
I figure I'll walk
as far as I can,
and see what I can
discover about myself.
[MOMO] Hm. Well, why
don't you give some
thought to this while
you're walking?
What is it?
I'm glad you asked.
Remember when we talked about
going on a trip to the
beach where we first met?
Well, I made us a reservation
for a couple days during the
last week of our summer break.
If you discover
somewhere on your walk
that you still
wanna be with me,
then meet me at the plaza
in front of the station
at noon on that day.
I'll only wait for five
minutes, after that,
if you don't show up,
I'll assume it's over.
[KAIRI]
All right then.
Well, I'm off.
Take care!
Happy walking!
[MOMO] I need to do
some discovering as well.
I need to become stronger.
That way, I'll be able to handle
whatever decision
he finally makes.
Well that was hardly
worth it... Ugh!
I guess it's time
to put this up.
[SAE laughs]
[phone rings]
[MOMO]
Nothing.
I have to stop doing that.
I keep forgetting
that "taking a break"
means that he isn't
going to call me, either.
I guess it's only natural
to hope it'll ring.
I'm so lonely without him.
This is pathetic! I don't
want to be this girl anymore!
When Kairi gets back,
the girl who freaks out over
every little thing will be gone!
I need to start living my life
for me and not a telephone call.
I need to stop doubting
myself so much.
I just need to be stronger!
Good morning, ma'am.
[MOMO]
Uh...
[screams]
Wha-What are you doing here?!
Well, I'm... I'm working.
[MOMO]
You... you work here?
Yeah.
[MOMO]
Since when?
[TOJI] As of right now,
it's just for the summer.
Oh...
I... I can't believe it,
I mean, I work here too!
Ah!
Here, since when?
[MOMO] I've been here
since school let out.
[TOJI] This is insane...
What the hell was Sae thinking?
Are you saying that
Sae got you this job?!
[TOJI]
Yeah, she called me yesterday.
Hey, Toji!
It's me! I was wondering if you
still needed a summer job?
Today is your lucky day!
I had to quit my job
at the convenience store
because I have so
much to catch up on.
They're looking for
someone to replace me,
so I told them that
you were interested
and that you could start
tomorrow, so don't be late!
Wait! Sae! Don't hang up!
So, here we both are.
[MOMO]
Sae!
[SAE laughs]
[MOMO]
Sae! What are you tryin' to do?
As if school wasn't bad enough!
I can't believe we're both
working in the same place.
This is insane!
What am I supposed
to talk to him about?!
Hey. I can quit, if you want.
Huh?
I totally understand if this is
making you uncomfortable.
It's no big deal. I'll find
someone to take my place.
Find someone else?
What are you talking about?
Don't be silly!
I'm not uncomfortable!
Hello??
--I'm so sorry, ma'am!
--I'll be right with you!
[MOMO] Ugh! Why am I
over-reacting like this?
I'm such an idiot!
I bet this is exactly why
Sae got Toji the job here!
She wants me to be tempted
while Kairi is gone!
Well, it's pointless. Toji
and I are a thing of the past.
The only one on my mind is
Kairi. I miss him so much.
[MOMO]
What am I going to do?
I can't deny that I'm starting
to have feelings for Toji again.
Oh, where is Kairi?
I told him I'd wait for him,
but for how much longer?
Next time on Peach Girl:
The Emotional Puzzle.