[MOMO] This summer was
the first of my life
that I had a boyfriend.
[MOMO]
But the summer flew past us
because we were
having so much fun.
[TOJI]
Momo.
Is it necessary to touch
my head every time you see me?
Aww, I can't help it.
It feels so good.
So, what are the chances
you'll shave it again?
I really loved the way
it felt right after.
I have to admit
that I was shocked
when he first shaved his head
at the beginning of the summer.
This is just my way of
turning over a new leaf.
Since I already messed up
our relationship once.
I want a fresh start this time.
Uhh...
[MOMO]
So, what do ya say?
How about we run to the barber
and shave it right now.
[TOJI]
I don't think so.
[MOMO]
A new semester starts today.
We went through a lot last year,
but now we're deeply in love.
[KAKO] So how far
did you and Toji go?
[KAKO, NAMI, RITSUKO]
What? Not even first base?!
Well, remember how he was
in the hospital last year?
He had to spend most
of the summer making up
for his classes he missed,
so I would usually spend time
with him at the library after
class and do homework with him.
Sometimes on the weekends
we would go the movies
and arcade together though.
And that's all you did?
Oh, and I almost forgot.
We went to the fireworks show.
You didn't even
go on vacation?
What? Of course we didn't!
[KAKO, NAMI, RITSUKO laugh]
[KAKO]
I thought you of all people
would have done everything.
[RITSUKO] I guess Momo's
reputation was exaggerated!
[MOMO] Who cares what
they think. I'm in no hurry.
Toji and I took quite a detour
to get to where we are now,
so I want to make sure
it works out this time.
The only thing that
worries me though is...
[KAKO]
Hey, look who just showed up.
[RITSUKO]
She barely exists!
[BOYS chatter]
[MOMO]
Maybe her ego
is too damaged for her
to counterattack.
[STUDENTS chatter, gasp]
Who knows where we can
find Momo Adachi?
[indistinct chatter]
Word on the street is that you
used to be on the swim team.
And you won the swim
competition for your class.
You won nearly every
race you swam in.
And not even professionals
swim in every single event.
[indistinct chatter]
[MOMO gasps]
Please help us, Momo!
We're in desperate need
of talent this year!
Me?
[TOJI]
Swim team, huh?
[MOMO] Yeah. Apparently
most of the team
were seniors last year
and have graduated,
so if they don't
fill out the roster
they'll have to
forfeit the season.
They spent a good hour
trying to convince me to join.
[TOJI] What are you
waiting for? You should join.
[MOMO] If I spend another year
in the pool, I'll be even darker
than I already am.
It's hard enough as it is.
[TOJI] But you really love
to swim, don't you?
[MOMO]
Yeah. That's true.
[TOJI] And you know that
I don't care how dark you get.
I actually kinda like it.
All right. Well if you're cool
with it, then I guess I'll join.
It'll be fun to do
something competitive again.
[MOMO squeaks]
Eh. What's up? Are you okay?
Uh. Uh... That was weird.
It's okay. It's nothing.
Forget about it.
[MOMO chuckles]
[sighs]
[MOMO]
Why did I just think of Kairi?
I wonder what happened. I
thought for sure I'd see him...
...at least a dozen times
by now. But I guess not.
Huh...
[SANGO]
All right, Kairi,
so when are we going
to the beach together?
[MOMO] That's gotta be what
it is. Kairi is avoiding me.
[MOMO]
It's one of Sae's victims.
What's up?
[SUMIRE]
So how's Sae doing these days?
Great. She hasn't
bugged me once.
In fact, she's about as
quiet as I've ever seen her.
[SUMIRE] Looks like our plan
to expose her really worked.
Yeah. You know I always
found it weird
that all of Sae's victims were
there that day to confront her.
What a coincidence, huh?
What?!
Are you saying that
you didn't know?!
I don't know how
he found out about it,
but Kairi called me the night
before the big end
of the year swim meet.
Hey, Sumire, it's Kairi.
I understand that Sae's been
pretty mean to you in the past.
What do you say we
get some sweet revenge?
[SUMIRE] But the thing is,
Sae was mean to me
back when I was
in seventh grade.
So why should I try to
get revenge on her now?
Not to mention
it was the first time
Kairi had ever talked to me.
But when I saw what
was happening that day
I knew that Kairi organized
this not to ridicule Sae,
but to save you.
[MOMO] Why would he
go through all that trouble
just to help me?
What an idiot.
But now that I think about it,
Kairi wasn't acting like
his usual self that day.
He was saying goodbye.
[MOMO panting]
--[MOMO] Kairi!
--[KAIRI gasps]
[MOMO panting]
Hey.
[KAIRI]
So what's going on?
You look like you have
something serious on your mind.
[MOMO]
I know. I'm sorry.
It's just that... I heard
something this morning.
Sumire. She told
me everything.
[KAIRI laughs]
So you found out.
Well, you got me.
I was planning on making
you indebted to me
so I could make my move once
Toji was out of the picture.
But damn him for breaking free
just in the nick of time
and saving the day.
[MOMO]
That's what Kairi does,
he jokes around
to put me at ease.
And even though he pretends
it's by coincidence,
he's always there for me.
[KAIRI] Well, I'm glad to see
that you two are working out.
I think that's great.
You know something, Momo.
I think Toji will do a
good job taking care of you,
considering all the drama
you guys went through.
[MOMO]
Thanks, Kairi.
[MOMO] If you hadn't been there
for me, I probably would have
ended up quitting school
and running away.
Arguing with you
actually helped.
I would forget about the pain.
And, if I'd met you
before I met Toji,
we probably would have
ended up together.
[KAIRI gasps]
--[KAIRI chuckles]
--[MOMO gasps]
I didn't see that coming.
You just made my day, Momo.
[KAIRI groans]
I can't do this!
I gotta go.
[MOMO]
You okay?
[KAIRI] Trust me. If I
stick around any longer,
I'll end up trying
to hug you again.
See ya around.
[KAIRI]
Oh, one more thing.
If you ever get bored with Toji
and you're lookin' for a change,
you know where to find me.
I'll even throw in a special
kiss to sweeten the deal.
[MOMO gasps]
Ha-ha.
[KAIRI chuckles]
[MOMO]
I'm sorry, Kairi.
Thank you for loving me.
[MOMO] Why am I crying? It's not
like I'll never see him again.
[TOJI]
Momo? Momo.
[MOMO gasps]
[TOJI] You okay? You've been
staring off into space.
Oh, I'm fine. I'm
just daydreaming.
Sorry, I'm making you help
me with my homework.
I suck at math.
[TOJI]
I don't mind.
But let's hurry up and finish so
we can grab a bite. I'm hungry.
What a nice breeze.
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
No!
[MOMO gasps]
[TOJI gasps]
[MOMO whimpers]
[MOMO]
Why did I do that?
[MOMO groans]
Why did you do that?
Oh no. He must have
gotten his feelings hurt.
It's one thing to do it
to him once, but twice?
Why in the world would you not
want your boyfriend kissing you?
[MOMO] One second I'm looking
out the window, and then
the next thing I know his face
is like right up against mine
with no warning or anything.
I need plenty of time
to prepare myself for something
as huge as that, ya know?
Sure, you say that now
after going out with him
for three months.
So tell us what happened
after you pushed him away.
It was just as you would
expect. Things got awkward.
He barely even spoke
to me on the way home.
What do you guys think
I should do about this?
[SUZU,YOKO giggle]
There's only one thing
you can do at this point.
You need to make
the move yourself.
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Make the move myself?
[MOMO screaming]
[MOMO] I don't think
I can go through with this!
I wonder if Toji was
this nervous, too.
Of course he was, and
look what I did to him.
[MOMO] Why did I push
him away like that?
I wanted to kiss him, too.
More than anything.
[MOMO]
I need to kiss him.
I'm finished!
Cool. Looks good.
Is that for Toji?
Of course.
I'll use this
to initiate the kiss.
[MOMO sighs]
[MOMO] Actually this will be
more of an "I'm sorry" gift.
Then we'll kiss.
[tray clatters]
[MAYU] I don't believe
this! Come on, Sae!
[CHIYOKO]
We're being graded on those!
[KAKO]
Uh oh. Here we go again.
It's Mayu's group's turn
to rip on her.
[NAMI]
Apparently Sae used to make fun
of those girls last year, and
now's their chance for payback.
[MOMO]
Hair, check. Make-up, check.
All right. I'm ready for Toji.
[MOMO] I made this
for you in home ec.
You still like chocolate covered
cherries, right?
[TOJI]
Yeah! I love those!
[MOMO] Good. Look,
I'm sorry about yesterday.
It was all so sudden
and caught me off guard.
It's not like I didn't want to,
I just wasn't ready for it.
'Kay.
[MOMO] What else can do
to show him that I love him?
Uh, Toji.
Let's make a secret sign
for just the two of us.
A sign?
[MOMO] What if we made the shape
of an L with our fingers
as a way to say "I love you"?
Look. See. An L.
[TOJI gasps]
[MOMO giggles]
[MOMO]
I love you, Toji.
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO sighs]
[KAKO] Check out Sae over there.
She's all by herself again.
[NAMI]
She's pathetic.
[MAYU]
Sucks for her.
[MOMO]
Ready!
Yeah!
--[SAE grunts, groans]
--[MAYU] Watch this.
[SAE yelping]
[SAE groans]
--[CHIYOKO, ETSUKO laugh]
--I'm sorry! Did I hit you?
[MOMO gasps]
[SAE groans]
What's the deal?
Do you not have anyone
to practice with?
I'll play with you!
Come on! Let's go!
There's tons of room
for us over here!
[MOMO] Sorry, Kako.
Pair up with Nami.
[SAE grunts]
[SAE]
Uhh...?
I'll practice with
you. Let's go.
[SAE]
Uhh...?
Good morning, Miss Momo!
It's so good to see you!
Can I carry your bag
for you? Pretty please?!
Oh, here you go, Momo. I'll put
your slippers on for you.
I'll brush all the lint off
of your uniform, okay?
And while I'm at it I'll
polish your dress shoes, too,
all right, Momo?
It's like she's a
completely different person.
She's her butler?
Thanks, Sae.
Would you mind acting normal?
It looks like I've
made you my servant.
[SAE]
Whatever you say, Miss Momo.
Uh... Morning, girls.
[MOMO grunts]
Miss Momo, I'm sensing
some tension here.
Did you get in
a fight with Toji?
[MOMO grunts]
That is none of your business.
[SAE] I'm so sorry!
It'll never happen again!
Gotta go. Bye!
Sorry, Momo. But I can't
do silly stuff like that.
It's too embarrassing.
How come? I don't understand
what the big deal is.
It's our secret sign, Toji.
No one else will know
what it means.
Yeah, but...
Okay then! I see
what's going on.
You don't want to say
that you love me.
That is not what I meant, Momo.
Just forget it!
You obviously don't care how
I feel about this, Toji.
Now leave me alone!
[MATH TEACHER]
Toji.
Come up to the board
and finish this equation.
[TOJI]
Okay.
[MOMO] I know Toji's not the
type of guy to say I love you
so casually, but he could
at least make an effort.
Good. You can sit down now.
[MATH TEACHER]
I said you can sit down.
Is something the matter, Toji?
[STUDENTS mumble]
[MOMO gasps]
[STUDENTS whisper, laugh]
[TOJI grunts]
[STUDENTS chatter, laugh]
Okay. That's enough.
[STUDENTS laugh]
[MOMO] That was awesome.
Were you embarrassed?
No. In fact, once I did it,
it wasn't a big deal at all.
[MOMO]
Well, it really made me happy.
--[SAE] Miss Momo!!!
--[BOTH grunt]
I grabbed your books
from your locker for you!
Your next class will be
meeting in the computer lab.
Here you go. Come on,
let's get going.
[MOMO]
I don't believe this!
That was the perfect moment
and now it's gone!
[TOJI]
Momo.
[MOMO]
Wow!
[HONDA]
Hey, you two! Over here!
My friend and I work
for Men's Mon Magazine.
[MOMO]
Men's Mon? No way!
We just signed our
newest model to a big contract.
You may have heard of him.
His name's Jigoro.
[MOMO] Of course!
I know all about Jigoro!
In our next month's
issue we're featuring
fashionable high school girls
from around the city.
And you have what I call style.
I like those loafers
you're wearing.
Mind if we take some
pictures of you?
Uhh, okay.
Yes! Take all the pics you want!
[HONDA]
Are you friends?
--[MOMO] Uh...
--[SAE] Yeah!
Not really feeling
a strong presence
from you two
just standing there.
Why don't you try some poses.
Give me something fresh.
[SAE]
A scarf!
A ghost!
A baby kangaroo!
[BOTH chuckle]
[STYLIST chatter]
[HONDA]
I think we found a winner here.
I was so impressed with
what she did on the street
I had to bring her
in to the studio.
[STYLISTS chatter]
[MOMO]
Uh...
[AD EXECUTIVE A]
Looking good, Jigoro.
[AD EXECUTIVE B]
You're putting those pheromones
in overdrive today.
[PHOTOGRAPHER]
All right, folks. That's a wrap.
[ALL scream]
[AD EXECUTIVE A] One wink
and he has them fainting!
[AD EXECUTIVE B]
What else do you expect
from the hottest
model of the season?
[SAE yelps, groans]
Oh, I'm sorry. Are you okay?
[JIGORO gasps]
Yeah. Fine, but thank you.
Can you... put me
down now please?
[JIGORO gasps]
I'm sorry.
No problem. See ya!
Who is she?
[PHOTOGRAPHER]
You're looking great, Sae.
Yeah!
[MOMO] Why am I here? I'd much
rather be at home right now.
--[camera clicking]
--[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Hey, that's Jigoro!
[PHOTOGRAPHER]
All right, let's take five!
[SAE]
Miss Momo!
[MOMO] Sorry, Sae, but
I think I'm gonna head home.
What? I can't do this
all by myself.
I need your support. Please,
Momo, stay a little longer.
[MOMO] But there's no reason
for me to be here.
[SAE] Come on, don't go!
Just stay for another hour.
Please! Please!
[MOMO]
Fine.
[JIGORO] You shouldn't have
to suck up to her like that.
[SAE]
You're the guy that ran into me.
[JIGORO] What's up with
your friend's attitude?
It's annoying.
[SAE]
Uhh...
It's funny you mention that
because I hate having
to suck up to her.
But if I don't, then she'll make
my life at school a living hell.
She's a bully, but what
am I supposed to do?
I don't want to get beat up.
What a horrible bitch.
She's probably just jealous
at the fact that
you're so adorable.
[SAE laughs]
[SAE]
He's so hot!
We had great eye contact.
I'm telling you
it was love at first sight!
He's taking me on
a date this weekend.
Are you positive this guy
was one of the models
from the magazine?
He's probably an
assistant cameraman or PA.
I'm serious!
Check it out. This is the guy.
[KAKO, RITSUKO stammer]
[KAKO, NAMI, RITSUKO laugh]
You're completely delusional!
Get real! There's
not a chance in hell
a celebrity like him would
ever be interested in you!
If you insist on lying, at
least make it believable!
I'm not lying!
It's the truth! I swear!
Well, it is true that Jigoro was
at the photo shoot yesterday.
But your track record
isn't great, Sae.
If you keep lying like this
then no will ever believe
a word you have to say.
You got that?
[MRS. MARUYAMA] Move your
car! You can't park here!
[GIRLS screaming, sighing]
[GIRLS] He is so much cuter
in person! Oh my gosh!
[GIRLS screaming, sighing]
[SAE]
Huh?
[GIRLS chatter]
[SAE]
What... are you doing here?
I haven't been able to
get you out of my head.
Sae, would you like
to go out with me?
[SAE gasps]
[GIRLS screaming]
[SAE] Everyone's looking at me.
And they're all totally jealous!
Looks like this gorgeous
hunk's gonna help me
out of my popularity crisis.
[SAE squeals]
[SAE]
I am back, baby!
[NAMI] Get real! There's
not a chance in hell
a celebrity like him would
ever be interested in you!
[SAE gasps]
What's wrong?
[SAE yelps]
This seems too good to be true.
After all, I did just meet you
for the first time yesterday.
It can't be true.
You're gonna lead me on
and then just dump me for
some other girl of the week.
[SAE cries]
[JIGORO]
You poor thing.
I can't imagine how terribly
you've been treated in the past.
I would never deceive you.
From now on, I promise to
protect you. No more tears.
[ALL screaming]
[heartbeat]
[JIGORO]
Uh...?
[JIGARO gasps]
What... happened?
Huh?
[SAE laughing]
[SAE]
Now I'm really back!
[SAE] Wherever Jigoro and I go,
we always cause a scene!
My life is so luxurious now!
I don't think I'll ever
be able to go out
with a regular guy again!
Next time on Peach Girl:
"Fame Isn't Enough."