What time are you supposed
to meet up with Kairi today?
At twelve o'clock. I told him
that I'd wait five minutes,
and if he didn't show,
I'd give up on him.
You don't need to worry.
No matter what happens,
I know you'll find happiness.
Thanks Toji.
I guess I'll see you at school.
Yeah.
[MOMO]
I'm almost there.
Ha, ha! Just a little while
longer until I see my love!
[KAIRI]
I'm early.
I guess I'll just hang out here.
Good afternoon.
[KAIRI]
Hey man.
I'd like to get half
a dozen peach blossoms.
[FLOWER GUY]
Um. Sorry, we're out of peach.
They're out of season right now.
That's too bad.
Kairi?
Misao. What's up?
Nothing really. What on
earth are you doing here?
Well, I'm about
to meet Momo,
so I thought I'd get her
some flowers. I was hoping
to get her peach blossoms,
but they're out of season.
That's too bad...
So tell me about this
little trip you went on.
Where did you end up going?
I worked at a noodle shop.
You what?
Seriously. It's a long story,
but in the end I found the
answer I was looking for.
[MISAO]
The answer?
That's right.
I finally realized that the
one I love the most is Momo.
You know, Misao.
I was in love with the idea
of being with you
more than anything.
I'm curious...
If you were forced to choose
just one person in the world
who you would wanna spend your
time with, who would it be?
Without a doubt,
mine would be Momo.
She's the only girl I know that
can make me feel comfortable
and relaxed all of the time.
Kairi. You changed this summer.
[KAIRI]
Really? How?
I don't know. You just seem
to be more together.
It's a good thing. It makes
you seem more manly.
It does?! All right!
I did it!! Whoo hoo!
Well I guess you're not the
only one doing some growing up.
Today I'm going to set
my life straight as well.
Oh really? You tellin'
Ryo the truth?
[MISAO] I'm actually on my
way to see him right now.
I know he's dating Sae,
and there's probably only
a slim chance of us getting
back together, but I figure
even if he turns me down,
at least I was true with
myself, you know?
I do.
I have a feeling I'll get
cold feet once I see him.
So I'm gonna give him flowers
to help convey the message.
That's just what I was thinking
of doing with the
peach blossoms.
Did you know that they're
meaning is "I'm your slave"?
[laughs] Let me guess.
You looked that up because
it's Momo's nickname.
Yeah, plus I thought she'd
get a good kick out of it.
So have you decided what
kinda flowers to get?
[MISAO]
Red roses.
They represent passion
and true love,
which is how I feel for Ryo.
Yeah? That's what I'll get, too.
[KAIRI] Where are you
supposed to meet Ryo?
[MISAO]
Somewhere around here.
[KAIRI] Misao,
I have to be honest with you,
I'm kinda hopin' things don't
work out between you two.
I swear it's not because
I'm jealous or bitter.
I hate to throw cold water on
your dreams now that you've made
up your mind and set
things in motion, but...
My brother is such a--
--[RYO] What am I?
--[KAIRI] Uh?!
Little brother with
big opinions.
Let's not forget who saved
your stupid ass when you found
yourself in the hospital
with pneumonia,
and no health insurance card.
So. Feeling much
better I assume.
I'm fine.
Then I can stop worrying. By
the way, isn't there something
you're forgetting to say
to your big brother?
Nope. Nothin'.
I know you're a busy man, so I
wanna thank you for taking
some time out of your schedule
to visit me in the hospital.
You sarcastic son of a...
Excuse me?! I paid for your
hospital visit. Now you owe me.
It was gonna be a gift
for my sick brother,
but now I want every penny
paid back with int--!
[THUG]
Okayasu!
[KAIRI, RYO, MISAO gasp]
[THUG]
You bastard.
Thanks to you my
business is gone,
and my family is on the street!
What are you talking about?
You just couldn't handle
some healthy competition.
[growling]
Ryo!
[yelling]
[WOMAN]
Ah! Stop him!!
[siren wails]
Kairi!
[MISAO crying]
What was that guy's problem?
Why did he attack us?
Ryo couldn't have done
anything to deserve that.
It's okay. He'll be all right.
--[phone rings]
--Hello?
[MOMO]
Kairi. It's me.
Momo! Hey, uh, what's goin' on?
Look, somethin' really
important came up
and I had to run.
I'll be late. Sorry.
[KAIRI] I'll call you back
in like thirty minutes.
Do you mind hanging out
there for a little while?
[MOMO]
But...
[KAIRI]
What?
[MOMO]
But it has to be now, not later.
[KAIRI] Momo, you
still on? I'll be there
as soon as I can, okay? Just
wait for me. See you later.
[dial tone]
[KAIRI]
Are you feeling any better?
[MISAO] Yeah, I'm okay now,
or at least not so hysterical.
Sorry I lost it earlier.
Don't be sorry. You have
every right to react that way.
I'm just glad that Ryo
wasn't seriously hurt.
[KAIRI]
He should thank you for that.
If you hadn't thrown
yourself in front of him,
that guy never
woulda held back.
I'm telling ya,
Ryo is a really lucky guy.
[MISAO] Shouldn't you be
getting back to the park?
How come? I'll stay here.
Plus, I wanna hear
what the doctors say.
I don't understand.
I thought you had big plans
to meet up with Momo today.
What kind of a person would I be
to leave you when
you're all upset?
And besides, Momo and I have
all the time in the world
to be together, so she can wait.
[MISAO] I seriously doubt
she sees it that way.
Huh? Oh, no.
All this time I've been
obsessing about Momo,
and being so happy and in love.
But I never told her.
For all she knows I'm
trying to avoid her.
Oh crap!
I can't let that happen!
You should call her!
Now, Kairi!
[CELL PHONE VOICE]
I'm sorry.
The subscriber you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
She must've turned
off her phone! But why?
If you discover somewhere
on your walk that you
still wanna be with me,
then meet me at the plaza
in front of the station
at noon on that day.
I'll only wait there
for five minutes.
After that, if you don't show
up, I'll assume it's over.
[KAIRI]
I'll be back!
[MOMO]
Why was Kairi with Misao?
Did they just happen
to run into each other,
or had they planned to meet?
[KAIRI] I'll be there as
soon as I can, okay?
Just wait for me. See you later.
[MOMO] I really do
come second with him.
Why did he lead me on then?
Don't hurt me like this, Kairi.
[TOJI]
What are you doing?
Huh?
Where is he?
He said something
urgent came up,
and that I should hang out here
and wait until he
can make it back.
Oh, that's no big deal.
I thought he--
[MOMO]
But, I saw him.
He got into a cab with
Misao and drove off.
[TOJI] There's gotta be
an explanation for that.
[MOMO]
Maybe. But, you see...
I just can't wait any longer.
[KAIRI]
I'll get out here.
Hey! Hey, Momo!
Momo, it's Kairi! Hey, Momo,
where are you? I'm here.
[MOMO] Kairi,
I tried. I really did.
I wanted to be the most
important person in your life,
but I guess sometimes,
even when you try your hardest,
things don't work out
the way you'd like them to.
I don't want to be
second anymore.
And if I can't have
you to myself,
then I don't wanna have
anything to do with you.
Hi, is this Nami?
Hey, This is Kairi.
I'm looking for Momo.
Is she over there?
Sorry Kairi, I haven't seen her.
Last time I heard from her she
said she was going on a trip.
Aren't you supposed
to be with her?
So in other words,
you blew off meeting her.
She probably got angry
with you and went home.
That's what I figured,
but when I called her house,
her mom said she wasn't there.
Anyway, if you happen to hear
from her, please call me
and let me know, okay?
Let's see. Where else
could I find her?
[KAIRI groans]
[SAE laughs]
[KAIRI]
Please, not now.
[ANNOUNCER] Due to
the approaching typhoon,
please make your way
away from the beach.
The surf is expected to pick up,
making conditions
extremely hazardous.
[MOMO] There was a storm
just like this one that day.
[MOMO] I wanted to see
the ocean with you again.
Kairi. I waited for you. I gave
myself, but it wasn't enough.
I believed that message
of yours, and I waited.
Good bye, Kairi.
I truly did adore you.
[MASHER]
Woah, cool braids.
Oh, man, are you crying?
Come on, cheer up.
Some friends and I are having
a typhoon party later.
You should hang out.
I'll help you up.
Hey, stop!
[TOJI]
Get your hands off my girl.
Uh?!
[MOMO]
Toji?
Whoa, chill out. Sorry.
[MOMO]
Why're you here?
I've been following you
since you left the park.
Because I wanted to make
sure that you were okay.
I'd rather be by myself so
I can sort my feelings out.
Okay.
I'm all right.
I'll stay here a little
longer and head back home.
I really appreciate you
checking up on me though.
But you can go home now.
I'll be okay.
I'd rather go back with you.
I'm in no rush.
Uh. But I...
I don't know how much longer
I'm going to be here.
That's fine. It's a good
thing I'm patient.
You idiot! Momo said
she'd wait five minutes,
and if you didn't show up,
she'd turn her back
and forget about you.
How could you break such
an important promise?!
Do you really think she went
to the beach by herself?
It's an awfully long way.
Where else could she have gone?
This boxed lunch totally rocks!
Listen. You don't
have to come with me.
You can turn around
at the next stop.
You're not gonna get
rid of me that easy.
I'm worried about Momo too,
ya know. I feel so bad for her.
The poor thing was looking
forward to this trip
before you went and shattered
her precious little heart.
What was I thinking
when I called?
I'm such a dork.
But in all seriousness.
Momo was pinning her entire
love life on this trip.
It was very important to her.
Her entire life changed in that
five minutes she was waiting
for you, and that was all it
took for you to lose her.
If you had just
been there on time,
she was ready to accept
all your old girlfriends,
and any other problems
you two've had.
She was ready to accept you for
who you are, no questions asked.
That's how important
that promise was to her.
It meant everything, Kairi.
But I guess it was just too much
effort for you to keep
a simple appointment!
What's wrong with you anyway?
Ryo was attacked.
He's in the hospital.
Uh?!
And you didn't tell me?!
How dare you keep that from me!
I have to be by my
man's side, but I can't
because I'm on this stupid
train! So what am I gonna do?
Lemme off this friggin' thing!
There's no way!
It's an ex-!
[BOTH]
Mm?!
It stopped.
[STATION MAN]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
due to the approaching typhoon
and the possibility of
landslides on the tracks,
all train service has been
postponed for the time being.
Excuse me.
I'm trying to get home.
Do you expect the trains to be
back up and running by tonight?
I'd say the earliest
would be in the morning.
[MAN A]
This is not what I needed.
I'm gonna end up
missing the big meeting.
[MAN B]
I say we find a hotel quick.
[MOMO]
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't taken so long,
we'd be on our way home.
It's not your fault. I made
the decision to come here.
But if you didn't
already cancel them,
you've still got
reservations at a hotel.
You can just hole up there.
What are you gonna do?
Don't worry about me. I'll just
find a bench to sleep on.
[STATION MAN]
Uh, sorry sir,
but the station's closing
at eight o'clock tonight.
I'm sorry, but we're
booked up tonight.
Because of the storm, we're
only honoring reservations.
[MOMO] Great.
Now what should we do?
Okay. I'm gonna head
back to the hospital.
[KAIRI]
Right.
[INN MISTRESS]
You poor things! You're soaked!
[INN MASTER]
You guys made it just in time.
The storm's about to get worse.
I'll get started
on some dinner.
Until then, make
yourself comfortable.
Baths are through that door.
[MOMO]
What am I going to do now?
I never thought
this would happen.
Um. That bath was awesome.
Uh, yeah. So, should
we check out the room?
I put brand new linens
down for you guys.
Oh, and remember to
leave your dishes
in the hallway once you're done.
[MOMO]
This is so awkward.
[MOMO] I know. You wanna see
if there's anything on TV?
Oh, sure, great.
You'd think they'd offer
TV for free nowadays.
I got it.
[BOTH]
Uh?
[screams]
[MOMO laughs] That startled me.
It sounded like a bomb went off.
[TOJI] Momo.
I've missed you, so much
[MOMO]
Toji.
[RADIO WOMAN] With the typhoon
increasing in strength
and heading right for our area
all air and train travel...
[TAXI DRIVER] I'm telling ya,
it's impossible kid.
This storm's really pounding us.
Your best bet would
be to wait it out,
and hope you can get on a train
first thing in the morning.
Otherwise you're SOL.
I don't care. Take me
as far as you can.
[phone rings]
[MOMO] Uh? Toji, aren't
you going to answer that?
It's the third time it's rang.
[TOJI]
No.
[MOMO] But what if it's
something important?
[TOJI]
Listen, Momo.
There's nothing more
important to me in the world
than being with you right now.
Do you realize that to
this day I still dream
about the night of
your birthday party?
Every time I think of it,
I'm overwhelmed with regret.
If only I hadn't
answered the phone,
if only I had chosen
to go along with you.
Then you and I never
would've broken up.
I don't wanna lose you again.
[TOJI]
You wore these that night.
Oh. Yeah, I can't believe
you actually remember.
That's so sweet.
When it comes to you, Momo,
I remember everything.
Toji.
[TAXI DRIVER]
I'm curious kid.
What's so important that you're
willing to brave a typhoon
just to get to Shiranami?
[KAIRI]
Someone's waiting for me.
She's been waiting
a very long time.
[TAXI DRIVER] If this person's
been waiting for you so long,
then what harm would it do
to show up in the morning
or the day after?
That's exactly what
I was thinking.
Unfortunately, I learned the
hard way that's not the case...
I just assumed she would
go on waiting for me
til I was ready.
I was so naïve.
[TAXI DRIVER grunts]
[door slams]
This isn't good. Damn typhoon.
[KAIRI]
Is there a way around?
[TAXI DRIVER]
'Fraid not. This is it.
This is the only road
that cuts through
the mountains within
thirty-five miles.
Sorry kid, but I can't take
you any further than this.
Time to head back.
[KAIRI]
Hold on.
How much further is it
to the coast from here?
I don't know, twenty?
Twenty-five miles?
Thanks man. I appreciate
you getting me this far.
[TAXI DRIVER]
Are you outa your mind, kid?
You can't walk
there in a typhoon!
You're gonna get
yourself killed!
[KAIRI grunting]
[KAIRI groans]
[KAIRI panting]
I wonder if Momo's all right.
Maybe I could...!
[KAIRI]
There it is.
[phone ringing]
[INN MASTER]
Ueda Inn. How can I help you?
Yes, hi.
I'm looking for someone staying
there named Momo Adachi.
[INN MASTER]
Yes, of course.
She and her friend checked
in about an hour ago.
Ah... A friend?
[INN MASTER] If you'd like I
could leave a message with her.
Just give me your name.
Hello? Sir, hello?
[TOJI]
Thanks for everything.
You two be safe.
[TOJI]
What a gorgeous day.
It's hard to believe there was a
typhoon here a few hours ago.
[MOMO]
Yeah.
With Toji, I can find happiness.
He's always taken care of me.
Always been at my side.
[STATION ANNOUNCER] The Green
Line is now arriving on Track 2.
The Green Line is now
arriving on Track 2.
[sighs]
Uh?!
[MOMO]
But am I doing the right thing?
The part of me that loved
Kairi is telling me
not to trust these feelings.
I never actually told Kairi
that we were breaking up,
but I can't hold out on some
hope that it will work with him.
[TOJI] I really wish I could
spend time with you,
instead of going to work.
You're working the
late shift tonight?
Yeah.
Hang in there.
[TOJI] Will do.
See you tomorrow at school.
Bye!
[gasps] Momo!
[gasps]
[MOMO] Let's make a secret
sign for just the two of us.
What if we made the shape
of an 'L' with our fingers,
as a way to say I love you?
[MOMO]
Toji. Toji!
[KAIRI]
Mm. Oh, Momo.
[MOMO] All I ever wanted
was to find happiness.
It's okay for me to
be happy, isn't it?
[MOMO]
Look at him!
He's acting like nothing ever
happened! It's so obvious!
He never thought of me
the way he said he did.
In other words, he lied to me!
Well, I've had enough.
Next time on Peach Girl:
Continuous Love Storm Warnings!