[MOMO] Thank you.
[TOJI] Let's have some fun.
[SAE] There they go.
Looks like our final
shakeup had no effect...
I guess this means
Toji's the winner.
[SAE] Well that sucks.
I was really looking forward
to a perfect storybook ending.
Oh! I know!
Kairi, do you
still have my cellphone?
Yeah, I do. What's up?
I want it back
so I can call Momo
and tell her that
we saw everything.
Forget it.
What's with you today?
After all you've been through,
you're really
just gonna let them go,
cooing like deluded love birds?
At least give them one last kick
in the teeth before they go!
If I know Momo,
she'll come back from the trip
pissed at Toji and
looking for someone else.
[KAIRI] I don't want to do that.
Why don't you?
She dumped you to
go out with another guy,
so you have every right in
the world to be mean to her.
[SAE] Wait!
Where are you going?!
He's gonna confront them!
[SAE] Kairi!
I'm really sorry
I was so late this morning.
We might not be able to see
everything we wanted to.
It's okay.
We still have half the day left.
[MOMO] I can't believe
he's able to sit next to me
as if nothing happened
without asking me
why I was so late.
The last thing I'd need to
be is a disappointment to him.
Both Kairi and Toji
love you very much, Momo,
and I think what they
want more than anything
is to see you happy.
[MOMO]
I know what Misao was saying,
but is it really all right
for me to hurt Kairi
and then turn around and
be happy with someone else?
Will I be able to
forgive myself for that?
Aren't you going after Momo?
This train's going
in the wrong way!
[KAIRI] I'm going to Shiranami.
[SAE] What for?
[KAIRI] I don't know. A funeral?
Huh?
You're gonna kill yourself?
Of course not.
I want to put all my feelings
for Momo in a bottle
and throw them out to sea.
I have so much pent up emotion
I need to get rid of
before I lose my mind.
Plus, I hope
this will help speed up
the recovery process.
Well enough about me.
How did you get over
breaking up with Ryo?
You wanna know?
I'm not like guys
where they feel like
they have to repress their
anguish and push it deep inside.
That just makes it worse.
I prefer to allow myself to get
as depressed as I possibly can.
Then when it's over,
I feel better.
That's interesting...
So by pushing yourself
into such a deep depression,
it cleanses you.
I know it works for me.
You did the best
you could, Kairi.
You really love her, don't you?
I'm glad we did this.
It would have been nice if the
weather had worked out better,
but oh well.
[TOJI] Are you tired?
You've been acting kind of weird
ever since we
got off the train.
Aren't you having any fun?
I don't know. I feel like I
shouldn't be enjoying myself.
What do you mean?
Did something happen to you?
I guess so.
[KAIRI] Damn you, Toji!
You smug bastard!
Your little trip
isn't fooling anyone!
I can see what you're after,
you sick pervert!
If you don't take care
of Momo, I'll kill you!
And if you don't
believe that, just try me!
[MOMO] Dear Kairi...
I made you a new
cell phone case.
Hope you like it! Momo
[KAIRI] Why, Momo?
Why wasn't I good enough?
[quiet sobbing]
So Kairi was in Shiranami
with us the whole time?
[MOMO] I'm just angry
with myself over this.
Without knowing the whole truth,
I really hurt Kairi's feelings
when he probably
didn't deserve it.
I feel guilty about having fun
when he's miserable
because of me.
[TOJI] Are you thinking that
if you hurt Kairi's feelings
then karma will
eventually catch up to you?
[MOMO] Maybe.
I just can't stand the idea
that I'm so happy and he's not.
You think he'd be happy
seeing you down on yourself
when you could be
having a good time?
I have to admit
that I was shocked
when you started dating Kairi.
I guess I just
didn't see it coming.
The only thing
that would have made me
even more unhappy
is if you'd been alone,
so I was glad you had someone,
even if it was Kairi.
[TOJI] And I think Kairi
would feel the same way.
I also think you're afraid
of hurting people
like Sae has done so many times.
That just shows
how sensitive you are
to other people's feelings,
which I love.
Let's take Sae, for example.
Do you hate her for
what she's done to you?
Would it bother you if
she was having a good time?
Absolutely not!
Sure, it bothers me
when she gets me all worked up,
but I certainly
don't hate her for it.
I mean she's still my friend.
[TOJI] That's my point.
All wounds eventually heal,
and often they make
the bond even stronger.
[gasps]
[SAE] You feeling better now?
[MOMO]
It's really coming down now.
[TOJI] The weatherman
said that a typhoon
was supposed to hit us...
What do you want to do?
It's getting late so we could
always start to head back.
Would you prefer it
if we headed home?
I'd like to spend
a little more time with you.
[SAE] This wind is awful!
I wonder if the trains
are still running.
[KAIRI] Sae, why don't you
head on back without me.
I'm gonna hang out
here a little longer.
With a typhoon blowing in?
What happens if you
can't get back?
It's a long weekend.
I got time.
Take care. See you Tuesday.
Kairi! Hold on a sec!
Can I use your phone?
The batteries died on mine
and my parents will have a fit
if I don't call and
let them know where I am.
Fine. Here.
Thank you!
[KAIRI] Oh crap!
Where's my cell phone case?
I can't find it!
What? You mean the one
Momo made for you?
I thought you
threw it in the ocean.
Then you thought wrong!
Well so what?
You were just
gonna throw it out.
No I wasn't!
I'm gonna go look for it!
He just can't seem to let go.
How about if
I made us some tea?
Sounds good.
[KAIRI]
Where is it? Where is it?!
How could I be so stupid?!
[MOMO] I'm sorry.
[TOJI] What for?
[MOMO] I don't know.
Be honest, Momo.
Are you still in love with me?
Of course!
I've always loved you.
Where're you going?
[TOJI]
I just need to go cool off.
[cell phone beeping]
[water running]
[MOMO] Why would Kairi
be texting me now?
[MOMO] Oh no!
You all right?
Toji!
Look at this.
I'm worried about Kairi.
He sent this weird message.
Look.
What should I do?
I tried calling him back
but he didn't pick up.
Are you positive
Kairi sent this?
I didn't think he
was the type of guy
to stoop to this level
just to get some attention.
That's the thing.
I don't think
it's for attention.
He nearly died in the
ocean a few years ago.
What if he really means it?
[TOJI] Look, It doesn't say
that he's going to kill himself.
Momo!
I need to go to Shiranami.
What, are you crazy?
His text doesn't even
say he's in Shiranami.
He could be at home
for all you know.
But if we sit
around here and wait,
we'll be trapped by the storm.
If I don't leave now
I may never see him again.
I'll live to regret it
if I don't do something now.
[TOJI] Is Kairi really
that important to you?
[gasps]
I won't let you.
Get off me.
[TOJI] Let's say
you go to Shiranami.
Then what?
You look for Kairi and on the
off chance you do find him,
you talk him off the ledge?
What happens then?
If you show up there now,
he'll expect
something out of you.
I know you don't
want to disappoint him,
so will you just get
back together with him?
If you're just worried
about him, don't leave.
Unless it's more than that!
I can't take any more
of this indecisive
back and forth with you.
Why can't you make up your mind
and commit to one of us?
If you walk out that door,
then break up with me first.
[TOJI] Sorry.
Please understand...
I've been acting like
I'm okay with everything,
but the reality is that I've
been a nervous wreck lately...
I'm afraid you're gonna
leave me and go back to him,
and I don't want that.
Please, look into my eyes...
and for just one minute
pretend he doesn't exist.
[TOJI] I promise
I'll be good to you, Momo.
[TOJI] Leave.
[TOJI] I don't care
what you do, just leave!
Hey, where are you?!
This is getting ridiculous.
Where the hell did he go
to look for that thing?
[cell phone ringing]
Momo? Is that you?
Momo, I can't hear you,
are you there?
[MOMO]
Yeah, I'm here, Sae.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
I don't know what to do.
I got this awful text from Kairi
saying he might kill himself.
To think that he'd do that
because we're not going out
anymore is horrifying.
All I can think about
is going to Shiranami
to try and save him.
Right...
So you want to go to him.
Then what's stopping you
from doing that?
[MOMO] I can't just leave!
Do you have any idea how much
that would hurt Toji?
Oh Sae, I'm so confused.
[SAE] Well if you're confused,
then you need to
simplify things, right?
Since you're going to be
offending one or the other
no matter what you do,
then just pick which guy
you want to be with more.
[MOMO] I can't.
Ugh!
Look, don't you realize
you're making this
so much harder
than it has to be?
Hell, I thought you already
made up your mind on this
a long time ago.
[SAE] Just do what
your instincts tell you.
But you need to be willing
to break one of their hearts.
That's the ugly truth.
Until you're ready
to do that, you're stuck.
[MOMO] Sae's right.
Sitting around here
trying to decide
isn't going to
accomplish anything.
[MOMO] I have to go.
I have to do something.
[TOJI] Momo.
Momo!
[MOMO] I made up my mind.
I'm going to Shiranami.
Knowing how impulsive
Kairi can be,
he might actually go through
with killing himself.
Sorry, Toji...
I know it's difficult
to hear this
after all we've been through.
And I know I've
had plenty of chances
to go back to Kairi before this,
but it wasn't until I thought
I might lose him entirely
that I realized...
That I realized how much
I'm in love with Kairi!
[MOMO] I'm sorry, Toji...
I should have figured
this out a long time ago.
It's funny because even
when you picked me over Kairi
at the hospital,
I had a feeling you
weren't entirely sure
of your decision.
That's why
I've decided for myself...
You should get going.
The trains will be
stopping pretty soon.
But where does that leave you?
Momo, you don't need
to worry about me any longer.
But I want to say
that you're giving up a guy
who would have made you happy,
and I hope that
whoever you end up with
treats you as well
as I would have.
[MOMO] Thank you, Toji.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Now go before it's too late.
[MOMO] Thanks, Toji.
You're the best.
Come on, Kairi!
Knock it off already!
It's too dark
for you to even see anything.
Let's come back
when the rain stops.
It'll be brighter then.
No! I can't wait that long!
What am I supposed to
do if gets taken out to sea
in the middle of the night?
You don't make any sense!
The reason you're here
was to throw it away!
And even if you
do happen to find it,
it will never bring Momo back.
[KAIRI] I know that! I know.
I can't explain why,
but I need it!
What's wrong with me?
Why am I so incapable
of realizing
how important something
is to me before I lose it?
I don't want to be alone
the rest of my life.
[TAXI DRIVER] Yeah, it's gonna
get pretty messy around here.
The ground in the area
is very loose,
and when we get a lot of rain,
the trains have to stop.
Now I don't mean to pry,
it's just the father in me,
but what's a
young lady like yourself
doing out here in
the middle of a typhoon?
[MOMO] There's someone
waiting for me in Shiranami.
Kairi, I've come to realize
that I've been trying
to run away from you
for so long.
I was hung up on the idea
of losing someone again,
and so afraid of that happening
that I avoided facing you.
Running away
never solves anything,
but at the time it was
the easiest thing to do
to stop the pain.
Well I'm not going
to run away anymore.
This time I'll come
face to face with you
and settle things like an adult.
I just hope I make it in time.
[surfers laughing, chatting]
[KAIRI] Excuse me...!
This is my cell phone case.
I've been looking
everywhere for it.
You don't know
how relieved I am.
Where was it?
Well it's mine now...
Unless you can show
some proof that it's yours.
You want me to prove it?
Sure, no problem.
I'll just have Sae come over.
She's good friends with
the girl that made it for me.
[SURFER A] Oh, she is?
Well I don't see anyone.
If you ain't got no proof,
then you ain't getting it back.
[surfers laughing]
Look man,
I'm not trying to scam you.
Someone very important
made that for me as a gift.
I've been looking
for it since last night.
I just want it back.
Well if this thing really
is that important to you...
...then I deserve a reward.
For finding it!
Oh, okay.
Huh... That's strange.
I think I might
have lost my wallet, too.
[SURFER B] What an idiot.
[SURFER A] Borrow some cash
from that chick you came with,
if she even exists.
Then I'll consider
giving it back.
Get off me, man!
I'm definitely not
giving it back now, you punk!
Let's jump him!
[KAIRI groaning]
Enough, Johnny, stop it.
Please. All I want
is for you to give it back.
Come on, guys.
Just do what he says.
Yeah, Johnny,
it's not funny anymore.
Sure, I'll give it back...
There!
[SURFER A]
Good luck finding it.
You're a jerk.
Yeah, get lost.
Where're you going?
Hey, wait up!
It was just a joke!
[KAIRI] Okay. Where is it?
[yells]
[coughing]
I'll find it.
I don't care
how long it takes me.
[MOMO] Thank you so much.
Keep the change.
[TAXI DRIVER] You take care.
[coughing]
[KAIRI] I found it!
Is that Kairi?
Oh my gosh!
[KAIRI] This isn't good.
I can't even move my legs.
I don't want to die yet.
Not before I see Momo
one last time.
[MOMO] Kairi! Kairi, wake up!
Can you hear me?!
[gasps]
[MOMO] He's not breathing!
[MOMO]
Come on, Kairi, wake up.
I came here for you.
You can't die on me!
Please, Kairi!
Wake up, Kairi!
Wake up! Open your eyes!
I can't live without you!
Did you hear me? I can't!
Kairi...
[sobbing]
[MOMO] Kairi!
[coughs]
[coughing]
Oh hey, Momo.
What are you doing here?
Are we in heaven?
Awesome. If I get to be
with Momo in heaven,
then I don't mind dying.
You dummy!
I just saved your life, so don't
you dare talk to me about dying!
Do you have any idea
how worried I was about you?
[KAIRI] So I'm alive?
Thank you, Momo...
Thank you for saving me!
I adore you.
I love you so much, Kairi.
Now wait a second...
How'd you know where to find me?
I never told you where I was.
You're kidding, right?
You sent me that
awful text message.
Where you said you'd
become fish food in Shiranami?
Hold on...
I never sent you
a text message.
Sae still has my phone.
Want a photo to commemorate
the beginning of
your future together?
By the way, the one who
sent the text message was...
...good ole' Sae.
I knew it!
Come and get me!
You're gonna pay for that!
[SAE laughing]
[SAE] Who cares?
It all worked out in the end!
[MOMO] That's not
the point, you psycho!
[MOMO] We met on the beach, and
the ocean has bound us together.
So many emotions
have dissolved in the sea.
[MOMO] I've made up my mind.
I can honestly say
I'm happy now.