[MOMO] Oh no. This is bad.
I have to get outta here.
Let go of me! I have to leave.
[MOMO yells]
I won't let you.
Don't. Please get off of me!
Let me go!
[MOMO grunting]
[RYO groans]
[MOMO panting]
[MOMO]
Ah!
[MOMO grunts]
[panting]
Why are you doing this?
Can't you see that no matter
how much I look like
your dead girlfriend, nothing
you do will bring her back?
You can't just replace
her with me!
Please. I'm begging you, Ryo.
Don't do it. I have nothing
but respect for you.
I know you're better than this.
[MOMO gasping]
I can't help myself.
I love you too much.
[MOMO]
Mm. No! Kairi!
[KAIRI panting]
He must have taken Momo
somewhere around here.
But which door? Momo!
[MOMO]
No!
--[MOMO grunts]
--[RYO groans]
[RYO groaning]
[RYO]
Ah!
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO screams]
[MOMO panting]
[MOMO]
What did I do?!
[MOMO yelps]
[KAIRI]
Momo.
[MOMO whimpers]
Are you okay?
What happened? Did Ryo try
to hurt you or something?
He did... He tried...
Oh my God!
[RYO groaning]
I'm here Ryo! What
happened to you?
[RYO] I'm all right.
It's nothing serious.
[SAE]
Uh!
[SAE] You're bleeding,
oh, you poor thing.
Wait. Did Momo do this to you?
Yeah. She really took
me by surprise.
She was climbing all over me.
And when I told her I wasn't
interested, she attacked me.
I fell backwards and knocked
those tables on top of me.
What?!
You were right
about her all along.
I honestly never imagined she
would come after me like that.
I should've listened
to you before.
[KAIRI] Wait here.
I'll check inside.
[MOMO] But if he's hurt,
then it's my fault.
I'm the one who pushed him.
[KAIRI] If he's alive,
I'll beat him to a pulp.
[KAIRI]
He's not here.
Where did he go?
Look. If he walked
out on his own,
then he's not seriously hurt,
so I wouldn't worry.
Ah. Thank goodness.
Momo. You okay?
[MOMO]
Uh?
Thank you, Kairi.
I'm so glad you're here.
[MOMO sighs]
[KAIRI] I'm just glad
nothing happened to you.
[MOMO] I was scared!
He was so nice to me.
I never thought he'd
do something like that.
[KAIRI]
It's gonna be okay.
I'm sorry about all this,
Kairi. I'm sorry.
[MOMO]
Next time you see your brother,
will you give this
back to him for me?
I don't want it. I can't return
the feelings that he has for me,
and I definitely can't take
the place his dead girlfriend.
Excuse me? Ryo said he had
a girlfriend that died?
That's the biggest load
of crap I' ever heard.
Before he dated Morika,
he went out with another girl
that he also stole from me.
[MOMO] Really? But Ryo
said that he loved me
based solely on the fact
that I look like her.
Hold on. My brother said
that he was in love with you?
What a hypocrite.
You should've heard what
he said to me about you.
[MOMO]
Uh?!
Earlier, when he
pulled me aside.
Listen bro, you need
to leave that ugly broad.
I asked her to come to this
party and she followed
like a sheep. You can tell she's
been around the block.
If you hadn't shown up,
we'd probably be in bed by now.
[KAIRI grunts]
[MOMO]
Uh...
So, when he said he loved me,
that was just a lie?
He'll go to whatever
lengths necessary
just to get
under my skin.
What about everything
with Morika?
Because he said he was dating
her way before you did.
He even told you about that? Is
nothing sacred with that jerk?
Let's get this straight!
I dated her first!
[MOMO]
He lied to me about everything.
Ryo manipulated me just
like Sae used to.
You were right all along.
When we talked yesterday,
everything he said to me was
so nice and considerate,
and when I was really
upset with Sae,
talking to your brother
calmed me down.
That's the trick he uses,
and everyone falls for it. See?
And...
And what?
I mean, he is your older
brother after all.
Maybe I saw a future version
of you when I talked to him.
Momo. I will never
be like my brother.
That's good.
I hope you stay just the way
you are right now, Kairi.
Uh. Wait. One more thing.
Your brother was able
to force a kiss on me.
He kissed you?
I couldn't stop him!
You'll never wanna kiss me
again for the rest of my life.
Uh?
After I sanitize your lips,
you'll be okay.
[MOMO]
Kairi. I love you.
[SAE] Thank God your
injury wasn't serious.
[RYO] Thank you, Sae.
I feel so grateful
that you found me
and walked me to the hospital.
[SAE]
Oh, it was nothing.
Really? I felt like my guardian
angel had come down to save me.
[SAE sighs]
[RYO]
Oh, I have something for you.
[SAE]
Uh?
For being my angel.
[SAE gasps]
It's for me?
Let me put it on for you.
[MOMO] I am so late today! Oh
no, all the lockers are taken.
[SAE]
I have an open one over here.
Yeah? Thanks a million.
[MOMO]
Uh?
[SAE laughing]
Uh, hi.
That necklace! Why?
Ryo, who you seem to be so head
over heels in love with,
is now madly in love
with me, bitch.
You two are a couple?
Since when?
Since none of your damn business
so don't worry about it, okay?
He even called me
his guardian angel.
You idiot! It's all
an act with him.
Trust me, Sae, he's playing
you like a fiddle!
Listen to all the jealousy
just because he didn't give
you the time of day.
Oh please. I am not jealous.
The guy's a scumbag and
besides, what about Toji?
Ah yes, Toji.
Lately I've come to realize
that spending time with Toji
is about as fun as counting
the hairs on my head.
What is your deal?
Oh, here's an idea! You two
should get back together!
[MOMO]
Uh!
You know you want him
back. Now thank me.
You're out of your mind.
The only man in my
life now is Kairi.
Yeah, sure.
Then if I were to set
my sights on dating
both Toji and Ryo at the same
time, you wouldn't care, right?
Great, I'm glad I have your
blessing. Later, loser. [laughs]
[KAIRI]
What?! Ryo and Sae?
Yup.
Man they'd be a shoe-in for
the worlds scariest couple.
Sae's being ridiculous,
but we've come to expect
that from her. What I wanna
know about is your brother.
How many of those necklaces
does he carry around?
[KAIRI]
That's it.
I'm going to my brother's office
to confront him about this.
[MOMO]
Why?
He called last night to say
he wasn't coming home
for a couple of weeks.
And with the crap he
tried to pull with you,
he and I need to talk
this through like men.
Then I'm coming with you.
[KAIRI]
Uh?
I wanna hear him explain
why he's going out with Sae.
But more than anything else,
I wanna slap him in the face.
Are you sure you're
up to this, Momo?
Yeah. As long as
you're with me.
I almost forgot.
Momo, I want you to have this.
It's for protection.
It's pepper spray,
and If he tries anything
funny with you again,
just spray him in the eyes and
you'll have time to get away.
Thanks Kairi. You're so sweet.
[FEMALE WORKER] Mr. Okayasu?
He was here just a minute ago.
[KAIRI]
Would you mind if we wait?
[FEMALE WORKER]
Not at all.
[KAIRI] Geez, he sure
is taking his time.
He probably found
out we were here
and snuck out through
the back door.
I need to go to
the ladies room.
[water running]
Ryo, I can see you
in the mirror.
Nice try though.
Woah, look at that. Isn't that a
bit dangerous for you to have.
Not when I'm being
stalked by a sicko,
especially in the
women's bathroom.
All right. I just wanted
to apologize to you
about yesterday. You're just so
cute, I couldn't help myself.
[MOMO] Is that the same
line you told to Sae?
[RYO gasps]
You know about that already?
Sae really likes to
talk, doesn't she?
What're you doing with her?
How can you fall in love with
someone that you just met?
Hey, all we did
was make out once.
Who said anything about
falling in love?
[MOMO gasps]
Whoa, hey! I'm sorry.
I'll never touch you again.
Every single thing you said
to me yesterday was a lie,
wasn't it, Ryo?
Kairi told me the truth,
and now it's your
chance to do the same.
Did you really steal
all his girlfriends?
That's true.
I don't understand why you would
do that to your own brother.
I mean, do you really
hate him that much?
That's not the
case at all.
I happen to love my little
brother very much.
In fact, I cherish Kairi.
[MOMO] He's more
demented than I thought.
[MOMO]
And let me guess,
when Morika slapped you in
the face outside your apartment,
it was because you tried doing
the same thing with her.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Kairi was right about you
from the beginning.
You truly are a despicable
human being, Ryo.
That's a bit harsh.
I'll be the first to admit that
I'm fast with most women.
But I do possess a
few redeeming qualities.
Somehow I doubt that.
If there's someone I truly love,
I'm too scared to make a move.
I guess I'm a lot like
Kairi in that way.
But after all, he is my
little brother, ya know?
[MOMO]
Huh?
Aren't you getting a little
frustrated with him?
Don't you wish he would make
a move once in a while?
Honestly, it just
seemed like you
needed a little
bit of attention.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Kairi can't keep his...
Why am I talking to
you about this?
It's none of your business,
and you can't be trusted.
Don't come any closer.
I'm gonna get my phone and
have Kairi meet us in here.
[MOMO]
Hey, it's me. Where are you?
What? He's in the ladies room?
Hang on Momo,
I'm on my way right now.
He'll be here in a minute.
Momo. Just answer
one thing for me.
Does Kairi get
intimate with you?
[MOMO]
You never quit! Yes, he does.
[RYO gasps]
That means you can't be
the one that he's truly
in love with.
[MOMO]
Uh?
He must still be
in love with her.
Wait, what? With who?
[MOMO]
Uh!
I'll See you around, Momo.
If you ever feel lonely
one night, you know
where to find me.
Where is he?
[MOMO]
Uh, he just left.
That bastard.
Are you doing okay?
Who the hell does he think he
is, coming into the ladies room?
[MOMO] I know I shouldn't
let his words bother me.
But there's something
about what he said.
All done. See ya.
I'm gonna empty
your trash for you.
[MISAO]
Thanks girls.
You seem little glum.
[MOMO]
Huh?
Is there something
bothering you?
[MOMO]
Uh...
That necklace.
Oh, this old thing?
It was a gift from Ryo Okayasu.
It doesn't have any real
significance for me anymore.
It was just the first thing I
saw laying around this morning.
It's been so long,
I can't even remember
the last time I saw him.
I happened to run
into him yesterday.
You actually saw him?
Where? How's he doing?
Does he still look good?
Um, he's fine I guess.
But don't you think it'd
be a good idea to keep
your distance from him?
He gives that same necklace
to every girl he meets.
I'm curious, when
he gave it to you,
did he turn real creepy and
try to seduce you with it?
No way. Ryo's a great guy.
He would never try to pull
something like that.
Why would you say that, Momo?
Um.
[MOMO] Just speaking from
personal experience.
I was talking to Kairi and
he said that his brother
always fools women
with that trick.
[MISAO]
Yeah, well what else is new?
You know he's made a habit out
of badmouthing his brother.
So you're positive Ryo never
tried anything creepy with you.
Of course not.
[RYO]
If there's someone I truly love,
I'm too scared to make a move.
[MOMO] Wait. Maybe the one
Ryo's in love with is...
[MOMO groans]
What's the matter Sae?
Is there something wrong?
[SAE seethes]
[MOMO]
Uh!
I hope you're happy
Miss Perfect,
'cause Ryo cancelled
our date today!
[MOMO gasps]
Where do you get off telling
him to break up with me?
Just because he dumped your ass
doesn't mean you have
to sabotage my life!
Hold on. Let's talk somewhere.
Get off of me!
I never wanna see your
ugly, leather face again!
And if you ever try to pull
another stunt like this,
I'll make it so you can never
step foot in this school again.
Ryo? Did she mean Ryo Okayasu?
[MOMO] Way to go Sae. Now I
have to deal with Nurse Misao.
Don't even listen to Sae.
It's not like they're
going out or anything.
Ryo was just polite to her,
so now she has one of those
innocent crushes on him.
[MISAO]
Okay.
But I'm sure Ryo has no
intention of actually
going out with her. In a few
days, Sae will forget about him.
There's no need to explain.
It's none of my business anyway.
[thunder]
[KAIRI]
There's some cover!
[MOMO]
Hurry!
Man this weather sucks.
I'm soaked.
[MOMO] Wasn't supposed to
start raining until tonight.
Well, there's no sign
of it letting up.
[KAIRI gasps]
--[MOMO] What?
--[KAIRI chuckles]
Your mascara's running
from all the rain.
Huh? Ah! Oh, no!
[MOMO groans]
Don't stare!
I don't mean to,
but you're so adorable.
Oh I'm a mess. I can't go
home looking like this.
Then clean up at my place.
It's right around the corner.
[MOMO]
Uh...
[KAIRI] Here's a towel and a
change of clothes for you.
You can take a shower
if you want.
Thank you.
Don't worry. My parents
work all day long.
They won't be
home until tonight,
so take your time.
I'll be in the other room.
[MOMO] I just realized
I came home with him,
and it's only the
two of us here.
I'm about to take a
shower in his house.
Anything could happen.
Uh! What should I do?
I'm too nervous!
[door opens]
[KAIRI] That was fast.
Did you not shower?
Uhh. No. I thought it might be
rude of me to take a shower
in a house I've never
been in before, ya know?
I don't think it's rude,
but whatever floats your boat.
Why are you sitting
way over there?
Just so you know I'm going home
as soon as my clothes are dry.
Don't be embarrassed! Come here!
Why is it that the only thing
that's ever on your mind is sex?
[RYO] That means
you can't be the one
that he's truly in love with.
Well you can't blame
a guy for trying.
Hey, what do you say we start
planning our big vacation?
Where'd I put those pamphlets?
[MOMO]
I'm not sure why,
but what Ryo said is really
starting to bother me.
[KAIRI]
Momo?
[MOMO]
Uh?
You were staring off into space.
Are you still wanting to go?
[MOMO]
Uh!
[KAIRI] You just don't
seem too enthusiastic.
No, I do wanna go, really.
There's just something
on my mind, that's all.
Maybe you can help
me out with this.
Do you ever find yourself
worrying about what
other people are
saying about you,
and then start dwelling on
it and doubting yourself?
Sure. Of course I do, Momo. I
always have doubts about myself.
Really?
[KAIRI]
Ever since I started dating,
girls have always betrayed me.
Every single girlfriend
I've ever had in my life,
has ended up dating my brother.
I often wonder why I
haven't run away from here,
to get a fresh start on life.
Wow. I have to admit,
I'm surprised to hear that.
I guess I just always assumed
that you were more together
than anyone else at our school.
Oh, I'm anything but together.
It's like the things I really
want are so unreachable.
The things that you really want?
Yeah.
[MOMO] Kairi. Did I make
you doubt yourself too?
Uh. Hey. Are you okay with this?
You usually pull away.
[MOMO]
Not anymore.
You know, I don't think
I've ever said it
while looking into
your beautiful eyes.
[KAIRI inahles]
[MOMO]
Kairi. I love you.
This is amazing.
I've never felt as strongly
for someone as I do right now.
[MOMO]
I love you so much, Kairi.
What's wrong?
Sorry.
[MOMO]
Uh?
I don't think this
is a good idea.
[MOMO]
What?
I don't understand.
Did I upset you somehow?
[KAIRI]
It's not your fault. It's me.
[MOMO]
Uh...
What a jerk!
I was laying there
with my mind made up.
I must have looked like a fool!
How embarrassing!
I could die right now!
I'm just so shocked.
How could he reject
me like that?
Or maybe...
Yeah, maybe he changed
his mind at the last minute
because he loves me so much.
Because he wants
it to be really special.
That's got to be it!
[MOMO] Oh, no. There he is.
I can't talk to him.
No, I have to at least
go in there and say hi.
[MOMO]
Kairi!
[KAIRI]
Uh?
Good morning.
[MOMO]
Did he just ignore me?
Hey Kairi.
Wanna grab some lunch?
Where're you going?
I know you can hear me!
[bell rings]
Kairi! Why are you avoiding me?
What? I'm not avoiding you.
Don't lie to me. You've
been ignoring me all day.
If something's bothering you
then just come out and tell me.
You're being paranoid.
I would never consider
ignoring you on purpose.
I was just busy today,
that's all.
Okay. Fine, whatever.
Do you wanna walk home together?
Sorry Momo, I can't.
I have some stuff I have
to do for my parents.
But I'll see you in
the morning, okay? Bye.
[MOMO]
Something's wrong.
He's not acting
like his usual self.
We planted peach
seeds right here.
Then little by little,
my heart opened up to him.
And now, it's in full bloom.
[MISAO]
Momo?
[MOMO]
Uh? Oh, hello.
--[door opens]
--[MISAO] Come on in.
[MOMO] I really appreciate
you taking the time to listen.
No problem. I'm gonna change
out of my work clothes.
Make yourself at home.
Thanks. Let's see...
Hey, would you mind
if I take a look
through one of your
photo albums?
[MISAO]
Go right ahead!
Oh wow, so cute!
Uh! I don't care for that one
so much. Hey, it's Kairi!
[MOMO] This must have been taken
back when she was tutoring him.
Look at how cute
he was back then.
[MOMO]
Uh?
[MISAO] Here you go.
Oh yeah, I like that one.
It was taken when I
went on a summer trip
with the Okayasu boys.
We were in a panic on the way
home because Kairi disappeared.
--[door bell]
--[MISAO] Coming!
[MOMO]
Why did he disappear?
--[door opens]
--[MISAO] You're here again?
[KAIRI] What do you mean
again? Can't I visit?
[KAIRI] I'm getting hungry.
Have anything to eat?
[MOMO]
Do you come here often?
I saw Misao's photo album.
She has the same picture that
I found in your school planner.
When I first saw it I
thought it was Morika
that was in the picture, but it
was Misao, wasn't it Kairi?
Does it mean what I think it
does?
That you're still in love with
her, after all these years?
Come on. Are you going to answer
me or just stand there?
[KAIRI]
It's true.
[MOMO gasps]
[KAIRI]
I'm sorry.
[MOMO]
What are you saying Kairi?
That you want to break up?
If we do, I'll cry,
I swear,
I'll cry for so long
that I run out of tears!
Kairi, why can't I
be the one you love?
Next on Peach Girl:
When Love Reaches Rock Bottom.