Hug me.
[MOMO] What? Are you insane?
I wouldn't do that!
Even if I had my clothes on!
Don't you dare take another
step! If you do I will scream!
Please, Kairi, I'm serious.
Don't! I mean it! Stop!
[KAIRI]
Momo.
You don't need to cry anymore.
[KAIRI] The other day when
you cried on my shoulder.
I was really touched.
I thought it was sweet.
[KAIRI]
You know what?
When you're with Toji, I always
notice that your face lights up
like a kid on their birthday..
I love that beautiful
smiling face of yours.
[KAIRI] I only wish I could
summon that smile myself.
I want you to be happy.
For the rest of your life.
Thanks, Kairi.
[KAIRI] See ya 'round. Good luck
with the rest of the swim meet.
[MOMO] Why is my heart
pounding like this... for him?
[STUDENTS chatter]
What's your deal?
You suck!
Hey, Momo! You need
me to get you...
[NAMI] Did you bring
your game this time?!
[MALE STUDENT D]
I hope you drown!
[POOL ANNOUNCER] Now up is the
women's one hundred meter relay.
Listen, Momo, you're the
anchor for this relay.
You better stop
dogging it out there.
You're supposed to be
the most experienced swimmer!
Are you even listening to me?
Oh, sorry.
Momo looks catatonic. She's
really starting to piss me off.
I know. It's like
she's not even trying.
[SAE]
Sorry, boys.
I think this all
may be my fault.
Why?
What are you
apologizing for, Sae?
I think Momo hates that
you guys are on my side.
So by losing all her races
it's her way of getting revenge.
Isn't that terrible?
I don't believe this! That means
she's losing on purpose!
[SAE giggles]
[YUJI] So she's willing
to sabotage the races
just to get back at us? Man....
No kidding. But seriously, this
is nothing compared to the crap
she's pulled lately trying
to break up Toji and Sae.
What'd she do exactly?
Haven't you heard?
When I'm not around she
physically attacks him!
She even went so far as to
break into his hospital room
and threaten to leap
out of the window
if he didn't agree to date her!
[KAIRI grunts]
[SAE gasps]
That's funny...
Because I just so happened
to hear a completely
different side to that story.
All right, guys, listen up.
--Toji's actual girlfriend is...
--[SAE yelps]
Mo--
Excuse me! I need to
borrow him now!
--[SAE] Be right back!
--[KAIRI] Hey!
[MOMO] I can still feel
Kairi's arms around me.
[MOMO] I can't believe
how perverted he can be.
Coming into the
girls locker room
while I'm in nothing but a towel
and practically groping
me against my will!
But the truth is...
I actually feel relieved.
For once, someone seemed to
genuinely care
about my feelings.
[MOMO] Of course I want
him to comfort me.
With all the drama going on
between me, Sae, and Toji,
I came to depend on him
being by my side.
That's why when he put his arms
around me, I didn't fight it.
[MOMO]
Ugh! What's wrong with me?!
I'm acting like I'm in
love with Kairi! Ugh!
Wake up, Momo! Here she comes!
You need to move it to win this!
[MOMO] I guess I never
realized until now...
...that I could switch from
one guy to the next so easily!
[KAIRI] Meet me back
by the bench in 30.
I've got something to show
you that you need to see.
[TOJI sighs]
I'm the one who should be
breaking up with you!
[TOJI grunts]
[SAE]
Kairi! Wait up!
[KAIRI]
Get lost!
Huh?
[SAE]
Will you stop already?
Look you're not
gonna get anywhere
by telling everyone
the truth about me.
Why's that?
Because if you don't shut up,
I'll have to tell the Principal
that you molested me behind
the dumpster after class.
You'll be expelled
from school for that.
Good enough reason, jerk?
I'm scared!
Okay, okay. You're totally
right, Sae. I give in.
I promise I won't tell anyone
about all that nasty
stuff you've done.
You know you're actually
pretty sharp for a chick.
You're very quick witted and
can read people on the fly.
Hell, it's almost as if you have
the entire class mezmorized
like you're some sort of
master at mind control!
How is it that you can get them
to believe anything you say?
They're like puddy in
your hands! It's brilliant!
Please, you have to tell me
your secret! I want to learn!
[SAE chuckles]
It's actually quite simple.
If you happened to see
a lion in front of you,
and next to that lion
is a wounded gazelle.
What would you assume happened?
Well, I would assume
that the lion
had attacked the poor,
defenseless gazelle.
'Kay. Now what if Momo
and I are together
and I happen to be crying?
Ahh....
It's the same thing.
The point is, the first one
to cry always wins.
You'd be amazed at how
people just assume
that the person who
looks weaker is the victim.
Fact is, when I said
that Momo was trying
to steal Toji away from me,
not a single person doubted
it was anything but the truth.
'Course it helped that
I had been spreading rumors
all over school that made Momo
look like a backstabber.
Everyone judges things from
what they see on the surface.
Even Toji's guilty of that.
Oh, I get it.
That explains why Momo and I
were always one step behind.
I've gotta say you
really surprise me.
You're quite the actress.
I'd be a lucky man if I were
born as clever as you are, Sae.
Your intelligence and wit exceed
almost everyone in school,
including the teachers.
And you can't look past
your gorgeous body.
Sure you have some ugly
personality traits,
but with these assets,
it's easy to look past them.
[SAE giggles]
[KAIRI]
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Allow me to introduce Japan's
most notorious man-killer,
--Miss Sae Kashiwagi!
--[SAE laughs]
But it's a worthless title.
[SAE groans]
[KAIRI] Your reign is
about to end, Sae.
[SAE]
Hmm?
Pretty soon Toji will be
released from the hospital.
If he denies that
you're his girlfriend,
then all the lies you've
spread will be exposed,
and you'll be painted as the
most evil girl in school.
You are such an idiot.
As soon as this swim meet's
over summer vacation starts,
and if I can make Toji my
boyfriend over the break,
then I win.
[KAIRI] Sounds like you
have it all worked out.
Yeah, I do. Now get lost.
Being seen with you
isn't helping my image.
Fine. And in return,
you might wanna try
being a little nicer to Momo
from now on, okay?
Later!
[KAIRI chuckles]
Hmm.
Toji.
That was a perfect
introduction to the real Sae.
[KAIRI]
Shocking, huh?
While we're on the
subject of kissing people,
why don't you go ahead and
explain to me what was going on
between you two in the garden?
Where did you get the idea
that its okay to go around
kissing other girls to practice
kissing the girl you like?!
I didn't think it was humanly
possible to be that stupid!
You're a stupid,
stupid boy, Toji.
[crying]
[TOJI]
Momo.
[SAE humming]
[SAE]
Hm?
What's going on?
No, let me guess.
We lost another race?
Ha... Guess again.
[ANNOUNCER] And coming in first
from Class Three is Momo Adachi!
Uh?
[TORU] She's won
three races in a row.
[ANNOUNCER]
And there's the start
of the women's
100-meter freestyle.
Breaking out to an
early lead is Momo Adachi.
She's already two full lengths
ahead of her nearest competitor
before the first turn!
[YUJI]
What happened to Momo?
I can't believe how fast she is.
[SAE]
Damn her.
[MALE STUDENT F]
She's amazing!
--[YUJI] Unbelievable!
--[SAE growls]
[TORU] I take back what
I said about her!
[OKADA] Who was it again
that was saying Momo was
losing on purpose? They need to
get their head checked out!
[OKADA yelps]
Woah, Okada! You okay, man?!
[HIRO]
He's out cold. Who threw that?
[SAE growls]
[TOMIKO]
This isn't fair.
Class Three has a swim team
member in all their races.
Look, isn't that the girl
we saw in the locker room?
Hey, what's going on?
[REN]
We saw her hugging a boy
and the only thing she
had on was a towel.
[CHO]
No way.
[EIKO] Did you get a good
look on who the guy was?
Of course. It was Kairi
from Class Four.
[TOMIKO] Get out! So I
guess it's true then, huh?
[CHO]
You mean about them going out?
[REN] Well, it's pretty
obvious now, don't ya think?
[SAE chuckles]
[MALE STUDENT J]
Man, I'm starving!
[MALE STUDENT K]
Momo! Nail that next race.
[MALE STUDENT L]
What's up, All Star?!
[YUJIO]
Keep it up, Momo.
[MALE STUDENT M]
I'm betting on Momo!
[MOMO]
This is strange.
I've gone from being
the least popular
to the most popular girl
in under an hour.
It probably won't last though.
[SAE] Sounds like your
stock sure has risen.
[SAE]
Hm.
You know I heard about you
throwing yourself at Kairi
in the locker room
with nothing but a towel on.
I would have loved
to have seen that!
Oh, Momo.
Here you are, barely
broken up with Toji,
and already you're getting
it on with some other guy.
I have to question
your taste on this one.
Kairi's famous in this school
for being a sex-crazed pervert
who will sleep with
anything that moves.
[MOMO grunts]
[SAE]
Everyone knows
that Kairi's never had a
real relationship.
He'll just have his fun with you
then toss you in the gutter
like he would with any girl
he picks up in the hallway.
I mean, just look at him.
He's the poster child
for a shallow,
good for nothing,
all around loser.
Granted he is kind of cute,
but that's all he's got
going for him.
Marginal looks with
a void inbetween the ears.
Or maybe you like that.
You don't know.
You don't know anything
about Kairi so shut up.
[SAE gasps]
[KAIRI] So I take it you've
never been involved with someone
as conniving and manipulative
as Sae before, huh?
You're too naïve man.
That's why she could take
advantage of you so easily.
You must come from a
good, honorable family.
[KAIRI]
You all right?
[TOJI] Hold on. I don't think
I can show my face to her.
Oh, come on.
[SAE crying]
Why?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
[SAE] I was minding my own
business! I didn't do anything!
And then Momo, she...
Stop it!
Okay, he may not
be the perfect guy,
but Kairi does have a lotta good
things going for him!
And at least he's honest.
But, Momo!
I thought we were friends!
[SAE cries]
Geez, Momo. I don't know
what just happened here,
but there was no reason
for you to hit her.
No kidding. Everyone in class
is digusted with the way
you've been trying to disrupt
Toji and Sae's relationship,
but since you've been
swimming so well today,
we were willing to root for you
and give you another chance.
And now you've gone ahead and
flushed that down the toilet.
[STUDENTS chatter]
[SAE snickers]
[KAIRI]
Comin' through.
[TOJI, KAIRI gasp]
No way. If there's anyone who
should be apologizing, it's Sae.
Are you delusional? You just hit
her in the face for no reason!
[YUJI] Poor thing. Her
cheek is starting to swell.
Oh no... This is not good...
It's just like the lion
and the gazelle.
Who cares about that?
We have to help her.
Hold on.
I've got the perfect plan.
[TOJI]
Where are we going?
If we don't hurry back and stop
them, they'll eat Momo alive.
[KAIRI]
There it is.
Hold on. How's a piece
of rope supposed to help us?
[TOJI gasps]
--Ha! I gotcha, dumbass!
--[TOJI grunts]
Get in there!
You come in here
at the last minute
and expect to save the day
and get the girl?
Sorry, bro, but this is my big
chance and I'm not giving it up.
Momo knows that I've been
on her side the entire time.
And she's gonna be so impressed
when I save her from those
bloodthirsty wolves.
Who knows, she might even
fall in love with me!
[TOJI gasps]
[KAIRI] You blew your chance,
Toji. Momo's mine now.
[TOJI]
Come on man, let me out!
You better hide 'cause
I'm gonna beat...
This is payback for
making Momo cry.
Now let's see how
you really feel.
[MOMO] Get your hands
off me! Let me go!
You have no idea
what this is about!
This is between me
and Sae, not you!
Look, Sae! If you've
got something
you wanna get off your
chest, then I'm all ears!
But I'd much rather
do it in private
than in front of
the whole class.
Do you guys see what I mean now?
If she gets me alone in a room
she'll end up
hitting me again!
That's what she
always does to me!
[MOMO]
Uh...
[YUJI]
Did you hear that?
[SHOJI]
What an abusive skank!
[NAO] I can't believe she's been
hitting Sae all this time.
[TORU]
She won't get away with this.
[MOMO growls]
[SAE snickers]
[MOMO] This isn't going well.
No matter what I say
she's able to twist it
to her own advantage.
[DAICHI]
I know how we can solve this.
Hey, Momo, get on your knees
and beg for forgiveness!
[SABURO]
That's a great idea!
[STUDENTS]
On your knees! On your knees!
[SAE chuckles]
Listen. You're making a mistake.
You may think you're on
top of the world now.
But when the truth comes out,
no one in this school will want
to have anything to do with you!
[YUJI] You've got that
all switched around.
[SHOJI]
Get down.
[MOMO grunts]
[YUJI]
Now apologize.
Swear to Sae that you'll
never harm her ever again.
[MOMO groans]
[MOMO]
I won't give in.
She's strong.
Just keep pushing.
[MOMO] No matter what they do,
I will never apologize.
[TOJI panting]
[ALL gasp]
[STUDENTS mumble]
[MOMO]
Uhh... Toji?
Hey!
Hey, man. I thought you
were still in the hospital.
[TOJI pants]
[MOMO] This is so embarrassing.
Toji can't see me like this.
[MOMO grunts]
[TOJI]
Get off her.
[SHOJI]
Uh.
Get off her!
[SHOJI grunts]
Every one of you!
Apologize now!
--[SAE whimpers]
--[YUJI, TORU gasp]
[MOMO gasps]
[YUJI] Do you know
what's going on, Toji?
Momo hit Sae in the face
for no reason!
[NAO] Why are you standing up
for her? That girl is trouble?
[TOJI]
Shut up!
Sae's a liar and I'm
in love with this girl.
[MOMO gasps]
[SAE whimpers]
[YUJI whimpers]
Wait, I'm confused.
Last I heard, you were
going out with Sae.
[SAE yelps]
Toji, listen to me.
You already broke up with Momo.
You can't get back together.
Especially after what she did
in the locker room with Kairi.
They were hugging
and she was naked.
Can you believe that?
[MOMO cries]
Okay, Toji. One more time.
Why don't you tell us
the truth in front of everyone?
I'm an idiot. Yeah.
I couldn't see that
this was all an act.
I thought Sae was
her friend, her best friend,
I thought she was
just giving me advice
and truly worrying about
Momo's well-being.
Why would I have doubted her?
Wait.
It's just like Sae said herself.
I saw her as
the wounded gazelle.
[SAE yelps]
What?
[TOJI]
I'm so sorry, Momo.
I am.
Of all people.
I'm the one who let you down.
I should have trusted you
and stood by your side
no matter what.
[MOMO cries]
[MOMO]
Toji...
Wait, so they're together now?
I'm as lost as you are.
I thought they hated each other.
If Momo and Toji
are now a couple,
then where does that
leave Sae in all this?
[MALE STUDENT T] Now that I
think of it, I don't think
I've ever heard Toji say
anything negative about Momo.
In fact, I'm sure of it.
Sae was always the one
that was bad-mouthing her.
That would mean, what? That Sae
was lying the whole time?
[SAE]
Why, Toji, why?!
You're ruining my life!
You said that you and
Momo were through
and you kissed me and then
made me fall in love with you!
Are you saying that when you
told me you loved me
you were lying to my face like a
dog?! Is that it?! Huh? Tell me!
Toji and Momo are the
liars, I'm the victim!
I'm the one you should
be consoling, people!
All right. That's
enough out of you.
You're embarrassing
yourself. It's kinda sad.
[SAE yelps]
What... What's wrong?
Still up to your dirty tricks
aren't you, Sae?
That's right. Remember
what you did to us?
Yeah. Don't try to say
you forgot all about it.
[CHINATSU, EMI, SUMIRE]
Every one of us
had our boyfriends stolen from
us by this back-stabbing bitch!
It's a lie... A... lie...
Wait, you guys don't
believe them, do you?
I would never do anything
dishonest like that.
You have to believe me!
Huh. You know a few weeks ago
I asked Sae out to the movies.
And she told me I looked
like a shaved poodle
--then nearly slapped me.
--[SAE whimpers]
Shut up, you cro-magnon mummy!
Eh.
[OKADA] See what I mean?
She's so hurtful!
[SAE chuckles]
[KAKO] So when you said that
you were afraid for your life
because Momo was picking
on you and that we should
ostracize her from our group,
that wasn't true either?
N... No...
Then we're all very sorry, Momo.
We acted like real jerks.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. Forgive us.
Wait... hold on.
Where's everybody going?
You haven't heard
my side of the story yet!
Oh, come on, please?
I didn't do anything wrong!
[SAE whimpers]
[clapping]
[KAIRI]
Attagirl, Momo!
Finally a victory for one
of the good guys!
I was starting to think
you wouldn't rescue
her in time, Toji.
What happened? Were you
tied up with something else?
[TOJI]
Very funny!
[KAIRI chuckles]
Have fun making up
you two. Later.
Sorry about earlier.
I basically announced
to the whole class
that you and I are in love
without talking to you first.
[TOJI]
Momo.
I know I'm asking for a lot here
and I don't really even
deserve it... but...
Let's give it another shot.
You and me. What do you say?
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
I was such a jerk
to you for so long
and I didn't even
realize it until today.
I'm... I'm sorry
for what I said
when you were in the hospital.
Then let's start over.
Right now.
Yeah.
[MOMO] Toji, how about if we
make a secret hand signal
for just the two of us. See?
We'll make the shape of
an L with our fingers
and that will mean I love you.
Oh, come on!
Next time on Peach Girl
"A Brief Love Sign."