[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
But why?
Hey, Momo?
What are you doing
in here? You okay?
[MOMO]
Mm? I'm fine.
[whistle blows]
[MOMO] What was Kairi
doing with my picture?
Why? I thought...
I thought if he were to have any
picture, it would be of Misao.
[TOJI]
Momo.
What do you wanna do?
We could catch an early
movie if you want.
[MOMO] I'd rather avoid groups
of people, if that's okay.
We could just do
it at my place.
I have tons of movies on
DVD we could watch.
Uh?!
[MOMO]
Oh my gosh!
I can't believe I agreed
to come here alone!
Great! Now I'm nervous!
Here we are.
You all right?
I'm fine. I just had
a bit of a flashback.
What?
[MOMO] Last time I was here,
you closed the door on me.
[TOJI]
Uh!
Forget it. Pretend
it didn't happen.
[MOMO] I haven't been
in Toji's room in ages,
although it does seem
like yesterday.
What am I talking about?
It hasn't even been a year!
So much has happened since then.
So much stupid drama.
I never did give
that back to Kairi.
I wonder if he even realized
he was missing it.
And that photo...
[TOJI]
Are you bored?
[MOMO]
Huh?
No. Do I look it?
It's just... It seems like your
mind is somewhere else today.
[MOMO]
Uh.
No, I'm having a good time.
Maybe I have ADD or something.
Oh.
[MOMO]
Come on, Momo.
How long are you gonna keep
thinking about Kairi?
He's in the past now.
Toji's my future.
He's the one I need
to concentrate on.
[MOMO inhales]
[MOMO]
Mm!
Wait!
[TOJI]
Uh?
[MOMO]
Uh...
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I'm sorry, too.
When I see you
looking pre-occupied,
like you did just a minute ago,
I get anxious and nervous.
I start to believe that
you're thinking about Kairi.
[MOMO]
Uh.
[TOJI] With the way
you two ended things,
and it being less
than a week ago,
I can understand if you're
still thinking about him.
I guess more than anything,
I really want things between
us to be normal again.
I'm sorry, Toji.
Don't be. I'd be shocked if you
weren't thinking about him.
It's perfectly natural.
I mean, you two were
serious for a while there.
I'm totally cool with that.
[MOMO]
Uh?
And until you feel like
you can devote
a hundred percent of your
heart to me, I'll be waiting.
Toji.
You're amazing.
[MOMO]
Seriously, I'm fine.
[TOJI]
But I wanna walk you home.
[MOMO] I can't believe
how relaxed I feel.
Toji really has
a way with words.
But at the same time,
I kinda feel guilty.
The truth is, I was really happy
to find that photograph.
Really happy.
[RYO] Okay, I'll see you
guys later guys. Hey you!
Hi there.
I didn't realize you were still
working this late. Sorry.
Don't be sorry. It's cool.
I've actually had a tough time
concentrating since you called.
How 'bout if we make
this a real date?
Ryo. Listen...
--[phone rings]
--[RYO] Mm?
Hello?
You're late, you ugly,
conceited jerk!
We agreed on six o'clock at the
plaza in front of the station.
Where are you?
Oh, right. It slipped my mind.
Just hold tight little brother.
I'll be there in ten or fifteen.
You were supposed to
meet Kairi tonight?
[RYO] Yeah, he wants to
talk to me about something.
Let's go, I wanna
show you off.
Misao?
Hey, are you all right?
[MISAO] Do you remember when I
said I loved you the other day?
I want you to forget
that ever happened.
Huh? But why?
[MISAO] I was being very
selfish when I said that.
I was so consumed with
the need to tell you,
but I never intended to get in
the way of your relationship
with Sae. I just assumed
you were single.
You're making a big
deal out of nothing.
There's no need
to worry about it.
Even if you hadn't
said that to me,
Sae and I have
no relationship.
What do you mean?
The reality is Sae's been
following me around
like a lost puppy and it's
borderline stalking.
She's decided to make me
her imaginary boyfriend,
and let me tell you, it's really
startin' to creep me out.
Wait. So she's stalking you?
She's just an inexperienced
kid with a crush, that's all.
I'll let her down easy, 'kay?
[SAE]
Uh...
[RYO, MISAO gasp]
Explain yourself, Ryo!
Why are you with her?
You tricked me.
You are such a bastard!
Here you are with this slut,
and you won't even
answer my phone calls!
Now what's going on?!
I'm with Misao because she
heals me like no other can.
She heals you?
That sounds like a load of crap!
You're obsessed with this
make believe relationship.
We've never had an
ounce of chemistry.
You're just in love with
the idea of being in love.
[SAE gasps] That's not true!
I do love you, Ryo!
I love you more than
you can ever imagine!
I wanna spend the rest
of my life with you!
I just don't understand
what you see in her!
What is it that she does
that I don't, huh? Tell me!
That's easy.
Whenever she's by my side,
all of my worries and
problems seem to disappear.
That's what you don't do.
It takes no effort on her part.
Her presence alone
is like magic.
Damn you.
This is all your fault!
None of this would've
happened if you had
just stayed out of my life!
That's enough. This is the
last time I'll say it.
We have never had a
relationship, and we never will.
[SAE]
Uh?
[MOMO] Thanks. You can
head back now if you want.
You sure?
[MOMO]
Huh?
'Cause I don't really want
tonight to end.
'Kay. Let's keep going.
[people murmuring]
It looks like something's
happening. Let's check it out.
[SAE] If that's how
you really feel,
then why did you sleep with me?!
You said you loved me!
You said I made you happy!
[TOJI]
Sounds like a stupid argument.
[MOMO]
I know that voice. Uh!
It's Sae!
Are you denying that you
said those things now?
Look, you need to stop
before you embarrass yourself
any more than you already have.
[SAE]
Uh!
Nothing you say can change the
way I feel. Come on, let's go.
[MISAO]
But...
There's something
you need to know.
I'm pregnant, and I
know it's your baby.
[ALL gasp]
[MOMO]
Pregnant?
Are you gonna man up now?
[MAN A] I can't believe
he knocked her up!
[MAN B]
I can.
What did you say?
Weren't you listening?
I said I'm pregnant,
and it's your responsibility.
Lying won't solve anything, Sae,
no matter how good
you are at it.
So try giving it a rest.
[SAE gasps]
[MAN B]
You tell her man!
Trust me, it's not a lie.
It's the truth! I swear.
She was always
pulling stunts like this.
Calling me up with
some ridiculous lie
so I'd agree to meet her.
Let's go.
[RYO]
Uh?
A young girl has accused you
of something very serious,
and the only thing you can do is
claim it's some elaborate story?
I noticed that you
never actually denied
sleeping with her, so it
could be true. Couldn't it?
[RYO]
U-Uh... Uh-huh.
You and Sae should go someplace
more private to discuss this.
Follow me.
[MAN A]
Show's over!
[KAIRI, MOMO]
Uh...
Hey guys! Did you get
to see that lover's spat?
It was like watching one
of those soap operas!
Uh... We got here
in the middle of it.
Why's your brother with the
nurse? Do they know each other?
Huh? Wait, you mean
you haven't heard?
Where've you been, dude?
Misao confessed her
love to my brother,
and now they seem to be
an item! Who'd of thunk it?
For all the details, you can
ask your lady friend here.
Me? I don't know
anything at all.
This is the first
I've heard of it.
I'm sorry. I thought you knew.
[chuckles] So much drama.
And I assume you heard
the other bit of gossip.
Sae's pregnant with
my brother's baby!
But is Sae really pregnant?
Your brother seems to think
it's one of her lies.
I honestly have
no idea if it's true.
This is the first time
I've heard of it.
Either way, I think my brother
handled it like a jerk,
but that's no surprise.
[MOMO] Listen to him. He's
acting like everything's normal.
Did Sae ever say if she
slept with your brother?
[KAIRI]
Why would she tell me?
All I know is I'm gonna
catch up with them,
and see if I can find out
any more dirt. Later!
Do you wanna get
outa here, too?
Okay.
[MOMO] Maybe that photo
didn't mean anything,
or maybe it means Kairi
still has feelings for me.
I guess he could be hiding them.
Wait, I'm way
over-thinking this.
[KAIRI] Why can't
I forget you, Momo?
Huh. Where's my ID book?
I thought I put it in here.
Uh!
Did I drop it?
If anybody finds those
pictures, I'm in deep trouble!
But we were dating
exclusively for months,
so having a photo of her
wouldn't be out of the ordinary.
Yeah I have nothing
to worry about.
Oh, Momo.
You're so beautiful.
[MOMO] Just being with you
makes me happy, Kairi.
[KAIRI]
Momo.
I love you so much.
[panting]
I can't take it.
I have to have her!
I will find a way to
get you back, Momo!!
She isn't home yet.
Oh, right... Toji.
Uh?
[dog barking]
You'd think after all this
time that dog would like me.
Stupid mutt.
What the... It stopped.
Maybe they let him inside
the house for once.
--[dog growling]
--[KAIRI] Uh...
Thanks for walking me home.
It's good to know I have a
my own personal bodyguard.
You're welcome. I like
being your bodyguard.
I guess I'll see
you tomorrow, then.
Yeah.
[KAIRI]
Uh.
[dog growls]
Night, Momo.
Good night, Toji.
[MOMO]
Mm.
[dog groans]
[dog barking]
All I ask is for one night
without any barking. Hold on.
[KAIRI]
Uh?
Wha... What are you doing here?
[KAIRI sighs] I must've taken
a wrong turn because I'm lost.
Sorry 'bout that. But I know
where I am now. See ya later.
[MOMO]
Kairi!
Kairi... I know you're not lost.
You came here for
a reason, didn't you?
[MOMO]
Uh...
I'm sorry.
Kairi?
I'm just emotional. Sorry.
[MOMO]
Uh!
Why was Kairi crying?
I just couldn't do it... Momo.
Wow! Look, it's the ocean!
A-ha! I'm so happy!
[RYO]
Aren't you tired, Sae?
Oh, no, I'm fine.
I can't tell you how
long it's been
since I've felt so
relaxed and happy.
Great.
[laughs] Thank you, Ryo.
Yesterday, I could've sworn
you didn't wanna have
anything to do with me.
[MISAO] Now I want you two
to talk this out like adults.
[SAE]
Uh?
Why's that? I promised
I'd take you on a drive,
and I'm not one to
go back on my word.
Yeah. You're right.
Where do you think
we should go next?
I'd love to see more
of the coastline.
First, we need to talk,
Sae. Right now.
Huh?
Here you go.
I want you to have this.
Please, just take it.
[SAE]
What is it?
Huh?
[RYO] Sae... I don't wanna be
involved with you any longer.
[SAE gasps]
I realize now that I
wanna be with Misao.
I need to focus all
of my effort on her.
What're you talking about, Ryo?
What am I supposed to do with
this? And what about our baby?
You can't just expect me
to raise it all by myself.
Damn you.
If you're really pregnant,
then I have no intention
of being a father.
You can use the
money for the baby,
or go shopping for all I care.
[grunts]
You're a heartless bastard!
[RYO]
Hm.
As far as I'm concerned,
you and I are finished.
Now let's head back.
Do whatever you want.
The train station's that way.
[SAE] Wait, don't go.
I need you, Ryo.
Please don't leave me. Please!
I'll do anything you
want me to do,
just promise you won't
leave me. Please Ryo!
Anything? In that case,
there's a very important
favor I'd like you to do.
Whatever you want. I don't
care what it is, I'll do it.
[RYO] I want you to
never contact me again.
[SAE]
Huh?
[engine revs, tires squeal]
Ryo? No!
[MOMO] I wonder how
long he was out there.
He probably saw Toji and I kiss.
Was that the reason
he was crying?
[SAE] It's that no good
bitches fault. I know it is.
Hey, Sae?
[SAE]
Hm?
You look as pale as a ghost.
Are you feeling all right?
Okay, uhh. On Friday,
Toji and I were at the plaza
near the train station and we...
We happened to overhear
your conversation with Ryo.
[SAE]
Oh?
So, um... Is it really true
that you're pregnant?
Oh my gosh. Are you okay?
What are you gonna do now?
Is Ryo gonna help?
[SAE]
Oh yeah. Everything's fine.
We ended up working it all out.
[MISAO]
Uh!
[BOY A]
Nurse Misao, are you okay?
[BOY B] If you had
taken one more step,
it would've hit
you in the head.
[KAIRI]
This looks like the work of Sae.
I just saw her in the hall
and she looked strange.
[MISAO] There's no reason
to jump to conclusions.
It's not like I
saw who did it.
Who knows, it could've
been an accident.
Maybe.
[MISAO] Although if I were to
suspect anyone it'd be her.
She really hates my guts.
[KAIRI] I think it's a warning
to keep your distance from Ryo.
That's funny.
I've been seriously considering
breaking it off with Ryo anyway.
Oh, really?
If you decide to go through
with that and break up with him,
it'll be the smartest
decision you ever made.
The coldhearted side
you've seen of lately
is what he's really like.
[sighs]
I can't believe I've been
acting like such a fool.
All this time I've
been so preoccupied
trying to look pretty
and impress Ryo,
that I never took the time
to look at the real him.
Deep down, I know I should give
up on him, but I can't deny
these feelings I've had
for him all these years.
I'm sorry.
I know exactly how you feel.
Your heart's in a knot because
what you feel is conflicting
with what your brain
is telling you to do!
Kairi?
[KAKO, RITSUKO, NAMI,
MOMO laughing]
I don't believe my eyes!
Check it out!
[RITSUKO]
Woah!
[MOMO]
Uh...
We should tell those
two to get a room.
[KAKO]
Let's get out of here.
[KAIRI]
Uh!
Momo, wait!
It's not what you think!
Momo!
[KAKO]
What?!
Oh, it's nothing.
Sorry to bother you.
Go ahead. I'll catch up.
[KAKO]
Uh?
[MOMO]
Kairi.
[KAIRI]
Huh?
Well?
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
I was in shock about
Misao last night,
and somehow I ended up
wandering to your house.
Uh?
You're the only one I've told
about my history with her,
and I had no one
else to talk to,
so I figured I'd stop by,
in case you were home.
[KAIRI]
I'm just emotional. Sorry.
[MOMO]
So that's why he was crying?
Sorry you had to see me
actin' like a baby. See ya.
[MOMO] It was Misao he
was emotional about.
There I go with another mistake!
[traffic noise, horn honks]
--[TOJI] The light's red, Momo.
--[MOMO] Uh!
Ya know, you've been
acting funny all day.
Did something happen?
No, of course not I'm fine.
[MOMO] I'm sick of these games
I've been playing with myself.
I'm done being dragged
around by Kairi.
From now on, I refuse to waste
one moment thinking about him.
[MOMO]
Wow!
[TOJI]
Ya know...
[MOMO]
Huh?
[TOJI] I've been looking forward
to bringing you here again.
This is the spot where
we broke up before.
I didn't wanna
have a bad memory
associated with this place.
[MOMO]
Uh?
But if we have fun tonight,
then whenever we think of
being on this ride together,
it won't make us sad.
From now on, let's agree to
do everything in our power
to create only happy memories.
M'kay?
[MOMO cries]
[MOMO] Choose?
Right here? Right now?
Between the two of you?
Why am I hesitating?
This should be a no-brainer.
I don't know!
I don't know how I feel!
Next time on Peach Girl:
Forced to Choose.