[MOMO]
What's she doing here?
Please do this for me Kairi.
I promise I won't ask
you for anything again.
If you're willing to do it,
I'll be at the Blossom
hotel tomorrow.
[sighs] Okay I'll do it.
[KAIRI grunts]
Screw you!
[gasps]
[MOMO panting]
[KAIRI painting]
[KAIRI]
Wait!
[MOMO]
Uh?
Please, don't take
this the wrong way.
There's nothing going on
between Morika and I.
--[MOMO] Jerk!
--[KAIRI groans]
[KAIRI groaning]
I know what I saw back there,
so don't bother lying.
[sighs] Well that
didn't go as planned.
[MOMO]
Dear Kairi.
I made you a new
cell phone case.
Hope you like it! Momo
[KAIRI]
Uh!
[THUG] Whoa there.
You got a problem, man?
[KAIRI gasps]
[KAKO] Momo. Do you know why
Kairi wasn't at school today?
Who cares.
[MOMO] He hasn't bothered to
call or even text me all day.
What's he waiting for?
Even he knows that you're
supposed to apologize
in a situation like this.
But what if Kairi and that
girl still have feelings
for each other?
If I don't watch out, they
could get back together.
He's probably
with her right now.
[KAKO]
Momo?!
[MOMO]
No! I can't live with that.
You said you wanted
to be with me, Kairi.
You said that I
was the only one.
[elevator dings]
[MOMO panting]
Kairi, it's Momo!
I know you're in there!
Open up the door! I swear, if
you leave me for that other girl
you'll be sorry. Come out here
and talk to me face to face!
[MOMO]
Uh...
Can I help you with something?
[MOMO grunts] I'm sorry.
I must have the wrong door.
[KAIRI]
Momo?
[MOMO]
Kairi?
You okay?
Ryo!
I was hoping to see you.
Morika.
--[MORIKA grunts]
--[RYO groans]
[MOMO gasps]
You slimy son of a bitch!
I've been trying to reach
you for two months.
Why are you avoiding me?
Did you think you could
ignore me forever?
Wait.
[MOMO]
Uh...
[RYO]
Come on let's talk this over.
That's my bro.
[MOMO]
Hm?
You know how Morika and I
were talking in the bookstore?
It was all about seeing him.
Apparently he's been
avoiding her lately,
so she came to me to help
them get back together.
I guess she thinks I'm actually
an influence over him.
Wait a minute.
So Morika just used you
to get to your brother?
Pretty much.
That is so mean!
How could she?
[RYO]
Calm down you two.
My brother got
jumped last night.
He should be in bed resting.
--[MOMO] Huh?
--[KAIRI sighs]
Stupid kid.
I can't believe he got his butt
kicked over this little thing.
Hey! Give it back!
That was a gift!
Here.
[MOMO grunts]
You fought over this?
Of course. You made it for me.
[MOMO] I didn't realize it until
after I thought I'd lost him,
but Kairi is more precious to me
than anyone else in the world.
[KAIRI laughs] I knew it
was only a matter of time
until you showed up at my door,
hysterical and over-reacting,
just begging to see me.
You're in love with me,
aren't you Momo?
Hopelessly, head-over-heels
in love with me.
Maybe we should grab a hotel
room to seal the deal.
[MOMO]
Uh?
--[MOMO] No way!
--[KAIRI groaning]
[KAIRI groaning]
[MOMO] We've been seeing
each other for two months now,
so I have been giving
it some thought.
But how dare he expect me
to wanna do it at a hotel!
[KAIRI]
Momo! What's the big deal?
I want my first time to
be a special moment
for me to remember.
In some place romantic,
not in a sleazy hotel!
Then you're not against it?
So as long as the time
and place are memorable,
then you'd be okay
with doing it, right?
Yeah...
All right! This weekend,
it is a date.
Let's make some sweet memories!
I'll make all the arrangements!
See you soon!
Kairi wait!
[MOMO]
What did I just get myself into?
--[horn honks]
--[MOMO] Uh?
[MOMO]
That's Kairi's brother.
Hey, do you have a second?
It's about Kairi.
I had no idea Toji  was so
boring! I swear,
dating him is no different
than watching paint dry.
Now that Momo's in love with
Kairi, I guess it's too late.
It got pretty ugly back there.
Sorry 'bout that.
Oh, right.
Honestly, I've been so
busy with work lately
that I haven't had
time to call Morika,
let alone any of
my other friends.
I think Kairi told me that
you make video games
for a living, right?
Yeah. The deadline
for our first beta's
coming up so I've been swamped.
So what did you wanna
tell me about Kairi?
[RYO]
So, what all do you know?
About Kairi and
Morika's past? Tell me.
I know they used to go
out with each other.
[RYO] And what did Kairi tell
you about Morika and me?
[MOMO]
Uh...
Yeah my brother
stole her from me.
[MOMO]
That's it.
[RYO] So that's what he's
believed all this time.
[MOMO]
Isn't that the truth?
No it isn't. I guess I should
tell you the whole story.
What really happened.
Morika and I dated way before
Kairi ever got involved.
When Kairi started
cutting classes,
I asked Morika if she
would tutor him,
and before I knew it they were
involved with each other.
Kairi took it all
pretty seriously.
But she was only doing
it to turn us against
each other for her
own entertainment.
She enjoyed having two
brothers fight over her.
But when I tried to break
off contact with her,
she freaked out and dumped
Kairi on the spot,
which he never saw coming.
Later on she and I ended
up getting back together,
--but Kairi couldn't handle it.
--[MOMO growls]
But couldn't you have
avoided all that
by just telling him the truth?
[RYO] If he found out that
Morika was just having fun
at his expense, do you have any
idea how hurt he would feel?
I couldn't bring myself
to tell him that.
But Kairi still thinks that
you stole his girlfriend,
and he's just gonna keep
on believing that until
you set things straight.
Wouldn't you rather the two
of you be on good terms
instead of fighting
all the time?
To be perfectly honest,
I really don't care what
Kairi thinks of me.
That's why you have to promise
me that you will never tell him
about any of this,
no matter what.
Lately Kairi's been really
upbeat and happy.
I was wondering what brought
on the sudden change,
then I figured it out. It's
because he started seeing you.
[MOMO gasps]
Ever since you've
entered his life,
he's become a better person.
I mean that. You're a
good influence on him.
And he deserves nothing but the
best.
I can't believe how nice he was.
[KAIRI] Momo! I'm here!
Which do you prefer? The
oceans or the mountains?
Although a weekend
trip to the hot springs
would be nice too, huh?
Sounds good.
[KAIRI]
Mm.
Geez Momo, can you
be any less enthusiastic?
We have to pick the
perfect spot together,
or it'll all be meaningless.
You're right. Sorry.
Oh, I ran into your brother
after you took off.
He seems like a really nice guy.
That whole nice routine is
just a façade he puts up.
He's probably just working
on some kind of scheme.
Whatever you do,
don't be fooled by him, Momo.
He's just telling you what
he thinks you wanna hear.
Come on.
You make it sound as if like
he's the devil or something.
What the hell?
You don't believe me?
My brother is like a
male version of Sae.
He thrives on
stealing from people
he's manipulated
into trusting him.
If he found out that Morika
was having fun at his expense
do you have any idea
how hurt he would feel?
To be honest with you Kairi,
I think you're just biased
against him since
he took Morika from you.
[KAIRI]
I thought you, of all people,
would understand me on this.
[MOMO]
Yeah, well,
you don't even know how
your brother really feels.
Do you think you're the only
one who was hurt by that girl?
I thought that looked familiar.
That's the beach
where we first met.
My gosh.
How many travel agencies
did he go to this morning?
[phone rings]
[RYO]
Hello?
[MOMO]
Hey Kairi, i-it's Momo.
Sorry about earlier.
Are you still upset?
[RYO]
No.
Well, would you like
to hang out tomorrow?
[RYO]
Sure.
I'll meet you at the
park at ten, okay?
[RYO]
Cool.
[MOMO]
It's ten after. Where is he?
[RYO]
Momo.
How are you?
Ryo, hi.
Sorry.
Something kinda urgent came
up so Kairi couldn't make it.
Oh. Well those things
happen sometimes I guess.
[MOMO] He could've
called to tell me himself.
Maybe he's still mad
at me about yesterday.
[RYO]
Sorry about all this.
Oh. You don't have
to apologize for him.
I only wish I had your
cell phone number on me.
I would have let you know
about this ahead of time.
You came all the way over
here to tell me Kairi
couldn't make it? I'm sorry.
Nah. I was coming to
this part of town anyway.
Don't worry about it.
[MOMO]
Kairi must be out of his mind.
His brother is so nice!
Comparing him to Sae
doesn't make any sense.
[SAE chuckles]
So what are you up to now?
[MOMO] Uh?
There's a company party I'm
heading to just down the street.
How 'bout you come along
with me as my special guest.
[phone ringing]
[KAIRI]
Hello?
[MORIKA] Kairi! I'm so
glad you picked up!
Look, I need a favor from you.
Morika?
[gasps] Oh wow.
Thanks Ryo.
But I don't think I belong here.
Don't be silly, Momo.
[MOMO]
Sorry.
Let's mingle.
[MOMO] I've never been
escorted like this before.
I have butterflies,
but it feels kinda nice.
[SAE]
Cheers!
Oh my gosh! Sae, what
are you doing here?!
Ha, ha. What do you mean?
I'm just enjoying the party.
You liar!
Why hello there.
I'm Sae Kashiwagi.
Momo and I are,
like, best friends.
[MOMO]
Best friends?
How could she say that
after what she's done!
And what's your name?
Or should I just call
you Mr. Gorgeous?
I'm Ryo Okayasu.
Uh. Okayasu?!!
Hey Ryo! When'd you get here?
I can't believe he
actually showed up!
[crowd chattering]
[MAN B] It is a huge
honor to meet you, sir.
[WOMAN B] I love your games!
I have every one.
[MAN C]
I can't wait for the new one.
I hear it's revolutionary.
Crazy. I had no idea that
he was such a popular guy.
It's too bad that's
Kairi's older brother.
[SAE sighs]
[MOMO] If you try to date him,
that would mean
you'd have to deal
with Kairi everyday,
and seeing that you can't
stand to be around him,
that makes your chances
look pretty slim, huh?
It's too bad really. You'd
probably make a cute couple.
He's obviously more
sophisticated than Kairi!
[SAE cries] Why do you
have to be so mean, Momo?!
[MOMO] Sae? Shed tears
over a man? No way.
She's just acting again.
I still got her. [laughs]
[MOMO] Sae should be happy.
After all, she has Toji.
[MOMO]
This garden is beautiful!
The flowers smell amazing.
Are you sure it's all right
to sneak away like this?
Won't your fans be disappointed?
[RYO]
Forget about them.
Besides, I'm having more
fun spending time with you.
[MOMO]
Mm.
Ah. This is nice.
I feel so relaxed with you.
Of course, you remind me
of someone I loved
very dearly a long time ago.
[MOMO]
Uh?
[MOMO] That is a little
strange, I guess.
What kind of person was she?
[RYO]
She's no longer of this world.
[MOMO gasps]
I was certain that she
and I would share
the rest of our lives together.
[MOMO] I'm sorry.
The thing is, I'm happy.
It's as if I've been given
one last chance to
see my lover again.
[MOMO] You're still in love
with her, aren't you?
I can never forget her.
Because it's not like
we ever broke up.
I think that's the
reason why things
haven't worked
out with Morika.
I just need to get
used to the idea
that I can never love again.
Hey, Momo?
Would it be all right if
I held you for awhile?
[MOMO]
Uh!
Oh, no... I mean...
Please forgive me.
That was way over the line.
[MOMO]
You can, if you want.
[SAE]
Uh!
[MOMO] I can't believe
I said that. But just this once.
So he can hold onto his
memories one more time.
Ryo's at a party
inside this building.
Will you go in there
and tell him I'm out
here waiting for him?
What's in it for me?
Let me guess, nothing.
But you're the only
one I can rely on.
Come on. Pretty please?
Fine.
[MOMO] I feel like I'm
being held by a prince.
What kind of a woman was she,
to be loved by
such tender hands?
[MOMO]
Uh? Kairi!
This isn't what you think!
I swear!
Ryo. You son of a bitch!
[RYO grunts]
[RYO groans]
Stop it! You've got him all
wrong, Kairi. You don't--
I'm sick and tired of you trying
to steal my girlfriends
away from me. I'm not
gonna take it anymore!
Hold on. Sorry, Kairi.
I haven't considered
your feelings.
It's just that seeing her
brought back so many memories.
Memories? I don't know what
the hell you're talking about.
Listen.
I don't think so.
Come with me.
[KAIRI]
Screw you!
Let's go.
[MOMO]
Uh...
[RYO]
Hmph.
[MOMO] Kairi, will you just
hold on for one second?
Didn't your brother explain
what that was all about?
He's--
Look, don't allow yourself
to fall for his advances.
In fact I don't want you
ever talking to him again.
If he ever approaches you again,
just walk away.
Keep at least thirty feet
away from him at all times.
Get your hands off me.
It's my business who
I choose to speak to.
Just because we're dating
does not mean you're allowed to
control every part of my life.
I'll admit that it was
wrong to let myself
get in a situation that could
easily be misunderstood.
I take full responsibility
for that, but what you saw
was innocent. Your
brother didn't want me,
he wanted to embrace
his dead girlfriend.
[KAIRI]
Huh?!
Besides, who are you to barge
in here and judge me?
I'm not the one who
stood me up for our date.
We had a date? No we didn't.
We set it up over the
phone yesterday.
Have you already
forgotten?
Ryo. He must've
answered my phone
while I was in the shower
and pretended to be me.
You're crazy. Blaming him
for your own forgetfulness.
[KAIRI] I swear I didn't
know we had a date today.
Momo, Ryo is trying
to trick you.
Right. I bet you can't even
give me one good reason
why he'd do that. You don't
have the slightest clue
as to how your
brother really feels.
That's why you hate him.
Oh, come on.
Am I hearing you right?
You believe my brother,
who you just met, over me?
That's not the issue.
It's you who doesn't believe me!
I do believe in you Momo.
More than you know.
Then stop trying to
tell me what to do.
I can make those
decisions on my own.
And I would never even
consider getting involved
with your brother in that way.
You can say that all you want,
but it won't matter.
He always gets what he wants.
I've told you from the beginning
to stay away from him.
That he isn't to be trusted.
Why can't you understand that?
[MOMO]
Uh...
[KAIRI sighs]
Just Forget it.
[MOMO]
Uh.
[sighs]
[MOMO]
Why are we doing this?
I don't wanna fight
with you, Kairi.
You're the only man in my life.
[MOMO] If he can't understand,
then I'll have no other choice
but to tell him everything
his brother told me.
[MOMO]
Uh! Sae?
It's the truth.
Momo is an incredibly shallow
person who thinks that stealing
boyfriends from other girls
is just some kind of game.
She even stole my
boyfriend recently.
I always thought
she was my friend.
[MOMO] That liar! She's the
one who stole my boyfriend!
Listen, Sae.
Yes, love?
It's not polite to talk about
someone behind their back,
especially your friend.
[SAE]
Uh!
And as far as I can tell,
Momo's definitely
not that type of girl.
[SAE gasps]
Well, trust me,
I don't usually talk about
my friends behind their back.
You just seem like a nice guy,
and I wanted to warn you about
what she's done in the past.
Uh... Bye!
Somehow I get the feeling that
girl isn't really your friend.
She's my sworn enemy!
Thought so.
Uh.
[MOMO]
Ryo understands me so well.
He's definitely related
to Kairi in that respect.
[RYO]
Where's Kairi?
[MOMO]
He ran off upset.
I think I should tell him
the truth about your history
with him, and I wanted to
know how you felt about that.
I see. Do what you need.
All right then,
I'm gonna go tell him.
Uh, wait.
There's something that I would
really like for you to have.
But I...
[RYO]
It won't take long.
[MORIKA]
Kairi!
Morika. If it has anything to do
with my brother then
I'm not listening.
But I've looked all
around for Ryo,
and I can't find him anywhere.
He must be hiding from me.
Oh, no!
Kairi?
[KAIRI panting]
[door locks]
--[RYO] Momo.
--[MOMO gasps]
[RYO]
Here.
I hope this makes up for all
the trouble I've caused you.
Oh, you don't have
to give me anything.
[MOMO gasps]
Morika has a necklace just
like this, doesn't she?
She does. That's because I was
the one who gave it to her.
Momo. You're so cute.
It's such a shame
that Kairi doesn't
know how to treat a lady.
[MOMO] Oh no. This is bad.
I have to get outta here.
Let go of me! Ah.
I have to leave!
[MOMO yells]
I won't let you.
[MOMO]
This is amazing.
I've never felt as strongly for
someone as I do right now.
But something's wrong. He's not
acting like his usual self.
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Just when I was ready for him!
Next time on Peach Girl:
Who Will It Be?