Today's my last day.
I don't work here anymore.
I see.
So what are you going
to do over summer break?
[KAIRI]
Well, as of right now,
I plan to thoroughly think
things over while walking.
[MOMO]
While walking?
[KAIRI]
Oh, yeah.
They say you do your best
thinking while walking.
I figure I'll walk
as far as I can
and see what I can
discover about myself.
Well, I'm off. Take care!
Happy walking!
[MOMO] I need to do
some discovering as well.
I need to become stronger.
That way, I'll be able to handle
whatever decision
he finally makes.
Good morning, ma'am.
[screams]
[phone rings]
[RYO]
What the hell's your problem?
Where do you get off leaving
a note saying you're
going on a trip,
but don't say where?
Mom is worried sick over this!
[KAIRI]
What, like you give a crap?
Just tell mom not to worry.
I'll be home in a few weeks.
[BOTH snicker]
This is a lot further
than I expected it to be.
[GUY A]
Comin' through!
[KAIRI groaning]
Are you okay, man?
You should pay attention
to where you're walkin', dude.
[KAIRI groans]
You son of a... Hey!
--[GUY A] Loser!
--[GUY B] Dork!
Keep on running, you cowards!
So the manager mentioned
that Kairi worked
here right before I was hired.
Do you know why he quit?
[SAE] Kairi and I have decided
to keep our distance right now.
He had another girl that he
was crushing on besides me,
but when he made his move, she
slammed the door in his face.
Now, with his ego
bloody and bashed,
he's taken a trip to do
some serious thinking.
Kairi said that until he
gets his own feelings
in check, he can't date me.
But if he wants to
give me another shot,
then on the last
day of summer break
we may go on a daytrip together.
I gave him a ticket
and everything.
I'm starting to wonder
if he'll even show up.
[MOMO] Sae! Will you
knock it off already?!
I'm just doing my job!
Spreading the truth!
[KAIRI]
That was delicious!
[slurping]
She'll roll over in
her grave for this,
but these noodles are
better than grandma's.
[KAIRI] That must be the chef.
Bet he runs a tight ship.
That'll be five hundred yen.
[KAIRI]
Okay.
My wallet... It's gone!
[KAIRI]
Those punks!
Oh, no. Now what am I gonna do?
[WAITRESS]
Oh.
--[foot steps]
--[KAIRI] Uh?
[CHEF grunts]
[KAIRI]
Uh!
That poor thing.
Having this wallet stolen
like that, it's so awful.
The boy can only blame himself.
There's no reason to let
him eat without paying.
You just had to come
out with that knife
and scare him to death.
I'm surprised he didn't
faint right there.
If anything, I should
be the one apologizing.
[WAITRESS]
Thanks for your help.
[door opens]
[WAITRESS]
You're a very hard worker.
Oh. Thank you.
My husband and I are about
to close up for the night.
Do you need a ride somewhere?
No, I can't go home quite yet.
I still have some things
that I need to figure out.
Is there something
that's troubling you?
Well, there's this
girl back home
and we've agreed to
keep our distance for now.
Before we started dating,
there was someone else
I was madly in love with.
Unfortunately, there's
no future with her,
so all I can do is
walk away from it.
But at the same time,
I can't just act like it
meant nothing to me
and start dating
this other girl.
And how do you
feel about the girl
you've become involved with now?
I'm crazy about her.
Now if Misao hadn't let...
I mean,
if the girl who turned me down
hadn't been in the picture,
I'm pretty certain this new girl
would be the love of my life.
[WAITRESS] It's getting late.
Why don't you stay here tonight?
If you want, you can work here
with us for a few weeks.
You are gonna need some extra
money in order to get home,
don't you think?
Really? That would be awesome!
[door opens]
[SAE]
Momo!
[MOMO] Shouldn't you
be in summer school?
Class doesn't start
till noon. Where's Toji?
He's on his break right now.
Why, do you need something?
No, not really.
I'm gonna go say hi!
Momo. You mind getting some
more soda from the back?
Yeah, sure.
[SAE]
Congratulations!
I guess that means you're
officially free of me now.
[TOJI]
And this is everything?
[SAE] Yup. I've erased
everything about
Momo and Jigoro from my cell
phone and my computer.
--It's gone forever.
--[sighs]
I'm sorry, Toji.
I understand if you hate
me for ruining your life.
I have to admit,
I never thought I'd hear
those three words
come out of your mouth.
[MOMO]
Neither did I.
Over the last few days
I've come to realize
that if I hadn't of threatened
to release those photos
of Momo and Jigoro to the media,
you never would have
split up with Momo.
And the only reason you started
dating me was to make sure
I couldn't do anything
bad to her, right?
--To keep an eye on me.
--[gasps]
To think that you put up with
my games all that time,
just to protect the girl you
were forced to give away.
Be honest, Toji. Are you
still in love with Momo?
[TOJI] Hm. I have to
get back to work, Sae.
So, how's it going with
you and Kairi's brother?
Still hitting it off?
It's going well.
Thanks for asking.
Although, Ryo's been
busy with work lately,
so I haven't seem him much.
I really don't get what
you're looking for in a guy,
and I honestly don't know
what you see in him, but,
since you've started dating
him you've turned into a really
sweet person and I'd really like
to see more of that side of you.
[SAE]
Uh...
[kocking]
I'm so sorry. I've been
a terrible friend, Momo.
[KAIRI]
Man, I'm beat.
That guy runs his kitchen like
a some sort drill sergeant.
[CHEF]
Got it!
[CHEF chuckles]
[KAIRI]
A jigsaw puzzle?
So the old man
likes brain busters.
--[phone rings]
--[KAIRI gasps]
Uh, hello?
[MISAO]
Hey Kairi. It's me.
[KAIRI]
Misao? What's going on?
What you said the other night.
It really affected me.
You said that if...
if you want to be loved
you have to just come
out and tell the person.
And I think you hit the
nail right on the head.
Truth is, I never told Ryo
how I felt. I was too afraid.
Uh.
I want you to know your
confession made me very happy.
It's given me the confidence
to finally tell Ryo the truth.
[MISAO] I have to
lay it all on the line,
and not be afraid
of the results.
[KAIRI]
Misao.
[MOMO] You used a photo of me
and Jigoro to blackmail Toji?
If I had gone through with it,
you'd have been
scarred for life.
And to protect you,
Toji agreed to be with me.
You have no idea how lucky
you are to have som--
Shut up.
But Momo I...
Get out of here. I can't bear
to look at you right now.
[MOMO] I had no idea that
had happened. No idea at all.
This whole time I've thought I
was the only one who got hurt.
But that's obviously
not the case.
[MOMO]
That day.
My gosh.
[MOMO] Did he break up with me
because he loved me too much?
I think I'm getting sick.
[CHEF]
Hey.
What is this?
Have you heard of
the group called
the National Noodles
Fan Organization?
Every year they pick the
best buckwheat noodles
in the country and
award the chef a prize.
Woah! You won an award
for these? Can I try 'em?
--[CHEF] Mm-hm.
--Thank you sir.
I can't believe I'm about to eat
the best noodles in the country.
[CHEF]
What do you think?
--Uh...
--They good?
They're really awful.
[CHEF chuckles]
Good answer.
They're the cheapest noodles
I could find at the market.
Ah! That's not fair!
[CHEF] I never said
anything about these noodles
winning an award. I merely
said that the award existed.
You just jumped
to that conclusion. Hm.
So, I guess I'll
see you tomorrow.
--[MOMO]  Toji.
--[TOJI] Hm?
I just want to say thanks.
I overheard your conversation
earlier with Sae.
[TOJI] I'm sorry for all
the nasty things I did
when we were breaking up.
I acted like a spoiled
child when in reality,
you and I probably could
have worked it out.
You're wrong. I'm here
thanks to your generosity.
If that photo had
gotten around,
I would have had to
move away from here.
The fact that I can still
live a normal life here
is all thanks to you, Toji.
And I thank you from
the bottom of my heart.
[fireworks]
[MOMO]
Are those fireworks?
I almost forgot. Tonight's
the big fireworks show.
Would you like to go check
it out? Just you and me?
[CHEF] I merely said
that the award existed.
You just jumped
to that conclusion.
I just don't get it. So what
if I jumped to the conclusion
that they were special.
Oh wait. Misao.
Of course.
[groaning]
[WAITRESS]
We must hurry.
I love you...
...Momo.
--What was that?
--Huh? What'd you say?
Um...
[BOTH gasp]
That's so beautiful!
It's hard to believe it's only
been a year since we were here.
Yeah.
[MOMO] Summer break had just
begun when we started dating.
Just holding his hand back then
would get my heart racing.
I remember not paying much
attention to the fireworks
because I couldn't
take my eyes off Toji.
[TOJI]
Momo.
What will happen if
Kairi doesn't show up
to meet you on the
day he promised?
I don't know. I guess
I'll have no other choice
but to move on with my life.
Do you really think you'll
be able to forget him?
What other choice
will I have, huh?
Well, I hope things
work out with you two,
but if for some
reason they don't,
will you agree to give
me another shot?
Sorry. What was that?
I couldn't hear what you
said over all the noise.
Oh. It's nothing. Never mind.
[MOMO] I don't know why
I pretended not to hear him.
[TOJI] Will you agree
to give me another shot?
He has a advanced case
of acute pneumonia.
We'll keep him for a few days
until his condition improves.
I love you... Momo.
[SAE]
I saw you!
--[MOMO grunts]
--[SAE laughs]
You and Toji were hamming
it up at the fireworks show
last night together,
you big fat cheater!
[MOMO]
Sae!!
I thought I told you I never
want to see your face again!
Do I need to repeat myself?
The only thing
I remember you saying
is that Kairi is your
one and only true love.
Or I guess it's the old
"a bird in the hand is
worth two in the bush",
especially since Toji
was your first.
Maybe you were considering
giving him another chance?
--[MOMO] No!
--[SAE screams]
Please. Get lost.
[SAE] You should feel lucky
that you're the only guy
I let manhandle me like that!
[TOJI]
Any word from Kairi?
[MOMO]
Uh?
You've been staring
at your phone all day.
I know.
I don't get it. Why torture
yourself? Just call him.
Because I can't!
We agreed to keep our distance,
and that means
no contact at all!
Besides, I made the decision to
be patient and wait
for his answer.
If I call him then he'll
think I'm crowding him
and being obsessive,
and that's the last thing
I want him to think!
[laughs] Then chill out. Don't
get yourself all worked up.
You get so worried over stuff
that's out of your control.
No I don't. Do you really
think I'm like that?
[TOJI]
Oh, please!
Anyone who threatens
to jump from a window
if I don't listen to her
is a bit high strung.
Wouldn't you say?
[MOMO]
Uh...
She has no reason to lie...
And then there
was the time when...
I'm not listening!
--And...
--Oh, Shut your mouth, Toji!
That's ancient history!
Aw, come on!
I've got a hundred more
stories where that came from!
Sure, you say that about me,
but what about you, Mr. Perfect?
What about me?
[BOTH laugh]
You haven't changed
one bit, Momo.
[MOMO]
My heart is aching.
Why am I having such a
difficult time breathing?
We didn't break up because
we hated each other.
What should I do? I can't stop
this desire to be with Toji.
Where are you Kairi?
I know I said I would
wait for you,
but I'm starting feel swept away
again, and it frightens me.
I don't know if I can resist it.
Toji was looking out
for me the whole time.
He sacrificed himself for me.
Why haven't you called, Kairi?
I need to know what
you're thinking.
I hope you get in touch with
me before it's too late.
[CHEF]
Morning!
Hey!
[CHEF] You look a lot
better than before.
I'm really loving this
jigsaw puzzle you gave me.
[KAIRI]
What? Uh!
I only have one piece left!
[CHEF] Oh yeah.
I never could find that piece.
This was such a waste of time!
I find it quite appropriate that
one piece is missing for you.
You know with your
wallet being stolen
and getting pneumonia in
the middle of the summer.
I really thought I was
gonna die on that beach.
I couldn't breathe and
the pain was so unbearable.
In a way, it kinda
cleared my head
and let me see how
I really feel.
When I was laying there,
thinking I was about to die,
I finally understood who it
is I really want to be with.
Ah. You must mean Momo.
What? How the hell
do you know that?!
How the hell do you think...?
You've been mumbling her
name for the past two weeks.
You know, I finally figured out
what you were trying to teach me
with the whole award
winning noodle thing.
I'd become so enamored
with this unrealistic
dream of being with Misao,
and caused Momo a lot of
heartache in the process.
It makes me wonder if we could
really start over again.
[CHEF] Every person's
life is like a jigsaw puzzle
that's one piece
away from completion.
[KAIRI]
Huh?
We're always looking for the
person that holds that
missing piece, to make
our lives feel complete.
[MOMO]
I'll be okay.
I just need to stay strong,
and not allow myself to
be swept up in the moment.
[MOMO]
But it's so hard to wait
when I haven't heard
from Kairi in so long.
If I had just one glimmer
of hope to hang on to,
that's all I would need.
[phone rings]
Is that him?
Yes, it is. I guess he
hasn't forgotten about me!
[KAIRI] Momo, sorry I
haven't written in so long.
I've been working at a noodle
shop for the past few weeks.
I'll be here for the rest
of the summer so I can
save up some money
for our big trip.
I have so much
to tell you about.
I can't wait to see you.
[MOMO]
I'm such a hopeless romantic.
All it takes is a quick
text message from Kairi,
and I'm on cloud nine!
[MOMO] I can do it!
With that message,
I know I can wait for him
without any
temptation to wander.
It's true! I really am
in love with Kairi!
[STORE MANAGER]
Good work, Momo.
You'll always have
a job here with us.
I may take you up on that.
--[MOMO] Uh...
--[TOJI] Uh!
It was a fun summer.
Yes, it was.
What time are you supposed
to meet up with Kairi today?
At twelve o'clock. I told him
that I'd wait five minutes,
and if he didn't show,
I'd give up on him.
You don't need to worry.
No matter what happens,
I know you'll find happiness.
Thanks, Toji.
Well, I guess
I'll see you later.
Yeah.
[MOMO] Toji. I'm so grateful
for having you as a friend.
More than words can describe.
Thanks for everything.
Here's what you've earned in
the time you've worked for us.
We can't thank you enough.
Uh! This is way too much!
We put in a little extra for ya.
I couldn't have found two nicer
people to work for this summer.
Thanks to you I finally got
my heart all straightened out.
Maybe next summer I'll
come out this way again.
[WAITRESS]
Take care!
Hang in there, kid!
[KAIRI]
Will do!
[phone rings]
Hello? Mi-Misao?
Hi Ryo, Sorry to
call you at work.
I'd like to see you,
if it's not too much trouble.
[MOMO]
I'm almost there.
[laughs]
[MOMO] Just a little while
longer until I see my love!
[MOMO] What happened
to our big reunion?
I thought we would
be together again!
I waited for you, Kairi.
I trusted what you said and I
waited patiently, but for what?
Next time on Peach Girl...
One Stormy Night.