[MOMO] You and I have
nothing to talk about,
so leave me alone before
I do something you'll regret.
[KAIRI] Toji's in the hospital
with appendicitis.
[MOMO gasps]
I think Sae's tried to
keep it a secret from you.
[MOMO]
I'm gonna kill her!
Woah... Chill out,
Momo... Settle down.
Sae!
[KAIRI screaming]
[KAIRI] Too fast! Momo, slow
down, ease off the gas some!
No way! Now, shut up!
I'm trying to concentrate!
[KAIRI whimpers]
[KAIRI grunts]
My tailbone's
crammed into my chest!
[KAIRI yelps]
I'm such a moron!
Sae got the entire class to
keep me out of the loop.
And here's me, never
suspecting a single thing!
It eats me up to
think of that sick,
satisfied look on
her face when she saw us!
I need you to explain
to Toji that it was you
who put your arms around me,
and not the other way around.
Even though I know she's
probably already shot off
at the mouth to Toji
about whole thing by now.
Yeah, sure. But why'd
you tie my hands up?
[MOMO] That's to teach you to
keep your hands to yourself!
[KAIRI grunts]
Oh, come on!
Okay, now you've done it, Sae!
This time you have
gone way too far!
[KAIRI screams]
[SAE] When you first told
me the whole situation,
I thought it was way messed up.
There's no reason
you should have to keep
your relationship a secret.
But now, after what
I've seen today, I get it.
It's the only way she could go
out with both Kairi and you.
I'm not one to speak
poorly about my friends,
but I never thought Momo would
act so whore-ish like that.
People who cheat are
the absolute worst.
I would never put up
with it. If it were me,
I'd dump that person
the second I had the chance.
Oh! I-I didn't mean that
you two should break up.
Tha-That's not what I'm
saying at all. Seriously.
[MOMO]
This train is too slow.
The driver must be
asleep or something.
[KAIRI] Momo, chill. Can't we
just sit down for a sec?
I kow you're in a rush, but
dragging me through the train
isn't going to get
you there faster.
I know that. I'm not an idiot.
I just feel anxious.
Thinking about Sae alone
with Toji makes me flip.
[SAE]
Open wide.
You wanna tell me
why you and Sae
are even friends in
the first place?
[MOMO]
I wouldn't call us friends.
Oh.
[MOMO] Before school started
this semester, I caught a cold.
[KAIRI]
Uh-huh.
[MOMO]
It lasted for a while,
and I missed the first
week of school.
When I came back,
it wasn't a disaster,
it was just an embarrassment.
No one even noticed me.
All the school cliques
had already come together
and there wasn't any
room for a newbie.
The one thing that made me happy
was that Toji was in my class.
Only I couldn't really talk to
him. Maybe I was intimidated.
Then the rumor mill
started production
and I became a punch line.
Everyone was saying how
I'm easy, a slut, whatever.
Like any of them
had even bothered
to lower themselves
to talk to me.
That sucks.
Keep in mind I didn't know
any of this at the time.
It's all just stuff crammed into
my ears by Sae since I met her.
[MOMO] Maybe that's how
the whole thing started.
I was depressed
and feeling alone,
and then someone was there.
It's good to see
you again, Momo.
Remember me?
I'm the girl who gave you
the eraser during the exam.
[chuckles]
[MOMO] I hadn't felt that
happy in a long time.
Ugh... I should have
noticed back then.
Sae swore she could help
me out with the others,
but none of the cliques
would even bother
to look in my direction.
[KAIRI gasps]
[MOMO] Maybe that's it.
Maybe Sae got to Toji
and messed with his head
like she did with mine.
And if that's the case,
then nothing is actually wrong.
He could tell me one more
time that he loves me.
And everything would be okay.
--[TOJI gasps]
--[SAE] Oh, Toji, I'm sorry!
No. I just spaced out.
[SAE] Here. This'll clean you
up. I'll get the mess down here.
Nice one. You gotta hold
on to girls like that.
[TOJI gasps]
[TOJI]
She's not my "girl".
[SAE humming]
Uh?
[BOTH panting]
[SAE gasps]
What is it?
Sae?
Oh, it's nothing.
Uh... Hmm...
I can't believe
Toji's in the hospital
and we never heard about it.
Yeah, thanks for telling me.
Sure.
If you hadn't told me about
Toji, I still wouldn't know.
And I probably wouldn't
until they released
him from this place.
It makes me kinda sick
to say it, but I think
you're the only person
who's on my side right now.
[KAIRI gasps]
[KAIRI]
My sweet baby!
Shut up!
[SAE groans]
Okay, patient. I think
it's time you changed your gown.
Take that off and let
me wash it for you.
Uh... I think I'm fine.
[SAE]
No, I wanna do this.
Let's see, they keep the clean
ones up in that cabinet, right?
Sae, don't. Seriously.
[SAE yelps]
[BOTH grunt]
[SAE] I can't believe that!
I'm so sorry!
[TOJI]
I'm okay...
[SAE]
Did I pop your stitches?
No.
[BOTH gasp]
[MOMO]
You!
What do you think you're doing?!
How dare you throw
yourself at him!
You--
[MOMO gasps]
Let go of me.
Sae just slipped on
some water I spilled
and she landed on me.
Oh, sure. Like I believe that.
And of course such an accident
would happen right
as I walk into the room.
[TOJI] Before you start
pointing fingers at both of us,
take a look at yourself.
Why did you show up
here with him?
Who, me? Don't worry,
I'm just here as counsel
to the accused
in these proceedings.
I'm sure we're all aware
of the events of recent days.
Momo was concerned that some of
these happenings have construed
some misunderstandings
of said events.
These are simply rumors
she'd like to dispel.
And for these reasons,
Momo and I decided to
arrive here together.
Would you please try
making some sense?!
How about this: You haven't
seen Toji in a while,
so why don't you start off
with a simple apology.
[MOMO gasps]
I'm sorry, Toji.
I promise I would have come
to see you sooner, but I--
I really had no idea
you were in the hospital.
I can't believe you're
lying to him again.
Why, you!
[MOMO mumbles]
She's telling the truth, man.
She didn't know you were here
with apendicitis until
today when I told her.
And as long as
I'm clearing the air.
You may have mistaken the reason
Momo had her arms around me
for the fact that she
likes me, which is wrong.
Actually, I was about to
fall down and she helped me up.
That's it. Nothing special.
They're lying. It's the one
thing these two do best.
Now, Kairi.
With pleasure, Momo!
--[KAIRI grunts]
--[SAE yelps]
[SAE]
What the--
Let go of me! You can't drag
me around like I'm your pet!
Put me down!
Seems like you two are
pretty good friends.
[MOMO gasps]
We talk sometimes. That's all.
But why? You know he's
got a thing for you.
Why would you bother
leading a guy on when
you know you don't
even like him back?
But I'm not.
If you came here to clear
up a misunderstanding,
bringing him was a dumb idea.
Bringing him was my only choice!
If I showed up here alone,
would you believe
anything I had to say? No!
Because you only believe the
lies that Sae tells you!
[TOJI] You're wrong about Sae.
Your opinion's all warped.
My opinion is that
you are warped!
Why would you believe
any other girl
over the one that you're
supposedly in love with?
Look, I just can't see
why she would lie to me.
I mean, what purpose
could it possibly serve
for her to lie and
piss everyone off?
[MOMO gasps]
Are you saying that
no matter what I do,
you'll never trust me over her?
[MOMO cries]
Wait, Momo!
She has no reason to lie?
There's no purpose for Sae
to deceive everyone?
Wouldn't all this
be worth it to her
if, in the end, she
had you to herself?!
It doesn't matter! Just get out
of the window before you fall!
[MOMO] No! I love you,
but no matter what I do,
I can't get you to trust me
and it just kills me.
Listen to me.
Listen to what I'm saying.
Listen to me like I matter.
Because if you don't, I swear
I will jump out of this window.
[FEMALE PATIENT A]
No! Please, don't do it!
[MALE PATIENT B] A fall from
this height would mess you up!
[MOMO] Fine by me. Some broken
bones, some stitches.
At least then I'd get to spend
some time with you, Toji.
Even if you don't
want me around.
[SAE] Okay, genius.
I thought you liked Momo.
'Cause if you do,
this is a royally dumb move
leaving her alone with him.
I do, but I'm doing this
because Momo's depending on me,
which has its own merits.
[KAIRI gasps]
--[SAE screaming]
--Oh no!
She's gonna fall off of there
and kill herself!
Momo... That's dangerous.
You need to get down.
[MOMO]
Then you have to promise me--
Promise me that
you'll listen to me, Toji.
That you'll hear what
I have to say about Sae!
I promise! Do you hear me?
Now, please, get down!
Say it then!
Say you'll believe me.
Yes. Now, stop all this.
Take my hand.
[MOMO gasps, screams]
[gasps]
--[SAE gasps]
--I can't bear to watch!
[KAIRI sighs]
[PATIENTS clapping]
I have never seen
such a heroic act.
[MALE PATIENT]
I'm so glad you didn't fall.
--[SAE growls]
--[KAIRI whimpers]
What am I gonna do?!
He was so close to being mine.
[SAE chuckles]
[KAIRI]
Uh?
[SAE] Kairi, how would you
feel about teaming up?
[KAIRI]
Huh?
This whole thing is kismet.
Look how perfectly our
goals seem to intersect.
You want to be with Momo
and I want to be with Toji.
If we join forces and
get them apart, we both win.
[KAIRI snickers]
[SAE chuckles]
Oh, Toji, I'm sorry.
I never considered
that you standing up
could pop your stitches out.
No big deal. They'll heal up.
You know you really lost it
for a minute there.
Threatening to jump if
I didn't hear you out.
But I was desperate.
I thought if I didn't do that,
you would have had me
kicked out of the hospital.
I would never have done that.
But you certainly did
get my attention.
[MOMO sighs]
[MOMO]
Finally!
Now I can tell him about
Sae's every lie, every trick!
What do ya say?
Are we partners or not?
Well... I never put those
pieces together like that.
But I guess if we can help each
other out, it might just work.
No, it will work.
Fill me in on the plan.
What are we gonna do?
I thought it was obvious. We
gotta stop them from making up.
And since they're already
ticked at each other...
We just have to give 'em
a little nudge over the edge.
How do we do that?
You want specifics, Kairi?
We consummate.
What?! You and me?!
No, doofus. I mean, like this.
[SAE]
Toji?
Toji, you must wake up.
Is that you? Sae, the
hour is quite late.
What's happening, Sae?
Toji...
Oh, I love you so much it steals
the very breath from inside me.
Sae, no!
We cannot do this!
We cannot do this.
[SAE]
Well, something like that.
And since he's all stitched up
and weary from surgery,
I don't think he'll be able
to get away from me
as long as I'm on top of him
while I make my move.
Awesome! That is one sweet plan.
I'm impressed by your strategy.
Now tell me, how do I fit into
this killer scheme of yours?
[SAE laughs]
Hey, I'm serious. Where's the
part where I get mine?
You snag Momo and
wait somewhere close by
while I get my side of the plan
with Toji off the ground.
After that, I'll text
you a signal
through your cell phone,
and then--
Then the two of us show up
and find you and Toji.
There you go! Your brain works!
[KAIRI laughs]
And Toji's got nice enough
manners that when he sees
me crying while I ask him
to take responsibility,
he won't even know
how to turn me down.
Then, once Toji
and Momo are split up,
all you have to do is find Momo
and comfort her in the way
that only a true man can.
[KAIRI laughs]
[SAE] The easiest person
in the world to manipulate
is the one who's just
lost everything.
Uh...
[BOTH laugh]
[SAE] Ow. O-Ow, that hurts!
My face doesn't work like that!
You've got guts.
That filthy mouth of yours
just spits out venom
like nobody's business.
[SAE yelps]
So do you want
to do this or not?!
Not in a million
freakin' years.
[SAE]
Wha--
Leave me, alone
[SAE gasps]
[MOMO]
Where should I begin this thing?
Oh yeah, right.
I'll start with the phone call
when you weren't feeling well.
Wait. I gotta ask
you something.
And I need you to
be honest with me
if we're gonna move any further
with this relationship.
Yeah?
After that, I'll listen to
everything you have to say.
[MOMO]
What's the deal?
I just wanna tell him
how horrible Sae is.
That's fine. What is it
that you need to know?
It's just one detail.
Kairi.
Okay.
How do you feel about him?
Is he your boyfriend
or the just some guy you see
in the halls at school?
Stop it. You only think that
because Sae has messed
with your head so much,
that you can't tell what's real
from what she wants
you to believe.
[TOJI]
No, you're wrong.
Everything that's happened
has made me nervous.
But to tell you the truth, I was
worried about him a long time
before you and I
even got together.
I was shy, but I knew if
I didn't make my move soon,
he'd get you first.
You don't have to worry.
I have much better sense
and better taste
than to waste my time
with a cocky, slacker,
know-it-all like him.
All right.
[TOJI]
But when I see you two together,
I see something that works.
You're so natural, full of life.
And your personalities
are more alike
than either of you would
probably care to admit.
Are you calling me
a know-it-all?
No. You're missing my
point completely--
[gasps]
Feel that? My heart is racing.
The only time my heart beats
that quickly is
when I'm with you.
I've never felt that with Kairi.
He's had his arms around me, and
he's even told me he loves me
but nothing compares to you.
I fell in love with you
the day I met you,
and that hasn't
changed since then.
[FEMALE PATIENT B]
Give them their privacy.
[MALE PATIENT A]
Aw, I was just--
[MALE PATIENT D] Eavesdropping
on teenagers. Come on, now.
[BOTH laugh]
[MOMO]
This is the first happy moment
Toji and I have had
together in days.
[KAIRI] It's only a matter of
time before your secrets
and lies wear thin on Toji.
This might be the perfect
opportunity for you to back off.
You know, before all your
bridges go up in flames.
Back off? Then you're going for
the same cautious approach
with Momo, I'm assuming?
Not a chance. Why should
I have to give up?
I can still love
whichever lady I choose.
Oh yeah? You can just
keep pushing forward?
Why do I have to be the one
who has to back off then?!
Because you don't
actually like Toji.
You're just chasing him
down to get at Momo.
I think you probably
have some weird,
misdirected jealousy issues.
You should see the counselor.
[SAE]
Uh! I do not have issues!
Of course not. Look, Sae.
You're not gonna win Toji
over by tricking him.
You need to try a
more direct attack.
[SAE growls]
[KAIRI] Keep in mind
this is my advice.
And seeing how I kissed Momo
before we had ever gone out,
I'd take me with
a grain of salt.
[SAE] So that rumor was less of
a rumor and more of a fact.
[KAIRI]
Yep.
Thank you, Kairi.
Later!
[KAIRI] Uh! Oh, great!
I opened my big mouth again!
[SAE chuckles]
[SAE] With this ammo,
I'm ready for my direct attack!
[MOMO] I never changed the
meeting place to the cafeteria.
I swear. I was at the pool.
So that was another
of Sae's lies.
Huh, I wonder why she
keeps doing all this.
I already told you.
It's so you'd dump me
and go out with her.
It just doesn't seem like
something Sae would do.
[MOMO]
Uh...
I've said it before.
Sae is a genius when it comes
to the art of the lie.
And talk about a mimic.
She's always copying
everything other people do.
[BOTH gasp]
Momo's the one who's lying!
Don't fall for her crap again!
Uh...
In which of your sick fantasies
have I been lying to Toji?
Oh, shut up. You have a
relationship with Kairi. I know!
What are you talking about?
[SAE] Don't act all innocent.
You kissed him.
[BOTH gasp]
Didn't expect that,
did you, Momo?
I'm sorry! It slipped out!
Eh... So, how's it going?
Are they telling the truth about
this, Momo? Did you kiss him?
Uhh... Why, don't you let
me explain what happened--
I'm not talking to you.
[KAIRI gasps]
[TOJI]
Momo, tell me.
Did you kiss Kairi or not?
[KAIRI grunts]
I don't believe it.
[MOMO] I'm sorry you had
to find out like this,
but I never lied to you, Toji.
I kissed Kairi,
but it was before you and I
started going out.
[TOJI]
So nothing that happened
before we started
dating matters?
It's not like I wanted to.
Before I knew it,
he was kissing me. I didn't
have a chance to push him off.
[TOJI sighs]
You had the chance
when I made a move.
[MOMO gasps]
You really are in love
with Kairi, aren't you?
No way. The only person
that I love is you!
It was the kiss.
He kissed you once and you
completely fell for him.
You sound like you've lost it.
[TOJI]
Maybe. Maybe not.
What've you two been doing
since I've been in the hospital.
Laughing at me behind my back?
Are you seriously suggesting
that Kairi and I would
do something like that?
You should really try screwing
your head on straight!
[TOJI gasps]
Oh, and while we're on the
subject of kissing people,
why don't you go ahead and
explain to me what was going on
between you two in the garden.
I saw you with Sae
so don't try to deny it!
It wasn't a kiss.
[MOMO]
That wasn't a kiss?!
Uhh... No, it was...
something else.
What else could it have been?
[SAE]
Practice.
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Practice?
Yeah, for when you
finally got to kiss Toji.
Toji... you didn't.
[MOMO] You did this with her
so you would be prepared
for the same thing with me?
Yes.
Are you insane?!
Where did you get the idea
that its okay to go around
kissing other girls to practice
kissing the girl you like?!
I didn't think it was humanly
possible to be that stupid!
You're a stupid,
stupid boy, Toji.
[TOJI] Call me stupid,
but you're a liar!
At least I'm honest.
You can't even do that much.
So I don't think this
is gonna work out.
We should break up.
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Get over yourself!
Who do you think you are?!
How could you even
say that to me?!
I can't believe
you took that away!
It was the only
thing I had left.
I'm the one who should be
breaking up with you!
[MOMO cries]
[KAIRI]
Momo, don't go! Momo!
[SAE cries]
[SAE]
Meow!
[MOMO] So there's this swim meet
and Sae recommended me for it.
Sounds like another one
of the rat's plans.
That psycho feeds on the
unhappiness of others
like she's never had a meal.
Next time on Peach Girl:
"The Swim Meet from Hell."