[MOMO]
Wait a minute! Hold on!
Don't pull me like this.
You're hurting my hand.
[MOMO] This is where I saw
Toji and Sae kissing.
Why did he bring me here?
[MOMO]
What's this all about?
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
No!
[SAE]
He must have assumed
that getting a kiss
from you would be easy.
[MOMO]
What just happened?
What's up, Toji?
Will you give this to Momo?
Uh...
Toji!
How's it going?
No one ignores me!
Toji! Why are you running?!
[TOJI gasps]
What's going on?
You totally blew me off.
Where's Momo?
[TOJI panting]
It's no good.
[SAE]
Huh?
I screwed everything up.
Momo hates me.
I know she does.
[cars honking]
[bus honking]
[KAIRI]
Watch out!
You almost got
yourself killed, Momo.
Yeah, thanks...
I'm aware of that.
[brakes squeal]
[KAIRI grunts]
See what I mean?
I better walk you home.
[MOMO] Don't bother.
I can get home myself.
[KAIRI]
So you claim,
but who was it that just
got smacked by a bicycle
and nearly flattened into a
pancake by oncoming traffic?
[MOMO growls]
What's with you today? Is it so
bad that Toji tried to kiss you?
Man, I don't get you.
I thought if the guy
you loved tried to kiss you
--you'd be happy about it.
--What's not to get?
He tried to kiss me in the same
place he made out with Sae.
I know that. So what?
[MOMO]
It's just wrong.
I would never kiss him in
the same spot he kissed her.
I can't believe Toji
would do such a thing!
Forcing me into the garden...
...without even bothering
to ask how I felt about it.
That puts him on the same
idiotic level as you, Kairi!
[KAIRI grunts]
[MOMO] He was like
a different person...
I guess he is only judging me
by my appearance after all,
even if he said it wasn't true.
He probably thinks
I'm some slut.
It just isn't fair.
[KAIRI]
You love him, right?
[MOMO gasps]
Then just tell him
that this idea that
you're a slut is wrong.
What's most important here
are your feelings, not his.
[MOMO]
Yeah, but...
This is true for all men.
We often have ulterior
motives with girls.
If you don't like that,
then be clear with him
and tell him how you feel.
And if he decides to leave
you for something that trivial,
then he wasn't worth
your time anyway.
[KAIRI] What's most important
here are your feelings, not his.
[MOMO]
I never expected Kairi
of all people to be
filled with such insight.
But I guess he was trying
to make me feel better.
[dog barking]
I'm thinking here, stupid dog.
[MOMO] Actually, regardless of
what's happened in the past,
he's really taught
me quite a bit.
[MOMO] I mean, if he hadn't
been there for me today,
I'd probably be
a complete wreck by now.
[water splashing]
[MOMO] Maybe it wouldn't be such
a bad idea to give Kairi a shot.
[MOMO]
We'll see.
[KAIRI]
You love him, right?
Then just tell him
that this idea
that you're a slut is wrong.
[MOMO] But I don't wanna have to
convince him of who I really am.
Oh, Toji...
[dog barking]
Would you shut up?!
Uh...
[TOJI gasps]
[MOMO gasps]
Why? Why? Why? Why is
Toji outside my house?!
How long have you been here?
Not long.
I happened to be walking
through the neighborhood.
[MOMO]
Liar.
He's still in
his school uniform.
He hasn't even been home yet.
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry.
When I saw you talking
to Kairi by the pool,
I completely lost it.
It looked like you were
laughing and I thought that
maybe you have more fun
with him than with me.
I saw you two together
and I just kept thinking,
"Hey! Get away
from my girlfriend!"
And...
I lost my temper.
[MOMO] He came all the way
to my house at this hour
just to tell me that?
I'm glad.
I was afraid you'd tell me
to get lost before
I could say that.
[MOMO]
I was wrong!
Toji isn't going out with me
because he thinks I'm easy.
He really cares
about my feelings.
But even if he did
want that... then maybe.
[TOJI gasps]
[MOMO]
Maybe...
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Ahh! What am I doing?!
I shouldn't be
thinking about that!
[TOJI]
Well, I'd better get home.
[MOMO] Wait. I'll walk
you to the corner.
[TOJI]
That's okay. It's pretty late.
I'll just see you tomorrow.
[MOMO]
Sounds good.
What a relief. Uh...?
Toji!
I took this out of your wallet
the other day
without telling you.
When I saw it there,
I was shocked.
But I'm sure you have a
reasonable explanation for it.
I'm sorry I kept it from you.
Will you please forgive me?
Uh, what?
It's okay. You don't have
to say anything. I trust you.
[MOMO]
Exactly.
What's most important is that
Toji and I love each other.
See ya tomorrow.
[STUDENTS chatter]
What is this thing anyway?
[TOJI]
Hm?
Morning, Sae.
Hey...
Does this thing belong to you?
Uhh... You're crying!
I didn't notice... Are you okay?
No, I'm not...
Momo's mad at me.
She is?
She must have
been watching us...
...when we kissed in the garden.
[TOJI gasps]
What should I do?
I was only trying to help her
--and now I've made her mad.
--[TOJI whimpers]
[SAE cries]
Wow... Sorry.
[MOMO]
Sae... You never quit!
Toji.
[SAE, TOJI gasp]
--[MOMO] I need to talk to you!
--[TOJI] What... Hey!
[TOJI grunts]
[MOMO] I don't want you
talking to Sae anymore.
What was she saying?
She's probably bad-mouthing
me again, right?
Look, I don't know what she's
been telling you lately,
but don't believe
a word she says.
Pretty much everything that
comes out of that girl's mouth
is a manipulative lie.
So even if she comes up
to you in the hall
and starts talking,
just ignore her. 'Kay?
Why would I do that?
She's your friend, right?
Her my friend? Yeah, that's
what I used to believe.
This will sound weird
but I've been meaning
to ask you for awhile.
You and Sae haven't been
going out on dates
--behind my back, have you?
-[TOJI gasps]
But... Momo, I'm with you.
Why would I be seeing Sae?
That doesn't make any sense.
[SAE]
She must have been watching us
when we kissed in the garden.
[TOJI]
So Momo did see us kiss.
That explains why
she ran off yesterday.
She must be
really angry with me.
Momo, why would you ask
me something like that?
Uh...
[MOMO]
I knew it!
Everything she's said so far
has been nothing but a lie!
[MOMO] Nevermind. It was a
stupid question. Forget it.
Yeah, sure.
[bell ringing]
[MOMO gasps]
So, Toji paid a visit to
your house late last night, huh?
How do you know that?
Because I was the one
who told him to visit you
in the first place.
[MOMO gasps]
[SAE snickers]
What's all this nonsense
about you not allowing
him to kiss you?
He told me everything
'cause we're close like that.
[MOMO]
No way.
Toji was so blown away at
the fact that you denied him
that he got depressed.
That's when I stepped in
and gave him the advice to go to
your house and make up with you.
You know, when it comes to Toji,
I've always been
there by his side.
Plus, he'll do practically...
[MOMO]
No. Don't let her get to you.
If you start accusing Toji
of dating Sae again,
then he'll distance himself,
which is exactly what she wants.
You should hope you get
another chance to kiss him
because his lips are way soft.
Get outta my way! I can't clean!
[SAE gasps, yelps]
[ALL gasps]
[TOJI gasps]
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[MOMO] What happened?
I barely touched her.
[TOJI]
Sae!
Hey, are you alright?
Look she's hurt!
Can you stand up?
[SAE whimpers]
I didn't... mean to...
Let's hope she
didn't break something.
[MOMO]
Great.
Now everyone's looking at
me like I'm the bad guy.
Sae, did that bruise on
your cheek come from...
[MOMO] I don't want you
talking to Sae anymore.
Uh... Just nevermind.
[MOMO gasps]
You lousy faker!
Sae! Wait for me!
Momo?
--[MOMO grunts]
--[SAE yelps]
Just as I thought!
Your leg is fine!
You're not injured
at all, ya big faker!
You made a big show
of falling down
in front of Toji, didn't you?
What's with you?
You're scaring me!
You never seem to get it!
Stay away from Toji!
Momo, stop this.
Do not buy into her crap.
She'll do anything to get her
hands on what she wants,
even if that means lying and
deceiving her so-called friends
Momo, please! Do you really
believe I would do that to you?
[MOMO]
Knock it off, Sae!
Now you're just trying
to get Toji to take your side.
Even though we both
know very well
that you don't care
about him at all!
It's like your goal in life is
to copy what everyone else does!
[SAE gasps]
When have I ever copied someone?
Every day.
[SAE]
That's not true!
[MOMO]
Yes, it is!
[SAE]
No, it isn't!
--[MOMO] You know it's true!
--[TOJI growls]
[SAE]
You're such a liar!
[TOJI]
That's enough!
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Toji?
Look, Momo, I understand you're
angry because I kissed Sae.
Well, she's not the only one
you should be angry with.
But... She's a liar.
Don't stand up for her.
I dunno what's up with you
two, but the last few days,
Sae's done nothing
but look out for you.
Yet, for some reason,
you can't see that.
It makes me think that maybe...
...I was wrong about you.
[MOMO gasps]
[SAE]
Meow.
[MOMO]
You're a jerk, Toji!
I'm sick of you
believing Sae over me
as if I'm some jealous freak!
If what you're looking for is a
lying tramp, then you found her!
I hate you so much!
[MOMO grunts]
[MOMO]
I know.
I'll tell him everything that
Sae has done to undermine me.
Otherwise, I'll come out
looking like a selfish,
jealous, violent girl.
[TOJI] Mom. Do we have
anything for a stomachache?
[TOJI'S MOM]
Oh... I'm sorry
you're not feeling
well, sweetie.
We should have some
medicine in the drawer.
[phone rings]
[TOJI'S MOM]
Hello? Oh, yes, hi.
Of course. Let me get him.
Toji, phone's for you.
It's Momo.
[TOJI]
Hello?
[MOMO] Oh crap. He sounds
like he's in a terrible mood.
I've got to do this though.
Uh, hi, Toji... I wanted
to say I'm sorry...
About what happened earlier.
[TOJI grunts]
[TOJI]
Uh-huh.
I know you're probably
thinking I'm crazy
and making this all up, but
what I said about Sae is true.
A perfect example was
last week at the mall.
I saw a bag and
said it was cute.
Next thing I know,
she's bought it.
So when she asked me
who I had a crush on,
I knew she was just
fishing for information.
That's why I told her I liked
Kairi, to get her off the scent.
I didn't want her to try to
steal you away from me.
And then another that Sae
always does is when she's...
Momo.
[MOMO]
Yeah?
Look I don't mean to be rude,
but I'm not in
the mood right now
to listen to you
bad-mouth Sae, okay?
[MOMO] I know it may sound
like I'm bad-mouthing her,
but please just hear me out.
She's a lot more calculating
that you give her credit for.
[TOJI]
I apologize for kissing Sae.
It was stupid and
I shouldn't have done it.
If I were in your place,
I'd feel the same way.
You got every reason
to be mad at me.
But I'm not.
I'm... I'm sorry for
the mistake I made.
I never meant to betray you.
You haven't betrayed me...
You have to believe me, I'm not
that angry about the kiss.
Well, I guess I can't say
I'm totally fine with it.
But what I'm trying
to say is that--
[TOJI]
I gotta go.
Toji? Toji!
[phone beeps]
[HOMEROOM TEACHER] Toji and
Momo are both absent today.
We got a call from Toji's
parents this morning.
Last night he was suffering
from what he thought
was a stomachache.
It turns out it was appendicitis
so he's in the hospital now.
[HOMEROOM TEACHER] If anyone
would like to volunteer
to take him class notes and
a study guide for the final,
I'm sure he'll appreciate it.
[GIRL C] This was my
third trip to the zoo this year
and the most revealing.
I spent the entire time...
[BOY A]
What's this?
[GIRL D]
It's a note for everyone.
[GIRL E] Read it then pass
it on. Keep it a secret.
[GIRL F] Oh, we are
so evil. Ha-ha-ha.
[STUDENTS whispering]
[MOMO panting]
[MOMO] I can't believe I
overslept! Ugh, I hate this!
What's going on?
[MOMO] Why's everyone
acting so weird?
[MOMO]
He's absent today?
[MOMO sighs]
[MOMO] I'm not sure if I'm
disappointed or relieved.
[HISTORY TEACHER]
When you take those factors
into consideration, it's quite
obvious why Buddhism began...
[MOMO] I wonder what's
wrong with him?
[GIRL E]
What a slut!
I heard she slept with,
like, ten guys last summer.
[GIRL E]
Yeah, she's a tramp.
[MOMO] How dare they
talk about me like that!
They don't even know me!
[SAE]
Hello? Toji?
How are we feeling?
Oh, hey there, Sae.
[SAE]
You poor thing.
I can't believe you
had appendicitis.
So the surgery went well?
[TOJI]
Hmm.
I got you these flowers, well,
they're from the whole class.
Oh, and here are some notes.
So, at what point did your
stomach start hurting?
Last I saw,
you looked fine to me.
Well, I started feeling it
right before dinner...
--Sae...
--[SAE gasps]
Are you here by yourself?
Uh... yeah, I...
I invited Momo but
I guess she didn't...
I see.
[SAE] Well, I better get going.
I hope you feel better.
[TOJI]
Huh? So soon?
[SAE]
If I stay here any longer,
I'm sure Momo will
get upset with me.
Let me know if you need
anything else, okay?
A message.
[SAE]
Huh?
[TOJI]
Last night Momo called me,
but it was right at the time
that my stomach started hurting
so I was barely able to speak,
let alone think straight.
I can't remember what I said
but I'm pretty sure
I hung up on her.
Really?
[TOJI] So, will you
tell her that I'm sorry
and I didn't mean it?
Sure, you got it.
Leave it up to me.
Oh, yes. Make-up. I love it.
Goodbye, bruise. Hello, beauty.
[SAE humming]
[MOMO] Should I call? I just
want to find out if he's okay.
But what if he thinks
I'm being too pushy?
Check it out. It's a card
from everyone in class.
Hey, that's great.
[TOJI laughs, groans]
My stomach hurts when I laugh.
[SAE giggles]
It looks like
Momo didn't sign it.
Huh... That's weird.
You know, I invited her
with me to come visit you.
I see.
[SAE]
I'm sorry.
Ever since I tried to help,
your relationship with Momo
has gone downhill.
Don't be silly.
It'd be best if I didn't
come back here anymore.
Goodbye.
Sae, hold on!
[KAIRI]
What's up with, Toji?
[MOMO] He's been absent for
three straight days now
and every time I ask
his friends about him,
they all claim not to
know what's going on.
[KAIRI]
Hmm... that's strange.
And speaking of strange,
my entire class has
been acting weird.
They keep talking behind my back
and when I look at them,
they either turn away
or stare me down.
Are you being ostracized from
the class or something?
Well... maybe...
[laughs]
[bell chimes]
Oh, great.
Yay. I get to face all the
people that secretly hate me.
Find me in the halls if
you get another break today.
I always have a good time
hanging out with you.
Yeah, right. If I do that, then
all of your friends will start
spreading more rumors about me.
Come on.
[MOMO yelps]
--[KAIRI gasps]
--[MOMO yelps]
[BOTH yelp]
[KAIRI grunting]
[KAIRI groaning]
[MOMO]
Kairi!
Kairi! Are you okay?
Wow, that hurt... What happened?
I'm so sorry...
I slipped on the stairs.
What? Come on, Momo.
You know you pushed me.
[MOMO]
No, I did not!
No matter how detestable
I find you and your dirty mind,
I would never try to push
someone down a flight of stairs.
[KAIRI] That sure is
a funny way of putting it.
Can you stand up?
[KAIRI]
I think so.
You sure you're okay?
[MOMO gasps]
What are you hugging me for?
Get your hands off me!
I can't resist.
You're just so cuddly.
Let go of me,
you filthy pervert!
Ugh! If you keep
pulling this crap,
people are gonna spread
more rumors about me!
Get off! Uh...
[SAE snickers]
[NORI]
What's wrong with you, Kairi?
You don't actually
like Momo, do you?
Like anyone but her...
She's a dirty slut.
Don't even give her
the time of day.
She actually tried to steal
her best friend's boyfriend.
[KAIRI]
What're you talking about?
Who's Momo's best friend?
Sae Kashiwagi.
[KAIRI] And who's the
best friend's boyfriend?
It's Toji, duh!
Uh?!
Momo and Kairi?
I'm sorry.
I know I said
I wasn't coming back...
...but this is just too
shocking not tell you.
How could she do this to you
while you're sick
in the hospital?
[TOJI] Momo and Kairi
were holding each other?
[TOJI]
I don't believe it.
Momo! Wait for me!
Stay away from me!
You and I have nothing
to talk about,
so leave me alone before
I do something you'll regret.
[KAIRI] Toji's in the hospital
with appendicitis.
[MOMO gasps]
I think Sae's tried to
keep it a secret from you.
[KAIRI] Apparently she
spread word around
that no one tell you
about Toji's illness.
I guess she told them
to not tell me either
because I'm just now
hearing about it.
I'm pretty sure she just wanted
to visit him in
the hospital by herself.
Why would she do that?
Momo, I think it's obvious
that Sae is not only trying to
trash you and your reputation,
but she's also trying to
make Toji her own boyfriend.
[KAIRI gasps]
[MOMO]
I'm... gonna... kill her!
Woah... Chill out,
Momo... Settle down.
[MOMO]
Sae!
Toji, you have it all wrong!
Sae's been feeding you
false information!
How can you believe a word she
says? Why don't you believe me?
That's it, Toji!
You and I are finished!
Next time on Peach Girl:
"The Catastrophe."