[MOMO]
Toji.
Toji!
[KAIRI]
Mm. Oh Momo.
[MOMO] All I ever wanted
was to find happiness.
It's okay for me to
be happy, isn't it?
I spent the whole
month at the beach.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[RYOZO]
Did you hear what happened?
[SHOJI, TORU, NOZOMI]
Huh?!
[NOZOMI] What are those
two doing together?
[TORU]
I thought they broke up.
[MISAO sighs]
[MISAO exhales]
[NAMI, RITSUKO, KAKO]
Uh?!
[KAKO]
Momo! Come here.
What's going on?
Why are you walking with Toji?
Everyone saw you guys together
and now there's
rumor's flying around.
Oh. Yeah.
We understand if you like him,
but try not to be
so obvious about it.
You know how this school is.
We were all thinking you
and Kairi were a done deal.
[MOMO]
Uh...
[RITSUKO] So he never met
up with you the other day?
[KAKO]
That guy is such an idiot.
I can't believe he
blew you off like that.
He doesn't deserve you.
How do you know all this?
Because he was frantically
trying to find you
all day yesterday. He called
each of us at least once.
[MOMO gasps]
[KAKO] We were starting
to get worried, too.
I must have tried calling
your cell two dozen times
in the last day, but I kept
getting your voicemail.
Sorry. I turned it off.
[KAKO laughs]
That's what I figured.
[RITSUKO] So, what'd you
end up doing yesterday?
[NAMI] You know,
yesterday I had to meet someone
at the train station
here in town.
I saw you walk
out of the station.
[KAKO, MOMO]
Uh?
I noticed you were with Toji.
I thought you'd just
bumped into each other.
Be honest, Momo. Did you
go on the trip with Toji?
[MOMO]
Huh?!
Basically, Kairi didn't show up
so you went and found
the nearest backup.
I can't believe you did that.
[RITSUKO]
Nami!
[foot steps]
[NAMI]
Be honest, Momo.
Did you go on
the trip with Toji?
Basically, Kairi didn't
show up so you went
and found the nearest backup.
I can't believe you did that.
[MOMO]
What am I going to do?
I wonder how Kairi will
react when he hears this.
Should I say something
when I see him?
[KAIRI]
Morning! Ha, ha!
[MOMO]
Uh?
[sighs] Sorry I missed
you the other day.
[KAIRI]
Hey, what's goin' on guys?
[SHOJI]
Homework!
[KAIRI] On the first day?
Summer school go that bad?
[SHOJI]
Shut up!
[MOMO] What the heck?
He looks so happy.
He's acting like
nothing happened.
[MOMO]
I'm so stupid.
He clearly had no intentions
on ever showing up
that day at the park.
I'm done with him, and I'm not
gonna let him bring me down!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] The opening
ceremony for the new semester
will begin promptly at 9:30.
All students, please make
your way to the gymnasium.
[MOMO sighs]
Uh?
Shall we go?
[MOMO]
Mm.
What about Ritsuko and Nami?
[KAKO] They went to
save us some seats.
So I don't mean to pry Momo, but
what's going on with you lately?
Are you and Toji seeing
each other again?
Yeah.
Oh, that's cool.
I'm happy for you.
Sorry if I acted weird,
but it all happened so suddenly,
you know? Can I ask
you something else?
Sure.
What was it exactly that
made you go back to Toji?
Because through all the
crap I've dealt with,
he was always there.
Huh? What're you saying?
Well, uh, it's kind
of a long story.
Tell me everything!
All the details!
I don't care how long it takes!
Okay.
[NORI]
Come on, Kairi.
What happened between
you and Momo?
She showed up this morning
hand in hand with Toji!
Are you okay with that?
You know those two worked at the
same place together all summer.
I was in there all the time.
They were always
flirting with each other.
[KAIRI laughs]
[NORI, SANGO, AKI]
Why are you laughing?
Uh?
Look, I'll catch up
with you later, okay?
[NORI, SANGO, AKI]
Huh?!
Hey, Misao. What's goin' on?
I hate to be the bearer of bad
news, but I saw your friend Momo
show up at school
this morning with Toji.
[KAIRI]
Uh.
You're only the twentieth
person to tell me that.
Did you ever meet her after
you left the hospital?
I missed her.
Well, did you at least
tell her why you were late?
Uh-uh.
Damnit, Kairi,
what's the matter with you?
I'll tell her myself,
if that's what it takes.
[KAIRI] No wait,
please don't! It's okay.
What's okay?
You made your choice.
You decided she was the one.
That's why you have
to tell her the truth!
She'll understand!
Huh?!
I think it's too late for that.
You're not acting like yourself.
I've never seen you give up
on anything this easily before.
Uh?
Woah. What happened
to your face?
Oh. It's nothing.
I just fell down
some stairs, that's all.
Do you expect me to
believe that? Let me see.
[KAKO] Oh. I see. It's all
starting to make sense now.
I had no idea that
was happening.
You did a good job hiding it.
Well, we better get going.
You're so secretive, Momo.
You never tell us anything.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
It's not like it's an
easy thing to talk about.
It is pretty cool though.
Now I know why Toji
started dating Sae.
Everyone assumed that he was
just chauvinistic jerk,
but the fact that he did it to
protect you is so romantic!
Most guys wouldn't go
that far for someone.
To be honest, I don't think
he coulda done anything else
in that situation. After all,
you two have been crazy
about each other for years.
[KAKAO] Oh.
[MOMO] Uh?
[MOMO]
Let's go.
[MOMO] So, even now, Kairi
still has feelings for Misao.
[PRINCIPAL]
I want you all to buckle down,
and really work
hard this semester.
Nami! Ritsuko!
[NAMI]
Mm.
[RITSUKO]
Uh...
Great. Now they all hate me.
No, it's not like that Momo.
Just a few weeks ago,
Nami had an ugly break up
with her boyfriend.
[MOMO]
Huh?
A few days went by where she
couldn't reach him on the phone
and the next thing she knew,
he dumped her. Just like that.
Now he's got some new girlfriend
he's traipsing around with.
Oh.
None of that has anything to do
with you, but I think the whole
Toji thing is a reminder
her of her own situation.
Don't take it personally.
She's just a bit on edge.
[NAMI]
I don't believe this!
Uh. She plans a trip with
Kairi and takes Toji instead!
Nami, keep your voice down.
Look, I don't think Momo's
the type of girl to jump so
quickly from one guy to the--
Oh yeah, don't be so sure!
I didn't mention this earlier,
but when I saw her
with Toji yesterday,
they were in each others arms!
What?
[NAMI] And the one who
made the move was Momo!
She did it right there on
street in front of everyone.
I have totally
misjudged that girl.
[MOMO] I wonder if I should
tell Kairi about Toji.
I'd rather have him
hear it from me
than from someone else in class.
But first, I have to be sure
I'm making the right decision.
Am I doing the right thing
by going with Toji?
[MOMO] Sae! Are you
just now getting here?
You missed the opening ceremony.
[SAE]
I started to feel sick
while I was walking
here this morning.
Are you okay?
You're as white as a ghost.
[SAE groans]
[MOMO] Let me help you
to the nurse's office.
Misao should be able
to do something.
No way! I don't need that stupid
bitch to take care of me!
[MOMO] Sae? Have you been
eating well lately?
You look a little too thin.
[KAKO] Starving yourself
is no way to lose weight.
It's unhealthy.
[SAE]
I'm going home.
All that's left today
is homeroom, then we're done.
If you can find
somewhere to lie down,
I can take you home after that.
No thanks. I can
manage on my own.
But. Uh.
Sae. What happened?
[SAE]
Huh? Nothing.
[MOMO]
Are you sure?
[ALL gasp]
Let's go.
It stinks in here.
[KAKO]
Nami, wait!
[foot steps]
[KAKO]
You need to cool off.
You've been acting
like a jerk all day.
Everyone knows you're going
through a tough breakup,
but don't bring Momo
down with you!
Sorry. I know I've been rude,
but as for Momo,
I just can't forgive her.
It's like she wanted
insurance on her boyfriend.
Like if things didn't
work out with Kairi,
she could rebound back to Toji
without missing a breath.
I think it's just
plain disgusting!
Couldn't you at
least wait a week?
[KAKO]
Nami, listen!
She did what she did because of
things you know nothing about!
I don't care what
happened to you, Momo!
All I know is that you're
shallow enough to take Toji
on a trip that you had
already promised to Kairi!
It's like you didn't care
which one of 'em went!
[KAKO]
Nami! That's enough!
[MOMO] Even if Kairi
had shown up that day,
I still don't think I
would've gone with him.
[KAKO, NAMI, RITSUKO]
Huh?
[MOMO] He knew that I would
only wait five minutes for him.
But why?
If you really loved him, you
would wait longer than that.
[MOMO] It was because I loved
him that I couldn't wait.
Those five minutes meant
the entire world to me.
What? Hold on.
You love him so much
that you can't wait for him?
I don't get it.
[KAIRI]
Nami.
[NAMI]
Uh?
You should give Momo
the benefit of the doubt.
--[NAMI] Uh?!
--[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO]
Kairi! He heard all that?
Help me make some sense of this.
You had a reason
for being late, right?
But she wrote you off without
giving you a chance to explain.
I made the mistake of putting
someone else first.
[MOMO]
Uh?!
Someone else? Wait,
are you saying you're in love
with someone
else besides Momo?
I heard that you and Toji got
back together. Congratulations.
I'm sure you two will
be happy together.
Sorry if I let ya down, Momo.
I never meant for
that to happen.
[SAE]
Uh...
[GIRL C]
Did you hear?
Kairi's got another girl he's
in love with besides Momo!
[GIRL D]
No way!
[GIRL E] So Kairi was cheating
on Momo the whole time?
[GIRL F]
Get out!
[GIRL G] He got tired of her,
so he found someone else.
[GIRL H] I never thought
Kairi would be so scheming.
[GIRL I]
What a disappointment.
[GIRL J]
I'd still go out with him,
I don't care about his past.
[GIRL I]
You're terrible!
[GIRLS giggle]
[GIRL K] So that's why
those two got back together!
[GIRL L]
Momo and Toji, right?
[GIRL K]
It's so typical.
She couldn't make it
work with Kairi,
so she ran back to
her old boyfriend.
I know people like to spread
rumors, but this is ridiculous.
Look, if someone's talking
trash, just let me know.
They're not.
Most everyone has been pretty
sympathetic towards me.
[TOJI] Well I'm sure people will
be talking for quite a while,
but as long as the two of us
hang in there, we'll be fine.
And if anyone says
something, just tell me.
'Kay!
[MOMO] Toji is so sweet!
He's always looking out for me.
I just feel so relaxed
when I'm with him.
I think if I had been alone
after what happened with Kairi,
I wouldn't have
recovered so quickly.
I'm so lucky to have
him here with me.
And this time, for sure, I'm
going to take good care of him.
Nice! That was a great!
[GIRL L] Wait, did you
just take my picture?
Oh yeah!
[GIRL M] Here!
Get one with both of us!
[GIRLS chatting]
[KAKO] Uh. Look at those
girls fawning over him.
That makes me wanna throw up.
Kairi! Don't forget
about us, babe!
Okay! Say cheese!
[gasps]
Swiss cheese!
[NORI]
How's it look?
That's a great one!
Oops, I missed that.
Do it again.
I've heard terrible
rumors about you today.
Flirting with all those girls
isn't helping your reputation.
But ya have to admit,
now that I'm a free man
I've become quite popular.
Are you sure you
wanna let this thing
with Momo fall apart like this?
Misao. If you really
wanna know the truth,
I feel like the marathon runner
that trips at the finish line
and comes in second.
[MISAO]
Huh?
[KAIRI] It was a race
I could have won easily
had I not looked away
in the final stretch.
After the fact,
it does no good to say
that race was mine,
I should have won.
It's too late now for regret.
All I can do is try to
move on with my life.
[KAIRI]
I have learned some things.
Like having a relationship
with someone requires
that you always pay attention.
Oh man. I can't
believe I let her go.
[phone rings]
[RYO]
Yeah?
Hey, Ryo! It's Sae.
Got a minute?
[dial tone]
[SAE]
Mm.
--[KAIRI] Ah!
--[SAE] Kairi! Help me!
With what?
I need your cell phone!
[KAIRI]
Uh...
Have you brother
meet you somewhere!
What? Why should I?
Because if you call him
then he'll listen to you!
He keeps hanging up
on me for some reason.
You're crazy. Do it yourself.
I told you already.
He keeps hanging up on me!
Sounds like someone's moved on.
Never mind!
Just call him you jerk!
Tell you what.
I'll call my brother,
but only if you agree to
do me a favor in return.
What favor?
Sae, did you ever say anything
to Momo about how I went looking
for her in the middle of that
typhoon the other day?
I haven't said a word.
Good answer. That's exactly
what I wanted to hear.
[SAE]
Huh?
It's just that I put
myself in harms way
to get to the beach that
night without getting killed.
Only to find that Momo and Toji
had been together
the whole time.
I wanna break
those two up,
and I think you're just
the person to do that.
Tell Momo how much effort
I put in to finding her.
After all, you are the only
one who really knows
what happened to me that day.
So, what do you say?
Well. I guess I could
give it a shot.
[KAIRI]
I'll believe it when I see it.
[phone rings]
Yeah?
[KAIRI]
Ryo? It's your brother.
Oh, hey bro. What's goin' on?
[KAIRI] If you have an hour
free in the next day or two,
would you mind gettin'
together to talk?
Tomorrow?
--[SAE screams]
--Yeah, that sounds perfect.
You'll have to wait to find out.
Otherwise, what's the point of
meeting?
What's wrong with me wantin' to
see my brother? Look, I'll send
you an email later with the
address as a reminder. Bye.
--Thank you Kairi!
--[KAIRI] Uh!
So, where are we gonna meet him?
Tell me everything!
We? Sorry, Sae,
but you're on your own there.
Oh, I don't think so.
You'll be going with me.
What? Why do
I have to go?
[SAE] Because if I go by myself,
then Ryo will leave!
[KAIRI]
I wouldn't blame him.
Give me one good reason
why I should do this.
That's easy. If you don't go,
then you can forget about me
breaking up Momo and Toji.
But you promised!
Hey Kairi,
you forgot this. Uh?!
Look who its is.
What the hell are you doing
showing your face to me, pig!
You're a real piece of work,
tryin' to steal my man away
from me, you chubby bitch!
You're delusional to think
he'd wanna have
anything to do with you!
Now stay away from
my man, you whore!
[SAE]
Ah!
[footsteps]
Uh? Misao. What the hell
was that all about?
She saw...
She saw me with Ryo.
[RYO]
Misao?
[MISAO gasps]
[MISAO]
Ryo!
It's dark out.
Have you been here
with me the entire time?
You're crying.
I know. I'm just
so glad you're okay.
[MISAO sobs] You have
no idea how scared I was.
It's okay. I was scared too.
[MISAO sobs]
[RYO]
I was dreaming a minute ago.
There was an amazing fragrance.
I thought it was flowers,
but now I know it was you.
It was soothing.
That's what you do to me, Misao.
Ryo.
Listen, I love you so much.
And I've been in love
with you for a long time.
Is that true?
I had no idea.
I'm sorry to throw that at
you now, but it's true.
[RYO]
No, no it's ok.
I've loved you from the
first moment I saw you.
[MISAO gasps]
--[door slams]
--[SAE] What are you doing?
[panting]
Sae. What are you doing here?
[SAE] How dare you touch him!
He's my boyfriend!
[RYO]
Get out.
[SAE groans]
[SAE whimpers]
Get out.
[SAE sobs]
Wow. I didn't realize you
had so much drama goin' on.
But hey, at least you got to
tell Ryo how you really felt.
That's good, right?
Did he happen to say if he
felt the same about you?
Yeah, but the thing is,
I'm actually confused now.
[KAIRI]
About Sae?
Well, yeah kinda of.
The idea that Ryo could
slap Sae around like that,
without a moment's hesitation.
And as she was crying and hurt,
he just gave her this
cold-hearted stare.
I never knew that side
of him even existed.
Well, then I guess you never
really knew my brother.
[MISAO sighs]
[KAIRI] It looks like my
brother's charm is wearing off.
[MOMO] Morning!
Were you waiting long?
Not really. Are you free
after school today?
[MOMO]
Sure.
Awesome. You Wanna go
somewhere and hang out?
[MOMO]
Uh?!
[MOMO] He just asked
me out on a date!
[MOMO laughing]
What're you so
happy about?
[MOMO]
Uh?!
What is that?
Are you being serious?
We're doing our
strength tests today.
Uh! That's today?
I totally forgot! Be right back!
Better hurry!
[BOYS chatting]
Whoa! Sumire got hot!
Where'd you get these
pictures from?
Wait. You took these yourself.
Sure did. If you want, I can
make copies for a small fee.
[GORO]
I'll take one of these!
[YUKIO]
I want Kyoko!
[KISHO]
I want 'em all!
[KAIRI]
Hold on guys. Patience.
Let me write these down.
Let's see.
That was one for Kyoko.
[MASAKUZA] I'm totally gonna
put those up in my locker.
[GORO] Hey, what are
we doing in gym today?
[YUKIO]
Basketball, I think.
[BOYS chatting]
[MOMO] I know that thing's
around here somewhere.
--Here it is!
--[pop]
Uh?
Whose is this?
Uh?!
[MOMO] Gross!
Who's taking pictures of me?
Probably some pervert!
Uh.
But why?
[SAE] Why did you choose her
over me, Ryo? Why?
I know you have better taste
than to fall in love with
a freaking school nurse!
I have to have
you for myself!
Please! I'll do anything
you want! Anything!
Next time on Peach Girl:
Imaginary Love Affair