Does it mean what
I think it does?
That you're still in love with
her, after all these years?
Come on. Are you going to
answer me or just stand there?
[KAIRI]
It's true.
[MOMO gasps]
What are you saying?
You looked straight into my eyes
and told me you loved me.
Was that a lie?
[KAIRI]
I'm sorry.
Uh... Is that all you can say?!
Why did you have
to do this, huh?!
Why'd you have to break my
heart? Tell me why! Tell me!
[KAIRI]
I'm so sorry.
You jerk!
[MOMO grunting]
Momo. I love you.
I'll always love you.
[MOMO] What a liar.
He was stringing me along,
the whole time. I'll never
believe anyone ever again!
[MISAO]
Momo.
You left your bag
at my apartment.
Thank you.
So what ever happened
with you yesterday?
You caught me by surprise
when you left so suddenly.
Did you and Kairi have a fight?
He wouldn't tell
me when I asked.
I just hope it doesn't have
anything to do with me
and those pictures
you were looking at.
I wanna be clear with you.
There's nothing between
the two of us.
I used to tutor him,
and that's all.
There's no reason for you
to worry, Momo. I promise.
By the way, what did you wanna
talk to me about yesterday?
It's nothing.
If it's something important,
there's no reason for
you to be embarrassed.
We can go in my office and
talk in private if you want.
[MOMO gasps]
Sorry. I'm in a hurry.
[MOMO]
I know it's not her fault.
But why, of all people, did it
have to be the school nurse?
I mean she's ten
years older than us,
and not even that pretty.
I can't even stand
myself right now.
Did you have another fight?
[MOMO]
Uh?
It's so obvious. You're avoiding
Kairi like the plague.
What was it this time?
Trouble with an ex-girlfriend?
Just forget it.
It was nothing, really.
--[KAIRI]  Momo.
--[MOMO] Uh?
Look, I really need
to talk to you.
Make-up make out sessions
are the best, you know.
[KAKO]
Momo?
[KAKO, RITSUKO, NAMI]
Uh?!
[phone rings]
[MOMO]
I can't forgive him.
No matter how much
he apologizes,
I have to stand my ground.
If he didn't love me, then why
did he let me fall for him?
He should've just left me alone.
I'll swim.
I'll swim until I can't go any
farther. Until I nearly drown.
I'll keep going until
my heart is a void.
A dark pit of nothingness.
Then I won't have to
think about it anymore.
[TOJI]
Here.
Oh, thank you.
Have you seen Sae
around here at all?
No. I try to avoid her.
That's cool.
She's with that guy again.
[MOMO]
Uh?
Wait, do you mean she's with
Kairi's older brother?
Probably. Last time we
spoke was two days ago.
She said she
wanted to break up.
And? What did you say?
[TOJI]
No.
You did? She flirted with
another guy and you forgive her?
She practically betrayed you!
The last thing I'd ever
do is forgive her,
but the reality of the
situation won't change.
We'll stay together
or we'll break up.
Either way we don't want
those pictures made public.
Besides, this was
never about forgiving.
It's about figuring out how
important that person is to you.
And most of all, making sure
your heart's in the right place.
Ha. Sorry. Here I am probably
boring you to tears.
See ya later. Bye.
[MOMO] Making sure your heart
is in the right place.
It's about figuring out how
important that person is to you.
My own feelings.
[MOMO]
Uh?
[MOMO grunts]
Momo!
[MOMO]
Uh! Just go away!
[KAIRI]
I'm sorry!
I know you don't wanna
hear this right now,
but I have to tell you
something! It's important!
[MOMO]
I can't forgive him.
Seeing Kairi right now
only makes me angry.
That's why it's useless to talk.
Go home already!
I'm not coming up
until you're gone!
I'll hold my breath for
five minutes if I have to.
[splash]
Wha... What are you doing?!
Momo!
Have you lost your mind?
You can't swim!
Get out before you drown!
[KAIRI groaning, gasping]
Kairi.
[KAIRI gasping]
Kairi!
[MOMO gasps]
[MOMO panting]
Kairi! Wake up!
[KAIRI]
I'm so sorry.
Will you listen to me now?
[MOMO]
Uh... You jerk.
[KAIRI] I didn't approach
you on a whim, you know.
I was incredibly happy when
I found out you liked me.
I'd wanted that for a long time.
But once I realized that you
were becoming serious with me,
I slowly began to lose
my confidence.
I'm being honest when
I say I love you.
I really felt we a
had a good chance
of having a very long
lasting relationship.
[MOMO gasps]
But some feelings from
the past have resurfaced
that I can't get over.
And now I keep finding myself
dwelling on them constantly.
[MOMO]
Misao.
Why can't you feel
that way for me?
Because, she was the first
girl I'd ever had such strong
feelings for. She was the first
to acknowledge me for who I am,
and not just as
Ryo's kid brother.
[MOMO gasps]
Like I told you before,
every girl I've dated has ended
up being stolen by Ryo.
I got to the point to where I
couldn't stand to see his face,
and for a long while,
I ran away from home.
I wanted to go a place
where I was unknown.
A place that Ryo
could never get to.
Misao was the only person
that could bring me back.
Do you have any idea
what time it is?
What? Do I know you?
I'm Misao. I'll be your private
tutor for the rest of the year.
Huh?
Now it's time to get to work!
I know all about how difficult
a student you've been.
You've gone through eight
different private tutors
over the last three years.
I want you to know that
with me it'll be different.
You'll pass your classes
and have fun doing it.
You sure are--
You'll address me as Miss Aki.
Miss Aki, you run in the same
circles as my brother,
don't you? If I
were to guess,
I'd say you have
the hots for him.
What other reason would
you take this job for?
Everyone knows I'm a pain
in the butt to work with.
I bet you expected someone a
lot cuter than I am, right?
Admit it. You're disappointed
that I'm not as perfect as Ryo.
What're you talking about? Do
you have an identity problem?
Of course I realize you're
different from your brother,
and I, for one, think
that's a good thing.
[KAIRI] That was the first
time anyone had said
such nice things to me.
I was so happy after
that I nearly cried.
Misao had accepted
me for who I was,
and before I knew it,
I was madly in love with her.
I was also glad that she acted
so indifferent with Ryo.
When she came over to tutor me,
I knew she was there
to see me and only me,
and that alone made
me feel good.
But I was wrong.
I finally realized what
Misao's true feelings were
when I tagged along
on a trip one summer.
[RYO] I still don't know
what you're doing here.
[MISAO]
What's the big deal?
He's just one more
person in the group.
[FRIEND A] Hey guys! Come on,
let's take some pictures.
[KAIRI] Thanks for standing
up for me back there.
[MISAO]
Don't worry about it.
What matters is we're here,
so let's have fun, okay?
Pretty necklace.
[MISAO]
Huh?
I mean, I don't think
I've ever seen you
wearing that one before.
Did you just get it?
It really brings out your eyes
and goes great with the
dress you're wearing.
Oh, thank you.
[FRIEND A] Let me get a picture
of you two. Say cheese!
[WOMAN] Careful!
Those rocks are slippery!
Hey, Misao! I'm over here!
[MISAO]
Okay!
[MISAO yelps]
[MISAO panting]
Misao! Are you okay?
Hey. The necklace
looks nice on you.
I guess I did pick
out the perfect one.
[KAIRI]
That's when it dawned on me.
Misao wasn't being cold to Ryo.
She would get nervous around him
because she liked him so much.
That night she told me she
would no longer be my tutor.
I felt like a dagger had
been thrust into my chest.
I'd been betrayed once again.
I spent that night
wandering aimlessly
around the island during
a typhoon. A surfer found me,
and let me stay at his place
until the storm was gone.
I returned four days later.
I wonder if I'd die
if I went out there.
[PEOPLE murumuring]
[PEOPLE talking]
You could've died out there!
[MISAO crying]
[KAIRI] During the four
days I was gone,
Misao had searched
for me in the typhoon.
She ignored everyone's warnings
and searched on her own,
risking her life to save mine.
If Kairi turns up there
before I get back,
promise me you won't
get mad at him.
And don't tell him I've been out
in the typhoon looking for him.
He's a good kid and I know he'll
just end up worrying about it.
And that had a huge
effect on me.
The fact that there was
no one else in the world
that cared for me
the way she did.
At that point, I didn't care
who it was that Misao loved.
[MOMO]
Kairi.
Kiss me.
[KAIRI]
Uh?
Kiss me.
Do you love me still?
[KAIRI]
Mm-hm.
But, you... But you love
Misao more, don't you?
Yeah.
[MOMO]
That sucks.
What should I do about this?
[RYO] What's most
important is what you want.
[MOMO]
That's right.
It's useless to force Kairi
to choose right now.
He has to decide on what
he wants on his own,
and it's up to me to
decide what I want.
How do I feel about Kairi
right this second?
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
[MOMO]
Kairi!
Aren't you forgetting
something?
What happened to
my kiss goodbye?
I can't do that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
A goodbye kiss wasn't exactly
the right way to put it.
How about we have a
make-up kiss instead?
Or at least, we could have
a let's-just-get-along kiss.
[KAIRI]
Uh?
I'd really like it if we
were friends again.
I admit, I was shocked
and really angry
when I found out
that you lied to me.
But now I understand where
all this is coming from.
Honestly, it's all right
with me if you're still
in love with her. I just
wanna be near you.
[MOMO]
Uh?!
We're through.
[MOMO] Why? You don't hate me,
do you? I don't understand.
I'll tell you why.
All guys have urges. Mixing love
into that can be dangerous.
Every time we'd see each
other, I'd wanna kiss you.
All right. I'm okay
with that, really.
Are you sure about that?
What if I were to take you
in my arms, or kiss you,
or stare into your eyes,
but I'm thinking of Misao
the entire time?
Wouldn't that bother you?
The last thing I'd wanna do is
hurt you, and that's exactly
what I would be doing.
That's why we should break up.
Well I don't agree with you.
If we break up I'll cry,
and I won't stop crying
until we get back together.
I don't want that. I'm saying
I'm okay with this, Kairi.
So why can't things just
stay the way they are?
If we keep seeing each other,
I guarantee you'll cry
more than if we broke up.
Because I can't stop
loving Misao. I just can't.
Uh?
Sorry.
Kairi!
Kairi.
[TOJI]
Momo.
Hey, what's goin' on?
Oh nothing. I'm just on my home.
It's wet.
[TOJI]
Momo! You forgot this.
Uh. Thanks Toji.
Did something happen
between you and Kairi?
No no. Everything's fine.
It just seems like
you've been crying.
[gasps] Oh come on.
I'm not crying.
I'm here to listen.
[MOMO whimpers]
[KAIRI]
Uh?!
Mind giving me a hand
bringin' that up here?
[KAIRI]
Here. Just like you asked.
Now Take it before I
drop it on your foot!
[KAIRI]
Uh!
[KAIRI groans]
[KAIRI whimpers]
You jerk! Just What the
hell was that all about?!
I brought your stupid dictionary
up out of the kindness
of my own heart,
and what do I get for it?
I gave Momo up without
a fight because of you.
[KAIRI gasps]
[MOMO] How pitiful.
Was that all we were about?
Just saying the words
without meaning them?
He made me love him so much.
How can he turn around
and be so cruel?
[TOJI]
Momo.
[MOMO]
Uh?
What's goin' on?
[MOMO laughs] I'm sorry.
I haven't been myself lately.
[MOMO] Oh. Why did I tell
Toji all about our breakup?
It's so embarrassing!
So, did ya need to talk to me?
Uh, Toji? Uh!
I can't take it.
I've held myself back up to now,
but not any longer.
I don't care what anyone says.
I can't let him have you.
Momo. Come back to me.
Let's start over.
[MOMO]
Start over?
[MOMO] Start over with Toji?
Is that possible?
[MOMO]
Uh!
Sorry. Look, Toji.
I can't start over
with you, I just can't.
Why not? Do you still
have feelings for Kairi?
Didn't you tell me yesterday
that he's in love
with the nurse? If that's true,
then come back to me.
That's easier said
than done, Toji.
In case you forgot already,
you're the one who dumped me
so you could start dating Sae.
And now all of a sudden
you want me back?
Do you have even
the slightest idea
of how I felt when
you dumped me?
You really did hurt me, Toji.
It was Kairi who
eased that hurt,
and helped me through
that awful time.
It was because of him that I
was able to get over you.
You have to understand Toji.
I love Kairi and...
and he means the world to me.
Then go to him.
Just tell him how you truly
feel. He'll understand.
[MOMO]
Uh?
Kairi would be a fool to
let a catch like you go.
[MOMO]
Did he do that on purpose?
Because I was so depressed?
Thanks Toji.
[MOMO]
Kairi.
[KAIRI]
Huh?
We need to talk.
[MOMO] Listen, about yesterday,
about the whole breakup thing.
[KAIRI sighs]
Well, uh... It's okay.
[KAIRI]
Uh?!
[KAIRI] Thanks for
being so understanding.
And I'm truly sorry
that this happened.
I know it's a cliché,
but you'll find someone out
there that's perfect for you.
Someone who will cherish
you for who you are. Bye.
Kairi.
I can't flip a switch
and stop loving you.
[KAIRI]
Uh?
I love you so much.
You're the most precious
thing I have,
and I can't live without you,
and that's why I don't
wanna break up.
[KAIRI]
Uh!
Listen, Momo, you're
not making any sense.
That's because you're the
one who wanted to break up.
So fine. Everything that's
happened up to now is done.
Finished.
This time I'll be the
one who chases you.
I'll chase you, and chase you,
and I won't stop until you
love me more than Misao.
[KAIRI exhales]
That won't work! I'm telling
you if you do that,
in the end you'll only end
up hurting yourself, Momo.
[KAIRI]
Uh?!
Listen. All you wanna do is
make things easy on yourself.
You say you don't
wanna hurt me,
but in reality you're just
afraid of getting involved
in a committed relationship
with someone.
You're afraid of being rejected.
And that's why you can't step up
and declare your love for Misao!
Don't you realize that no
one will ever love you
if you keep yourself
closed off like this?
You're just pushing people away.
Is that what you really want?
I'm not gonna let
you get away, Kairi.
I don't care what it takes.
I will get you back.
Oh man.
I gotta say,
I am blown away by how
passionate you are about this.
But if you do what
you say you will,
I won't be able
to contain myself.
That's fine. You can have
me any way you like,
as long as I get a fair
second chance with you.
So do we have a deal?
[KAIRI laughs]
I do love you, Momo. I do!
[MOMO]
Hm.
But I'm still second?
Uh?! For now.
[MOMO]
Second best for now.
Someday soon, I'll be first
in your heart, Kairi.
[SAE] Ryo! I've done a lot
of thinking about this.
You and I need to start
dating, like, yesterday.
I know you probably
wanna play the field more,
but I can't help it.
I love you Ryo!
Next time on Peach Girl:
Direct Line to Pure Love