It's funny how you wake up each day
and never really know if it will be
one that will change your life forever.
But that's what this day was.
The day I left the city to spend a
week in the house where my mother grew up.
A day I'll never forget.
So many years have passed.
Almost there. Feeling all right?
I'm okay.
I left my childhood.
In a garden green.
Come in the garden.
And look at the trees.
I used to play there when I was a child.
Oh, Hara. How many times have I told her?
Wait here. All right? I won't be a minute.
Okay.
Hara! Your car's blocking the driveway again.
So many years have passed.
The dew is still on the roses.
I left my childhood.
In a garden green.
Shawn? Where are you?
Shawn?
I'm here, Aunt Jessica.
Come meet Hara!
Supper is done and night has come.
Let's have tea together near the fireplace.
Nice try.
My house, my home Is so small, so pretty.
My mom, my dad We are family.
Joy everywhere.
Hey, back off!
Hey! Go get your own!
Arrietty!
What?
You went outside again, didn't you?
How many times have I... What happened to your room?
It's my own little garden.
If you ask me it looks more like your own little jungle.
Hmm.
Is that a bay leaf?
Where did you get that?
Oh!
I wanted to wait and give it
to you on your birthday, but...
Happy birthday!
This will last me all year.
But the bay tree is so far away.
If a bean saw you it would...
Beans don't scare me.
The beans should scare you. That's what worries me.
The world is a dangerous place for a Borrower.
Your Aunt Eggletina wasn't scared either and she...
Was eaten by a toad. I know, I know.
If you don't like your gift I can put it in my room.
No, no, I should keep it.
I have just the recipe for these.
I'll have your father borrow some sugar.
Oh, you don't have to.
Because tonight I'll borrow some for you.
What?
Don't tell me you forgot!
Tonight's my first borrowing!
Look, Papa's home.
Papa. Papa, I made it all the way to the bay tree today.
Mmm-hmm.
And I used the leaves over my head just like you said.
And I didn't even get seen by the cat.
Mmm.
So, what I'm trying to say,
if there was any doubt...
There's a new bean in the house.
What?
I know. I saw him.
Arrietty, I told you to be...
Yes, Mama, I was careful and he didn't see me.
And he's much smaller than other beans.
Papa, you just have to let me come borrowing tonight.
We know nothing about this new bean.
But you promised this would be my night.
And I've seen him.
Papa, please, I am telling you, he's just a child.
And the children are more vicious than the grownups.
I'll be fine.
Well, the young beans do go to bed early.
Oh, thank you, Papa!
Pod!
The boy is very sickly and weak. She'll be fine.
But...
Oh, and don't worry, Mother. I'll get Papa back safely.
Arrietty will be turning 14 soon.
She'll need to know how to take care of herself out there.
Without our help.
Sometimes I worry that we are the only Borrowers left.
What'll become of us?
Remember what the doctor said, Shawn.
Your heart needs rest. No excitement.
Is that clear, Hara?
Yes, ma'am, I'll see to it.
Whatever you need, Shawn, you ask Hara,
and she'll get it for you, all right?
Yes, Aunt Jessica.
Make him feel at home, Hara.
Yes, ma'am.
Hmm.
We'll start by keeping the bugs out.
Mmm-hmm.
Don't you think you should wear
something a little darker and longer?
No, I think this one's perfect.
Mmm-hmm.
So, I need you to get me some tissue paper and some sugar.
Oh, and promise, dear husband,
you won't let our daughter get
eaten or squashed like a bug.
Oh, please God. Please help them.
Don't worry about me. Everything's fine.
Hmm.
Okay, bye, Mom. I love you.
Oh, goodbye. Love you, too. Stay close to your father.
I will.
Do I get one of those?
Nope? Okay.
Wow.
Arrietty!
Hmm?
Ha!
Oh!
Did you see that?
That's my girl.
Don't look down.
One step at a time.
All right. You need to hold this for me.
Okay.
Arrietty, make sure you hold on tight.
Mmm-hmm.
Arrietty!
Let's go.
Right.
Wow.
It's so big.
Papa, what is this place?
This is where beans store all their food.
The sugar is over there.
When you get down there, wait for me.
Yeah!
Papa, you are great!
Yay!
Huh? Oh.
There. That wasn't so hard.
Where to now?
Tissue paper. Then home.
Wow.
Papa, look what I found.
Looks like someone got their first borrowing.
Hmm.
Careful with it, it's sharp.
Okay.
Papa, borrowing is so much fun!
Hmm.
Look down there.
Mmm?
Filthy rats. You want to stay away from those things.
I'm not afraid.
I will cut them down to size with my sword.
Sometimes it's best not to go looking for danger.
What is this place?
I've heard human beans call it a dollhouse.
Dolls are toys for beans.
And we are not toys.
These things are not for borrowing.
Oh, but it's so perfect for us.
Don't you think Mother would
absolutely love that dresser over there?
If anything went missing, they'd know right away.
Borrowers take only what they need.
Oh.
Don't be afraid, okay?
Hey.
I know it was you in the garden. I knew I saw you.
My mother used to tell me stories
about the little people who lived under the floors.
Was it you?
Was it?
Please don't go.
I'm sorry. I should have told you.
He might have seen me out in the garden today.
We all make mistakes.
So we'll just have to be extra careful now.
Best not to tell your mother about this.
You know how she worries.
Right.
I'm very proud of you.
A lesser Borrower would've panicked and run away.
Mmm.
Oh.
Well, we're home.
Safe and sound.
Mmm-hmm.
Is everything okay?
Not quite the adventure we'd hoped for.
This old light gave out halfway to the kitchen.
No.
Mmm.
Well, I'm afraid we had to give up on the sugar.
That's okay. I'm just happy you made it home.
It wasn't a total loss.
Arrietty, why don't you show
your mother your first borrowing?
What a beautiful pin.
Hmm.
Okay. Off to bed.
Night, Mama, Papa.
She looks so worn-out.
Should I make us some tea?
Mmm-hmm.
Shawn, come inside. You'll catch your death of cold.
What did you say? Why would he do that?
I think he was just being nice.
It's the same cube of sugar I
dropped in his room last night.
Pod,
what does she mean, she dropped it?
Do not touch it. Do you understand me?
It's a trap.
I just know it. They're going to trap us like cockroaches.
Homily, let's try not to get hysterical, okay?
Don't tell me to not get hysterical!
We'll probably have to move now.
Goodbye, old table.
We had so many fun times together.
Let's not say goodbye to anything just yet.
Eat your soup before it gets cold.
I told you that young bean would be trouble!
But no one ever listens to me.
Thank you, Arrietty.
Smart girl, doing this when the sun came out.
Or maybe I have a smart mama who taught me.
You're a good girl.
If you've got this, I think I'll go lie down a bit.
Okay.
Is that you from last night?
No, wait. Don't go.
I'm sorry if I frightened you.
Please leave us alone.
We don't need your help.
But can I please just talk to you?
No! Human beans are dangerous.
Whenever we're seen, we have to move. My parents said so.
So you have a family. That must be nice.
You don't have a family?
Yeah, I have one.
But they sent me here to get
the care and attention I need.
Because they're both very busy with their work.
Sorry to hear that.
Anyway, my name is Shawn. What's your name?
Hmm?
What do they call you?
Not that it's any of your business, but it's Arrietty.
Arrietty. Arrietty.
That's a beautiful name.
Maybe we could be friends?
Could you at least come out so I can see you?
I want to make sure I'm not dreaming.
Hmm?
Mmm-mmm! Mmm-mmm!
I won't hurt you, I promise.
Help me! Help me!
Ow!
Ah! Whoa!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What in the world? A crow!
Oh! Attack! Ow!
You get out right now!
What got into that bird?
Don't think I've ever seen one behave like that.
Maybe it's nesting season or something.
I don't know. Looks me to like it was after something.
Oh, look at the holes in the screen.
Which I'll have to replace, of course.
Oh, my goodness. Are you all right?
Your aunt said for you not to get too excited!
Should I get your medicine?
No, that's okay, Miss Hara.
I'm actually feeling pretty good.
Mmm-hmm.
Nesting season, huh?
Well, Shawn, you have a nice, long rest now.
Phew.
Papa!
I hear you visited the young bean.
I'm sorry.
I went to ask him to leave us alone.
But I really don't think he intends to hurt us.
Many Borrowers have lost their lives thinking the same.
It must never happen again.
Do you understand me?
Yeah.
We'd better start looking for a new home.
Huh?
The boy knows that we're here.
Are we safe?
Delivery. Package for you, ma'am.
Thanks for the drink, Hara. It's pretty hot today.
Do you happen to know of any good pest control companies?
Pest problem, huh?
Here's one. "Squeaky Klean Pest Extermination ."
1 -800... Oh, hang on.
So you got yourself a mouse problem?
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
Maybe it's mice, maybe it's little tiny people.
Huh?
Strange things have been happening here and I know why.
That's just the craziest thing I've ever heard.
I mean, when Hara told me, I just couldn't believe it.
Why on earth would a crow try to fly into your room?
Were you frightened?
No, I wasn't scared. Hara came and chased it away.
And it's a good thing I came in when I did.
That bird had huge wings and claws...
Let's not relive the excitement, Hara,
considering Shawn came here for a little peace
and quiet and tranquility before his operation.
Yes, ma'am. Forgive me.
I'm sorry, Hara. I don't mean to be short with you.
But why his mother chose this time to
go away on business is just beyond...
It must be terribly hard for you
without your mother here to look after you.
Hmm. You know, not so much lately.
I suppose the divorce couldn't be helped,
but honestly, why couldn't she
be here when her son needs her so?
It's the last thing his poor heart needs.
Aunt Jessica, I was noticing
that miniature house in my room.
And the detail's amazing.
Oh, you mean the dollhouse.
That beautiful little house belonged to your mother.
She had to leave it here when
she moved away to go to college.
It was Mother's?
Your grandfather had it specially made
because he was hoping it would be
a lovely home for the little people.
What?
That's right. Little people who lived in the walls.
He was quite obsessed with them.
People laughed, of course, and called him mad.
But your mother, she believed him.
They worked on that house together for hours.
And he told her they would come,
but of course, they never did.
Tell me, Shawn, have you ever seen
any tiny little people in your room?
Mmm...
Mmm-mmm. Can't say that I have.
I think it's why your mother
doesn't like to come here anymore.
Too many memories of wishes that never came true.
Can we look inside it?
Yes!
You know, I haven't looked inside it in quite a long time.
Hara, could you be a dear and turn off the lights?
Ma'am.
So many years have passed.
This is the living room.
Your grandfather had all of this handmade
by a real furniture maker in England.
Isn't that just insane?
Look at the attention to detail.
They really were preparing it for someone to live in.
And just in case you don't believe
what I'm saying is absolutely true,
have a look at that room right there.
Come in the garden.
Wow, what a kitchen!
And look at the trees.
Everything in it a miniature of the real thing.
That oven actually works. You could bake real cookies.
Some really little cookies.
What a pity their dream never came true.
It really would've made a lovely home.
Settled down there long ago.
So many years have passed.
The dew is still on the roses.
I left my childhood.
In a garden green.
Come in the garden.
And sit on the grass.
I used to sit there when I was a child
Ivy and moss.
Little daisies.
Covered the lane long ago.
You know, Mother, we've had these same pictures for years.
Wouldn't you like some new ones?
Well, Arrietty, I like those pictures.
And I've always dreamed I'd see the real ocean someday.
Besides, there's no point in changing them now.
I wonder what's taking Papa so long.
Why is my first thought always
that he got eaten by the cat?
What's wrong with me?
There he is!
Does he look eaten?
Hey, Papa, how was it out there?
Oh.
I slipped and twisted my leg.
I'm lucky that Spiller here found me.
Well, what is going on down...
Pod, you're hurt!
It was the cat, wasn't it? See, I'm not crazy.
Get up here!
Does it hurt, Papa?
It's just a sprain. Go calm your mother.
I'll get some cold water. I'll be right back.
Everyone relax!
Here's a towel. Dry yourself.
Who's that?
I wonder if he has news about any of the other Borrowers.
Okay, I leave now.
Can't you at least stay and have some tea?
Arrietty, I'll take care of your father.
Why don't you see if Spiller would like a cup of tea?
Won't you please stay, Spiller?
I've never met another Borrower before.
Hmm.
We can't thank you enough for your help.
Tell us, have you seen other Borrowers?
We're all alone here
and we're starting to believe
we're the only ones left. Are we?
This many.
Oh! Then cousin Lupy could still be alive.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, that's a bow, isn't it? Can I see it?
You use this for your borrowing?
Give that back, Arrietty,
before you shoot someone's eye out.
Okay. Go now.
Oh, but couldn't you stay a little bit longer?
I'll cook dinner.
Already got this.
A cricket leg!
Want some?
Very fresh.
No, thanks.
Bye.
Thank you, my friend.
I'll go with him. To see him out.
What were you doing out there in that storm?
I was looking for a safe route for our journey.
And now I know which route not to take.
Oh, Pod.
Spiller knows of more Borrowers a few days journey away.
There's a small river past the forest.
He's offered to take us on it.
Mmm. That's great.
I'm sure we'll find a new place in no time.
And I'm sure it will almost be as nice as this.
I'm really glad I met you, Spiller.
Or that I met anyone.
Hey, maybe next time you could
bring your whole family with you.
No family. Only Spiller.
Oh.
Well, we... We could be a family.
And when you come back you could stay for a family dinner.
Hara?
Arrietty, your stitches need to be closer together.
You'll have to start over.
Aw!
Why do we need such a big bag anyway?
Are we putting the whole house in here?
Hmm.
I think I'm gonna go check on Papa.
Papa, can I come in?
Mmm-hmm.
How's your leg?
Ah, well, better than that cricket's.
I'm serious.
Papa, why do we have to move?
Once a Borrower has been seen, the
beans' curiosity can't be stopped.
Well, isn't it possible that
not every human bean is dangerous?
Arrietty, before you were born
there were two other families
who were living in this house.
One family went missing, they just disappeared.
The other one moved away.
They were seen by humans.
And so, we have to do whatever it takes to survive.
But, Papa...
Oh! Oh, no!
Huh?
Pod, what is it? An earthquake?
Mother!
It won't open!
Frame is buckled!
The wall!
Homily!
Homily, are you all right?
Pod, remember how I always said I wanted a new kitchen?
Huh?
Huh, more bills.
Oh.
Hmm.
Remember, take only the things we need.
Mmm-hmm.
We can't possibly carry all of this.
And, Homily, don't take anything from the dollhouse.
I'm gonna go make sure that it's safe.
You stay with your mother.
Okay.
So you finally came.
Did you like your new kitchen?
Well, our house looks like a train wreck.
But it doesn't matter. Because I came to tell you goodbye.
Can I turn around?
Mmm-hmm.
You're beautiful.
My papa said we have to move now.
We've been seen, and.
Borrowers aren't supposed to be seen.
What are Borrowers?
My mother, father, and I are all Borrowers.
We borrow things that beans won't miss if they are gone.
Just little things, soap, cookies, and sugar.
All things that we need to survive.
Even my great-grandfather was a Borrower.
I think my grandfather saw one of you once.
Hmm. It's possible.
And it's my fault that you're leaving.
Niya! Niya!
Don't be like that. Be nice to her.
So, in my aunt's house,
how many other Borrowers are
there who are living with you?
It's just my father and my mother and me.
What about in other houses?
I'm sure there are some.
But I've only met one other so far.
Oh.
You must be afraid you'll be the
only ones of your kind who are left.
What?
Every year there's fewer and fewer of you, right?
Aren't you scared that soon you'll all be gone?
What a horrible thing to say!
I know that there's more of us because Spiller said so!
Who's Spiller?
He's one of us. He lives out in the forest,
and he said that there are hundreds more of us.
That might be true.
But, you know, none of us can live forever, can we?
We all have to die sometime.
Why would you say something like that?
Because it's true.
I guess so.
Believe me, I know what I'm talking about.
Sometimes things happen to us
that are just beyond our control.
And when these things happen, there's
really nothing you can do about it.
You just accept it and prepare for the worst.
I wish it wasn't that way.
But you can't live a life
that's built on nothing but wishes.
It isn't practical.
Sometimes you just have to accept the hand of fate.
Oh, no, you don't.
Sometimes you have to stand up and fight
for the things that are worth fighting for.
You have to survive. That's what my papa says.
And so we're leaving even though it's dangerous.
And we are going to survive.
We are Borrowers and we'll make do. We always have.
As long as we have each other
to live for, we'll keep on living.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to upset you.
I'm actually the one who's going to die.
What?
There's something wrong with my heart.
They're gonna operate next week, but
it probably won't help.
That's terrible.
I've always been sick and I've
had someone looking after me.
And that's why when I saw you,
I just wanted to find a way to protect you.
But I guess I messed up.
I made it worse. I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry to hear about your heart.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Now what on earth is this doing here?
Hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
Now how did you get in there?
There you are!
Mom!
What? What's wrong?
My mother, I think she's in danger.
No!
Give me that, you little thief!
Now we'll see who they call crazy.
And I bet there's more of you, aren't there, hmm?
Wait, no! Wait, wait! Wait!
I have to go help her.
But...
Oh, no! Help! No, no, please! Help!
Pod! Arrietty!
Let me out of here!
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Let me out of here!
Arrietty! Help!
Ah! Watch it!
Hmm. Let's see.
Now to find the others.
Let me out! No! No!
Huh?
Something terrible has happened.
Squeaky Klean.
Yes, hello.
I'm calling from 833 Elm Lane.
Could you get out here right away?
I have a very unique pest problem.
Is it mice?
Oh, much worse than mice.
Do you want them exterminated?
No, I need you to trap them.
Shawn! Shawn! Shawn!
Shawn! Shawn!
Arrietty!
My mother is missing.
Someone took the roof off! I think a human bean got her.
Oh, Mama.
We will find her.
What?
Someone's locked us in.
There's a room next door. Hold on tight.
Oh!
One step at a time.
Right.
It's stuck!
Wait.
I can get us in.
Oh, no, no!
Keep going.
What do you mean you're lost?
How can you possibly be lost?
It's the only road!
Is it before the bridge?
What bridge? There's no bridge!
Hara must have found it and opened it.
This is what I was afraid of.
Mother's been taken.
Oh!
Are you okay?
Be careful. Shawn, please.
Where are those idiots?
Huh?
Mother! Where are you?
...be wise. They're supposed to catch pests.
But... How did you...
Hara.
Could I have some warm milk?
Okay! Wait just a minute.
Thank you, Hara.
Mmm.
I'm a little hungry. Are there any cookies?
Cookies? Now he wants cookies.
Mother!
Arrietty!
Huh?
Over here!
Arrietty! Here I am! Here I am!
Oh, Mother!
Oh, Arrietty.
Oh, good. There they are.
They finally found the road. The only road.
Another bean!
It's okay, Mother. He's a friend.
Mmm-hmm. Ma'am, we'd like to take a look around.
See what we see.
Yes, of course.
Mmm-hmm.
Squeaky Klean Exterminators?
Hara? Hara!
Oh!
What's going on here?
It's finally happened.
I found the little people.
Little people?
Mmm-hmm.
Yes! And what little robbers they are.
I wouldn't have believed it either
unless I'd seen it with my own eyes. It's remarkable!
It's the eighth wonder of the world.
And they're so teeny!
And they have a whole house full of things they've stolen.
Are you sure you didn't find the sherry again?
All these years you thought I was losing things.
But it wasn't me. It was them!
You didn't mention little people
to the exterminators, did you?
No. I didn't want to scare them off.
Because I'm sure the house is just full of them.
You'll see when I show you.
This is their nest.
Nest?
Mmm-hmm.
Looks like a pile of old junk to me.
W-What?
It was here! It was here!
Where's that little teapot?
Okay, Hara, I'm sending the exterminators away.
No! No, no! Wait just a minute.
Oh. Oh! I'll clean that up later.
Oh, please!
Hello, Shawn. Can we come in for a minute?
It's open.
You'll see. Those little thieves stole the tiny kitchen.
I don't know how they did it, but the whole thing is gone.
Huh?
Not gone.
Perhaps you need a little time off, Hara.
Yeah. Hmm!
Wait! Wait! I can prove it!
I've got one of them in a jar!
Poor Hara. I think she's finally gone bonkers.
Do I smell fresh herbs?
Mmm!
Someone's been making tea.
It's just as my father told us.
There really are little people living here.
Yes, there are.
Your mother really should be here to see this.
She waited so long for some proof of them.
But they're not thieves like Hara said.
They're just Borrowers.
What?
I mean, they must be very frightened.
I just hope they're still here.
I hope so, too.
Excuse me. Ma'am!
Where would you like us to start looking?
Oh, are you all right?
Where did she go?
Who took my lady?
There are little people! There are!
Easy, easy.
And, no, I'm not losing my mind!
If I collapse, leave me behind.
With my tea kettle.
You're doing great. It's just a
little further until we break for food.
Can't we just head back?
We can live with the rats in the compost heap.
Shh!
Oh!
Oh, no!
Let's hurry.
I can't do it.
Arrietty, you really should eat something.
We're gonna be walking at least until morning.
What?
I'm so sorry.
I feel like maybe it's all my fault that
we had to leave such a wonderful house.
That's in the past.
We'll make another wonderful
house, the three of us, together.
I'm going outside for a bit.
Arrietty, don't go too far.
Mmm-hmm.
Niya.
Huh.
Just a little further.
Ah! Spiller!
That's the last of it.
Come on, we should keep moving.
Okay.
Mother, are you all right?
Arrietty!
Shawn.
Arrietty.
We have to leave.
But Spiller says there's more of us not too far from here.
A two-day's journey, at most.
He thinks it might be my mother's family.
You won't be the last of your kind.
But how did you find me?
Niya here showed me the way.
Thank you, Niya. Take care of him.
I brought you something.
Now think of it as a gift from one friend to another.
Thank you, Shawn.
Um, I have to go.
When is your operation?
Tomorrow. But I'm not scared.
Because someone taught me how to be brave.
So you'll remember me.
Oh.
How can I forget you?
You protected me after all.
Arrietty.
I hope you have a happy life.
Goodbye, Shawn.
Arrietty, my heart is strong now because you're in it.
And you always will be.
Forever.
I never saw her again.
But the following summer I returned
and was happy to hear the
people in the house down the road
talking about how many things in their home had gone
missing.
I'm 14 years old, I am pretty.
I'm a teeny tiny girl, a little lady.
I live under the kitchen floor.
Right here, not so far from you.
Sometimes I feel happy, sometimes I feel blue.
In my dreams, oh, I wish I could.
Feel my hair blowing in the wind.
See the sky and the summer rain.
Pick a flower from the garden for you.
Now I know there's another world.
Butterflies floating in the air.
There is someone out there for me.
Walking down, picket fence.
Run my hands along the edge.
And music plays in my head.
Hear the song before I go to bed.
When stars are bright outside my window.
Wake up to tree boughs filled up with snow.
And I remember Oh, I remember
I remember my summer with you.
Cherry popsicles, sand in my toes.
Rolled down windows Hold my hand, hold me close.
Pick up your phone Wanna hear your voice again.
Like a fresh air, like a windblown hair
I like you, I don't care.
Why did it have to end?
Summer love with my best friend
I'd fly to you all the way across the states
I'd fly to you hear me, the winter day.
Oh, I'd follow the sun and come right to your door.
I remember my summer with you.
Cherry popsicles, sand in my toes.
Rolled down windows Hold my hand, hold me close.
Pick up your phone wanna hear your voice again.
Like a fresh air, like a windblown hair
I like you, I don't care.
Why did it have to end?
Summer love with my best friend.
I will miss you in summer again when.