[KASUMI'S MOTHER]
What's this?
[KASUMI'S FATHER]
I love you so much.
Will you marry me?
[church bell ringing]
[KASUMI laughing[
[KASUMI]
Hey! Wait!
[laughs] Butterfly!
Are you serious about this?
Yeah.
My colleague's death
was rather unexpected.
And the poor boy desperately
needs a place to call home.
I know it'll make things
things more difficult for you,
but please.
[KASUMI]
Daddy! Mommy!
Look! Look!
[KASUMI laughing]
[KASUMI'S MOTHER]
All right.
Let's give that poor
child a good home.
I think Kasumi will be
overjoyed to have a new brother.
So tell me, what's his name?
Ren?
[KASUMI'S FATHER]
Yes, that's right,
and he's going to be
part of our family,
so be sure to treat him well.
Go ahead, darling.
Say hello to him.
Hello, I'm Kasumi.
[KASUMI yelps]
[KASUMI'S MOTHER gasps]
Hey! That hurt!
What'd you do that for?
Big meanie!
[KASUMI'S MOTHER]
Stop it, now! Both of you!
[KASUMI]
But he should apologize to me!
[MERCURIUS]
Ja.
For you, this is how
our twisted story began.
[MERCURIUS] And now, beloved
factor of self‐destruction.
I will share with you
the requisite conditions
to be the star of the show.
[MERCURIUS] One of
God's featured playthings.
[MERCURIUS]
Every man has his own path
that fate leads him down.
For example, there are those
hunters who are destined
to always have their
favorite quarry stolen out
from under them.
And others, forever unable
to escape from the depths
of their own soulless husk.
And thus,
they desperately grab
at the legs of others,
only pulling them
to their deaths.
Like a drowning man,
flailing and sputtering for air.
[MERCURIUS]
I'm only describing the two
with whom you've interacted.
But they have been quite
entertaining in their own way.
As Shakespeare once said,
"All the world's a stage,
and all the men and women
merely players."
In other words‐‐
Shut up!
Who the hell are you?
You keep going off on all this
crap I never asked about!
I don't give a damn
about your moody poetry!
[MERCURIUS] I suppose
the question you want answered
is why you are still alive.
But that's a foolish
question for you to ask.
You should already be
well aware of the answer.
As long as you feel
that sense of déjà vu,
death will never
be able to claim you.
And as impossible as
it sounds, it's true.
You cannot die.
Because I won't let you perish
before your work is done.
[SHIROU]
You what?
[MERCURIUS]
I suppose I should start from
the beginning.
When you were a young boy,
a seemingly minor change
occurred in your life that would
set your course.
It began with the arrival of
your new neighbor, Ren Fujii.
What did you think of him
that first time?
[SHIROU]
Nothing.
He just seemed kinda gloomy.
[MERCURIUS]
Indeed, but was that all you
thought about him, nothing more?
If so, then why
did you build a
friendship with him
in the first place?
One that has lasted
to this very day.
[REN whimpering]
[chuckling]
[KASUMI'S FATHER gags]
[MERCURIUS]
You remember.
That sensation you
first felt that day,
at that precise moment.
That twinge at the
back of your mind.
[SHIROU]
It felt like I'd done it before.
[MERCURIUS]
Yes.
That was the moment when
your déjà vu first began.
[MERCURIUS]
The father in this sordid tale
didn't have what most might
call an average background.
His role was to cultivate a
subject of vital importance
in a project I'd
first envisioned
during the height of
the Second World War.
He also set about
the business
of incorporating another
special bloodline, as well.
"Eugenics" is what they call it.
Put simply, both of your
childhood friends were born
as a result of
decades of planning
and genetic coordination.
Ironic, is it not?
You, the greatest
rule‐breaker of them all,
were actually the most
normal among your friends.
Just your luck, eh?
If you had never been
involved with them,
you would have been able
to die like any other human.
What the hell
are you getting at?
Are you trying to make me
believe killing that old bastard
wasn't even my decision?
Well, that is the truth.
You were never intended
to be a part of this plan.
So the question remains thus:
why did you become the
murderer, a central character
in our macabre play?
Or perhaps I should
put it another way.
Who was it that stood to gain
the most from the death
of the cruel father?
[MERCURIUS]
If Ren had spoken up about
what was happening to him,
Kasumi would have
been devastated.
Thus, when he decided
to suffer in silence,
his feelings were genuine.
But all things have
front and back sides.
His wish to destroy his false,
everyday life was also genuine.
However, you were
able to take its place.
To both rescue it
and destroy it.
Just as my dear friend
is to me...
You, the manifestation
of the urge for ruination,
the self‐destruction factor.
That is the role you must play.
I will not allow you to die
as long as you are useful to me,
and as long as you don't
overextend your déjà vu.
Show me the unforeseen
conclusion I've longed for.
That is the reason I've gifted
you with such incredible
power and uncanny luck.
[SHIROU laughing]
Damn.
You really think I'm gonna
believe that your pompous ass
is God?
And me and everybody
else are just toys
for you to play with?
You can take that‐‐
and shove it up your ass!
I believe you're that much
of a dick, but Ren isn't!
His friendship with you is
both true and important.
And you can be certain the
feelings I have for my friend
and counterpart are exactly
the same as the ones
my son holds for you.
Like the fleeting thought
of falling from a high place,
or lacerating oneself
whilst handling a blade.
No matter how hard we try,
we always build a
destructive relationship.
As you know,
from the moment you
picked up that blade,
you brought his
normal life to an end.
[MERCURIUS]
Which brings us here.
I am hoping that you choose
to disrupt things once again.
I'm counting on it.
[REA gasps]
[REA]
Riza?
[RUSALKA]
That surge.
Came from the hospital's
direction, I think!
[REA gasps]
Easy, girl. Don't push
yourself too hard!
I'm sure it must be taking
its toll on your poor body.
Each time a swastika opens up,
you feel pains in
your stomach, right?
It's almost as if
you were pregnant.
"There's no way I could be
carrying a child inside me.
I've never even had
sexual intercourse.
I'm a virgin as
pure as the snow."
Does that sound about right?
[REA whimpers]
I thought you would like to
know, Riza has passed away.
How's that make you feel?
The rumor is
Riza was actually
your great‐grandmother.
Were you aware?
[laughing]
Guess I can chalk
that one down as a "no."
It's fine.
it's nothing for you to worry
your pretty little head about.
To be honest,
she was a very evil woman.
All the pain you're suffering
through right now is a direct
result of the choices
that she made.
So laugh at her demise, child.
Go ahead!
That's enough. Be quiet.
I don't wanna hear another word
coming out of your mouth!
[RUSALKA laughs]
Oh, how adorable!
Just because you're going to
die in the very near future,
doesn't mean you
should get so sensitive
about every little thing!
I, for one, am not
planning to die.
I'll sacrifice you, Riza,
and thousands of others
if it means I'll live forever.
And I won't even think
twice about what I've done.
Got it?
Don't look at me
like that, you sow!
[REA] Hey, it looks‐‐
like... your stomach hurts too.
Maybe you ate
something really bad.
Hallo!
I decided to drop in.
Tell me, Malleus.
Do you believe that certain
things happen because of fate?
Whenever I take aim
at something of late,
it either escapes,
or the damn thing dies,
or someone else
claims it as their own.
A hell of a predicament, huh?
[RUSALKA]
Hold it.
Do you really want to fight me?
Because I killed
your little boytoy?
I want an answer!
Damn you!
Seriously?
You killed him?
You honestly expect
me to believe that?
What are you implying?
Of course I killed him.
No, I don't buy it.
That would be impossible.
I couldn't even kill that
slippery biker bastard.
So that means...
...he's right there.
Isn't he?
That doesn't make any sense.
I'm afraid you've
lost your mind, Bey.
Let me put you
out of your misery!
[RUSALKA yells]
[wretching]
[gasping]
This just can't be.
This is impossible!
[RUSALKA yells]
What'd I tell you?
Come on out, kid!
I knew you wouldn't let me down!
[laughs] We've got unfinished
business, you and I!
[SHIROU grunts]
Ja, good stuff!
You pilfered that little move
off of Malleus, didn't you?
Just what I'd hoped for!
I believed this would happen.
I just knew you'd evolve!
You spouted off a lot
of crap about déjà vu.
But even you can't say
you've seen anything
like this before!
As you wither away, my lover,
and remember, I alone know you.
The one my love causes to rot.
[WILHELM]
Briah!
Rosenkavalier Schwarzwald!
Here we go!
[RUSALKA yelling]
I don't want to die.
I don't want to die!
[RUSALKA gasping]
That's it.
I'll be like her
before much longer.
If so, then I'll just...
[REA gasps]
[RUSALKA screaming]
[RUSALKA]
God, no!
[RUSALKA gasping]
[growls]
[RUSALKA gasps]
[WOLFGANG]
Hello, Anna.
Been a while, hasn't it?
Just like old times.
What? Is that you?
Schreiber...
Schreiber, you have to help!
Please!
I think I'm going to die!
No, wait!
Please don't go!
I love you, Schreiber!
You can't just leave
me behind to die!
[WOLFGANG]
I never knew.
You love me? Really?
Ja. So please, darling.
I need your help now!
I don't want to die.
I want to live.
You and I together!
Because I love you!
[WOLFGANG]
I understand.
I just never knew.
Anna. I love you, too.
I'm happy.
Promise that you'll
always protect me‐‐
[gasping]
[WOLFGANG laughing]
It's wonderful!
I love the way this feels!
I never knew what I was missing!
I'll slaughter the
beast that did this
to my liebchen !
So tragically poignant!
And yet dreadfully romantic!
My love!
I've never killed anyone
for this reason before!
I will avenge you.
You may die,
but our love never will!
[laughing]
[WILHELM yells]
[HELGA laughing]
[HELGA] What do you think
you're doing, miscreant?
Leave my dear Wilhelm be!
[WILHELM] You two haven't
met yet, have you?
[WILHELM chuckles]
[WILHELM]
Allow me to introduce Helga.
Both my sister and my mother.
[HELGA]
Villi. Villi.
Oh my treasured
little boy, Vilhelm!
I won't let anyone
be cruel to you.
And if they are, kill them‐‐
butcher every last one!
[WILHELM] Ja, she can
be a bit overprotective.
Whenever I get too
excitable, she comes out.
Goddamn, you really are
one crazy motherfucker!
Don't you dare speak
that way to my son!
[HELGA laughing]
[WILHELM yells]
[SHIROU gasps]
[WILHELM laughing]
I love it! Keep the
good stuff coming, kid!
I want more, so don't stop!
That was all right
for an appetizer,
but now it's time
for the main course.
Yeah?
Well save room for the
ass‐kicking I'm serving ya!
[WILHELM grunting]
[WILHELM]
Schreiber?
Let me go!
[WOLFGANG]
Quiet down.
You're in my way.
I think it's about
time you got lost.
I'm here for him.
[WILHELM yelling]
[WILHELM]
Not yet! No!
[WOLFGANG chuckles]
I must say you've surprised me.
I can't believe Bey
lost to you like that.
I swear, I never would have
imagined that outcome.
Look, you're the one
who killed him, Patch.
That's not important.
You're responsible
for this, yeah?
I guess our love was like
ships passing in the night,
but I still have to
avenge her death.
So I'm going to kill you
for what you did.
[RUSALKA]
Help me.
Please, help me.
It hurts.
Please, Schreiber.
I don't want to die‐‐
Once she's dead,
I will seek my revenge.
Run away while you still can.
It doesn't matter
where you hide.
I'll find you,
and then rip you to pieces.
[WOLFGANG laughing]
We'll meet again soon.
You have the word
of Wolfgang Schreiber:
Einherjar of Lord Heydrich!
A fallen warrior lifted by
valkyries into golden Valhalla!
[WOLFGANG laughing]