[REINHARD gasps]
[REINHARD grunts]
Days ago,
a bomb went off in the hopes
of assassinating the Führer.
This act of terrorism had
been foretold. By you, in fact.
Surely this can not
be mere coincidence.
Look at me.
You were arrested under
suspicion of treason
against the Reich.
My name is‐‐
[KARL] Reinhard Heydrich,
director of the
Reich Main Security Office,
and Chief of Security
Police and the SD.
I assume you know my
name is Karl Krafft.
But did you know that
some call me a mage?
[REINHARD grunts]
[KARL] Ah! You recently
witnessed a strange vision,
did you not?
[KARL] To put it plainly,
you're seeking my assistance
in your propaganda efforts?
[REINHARD] Indeed. That is my
condition for sparing your life.
Essentially, we require
our own Nostradamus.
Someone to help restore our
sense of national pride
after our great defeat, and the
humiliation at Versailles.
[KARL] I understand.
You have my support.
If you wish me to be
the new Nostradamus,
then I gladly accept.
And I give you my word.
I will lead you to your destiny.
[CROWD chatters]
[MAN A grunts]
[MAN A groans]
[WOLFGANG hums]
[whistle blows]
[POLICEMEN grunting]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[POLICEMAN E gasps]
It looks like you're having
a lot of fun out here!
Do you mind if I join in?
[POLICEMAN D shouts]
[WILHELM]
Back off, brat!
[POLICEMAN D grunts]
[WILHELM chuckles]
[WOLFGANG chuckles]
[both grunt]
[MAN B] As long as
we have you around,
Herr Heydrich, the glorious
future of our nation is assured.
[MAN C] You're precisely
what the Führer means when
he expounds upon the virtues
of the "master race".
A perfect specimen.
[MAN D] A toast! To our hero,
the Golden Lord! Prost!
[MAN B, C]
Prost!
I'm honored, but you give
me far too much credit.
I followed my orders.
Just as any good soldier
of the Fatherland would.
And as for this
"Golden Lord" business,
I'm simply a man working
toward the glory of his country.
[MAN B laughs]
And he shows such
humility as well!
Everyone knows the
fate of the Reich
falls upon your
mighty shoulders!
[MAN C] Thanks to the efforts of
our esteemed lieutenant‐general,
we have nothing
to worry about!
[MAN D] Ja, all political
dissidents have been dealt with.
[MAN C]
Indeed.
[MAN B]
And the trains...
[MALE SOLDIER A]
Herr.
[MAN D] Oh, I didn't see
you step in, Benito!
Something requires
my attention. Excuse me.
[KARL] Come now.
Why the hasty retreat?
All of the dignitaries at the
party seemed to be more than
impressed by you.
[REINHARD]
A work issue arose.
[KARL]
Ah...! And this "work issue",
was something you had to
attend to personally, was it?
[REINHARD] I used the excuse
as my chance to leave.
The fact that my duty converged
with my desire was good fortune.
There's nothing else I could do.
[KARL]
Said like someone
who doesn't have a
choice in the matter.
Your self‐effacing nature
never changes, does it?
But I have to wonder.
[ELEONORE]
Ahem. Pardon.
I apologize for
interrupting you gentlemen.
I am Eleonore von Wittenburg.
Obersturmführer in
the Schutzstaffel.
Beatrice Kircheisen!
Sturmscharführer,
at your service.
My name is Riza Brenner
from the Lebensborn.
Pleased to meet you.
[KARL] Ja, ja. I'm familiar
with your names.
Working for the RMVP, I've
learned all about you ladies.
But I am at a loss as to
why the Three Valkyries
felt the need to intercept our
retreat from the festivities.
Well, we've come here in
regards to Herr Heydrich's
earlier decision. It is our
wish to accompany the General,
and assist him
however we can.
The General's work is outside
the scope of your duties.
True, but we are
servants of the Reich,
and are ready to
do what we must.
We believe in the
work you're doing, sir.
Thus, we would like to pledge
ourselves as your swords,
if you'll do us the honor,
General Heydrich. Please accept.
[REINHARD] Do as you please,
but be prepared for punishment
for insubordination
further down the line.
And of course, you're all
responsible for you own safety.
[gasps]
Thank you very much, sir.
[exhales]
[BEATRICE giggles] I bet you're
as pleased as punch now, eh?
Dummkopf! Get that stupid
grin off of your face!
[BEATRICE] Hey! Why the
hell did you hit me?
Now, now. I think both of
you girls need to calm down.
[KARL]
Was that a wise decision?
[REINHARD]
No matter.
This next move falls outside
of your duties, as well.
But you will come
along anyway, won't you?
Of course.
I haven't forgotten the
promise I made to lead you
to your destiny,
and the time to fulfill that
promise is drawing nigh.
[REINHARD]
A promise?
[KARL] No, more like
a statement of fact,
of things that have yet to be.
[ANNA]
Once again, Father,
I would like to
express my gratitude.
Thank you for entrusting a relic
of such absolute importance
to my department.
I'm just glad to
be of assistance.
I would do anything to
support the Ahnenerbe.
I hope it will help you.
Though interesting from
a cultural perspective,
the relic itself is
an ill‐omened thing.
If you and your organization
are willing to take
it off my hands,
then I'm glad to be rid of it.
[ANNA]
Oh really?
Then I would expect you to look
a lot happier than you do.
Or is something else bothering
your delicate sensibilities?
Not at all. I was just‐‐
Well, cheer up!
In another time, this little
box would have seen you tried
by the church for heresy!
I can completely
understand your concern.
Speaking of such
a thing reminds me.
Several years ago, someone told
me about a priest who could
read the hearts
and minds of men.
That would certainly be
labeled heretical, wouldn't it?
In a different era, he would
have been burned at the stake
for practicing
the dark arts.
When you think
about it that way,
I suppose he would
feel very fortunate.
Well, perhaps he would have
been happier back then.
He might not have had to witness
the sorts of things a man can't
unsee unfolding all around him.
There are horrors
in our era, too.
[gasps, grunts]
Dear god, no! I can't stay here.
I... I have to leave!
[WILHELM laughs]
[WILHELM chuckles]
[WOLFGANG chuckles]
What could have
happened here?
The place looks
like a battlefield.
One thing is certain, this was
not the work of an amateur.
We were right to come.
Now Brenner, you're to
go with General Heydrich
and protect him.
He's vital to our
nation's future.
He can not be put in danger.
Ja, I understand. And what
will you do in the meantime?
Kill the attackers, obviously.
Let's move out, Kircheisen!
[BEATRICE]
Ja wohl
[engine rumbles]
[RIZA gasps]
[WOLFGANG giggles]
[WILHELM laughs]
[WILHELM shouts]
[BEATRICE grunts]
[exhales]
Who the hell do you
think you are?
You've got a lot of nerve,
getting in my way!
I've come to punish you!
We can do this the easy way,
or the hard way.
But if you do resist, I will cut
off your limbs and drag you in!
[WILHELM chuckles]
Listen to you!
This oughtta be a riot!
You're a brave one girlie,
I'll definitely give you that!
But, someone so frail
and weak like you
will surely crumble before
the power that I possess!
What's left of you will scatter
like leaves in the wind!
So you choose the hard way.
There's no salvation
for scum like you!
[BEATRICE, WILHELM grunt]
[chuckles]
[ELEONORE]
Hey. What the hell are you?
A man? A woman?
Or not quite either?
Disgusting.
You and the society
that created you
cannot be allowed to exist.
You're an abomination!
To think, a single wartime
loss could fill our country
with wretches like you.
Removing such vermin,
and restoring glory to the
Fatherland is my destiny.
Now face me,
you filthy rodent!
I am going to fumigate you!
[laughs]
[WOLFGANG shouts] You're
certainly welcome to try it!
[ELEONORE grunts]
[ANNA]
Oh, dear.
We seem to have found ourselves
in the lion's den, haven't we?
Are you all right, Father?
[VALERIAN]
Yes, thank you.
But you should hurry
away from this place.
[ANNA giggles]
Well, ja, I probably should,
but my bestial
instincts are aching.
I'd rather stay and see how
things turn out here instead.
You can't! It'll be too late.
Every second you stay here,
we're one tick closer to doom‐‐
[grunts]
[ANNA] Are you sure you're
all right? What happened?
[gasps]
What is that?
Well, now.
[RIZA]
General, please reconsider.
You're plowing
head‐first into danger!
My goodness, what a
terrifying situation.
I can barely stop myself
trembling with fear.
This nation has no shortage
of entertaining individuals.
It's fascinating.
I'm sure the esteemed General
Heydrich would agree with me.
You sound of the opinion that
I'm the most entertaining
individual of them all.
Don't get the wrong
idea about me, mage.
I'm not as impressive a
person as I'm often painted.
I know only how to perform the
duties I have been assigned.
That's all I could ever do.
Yet, at some point
along the way,
I found myself in my
current position.
When it comes down to it,
I'm just like the
incompetent automatons.
And you're content with being
one of the countless masses
on the great stage,
with nothing to show for it
but a vague notion of valor?
[REINHARD]
Indeed.
I'm happy being just another
soldier, doing his job,
and dying if need be.
Someday, I will die,
and that's fine with me.
Even if I lack passion,
I'm doing the things I'm
capable of while I'm here.
That is the only raison d'etre
I need out of this life.
[KARL]
Ah, I see.
But perhaps, there is a
more important question
you've neglected
to ask yourself.
When was the last time your
situation was so serious,
you threw everything
you had at it?
Out with it.
[KARL] From my perspective, you
could be directing your efforts
in a much more efficient way.
To begin with, you should
stop spending every moment
of your life trying to avoid
using the full scope
of your latent power.
[gasps]
[KARL] Was the lion,
king of the jungle,
given its claws and fangs
merely to break an egg open?
Did the hawk use
its mighty wings
to race an insect
crawling on the ground?
No, of course not. The truth is,
you have yet to use your
strength to its fullest.
In fact, if you
ever lost control,
the world wouldn't last
more than an instant.
Nonsense. I wonder how far these
ridiculous little fantasies
of yours spread, Krafft?
Insinuating I could destroy
the world is laughable.
But it does not
make it inaccurate.
[REINHARD grunts]
You act, and everything
around you is brought to ruin.
It's sad, you can't move your
body a single inch without
breaking something.
But despite that malady,
you have still arrived at
your present position.
How much more must you
control yourself in the future,
as your power increases?
You've done what you could,
but still the war expands,
drawing all parties ever deeper.
A cruel cycle, and sadly,
one that won't end well.
Thus you close off your heart,
so you'll feel nothing at all
about everything
you've seen and done.
I've discussed this very
subject with you before,
both standing exactly
where we are right now.
We've met this way many times.
It is not the first time,
nor will it be the last.
Just remember.
You love the whole world,
because it is a part of you.
[KARL] Of course. You may love
something yet still destroy it.
The two concepts are not
necessarily mutually exclusive.
So love the world as
it falls before you.
For that is the destiny
you were born to.
Reinhard Heydrich,
lord of destruction!
How stupid.
[WILHELM chuckles]
[pants]
[REINHARD] The destruction
of love is the destiny
you say to which I was born?
But isn't that‐‐
[KARL] Impossible?
No, you will destroy.
I know, for I have foreseen it.
[BEATRICE gasps]
Herr General, wait!
[REINHARD]
Be gone.
[REINHARD] I decided
I would feel nothing,
would allow nothing in the
world to elicit my emotions.
I am merely a template.
Put simply, Reinhard Heydrich
is an utterly boring man.
The world as it exists,
created that template.
And thus,
created my limitations.
Hey. What are you,
her big brother?
[REINHARD] No matter what I do,
the end is always the same.
I feel no sense of
accomplishment.
I will live this way, then die.
[WOLFGANG laughs]
[REINHARD]
I thought it was inevitable.
It is the way things have
to be. But is it true?
[shouts]
[WILHELM]
[WILHELM shouts]
[WOLFGANG chuckles]
[ELEONORE gasps]
[REINHARD] What do I believe in?
What do I wish for?
What do I desire from
this life? I can not say.
Get back!
It's too dangerous, sir!
[REINHARD] But didn't
I know those answers
at one point in time?
[WOLFGANG screeches]
[WOLFGANG groans]
[ANNA gasps]
[REINHARD] The surges of emotion
that everyone else felt
in their childhood. To tackle
the impossible head‐on.
[REINHARD]
That which I truly yearned for.
[RIZA gasps]
[REINHARD]
From the bottom of my heart.
[REINHARD] Was it always
that same dream?
Now, then. How do
you feel, Herr General?
[REINHARD]
Ever since I met this man,
there's been a strange emotion
burning in my heart.
It seems familiar.
And now I realize, the answer
which had eluded me in the past,
is a thought that
keeps recurring to me
over and over again.
[REINHARD grunts]
Ja, the vision.
[REINHARD]
Krafft.
You and I have had this same
discussion before, have we not?
Indeed we have, Herr General.
It's been too long, my friend.
How good to see you again.
[WOLFGANG laughs]
[SOLDIERS scream]
[ANNA giggles]
[SPINNE growls]
[WILHELM screams]
[HELGA screams, giggles]
May we achieve victory.
[REINHARD]
I love everything.
[KARL] I know everything,
and thus, my dear friend,
I shall prepare a place for you
to finally unleash your power
at its fullest.
[REINHARD] We will destroy this
stifling sense of déjà vu.
Dies Irae.
Now, my friend. Let us celebrate
the creation of a new world.
♪