It hurts.
I'm scared.
[MARIE]
And I'm sad.
It's the end.
[MARIE]
Ren.
[MARIE gasps]
So you've awakened,
Dear Marguerite.
I have prepared a small
party in your honor.
I hope it is to
your satisfaction.
Who are you?
[REINHARD] Did he not tell you?
Karl and I are very old friends.
Or, perhaps he gave you a
different name to call him.
That must be, ja?
Cagliostro?
[REINHARD] Mm. He has spoken of
your charms to me a great deal,
I assure you.
His words: "A woman
like a goddess".
[MARIE gasps]
He has strange tastes,
und always has,
but I'm inclined to agree
with him this time.
And now, I put the
question to you.
What do you think
of me, my dear?
What I think?
[gasps]
[REINHARD]
Your answer?
[MARIE] I'll tell you.
You let everyone die.
You destroy them.
You turn everything
into whatever this is.
You are an absolutely
horrifying person.
I see.
[gasps]
My path to glory stirs
fear in your heart.
But that means
something is amiss.
The goddess for whom
I have waited to join me,
should be one who is
incapable of feeling that way
towards others.
Emotionless, und thus,
infallible.
Put simply, I was lead to
believe you had no heart.
[gasps]
You were the cause
of this pain.
[REINHARD] Indeed. My love
is complete destruction.
Und with this Valhalla,
I shall conquer all
that stands in my way.
I told you. I would teach you
how to love, mein liebchen.
I'm afraid. Please don't.
I don't want your love.
Your entire world is wrong.
Then we shall not
receive heaven together.
There is simply no
need for two rulers.
Come celebrate! The war
has at last been declared!
♪
[KASUMI'S FATHER gasps, laughs]
Finally, after all this
time! It's a success!
Welcome, Zarathustra.
Bastard child of Karl Krafft!
No, that doesn't
feel right. I've got it!
How about "Ren"?
A lotus flower of hope
raised up from the mud.
From now on,
you'll be my son!
You can come live with us.
I'm certain my wife and daughter
will love you and
make you very happy.
[KASUMI'S FATHER chuckles]
We'll care for you until
you're ready to bloom!
[REN] Ren... Ren.
Is that me? What am I?
[REN]
Maybe I knew from the beginning,
that no matter how hard I tried,
I would never have a chance
for a "normal" life.
That everything was ephemeral.
Like a dream.
Lurking beneath the surface
of my everyday life.
The real world, was waiting
to tear its way in.
That's why I hoped against hope
that I could make
time stand still
That what we had
could go on forever.
That I'd never lose what
was important to me.
[REN] I wished... that this
future would never come.
[REN] But fate doesn't
care what you wish for.
Marie! No! Marie!
[REN]
Where am I?
[REN gasps, grunts]
Damn. It's no use!
Marie? Marie!
Are you there? Hello?
[door creaks]
Hi Fujii. How are you?
[REN gasps]
Rea?
[REA] Hold on.
I'll unlock the chains.
Are we inside the church?
[REA]
We are.
[REN]
The basement?
That's correct.
Is this your secret fort?
Don't be such an idiot.
[metallic clang]
You wake up down here in chains,
isn't there anything you
want to ask me?
Like why you're here?
But the only thing
you care about
is finding out where
you are. Unbelievable.
I've already learned the
information I most wanted
to find out from you.
Look. It's pretty obvious to
me that you're on my side.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be
here doing this, now would ya?
[REA grunts]
You're a nasty perv, right?
And supposedly I'm
a wicked woman.
Somehow, in the end, I always
knew this day would come.
Everything in my life
was merely a dream,
and there was no way the
forces that be would ever
give me a shot at
something normal.
Now first things first,
we have to close our eyes.
[REA] Let's stop listening.
Stop talking.
Stop breathing, and never move.
Keep your heart as hard
as stone, so you feel nothing.
Don't notice anything.
When I did that, Fujii, I...
...I started thinking
that everything I knew
would just cease to exist.
Would simply vanish away.
I was so frightened of
doing anything, I...
[REA sobs]
[REN]
Listen. I felt the same
Maybe I knew this would
all happen someday too.
So I looked the
other way. Pretended.
Ignored what I
didn't want to see.
But it isn't too late!
There's still time to do
something about it!
I refuse to give up hope.
In my heart, I know I can
be free from this one day.
Then, will you make love
to me right here, Fujii?
[REN]
Uh.
[REA] If you really
want to do something,
then take me, right now.
And if you can't do that,
then just kill me.
I've always felt like
I shouldn't be alive.
Like I'm out of place.
[REA gasps] Sorry. Joking.
Do the rest yourself.
Bye‐bye.
No, please don't leave
me down here! Hey!
[REA gasps]
[VALERIA]
You give up so easily, Theresia.
That must be rather
disappointing for poor Fujii.
If you come up with an idea,
you should see it
through to the end.
Of course, there are
certain things in life
about which nothing can be done.
[REA] Shut up!
I hate you, you jerk!
I don't want to talk
to you ever again!
[RIZA gasps]
[VALERIA sighs]
Okay.
[VALERIA]
Rough day, eh, Fujii?
Allow me to apologize for
Theresia's rudeness.
I want you to tell
me where she went.
I cannot say, but she
did seem somewhat upset.
Generally speaking, I try
to stay out of her way
when she gets like that.
Given the right circumstances,
I'm willing to take a slap.
Just not here and now,
you understand.
That's adulterous.
Come with me, Fujii.
Lord Heydrich is
waiting for you.
[REN]
So what?
You're saying she doesn't know
anything about what's going on?
Correct. She was
born in this era,
und had lived a normal
life until recently.
Though, having grown up with
creatures like us around her,
"normal" may not be the most apt
qualifier in Theresia's case.
But, one mustn't
blame her for that.
The human mind always finds a
way to see what it wants to see.
Especially without proof to
contradict those thoughts.
She may have a vague
sense of unease,
but that isn't enough
to act upon.
That's only because you
monsters kept her in the dark
and fed her lies.
I cannot deny that fact.
Though Riza deserves most
of the credit, of course.
But for now, you should
worry about yourself,
und forget about her.
To be quite frank, the last
thing I would want
is to be in your
shoes right now, Fujii.
Know that I speak from
the heart when I say this.
I wish you the
very best of luck.
Lord Heydrich is a
man unlike any other.
You must not make the
mistake of judging him
as an average human being.
[grunts]
[gasps]
That sign. Is it? Kill?
Slaughter? No, not quite.
I know that sigil.
[REINHARD]
"Hagall."
[gasps]
[REINHARD]
Destruction. The end.
The death of the old order,
und the power to make it happen.
The unstoppable force
of nature. Pure calamity.
The twilight of the gods.
The final war.
It is Dies Irae. Long have
I awaited its coming.
Please take a seat, boy.
You need not to be
so afraid, for now.
The Grail Priest no doubt
frightened you as he brought you
to me, but I place great
value on politeness.
As the master of this place,
I know how to extend
hospitality to our
esteemed guests.
Now then, do sit.
[REINHARD chuckles]
Ja, I see.
An interesting choice,
I'll give you that.
Quite symbolic,
one could even say.
Tell me. Do you have any idea
which seat you've chosen?
No clue, and I honestly
don't give a damn.
Just tell me what you're
planning to do to me.
Do to you?
[scoffs]
I simply wanted to have a
conversation with you,
face to face.
[gasps]
[REINHARD] Every fraction of
every single moment. I'm aware.
Testing my perceptions for the
slightest hint of the unknown.
Und contemplating how I might
better sense the undetectable.
In other words. I am
a prisoner of déjà vu.
[REINHARD] I thought that would
be the easiest way to explain
my experience to you.
[gasps]
[REINHARD]
I remember this moment.
I have repeated it an
infinite number of times.
Without even the
most minute deviation.
At this point, I can no
longer dismiss it as
"as mere hallucination". Not
since the first time I met Karl.
You mean Karl Krafft.
[REINHARD] Ja. A stranger
man than most.
It is said that he has possessed
thousands of appellations
over the years.
Such as Faust, for example.
Saint Germain. Paracelsus.
Cagliostro.
[REN grunts]
[REINHARD]
And of course, Mercurius.
Which is, I believe,
the most well known.
That's ridiculous!
So what, he's been alive
for countless centuries?
Do you really believe that crap?
What if I do believe it?
Would that change anything?
Besides, that's not
the important part.
His power is what mattered,
und he was quite interesting.
His objectives matched
my own, und so,
there were no
problems between us.
What objectives?
To make it stop. This Déjà vu.
After meeting him, I formed
a friendship with the man,
und thanks to that choice, the
whole world now seems blurry.
My life had always
been passionless,
but this was somehow
even worse.
I have never felt a
sense of achievement
at any point in my life.
Und without free agency, there
isn't any sense of satisfaction.
No matter what
position I held.
What glory and honor
were heaped upon me.
I never had a sense
of fulfillment. But why?
Like Karl said,
[MERCURIUS]
The truth is,
you have yet to use your
strength to the fullest.
[REINHARD]
Clichéd, perhaps.
Like a boy's fantasies of
being drunk on omnipotence.
But he also shared
the following with me:
The closer to the extreme,
the more clichéd you are.
In other words. I seem to have
been born into the wrong world.
But he said controlling myself
would be untrue to the core
of my very essence.
If I turn to truly face
the world head on,
and this world is
consequently destroyed,
then my love is
that destruction.
It is my wish, to both
embrace und destroy.
Whatever. You'll kill millions
so you can feel satisfied?
What else can one
hope for from this life?
Two things, specifically:.
A situation in which I
have no choice but to use
the full extent of my power,
und one in which what follows
is completely unknown to me.
This is not my world, currently.
Thus, I must create the
new world that should be,
und release the flow.
[REINHARD] I must forge a
mountain worthy of climbing,
und then ascend it.
That will be the
end of my déjà vu.
Because I love everything,
I will destroy everything
and paint it over.
I once sacrificed all of Berlin,
but it still was not enough.
It is no secret. The result of
making a world to rival the law
of déjà vu simply shifted
it into another dimension.
Like two great powers,
staring at each other from
across the expanse of the sea.
Therefore, to invade.
I require a sacrifice now,
und that means...
[REN]
This whole town?
[REINHARD]
Hm. Indeed.
[REN]
Really?!
Everyone that lives here is just
a tool for achieving your goals?
Your outrage is directed
at the wrong man.
If it were not for
our persistence,
this town would never
have come to be.
Lovely Shambhala.
The Eastern Paradise.
Ever since World War Two,
Karl has been making this
eastern jewel into
a second Berlin.
A special place,
with eight ley lines.
Manifest eight battlefields
on those points,
und sacrifice countless
souls in our wake.
[REINHARD] The resulting
magic will give you
a city‐sized relic. A swastika.
A golden alchemical circle
that will grant my wish
for an end to my
plight at long last.
Und of the eight sites, two of
them have already been opened.
Thus, six battlefields remain
between us und the end.
A great deal of blood und a
soul's penitence are required.
Do you understand? Und that
is where you come in.
Conquer the eight battlefields
here in Shambhala,
which will allow
me to manifest.
Refusal will only result
in the death of the masses
being meaningless.
You cannot refuse.
[REN gasps]
Tell me, Ren.
What will you do now?
You understand
what is happening,
so it's time to decide.
Will you withdraw or advance?
Show me what I
haven't seen before!
Give Marie back to me!
You've got nothing to lose!
You might get that surprise
you've been waiting for.
The unknown?
Yeah, I'll show it to ya!
But that will be the last thing
you ever see, Reinhard!
[REINHARD laughs]
How delightful. Bravo!
Ja. Truly splendid.
I applaud your efforts Karl,
it would seem your education
is paying off too well.
But I have to admit.
Though the process is already
on track, waiting is a bore.
Him risking his life is known.
Thus, pointless.
Perhaps, I should simply accept
it as a path to the gospel.
The ending is nigh. Take her.
[REN grunts]
I bid you farewell for now.
You will not run.
You have vowed to defeat me,
so keep your word.
The final battle is coming.
I promise my legion und I will
give you the fight of your life,
child of Karl.
He vanished.
[sighs]
Man, I sure talked a big game,
so let's hope that
I can back it up.
What the hell do I do now?
It doesn't matter.
Hi, Marie. Welcome back.
[MARIE grunts]
Huh?
What's this?
Where am I? That man!
He stabbed me right here.
[MARIE gasps]
Please. No! Don't stare!
What?
I'm embarrassed! Dummy!
Wait! No! Hold on a sec!
You weren't particularly
worried about your modesty
when I woke up next to
a naked you in my bed!
No! You're trying to confuse me!
You're too close anyway,
so back off!
[REN]
Why are you acting like this?
[MARIE giggles]
[MERCURIUS laughs]
[REINHARD laughs]
♪