[REN shouts]
[REINHARD]
Listen. At this moment you und I
are at the very
center of the world!
The stage is set! Let's perform
the final act of this opera!
You just want to steal
the souls of innocents!
That's your only
true desire, isn't it?
[REINHARD] Ja. Their passions.
Love, hatred, und anguish.
A small taste leaves
me wanting more.
So many lives playing
out for our pleasure.
There are those who fear me,
those who worship me,
und those who want me to grant
them what they have lost.
Those wretched souls.
They are the greatest offering.
You've fed on them for too long!
But I will not let
you take any more!
[REN yells]
[KARL] Think of emanation
as a work of art.
One which uses all that
exists as its canvas.
The colors are entirely
of the artist's choosing.
Once it has begun,
it cannot be stopped.
It cannot remain unfinished.
Und when the artwork is
completed, it cannot be undone.
However, it can be repainted
by another artist.
Ja. Therein lies
the eternal conflict.
These forceful brush strokes!
Layering upon the former's work.
The frame may not
withstand such intensity!
What happens when it breaks?
Ah. That's when an
opening appears.
The time is upon us. It won't
be long now, my sweet flower.
[ISAAK breathing weakly]
Vater.
Please tell me that
you need me now, Vater.
I'm ready, Vater! Just tell
me that you need me! Please!
[ISAAK sobs]
[REINHARD]
Now come! My beautiful children!
[REINHARD] The ninth
Hohenstaufen awakens!
[REINHARD] I see.
You wished for time to stop?
However. You understand
what's happening.
We are on the same level.
Both performing an Emanation.
[REN] Yeah, I realize that,
but it also means...
...everything that
you do, I can undo.
You would revive
them over and over.
Bring them back only to die.
Your Valhalla is just
a city full of corpses,
suffering for eternity!
You've turned them into slaves!
It's over! I refuse to
let it happen again!
[REINHARD chuckles]
[REINHARD] The rejection of what
one chooses not to believe
is one of man's greatest sins.
An indelible stain on humankind.
Your refusal means nothing!
War's engrained in us,
not something you can escape.
If this destiny
cannot be avoided
no matter how hard we may try,
then why not embrace it?
[REN grunts]
[REN shouts]
[REN yells]
[REINHARD scoffs]
[REINHARD] So many experience
life as a slow march to death.
They simply do what
existence requires.
I'm beginning the great finale!
The death that they've
all been waiting for!
This is the last
act of this play,
but it will be
followed by another!
We will witness the
birth of a new world!
I love everything! Equally und
without constraints!
Therefore, I must...
...destroy it!
Now weep for me,
und sing the Dies Irae!
[REN]
I had it, what I wished for.
My days were peaceful.
I was surrounded by friends.
People I loved.
So what I refuse,
is to give up hope!
I'll protect what I cherish!
And I will stop you! Now!
[REINHARD] Well then.
Go on und annihilate me!
[growls]
[gasps]
[WILHELM]
Wither away my lover.
[BOTH] Briah Rosenkavalier
Schwarzwald .
[REN grunts]
[RUSALKA]
Don't go or fade away.
[RUSALKA] You will not leave
me behind. I won't let you.
[RUSALKA, REINHARD] Briah
Csejte Ungarn Nachtzehrer .
[grunts]
[REINHARD]
Seems you've been stopped.
I'll show no mercy!
You've lost! Face death!
[REN grunts]
[REN]
Shirou. Sakurai.
You may be gone, but I
can still feel you.
[REN gasps]
Now. Let's do it!
We'll take him down as one!
[gasps, chuckles]
The unknown, it is here.
[ELEONORE] I am she who was
burned by the glorious light!
Eternally following an
unreachable star.
Because you are blessed,
you shall never reach it.
[ELEONORE] The burn from
its radiance is the blessing.
Your arms. They are
my eternal sanctuary.
[ELEONORE, REINHARD]
Muspellzheimr Laevateinn !
[BEATRICE]
Totentanz Walküre !
[REN shouts]
[yells]
I've got you!
You're wrong yet again.
[WOLFGANG]
No. I'm begging you.
Please don't touch me
[REN grunts]
[WOLFGANG, REINHARD]
Immortal race.
Niflheimr Fenris Wolf .
[REN grunts]
[REN]
Stop! Now!
[REINHARD gasps]
Ah. The blood in
my veins is boiling.
This moment I know...
I am alive!
[REN grunts]
[grunting]
I'm not done! I need more!
You will not stop me! Never!
[ISAAK gasps]
[gasps]
Please no. It's as I feared.
I will never mean
anything to you, Vater.
[REA]
Isaak!
[KARL]
The opening presents itself.
[KARL] Let me welcome you
both to the new world.
For now,
we've gathered together at the
very center of the universe.
[KASUMI pants]
What is that?
[KASUMI] Oh, I really wish
I knew where everybody went.
Or, uh, what in the
heck is going on.
But still, I'll be
here waiting for you!
So please come back.
[REINHARD] How rude, Karl.
You've interrupted our battle.
I do not need your help.
[gasps]
That was not my intention
in the slightest, my friend.
But there's a more fitting
locale for the conclusion.
Und my wish is to
see it transpire.
That's the sole reason I've
chosen to live this long.
You're him. You're Karl Krafft.
Mercurius.
[REINHARD chuckles] You always
know how to make an entrance.
This is no exception, friend.
Forgive me,
but I can't allow you to
be the one to replace me.
That person has
already been chosen.
[KARL] She will fit
the bill splendidly.
Very well then.
[REINHARD] My deepest desires
were indeed made flesh.
[REINHARD]
I explored the arcane,
searching for truth und
the meaning of life.
You kept the promise
you made to me.
Take the death you've
been waiting for.
[REINHARD] It's time
for us to say farewell.
[KARL]
Indeed.
Farewell, my old friend.
So, Ren, listen. I uh...
[REN]
Tell me. What happened to Rea?
I can't be sure. In the midst
of all the commotion,
I did see Isaak shatter.
But your battle was so
incredible it tore a hole
through the fabric of existence.
If she survived that,
then she's likely somewhere
in the outer reaches.
Far enough to remain safe,
if she stays there.
You're sure of that?
Ja. As long as you
ask nothing of her.
[REN grunts]
Please don't leave me!
I'll go with you.
No. You need to stay here.
Please Ren!
[MARIE gasps]
[REINHARD] You've said
your goodbyes, then?
[REN]
Yeah.
An idiot like me doesn't
belong in a place like this.
Ah. Then you und Karl
are of the same mind?
Guess you could say that.
The ones who reached
the emanation level
were me, you, Mercurius,
and Marie. That makes
for quite the quartet.
But only one of us
can stay here.
That's how it
plays out, isn't it?
Indeed. There cannot be multiple
rulers at the same time.
A single artist will
choose the colors.
They alone will paint
the new world.
Karl's time is up. He's more
than ready to drift into death.
[REN] Whatever happens to him,
I can't let you take his place.
Und you don't want the honor?
No. I am not worthy of that.
What I really want is for
everything except me
and my friends to freeze.
Not a great world
for everyone else.
I'm no better than you.
I'm just another selfish
idiot and troublemaker.
Do I deserve to
be a god? No way.
[REINHARD]
Very well then.
I've found there are two types
of strength in this world.
One for one's own sake und
one for the sake of others.
Neither is better or worse.
If there is a difference,
it is our faith.
If you wish to be the
knight to our new queen,
this will be the first
test of your loyalty.
I shall destroy you with the
utmost respect in my heart.
Come!
[REN] Marie. Please forgive me.
I'm sorry for making you cry.
For leaving you behind. I'm sure
you're disappointed in me,
but I did what I had
to do to protect you.
It was my only choice!
[KARL] I've fallen madly
in love with you.
I kneel down before you
in absolute adoration.
Sweet flower.
[MARIE] What you're saying is,
I should be as you are.
In a way, but,
do as you see fit.
Those men have strong desires,
full of nothing but problems.
One wishing for a
world ruled by war,
the other wanting time
itself to fall static.
Neither would be suitable
for humankind.
I can't, because my
heart belongs to Ren.
Does it? Und you're
solely devoted to him?
We're together!
So, what flows from me, is the
same as what flows from him.
We shared our hearts.
We laughed and cried together.
We fought by each other's side.
We loved!
[MARIE sobs]
[MARIE]
These feelings are so important.
I know he would say
the same thing.
[KARL] You believe that he
understands your feelings.
I know he can be such
a fool sometimes!
He loves to show off and brag.
He says he understands when
he really doesn't at all.
But he can't help it. He doesn't
want anyone to doubt him!
So he pretends, and it's stupid.
Somehow it makes
me love him more.
So you can tell me
whatever you want,
it won't change my
feelings for him.
[KARL]
Hm.
Let's assume that you know
his heart as well as you say.
How do you plan to live in
the world which he creates?
A world frozen in time.
The two of you living forever,
und everyone else
not living at all.
[MARIE] I... Can't things
just stay as they are?
[KARL]
They cannot.
[MARIE gasps]
[KARL]
I won't accept that outcome.
For if you were to make the
choice for continuation,
my old friend would
surely kill you.
There would be no future.
[MARIE gasps]
What do you mean?
How can you say that?
I swore that one day I
would truly let you bloom.
But first I would have to set
you free, my sweet flower.
Beautiful goddess.
I fell madly in love with
your soul, Marguerite.
At this moment,
your desire is clear.
You wish to hold me in
your arms, don't you?
[ERI]
Rea. Hey, Rea.
[SHIROU] I'm sorry, but we're
gonna need to tag you in.
Und victory, is mine.
[REN yells]
[REINHARD] You have been
a worthy adversary.
But in the end, my desires
proved to be stronger.
They simply overpowered
your faith.
Und now I shall take
the gold I longed for.
[REN yells]
The entirety. All that exists,
shall be mine.
[REN grunts] No. Never.
I'll never let that happen.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I can't let you win.
[SHIROU]
Some hero line.
[ERI]
It's not bad.
[KEI]
You can do better though.
[REA] Please don't die, Fujii.
You have to live.
[REINHARD]
Impossible.
This is her. Theresia.
O‐kay.
[REINHARD groans]
[REA]
What got you in the end,
was the way that
you treated Isaak.
You left your son
frightened and all alone.
That's the only reason
I could do this.
[REINHARD gasps]
[REA] No matter how many
souls you collected.
How many millions
you took with you.
When it came down to it,
you had no one.
You were alone. And you lost.
[REINHARD chuckles]
Now come beautiful death.
Behold the glorious unknown.
[laughs]
[MARIE gasps]
I do want to hold you.
Oui . It's true.
But I love Ren
with all my being!
And I know it's wrong
to commit adultery.
Wait. That's him! Ren!
[laughs]
The unknown. This is it!
[REN pants, grunts]
[REN]
I won.
[REN] Shirou. Honjou.
Sakurai. Rea. Kasumi.
[REN] It's all because
of you. Thank you.
[REINHARD]
Why do you cry?
[REINHARD] You've claimed
victory. Take pride in it.
Allow me that in my defeat.
I simply couldn't
bear losing to someone
who shrank away from triumph.
Und I don't believe you
were alone in your fight.
No. I wasn't alone.
I had my friends
and the strength of those hoping
for a new world on my side.
[REINHARD] Well then. You have
the pride of the righteous.
Blessings unto you. Farewell.
[KEI]
So uh. How is she doing?
[ERI] Well, I mean.
She's getting really old.
And nobody can live forever.
[ERI] Look. I know you're
worried about Ms. Kasumi,
but she's still got
some life in her.
[REA]
I'm glad to hear it.
[SHIROU] Wouldn't be surprised
if the ol' battleaxe outlives
all of us.
Ah. It's been a long time.
I hope you're doing well
[REN]
What about you? All good?
[KASUMI]
Nothing worth complaining about.
So, tell me what brings
you here today.
I've spent more years
than I should have
worrying half to
death about you.
And to this very day,
you've never told me what
really happened back then.
Ah. Sorry. Forget it.
I understand how you feel.
[KASUMI]
Anyway, I've been thinking a lot
about something lately.
Reincarnation.
I'm actually starting to
believe that it really happens.
[REN]
Yeah. I believe in it, too.
Without a doubt.
[MARIE] Hey there Kasumi!
It's me! You see?
These flowers are so pretty!
[gasps]
Marie...
[MARIE giggles]
♪