[VALERIA] Now, then.
That's enough waiting.
The farce is over.
Bey, Malleus, Leonhart,
Babylon, und Tubal Cain.
Dawn approaches.
Und when it comes, the
long‐awaited war will begin.
Let it drive you to the
very depths of madness.
Two swastikas have
been opened thus far.
Both sites have received
their requisite sacrifice
for our great Lord Heydrich.
The first was Lady Kircheisen.
Und the second, Spinne.
These two were deemed worthy of
receiving the Golden Blessing.
But six sites still remain.
And six of us to open them.
Thus, everything
should work out.
Assuming we don't get greedy.
Our Lord Heydrich,
as always, wants blood.
He hasn't changed a
bit since the old days.
I suggest you all
keep that in mind,
when you act as
his fangs und claws.
I'll allow three more,
which will bring the
count up to five.
Und then we'll see
where things stand.
One last thing:
if possible, please try to
avoid choosing the same day.
For a war is preferable
to a massacre.
[ALL] May our victory
be swift und merciless.
[REA gasps]
Fujii.
Huh. But I am left
to wonder one thing.
Will Lord Heydrich wait for us
to achieve our objective?
I for one, am not inclined
to think that he would.
[REINHARD] Samiel. I task
you with opening the fifth.
You'll need to force it,
so feel free to get rough.
Then play with them for a little
while. Pound them into shape.
Jawohl, Lord Heydrich.
♪
[FEMALE REPORTER]
It's unbelievable.
The bridge has been
completely destroyed.
The cause is still unknown,
but multiple reports say that
some kind of giant destroyed it.
Many find this answer to
be suspect, claiming this
supposed "giant" to have been
a gas‐induced hallucination
from a broken line. The besieged
city of Suwahara has already
been plagued by a string of
grisly murders over the
last several months.
What's going on? This is
no time to go to school!
[KASUMI] Besides, I'm too
worried about Ren.
He might be in trouble!
I can help!
Hi!
Hi?
[ERI]
Bang Bang.
[KASUMI gasps]
[ERI giggles]
[phone rings]
[ERI]
Hey! What's up?
You wanna explain this
note you left me, Honjou?
[ERI] Oh. So you made
it home safe and sound.
I'm glad to hear it.
[REN exhales]
Yeah, but back to this note.
Huh? Oh! You mean the
one about taking Kasumi?
She's right here.
You big dumb jerkface
tough guy wannabe!
I thought you were dead! But no!
You've just been clubbing?
[SHIROU]
Shut up, already.
Would you just cool it,
you psychotic gnome?
Who are you calling a gnome?
And...
[ERI]
You could hear that, right?
She's perfectly fine and
full of vim and vigor!
Same for Shirou.
[sighs]
Okay, that's reassuring.
The note had me worried, but
you did save me some trouble.
I couldn't let Kasumi
go to school right now,
with this whole
situation we're in.
[ERI] It didn't seem like she
was planning to go anyway.
But you're right,
this definitely isn't
the time for anyone
to head up there.
Stop...!
[ERI] So, tell me. Are you
interested in talking with us
about what's been
going on, now?
[REN] Yeah. You have
information, don't you?
I want it.
But first thing's first.
[ERI]
Yeah, I know.
[SHIROU] Yo, Ren. How goes it?
What's the word, turd?
[REN]
Cut the crap!
And don't tell Kasumi about
that fight the other night
or any of this other stuff!
Yeah, fine. Looks like
you'll owe me one, though.
Hey wait! Are you
talking to Ren?
Let me talk to him, okay?
No way. Stop it. Get off me.
[SHIROU] Here, come on!
You can tell me instead, okay?
So have you made any
progress with him?
What? What do you
mean by progress?
[SHIROU] Oh man, you're gonna
stay a virgin forever.
Heartbreaking.
[KASUMI]
Stop being gross!
Well, should we get back
to business or what?
[ERI] I see. That sounds
like a rough situation.
So this Rea girl,
was leaving her okay?
Not with me, no.
But the priest told me
something while I was there.
[VALERIA] I know I haven't given
you many reasons to trust me,
but I would like to
say this, at least.
I have no intention whatsoever
of hurting Theresia.
I assure you.
[REN grunts]
[ERI]
Do you trust him?
[REN]
Of course not,
but Father Trifa didn't seem to
be outright lying to me, either.
[ERI] Hm. It's pretty clear
she's tied up in this somehow.
If you'd tried to take
her when you left,
hm, the situation
could've gotten way uglier.
So don't worry.
You made the right decision,
considering the circumstance.
Seems to me, what you've
got's an intel problem.
And that's where you
come in handy, Honjou.
The eight places these
freak‐show fascists
say they've set up across town.
You know where they are, right?
[ERI] I do... Suwahara City's
been home to a bunch of
weird companies
for a long time now.
If you include places even
remotely under their influence,
then the list covers
pretty much everything.
Like you may have heard,
this entire town could have been
built for their
nefarious machinations.
At least that's what my
grandpa always told me.
Grandpa?
Yes, dimwit.
Have you already forgotten
the name of the hospital
you and Shirou
were both taken to?
Guess what? My parents
are in charge of the place.
Honjou General Hospital.
[REN gasps] Your family's
loaded, and you act like that?
What are you implying, Ren?
Back to what we were saying.
Because of my family, I know all
the shady stuff about this town.
And these things you called
swastikas, there are eight?
[REN] Yeah, and they said two
of them have already opened.
[ERI]
Any idea where?
Yes. Probably the
park and the museum.
[ERI] Then, at least half
of the remaining six
should be pretty obvious.
My hospital, the school,
and the church.
But I'm sure you already had
those on your list, didn't you?
Yes I did, though I only
figured out the hospital
after what you told me.
The other three,
I don't have a clue.
And it's important that I know.
[ERI] The amusement park,
the City Tower, the Civic Hall.
That makes eight.
And we'd be foolish to overlook
what most of these focal
points have in common.
Outside of the church,
the rest of them see a
lot of people every day.
Which means no shortage of
souls for their sacrifices.
[REN grunts]
[ERI]
What will you do?
You can't realistically protect
all six places at the same time.
Right. I'll go up to the school.
Yeah. I know it's selfish,
but I have to.
Also. Sakurai and
Rusalka were up there.
They can't be ignored.
All right! I had a
feeling you'd say that.
The bridge was destroyed,
and there are pictures of the
giant all over the internet.
With all the chaos
that's been going on,
everybody staying in their
houses for a few days
would be the most
favorable outcome.
But Japan's been at
peace for so long.
I doubt you can count on that.
You think you could do
something about the people
at the hospital
before it's too late?
[ERI sighs] I'm certainly
going to do whatever I can.
[REN] Fair enough. Thanks for
taking the wool off my eyes.
I owe you one. I'll pay
you back somehow.
So ya gotta be careful, okay?
See ya.
[MARIE] Are you done talking?
Look what I've found, Ren!
I borrowed Kasumi's
school uniform!
We are going to the school, no?
Does it look good?
Yeah. You look gorgeous.
[REN]
I mean it.
[REN sighs]
[REN]
It's time to go. Come on.
[REN grunts]
[MARIE]
Everyone's acting so strange.
[REN]
You're right.
And worse, Sakurai and Rusalka
are nowhere in sight.
Rea either.
\Which could mean they've
already got a plan to prevent
anyone from escaping.
And somehow they got
every student to show up.
Might be hypnosis or something.
[REN] But if that is what's
happening, why aren't they here?
And where the hell are they?
They were able to orchestrate
this right under my nose.
[MARIE]
Ren! Come sit with me!
Your face, it looks like this.
You haven't had a
chance to rest at all.
So come here and sit down.
It's really quite nice!
[MARIE giggles]
[giggles]
[REN]
Uh...
Thank you.
[MARIE giggles]
[REN]
My stomach hurts.
[MARIE]
Is it because you're hungry?
[REN] Yeah. I guess.
How are you feeling, Marie?
I'm feeling okay
for the time being.
Would you like me to go
and get something for you?
No, stay with me. I don't
particularly want to be alone
with my thoughts right now.
The company is much nicer.
But thank you.
[gasps]
[MARIE] Tell me everything.
I want to hear all about
the things you used to do
when you came to school.
This building reminds me of
a castle in certain way,
it's so big.
And since there are so many
people that are around the
same age, I bet you
had a lot of fun here.
[giggles]
[gasps]
Yeah, it was fun.
Tell me about it.
Sure. Kasumi, Shirou, and I
have been friends as
long as I can remember.
They're both dumb and noisy,
which meant they were
both magnets for trouble.
[REN] But. I think that
was part of the fun.
I wished it could
keep going on forever.
I'd always go up to the roof
when I felt like getting away.
My first year here,
I met this weird older girl.
Then Kasumi came
looking for me,
and it ended up being somewhere
we would go to hang out.
[REN]
Shirou was always a bonehead,
and Rea would eat the most
stomach‐churning sandwiches.
To think, not so long ago,
the four of us were
together all the time.
But things have changed.
[MARIE] Oui. Now you've got
me as the fifth person.
[REN gasps]
Well? Is that okay with you?
[gasps]
You bet. I'm sure it'll be fun.
That's a promise.
[giggles]
[music thumping]
[MEN chuckle]
[MAN A grunts]
‐‐[MAN A screams]
‐‐[MAN B gasps]
[RUSALKA sighs]
Gute Nacht. Danke for
a hell of a time, boys!
They're here.
Yep, so it would seem.
Huh? Whoa, wait.
What's going on, you guys?
[gasps]
What is that?
Thanks. Stash her
somewhere, would ya?
Of course I will.
But Ren's not gonna like
it that we lied to him.
If we let her die, he is
gonna be super pissed.
[gasps]
[MARIE gasps]
Ren?
[REN]
What was that?
No way, a swastika?
[RUSALKA] In der Nacht ,
wo alles schläft .
Wie schön , den
Meeresboden zu verlasse.
Ich hebe den Kopf
über das Wasser .
Welch Freude , das Spiel
der Wasserwellen .
Durch die nun
zerbrochene Stille .
Rufen wir unsere namen .
Pechschwarzes haar
wirbelt im wind .
Welch Freude .
Sie trocknen zu sehen .
[clapping]
[SHIROU] Bravo! That was
actually kind of impressive.
I didn't think an old crone
like you could pull that off.
And welcome. But you know,
if I'm being honest,
you weren't the one
I was expecting.
[RUSALKA] Oh? You're talking
about Bey right now, aren't you?
Just between we three, he seems
pretty smitten with you.
But I do have a bad habit of
taking other people's things
for my own. But why.
Why would I do that?
Because I enjoy depriving
people of the things they want!
Oh, how precious!
That almost tickles!
But it also feels kind of good!
[ERI] Isn't your territory
supposed to be the school?
Was cosplaying as a schoolgirl
starting to hurt, old bag?
[RUSALKA] No, no.
I'm taking that one too!
I'm mean‐spirited, greedy,
and always ravenously hungry.
So won't you indulge me.
Let me feast.
Briah‐Csejte Ungarn Nachzehrer !
[SHIROU grunts]
[ERI grunts]
[RUSALKA giggles]
Take this!
[SHIROU chuckles]
[ERI grunts]
[RUSALKA laughs]
Aw, how adorable!
You knew you could
never win the fight,
but you still gave
it your all.
[RUSALKA]
Now then, kids,
do you have any final
words you'd like to share?
[SHIROU]
Déjà vu again? Boring.
You're yawn‐city. Old lady.
[RUSALKA growls]
I'll crush you worms!
What the hell were
they talking about?
Vermin like that never make
any sense to me at all.
[WILHELM grunts]
So. What are you doing here?
[VALERIA] Sorry. I swear,
it was never my intention to
get in your way while
you were working.
[WILHELM] Heh. How
about you tell me why
you've been sticking to my
ass like a damned shadow?
You've been following me
for several hours now.
I was thinking you'd
kill me at any moment.
But I get an apology, instead?
Explain yourself.
I had an errand that
needed tending to
in the place you
were already headed.
I was hoping to make my way
there as quietly as possible,
so I tailed you this far,
which seems to have only
worsened the matter.
[WILHELM grunts]
[VALERIA] Even so,
there's a silver lining.
This situation is fixable.
[WILHELM laughs]
[WILHELM] You think those
words will work on me?
Especially after you dare
interrupt me for your
own purposes, you should
know better than that.
If you really want to apologize,
then tell me one thing.
What was it you and Spinne
were up to that had
to be kept so secret?
From the outside, it looks like
you were trying to shut him up.
[VALERIA]
Hmph.
♪
[VALERIA] Oh, dear. Species that
act based on intuition
make things so difficult.
Very well.
The Sonnenkind bloodline.
That's what we were looking
into before Spinne died.
[WILHELM]
What?
[VALERIA] The one who activated
the swastika in Berlin,
so long ago. Do you
remember him?
Isaak, who was absorbed
by Lord Heydrich,
became the core of Valhalla.
His mother was our
very own Riza Brenner.
Isaak had a brother,
if you recall.
[WILHELM] Ja. His twin.
Johann, was it?
Whatever his name,
I was told he was dead.
[gasps]
Don't tell me.
[VALERIA]
Ja. Johann's death was a lie.
Riza fabricated her
dear boy's passing.
Most likely, she didn't want to
see him sacrificed as well.
In other words, there was
a second Sonnenkind.
Und I wonder. Where can that
bloodline be found today?
Ah. I see now. Of course.
I should have known sooner.
You're playing your own game.
Ja, und I shall use every piece
that has been prepared for me.
As the acting
leader of our order,
that is the justice
I must see done.
[siren blares]