[KARL] In our world, a man's
desires can be made flesh.
The stronger the desire,
the truer this is.
It's a rather simple concept.
I'm sure you understand,
old friend.
Of course.
But still.
Ja. Flowers wilt und die.
Alas, no being yet exists
who can enforce his will
upon the world for all eternity.
That would require a
true miracle of God.
What could be a more
extraordinary circumstance,
than to allow a person's will
to blanket the universe
und then shape it as
they alone see fit?
Extraordinary,
but not impossible, Ja?
Indeed.
It can be achieved through the
magic that I shared with you.
Structured among four
different levels of mastery.
[REINHARD] Activity. Formation.
Creation. Emanation.
[KARL] Think of them as
following the miracles of God
in reverse order. That is
to say, the higher the level,
the closer you are to
the very root of God.
Creation seems liberating,
but there are still limits
to how you can maintain
what you create.
If one reaches emanation,
those fall away.
God declared,
"Let there be light."
Und, thus all things
began to flow from him.
The laws that govern this
world of ours all came to be
in such a manner, did they not?
Primary among them is one which
I call "Eternal Recurrence".
An existence where everything
repeats in an unending cycle.
Und that explains our
sense of déjà vu?
A constant remembrance of the
many versions of ourselves
that came before.
I can assume the only way
to finally be rid of it,
is to remove God
from his throne.
[KARL]
That is correct.
Und that is your true
purpose in this life,
why it is paramount you
reach the Emanation level.
This is the same way in which
the current God of our world
took his place.
He destroyed his predecessor
und claimed divine sovereignty.
So you believe that even
God himself can be replaced.
That he too falls
victim to the cycle?
You're correct once again.
The show is over und it's
time to leave the stage.
When you say it aloud,
it sounds quite simple.
The natural order of things.
[KARL] My friend,
I don't consider myself
to have lied back then.
I wholeheartedly believe
that you can kill me.
Und that is exactly
what I want to happen.
However, the ultimate conclusion
for which I long...
...is to relinquish the
throne to another.
One who is truly worthy.
♪
[VALERIA] Is that all
the time you needed?
[REN] Yeah, for now
at least. Let's go.
[REN] So, Rea is the
nun's great granddaughter?
[VALERIA] Ja. Although Theresia
herself is unaware of this fact,
Riza was in the Lebensborn.
A "farm" of sorts that viewed
its goal as rather noble.
They were attempting to bring
humanity to what they deemed
the next level of evolution.
It's what's more commonly
known as eugenics.
Riza's ambition was
to create a new race.
One that possessed
superhuman powers.
Unfortunately for
all those involved,
the program was a failure.
The children couldn't handle
their new‐found abilities
and broke down like
overheated machines.
So many poor, innocent souls
lost in those experiments.
Und so much blood
staining Riza's hands.
Well, that explains something.
[VALERIA]
Ja.
Her wish was to bring those
children back to life.
At that point her research
delved further into madness.
Isaak was a result
of such efforts.
He was Riza's child und
Theresia's grandfather.
Also, a component of the
Swastika, a city‐sized relic.
His function was to
activate it und strengthen
Lord Heydrich's world.
A human sacrifice,
to put it plainly.
Riza was so desperate
to save those little lambs
she'd led to slaughter.
She was even willing
to offer up her own son.
But if it's actually true
that Isaak was consumed
by Reinhard way back then,
I don't understand how
Rea was even born.
[VALERIA] The only part of
Isaak that merged with Heydrich
was his soul.
His body remained.
You can imagine how
it was accomplished.
[REN]
Eugenics.
[VALERIA] Ja. I'm sure
you've heard this by now,
but the Berlin Swastika
wasn't quite enough.
Thus, the process must
be repeated once more.
What's needed now is a
second Isaak, so to speak.
Und that's...
It's Rea, isn't it? But Riza
told me to save her, too.
It was one of the very
last things she said,
as far as I know.
I guess, despite her past,
she came up with her
own answer in the end.
[VALERIA] You can agree
that a woman's mind
is a terribly
complicated thing ja?
Ultimately, quelling that
internal discord was Riza's
highest priority in
her final moments.
We came extremely close
to killing each other
back at the hospital,
but I feel she was the
one who tasted victory.
However, we can
share in that triumph.
See it through to the end.
Indeed, that is what
she tasked you with.
I'm sure you understand
the reality. That the most
effective way to seal Lord
Heydrich is to kill Theresia.
Remove the sacrificial offering.
With that being said,
how will you proceed?
Well. I'm surprised
that you even have to
ask that question of me, Father.
[REN]
And you?
I'm of the same mind,
of course.
I must protect Theresia.
So does that mean you'll
give up your wish?
I'm a little surprised that
you don't have somebody
you're trying to
bring back, too.
Because between saving Rea's
life and seeing your wish
come true, you're gonna
have to make the choice
of one or the other.
There's never just
one way, Fujii.
Even in this conundrum.
The ritual to be performed is
one known as the Golden Alchemy.
Und there are several
crucial components to it.
Obviously, at its very
core is Theresia.
But we can destroy
some of the others.
[VALERIA] If that happens,
the gold will be incomplete.
Meaning she won't have to die.
[gasps]
[VALERIA]
My wish...
...can only come true because
the miracle is incomplete.
[VALERIA]
Listen to this:
"All your dead loved
ones will return.
Everyone will live
happily ever after."
Do you believe that
Reinhard Heydrich,
of all people, would truly
give us such a world?
[gasps]
[VALERIA]
Everyone is being naïve.
In their greed for the gold,
they sign their name
to the devil's contract.
But the love of destruction
only leads one down
the path towards more war.
[KEI]
Oh man, I'm running so late!
Outta my way!
Kinda rude, doncha think?
What's with the big rush anyhow?
Because you've been in
here for, like, forever!
I'm surprised they
haven't fired you yet.
[gasps] Yeah, maybe I'm not
the most punctual employee,
but I'm doing the best
I can for our family.
Yeah, yeah. Well you better be
careful not to mess things up.
You think Beatrice wants to
be with some jobless bum?
[gasps]
[KEI]
See ya!
[KEI chuckles]
[KEI] I know.
This is all just a dream.
This stupid dream that only
fools me into believing
a normal life is
somehow still possible.
That's why I had to put my
faith in a miracle. Because...
...it's that important to me.
The warmth I felt. The love
they shared meant everything.
So I can't waver. No matter
what obstacles I may face.
Who I fight. Who I have to kill.
No matter what I may risk.
I know that I have
to remain strong.
Unwavering. Resolute.
I have to believe in it.
[KEI grunts]
I was dreaming.
It was so mundane.
But so beautiful.
Just everyday life.
So outside how things
really are for us.
We were a happy family.
Like we should be.
[SHIROU]
Ya know...
[SHIROU] ...It feels kinda like
I've been playing the role
of bad guy here, and that's
totally not my style.
[VALERIA] I'll spare you
the excruciating details.
Just know that five elements
are necessary for the
Golden Alchemy to be successful.
The first is Theresia.
Und the second after that would
be Lord Heydrich's relic itself.
We have decided against
removing the former.
Und the latter
cannot be destroyed.
Well, then what about
the other three?
You saw the battalion leaders
of the Black Round Table,
did you not?
Just defeat a
single one of them.
Which is a Herculean
task in and of itself.
Thus, we need an alliance.
I propose that we try to bring
Leonhart over to our side.
There seems to be some room
to negotiate with her.
[REN gasps]
Hey, how's it hanging,
ol' buddy?
You're here?
It seems as though he took
over Malleus from the inside.
I distinctly remember
saying that
the both of you were oddities.
Anyway. I can only
imagine you've come
because you're
looking for a fight.
Very well, I can indulge you.
I'm sure you know, but this is
a golden opportunity for you.
[REN sighs] I don't know if
I can take much of this.
And why do you look like
you're enjoying yourself?
[VALERIA] I'm sorry, but I miss
the conversations of children.
Father.
Ha. This is gonna get
even weirder isn't it?
[VALERIA]
Now, Leonhart,
I think you may be misreading
the situation we have here.
Fujii und I would like‐‐
[ALL gasp]
[VALERIA chuckles]
[ALL shout]
[REN grunts]
Was that a thunderbolt?
[VALERIA]
Oh, dear, you got me.
[REN gasps]
[KEI]
No way.
You gotta be kidding.
How tough is this dude?
[VALERIA] He's merely following
the orders Riza gave before
she left our Earthly plane.
I did tell you about our spat.
We were at the brink
of killing one another
when our paths crossed,
that final time.
[VALERIA]
Give up.
The Grail cannot be destroyed,
so save your energy.
Although I doubt you've any mind
remaining to comprehend that.
[VALERIA] Fujii. I'd like
for you to help me,
if it's at all possible.
That's within the bounds of
our current relationship, Ja?
Uh... well...
[VALERIA] Can you please
convince this fellow to stop?
[SHIROU] I mean, I knew it, but
seeing it in person like this
is still pretty freaky.
Father goldilocks really
is the grail, isn't he?
Say what?
What's her name over there
kinda just mentioned it.
But I stole a lot of stuff from
that little Nazi vampire chick.
Most of it was in the form
of information, so I've actually
got a pretty good idea of
what in the hell's going on.
If you ask me, teaming up
with that guy would be
an epically dumbass
thing to do, even for you.
There's a reason he
can take all this.
[growls]
I don't get it. Why won't
you just die already?
What in the hell do
you want from me?
Tell me what you want!
Brother!
[ALL grunt]
Seriously? Come now.
You don't know this?
[KEI gasps]
Ask yourself this question
und I'm certain you'll
find the answer.
Do you truly wish to join
Lord Heydrich in Valhalla
und be counted among his
most trusted Einherjar?
I'm just... Not sure.
[VALERIA]
Now then. Mr. Fujii.
It seems it will prove difficult
for us to cooperate officially.
But our task remains unchanged.
In order to save
our dear Theresia,
we must defeat the
three battalion leaders
as we had previously discussed.
We'll do it tomorrow evening.
At the church. I expect
you to give it your all.
[REN]
Hold on!
Do you think that you
can just walk away?
[VALERIA]
Before you arrive,
you must learn about
the Emanation level,
which is above the
Creation level.
[VALERIA]
It's not all that difficult,
just let it flow as
the word implies.
[REN grunts]
[SHIROU]
Whoa! Ren?
[grunting continues]
[SHIROU]
Hey! Ren, you okay?
[MARIE]
Ren... Ren!
[KARL]
This world is ruled by laws,
chief among them is the
law of eternal recurrence.
I created this universe
according to my laws,
but I can no longer
stop of my own will.
Therefore, I have waited.
A countless number of times
for the birth of the one who
would take my place.
For someone who's worthy to
sit upon this sacred throne.
[KARL]
Marguerite. After all this time,
I am certain that I created
this eternal recurrence
for one purpose. Und that
was so I could meet you.
Living under this stifling law.
Where everything repeats itself,
and nothing is unknown.
Meeting you was the one repeated
act that truly brought joy
to my weary soul,
time and time again.
That being said, I can no longer
rein in my strongest desire.
The longing for self‐destruction
that burns within me.
But I ask that you let
your nature as a goddess
flow throughout the universe.
Its emptiness exists
solely so you can fill it.
[MARIE whimpers]
I have made the
necessary preparations.
All that's left is for
you to grant my wish.
My sweet, beloved flower.
[MARIE gasps]
[REN grunts]
Hello.
Something wrong?
[MARIE grunts]
Oui. There seems to be
quite a lot that's wrong.
But for me, I fear
that I'm too strange.
It never troubled me
this much before.
But meeting you
changed me somehow.
I've begun to think more about
myself and all the people
I've encountered
throughout my life.
Now I see. I understand what
Cagliostro told me before.
This world we live in is
constantly repeating itself,
over and over again
with no sign of stopping.
Instead of death being the end,
I'll simply return to
my mother's belly.
To be born and live the exact
same life as I did before.
But if that's true,
I don't belong as I am.
Ghosts cannot exist
in this world,
so I feel out of
place and crazy.
[MARIE whimpers]
What am I?
There are two big parts of
my life I can't talk about.
The first is all these memories
that I can't explain.
I guess they're from
my previous life.
I remember a "me" who's
different from who I am now.
Someone who lived and
died in a different time.
It gets pretty hazy at the end,
but I know it's more
than just a dream.
And if it's real, then I'm
just as crazy as you are.
I'm breaking the rules of
this world the same way.
[MARIE gasps]
You're different, Ren!
It's true you may
be a bit crazy,
but there's nothing
wrong with who you are!
There's something about
your soul that's beautiful.
Spending time with you
makes me so happy!
I'd stay with you for
eternity if I could.
But I'm afraid that if I were to
stay, it would be bad for you.
I'd get in your way.
[REN] The second secret I
carry with me. It's bad.
When I was a little boy,
I saw somebody get killed
right before my very eyes
and that image has haunted
me ever since that day.
I can never say
anything about it,
because if I were to let
it out, it would hurt Kasumi.
It makes me feel like
such a damn coward.
To be perfectly frank,
even though they
weren't a good person,
sometimes I wish
they'd come back
so I wouldn't have
to keep lying.
But I know that's
not right either.
Uh, I suppose what I'm
really trying to say...
[MARIE grunts]
...is that I can't run from
ghosts or things that can
carry the weight of
the past anymore.
And I'm glad that I have
you right here by my side.
Meeting you's changed my life.
It's a wonderful thing.
[MARIE gasps] So the fact
that I'm not a normal girl
actually makes you happy?
You're saying you
like that about me?
[MARIE] You are strange.
I can't deny that about you.
But still, in my heart,
I feel as though I'm nothing
more than a burden.
Because of me,
you've been in too many
dangerous and scary situations.
I know all of it's caused you
so much pain and suffering.
I'd be crying if I were you.
But through all of this,
you've never complained.
Tell me why..w hy are you always
so sweet and kind to me?
A fair question. And normally,
I would be complaining
a little bit, at least.
You think so?
[REN]
Well, can I?
[MARIE gasps]
Of course.
I want you to share all
your feelings with me.
Thank you so much, Marie.
[MARIE gasps]
[REN] There's something you've
made me finally realize.
[REN]
As long as I can remember,
I've always wondered how
I could atone for my sins.
You've given me the answer
I was looking for.
It's not for the dead
to come back to life.
Or to repeat the same
thing for the rest of time.
There's a way to do it that's
only possible because I met you.
And protecting that is the real
reason I was put on this earth
in the first place.
[MARIE]
There really is another way?
[MARIE sobs]
I hope you're right.
Then I shall also be praying
for that wish to come true.
Goddess of twilight.
Eternal feminine that
draws us on high.
♪