[RUSALKA]
Hm... I see.
You'd like to know...
what we're after, right?
[REN] Uh‐huh. And what are
you doing here at my school?
No. Why did you
come to this town?
And that woman. Why did I‐‐?
[grunts]
[REN grunts]
What the hell is
happening around here?
You're planning to
do something, aren't you?
[RUSALKA]
You want to know?
But once you take that step, you
may not be able to come back.
[REN gasps]
[RUSALKA] The truth is,
we aren't certain about you yet.
The information we have
might be incorrect,
and we're in no particular rush.
Enjoy what's left of
your ordinary life
while you still can.
You know how quickly
things can change on you.
But hey. Know what?
I suppose. I could tell
you the tiniest bit.
[RUSALKA]
We're here for a reason.
There's something we want.
For decades, we have bided our
time anticipating this moment,
and now our wish can come true.
[RUSALKA]
No.
[RUSALKA] We're making it.
That's why we came here.
What do you mean, decades?
[RUSALKA] Hasn't anyone
ever told you it was impolite
to discuss a lady's age?
But ja, that is the situation.
This plan of ours is indeed a
very old one, und we could not
care less about how it affects
the people living here now.
Treating your elders
with respect is a virtue,
isn't that right?
[REN grunts]
Shut your mouth.
[RUSALKA]
Huh?
[REN] I don't know what it
is you psychopaths want,
but if you and that albino are
planning to hurt the people
around me, then‐‐!
[gasps]
If we hurt them, then what?
What exactly will you do?
[RUSALKA]
Just so we're clear.
I wield the kind of power that
could crush this entire schüle
in under ten seconds.
[REN gasps]
[RUSALKA] If you want to
continue this conversation,
you'll have to
come up with a way
you could possibly win, boy.
♪
[REN] Hey Kasumi.
What's going on with you?
Anybody in there?
Earth to Kasumi.
Huh? Oh, sorry about that.
I drifted off.
Well, It's time
to get outta here.
Are you going to skip out on
kendo practice this afternoon?
[KASUMI grunts] I'm going.
Just like everyday.
All club activities
have been canceled
because of the murders,
but I've been feeling uneasy,
and a little practice should
take my mind off things.
What are you gonna do, Ren?
Go home and enjoy
the peace and quiet?
No, I'll stick with you.
Walking home
without a bodyguard
is far too dangerous
to even try.
I'd feel so weak,
and vulnerable,
I'd want you there
to protect me.
You'd feel vulnerable?
Doesn't sound like you.
[REN chuckles]
[KASUMI gasps]
Oh, okay.
With a sense of duty,
I will once again give
my all unto the princess!
[REN] As it should be.
Work hard, sweet Prince.
[KASUMI] You're supposed to
be the damsel in distress.
You sound too bossy.
[KASUMI grunts, shouts]
[grunts]
[REN] It's crazy.
Can't believe it's been a week.
[REN]
Damn it!
I'm sorry, Kasumi,
but I can never tell
you what I've done.
[REN gasps]
[chuckles]
[KASUMI shouts]
[REN]
Whoa! Kasumi!
What in the hell do you
think you're doing?
Hey. What's up? I zoned out,
is something wrong?
Well for starters, there's that.
[KASUMI gasps]
Oh, wow. Did I do that?
[REN] Look, I'll clean
everything up here.
You go and change. Then we
can head home for the day.
[LITTLE GIRL A]
A bunch of people already died!
Why else do ya think all
the grown‐ups at school
said we need to go
home in groups?
[LITTLE BOY A]
Yeah, Whatever.
I have better things to do than
hang out with scaredy‐cats.
Buzz off!
[LITTLE GIRL A gasps]
No, I don't think so!
We're not about to let
you go off alone, are we?
Whoa, don't look at me.
This isn't my problem.
[LITTLE GIRL A grunts]
Hey, wait for us!
[LITTLE BOY B]
Stop pulling.
[REN] Hm. Those kids
really remind me
of how we used to
be way back when.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
You, me, and Shirou.
We were just like that.
Shirou would come up with
some crazy plan, as usual.
That I would inevitably
try to talk him out of.
And yet, I would somehow always
get swept up in the craziness.
[BOTH laugh]
[KASUMI] But sometimes, you had
fun with his crazy plans, right?
[REN]
Did I? I mean, I guess so.
[REN] Do you remember
when the girl's shower
at the swimming
pool was broken?
I might have been
responsible for that.
Oh really?
Shirou had gotten into some
weird type of fortunetelling
he found on the net. He told
me to keep an eye out
for the girl with a mole
on her right breast,
and when I found her,
she would be my soul mate.
We climbed into the attic
to get a better view
of our prospective candidates.
And then, I saw her.
It turned out to be you.
You should probably get
that looked at. Boink!
[KASUMI gasps]
There, story time's over.
Now let's get going.
Hey! Pervert!
Now you've made me mad!
You're going to have to make
this up to me, you know!
[REN exhales]
[REN] Seriously? This is
where you wanted to go?
Why'd you make us
change clothes?
[KASUMI] If we went out
in our school uniforms,
we could get in trouble.
Of course I changed.
Is that so crazy?
[REN]
Nah, I guess not.
[KASUMI]
That's right!
And this is your
punishment for peeping!
I'm going to drag you around
here with me all night!
By the way. Thank you, Ren.
[REN]
Uh. For what?
[KASUMI] You were trying to make
me feel better, weren't you?
You've always been like that.
You really care about
the simple things.
You do everything you can
to make sure our little,
ordinary life
doesn't fall apart.
Sometimes I get
worried about you,
'cause I think you do too much.
When it comes to stuff
like that, I know you.
Whenever you get that
look on your face,
it means you're trying to
hide something from me.
I can always tell when you are.
[KASUMI]
This is for you.
I'm a bit early, but it's
your Christmas present!
[REN]
Uh...
[KASUMI] I know you're
not big on jewelry,
But think of it as a symbol.
To remind you, that I am, and
always will be on your side.
You never told me why you
and Shirou had that big fight
in the first place.
You're bottling it
up like always.
[KASUMI] You have a
bad habit of leaving me
completely out of
the loop, Ren.
And, frankly, it's frustrating.
I'm sorry.
So whenever things get hard,
I want you to come right to me.
If you need someone to fight
for you, I'm good at kendo!
Yeah, I know you are.
I want to help you out
in any way I can, Ren.
Always remember that. Always.
[KASUMI] So, is there anything I
can do for you? Anything at all.
[MERCURIUS] Certainly,
but there is no need to ask.
[MERCURIUS]
My luminescent goddess.
I have fashioned
the ultimate necklace
to adorn your beauteous frame.
Now then. Let us begin tonight's
Grand Guignol, shall we?
[VALERIA] Things seem to finally
be set in motion. Come, behold.
Cast your gaze upon
this most holy relic.
You can see the synchronization
has begun as of now.
It already has enough
sacrifices to activate, does it?
[VALERIA] Ja. Und as I'm
sure you'll remember,
this is where Kirc‐heisen fell,
now eleven years ago.
Thus, the souls required
to open the swastika
are already in place.
But at the time,
those conditions had
not yet been met,
und a delay was
deemed necessary.
It's entirely possible
the murders in town
are an attempt to get
the process started again.
All to prepare the stage.
[VALERIA] Though this guillotine
should already be complete
in and of itself. It doesn't
need any lesser souls.
You understand that, don't you?
The power that dwells
inside this relic?
[KEI] In preparation, I shall go
and personally supervise things.
[MARIE]
Now, Cagliostro.
[REN gasps]
[MARIE] Tell me. What do
you want me to do?
[REN] No, you have it wrong.
That isn't my name.
I'm Ren. Ren Fujii.
And what do I call you?
My name is Marie.
I've been waiting here,
for a very long time.
Tell me something.
I need to know.
[inaudible]
[REN gasps]
What was I doing?
Kasumi!
Where are you?!
[REN] Damn it.
This can't be real!
[POLICEMAN A]
Stop! Hold on, young man!
You can't go in there! Hey!
[POLICEMAN A, B]
Hey!
Kasumi... Kasumi!
[REN]
Where are you...? Kasumi!
[REN gasps]
[KEI] What's the matter?
Aren't you going to call her?
[REN gasps]
[KEI] You'd sort things out
quickly that way, but no.
You already know
what the answer is.
What answer? What do you mean?
[KEI]
Once upon a time,
there was a powerful
mage who had gone mad.
He secretly controlled a
certain nation's army,
and changed them
into inhuman monsters.
The man's name was Karl Krafft.
His second name was Mercurius.
[KEI]
Did you know?
The symbol of Mercury.
It's a two‐headed snake.
The snakes wrap in from both
sides of the central stave.
One decoy, one real.
[KEI]
The purpose of a side character,
is often to prepare the stage
for the main character.
That girl did everything she
could, and all for your sake.
But even if she were killed
by someone before her time,
she could be replaced.
[REN]
Shut up.
[KEI] Of course, I'm sure
you already knew all this.
Isn't that why you
subconsciously chased after her?
That was how Bey and Malleus
got their hands on you.
Now, there's one question
I don't have an answer to.
[REN gasps]
[KEI] Your little friend that
you were with that night.
If she'd been caught and killed,
what would you have done?
I told you to shut up!
What are you even talking about?
I don't know what you're‐‐
[KEI] Stop lying.
We both know the truth.
We have arrived. And we're
prepared for total war.
I'd gain some power soon,
if I were you.
[KEI] Or else the
game can't begin.
Then everything she's
done will be for naught.
[REN gasps]
I want to help you out
in any way I can, Ren.
[KASUMI] So, is there anything I
can do for you? Anything at all.
[REN gasps]
[KEI]
Very well. I'll be watching.
Do your best.
[REN gasps]
[REN pants]
[REN shouts]
[phone rings]
What the hell is going on?
[gasps]
[REN gasps]
[KASUMI sighs]
Ren. You're here.
Kasumi. What're you
doing here, you idiot?
[KASUMI RECORDING]
Hey‐a! This is Kasumi!
I'm a bit busy at the moment,
but if you need something,
please leave a message!
[REN]
This can't be right.
Did you do all of
this because of me?
Then this isn't
your fault at all!
[REN] I won't let anyone
blame you for this!
I can vouch for you!
You aren't the kind of person
who's even capable of this!
[REN]
So let's just go home.
And we'll be done with it,
like it's a bad dream.
[MERCURIUS] Rejoice, for
this merely marks the ending
of the prologue.
[MERCURIUS] An opera,
offered up unto my dear friend,
and my beloved goddess.
Sing, dear child, for you are
the featured player in this
season's company.
I know all that was, is,
and shall come to pass.
My universe eternally
and equally repeating.
A perpetually recurring cycle.
Déjà vu crashing like waves
on an infinite ocean.
All I yearn for is
an unknown moment.
Grant me the salvation
of a grand finale
I have not foreseen.
This is the one opera
that you were always
destined to sing, child.
For you know that what has been
lost can never be regained,
and no amount of wishing
will change that.
[REN]
I've heard enough!
[REN groans]
I haven't lost anything yet
that I can't still save!
I'll protect it all,
starting now!
Just don't drag people that
aren't involved into this!
But I am involved.
Why would you say something
so insensitive? I hate it.
You really hurt my feelings.
So what?
Am I really that oblivious about
everything that's happening?
Have I been getting
in your way,
or pulling your attention from
more important things?
Am I totally useless as
far as you're concerned?
Well? Do you honestly believe
I can't do anything?
There's got to be
something I can do
to prove how helpful I can be!
It's beyond frustrating.
It makes me feel so small.
So I did what I could.
Did my best. My best.
To help you.
But it was such a tough job,
I didn't know where to start.
I was completely clueless.
And then I focused on
it as hard as I could.
[REN grunts]
[KASUMI]
And this.
This seemed like the
best way for me to help.
[grunts]
[KASUMI]
Are you proud?
I really hope I can
help you out again soon.
[REN shouts]
You drained it. But why, Ren?
You should know that by now!
[REN]
Because I care,
and I don't want you to have
to keep doing this any longer!
This thing belongs
to me, Kasumi.
So it responds to my words
before anyone else, even you.
Though, it seems to have the
wrong idea about what I want.
But you don't need it
to be useful to me,
you're always helping me out!
[REN] Without you. I would have
come unglued a long time ago.
[REN]
That's why...
...I need you to stay where
things are still bright.
Or else, I'm afraid I might
get lost in the dark.
And I apologize for
being so selfish,
but I promise that
I'll come back for you.
So wait for me.
[gasps]
Ren.
[KASUMI]
You're right about one thing.
You are totally selfish.
And yet, I stick by your side.
I must be a special
kind of idiot.
[VALERIA gasps]
Could this be?
[chuckles] This pain
I feel. It's delectable!
I can sense Lord
Heydrich is nearby.
[chuckling continues]
It seems the first swastika
has already opened,
hasn't it, Father?
[VALERIA]
Ja. Only seven others remain.
Und what of the
investigation I requested?
Is it complete, Spinne?
Indeed, und the findings were
precisely as you expected.
Johann's alive, und he's close.
Very close.
[VALERIA laughs]
Is that so? How marvelous!
Of course, now I see it!
The vice commander's
approach is truly inspired!
What a mad genius!
[laughs]
Then, that's it.
I'll need to hurry to set
my next move in action.
I'm going head to head
against the mind of a devil.
[SPINNE]
Well, from my perspective,
you aren't that far from
being a devil yourself.
Get some rest, Kasumi.
I'll take it from here.
I swear I'll defeat them.
♪