[REN] I've had the same dream
every night. Without fail.
[REN] And when I wake up,
someone is dead.
Beheaded. As if
by a guillotine.
That's just crazy.
[KASUMI sighs] How'd I
know you'd be up here?
Uh...
Come on. Just because you
don't want to go to class,
doesn't mean you
don't have to go.
Light blue. And white.
[REA, KASUMI]
Hm?
[REN]
Thank you.
[camera snaps]
[REA, KASUMI gasp]
[KASUMI growls] What the hell do
you think you're doing? Asshole!
♪
[KASUMI] Ugh! You're perverted,
rude, and worse, stupid!
You're just awful!
You should be ashamed.
Enough already, you've been
chewing me out for blocks.
That's what I was greeted with
when I looked up so I took
the opportunity to
immortalize the moment.
Oh yeah? Well, I took the
opportunity to kick your ass.
You did delete
the picture, didn't you?
Probably.
What do you mean by "probably?"
[WOMAN A]
Pervert!
[VALERIA grunts]
No. Forgive me.
You have it all wrong, miss.
I mean you no harm.
I merely needed direct‐‐
[WOMAN A] No! I told you
to keep away from me!
‐‐[thudding]
‐‐[VALERIA grunting]
[REN] Wow. I suppose
we should expect to see
more of this kind of
stuff at a time like this.
Being approached
by a suspicious man,
with all these murders happening
in town. I can't blame her.
Hey, are you all right?
Whoa, hang on!
[VALERIA grunts]
Do you need some help?
A‐Apologies.
I'm okay... now.
You're really tall.
Come on. Get out
of the man's way.
Pardon me, do you think you
could tell me which way
to go to get to the church?
[KASUMI] Hey, Father,
do you know Rea?
She's a friend of ours from
school who stays at the church.
[VALERIA] Ja, but I haven't
been here in almost a decade.
The town's changed
so much since then.
I imagine she has too.
I can't tell you how relieving
it is to hear that dear Theresia
has such good friends at
school as the two of you kids!
Out of all the upperclassmen,
Himuro's always been
the coolest to us.
When we first met her she told
us to just call her Rea,
but I guess "Theresia"
must be her real name?
I think she's actually,
what, a quarter Japanese?
[VALERIA] Indeed! And I
was the one who named her.
[KASUMI]
Oh, that's cool.
So that means you're sort
of like Rea's dad, huh?
[VALERIA laughs] Oh my,
how very embarrassing!
But, ja, I suppose
that's accurate.
I changed her diaper
countless times,
and gave her baths as well.
And I also made a promise
to do everything in my
power to protect her!
I do it all for
the sake of love!
Theresia! Oh!
Mein kleines knuddelbar!
Daddy dearest has finally
made his way back to you!
[REA]
Creepy.
[VALERIA grunts]
It's time for you to hit
the bricks. Or better yet, die.
[VALERIA shouts] Theresia!
When did your tender eyes
grow as cold as a graveyard?
[VALERIA] No. I like them.
The new look works!
[KASUMI]
Okay.
[REN] What are we supposed
to do with this weirdo?
[RIZA]
Ahem.
It's been a while since
our last meeting,
and though hard to believe,
the subtext of your speech has
grown even more disturbing.
So, Father Trifa, are you
trying to get banished
to the Mexican
countryside again?
[VALERIA gasps]
Riza?
You two must be
famished after dealing
with the Father's nonsense.
As an apology, I'd love to
whip up some food for you!
[REN] It's starting to
get late, so we'd better go.
Thank you for the
delicious meal.
[RIZA] And thank you
for your help today.
Father Trifa can be
quite a handful.
[REN]
Glad to help.
Especially when I get
repaid with such great food.
[RIZA]
You think so? But still,
I'm sure it can't be as good
as Kasumi's home cooking.
Nah. She can be kinda
lazy sometimes,
and she doesn't make
anything special, so‐‐
[RIZA] Uh‐uh! You shouldn't
say that so cavalierly.
And if trying to flatter someone
is your actual intention,
you need to pick a
different someone than me.
For example.
Tell me, Ren. You don't know
Rea's birthday, do you?
It's coming up soon
on the twenty‐fifth.
She was born on Christmas Day!
Wow, is that true?
Riza, please mind
your own business.
I don't want to hear
you talking about it.
[RIZA]
Ja, ja, I understand. I'm sorry!
She's so shy, it's adorable.
[REN grunts]
So, yeah. Christmas.
I'd like to maybe
get you a present,
if that's okay with you.
Sure. Thanks a lot.
That's so sweet.
[REN]
Uh?
We should get married.
[VALERIA] Theresia! What did
you just say, young lady?
That's too forward!
[RIZA] She has to
grow up sometime,
so just knock it off!
I had a great time!
See you tomorrow, Rea!
[REA]
Yeah. Take care.
[VALERIA]
Fujii, wait.
[REN]
Hm?
Pardon us. I had a question I
wanted to ask him in private.
[KASUMI]
Mm‐hm.
[VALERIA] You and Miss Ayase.
Were you both born here?
[REN] No, we weren't.
Why do you ask?
Ah. You must be worried
about the recent spate
of murders occurring in town.
And you think we should move
out to the country until this
all blows over, don't you?
Ja, am I that easy to read?
And what about your parents,
Mister Fujii?
My parents?
[REN]
Well...
My mother and father
both passed away
when I was a still
a little boy.
Kasumi's family took me in after
that and raised me like a son.
And sadly, just a
couple of years ago,
we lost Kasumi's father.
[VALERIA]
Oh, I see. My condolences.
Now then.
I can only imagine how badly
you'd like to meet them.
Do you mean meet the dead?
[KASUMI] It's freezing
out here. Can we go?!
That's impossible.
Once you die, it's over.
You don't get to come back.
That's why the here and
now is so important,
and I think anyone who can't
understand that is crazy.
[VALERIA] Of course.
You're absolutely right.
That does sound crazy,
doesn't it?
Did you hear that? Leonhart?
[KEI]
Yes.
[VALERIA] And what do you think
of that young man's opinion?
I'm not bothered. A person is
free to have their thoughts.
Ah. In other words, you didn't
find what he said upsetting?
[laughs] How frightening.
I joke, of course.
But then, Shambhala
has always been a place
where the crazy are
born and converge.
Correct or not, if someone
falls into its grand net,
they'll be tested.
I'll allow you to make the
decisions on the ground,
for now.
And I will be able to
adapt as I see fit?
Whatever you command of me,
O Priest of the Grail.
Huh. Oh, my, what do
we have here?
I suspect you might be another
toy of our vice commander's.
You poor thing.
[REN grunts]
[grunting contiues]
[footsteps]
[WOMAN A pants]
[WOMAN A gasps]
[REN gasps]
[REN gasps, vomits]
[pants] No way. This can't
be happening! I didn't...
It wasn't me. It wasn't me!
I didn't do it!
[WILHELM] Your taste in prey
is excellent. I am impressed.
[REN]
H‐Huh?
[WILHELM]
Looks like your reflexes
are rather sharp as well.
I am extremely fortunate
to have found you.
[REN gasps]
You going to just
stand around staring?
You are able to speak,
aren't you?
[REN gasps]
[RUSALKA]
Ha!
[REN shouts]
Hey! Trying to run isn't
going to get you very far.
[REN gasps]
[RUSALKA] My, my! This little
one is quite interesting!
It's almost as if he's actually
trying to resist my Nachzehrer.
[WILHELM]
So? What do we do, Malleus?
Want to play with him?
[RUSALKA]
Ah! Hold on.
You are the one that Mercurius
sent to us, are you not?
Did he give you some
kind of message?
Hu, what?
[RUSALKA]
Does Karl Krafft ring a bell?
The hooded,
mercurian mystery man?
You've seen him, haven't you?
And you did this because
he compelled you to.
[REN] No! I don't know anything!
I didn't kill her!
[WILHELM]
Buffoon.
[REN grunts]
[WILHELM] I'm only going to
ask you this one more time.
You sliced her head off,
did you not?
Because that shitheel
Mercurius told you to.
[REN grunts, shouts]
[WILHELM] Ja, that's right,
you know how I like to have fun!
And if you're faking it,
I'm sold anyway.
But I'm not the patient type,
I get bored quite easily.
And if I think you're holding
out on me, then well,
I might not wait
for your answer.
[shouts]
Get your filthy claws
off me, you vermin.
[REN grunts]
[WILHELM]
Last chance.
You murdered her,
isn't that right?
[REN groans]
I'm getting sick of this.
Okay, Malleus.
I'm going to kill him.
[sighs] How did I know
that you would say that?
Fine. Do as you will.
Always so predictable.
I suppose torture is
too delicate of a task
to expect out of you.
But please, do try not to
mangle the head too much.
I should still be able
to use it, if I have to.
Sure. I'll see if I
can restrain myself.
[REN] What is this?
What's happening?
I'm so confused.
What's going on?
[REN] I killed that woman?
But why? I don't understand.
[REN] And who the hell
are these people?
What do they want from me?
Time to die.
[REN]
He's gonna kill me.
No... No!
Show me the path I was
meant to tread upon.
[REN gasps]
Oh?
[RUSALKA]
Maybe you do have a tiny bit
of survival instinct in you.
But you should put
in more effort,
like you actually have
something to live for.
Tell me. You went to visit the
church earlier, didn't you?
[REN gasps]
Did you have some fun?
Did it make you happy?
[RUSALKA] I suspect you care
for those friends of yours.
Stop it... Stop it.
Don't you dare.
So maybe I'll kill them
when we're through.
Shut up!
[shouts]
[REN groans]
[chuckles]
[REN grunts]
[WILHELM] Looks like you aren't
interested in running anymore,
but that's not enough!
Show me your power!
[REN grunts]
Power? The hell?
[WILHELM] Don't worry.
I'll take it easy on you.
I won't even use my weapon.
Hell, I'll only use one hand!
And you can use
whatever you want!
If I'm a good enough sportsman
to give you this much
of a break, and you
still don't satisfy me,
I'll have no choice but to
wipe this town off the map!
[gasps]
The Fourth of the
Longinus Dreizehn Orden's
black round table. I am
Wilhelm Ehrenburg.
A.k.a. Kazikli Bey!
This is the part where
you say your name.
Don't you know how to fight?
You wanna know my name, asshole?
Then make me tell you!
[shouts]
[REN groans]
[WILHELM chuckles] You're
messing with me, aren't you?
Is that really all
you've got, kid?
[WILHELM shouts]
[REN, WILHELM grunting]
[gasps]
[WILHELM laughs]
[REN] I wished that I could
make time stand still.
Because I didn't
want my meaningless,
everyday life to end.
I wanted to protect it.
To keep going.
No matter how many
times it repeated.
[MERCURIUS] I've fallen
madly in love with you.
And I swear to
release you, darling.
Grant me a finale that
I have not foreseen.
Dearest Marguerite.
My goddess. My beloved.
[REN shouts]
Bey. Explain what's
going on here.
Are you really asking
me that right now?
Can't you tell for yourself?
I'm testing this one's strength.
Und if he just dies here,
he's obviously not who
we were looking for.
Then, he's passed the
first round of testing.
He's survived this long,
which is good enough.
And this matter does fall
under my jurisdiction.
You must not
disobey my orders.
We understand
one another, don't we?
[grunts] Ten four, roger.
Signal's loud and clear, miss.
But one quick side note.
Which is?
[WILHELM]
It's simple!
Where the hell do you get off
thinking you can touch me
with your filthy little
monkey paws, you tramp?
[KEI, REN grunt]
What the hell are
you doing? Fool.
That's supposed to be
my line, you upstart bitch!
You're just a
pathetic baby ape
who hasn't lived
a quarter century.
You think you can talk
to me like an equal?
[WILHELM chuckles]
I get it. You're horny!
The action get you going?
You two filthy little
monkeys can't wait
to bang each others'
brains out, isn't that it?
Go ahead and get started,
I enjoy watching!
I'll kill you.
[WILHELM]
Just try it.
[RUSALKA] This is the kind
of problem you get
when working
with barbarians.
Apologies.
I had hoped to be able to watch
you a little while longer
than this, but that's quite
enough for today.
I must stop these two
before things get messy.
We shall have to pick up where
we left off another time.
It's been a lot of fun!
[REN gasps]
[REN]
What the hell? So weird.
Doesn't make any sense.
[REN]
A dream? It has to be.
[REN grunts] Just tell
me it's a dream, dammit!
Can't let anyone
know about this.
[REN]
Kasumi. Rea.
[KASUMI] Hmmm. No fever,
but you're not lookin' so good.
Do you wanna stay home?
No. I'll go.
I just need a little time to get
ready, so go ahead without me.
Okay, but don't push yourself.
I'm shocked you're still
interested in going to school,
that's rare for you.
Well, I guess we'll meet
up in a bit, okay?
[grunts]
I used to hate school.
But last night changed a
whole bunch of stuff for me.
[REN grunts] Right now,
I want to go back to things
that feel normal more
than anything else.
[REN] Uh. Hey, Rea.
Are you leaving?
Uh‐huh. Are you just now
getting here or something?
[REN] Oh. Uh, yeah.
Rough morning.
Well, be careful, okay?
[gasps]
[RUSALKA] Hallo. Did you
sleep well, my friend?
We meet again, Ren Fujii.
My name is Rusalka
Maria Schwägerin.
nd the girl with the
scary face is Kei Sakurei.
This schüle of yours is
rather lovely. I like it here.
We're classmates now,
so let's try to be friends.
Doesn't that sound pleasant?
Just you,
Kasumi Ayase, und us.
I'm certain we're going
to have a spectacular time.
♪