Briah Vanaheimr.
Goldene Schwan Lohengrin!
Briah Midgard Volsunga Saga!
[gasps]
Auf wiedersehen. This will
be the last time we meet.
[VALERIA groans]
[REA gasps]
[VALERIA gasps]
Please. Theresia. Remember this.
I've always loved you
like my own daughter.
This is punishment for my sins.
The children I couldn't save!
No, Father! Please don't go!
[WOLFGANG] I'm afraid
we've run out of time.
Lord Heydrich is
calling me home for now.
[WOLFGANG]
We'll pick back up in Valhalla!
Be sure and tell all your
friends to be there.
[REN]
Wait!
At last. The Dies Irae
is truly beginning.
♪
[KEI grunts]
Where am I?
School, unfortunately.
Pretty sure we're
in your homeroom.
Haven't been here lately.
Well, I think classes are
gonna be canceled for a while.
[gasps]
[KEI]
No.
[SHIROU] I reckon it's been
about 20 hours or so
since me and Ren met up.
Not that we can check the time,
since clocks and
cellphones quit workin'.
But it feels just
shy of a day, to me.
[REN]
We're the only ones left.
[REN] Everybody else
had their souls taken.
[KEI gasps]
[REN] I'm pretty sure I know
why you were left alive.
So they can sacrifice you.
They're keeping you to
open up the last swastika.
Those are your friends.
If I were you, I'd be telling
us everything you know.
Yeah. Very well, then.
Something seemed off,
so I followed the father.
[SHIROU]
Soldiers in Valhalla, eh?
Sounds like immortality
with a major catch.
I can't believe I've
been such an idiot.
At this point, maybe the best
course of action would just be
to call it a loss
and commit suicide.
Yeah, 'cause there's nothing
left for us here, anyway.
[REN]
No way in hell.
[KEI gasps] Why? You do
realize there's no point.
Do you think we have
a chance against them?
[KEI] I don't have a
reason to keep fighting.
There's nobody left
I want to protect.
No wishes that could
come true. I'm done.
[SHIROU gasps]
[REN] I won't force
you to do anything.
And if you're really ready
to throw in the towel,
then that choice is
entirely up to you.
I understand why
you'd feel that way.
All I ask is that you don't
waste any of the time
I have left arguing
or fighting with me.
Stay out of my way
and do your own thing.
[KEI]
So you're leaving?
[REN] Yeah. It may surprise you,
but I've still got hope.
And honestly, I worked my ass
off to make sure this wasn't
how everything ended up.
I'd thought that you felt the
exact same way. Was I wrong?
[gasps]
[REN] I may not like you,
but I gotta admit.
I can respect all the work that
you put in to try and make
your dream come true.
[KEI gasps, whimpers]
What's your deal?
Fujii. Why the hell are
you saying this to me?
If you don't like me,
that's okay.
You'd be better off if
you just forgot about me.
I made up my mind
a long time ago
that being alone was
in my best interest.
But you're such
a stupid dreamer
that you almost made
me start to hope
for things I know
will never happen.
[KEI sobs] I fought so hard
for things to be different.
You can "respect that"?
No matter what you do, Fujii,
you have an uncanny ability
for making me angry.
I hate your guts.
[REN] Does that mean you don't
wanna come to the party?
Because once all of
this crap is over,
we're gonna have one hell of
a celebration up on the roof.
And I think you'll have fun,
even if I am there.
I mean, it's a given
we're gonna fight
with Shirou and
Honjou egging us on.
There's no doubt my
dear old friend Kasumi
is gonna be in your corner.
She always wants
to argue with me.
Probably because she's
got nothing better to do.
Rea will be neutral, of course.
Off at a safe distance,
so she can judge all of
us equally as harsh.
Since Marie doesn't have much
experience with knuckleheads
like us, she'll be confused,
but still entertained.
Think of all the fun we can
have when this part is done.
I don't know about you,
but that sounds like a reason
to keep fighting to me.
What? The hell are
you talking about?
Don't be ridiculous.
Besides, I don't belong in your
little best friends' club.
No one would have a good time.
Yeah, you kinda do have the
tendency to be a huge killjoy.
[gasps]
[REN]
Now, don't pout.
I'm not pouting!
[REN grunts] Well, the bad guys
aren't gonna beat themselves,
so are you coming or not?
[KEI grunts]
[sighs]
Where did he run off to?
[KEI grunts]
[REN]
Uh...?
[KEI]
Thank you Fujii.
[SHIROU]
And... cut!
[MARIE] What's going on?
Care to explain yourself.
Ren, dear?
Wait. It's not what
it looks like!
[SHIROU]
Naughty boy! How could you?
It's bad enough that
you were ignoring your
sweet little girlfriend,
who was going out of her way
to make sure that we all
had something to eat.
And then you made it
worse with adultery?
No way!
Is that so? You're blushing.
Why's that?
Uh... Well, I...
It's his fault, not mine.
Fujii just started being
weird for no reason.
What do you mean by that?
No lie, it sounds like
something you'd do.
Well then. Kei is right.
It's your fault, you bad boy.
Oh come on Marie. Listen.
Don't you think arguing about
this now is gonna tire us out?
Ah! I don't get tired!
You're the one who does that!
That's why I was
trying to help you.
I wanted to find food
to restore your health.
But it looks like you
have plenty of energy.
I leave the room, and you do
this adult thing with her.
This... Uh...
Adultery?
Oui, you did adultery!
[KEI, REN]
It's not adultery!
Wow! You guys work
well together!
You speak and move as one?
Can ya give me a break?
Well, don't you have
something to say?
[REN chuckels]
This is not a laughing matter!
Can't you tell how angry I am?
[REN]
I'm really sorry, Marie.
[ALL chuckle]
No, but seriously. I'll try
harder to avoid bad influences.
What's that mean?
Does that make you feel
any better about things?
Oui. I feel much better.
And so will you after
eating some of this food.
A Rea special.
[SHIROU]
Ew...
Yuck.
Is the food not good?
No, it's delicious.
[SHIROU]
I'll bet. Here ya go.
Okay?
[SHIROU]
We'll drink to our loyalty.
I know it's not sake',
but it's all we've got.
[MARIE]
Our loyalty?
[REN]
I get it.
[SHIROU] To show we'll
be there for each other.
Now take a big swig!
Alright.
But don't take this to mean that
I'm looking to die with you
two idiots, you understand?
Point taken. Down the hatch.
How 'bout none of us die.
Does that work? Yeah?
Oui. I will drink to that.
And we must all make a vow to
meet here again. Once it's done.
Sounds good. I'll be here.
[REN] We'll win. No matter
what it takes!
Always gotta show‐off.
[MARIE] After this,
we'll have our victory party!
Tell me this. What does the word
victory mean to each one of you?
Victory is that which shines
majestically from up on high.
Victory is something
that you look back on,
rather than forward to.
I look at victory as the
ultimate climax
that one can reach.
Samiel. If it
shines majestically
in the highest heavens,
Then it stands to reason that
one would get
burned pursuing it.
Much like young Icarus.
Ja. We long for it,
because we can't reach it.
What I desired was only to be
burned by its glorious light.
Und the mark it left on me
I wear proudly as
a badge of honor.
It sounds like you're talking
about being in love to me.
I never knew you
could be so cute.
But I think I like this softer,
more feminine side
of you, Samiel.
You freak.
Well, Schreiber. Explain your
thoughts on victory.
Your response earlier
was rather puzzling.
Would you please be so
kind as to enlighten me?
I'll try my lord.
All my life, I've acted first
und thought about it later.
But when I look back, I see
footprints leading to victory.
I've only looked back und
found myself to be the loser
once in my life. It won't
happen again, because I
swore absolute loyalty to
you after that, Lord Heydrich.
Und now I share all
my victories with you.
Now I see. I suppose that
explains what you meant.
Machina, you referred to
it as "the climax," ja?
By that, you mean "the end".
Throughout history,
the stories of heroes
often end with their death.
That is what you wish for?
The ultimate battlefield,
und the ultimate rival.
Two crucial components for one
to attain the "hero's end"
that you desire. Very good.
Ja, very good, indeed.
The wait is over.
Now that time is upon us.
Onward!
Wait. Stop this.
[REA]
Please... I beg you.
[REINHARD]
What is it?
[REA gasps]
You wish to speak,
honored child?
I will listen.
You will?
[REA whimpers]
I want to know something.
I want to know if you were
really Isaak's father!
Is that why Riza was
so afraid of him?
She thought he'd turn out
to be a monster like you.
I need to know the
truth about myself!
I don't know who, or what, I am!
[REINHARD chuckles]
[REA gasps]
Oh, Theresia. Lovely child.
You possess many qualities
that remind me of Isaak.
But I am afraid that I do
not know who that thing's
father was, liebchen.
You do!
[REINHARD]
How very rude.
You may not believe this, but I
am not the sort of man who
neglects his familial duties.
If I could answer you, I would.
Okay.
Isaak was an abomination.
But I want you to know this:
I love everything equally.
If that is all you have to say,
I shall take my leave.
[REA gasps]
So then, you won't ask
what victory means to me?
[REA]
I pity you, really.
Because you have so much
power but so little insight
into the world that all of
it is just wasted on you.
Loving everything the same
is no different than saying
there's nothing that
you think is special.
I think victory is impossible
for a person like you.
Chirp away little bird.
You make sweet sounds.
Full of passion.
Both Karl und I are quite
lacking in that aspect.
You pity me, do you, child?
Such honest words from a
beautiful girl like you never
fails to stir my heart.
For that, I thank you.
So what is your victory?
You wanna know?
To be surrounded
by everyone I love.
Unlike you, there're people I
value more than anything else
in the world.
[REINHARD] Is that so?
You will meet Isaak quite soon.
I pray that fortune smiles
down on you, Theresia.
[REA grunts]
[REINHARD]
Let us begin.
Drink deep, und test the limits
of your maddening desires!
My lord. We do so to your glory.
We'll feast on their souls
till there's no one left.
Our glorious crusade
will end tonight.
We shall taste victory!
[REINHARD]
This world is beautiful.
And thus I've no choice
but to destroy it.
Erase the canvas before me.
Tonight I shall finally
be rid of this Déjà vu
und establish an absolute,
unchanging order.
[REINHARD] Come. You und
I will fight one‐on‐one.
I believe this is your last
chance at salvation, ja?
[REA]
Fujii... Yusa...
Isaak. Where are you hiding?
Show yourself! Isaak!
[ISAAK]
Theresia! Theresia!
Welcome, my precious Sonnenkind.
I'm so glad you could join me.
[REA gasps]
[ISAAK] I am Isaak.
The very heart of Gladsheim.
[ISAAK groans]
[REN grunts]
To put it mildly,
this freakin' sucks.
What the hell do we do now?
[KEI] Please forgive my
rudeness in not introducing
myself sooner, Lord Heydrich.
I'm Kei Sakurai.
I was discovered a few years
ago by the grail himself.
Chosen to take Kircheisen's
place and serve the order.
[REINHARD] Hm. I am
aware of the succession.
Und you will soon take your
place as the eighth sacrifice.
Your loyalty pleases me.
[KEI chuckles]
First, let me take this
opportunity to make it clear
that I'm not with
these delinquents.
But I must clarify
something else.
Never once did I swear my
loyalty to you or to the
damned Black Round Table!
So you would pass
up the opportunity
to help me remake
this world?
[KEI] Why would I help the man
who I hate more than anything?
You turned my
family into slaves.
You robbed us all
of a normal life.
But we still believed that
someday we'd know freedom.
We had hope. It drove us.
But it wore away our souls.
[KEI]
I'm the last of my clan.
So it's up to me to make my
family's wish come true at last.
Which means... I must
strike you down!
End this curse for good!
All I ever wanted was to
get back the people I loved.
The time I'd missed.
But my foolish desire made
me blind to all the evils
I surrounded myself with.
I confess to that sin!
And now, it's my duty
to atone for it.
I don't long for Valhalla.
I'll use everything in my
power to make sure you die!
What a sad little girl.
But I shall swallow
every bit of your pain.
Your weary, tormented soul
will find eternal comfort
as one of my Einherjar.
I'm supposed to believe
everything I've lost is there?
Indeed. All that you
desperately long for.
[REN]
You liar!
[gasps]
You're promising something
that you could never give.
You don't have the power to
grant her wish, even if she
does give up her soul to be
your mindless slave in hell!
[SHIROU] That's the dumbest
thing I've ever heard.
Let's go!
[ALL shout]
Ah! At long last,
the Emanation has begun.
♪