[ISAAK]
Mutter... Mutter.
[GIRL A]
Mutter.
Huh? It's Mutter!
Hallo, Mutter!
[CHILDREN chatter]
Mutter! Look here!
I did it, Mutter!
My darlings are all so clever.
Keep up the
good work, liebchens.
[gasps]
Ja, Mutter.
[BOTH]
We promise!
I don't feel good.
[coughs]
[CHILDREN coughing]
[RIZA gasps]
[gasps]
[ISAAK]
Mutter.
[GIRL A]
I love you.
[BOY A, B]
I love you mutter.
[heartbeat]
[ISAAK]
Mutter.
[cries]
[RIZA gasps]
[grunts]
[FEMALE NURSES gasp]
[RIZA gasps]
[ISAAK]
Mutter.
[RIZA]
No!
[footsteps]
[RIZA chuckles]
♪
[MAN A] What the hell is
going on in this town?
These cases are making
less and less sense.
[MAN B] You can say that again.
Anything from forensics?
[MAN A] They say the blood
is definitely human,
and we're not talking
about a dozen people.
There's gotta be
enough blood here
for at least a
hundred murders.
But all the bodies
this blood came from
are nowhere to be found.
Almost as if they
had been... eaten.
[MAN C] So for now, the girl
we found at the scene
is our only real lead?
[MAN A] Afraid so. She's got
a lot of questions to answer.
So keep an eye on her.
[MAN C]
And what about the other one?
She said she didn't
know anything.
or the time being,
we'll let her rest.
But make sure to keep
an eye on that girl, too.
[MAN C]
Understood.
[LOTUS'S GRANDFATHER]
You ungrateful fool!
You'd rather be a soldier?
Don't you care about breaking
from our family's duty?
Murdering people? It's all
the same, either way.
So, I'd rather take on a new
job that I can be proud of.
It's definitely preferable to
taking over a family business
like ours.
How dare you!
I hope you die out on the
battlefield, you pompous ass!
That was it. I've never
seen grandpa so mad.
So, I don't really have
anything to go back to
when this is all over.
Well. I don't regret
my decision.
Now then, it's your
turn for story time.
[MICHAEL chuckles]
[LOTUS]
Tell me.
[LOTUS grunts]
[MICHAEL shouts]
[LOTUS, MICHAEL]
Mein Kamaraden.
[REN grunts]
[REN gasps]
[door clatters]
[REN]
Mm?
What are you doing?
Just enjoying the view?
You must be cold.
Then again, I'm guessing you
probably don't get sick.
Was there something
you wanted to see?
Oui. The roof. You said
how much you liked it.
Did I?
[MARIE]
You did. Don't you remember?
The school roof is where
the group always met up.
I'm getting some practice in.
Then I'll be ready to
become the fifth member.
I thought spending time here
would get me used to being
up so high.
[gasps]
I wonder what kind
of conversations
we'll have on the roof.
What will we do, what new
things will we try together?
I'm getting excited
just thinking about it!
I can't wait for us
to start having fun!
This place is tres magnific, no?
You wanna be the
fifth member?
Not sure we have
that number anymore.
Why the hell didn't Honjou tell
me that the club was one of the
swastikas when we talked?
There's no way she didn't know.
Shirou must've
made her, but why?
Did she want to
kill herself? Idiot!
Because of that, they're both‐‐
[MARIE]
It's okay.
[REN gasps]
They're both still alive.
I'm sure of it!
[REN chuckles]
[REN] Oh yeah?
What makes you say that?
Because I've come
to realize that
I've never really
seen you smiling.
instead, you have
such a sad expression.
Almost always,
ever since we met.
It hurts me to see you
looking so morose, Ren.
It is as if you are telling me,
you wish we had never met.
It's not that.
[MARIE]
So I made the decision,
that I'd work hard
to make you happy.
So please, don't worry.
You can cheer up, Ren,
because nothing sad will happen.
And if it starts to get that
way, I won't let it keep going.
You see?
[REN chuckles]
Yeah, you may be right.
When something happens, I always
focus on all the bad parts.
I mean, If Kasumi was able
to survive the attack,
maybe they were able
to survive it, too!
Oui, try to look on
the bright side!
Listen, Ren, I've changed.
I'm not the same as I
was when I first arrived.
It's strange to say that
about oneself, but I can tell.
Ever since the golden one
skewered me through the chest,
I've become something different.
Sort of like waking up.
[MARIE] And since then it has
felt like I can understand you
better than ever before.
I can say the same about Kasumi,
as well as both Rea and Shirou.
Almost everyone I've met.
I've had to deal with so much
sadness but there's happiness
in there as well.
And that's the part that's
so dazzlingly bright.
It's become dear to me.
But, do you think
this change is bad?
[REN]
Huh?
Since it came from
something he did to me,
do I need to throw it all away?
That would make me very sad.
I'm afraid to lose it.
No, Marie.
[REN] It isn't something bad.
Hold on to it.
I don't know what Reinhard
and Mercurius are thinking,
or if what you feel has
anything to do with them.
But what I do know, is that I
like you much better this way.
I want you to stay like this.
So if what you're feeling
is important to you,
then you shouldn't
doubt those instincts.
What I want for us, is for
us both to never feel
like we need to hide
who we really are.
Do you remember
talking about that?
I do, and you're right!
I'll try, I promise to.
[footsteps]
[REN gasps]
[REN] So that's the
look you went with?
[RIZA gasps]
That outfit doesn't work
for you. Not in the least.
[RIZA] The only one who
thinks that... is you, boy.
Are you sure you really
wanna do this, sister?
I'm not letting you through,
so you should give
up now and go home.
[RIZA] What about you?
Will you leave, Fujii?
Why don't you take Kasumi
while you still can,
and run far from here? I cannot
let you take anyone else,
but I can allow you to take her.
[REN gasps]
We aren't going anywhere.
So I suggest we try to
do this the easy way.
For Rea's sake,
I'm telling you to turn
around and get out of here!
[RIZA gasps]
What kind of world are you
going to leave for her?
Do you honestly think
she'd be happy
to have a killer in her family?
[RIZA gasps]
Thank you, Fujii.
I'm flattered you
think so highly of me,
und care about Rea.
But I fear I cannot.
[RIZA] I cannot afford myself
the luxury of compassion.
To be kind, like you are.
This is the kind of woman I am.
Rea knows, und expects
nothing more.
She dislikes me at best.
Und I am frightened of her.
[REN gasps]
Leonhart.
[KEI shouts]
[REN gasps]
[RIZA]
Stall him for me, won't you?
I will open the swastika here.
[REN gasps]
Understood.
[KEI shouts]
You are naïve.
Und far too optimistic.
It's hard to believe you're
a descendant of Karl Krafft.
For what it's worth, you were
a fine young man, Ren Fujii.
But here, things will
end horribly for you.
Whatever made you think I
would come here alone?
You won't be able to
protect anyone like that.
Hold on!
Don't look to her, Fujii.
First you have to get past me.
[REN grunts]
[KEI] I'll fight with my
true strength this time,
so that I don't bore you.
Your true strength?
Correct. Don't you
remember my tutoring?
There are different levels of
ability based on our experience.
First activity,
and then formation.
Those are the only
levels you've achieved.
But I rise above.
Creation level.
Remake the rules.
The ability to form a world
which realizes my
soul's desires.
I decided, Fujii. That I
would never forget my vow,
so my desire could
be made flesh.
Like an eternal flame,
burning in memorium.
Creation!
[gasps]
[KEI] Koko ni. Amatsukami no
mikoto mochite .
Futoma ‐ ni uraete
noritamai tsuraku !
[REN grunts]
[KEI]
It's useless.
[REN gasps]
Flames are unbreakable.
You can't cut through them.
So...
Now I've become them.
You can't stop me!
[REN grunts]
[gasps]
[screams]
[footsteps]
[RIZA]
Who's there?
[VALERIA] Oh, so it seems
you've found me, then.
It was my intention
to remain unseen.
You aren't fooling anyone.
Despite all the noise outside,
no one woke up, no one
took off in a panic.
That was your doing, wasn't it?
I never asked you for
your help, though.
Now, Riza, you wound me.
We've known each
other a long time.
I think I know you better
than you give me credit for.
Going around killing
hospital patients
while they flee in terror
isn't exactly your thing.
No, it's not. But, if you'd
be so kind, please leave me.
I'd prefer to not be
seen while working.
[VALERIA] You despise yourself
for being a murderer?
Indeed, quite funny, isn't it?
Too little, too late.
But that's simply the way
I've always been, I suppose.
Wishing only to
bask in the drama.
Somehow, gnawing guilt
makes me feel more complete.
Is it because if you
forget about your doubts,
you'll lose the last vestiges
of your humanity?
[RIZA]
Perhaps. Much like you.
[RIZA] I don't want to kill,
but killing is a necessity.
I will not waver from the
course I've been set on,
but I want to continue
having that uncertainty.
It's hypocritical and cowardly,
but at the very least,
I can be thankful I
didn't end up like you.
Riza. I must know.
When you were pregnant,
who was the father?
[RIZA gasps]
You had two sons,
isn't that right?
But you allowed one of
them to escape his fate.
This much I know.
[RIZA gasps]
[VALERIA]
In this dark drama.
How did you come
to your decision?
To sacrifice one son to
the black round table,
and let the other
live as a human?
Was he too much
like his father?
Did you fear the other
half of his blood?
Is it that very same fear
that continues to drive you
to abandon Theresia?
[RIZA grunts]
[RIZA]
That isn't your concern!
Oh, but I think it
is indeed, Riza.
I love young Theresia,
as you well know.
But I am uncertain as
to her exact origins.
And so. I'm left to wonder
if this feeling can really
be called my own love.
Or, perhaps they're naught
more than the emotional stains
clinging to the body I inhabit.
[RIZA gasps]
[VALERIA] Thus, I wish
to find out for myself,
and I know just how
to go about doing it.
Because the other son,
the one who you freed,
the one whose
happiness you longed for,
just as any good
mother would.
His bloodline continues here,
somewhere in Shambhala.
[RIZA gasps]
[VALERIA] By offering up
the scion of Johann,
I can prove that my love for
Theresia is indeed my own.
Perhaps prove that there's
more than borrowed emotions
tugging on my heartstrings.
The only way I can feel certain
that I am not driven by
something so trivial, is by
putting a decisive end
to Johann's bloodline, as proof
of my absolute devotion.
By now you must know who it is,
without me having to say a word.
[gasps
I've heard enough!
I won't let you. I will
never let you do it!
I chose to let Johann live!
I made my decision.
I see, and you have chosen
for Theresia to die?
[RIZA gasps]
That's right!
I won't sit idly by. I won't
let you deny who I am!
Your soul is fetid, Valeria.
You accepted a monster's body...
so you could be strong!
Of course. You are
no different, my dear Riza.
Then I take it my
assumption was correct?
You couldn't love Isaak because
he was too much like his father,
but as a failure in that regard,
Johann could be loved.
I knew it, you were
never a real mother.
Even a three‐legged bitch
on the street can give birth
and then abandon
her litter to die.
[RIZA]
Now Come, Cain!
[VALERIA]
So that's how it is.
Are you prepared
for your demise?
I suppose if you met
your end here,
it would prevent Theresia's
tender heart from breaking.
Quite the arrogant tone
from such a broken man!
[REN gasps]
[KEI] It appears one
of the swass‐tikas
has been opened elsewhere.
Bey, most likely.
So that makes four.
Five, once we're done here.
When eight are opened,
my dream will come true!
Lord Heydrich will
grant my wish.
My family will return to me!
[gasps]
[KEI]
He'll bring them back to life!
[REN grunts] You think
he's gonna bring back
your dead family?
You heard me! Impossible, right?
I know that's what you think!
But what if I told you that
once you die, it isn't over.
What would you do?
All it takes is the
wholesale slaughter
of a few thousand people whose
names you never have to know.
And you can be reunited
with the ones you love,
those torn from you. How could
you refuse such a great deal,
when it's in front of you,
waiting to be taken?
You'd be a fool too! That is
the miracle I long for.
The gold beyond price that
Lord Heydrich will give me.
What else can I do?
[REN]
That's insane.
[gasps]
Do you realize how crazy
everything you're saying sounds?
If they were really
that important to you,
if you loved them half
as much as you say,
Would you really do such
horrible things in their name?
Think about it. If you
have to pay for it
with "a few thousand lives."
How in the hell can you tell me
that it's "beyond price?"
[KEI gasps]
That's your gold?
Don't make me laugh!
Your "great deal"
isn't a bargain, Kei.
It only lowers the value of all
the things you claim to love!
[KEI] Shut up... Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
[REN grunts]
[grunts]
[gasps] You're wrong.
What do you know about it?
And what the hell do
you know about me?!
[ELEONORE] Disgusting.
You lose, little girl.
[KEI shouts]
[ELEONORE] And you're quite
the orator, aren't you?
That was an impressive speech.
[ELEONORE] Now come,
bastard child of Karl Krafft.
I will be the one to judge the
blade that has been offered up
to Lord Heydrich.
And if I find the
edge is dull,
not even your
bones shall remain.
♪