[KEI] In the days of
the Second World War,
my great‐grandfather,
skilled at the forge,
was invited to Germany,
tasked with the replication
of the Holy Lance.
[KEI] In and of itself, that
wasn't particularly strange.
In order to protect famous
relics from wear and theft,
replicas were often
used in displays.
It was a rather
standard precaution.
But, there was a
miscalculation, or perhaps,
it's quite possible
that what happened
had been the plan all along.
It seems my great‐grandfather
was too capable.
He had made more
than a mere replica.
The new Holy Lance
he had crafted
possessed and killed him.
[MUSASHI gagging]
[KEI]
The founder of blacksmithing.
Tubal Cain.
One of several titles
he was given.
[KEI] Thereafter, members
of the Sakurai bloodline
have been possessed
by that cursed blade,
and have been part of
the black round table.
Even with their
souls sucked out,
their corpses keep moving.
When they decay, the lance
moves on to the next Sakurai.
A neverending cycle.
[KEI]
One day, my turn will come.
But, there was someone who
tried to save me from that fate.
You don't have to worry
about anything at all. 'Kay?
I'm going to put
an end to all of this.
You're going to be
happy from here on out.
And that's a promise.
You got it?
Yeah.
I love you, Kai and Beatrice!
I want to be with you forever!
[KEI] It's frustrating to think
how stupid and naïve
I was back then.
I knew nothing at all.
With no way to comprehend
what he was talking about,
I just expected everything
to stay the same.
But then, in the
blink of an eye,
the people I loved were gone.
That's why I wanted
to take it all back.
I would do anything
to see them again,
no matter how
great the sacrifice!
I love them.
My brother. Beatrice.
[VALERIA] Well, this is
an unexpected issue.
It appears Samiel felt the
urge to make an appearance.
Why don't we suspend
hostilities? For now.
We haven't the time for this.
Is she here on orders?
Sent by our Lord to
open the fifth swastika?
The target has been
set and lined up
in the crosshairs.
Just look.
It's quite obvious
that you are her quarry.
If you make one wrong move,
I fear Samiel will
pull the trigger.
But I seem to have
gone unnoticed so far.
That said...
You want me to put
Johann's bloodline
under your protection for now?
[VALERIA]
Correct.
What do you think?
[RIZA]
Not happening.
[VALERIA]
Why not?
Do you really trust me
so little, Riza?
Or is it Samiel?
I suspect you may be trying
to put on a brave face
now that she's here
to observe you.
That's ridiculous.
You need to be smarter
about this, my dear.
How many people
have you let die
because of your
penchant for indecision?
You've lost the ability
to read the hearts
of others, Valeria.
You're too far gone.
[RIZA] A lifetime ago,
you were a weak man.
At times, even pathetic,
but I liked that about you.
It was so very human.
But I know the shame
it made you feel.
Tenderness isn't
a masculine trait.
You threw yourself away
only to become this.
It isn't very wise to
say that sort of thing.
Perhaps.
But we've both proven
what fools we really are.
Thinking we have the
power to protect anyone
is pure arrogance.
Which is why...
...I choose Ren Fujii
for the job.
He'll protect
Johann's grandchild.
Unlike you, Valeria,
I am not scum.
Real men protect their women.
It's really quite simple.
You stand right there
and be a good little boy.
I'll keep my eye on you.
If you move, Cain will attack.
Even a rodent as
capable as yourself
can't stay concealed while
using his energy to fight.
Get back here, Riza!
Unfortunate.
[ELEONORE] What sort of
trickery are you trying
to pull off, Brenner?
No matter.
[KEI grunts]
Now get on your feet, Leonhart.
You have my permission to move.
Apparently, that
zeppelin‐chested harlot
would like to have
a word with me,
but I have no intention
whatsoever of listening.
Handle that situation for me.
Yes, ma'am.
Now, back to you.
I told you to prove to me
that you have worth in battle.
That won't happen if
you just stand there.
Or maybe, you want to see
what I'm capable of first.
[REN gasps]
Solid instincts!
You might pass my test.
But is running away
all that you can do?
[REN yells]
Got nothing, is that it?
I would suggest you try
not to disappoint me.
[REN groans]
[ELEONORE] If you're stupid
enough to want to face
Lord Heydrich in
your current state,
you deserve the
death he'll deliver.
I was given instructions
to test your strength,
but nothing was said
about keeping you alive.
[REN yelling]
Let's see if you
have what it takes
to survive my testing.
Open fire!
[REN yells]
[ELEONORE] Thank you
for the demonstration.
You're very enthusiastic.
However, this is a problem.
You won't be able
to continue your testing
if you keep lying on the ground.
Break time is over;
stand back up.
Lord Heydrich isn't nearly
as friendly as I am.
If you're a hero, then
make the impossible happen.
You either find your wings
when you need them,
or you don't.
Those are the two types of
people that exist in this world,
and I wonder, which one are you?
I see, so that's the way it is.
[ELEONORE] Your guardian
angel arrives to overcome
what stands before you.
That works, too.
Earning the love of a
goddess is often required
of a classic hero.
How delightful it is
to see you again, my lady.
Please allow me
to introduce myself.
Eleonore Von Wittenburg, one
of Lord Heydrich's elite guards.
You interrupt our business
with that expression
on your face.
I wonder, what is
your objective here?
I know what mine is.
Just keep away from Ren.
I won't let you do
anything to hurt him!
[ELEONORE]
So what?
Does that mean you're ready
to take on all three of us
to protect your little friend?
[MARIE]
No. Just you.
You're the only one here
with that sort of intention.
[ELEONORE]
That's true.
You've got a point.
The situation looks
that way to me, too.
I respect my enemies
more than so‐called allies
incapable of overcoming
conflict on the battlefield.
Now then, what do we do?
You have ultimate
command here, Samiel.
I will follow the
orders you give me.
I have no opinion of my own.
[ELEONORE chuckles]
That's the way it should be.
And what about you, Brenner?
How do you want
to handle things?
[sighs]
How typical.
You weren't a part of this
mission from the beginning,
but now you've come
to take command?
Why don't you stay
out of this, Eleonore?
[RIZA]
Leon.
You should know
Samiel's an immortal.
The magic of the Golden
Blessing can either be used
for resurrection or for
granting one immortality.
She sacrificed all
the souls she needed
in the Battle of Berlin,
and has had her wish granted.
So I insist that you
not cause any trouble.
I have a claim to
every last human soul
that remains in the building.
After all, I can't imagine that
you need any more, now do you?
You aren't wrong.
If I had to choose,
I really don't need them.
However, Lord Heydrich
gave me instructions.
He tasked me
personally with seeing
the fifth swastika opened.
Give it a rest, Brenner.
You cannot fool me.
I've known you for far too long,
and I can tell
what you're thinking.
I don't know your
reasoning, exactly,
but there's somebody
out there you don't want
to let die.
You may lack the resolve needed
to reduce this place to ashes.
[RIZA gasps]
But I have no compunctions
in following through
with my orders.
Wait! Stop!
[ELEONORE]
Be quiet.
It's a bit late to mention this,
but I've hated you
for a long time.
After all...
It was Kircheisen that always
stopped us from fighting,
but she's no longer with us.
Pay close attention, girl.
I'll give you an order
that even someone
as stupid as you can understand.
If that wench so much
as moves, kill her.
If you want the glory of
opening the fifth swastika,
then you can kill each
other over it, Brenner.
I'd imagine you're quite
used to getting rid of brats
by now, aren't you?
If I happen to see
you lurking around
when I've completed
my work here,
I'll leave nothing of
you behind but cinders.
[ELEONORE]
Now, where were we?
In order to get the
proverbial ball rolling,
I need for this young man
to make a move.
To instigate things
with these half‐wits.
Think you could wake him up?
I won't.
And you can't make me.
[ELEONORE]
Oh, really?
You're going to stand
between me and him?
[ELEONORE] I'd like to ask
you something, if I may.
Do you truly understand
what it means to fight?
To put yourself in harm's way?
[MARIE gasping]
You wouldn't be surprised
if you'd listened.
I'm immortal, remember?
[ELEONORE] You do not
intend to take a life.
And you aren't prepared to.
As long as that
remains the case,
you can't hope to slay
the einherjar of Valhalla.
That's not it.
I don't care about
what you're saying,
I just want to
become the fifth!
Which means I won't
let Ren go anywhere,
and same with Kasumi!
They matter to me!
[MARIE gasps]
You long to be with him,
so you'll stay close in
whatever manner you can.
How ridiculous.
You made a wish, but haven't
paid the price for it yet.
[MARIE grunts]
If you desire something
greater for your future,
you must show the
necessary resolve.
[MARIE whimpers]
My duty is to
sharpen the blade
that will be offered
up to my master,
the great Lord Heydrich.
[MARIE yelps]
But will you shatter
under stress?
Why don't we find out?
[MARIE yells]
[MARIE]
The pain.
It hurts.
So bad.
Ren, is this what you've
been having to endure
this entire time?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't understand what
you were going through.
I made you handle
everything on your own.
How can you work so hard?
How can you keep
taking all of this?
Tell me, Ren.
[MARIE]
I'll listen.
Because I want to be like you.
Glad you're awake again.
How are you holding up, boy?
[REN]
Damn you.
Who the hell do you think
you are, hitting her like that?
I'll tear you apart!
I apologize for that.
I was simply following
my master's orders.
However, it appears the
approach worked quite well!
Poor thing.
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
That had to have hurt.
[MARIE]
It didn't bother me at all.
Ren.
Let's fight together.
And let's defeat her!
I'm going to do whatever
I can to keep you safe.
Now listen to me, witch.
Don't you dare hit my Ren!
We'll make you pay for this!
[RIZA]
So, tell me.
What exactly do you
think you're doing?
Following my orders.
I was told to keep
an eye on you.
[RIZA chuckles]
Think very carefully about
the situation, Leonhart.
The way things are going here,
everybody will be killed.
Eleonore is charging up;
we're in the middle
of a countdown.
[KEI] Tell me, was she
ever close with Beatrice?
[RIZA] Ja, she was
her direct superior,
but they were
almost like sisters.
And yet, knowing
that hasn't changed
your impression
of Eleonore at all.
Run while you still can.
Why would I turn around
and run right now
with no guarantee
that you won't attack me
the moment my blade is no
longer pointed at your throat?
[RIZA]
If you do not trust me,
then I'll just say it
while there's time.
Father Trifa‐‐
he's here right now,
inside the hospital.
I left my means of attack.
Tubal Cain is minding
him as we speak.
[KEI gasps]
You weren't able
to make it; too bad.
Let's see...
...if you're strong enough
to withstand what's next.
[VALERIA]
Now!
What?
Quite a lot is at stake here.
Who saves whom today
is more important
than you could ever realize.
I hope you'll accept
my apology, Fujii.
I know this desire of mine is
rather selfish, but if you can,
I'd like you to
try and save Rea.
[REN yells]
[REN grunts]
[REN]
Kasumi?
Why do this?
So that's what's going on.
You've underestimated
me, Brenner!
[ELEONORE]
As you wish.
I'll blow you away!
[RIZA]
Poor Isaak.
Johann. Rea.
I'm so sorry,
my darling children.
[RIZA]
Auf wiedersehen .
[REN]
Damn it, it's gonna get us!
How can I‐‐?
[REN] Formation is
followed by creation.
I have to harness my own desire.
[REN]
I wanna make time stand still.
I want everything to stop!
[REN yelling]
[CROWD gasps]
Insolent whelp.
What makes you think
you can get away?
Fall back, Samiel.
[MICHAEL] You have completed
your assigned mission.
[REN panting]
[ELEONORE]
Understood.
Don't worry, Mein Kamaraden .
I have no desire
to poach your prey.
Though...
I'll admit things
got a little hot
during the course of testing.
It's in my nature.
Sorry.
By the way, Machina.
What happened to Schreiber?
[MICHAEL] He's with the
Sonnenkind, no doubt.
Lord Heydrich now plans to open
the sixth swastika by himself.
Oh. That should be interesting.
What do you know?
I've found a rat!
He's the only other
one who can withstand
the heat of my flames.
Now then, what to do about him?
[VALERIA]
Oh, my.
It seems I've been discovered.
Fujii, did you see them?
Those two work very
closely with Lord Heydrich.
Even though we all
belong to the same order,
they are my mortal enemies.
Anyway, let us move on.
I'd like to suggest
an alliance between us.
I will tell you
everything I know.
Riza is no longer with us.
Why not join forces
and take revenge
on those monsters?