[JEANNE]
Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY]
Jeanne!
Where are you?!
[JEANNE]
Montmorency. Save me.
I'm coming!
[panting]
Out of my way!
Get out of my way!
Move!
[JEANNE]
Save me.
No. No! You fools.
I said, get the hell
out of my way!
[panting]
[ALENCON] You lost consciousness
on the battlefield.
Quite the blunder.
Where am I?
[ALENCON]
Augustine's Fortress.
We snatched it back
from the English
amid the confusion
of the last battle.
In a way, it's thanks to--
Wait, Jeanne!
[groans] She died
in that battle, didn't she?
It appeared that way, but no.
[gasps]
[ASTAROTH]
She has lost her heart.
And that wound from
the Holy Lance
isn't healing as it should.
Fortunately, her head
is still fully intact.
The Philosopher's Stone is just
barely keeping her alive.
She's in a comatose state
to avoid dying completely.
If she wasn't, I doubt
the stone could do much.
[BATARD]
I understand what you're saying,
but it's still
very difficult to believe.
If she has yet to perish,
then there must be a way
we can save her.
Am I correct, Astaroth?
Indeed.
The legendary sword Excalibur.
It's a Philosopher's Stone with
incredible healing abilities.
If we can attain that blade,
then there's a chance.
Wait. Montmorency,
you have to listen to me.
Even if the young maiden
is revived,
our troop size
can no longer hope
to match the English army
after our latest retreat.
We were fortunate
to take this fortress,
but we cannot
defend it forever.
We need troops, badly.
Two thousand soldiers more,
at the bare minimum.
What do you expect me
to do about it?
The blade, Excalibur is hidden
somewhere in the forest
of Brittany.
Your home is nearby there,
is it not?
[groans softly]
If you think my grandfather
will let me borrow soldiers,
you're wrong.
We will retrieve
the sacred blade.
It's up to you to return home
and do what you can
to convince--
It won't work!
You know my relationship
with that man.
[ALENCON]
I do.
But even so,
you are the only one
who has a chance
at bringing us reinforcements,
Montmorency.
No, Gilles de Rais.
♪
[inaudible]
[thunder rumbling]
[sighs]
[CATHERINE] It was raining
like this that day, too.
[MONTMORENCY]
Catherine.
It's good to see you.
Brother? Is that you?
That's right.
I'm sorry that I left
and came back without a word.
[cawing]
Really?
He's returned after
all this time?
-[SOLDIER] Yes, sir.
-And what does he want?
To borrow soldiers.
Or so it seems.
[JEAN]
Hmm.
What does that imbecile
want with my soldiers?
[thunder rumbling]
[MONTMORENCY]
Uh...
We still have the grimoire
from the workshop.
I'm surprised it wasn't
confiscated by the Inquisition.
They did try to take it away,
but we were able to bribe
a bishop to save it.
-Huh?
-[chuckles]
I didn't know
when you would return home,
so I had to make sure everything
was to your liking
for when you did.
I had very little time
to be upset.
Truly.
[gasps]
Um, now that you're back, I...
[sobbing]
[BOTH gasp]
[MONTMORENCY]
Old man.
[scoffs]
[CATHERINE]
Welcome back, Grandfather.
I'll prepare your meal
right away.
[CATHERINE gasps]
[JEAN exhales]
-I hear you need soldiers.
-[MONTMORENCY] Yes.
How many of them?
[MONTMORENCY]
Two thousand.
[JEAN chuckles]
[exhales]
Very well.
Take as many as you like.
But there's one condition.
[MONTMORENCY]
Hmm?
[JEAN]
You will marry Catherine.
[MONTMORENCY]
I thought that arrangement
was called off years ago.
[JEAN] Catherine's family
is incredibly wealthy.
You would have more fortune
than the French royal family,
or the Duchy of Burgundy.
I don't remember asking you
to make me wealthy.
Besides, she's my cousin!
Well, it doesn't make
a difference to me.
You just won't get
any of my soldiers.
What kind of man
demands such a thing?!
[groans, gasps]
Montmorency!
-[groans]
-[gasps]
♪
-[JEAN scoffs]
-[CATHERINE] Brother!
Are you all right? I'm here!
[knock on door]
[door opens]
I had a feeling I might find you
in this place.
It never occurred to me
that he'd still try to
force me to marry you.
I'm sorry.
-You must hate this.
-[thunder rumbling]
But I don't intend to burden you
with the crime
of marrying your cousin.
Don't worry about the soldiers.
I'll think of another way.
It actually doesn't bother me.
Because I'm quite fond of you.
Well, it goes without saying
I'm fond of you, too, of course.
But we're talking about
a different kind of--
No we're not!
Even if I receive God's judgment
and I'm cast down into hell,
I still... I still want
your love more than anything!
-To do things only a wife could!
-[thunder crashes]
To have your child!
[sobbing] Please, don't leave me
alone again.
[CATHERINE] It was raining
like this that day, too.
♪
[JEAN] I'm sure you've
already heard from your mother.
You'll be marrying my grandson.
To be quite blunt,
I am after the wealth
that you will inherit.
Any questions?
[CATHERINE groans softly]
None at all?
Wise choice, girl.
[laughing]
♪
[CATHERINE]
Jean the Redbeard as he's known,
plotted to marry
his grandson to girls
from many different
wealthy families.
But the fiancees who were
practically kidnapped
and brought here,
became deeply depressed.
All growing frail
and passing away.
[sobbing quietly]
Huh?
[grunts]
[sobbing]
[JEAN]
Have you greeted her yet, boy?
-[MONTMORENCY] No.
-[JEAN sighs]
I suggest you do.
Now, as you're well aware,
that girl is your cousin.
Marriage between relatives
requires the execution
of several
bothersome formalities.
However, things are made
much simpler
if it's a fait accompli.
Huh?
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crashes]
Hmm.
[heavy breathing]
Huh?
[groaning]
[exhales]
[MONTMORENCY]
Are you all right?
[gasps]
[CATHERINE shuddering]
I feel... so strange.
[gasps]
♪
From this moment on, I'm going
to be your big brother.
I promise to always protect you.
[sighs]
[gasps]
Where are we? I'm gonna fall!
[MONTMORENCY] I know this forest
inside and out.
Besides, you don't think
I'd let you get hurt, do you?
[laughing]
[CATHERINE] The marriage
proceedings didn't go smoothly,
and I ended up
living in the castle
as his little sister instead.
The grandson
of Jean the Redbeard,
Gilles de Rais
Montmorency-Laval.
[MONTMORENCY weakly]
I'll protect Catherine.
[grunting]
[CATHERINE]
On that fateful, rainy night,
he became my brother.
Montmorency! Montmorency!
Will you pat my head,
Montmorency?
Ooh, me too, pretty please?
[MONTMORENCY]
I don't see why not.
One at a time, okay?
This lady is really pretty.
Pretty lady, can I touch you?
-[laughter]
-[CATHERINE] Uh...
Come on. Be gentle, you guys.
Catherine's my little sister,
so be careful not to hurt her.
♪
-[chuckling]
-[laughs]
That's the first time
I've seen you laugh.
I guess you're right, brother.
[ALL laughing]
[SOLDIER]
Farewell.
[RICHEMONT]
Thanks for the report.
So, Montmorency is in Champtoce.
I want to see him,
but what good would come of it?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[yawning]
[SOLDIER] Lord Glasdale,
please prepare for battle!
[sighs]
All right.
[gunshot]
Which one of you
wants to die next?
[yelling]
[shouting]
[grunts]
The merciful La Hire only holds
back on women and children!
There'll be no pity for you men.
Ah! You truly are
the most beautiful
when you're on a rampage.
Much better than when
you're brooding over
your responsibility as a leader,
that doesn't suit you--
[screams]
Shut your mouth and fight.
I don't want you
screwing this up
when we've already been paid
for it in advance.
♪
The Mythical Joyeuse is
a small price to pay for Jeanne.
-I'm counting on you, La Hire.
-[gunshot]
[LA HIRE]
Forgive me, Jeanne.
It was a mistake
to leave you behind.
Hear me, English scum.
I'll make every one of you pay
for hurting a child.
[GLASDALE]
It's just a reinforcement
of a hundred mercenaries.
You must not be taking this
seriously if you need my help.
[SOLDIER]
I apologize, sir.
Hmm.
[GLASDALE]
Noire.
Prove that I'm right
to not worry about you.
Put that Holy Grail
to use and heal.
-[door opens]
-[footsteps approaching]
[JEAN]
You haven't departed yet?
Then share a bed
with Catherine tonight.
Do so and you will have
your soldiers
as well as new inheritance.
Do you wish to decline
all the fortune and power
accumulated by Jean
the Redbeard's tireless schemes
or do you wish to inherit it?
[MONTMORENCY] Tell me,
why must you try so hard
to pass down
your wealth to me?
[JEAN laughs]
It is the tradition of all men
who are born in Reims--
Hmm.
♪
I think you were truly ready
to kill me just now.
[MONTMORENCY]
That's right.
I've become a different man
since leaving these walls.
-[rumbling]
-Hmm?
♪
Hmm?
It's been a long time,
Nicolas Flamel.
Are you here to laugh
at my foolishness?
You were right, as it turns out.
I should have killed Gilles
all those years ago.
♪
[NICOLAS]
If you do not kill him now,
calamity will fall
upon the world.
That's absurd.
I don't believe in astrology
or numerology,
or whatever it is
that you practice.
Save your breath.
[NICOLAS] This boy,
Gilles de Montmorency-Laval
has the imprint of the beast,
as predicted by
the apocalyptic literature.
But he can still be saved, yet.
Even the most privileged men
are still human.
They have a limit
to what they can attain.
As long as he remains human,
the latent qualities of the
demon lord will stay dormant.
He will live a normal life
with human limitations.
Hmm. I remember your warning.
I'll make sure he stays human.
But Gilles has already
been attracted
by the realm of alchemy.
He's been seduced by something
beyond the limitations
of a normal man.
Even that look he gave me
was inhuman.
I've committed countless
evil deeds,
but that chilled me
to the bone.
[NICOLAS]
Where are you going?
[thunder rumbling]
[knock on door]
[door opens]
Brother.
[MONTMORENCY]
Forgive me, Catherine.
[CATHERINE]
Huh?
[MONTMORENCY]
I cannot marry you.
Not because we're cousins.
Because I swore an oath
to the maiden of Domremy.
I have made
a promise to Jeanne.
♪
[inaudible]
That girl is all alone.
There's nowhere in this world
that she belongs now.
I'm responsible for that.
For making her
what she's become.
What about the soldiers
waiting for reinforcements?
What will Princess Charlotte do
without help?
What about the girl
in front of you,
who's just as alone
as that maiden?
♪
I'll take those soldiers,
as you promised.
♪
[CATHERINE] You must love
the maiden of Domremy.
[MONTMORENCY]
Love her?
That's right.
[MONTMORENCY]
Me?
Even if the whole world
had turned against you,
you would still dedicate
yourself to her entirely.
That's the definition of love.
Don't you see?
♪
[gasps]
[MONTMORENCY]
I love Jeanne?
I have an idea.
Let's say that we laid
together tonight.
Then you can take the troops
you need tomorrow.
[MONTMORENCY]
And you're all right with that?
[CATHERINE]
I just have one request.
What is it?
Hold me in your arms
until the sun rises.
Just like back then.
[MONTMORENCY] I was stuck
in the alchemy workshop
for seven years.
And only now do I discover
that you've become
more mature than I, Catherine.
[crying]
[NICOLAS] Oftentimes,
it's impossible for one
to change the fate
that life has given them.
However, perhaps it is
different for someone
who has experienced love.
At least, that's what I want
to believe is the case.
[MONTMORENCY]
I've been true to my word.
You'd better do
the same, Alencon.
Mercenaries and knights alike,
hear me now!
We ride to Orleans,
where we shall turn
the tide of battle!
[cheering]
[NARRATOR] Would you be
interested in the story
of an earnest high school
baseball team manager?
I didn't think so.
What you're interested in
is breasts.
Now, imagine if Batard
had large mammaries.
Would that not make you question
your own existence?
Episode 8,
"Return of the Female Saint."
Say, Alencon,
care to weigh in on this?
[WOMAN]
Je veux un enfant de toi.