[GLASDALE]
Poor little French girl.
My first projectile was a feint.
Now, have a taste
of my actual weapon.
Ashes to ashes, demon.
No. It can't be!
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
Ashes to ashes.
Those who pass away are destined
for the realm of the dead.
So, die, Jeanne.
♪
[BOTH groan]
[gasps]
[MONTMORENCY]
You can't die!
[ASTAROTH]
She has lost her heart,
and that wound
from the Holy Lance
isn't healing as it should.
Fortunately, her head
is still fully intact.
If she has yet to perish,
then there must be a way
we can save her.
Am I correct, Astaroth?
Indeed.
[ALENCON] We will retrieve
the sacred blade.
[ASTAROTH]
The legendary sword Excalibur.
A Philosopher's Stone with
incredible healing abilities.
And with that blade,
we might have a chance.
Listen.
The sword we seek, Excalibur,
didn't it belong to
the legendary knight
called Roi Arthur?
[ASTAROTH]
Yes, it did.
However in England, he's known
as the legendary King Arthur.
[BATARD] According to
all the legends I've heard,
the king returned the sword
to the Fairy of the Lake
shortly before he died,
and if that's true,
then how did it
somehow end up in France?
In a remote forest
like this one, no less.
[ASTAROTH]
To be precise, we're not looking
for the actual sword.
We're trying to find
the scabbard.
The scabbard?
[ASTAROTH] It's too dangerous
to keep a sword that powerful
in the same place as its sheath,
so I hid them separately.
If someone found them both,
the results could be disastrous.
Hold on, are you telling me
that you're the famous
Fairy of the Lake?!
[chuckles]
[BATARD] So, you lived
for a thousand years?
[chuckles]
Much longer.
Oh, wow!
What are you going to
divulge to me next?
That you witnessed
the great flood
in the book of Genesis?
Don't tell me you're thousands
of years old.
[sighs]
What?! For real?!
You saw all that?
Well, what about
Noah's Ark, then?
Who cares? I can't stand this
inane chatter. Stop it.
Don't you realize
how distracting it is?
Uh, but this is more than just
inane chatter.
At least...
I don't think it is.
[ALENCON]
Lord above,
I pray that you'll watch over
Orleans in our absence.
Please have patience, Jeanne.
We'll be able to
revive you very soon.
Careful. If we screw up
this operation somehow,
we don't have the luxury
of being revived.
[GLASDALE]
Are you ready, men?!
Fire!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[grunting]
Men, regroup
and take the fortress!
We have to push through
and then the day is ours!
♪
[LA HIRE]
Where are they with Excalibur
and the reinforcements?
[BATARD sighs]
[BATARD] I had no idea it would
take us this long to find it.
I can't help but feel misled.
[sighs]
So, we're lost?
Yes, well,
what do you expect, sir?
I hid the thing
a thousand years ago.
And you call yourself
"Queen of the Fairies."
[ASTAROTH] How dare
you question me, lowly human?
[BOTH grunting]
Uh, pardon.
-May I speak?
-[BOTH] You keep out of this!
Sorry!
[ASTAROTH]
Humans have such giant bodies,
but judging
by the way you think,
your brains must be
the size of walnuts.
[ALENCON]
You're one to talk.
The Queen of the Fairies
can't even remember
where she hid a scabbard
that's the key...
[BATARD]
Just as I thought. Look!
[ASTAROTH]
What now?
Can't you see the adults
are talking?
[BATARD]
The stones! They just moved!
-Don't you see?
-[ALENCON] No.
They look to me like they're
in the exact same place.
[ALL gasp]
♪
What is this, devil's magic?
[ASTAROTH]
Oh, yes, one of the traps I set
to deter would-be thieves
from finding the scabbard.
Oh, that's great, another thing
you forgot about.
[ASTAROTH]
Hold your tongue.
Alencon.
Hold up the Philosopher's Stone.
[ALENCON]
What? Why?
[ASTAROTH]
Fool. Don't question me!
Just do as you're told.
[grunting]
[ASTAROTH]
Halt, you imbeciles.
Can't you see
the Philosopher's Stone?
♪
[BATARD]
They stopped.
What just happened?
[FAIRY 1] That's a real
Philosopher's Stone.
[gasps]
But why is it rent in two?
[FAIRY 2]
Why would you destroy it?
[BATARD]
Uh, fairies?
The Korrigan Tribe.
About a thousand years ago,
I ordered them to guard
this forest at all costs.
Wow.
My gatekeepers,
I order you to deliver us
to the scabbard at once.
-She's a witch.
-She's scary!
Why is the witch yelling at us?
What's the matter?
Don't you all remember me?
Don't tell me I picked
the three dumbest fairies around
to do my bidding.
[FAIRY 1]
Who are you again?
[FAIRY 2]
I don't think we've met.
[FAIRY 3] Is she talking about
our ancestors?
Didn't your ancestors teach you
to write anything down?
Things that might be important?
I don't think she has much room
to criticize them.
[sighs]
[FAIRIES murmuring]
Wait. No.
[FAIRY 1]
Is it here?
[FAIRY 2]
That's really strange.
[ASTAROTH]
Is something wrong?
It isn't where we put it.
[ASTAROTH]
Huh?
[BATARD]
Look! Someone's in the tree!
Oh, hello.
Found me faster than I thought.
I guess you're not as dumb
as you appear.
Who are you, then?
Ah, forgive me.
Sir Thomas Malory,
at your service.
I'm head of the Philosopher's
Stone search party.
Which means I work
for the Duke of Bedford.
You're in the English Army?
No, not quite.
To be perfectly precise,
I am a princess knight of Wales.
Do any of you happen to know
where Wales is?
It's a small nation
in the southwest of Britain.
Although not quite
what it once was,
it's been all
but assimilated into England.
Now I understand
what's going on.
What's that?
Wales was primarily under
the domain of King Arthur.
It wouldn't be the least
bit surprising
if he had drawn up a document
detailing
the approximate location
where he gave me the scabbard.
That's correct!
Well done! But I beat you to it.
Sorry.
That means Excalibur's scabbard
will be reunited with the sword
and returned
to its rightful place.
No hard feelings.
♪
[gasps, yells]
[FAIRY]
I have to warn them!
[grunts]
Here's a fun fact.
Originally the longbow
was designed by the Welsh army
as a form of long-range defense
against attacks
by English cavalry regiments.
[ALENCON] Enough history,
get down here and fight.
If you hand over the scabbard,
we might consider
sparing your life.
You can't stay up there forever,
and we're willing to wait.
[FAIRY]
My queen! My queen!
A whole bunch of knights
are headed this way!
There has to be
a hundred of them, at least.
[ASTAROTH]
It can't be.
That's how these things go.
My search party will make
short work of you lot.
Then I'll climb down from here,
dignity intact,
and escape with the scabbard.
Oh, and you still have
the option of running away
with your tails tucked
between your legs,
if you would prefer to live.
What will you do?
[ASTAROTH]
There's no way the three of us
can defeat a hundred knights.
And yet, without the scabbard
we have no hope
of reviving Jeanne.
If we fail on that front,
then Montmorency would...
Batard, distract her.
Uh, okay. Got it.
Hey, you had better come down
from there now,
or I'll be forced
to light this tree on fire!
No, idiot.
Do you want to burn down
the whole forest?
Ha ha, you fool.
I'm gonna get rid of this
evil princess knight.
There's a smarter way to do it!
Let go of me now!
[ALENCON]
What's gotten into you?
My search party will arrive
long before you have a chance
to set fire to anything.
You're smart enough
to know that,
or else I've overestimated you.
So, I suspect you're putting on
this farce to draw my attention,
but I'm not sure why.
[gasps]
That's the answer!
It's a distraction!
[gasps]
♪
Astaroth!
[THOMAS laughing]
It's quite unfortunate
that I had to eliminate
thousands of years of vault
information by shooting you.
If I had my way,
I would have captured you
and kept you locked up forever
in a little iron cage.
[chuckles]
I'd love to know
what you think is so funny.
[gasps]
[screaming]
[FAIRIES gasp]
[FAIRY 1] Silly girl,
the Queen of the Fairies
can never be killed.
[FAIRY 2]
Not even if she wanted to be.
[FAIRY 3] She's the protector
of the Philosopher's Stone.
So she's destined to be revived,
no matter what,
though she may die
hundreds of thousands of times.
[SOLDIER]
Over there!
[FAIRIES gasp]
What?
[ALENCON]
I'm not pleased with the idea
of taking a woman hostage,
but it will buy us some time.
You two had better go on ahead.
We can't possibly
leave you here!
[ALENCON] The revival of
the maiden will do a great deal
to boost the soldiers' morale.
Take the scabbard,
deliver it to Orleans.
You must make sure it gets to
Jeanne, no matter what it takes.
♪
[FAIRY 1]
What will you do?
[FAIRY 2]
Will you be all right?
-We had better go.
-Huh?
That way is safe.
Hurry.
[FAIRIES panting]
[BATARD gasps]
Alencon!
"Alencon died gloriously
in battle as a knight should."
If you were ever
truly my friend,
that's the story you'll tell.
[sighs]
[sobs]
That is how it should be.
I'm certain.
[MAN 1]
Wonderful technique, sir.
I'd expect no less of
Lady Richemont's brother.
[WOMAN] Lady Richemont
would never have made
a simple mistake like that.
[MAN 2]
And you dare call yourself
Arthur de Richemont's
little brother?
♪
[panting]
[yelling]
[groaning]
[grunts, yells]
[ALENCON] I was born
with a predetermined purpose.
To surpass my older sister.
I will finally achieve that aim.
After this, no one will ever
underestimate me again.
[grunts]
[ASTAROTH]
Montmorency!
[MONTMORENCY]
Astaroth.
Batard retrieved the scabbard.
He's carrying it to Orleans
as we speak.
Perfect.
Did Alencon go with him?
Hmm.
Are you serious?
Mm-hmm.
[SOLDIER] Commander,
there are enemy troops up ahead!
[horse neighs]
♪
[LA TREMOILLE]
I put every bit of my fortune
into assembling these soldiers.
If Orleans were to be liberated,
then the princess
would proceed to Reims.
I would forever be robbed
of any future opportunity
to sign a truce
with the English.
[MONTMORENCY] You're nothing
but a traitor and a nuisance.
This is the official
French army.
How will you answer for your
treasonous attempts at sabotage?
This isn't really the time to be
bickering with La Tremoille.
We have to depart for Orleans
as soon as we can.
[LA TREMOILLE]
I won't let you play
the part
of the heroic liberator.
I am the one who will
save France from its doom.
I heard a rumor
that the false saint Jeanne
perished in battle.
She really was
a witch all along.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
I heard she died
in a most gruesome manner,
having her heart squeezed
till it burst.
[laughing]
A fitting death for a servant
of the devil, wouldn't you say?
Don't give in
to his provocation.
[MONTMORENCY]
You bastard.
You're not even worthy of
speaking Jeanne's name,
so you'd better keep it
out of your mouth.
Or I'll kill you.
Ha! I know that look.
It's one of villainy.
You are anything but a hero,
and you know it.
I'm glad to see you're finally
taking off your mask.
[grunting]
-[ALENCON] Montmorency!
-Huh?
[MONTMORENCY]
Alencon.
[ASTAROTH]
I can't believe it, you're safe.
Of course, and I
haven't come alone.
♪
Wha... Who are
all these people?
[ALENCON chuckles]
[ALENCON]
Who, them?
They're my sister's
personal regiment.
[thudding]
All troops, pull back at once.
We need to make
a tactical withdrawal.
[groans]
[weakly]
I can't stop now.
[RICHEMONT]
I received intelligence reports
of English troops traveling
covertly in our territory.
But I didn't expect to find you.
[laughing]
[ALENCON] I guess I'm just
a laughing stock no matter what.
And here I thought I was
making a grand gesture,
sacrificing myself
to let my friends escape.
But in the end,
I had to be saved by my sister.
[sobbing]
I'm-I'm a failure.
[RICHEMONT] I would never
laugh at you, Alencon.
You've done well.
There are no words to express
how proud I am.
[ALENCON sobbing quietly]
[ALENCON]
I get it now.
I never needed to be validated
by the whole world.
All I ever really wanted was
for you to be proud of me.
Facing traitorous soldiers
after beating English troops.
Never a dull moment for us
in this war, is there?
Montmorency.
You mustn't let
that scoundrel distract you
from who you are
and what you must accomplish.
I, Arthur de Richemont,
hereby decree battle
on the basis
of a personal grudge
against the Count.
Our enemy is La Tremoille.
Ignore Montmorency's troops
and allow them to pass through.
And remember, this is a fight
to the death,
so give it your all!
[MONTMORENCY]
Richemont, wait.
Let the official
of the royal family handle this.
Fight to the death or not,
this is going to put you
in a difficult position.
Go to Jeanne, Montmorency.
You swore an oath.
You must do whatever it takes
to make sure she does not die.
Don't look at me with tears
in your eyes.
I'm a warrior.
I don't need to be protected
by a knight in shining armor.
We both know you're useless
in that regard.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
♪
[SOLDIER groans]
[RICHEMONT] Montmorency,
you must fulfill your duty.
Only then will you become
a true knight.
What do you think of it,
Astaroth?
Catherine forgave me
for leaving her.
And Richemont saved me
from certain death.
Do you think I will become
the kind of man
who can protect them
both someday
or will I always be this weak?
You will, soon.
You must.
[JEANNE]
Montmorency?
[groans]
[sobbing]
[weakly]
It hurts. Help me.
Don't leave me alone.
[ALENCON]
Hey! Batard!
Alencon!
You're still alive!
I'm so glad. I thought--
We can talk about that later.
What's going on?
Things are only getting worse.
The troops are managing
to hold off for now,
but it's only a matter of time.
[ALENCON] If Montmorency
can reach Jeanne,
then I know we can beat them.
We just have to get him to her.
Now clear a path
to the fortress!
As much as I don't like women,
I will slaughter as many men
as it takes to save her.
Are you ready to do this now?
Yeah, let's ride.
[ALL]
Yeah!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[JEANNE crying]
[JEANNE]
I'm afraid. It's so lonely here.
♪
[JEANNE]
I don't like being alone.
Save me, Montmorency.
Please come to save me!
[yelling]
[MONTMORENCY]
Jeanne!
♪
Montmorency is on his way,
but not to rescue me, of course.
He's coming to save
the light Ulysses.
[grunts]
[MONTMORENCY panting]
[MONTMORENCY]
Why isn't it working?
[ASTAROTH]
The elixir in her body
is drying up rapidly
in this state,
so the scabbard's not
reacting as it should.
Montmorency, you have to let
her drink some elixir.
Like in a children's story.
The cursed princess will awaken
with the prince's kiss.
♪
It's working! Look!
[JEANNE moaning softly]
[JEANNE]
Montmorency.
I'm sorry it took me so long.
But I came here to wake you.
♪
[sobbing quietly]
[sobbing]
[JEANNE]
Montmorency, you smell terrible.
[MONTMORENCY] Sorry.
I didn't have time to bathe.
[JEANNE]
It's all right.
Can we stay like this
a little while longer?
[SOLDIER 1]
Enemy reinforcements
are at least 2,000 strong!
What do we do, sir?
[SOLDIER 2] Commander Campbell
has fallen, sir!
We've just received a report
that the dark alchemist
has entered the fortress, sir,
what should we do?
[grunts]
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
Glasdale.
How's your wound?
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
It's fine.
As long as I have
the holy grail,
I can never partake
in death's blessing.
[chuckles]
♪
[NARRATOR] Light and dark
are to meet in battle once more.
At last, a conclusion
to the two warring Ulysses.
Who will win,
the small or large ones?!
I mean, the light or dark.
Episode nine, "Dance Music
of White and Black."
This time, I've no choice
but to cheer for the small ones.
[WOMAN]
Tu es serieux?