♪
This force is something
far more terrible.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
The fifth dimension's unfolding.
Alongside the sixth one.
And the seventh.
They're all...
[gasps]
No.
It can't be.
This is the end.
We're doomed.
♪
This is something
I never thought I'd see.
The Philosopher's Stone
will kill us all.
Wait, hold on.
I thought you said
I was just going to die
if it went out of control.
What is that thing?
♪
[SOLDIERS coughing, groaning]
What's happening to the sky?
Dear God, help us.
[LA HIRE]
Montmorency!
What's going on?
How is there a hole in the sky?
And what is that
terrible monster?
[MONTMORENCY]
La Hire,
take Jeanne
and Astaroth and run.
Get as far away from this place
as you can.
[LA HIRE]
And just leave you here?
What will you do?
[MONTMORENCY grunts]
♪
[growling]
Leave, now!
Mur d'Air!
♪
[ALL groaning]
[NICOLAS]
This is it.
[grunting]
Be gone, foul monster!
[grunts]
I don't know what you are
or why you've come here,
but you are not welcome.
Now back to the hell
from whence you came!
[roaring]
[grunts]
[ALENCON]
Retreat at full speed!
Keep moving!
Babylon's Hole.
[grunting]
[screaming]
[ASTAROTH] I never imagined
it would happen like this.
It couldn't possibly have
manifested in a worse way.
[MONTMORENCY groaning]
[screaming]
[MONTMORENCY]
Where am I?
What am I looking at?
Am I dead?
[gasps]
♪
I am king of the gods!
Lowly, insolent human.
How dare you attempt
to seal a divine being
in the Void Dimension?
Astaroth?
[Z] We are the makers
who created the human race.
What you are attempting to do
is heresy, the murder of a god!
It is a mortal sin!
Humans are lost
without their masters!
Deprived of our guidance,
your race will let loose
your drives and desires!
This can only lead
to eternal war and strife.
We maintained the peace in
your realm by ruling over you.
Your species has proved
time and again
to be incapable
of surviving on your own!
As a result, you will lose
your chance
of achieving utopia permanently!
[groans]
We will return, no matter
what you do to keep us away.
This I promise you!
♪
[gasps]
Goodbye, friend.
We must now part.
[ASTAROTH]
You can't die, not right now.
Don't leave me here in a world
without gods.
I can't make it on my own.
Do not worry,
for not all the gods
have vanished from this world.
There is still a goddess here.
It's you, for you have the power
needed to save humanity.
Bless us.
The future of utopia...
is with you.
Farewell.
[rumbling]
[ALL gasp]
♪
No. It's a demon!
Attack!
[arrows shooting]
♪
[SOLDIERS clamoring]
[distorted voice]
I've obtained it at last.
The Philosopher's Stone
that once sealed me away.
It's within my grasp!
[yelling]
There's nothing for me
to fear now.
[evil laughter]
Vessel in the heavens.
Hasten to my voice.
♪
[screaming]
[MONTMORENCY] The Hole
of Babylon has opened at last,
and it is under my control.
We shall have our utopia,
that idyllic realm
shall begin once more.
But before that,
I must cleanse it
of the filthy human scourge.
[NICOLAS] It is coming to pass
precisely as foretold.
[ASTAROTH]
It's you.
[NICOLAS]
I should have acted that day,
and taken his life
when I had the opportunity.
But no,
I still wanted to believe.
I held out hope that people
weren't slaves to fate.
I thought love had the power
to alter his destiny.
Could you at least talk
like a normal person?!
What in the hell just happened
to Montmorency?
What was that horrible monster
that came out of the sky?
And what is going on right now?
[grunts in frustration]
Fine then, keep your secrets,
but tell us what to do,
at least.
How can we stop this?
Nothing can be done.
[gasps]
He is our only remaining hope.
"Only hope"? Who are you?
I am Nicolas Flamel.
And I am here
as a representative
of an organization
formed to establish
a utopia for humanity,
called the Knights Templar.
I am its last surviving member.
Now, Astaroth,
you cannot escape.
At long last,
I have come to kill you.
[gasps]
Hurry up!
Get to the fortress, quickly!
[BATARD]
Right.
[explosion]
[LA HIRE]
Will Astaroth be all right?
I don't like leaving her.
[ALENCON]
We don't have any choice.
We must get to
Augustine Fortress
as soon as possible.
[BATARD]
Even if we hide in the fortress,
it will probably meet
the same awful end
as the Tourelles Complex.
[whimpers]
I had hoped I'd be able to die
looking like a boy,
or at the very least,
that I wouldn't have to perish
wearing frilly
women's underwear.
Please, Lord,
let me go to heaven
where I may dress as I wish.
You can't be serious right now.
Don't pray to God.
We must defeat divinity
to survive.
[NICOLAS]
We, of the Knights Templar,
fought our way toward the east
with a single,
particular goal in our hearts.
We wanted nothing more than
to destroy
every Philosopher's Stone
that lie hidden there.
But then, a traitor among us
smuggled one of the Stones
back into France,
and it somehow ended up
in Montmorency's hands.
[grunts]
[gasps]
♪
[MONTMORENCY]
Astaroth, you are a sinner.
I have been dreaming of the day
I'd exact my revenge
for thousands of years.
[NICOLAS]
Now that I think of it,
perhaps this was our destiny,
a curse upon humankind.
For it was inevitable
that the gods would wish
to take their world back,
no matter what the cost.
[MONTMORENCY]
You're in my way, human.
Stand aside, or else--
I refuse.
Oh, do you?
[NICOLAS]
This is the realm of humanity.
Now, gods, bear witness
to human magic.
Behold, a technique developed
solely by humanity.
We call it Alchemy.
[groans]
[NICOLAS]
This world has no need of you.
No gods,
nor Philosopher's Stones.
Be gone.
We will build our own utopia.
The human race shall create
it alone, with our own hands!
These attacks are nothing
but cheap theatrics.
[screams]
[grunts]
[MONTMORENCY grunts]
[NICOLAS groans]
I gave you a command,
now move aside!
[groans]
A utopia crafted
by mortal hands?
It's laughable.
Well, Astaroth,
didn't I warn you?
Humanity is lost
without its masters
and will give in
to base desires and ambitions
with reckless abandon
resulting in endless war
and discord.
You will lose your utopia,
with no hope of recovering it.
You must admit, I was right.
I am the guardian
of the Philosopher's Stone.
Therefore, you cannot kill me.
[MONTMORENCY]
Oh, but I can, my darling.
And I will continue killing you,
until the end of everything.
It's quieted down.
Let's go!
[yelling]
Take care of Jeanne for me.
Don't do it.
You've no elixir.
You know what will happen.
If you use
the Philosopher's Stone
without it, you will die.
If I restore
Montmorency's sanity
before the poison spreads,
and get elixir--
That's impossible.
Please, give me Joyeuse.
I'll become Ulysses.
[LA HIRE]
Hold on, Jeanne.
I'll get Montmorency back.
I will save you,
even if I die doing it.
[screams]
[gasps]
[screaming]
Montmorency, please!
I know you're in there!
[screaming]
[groans, sighs]
[screams]
[evil laughter]
[screaming]
[LA HIRE]
That's enough! Put her down!
[MONTMORENCY]
Huh?
La Hire. What are you...
[LA HIRE]
Tell me, Astaroth.
How can I bring Montmorency
back to us?
I'll do anything.
[ASTAROTH]
There's only one way.
You have to take the
Philosopher's Stone out of him.
If you do that,
the Hole of Babylon will close,
and the gods
will be sealed away
back where they came from,
in the Void Dimension.
[MONTMORENCY] You really think
that's possible?
[LA HIRE gasps]
You're nothing but livestock!
[grunts]
♪
What is this strange weapon?
Such speed.
Not only that, but I can't
determine its course.
Enchanted bullets?
What magic is this?
[LA HIRE]
What a rotten world we live in.
One filled to the brim with war,
murder and betrayal
at every turn.
And yet, one girl chooses to
live with honesty and integrity
in the face of such horrors.
I refuse to let her down
by not giving all that I have
to protect her!
[evil laughter]
[MONTMORENCY]
You may shoot a magical gun,
but you cannot possibly
hit my lances,
fashioned from hardened air.
I'll smite you
with my Invisible Spears.
First I will impale you,
then bite your head off
as you writhe in pain.
Now die, human.
Damn it!
[gunfire]
[screaming]
[LA HIRE grunting]
You're incredible, La Hire.
Perhaps you'll beat him.
[MONTMORENCY]
What is this?
[laughs]
It would appear that the Joyeuse
imbues its user
with the skill of
virtually infallible accuracy.
Whether or not
I can see the target,
it's impossible to miss!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[LA HIRE groans]
Have I reached
the time limit already?
[panting]
[JEANNE] Though it was
only for a short while,
I am grateful
for your protection.
Please take this.
No, not yet!
[grunts]
♪
[panting]
You're no god.
You're just a giant pain.
Oh, God.
How can this be?
[groaning]
[in normal voice]
I'm sorry you got involved.
Forgive me, La Hire.
[breathes shakily]
[LA HIRE groans]
Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY] I beg you,
please kill me and let it end.
You have to shoot me in the head
and finish this.
These awful gods have no place
in the world of humanity,
so seal them away.
[groaning]
Hurry, I can't hold him back
much longer!
I'm begging you to kill me!
[LA HIRE]
I can't do that.
[MONTMORENCY]
You have to.
It's the price we must pay
for Jeanne's future,
for the future of our world.
My life's a trifle
compared to that.
[LA HIRE panting]
[gasps]
♪
[grunts]
[ASTAROTH]
Montmorency, keep fighting!
Come back to us!
[in normal voice]
Do it now.
Someone please make it stop!
Let me die and save the world.
I beg you to kill me!
[grunts]
[gasps]
What fresh hell is this?!
I didn't think you could become
Ulysses twice in the same day.
Isn't that breaking the rules?
That's true, or so I thought.
Is that a problem?
[grunting]
Montmorency.
Don't give up yet!
I'm coming for you!
[grunts]
[groans]
[gasps]
[JEANNE breathing heavily]
[JEANNE]
You beg for death?
Don't you dare
even think such a thing.
How could you be such a fool?
You promised to always
protect me.
You swore it, remember?
You vowed
never to leave me alone.
To stay by my side
until the moment of my death.
Have you forgotten?
Well, then, be ready.
Because I'm about to beat
the sense back into you!
[distorted voice]
That's enough babbling, human.
[grunts]
I have no business with you,
foul demon,
so you had better
stay out of my way!
[grunts]
[MONTMORENCY]
How dare you insult your god?
You will pay a heavy penance
for that!
♪
[blows landing]
Montmorency, look into my eyes!
I know you're in there.
[in normal voice]
You're here? Jeanne.
[gasps]
[distorted voice]
No. I won't let this happen!
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAN] I hereby declare,
justice has been served.
She made a false claim
of sainthood
and lied about her purity.
But it's over.
She who would have plunged
France into eternal darkness
has perished at last.
[MONTMORENCY gasps]
[MAN] Let it be known
throughout the land.
The foul witch shall plague
us no longer.
[shudders]
[MONTMORENCY screaming]
[MONTMORENCY in normal voice]
How disturbing.
What a horrific nightmare.
But it's only a dream, right?
This can't possibly
come to pass.
So, then, what is this
heavy feeling
in the pit of my stomach?
This dreadful intuition that
what I glimpsed is the future.
Is this the wretched fate
that awaits Jeanne?
Is this her destiny,
no matter what I do?
[sobs]
[JEANNE]
Montmorency?
[evil laughter]
[NARRATOR] Montmorency's heart
is so full of darkness
that Jeanne's voice
cannot reach him,
and the powerful gods
descend from the void.
I've always been fond of
the saying, "Bigger is better,"
but I think
this is a little much.
Episode Eleven,
"Utopia, Then."
Sorry, folks, but this is
probably not the best time
to start talking about boobs!
[WOMAN]
Quel monde de merde.