[NARRATOR]
As the English army advanced,
the French royal court
escaped Paris
and relocated their palace
to Chinon, in the southwest.
When the king of France died,
a successor had to be crowned.
But his male descendants
had all perished in battle.
As a result, a female heir
ascended to the throne.
Princess Charlotte now sits
at the head of the royal court,
frightened,
and unprepared to rule.
With immense responsibility
and crushing loneliness
weighing on her heart,
Charlotte calls out a name,
that of an old friend
with whom she'd shared
a promise years before.
Montmorency.
-[JEANNE] A saint?
-[MONTMORENCY] Yeah.
-You mean me?
[MONTMORENCY] "France will be
saved by a brave young woman."
At least, that's the rumor
spreading throughout the land.
It's the talk of Paris,
Reims, Rouen,
and every other city and hamlet
from Flanders to Gascony.
Has this town heard the news?
I come bearing good tidings.
These whispers are more than
just fleeting gossip.
Truth be told,
it's just a rumor.
But a story like that
has only caught on
because the people of
this country want to believe it.
That the only ones capable
of ending this awful war,
are those who have been anointed
to the task by God himself.
Fear not.
God has not yet
abandoned France.
The Archangel Michael
descended from heaven
and chose a female saint
to save us.
[JEANNE]
No one in their right mind
would ever think
that's really true.
It's human nature to believe
what one wants to be the truth.
Hmm.
[MONTMORENCY] They want
a female saint to save them.
And if that saint happens
to have been born a peasant,
someone with whom
they can identify,
how happy would they be?
-I shall introduce her.
-[gasps]
[MONTMORENCY] The savior
of France is this young woman:
Jeanne of Domremy!
-[murmuring]
-[laughter]
That's your cue.
[crowd gasps]
[ASTAROTH] God appeared
to the maiden, Jeanne,
and he spoke thus:
"You will save France
from the English.
"You must end this bloody war
that has ravaged your land
for these past 80 years."
[MAN 1]
A fairy?
[MAN 2] No, I know fairies,
and I've never seen
nor heard of one
with wings like that.
[MAN 3] So, does this mean
this creature is...
It's an Archangel!
That's right.
This winged thing must truly be
the Archangel Michael.
[MAN] So, then, that girl
is the female saint!
Hmph!
[heavy breathing]
[heart beating]
[horse snorts]
[neighs]
[ASTAROTH] If we're able to gain
enough support
in the countryside
as we travel,
it will make it more problematic
for the inquisitors to label
-Jeanne as a heretical witch.
-Mm.
I'd also like to note
that you have far more talent
as a con artist
than an alchemist.
Thanks to
my archangel accomplice.
Excuse me?
I'm the queen who presides over
all the fairy tribes.
How dare you belittle thus?
I am far superior to archangels.
They're not even worthy
to clean my wings.
You sure are tiny for one
with such a lofty title, huh?
[chuckles]
Stop patting me on the head
like a dog!
You are my slave, and I refuse
to let you think otherwise.
Now that you've devolved
into a glorified elixir factory,
you can't even become Ulysses.
Yet for some ungodly reason,
I continue to keep you
on as a slave.
So, show me some gratitude.
Hmph.
[LA HIRE]
Aw! Damn.
She's just too adorable!
-[MONTMORENCY] Uh...
-[LA HIRE chuckles]
Your obsession with small women
is a disease.
Perhaps you should
go see a doctor.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
She was small once.
Before her town was torched,
and she lost everyone she loved.
La Hire was
an innocent little girl
by the name of Etienne.
Small women must remind her
of a time
before she was tainted by--
[grunts]
Not another word,
or I'll make you regret it.
How dare you call me
"tainted"? [grunts]
[XAINTRAILLES] Please.
I swear, I meant no offense.
-[JEANNE] Montmorency.
-What is it?
And what are you
even doing awake still?
Well, uh, I have
a small request to make.
Aw.
Jeanne, you're like a younger
sister to me, you know that.
And just like family, I would do
anything for you, understand?
-[JEANNE] You mean it?
-Yeah.
[JEANNE] Like, you really,
really, mean it?
Yeah.
Well, then can I have a kiss?
-Huh?
[JEANNE]
I've been burning up
ever since we left
the last village.
My throat feels so dry.
You can see why I'd feel awkward
asking you, but still.
It's the only way
I can get the elixir.
I really don't know
what else to do.
-Please help me.
-Ugh.
This is a very unfortunate
side effect of that idiot
breaking the Philosopher's Stone
in half.
Under normal circumstances,
the elixir only needs
replenishing every few years,
usually every few dozen years.
But in this case, it looks like
Jeanne will need it
every time
she activates Ulysses,
after the powers
have been used up.
In other words,
every time she becomes Ulysses,
she's going to have to pester
Montmorency for kisses,
like some saliva-crazed demon.
-No. Please, wait!
-[JEANNE] I can't.
[MONTMORENCY]
Can we at least do this
where no one else can see us?
No. Please help me.
I have to have the elixir now.
[LA HIRE] Dammit.
Montmorency, you bastard!
[ASTAROTH]
Satyr! Sick degenerate.
[MONTMORENCY] I'm not to blame.
She's resolute!
[shrieks]
[grunts]
We have to get out of here!
Don't just stand there,
you imbecile. Fight.
You have to protect Jeanne
at all costs.
[MONTMORENCY] Considering
we've been preaching for weeks
in every village we pass,
it's no surprise the Burgundian
troops would be after us.
-[MONTMORENCY grunting]
-[heavy breathing]
[MONTMORENCY] Right.
Let's go, Jeanne.
[grunts]
[JEANNE moaning]
♪
You... You just...
The elixir is so cool
and refreshing.
Thank you, I feel better.
I can hold them off,
so you should just run.
I refuse to leave you.
You only have three minutes.
Please don't forget that.
Hmm.
[ASSASSIN]
We won't stand a chance
if we fight her head on,
we must find another way.
I know this,
she can only maintain
the Ulysses state
for three minutes.
[groans]
[ASSASSIN chuckles]
She couldn't take
a life, then, could she?
[knock on door]
-[SOLDIER] Count La Tremoille.
-[LA TREMOILLE] What is it?
[SOLDIER] We've received
a letter for Princess Charlotte.
It's signed by someone called
"Montmorency."
[LA TREMOILLE gasps]
Say that again.
What was the name of the sender?
[SOLDIER]
It's, uh, Montmorency.
[shudders]
[gasps]
I'll be keeping that, thanks.
[indistinct conversations]
Hmm?
[MONTMORENCY]
I'll ask Charlotte.
She'll agree to confer
knighthood upon Jeanne.
A female saint allying
with the exiled government
will boost army morale
and energize the citizens.
This may be our chance
to actually end the war,
once and for all.
[XAINTRAILLES]
That Montmorency's quite a card.
He sure has some wild ideas,
don't you think?
Who would've thought he was
the Princess'
close childhood friend?
He's mysterious.
Just who is he?
-[JEANNE] Montmorency?
-Uh...
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
It's been seven years
since I last saw her, you know.
[JEANNE] If you explain
why you weren't able
to reach her all this time,
I'm sure she'll understand.
She is one of
your oldest friends.
-I hope so.
-[chuckles]
Hmm.
But I must admit, I'm feeling
a little nervous myself.
Would a princess really appoint
a peasant like me as her knight?
I just can't see why she would.
But what do you think?
Huh?
[SOLDIER]
This way, mademoiselle.
[JEANNE]
Monsieur.
Don't tarry.
Uh...
[sighs]
[MONTMORENCY groaning]
Hey!
[screaming]
[grunting]
That hurt.
Damn! What's this all about?
Are you...
Uh...
Richemont?
♪
[indistinct conversations]
[gasping]
[door hinges creak]
[JEANNE]
Um, pardon.
[sighs nervously]
Your Majesty, thank goodness.
[chuckles]
[CHARLOTTE] So, another
self-proclaimed saint
seeks my favor.
Self-proclaimed prophets,
self-proclaimed alchemists,
and all
the self-proclaimed mages.
So many false saviors
have made their way to my court.
And then, they knelt
before my decoy
and made embarrassments
of themselves.
Proving to all
that they possessed
no real power to speak of.
No one can save France,
and there is certainly no one
out there who can save me.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Jeanne.
I hail from
the village of Domremy.
By the way, is it common
practice here for someone
other than the princess
to sit upon the throne?
-[gasping]
-[murmuring]
[COURTIER 1] She saw through
the princess' wile.
[COURTIER 2] Could this
young woman really be a saint?
[COURTIER 3]
No, it's not possible.
[gasps]
[JEANNE]
Up there!
You have to be
the true monarch, Majesty.
I beg you.
If it be your will,
please make me a knight.
[exhales]
♪
[MONTMORENCY]
It's been seven years.
I have heard the rumors,
that you escaped on your own,
fought your way free
from the English.
But after you escaped, you came
under Charlotte's command.
I thought you had
become a general.
So, what are you doing
down here?
I investigated
rumored misconduct
high in the army's ranks.
For my pains, I was ostracized
by the corrupt nobility
and ended up in chains
for doing the right thing.
[MONTMORENCY laughs]
You've always been
a crusader for justice.
You're too righteous
and turn everyone against you.
-Tell me why.
-Huh?
Why did you abandon me
when I needed you most?
♪
[thunder rumbling]
[yells]
[groans]
[grunting]
[coughing]
♪
[grunts]
Kill me, then.
[HENRY V]
I like you.
Now that we are
no longer strangers,
I want you to become my knight.
[RICHEMONT exhales]
[BEDFORD]
Hmm.
[RICHEMONT] I accepted his offer
and joined with him.
France would be annihilated,
at any rate.
Someone would then have to play
the role of conciliator.
I thought it should be me.
However, not long after that,
Henry V,
who took me in,
passed away very suddenly.
My plan to redeem myself failed.
I returned to France as a knight
for the English,
a traitor to my homeland.
But then...
[BEDFORD]
"Upon my imminent death,
"I want you to continue
our noble quest
to make France
an English territory."
Those were
the King's dying words.
Don't make me repeat myself.
There will be no peace treaty,
and Princess Charlotte will have
to be overthrown, unfortunately.
You can't.
Oh, by the way, Lady Richemont,
I think that you should become
my wife now.
[RICHEMONT]
Huh? Your wife?
What are you talking about?
I am about to conquer
what's left
of your precious country.
No. I shall not stop
till I rule the heavens.
But first, I will
conquer you, my dear.
[gasping]
[BEDFORD] That little girl
I found on the battlefield,
she sure has grown up,
hasn't she?
-[RICHEMONT grunts]
-[thudding]
[groans]
Dammit, wench.
-[panting]
-[BEDFORD] Guards!
So, I did escape
the English army, technically.
Even though it meant being
labeled a treacherous deserter.
However, I had no other choice.
[MONTMORENCY]
Richemont.
I truly believed
that you would come rescue me.
But you let me down,
just like the rest.
So what happened,
why didn't you come save me?
[screaming]
[gasps]
What is the matter, madame?
Huh?
Huh.
[gasps]
[ASTAROTH] Grand Chamberlain
of the palace, La Tremoille.
I sensed something was off
about him from the start.
Now I know something
is very wrong in this castle.
Montmorency's
sudden disappearance
must be related to this.
Has to be.
[LA TREMOILLE]
Who would've guessed
the Archangel Michael
was actually a rare fairy?
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
How did you figure it out,
that the woman on the throne
was a double?
[JEANNE] Uh, well,
I was told the princess
had very large breasts,
even bigger than La Hire's,
which is saying something.
Montmorency was right.
Do you actually know
someone called Montmorency?
[JEANNE]
Uh, of course I do.
We're here because he gave
a letter to the gatekeeper.
It was addressed to you.
They told us you gave permission
to enter the castle.
So you should know Montmorency
sought an audience with you.
[CHARLOTTE]
I didn't receive any letter,
and where's Montmorency now?
[JEANNE] Um, well,
he disappeared without a trace
when we first arrived here,
which really puts me in a bind.
I see.
So, he just ran away.
[JEANNE]
Huh?
[CHARLOTTE chuckles]
Of course he did.
He must be too ashamed of
himself to look me in the eye.
[JEANNE]
Um, Your Majesty?
[CHARLOTTE]
He abandoned me so long ago.
All to play alchemist
in that silly little workshop.
It makes sense
that he'd forget his promise.
[JEANNE]
Montmorency isn't the kind
who goes around
breaking promises.
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[MONTMORENCY]
I never knew practicing alchemy
would distort my sense of time.
Forgive me.
I know that doesn't pass
for an excuse.
I'm a worthless piece of trash
who couldn't save his friend.
But please believe one thing.
[thuds]
The Inquisitors chased us
throughout France,
and we ran like
cowards the whole time.
But not because
of some fear of death.
I fled 'cause I had
to keep our promise.
[RICHEMONT]
Well, what are we waiting for?
[MONTMORENCY]
We solemnly swear...
[CHARLOTTE]
That no matter what...
[PHILIP] Even after we graduate
from the academy...
[ALL] We'll remain
best friends forever!
I always wanted it
to be a reality.
I knew the war
would get in the way,
so I wanted to end it.
That's why I continued running,
and why I came to this place.
Our vow has been in the front
of my mind this whole time.
See?
So, don't lose faith
in Montmorency.
Your Majesty, are you well?
[CHARLOTTE] You mean,
he lost all sense of time
for seven years?
In that case, he's not to blame.
But I simply can't forgive him!
He has no idea
how lonely and scared
I've been all these years.
For if he knew, he'd never
expect me to have faith in him.
[crying] I had no one
on my side to help me.
Not even my mother.
She abandoned me, too.
I'm so sorry, Your Majesty.
[gasps]
[shatters]
[gasping]
[screaming]
[MAN] I'm impressed
by your speedy reaction,
though it's too bad
you had to sacrifice your arm.
You think you've won
just because you broke my arm?
Your name?
I'll need it if I'm to give you
a proper burial.
[gasps]
Call me Maugris.
It's only an alias, though.
I shed my given name when
I decided to become an assassin!
-[grunts]
-[screaming]
[MAUGRIS grunting]
[MAUGRIS gasps]
You're a monster who's taken
the form of a young woman!
[shouting]
[grunts]
It appears this might be
your first fight to the death
in an enclosed space.
Let me tell you,
it's a whole different game
than fighting outdoors!
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
No!
[MAUGRIS grunting]
How pathetic,
you can't even fight a girl
without covering yourself
with that filthy breastplate.
Well, no matter.
I'll just have to crush it
along with your
useless war hammer!
[groaning]
[laughing]
If the metal had just been
a bit thinner,
I would have crushed
your stinking guts
with that last blow,
don't you think?
[groaning]
[snaps]
[groans]
[moans]
[ASSASSIN] The Domremy girl
reached her time limit
exactly on schedule.
I took advantage
of this one, fatal flaw.
[CHARLOTTE]
Who's there?
Who speaks?
[ASSASSIN]
I have sinned.
Forgive me, Majesty.
[gasping]
Richemont.
-[footsteps approaching]
-Huh?
[RICHEMONT]
It's you.
Why, hello, there.
It's been a while.
I never would have guessed.
But I'm somehow unsurprised
you'd be the one
to intercept my letter
to Princess Charlotte,
La Tremoille.
So, you're alive and kicking,
little step brother.
[ASSASSIN]
I left the unseemly fighting
to that brute and bade my time,
while she exhausted herself
battling him.
Help!
[ASSASSIN] There's no use
making a fuss, Majesty.
Rest assured,
I have no ill will towards you.
After all,
I'm only following orders.
To obtain
the Philosopher's Stone
by any means necessary.
[gasping]
♪
[NARRATOR] Some say breast shape
correlates with personality.
General Richemont is sharp,
like a sword,
and she has pointy breasts.
Princess Charlotte is selfish,
and her ample bosom
demands attention.
Philip the good
should have a good pair, no?
Episode four:
"Who was the Promise for?"
Philip's chest must be
something quite remarkable.
[WOMAN]
Tu me fais un bisou?