♪
[MAN]
Citizens, hear me!
Alas, Harfleur has fallen.
Nonetheless, fear not.
God has blessed France
with His divine protection!
The day is nigh whereupon
we drive out
the dogs of the English army,
and end this bloody war
once and for all.
[panting]
♪
[dog barking]
[SHOP KEEPER] Who goes there?
How dare you just barge in?
Can't you see
the store's not open yet?
[BOY] And when exactly
will you be open?
[SHOP KEEPER] Ah, I might have
known it was only you.
I don't have any new grimoires.
I should think you'd tire of
asking for them day after day.
Ugh.
Huh? What's that?
[sighs]
[gasps]
[scoffs] That volume exceeds
your reading aptitude.
Put it on my tab.
[door opens, closes]
Ridiculous.
Hmm?
[BOY]
Thank you kindly, Master.
I'm not your master, now leave.
[sighs]
Beast of the Apocalypse, huh?
[birds chirping]
[PROFESSOR] Our great nation
has long been under siege
by our neighbor
across the channel.
War with England
began in the last century,
the year of my birth, in fact.
You might be surprised to learn
that was nearly
80 years ago.
If this conflict persists
much longer,
historians of the future
wouldn't be remiss
to refer to it as
the "Hundred Years' War."
This vicious, enduring conflict
between the world's two dominant
Christian nations
for rule of the kingdom
has resulted in
copious bloodshed
and scorched earth,
plunging the populations
on both sides
into devastating hardship.
Absent again? Good grief.
[sighs deeply]
[grumbling]
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
[groaning]
[grunting]
That's as far as
I'll get on my own.
-[RICHEMONT] Montmorency.
-Uh...
[gasps]
Oh.
Richemont.
Can't you knock?
Why should I?
You left the door wide open.
[sighs] You have
the lowest marks
in military arts, martial arts,
and equestrian arts.
On top of that,
your poor attendance
puts you at an even
higher risk of failing.
As for this heresy you study--
It's not heresy.
It's called alchemy, all right?
[sighs]
[laughs]
Montmorency, where have...
Huh?
[BATARD] It looks like Richemont
got to him first this time.
[gasps] Never mind. Sorry.
Hmph.
Uh, so, um,
Montmorency's not here then?
He's not.
How is that boy so popular?
Ugh.
[MONTMORENCY] Transmutation
with the Philosopher's Stone.
It's the ultimate,
secret divine art.
They say the Stone has the power
to grant its owner immortality.
Which means,
if we can master alchemy...
Uh...
As I was saying,
if we master alchemy,
we can make sure
no one dies in battle again.
Was that a reaction?
I've heard this a hundred times.
[annoyed grunt]
So, you're gonna buy up
all the grimoires
you can find, then what?
I don't know yet.
I've read tons of them, and it's
like they're written in code.
I won't get anywhere
unless I convince that old man
to teach me to decipher them.
Nicolas Flamel.
He's an alchemist
rumored to have learned
the secret art of Kabbalah.
I don't know what
scurrilous rumors you've heard,
but I'm an old bookseller,
nothing more.
Ask someone else.
He's not fooling anyone.
You done talking now?
-Hmm?
-Good, come back to reality.
Don't you realize
our military has all
but escorted the English army
across front lines?
They've taken Harfleur,
and they're gaining traction.
As a member of the nobility,
you have a duty
to become a knight
and help your people
put an end to this war.
I don't want a job
that requires me to take lives.
I'd rather save them instead.
You're hopeless.
Oh, yeah. Are you free tonight,
by any chance?
[gasps]
♪
So, what am I
doing here, exactly?
-[MONTMORENCY screaming]
-[gasps]
-[CHARLOTTE] Hold it!
-Huh?
-[MONTMORENCY] Charlotte?
-[chuckles]
-[PHILIP sighs]
-[RICHEMONT] Philip?
Wait, fairies?
Yeah.
I saw them, plain as day.
[gasping]
Hey, were those... Uh...
♪
As you might know,
fairies are seen
as the familiars of demons.
They're hunted down
by the church.
So what is
Nicolas Flamel doing
keeping a bunch of them
in his house?
Well, I have a theory,
they must be
well-versed in alchemy.
[horse snorts]
Which brings us here.
If the old man
won't teach me alchemy,
then I'll just seek help
from the fairies.
Perhaps they can help me
get started, at least.
Hey, fairies don't typically
bite humans, do they?
Yes, I once heard a story
about a fairy
biting a little
girl's finger off.
[shrieks]
[MONTMORENCY]
Cut it out, Charlotte.
[annoyed grunt]
I also heard about a fairy
who entered a girl's body
through her mouth
and ate her innards.
-[gasping]
-[MONTMORENCY] Charlotte.
-Leave her alone.
-Hmph.
Be quiet.
You'll scare away the fairies.
Montmorency, why are you
so much nicer to Philip
than everyone else?
You know, you have a penchant
for stirring up trouble.
[all screaming]
Huh?
[groaning]
[PHILIP groaning]
[MONTMORENCY]
It happens to the best of us
every once in a while.
Don't worry about it.
It's all right.
Just so you know,
he's equally nice to everyone,
but Philip is very sensitive,
unlike you.
Why do you think I get so mad?
[gasps]
[RICHEMONT]
Watch out! In the trees!
-[groans]
-[grunting]
♪
[MONTMORENCY]
What is it?
Are these guys...
[RICHEMONT]
English soldiers.
Really?
-[grunts]
-Richemont!
[grunting]
[yelling]
Your fight is with me!
Leave her-- [groans]
-So weak.
-Oh.
Are you okay?
I'm perfectly fine.
-[groans]
-[yells]
[RICHEMONT]
No!
-[chuckles]
-[grunts]
[PHILIP]
Huh?
[MONTMORENCY]
Take this, you English dogs!
[coughing]
[CHARLOTTE]
You did it. What was that stuff?
-Pepper and ash.
-You mean it's not even poison?
[MONTMORENCY]
I don't make anything like that.
[CHARLOTTE]
For crying out loud.
-[groaning]
-[grunting]
-Just play along.
-Huh?
Turn back now,
for your own good!
Do you have any idea
who you're dealing with?
He happens to be
the foremost pupil
of the infamous Nicolas Flamel.
This young man is known
throughout France
as Montmorency,
the Alchemist of Black Death.
Now tremble before him!
[MONTMORENCY]
That's right.
And, for my next trick,
I shall turn your men to stone.
Sadly, I don't have
the antidote,
which means the effect
will be permanent.
[SOLDIER gasps]
[grunting]
[MONTMORENCY]
I just have to buy time
until Richemont
can take that guy out.
[grunting]
Now, Philosopher's Stone,
by your limitless magical power,
behold!
This mortal shall become
a mighty berserker.
Huh?
[yelling]
[grunting in effort]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[snickers]
Did you plan to die
together tonight?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[loud grunt]
[gasp]
[body thuds]
[shuddering breath]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[screams]
I knew the English
had crossed into France,
but they're farther
than I thought.
Hmm. You should be
all right now.
It's so different
than mock battle.
[MONTMORENCY]
You should be proud.
Hmm?
[MONTMORENCY] You're incredibly
strong, Richemont.
[RICHEMONT]
Montmorency.
[CHARLOTTE] We beat them
because of my strategy.
[MONTMORENCY]
Yes, I know. Excellent work.
[PHILIP] Um, I'm pretty sure
I played a significant role
in defeating those guys, too.
[annoyed grunt] You had better
give some of the credit
to my Philosopher's Stone,
too, you know.
[CHARLOTTE]
It's just a rock. Hmm?
[annoyed grunt]
[MONTMORENCY]
I found this thing buried
way back in the corner
of my family's storehouse.
There are heaps of ancient
magical treasures in there.
[PHILIP] Hmm. I'm pretty sure
it's just a rock.
You don't have to be
so condescending.
Jeez!
[chuckles]
[RICHEMONT] I wish we could
stay like this forever.
We study side by side,
and have such a close bond,
but I am of
the house of Brittany.
Charlotte's of
the French royal family.
And Philip's of
the house of Burgundy.
We live in mad times.
We may have to face each other
as political opponents someday,
or even fight
on opposing sides
of the battlefield,
heaven forbid.
But if at all possible,
I hope that we can remain
friends like this forever.
[sighs]
[MONTMORENCY]
I believe we can.
If that's what we want, why not?
We're the most
formidable team around,
and there's nothing
we can't do.
We did beat up these
English soldiers, after all.
Yeah. See?
[CAPTAIN] Curse all
you dirty French bastards.
-Shut up!
-[grunts]
-[CHARLOTTE] The stone.
-[MONTMORENCY] Damn it!
[all giggle]
[PHILIP]
Hey, we should swear an oath.
Huh?
A promise
to stay friends forever.
Hmph.
Well, what are we waiting for?
We solemnly swear...
That no matter what...
Even after we graduate
from the academy...
[ALL] We'll remain best
friends forever!
♪
[horse galloping]
[BATARD] Please, try to consider
the nature of your situation.
You are a noble lady, Charlotte.
And one in line to succeed
the throne, on top of that.
I do have two
older brothers, you know?
So, I highly doubt I'll be
succeeding the throne.
[BATARD] You should have let me
accompany you, at least.
I am your attendant, after all.
It is my sworn duty to put
my life on the line for you.
Oh.
That's so manly of you.
Yes!
Beginning tomorrow, you'll wear
women's undergarments.
Do you understand?
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE] Honestly,
it's a curse to have
a full, womanly figure
at such a tender age.
Must all men behave
like wild animals in heat?
[BATARD] I think you
misunderstand my intent here.
-[ALENCON] Then, we'll fight.
-Huh?
All you're doing is darting
around like a fly.
How dare you call yourself a
knight in training, Montmorency?
I hereby challenge you
to a duel.
Must we resort to violence?
[ALENCON] You put my Philip
in grave danger,
taking her into
the forest at night.
Philip does not belong to you.
Wrong! Don't you know
how it works?
No man may call himself a knight
until he swears
his love to a lady.
I've made up my mind.
I devote myself
entirely to Philip.
Well, then, Philip,
you heard Alencon.
How do you answer?
Hmm.
I apologize but I must decline.
-Huh? What?
-[SPECTATORS gasp]
[MONTMORENCY]
Great. Can I go now?
[ALENCON]
Curse you!
That's quite enough, Alencon.
[ALENCON]
Ah, sister.
I also went into the forest
with them last night.
Shall we have a duel too?
[ALENCON] No, I'd never do
something so dastardly.
Pathetic.
What could a child possibly know
about love
between a man and a woman?
I know a lot.
I have read
erotic literature, you know.
-Ah! Forget I said that.
-[SPECTATORS gasp]
Oh, Alencon,
this is clearly a result
of my sisterly negligence.
If this is to be righted,
I must harden my heart
and dole out a healthy dose
of discipline.
[ALENCON] Sister, please.
Let's not be--
[ALENCON grunts]
-[SPECTATORS gasp]
-[groans]
-You and I need to have a talk.
-Huh?
[wheezing]
♪
[RICHEMONT] I have received word
from my older brother.
He says the English troops
at Harfleur
have been stricken
by an epidemic
and intend
to retreat to Calais.
The French army will lie
in ambush at Azincourt,
waiting to deal
the decisive blow.
I see.
And so, I leave
for Azincourt tomorrow.
[gasps]
I'm joining the battle
as a representative of my line,
the house of Brittany.
Why does it have to be you?
Because my other brother
despises the battlefield.
By sending me,
my family can save face.
[grunting]
Then, I'm going with you.
What? Why that face?
[chuckles]
I remain undefeated in
the tournament of knights,
but you've lost
every round you've fought.
Hey, that's not nice.
Yeah, you're strong and smart,
and you come
from a noble family.
And you have a pretty face,
which you did nothing to earn,
by the way,
but that does not
give you the right
to look upon me
with such blatant pity.
-So stop it.
-[chuckles]
I'm glad we had this talk.
And look at that blazing sunset.
I don't think
I'll ever forget it.
Its beauty is seared
into my memory.
[NICOLAS]
Hmm.
Use the Philosopher's Stone
to make your friend immortal?
-No.
-[MONTMORENCY] Please.
There's not much time left.
I'm begging you.
To become more than human
carries enormous risk.
At the very least, it would mean
banishment from the church
for the rest of one's life.
I know.
Furthermore, immortality means
being on the run
for all of eternity,
living a solitary existence,
utterly devoid
of human connection.
I don't care.
I'm an old bookseller,
nothing more.
Ask someone else.
[sighs]
[NICOLAS]
Montmorency...
I'd hope that you'd remain
ignorant until your dying day,
but alas, you will not.
Fight against fate.
Beast of the Apocalypse.
[panting]
Brother.
-You're coming, then?
-Of course.
[chuckles softly]
[thunder rumbling]
[BEDFORD]
The French knights will mock us.
They'll say we sold our souls
to the devil.
Even as we meet them in hell.
[HENRY V]
Hell does not truly exist.
It's fiction, fodder for
the rambling of priests.
In my world view,
the only extant realms
are earth and heaven,
nothing more.
Now, let us offer the Frenchmen
our finest hospitality.
♪
[horse neighs]
[battle cry]
[KNIGHT]
Damn you.
What self-respecting Catholic
would bear the crest
of the devil so brazenly?
[gasps]
Henry V?
God, if you truly exist,
I beseech you...
-[shouting]
-[grunting]
...hear me.
Please don't let
Richemont perish.
[RICHEMONT panting]
[gasps]
[horse snorts]
[sobbing quietly]
[gasping]
[sobbing]
Richemont!
♪
[shuddering]
[JOHN]
Welcome back, daughter.
[PHILIP]
Hello, Father.
We have nothing
to fear now, my love.
We have finally finished
laying the groundwork
and will join forces
with the English army very soon.
[chuckles]
[PHILIP]
Hmm.
There is only one way
to rescue Richemont,
now that the English
have taken her.
I, myself, must become immortal
and strike out after them.
And if there's no God to aid me,
I shall sell my soul
to the devil.
♪
If you are truly a relic
of a civilization
that fell before
Christianity existed,
if you are a product
of sacred alchemy,
I implore you, be my guide!
In return, I offer you
my mortal soul!
Uh... [sighs]
Uh...
Hmm. [gasps]
♪
[gasps]
Who summons Astaroth,
queen of all fairies?
Wherefore...
[gasps]
What, a human?
You dare rouse me
from my sweet slumber?
What impertinence.
[cries]
The queen of the fairies
shall never lower herself
to a human's plaything,
no matter how dire her straits.
Therefore,
you shall be my servant.
-I accept.
-Uh...
You're not supposed to acquiesce
without a fight.
I only seek the power
to protect human lives.
I prayed for that
and you appeared,
as if in response.
It's almost like
some otherworldly force
impels me to become
such a protector.
[scoffs]
Very well, then.
I shall grant your wish.
I am the guardian of the
Philosopher's Stone, after all.
You need only swallow the stone,
and its immense power will be
yours to wield as you wish.
King Solomon.
Clovis I.
Otto the Great.
Even Jesus Christ himself.
Each achieved great things
through the power of the Stone
earning them the title
of "Ulysses."
But, wait.
If I am to wield the stone,
then you must show me
where it is.
You're dumb, even for a human.
In your hand.
One of your ancestors
must have been a member
of the Knights Templar, yes?
Contrary to popular belief,
their goal was not to reclaim
the Holy Land,
but rather to find
the Philosopher's Stone,
which you hold in your hand
like some cheap trinket.
[grunts]
[ASTAROTH]
But take care, Montmorency,
do not act rashly.
If you swallow
the Philosopher's Stone
in its current form,
it will turn to
a lethal poison and kill you.
You must first
transmute the stone
into a singular liquid,
known to the initiated
as "Elixir."
After you drink it,
your body will be able
to withstand the poison.
[grunting]
Ah! Damn it.
Nothing I do
seems to be working.
Well, you've no real talent.
[MONTMORENCY]
Shut up.
[MONTMORENCY sighs]
How long have I been
at this now?
Seven years.
What?
Uh...
[sighs]
[MAN]
Small breasts are perilous.
Should you become entranced
by them, it's over!
And you're not
the kind of sickos
who would lust after
the flat chests of little girls?
Well, are you?
Episode two.
"The Girl Called Jeanne."
I needn't worry about you lot.
Right?
[MAN 2]
Encore en rut, tel un animal.