[JOHN]
My daughter.
Father.
[JOHN] This is our chance
to turn Burgundy
into the most
powerful empire on Earth.
[VOICES overlapping]
[PHILIP]
Montmorency.
♪
[indistinct voices chattering]
[MAN] I hereby declare,
justice has been served.
She made a false claim
of sainthood
and lied about her purity,
but it's over.
She who would have plunged
France into eternal darkness
has perished at last.
[MONTMORENCY gasps]
[MONTMORENCY screaming]
♪
[JEANNE]
Montmorency.
[snickers menacingly]
[JEANNE cries softly]
Jeanne, what's become
of Montmorency?
What's going on?
You okay?
[gasps]
What now?
[grunting]
No. Could this really be
happening so soon?
[screaming]
Jeanne, no!
I've lost him.
I can't hear Montmorency's voice
anymore.
It feels as though
he's truly gone.
Montmorency!
Mur d'Air, was it?
Look familiar?
[JEANNE gasps]
[evil laughter]
Montmorency.
[ENLIL] No, love.
You shall address me as Enlil.
Ruler of the true Utopia,
and king amongst
all the 72 gods.
Show some respect.
[gasps]
[PHILIP]
Montmorency.
You're truly gone.
[JOHN]
You must avenge him, daughter.
[PHILIP gasps]
Avenge him?
[JOHN]
Yes.
Kill the God and gain
a reputation as the God killer.
Become the savior in black.
Saint Philip.
You will be known
throughout France and England.
This shall be the foundation
for the rise
of the Burgundian Empire.
[PHILIP gasps]
[JOHN] For you, my daughter,
have the upper hand.
[gasps]
Huh?
[GLASDALE] I pulled you out
of the river, along with this.
[PHILIP]
The Grail.
Indeed.
The truth is,
if that young alchemist
turned into Ulysses,
then my arrow
should be effective.
That's good news.
But unfortunately,
he also has the ability to block
my attack with a wall of air.
[PHILIP]
We can use Jeanne as a sacrifice
and create an opening
for you to take the shot.
[GLASDALE]
Oh?
[PHILIP] This will be
quite a boon for you,
as well as Lord Bedford.
May I count on your assistance?
-Can you do it?
-Huh?
[GLASDALE] Noire, or rather,
Princess Philip of Burgundy.
I hear you refuse to squash
even a single insect.
Your nickname is
Philip the Good, after all.
[PHILIP]
Mm-hmm.
Will you prevail?
[PHILIP] I suppose
this must be my destiny.
I'm fated to avenge Montmorency.
Now I understand this must be
why the helm
came into my possession.
In which case,
I shall defy my nickname,
and clothe myself in black.
♪
Now, should I
put my faith in you?
[GLASDALE]
Absolutely.
[gasps]
Oh, no.
Pierce them both at once.
-Die, you scum!
-[gunfire]
Protect yourself!
[LA HIRE groaning]
♪
-Jeanne.
-[JEANNE] What is it?
How long can we fight
as Ulysses?
Not for long, I'm afraid.
[BOTH gasp]
[grunts]
I'll act as your shield.
You have to destroy
Montmorency's head.
[JEANNE gasps]
Your hearts are linked, so you
should know better than anyone.
That creature over there
is no longer Montmorency.
[JEANNE sobbing quietly]
There's no time
to wrestle with it!
[evil laughter]
[LA HIRE]
Strike, magical bullet!
[groans sharply]
[LA HIRE]
Do it now.
Go!
♪
[yells]
[groans]
Could this really be the end?
[coughs]
[scoffs]
[ENLIL]
And now, come, my followers!
The time of judgment
is at last upon us.
♪
Hmm.
It seems you have remained
in the Void Dimension
far too long.
Hold on. This is not at all
what we expected.
Is that monstrosity
even a Ulysses?
I'm having doubts that my arrow
will serve its purpose.
[ULYSSES NOIRE] This "god" made
no attempt to kill Montmorency
and take out
the Philosopher's Stone
from his body.
Why do you suppose
that might be?
Just as I suspected,
a superior host
will be necessary.
It's the only way
we can maintain our form
and consciousness
at their full power.
Oh, well, then I shall become
the one and only god
to ever obtain a host
for such a purpose.
That is a Ulysses.
Ready your bow, Glasdale.
[XAINTRAILLES]
Damn it!
I promised myself
I wouldn't die a virgin!
[BATARD]
What?
I had my heart
set on you, Etienne,
but it doesn't look like there's
any hope of that happening.
I suppose I'll just have to
settle for you, then, Batard.
[ALL screaming]
[ENLIL]
Utopia will be restored.
I'll return the Earth
to its rightful state
and there will no longer be
a place for humanity in it.
The next generation of slaves
shall not be made in our image
as they have been in the past.
They will obey our commands
without resistance
or conscious thought.
[NICOLAS]
Such tragedy.
Will this be the end
of the human race?
Is this how our species
will fall?
What are you doing?
I am the one who turned
the humans against their gods.
If you need a scapegoat,
punish me.
Burn me forever.
Rip me apart all you want.
I don't care.
But please spare the humans.
Just punish me!
Do not-- [groans]
[gasps]
[screams]
I'll hear no more from you.
Just lie there helplessly
and witness the destruction
of this false Utopia.
[GLASDALE]
It isn't time, not yet.
Now, respond to the sound
of my voice,
vessel in the sky.
♪
[gasps weakly]
-[ULYSSES NOIRE grunts]
-[ENLIL groans]
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
Glasdale, do it now!
[arrow firing]
[ULYSSES NOIRE] I dedicate
this act of revenge to you.
I love you, Montmorency.
I always have.
♪
How is that even possible?
This story isn't over,
not just yet.
Montmorency hasn't left
this realm completely.
I can sense
his presence even now,
waiting to be restored.
[ULYSSES NOIRE gasps]
[ENLIL] How long do you intend
to cling to me like this?
-Release me!
-[groans]
[ULYSSES NOIRE groans]
Damn it all.
Pathetic human.
-[groans]
-[ENLIL] Hmm?
[ULYSSES NOIRE groaning]
[ULYSSES NOIRE] I couldn't tell
he was still here.
But you could.
You were able to feel
his presence,
and that means...
you are the only hope we have
of saving Montmorency.
[JEANNE sighs]
[ENLIL] Enough of this
ridiculous babbling.
[groans]
[chuckles]
Montmorency!
♪
Huh?
Where am I?
Hello?
Excuse me, sir.
Have you seen my friend,
Montmorency?
Huh?
[JEANNE]
Sorry. I, um...
I think I've heard
Jean the Redbeard's grandson
called that before.
There.
The school.
[birds chirping]
[MONTMORENCY] Transmutation
with the Philosopher's Stone.
It's the ultimate secret
divine art.
They say the Stone has the power
to grant its owner immortality.
Which means,
if we can master alchemy...
[gasps]
As I was saying,
if we master alchemy,
we can make sure
no one dies in battle again.
Was that a reaction?
I've heard this a hundred times.
[MONTMORENCY sighs]
So, you're gonna buy up
all the grimoires
you can find, then what?
I don't know yet.
I've read tons of them,
and it's like
they're written in code.
I won't get anywhere unless
that old man can teach me.
[JEANNE]
Montmorency!
I'm so relieved.
I was afraid
I wouldn't find you!
[chuckles]
And who are you?
[JEANNE] What do you mean?
It's me. Jeanne.
Only students are allowed to be
on the premises,
so you had better go.
You don't wanna get in trouble.
[JEANNE] Come on, stop playing
dumb with me, Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY]
Let go of me.
I do not know you.
So, I'll thank you
not to touch me.
Please leave.
♪
[gasps]
Could it be?
Montmorency is stuck
in his past,
reliving all his old memories?
[PHILIP] Hey,
we should swear an oath.
[MONTMORENCY]
Huh?
A promise to stay
friends forever.
Hmph.
Well, what are we waiting for?
We solemnly swear...
That no matter what...
Even after we graduate
from the academy...
[ALL] We'll remain
best friends forever!
[JEANNE]
Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY]
You again?
Please just hear me out,
Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY]
How dare you?
Don't speak to me
as though you know me.
You must think I'm someone else.
[JEANNE]
The Philosopher's Stone.
You split it in two
and gave me half.
I was on the verge of death
and you did it to save my life.
So many things have happened
since then.
We went to the palace in Chinon,
and Charlotte made me a knight.
We fought together against
the English army at Orleans.
When my heart was pierced,
you stepped in and saved--
[MONTMORENCY]
Please stop.
You swore you'd protect me
for as long as we lived.
No matter what!
And you said you'd never marry.
Like the knights
who professed allegiance
to noblewomen,
-maintaining their purity...
-Stop it.
-...and devoting themselves...
-Quiet!
...to service.
I can't take any more!
[JEANNE screaming]
[JEANNE]
Where am I now?
♪
[CATHERINE]
What are these?
[MONTMORENCY]
My sisters are sleeping here.
The girls who were taken
to the castle.
I never saw them after that
because they all died
in the tower.
They wanted to go home
and see their families again
but when they realized
that would never happen,
they lost all hope
and died of broken hearts.
I wish I could have saved them,
but I failed as a brother.
No, Montmorency,
it isn't your fault.
Jean the Redbeard did this.
The old man has gone mad, true.
But he became that way
only because of the war.
The strong are the ones
who survive.
You have to step on others,
or else you'll get trampled
like all the rest.
In a world that cruel,
people have no other choice
but to be like him.
Even if we killed him,
that truth would not be changed.
It's just how things are.
Unless someone can end this war,
the tragedies will never cease.
Alchemy.
If I master this art,
I will make sure
no one dies in battle again.
No.
I will aim higher
and put a stop to war itself.
[JEANNE]
Montmorency.
-[MONTMORENCY] Hmm?
-[JEANNE] Let's go home.
Let's work hand in hand
to end the heartbreak.
I'm sure the two of us
can do it.
If we work as one,
nothing can stop us.
We cannot be together.
[gasps]
♪
[JEANNE gasps]
[JEANNE]
Is this my ribbon?
[MONTMORENCY]
I've seen the future.
I know what will happen to you.
[JEANNE]
What do you mean?
Is it bad?
Oh, no. But this can't be.
[MONTMORENCY]
I witnessed the flow of time,
when I merged with Enlil.
I learned about events
that happened in the past,
and some that are yet to come.
Can't you feel it?
This isn't an illusion, Jeanne.
It's what's destined
to become of you.
But it'll be all right,
as long as we stay
right where we are.
♪
[JEANNE]
I remember this place.
[MONTMORENCY] Yeah, it hasn't
been so long since we were here,
and yet that day
still feels like ages ago.
This realm isn't real,
at least not in a literal way.
We stand outside of time.
We could settle down
and forget all about the world
we came from.
As long as I have you,
I will want for nothing.
♪
[JEANNE]
We can't stay, Montmorency.
I know our world
is full of sadness.
There is war, misunderstanding,
betrayal, too.
But I still love it,
in spite of its faults.
Princess Charlotte's there,
La Hire, Astaroth,
and Richemont, too.
And there's Alencon, Batard,
and even Xaintrailles.
The Maiden Volunteer Corps,
and the villagers,
and the fairies, and...
I cherish that world
because they're in it.
I know you feel the same way.
That's the whole reason
you studied alchemy.
To make the world
a better place.
I refuse to live in a world
without you in it,
where we cannot be together.
That's true.
We can't be together
in the way we want,
but I will always be with you.
In a world where not just
the strong survive,
and no one has
to step on each other.
You and I are going to create
that reality together.
If we do that, we'll never die.
I will be there in every smile
and every laugh.
I am never going to desert you,
Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY]
You're so foolish.
You're starting to sound
like an actual saint.
[MONTMORENCY sobbing quietly]
I left you all alone,
and I was gone for far too long.
But from now on,
I'll stay by your side.
Let's go.
Come back to our world with me.
[MONTMORENCY]
Yes, it is our world, isn't it?
[ENLIL groaning]
[screaming]
[MONTMORENCY]
Get out of my body!
I banish you forever!
♪
[gasps]
[ENLIL]
No, impossible.
This simply can't be happening.
[chuckles]
[ENLIL]
Damn you, filthy human!
Vessel in the sky!
[screaming]
No.
This is nothing
but a false utopia.
You are wrong, fools.
It must not be allowed to exist!
♪
We two have been chosen,
but not by the gods,
and not by destiny.
Yes, you chose me,
and I chose you.
[MONTMORENCY]
Creating utopia.
That must be something
that can't be achieved alone.
We have to do it together.
Our eternity will soon exist,
but only in the world
that you and I will create.
♪
[ENLIL]
No. Impossible!
Your time is over now, demon.
We'll build our world,
and with our own hands.
♪
[NARRATOR] As we walk
through this world without gods,
our footprints
will eventually disappear,
yet our feelings
will endure forever.
They shall be written
into history
and passed down
till the end of time!
Final episode.
"In this Wonderful World."
Viva la boobs!
[MAN]
Proteges tes bijoux de famille.