[NARRATOR] The conflict between
England and France
continued to escalate
and was set to reach its climax
at the Siege of Orleans.
If the English were to succeed
in conquering the city,
they would surely
be able to topple
the rest of southern France
with relative ease.
On the other hand,
if France were to defend Orleans
from being taken by the English,
they would then be able
to escort Princess Charlotte
to her coronation ceremony.
In service of the cause,
Montmorency was hard at work,
attempting to lead a regiment of
about a hundred men to Orleans,
along with provisions.
However, the only bridge
they could use
to cross the Loire
was already occupied
by the English army,
and the impregnable
Tourelles complex
sat on the southern shore,
preventing Montmorency
from crossing.
[MONTMORENCY] A frontal assault
will be quite difficult.
-[grunting]
-Hmm.
[MONTMORENCY]
It looks like our only option
is to sneak around
to the eastern side,
where it's not
as heavily guarded,
and transport the provisions
across the Loire on boats.
-Astaroth.
-[ASTAROTH] Hmm?
[MONTMORENCY] Find the
commanding officer in Orleans.
Have him send us troops
to use as a diversion.
[sighs]
Yeah, yeah.
[ASTAROTH sighs]
[ASTAROTH] All this work
almost makes me wish
I couldn't fly.
[SOLDIERS clamoring]
Bring everything to the barn
in back.
And please be careful,
there's no need to rush.
We're almost there!
I believe in every one of you.
[BATARD]
Montmorency.
Oh, hello, Batard.
-[JEANNE gasps]
-Long time no see.
Oh, wow! had no idea
the commanding officer
was a princess knight.
Uh, I'm not a girl, I'm male.
It's just that
my cousin, Charlotte,
has forced me to dress
in girls' clothing
ever since I was a baby,
so I get why you'd think that.
I don't want a boy cousin.
I want a girl to play with,
someone like me.
Oh. I see.
Well, that explains
why your chest
is even flatter than mine.
[screams]
Girls scare me a little,
so please don't touch.
[MONTMORENCY]
Being bullied by Charlotte
left him with some scars, I see.
[BATARD] I'm not scared
of gentlemen, though.
So feel free to touch me
if you'd like, Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY]
I think I'll pass.
[JEANNE] If you don't want to,
then why are your cheeks so red?
[MONTMORENCY]
Could we focus, please?
-Ugh. What a bunch of fools.
-[MONTMORENCY] Huh?
I'd heard rumors, but I wasn't
prepared to see you
with an archangel on your hat.
Who's he?
Alencon.
Richemont's younger brother.
My sister is a selfish brat.
Don't say that.
[ALENCON] She is a disgrace
to the tradition of knighthood.
[BATARD]
Uh-uh.
Well, at least we have her.
I have always dreamed
of fighting alongside
an inexperienced shepherdess.
[giggles]
I'm flattered.
[MONTMORENCY] You're not
familiar with sarcasm, are you?
Huh?
It's not too late
to turn this around.
Send the poor thing
back to Domremy.
[JEANNE]
What?
[door opens]
[SOLDIER] They're about to break
through the front line!
[ALENCON]
I'll be right down.
Don't you understand,
Montmorency?
Dressing a poor shepherd girl
in armor
and throwing her into battle
violates the very code
of chivalry we knights live by.
[MONTMORENCY] He's even more
insufferable than he used to be.
It's not been easy for him,
living in his sister's shadow
all these years.
[JEANNE sighs]
♪
[neighs]
[ALENCON] You must view this
as an opportunity, Alencon.
If you shift the tide of this
battle on your own,
without your sister
getting in the way,
then no one can ever call you
the useless
little brother again.
♪
[SOLDIERS clamoring]
[ALENCON]
Fear not, men.
Justice is on our side!
Therefore, God is
on the side of France as well!
[neighing]
Hyah!
[gasps]
Out of my way!
What?!
[grunts]
[groaning]
[ALENCON]
What on earth was that?
♪
[gasping]
[JEANNE]
Why not fight me instead?
I'm a worthy adversary.
[ALENCON] Is this
the same girl from before?
What happened?
She carries herself
like a warrior now.
Who are you, then?
I'm Ulysses Noire.
[JEANNE]
Noire?
You call yourself
the Black Ulysses?
Interesting.
Then I shall test your mettle.
Let us see if you deserve
to bear the name Ulysses.
♪
[ALENCON] This is no fight
between mere mortals.
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
I've been dying to watch you.
Honestly, the main reason
I came here
is to see you in action
on the battlefield. [laughs]
[JEANNE] You wont be laughing
for much longer!
♪
[grunting]
-[JEANNE chuckles]
-[ULYSSES NOIRE] She's too fast.
[groans]
[grunts]
[panting]
[grunting]
♪
[scoffs]
I can't believe you actually
dodged my attack.
[chuckles]
-[MONTMORENCY] Jeanne!
-[ULYSSES NOIRE gasps]
Come back!
[MONTMORENCY]
Stop chasing her.
Remember, you can only fight as
Ulysses three minutes at a time.
Ugh!
[MONTMORENCY]
Are you all right?
[sighs]
[yelling]
Fall back at once!
I am just so honored!
To bask in the presence
of a real saint?
I can't believe
I would be so lucky!
I never knew there was a woman
as wonderful as you
in the entire world!
Relax, you can give her
a handshake later.
Oh, no, I'd prefer
not to, thanks.
[groans]
[grunts]
♪
[BEDFORD]
Ulysses.
I suppose they're saying
the legends are true, then.
Overwhelming fighting power?
I'll buy that.
But England has always
been known
as a land of monsters, too.
When one studies
our military history,
they essentially study
the history
of hunting abominations.
This is nothing we haven't
encountered before.
Isn't that right, Glasdale?
[GLASDALE]
It's gonna cost ya.
[BEDFORD]
Don't worry about that.
Money is no obstacle
to our aims.
Bring her to me dead or alive.
Hunt down that hideous monster.
Forgive me if my saying
"monster" was insensitive.
I meant no offense.
[BEDFORD laughs]
[chuckles]
[GLASDALE]
I hope you can refrain
from taking matters
into your own hands next time.
We work as a team or not at all.
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
Yes.
[chuckles]
[cheering]
[MAN 1]
Our beloved saint!
[MAN 2]
The Blessed Maiden of Domremy!
[MAN 3] The archangel
is with them as well!
I don't feel right
receiving this praise.
I'm not a real savior,
so the fanfare
makes me feel bad.
[ASTAROTH]
Stop with that nonsense.
You are a real savior
in your own right.
Really?
Well, then, thank you!
Thank you!
Let's beat England as one!
♪
I still can't believe you were
able to get past
an English fortress so easily.
The most important factor in war
is the person in command.
Also, at this time of year,
strong winds blow
in from the Loire
at certain times of day,
and I know when they do.
Light up a fire, and the rest
will take care of itself.
France is our country.
-We've a geographical advantage.
-[gasping]
[laughs]
[BATARD] You're the best,
Montmorency!
[MONTMORENCY]
Please, I mean no offense,
but I don't like boys.
[BATARD laughing]
[grunts]
Enough!
[MONTMORENCY]
Um, sorry.
[gasps]
♪
[JEANNE moaning]
[exhales]
That's so rejuvenating.
Would it kill you
to ask me for once?
Sorry. I can't help it.
I simply don't feel like myself
unless I've had a little elixir.
♪
[MONTMORENCY groans]
[JEANNE]
I need more, Montmorency.
Just a little, and then I
promise I'll leave you alone.
[MONTMORENCY] Get away!
Now you're just being greedy.
[JEANNE]
No, I need more. Please!
[MONTMORENCY]
You've had plenty.
This is absurd.
Leave me be!
[JEANNE breathing heavily]
Ugh! This is wrong.
Why'd I agree
to let her sleep here?
[ASTAROTH]
Montmorency.
The more Jeanne kisses you,
the faster your feelings
toward her change.
You're starting to see her
as an attractive member
of the opposite sex.
It's not like that.
[ASTAROTH] But you are male,
and she's female.
You cannot deny your
primal instinct to procreate.
Humans are no different
from animals
in that regard, unfortunately.
[MONTMORENCY]
This is absolutely wrong.
I have to come up
with a solution at once.
[MONTMORENCY grunts
in frustration]
There is one solution
that comes to mind.
[MONTMORENCY]
What is it?
[ASTAROTH]
I need the Stone.
[MONTMORENCY]
Huh? Okay.
♪
[gasps]
Who is this?
If you manage
to harness the power
of the Philosopher's Stone
to its fullest extent,
this ethereal beauty
will devote herself to you.
I had no idea
the Philosopher's Stone
held such secrets.
I assure you,
if you take her into your arms,
you will never again be charmed
by the wiles of human women.
-[MONTMORENCY] I can't do it.
-[ASTAROTH] Hmm?
[MONTMORENCY]
I won't deny
the intoxicating
power of her beauty.
Nevertheless, true love
cannot be built
on physical attraction alone.
You have to know
your partner deeply.
[chuckles]
Fooled you, huh?
That's just something I read
once in a silly romance novel.
[ASTAROTH sighs]
Uh...
Where are you going?
[ASTAROTH]
No one has succeeded yet.
No wielder of the Stone
has been able to hold her.
I blame heroes
and their lust for glory.
They swarm like moths
to the fires of war,
blinded by their desire
for power.
And, thus, every one of them
chooses to forget her.
♪
[MONTMORENCY]
What's going on out there?
The peasants are
attacking the tower.
[MAN 1]
We're tired of the English
doing whatever they please.
We'll stop them
once and for all.
[MAN 2] We have a saint
fighting on our side.
[MAN 3]
If we die in battle,
we shall be rewarded
in the kingdom of God!
[MONTMORENCY] They're heading
toward the Tourelles complex?
But all the English troops are
holed up inside the fortress.
They'll all be slaughtered.
We don't have a sound strategy
for defeating
Ulysses Noire, either.
So why didn't you stop them?
[BATARD]
I tried, believe me,
but none of them
would listen to a word I said.
[ALENCON]
This whole thing is your fault.
Excuse me?
If morale is too low,
people refuse to follow orders.
But if they get too worked up,
they become even
harder to control.
You and that saint.
You filled their heads
with fanatic nonsense.
I will take command.
Any objections?
Uh...
[ALENCON] This violates
the code of chivalry,
but as we are desperate,
we must use the mob headed
to Les Tourelles as a diversion
and direct our forces
toward the other fortress.
We'll have to accept
that many will die,
but it won't be in vain.
[MONTMORENCY] That's a logical
course of action.
Richemont trained him to be
a highly effective warrior.
[JEANNE]
Count Alencon, we can't do that.
[MONTMORENCY]
Jeanne.
We must fight alongside
those headed towards Tourelles.
We came all this way to save
the citizens of Orleans,
and if we use them
as a diversion,
the journey to this point
will have been for nothing.
We simply don't have
the manpower
to stand a chance
against professional soldiers
guarding an impregnable
fortress.
[JEANNE]
I'll fight at Les Tourelles,
even if I have to go alone.
But, Jeanne, if you get
killed there,
then Orleans will surely
fall to the English!
And if that happens, the English
soldiers will work themselves
into a frenzy of bloodlust,
and they won't care
that I'm a boy.
They'll just take me anyway
and use me as they please!
[crying]
Oh! I want my mother!
War calls for careful strategy
and discipline.
If our emotions take over,
then we are lost.
-We'll fall to them one by one.
-Please help me!
You must remain strong.
And, Jeanne...
[grunts]
[ASTAROTH] Jeanne's emotions
are reverberating
against the power of the Stone.
She's on the verge
of losing control.
How can we stop it?
[ASTAROTH]
We can't, I'm afraid.
No one can stop her
at this point,
she's too far gone.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
What a strange turn of events.
-[yelling]
-[grunting]
[grunts, groans]
[ALENCON]
Damn it!
Who would've thought they'd
attack head-on with no strategy?
That movement reeks
of sheer desperation.
Well, no matter.
I am here to do a job
and I'll follow through,
regardless.
[JEANNE]
I'm sorry, Montmorency.
There's no need to be sorry
that you're fighting
for the lives of peasants.
I expect that.
Now, if you'd agreed
with Alencon,
-I'd have been shocked.
-[JEANNE] Hmm.
Wait for the right moment,
you got it?
[JEANNE]
Hmm.
[MAN 1]
God save the maiden!
[MAN 2] You are no longer men
but shields for her,
Heroes of Orleans!
[SOLDIER 1] These are not
the French peasants
we're accustomed to fighting.
[SOLDIER 2] The witch of Domremy
turned them into demons!
She's made them immortal!
[ALENCON] Their fear
is giving over to passion.
So far, it's just as
Montmorency predicted.
[gasps]
[GLASDALE]
Where's the Ulysses?
Glasdale.
One William Glasdale, that is.
Before you perish,
I think you should know the name
of the man who's responsible.
You witch. Ulysses.
Enemy of all mankind.
You couldn't be killed.
And so, I've come
to help my fellows
reduce you to dust and ashes.
-Here they are.
-[BATARD shrieks]
That's right.
When the battle drags
on like this,
the commanding officer will come
fight on the front line.
Where's Jeanne?
Run for cover, men!
Go! Now!
Retreat!
Go!
Hurry!
Now! Attack!
♪
What?
[JEANNE]
You're mine!
[JEANNE yelling]
[grunts]
Jeanne! She's hit!
♪
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
The power granted to you
by your Philosopher's Stone
is known as "acceleration."
But it's not possible
to accelerate
while you're in free fall.
Sorry, that's the rule.
Glasdale's attack
was only a diversion.
Designed to make you
launch into the air
and initiate a free fall attack,
so that I could step in
and capture you.
[GLASDALE]
Poor little French girl.
My first projectile was a feint.
Now, have a taste
of my actual weapon.
Ashes to ashes, demon.
No! It can't be.
[JEANNE]
Let go of me!
[ULYSSES NOIRE] How fitting,
that this is the end
God chose for us.
We will die together,
with our purity intact.
While our dear Montmorency
watches helplessly from afar.
[gasps]
You speak as if you know me.
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
Ashes to ashes.
Those who pass away are destined
for the realm of the dead.
So die, Jeanne, and we
will meet again there.
♪
[BOTH groan sharply]
[gasps]
[thumping]
[GLASDALE] Just as
one would expect of monsters,
you're still alive,
animated by the devil.
But, alas, this arrow
was fashioned
from a sliver
of the Holy Lance of Antioch.
The spear that killed Jesus.
It is a Philosopher's Stone.
Even without drinking the elixir
or sacrificing my own humanity,
I have the power to wield it
as a weapon.
One that is capable
of killing any Ulysses,
no matter how powerful.
Ordinarily, Ulysses can
regenerate any part of the body
except for the brain.
However, organs taken
by this weapon will not heal.
He who wields the Holy Lance
is an agent of God,
sent to hunt you down.
You're a scourge
and must be exterminated.
Hear my holy title.
I am the Ulysses Hunter.
[ULYSSES NOIRE scoffs]
[ULYSSES NOIRE]
Eternal separation
from the one you cherish.
Your love for Montmorency
is a weakness,
for it makes you fear death.
And then there's me.
I'm simply awaiting death
with nothing binding
my heart to this realm.
I was no match for you
from the beginning.
Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY]
Jeanne.
[gasps]
Please, no.
[heart thumping]
[JEANNE]
Montmorency.
[MONTMORENCY screaming]
You can't die!
♪
[gasping]
Retrieve the witch's body, now.
And remove
the Philosopher's Stone
from within her corpse.
He who takes the stone from her
will be handsomely rewarded
by the Duke of Bedford.
[SOLDIER] Who's this man
who killed our saint?
How are we going to win
without her?
[clamoring]
[MAN]
Get out of the way!
Montmorency, we must retreat.
Did you not hear him?
Get going!
Snap out of it.
Do you wanna die here?
♪
[MONTMORENCY]
Jeanne.
She's dead.
[NARRATOR] The most
beautiful shape in all of nature
is that of Etienne's breasts,
which are almost
perfect spheres,
uniform in height,
width and length.
That's why I refer to them
as golden breasts.
Episode seven,
"Rain and Memory in Brittany."
My earlier speech had naught
to do with the preview,
but I'm sure you'll get over it.
[MAN] Il y a vraiment des femmes
splendides en ce Monde.