♪
[HAIRO]
All right, Class Three,
the big PK Festival's
in a month.
Let's hear some ideas.
[SAIKI]
Every fall, PK Academy
holds the PK Festival.
And as you can see
by my expression,
I'm very excited.
'Kay, that's one.
Hang on, I can't participate
because I'm doing dance club.
It's the same thing
with my music club.
[HAIRO]
We can work something out.
[GIRL 1] What about a display?
That way, we're free
during the festival
to have fun?
Hm. Not bad.
We could work hard on it
every day after school.
I'm in a club after school, so
that won't work for me, either.
Yeah, I can't do anything then
because I have work.
Dude, what's that
in your hand?
What? Oh, this?
Just a rock
I found out front.
It's so funny-looking,
I couldn't resist it.
Hey, we could put that
funny poop rock on display.
[all cheer]
[AIZAWA]
In fact, we can display
every weird-looking rock
we find!
[BOY]
We could knock out this thing
--in one afternoon!
--[ALL] Yeah!
What you say, Hairo?
--Are you in?
--[ALL] Yeah!
Great! Class 3 will display
weird rocks found lying
--around in the schoolyard.
--[ALL] Agreed!
No way!
We only get to do three
PK festivals during high school,
and we are not wasting one
on rocks!
I wanna see some
real passion out of you!
He's right, guys. We gotta do
better than that.
Better cancel
all my after-school plans.
Do it for
Hairo.
--Of course.
--[SAIKI] That was easy.
--[HAIRO] Brainstorm, take 2.
--[ALL] Yeah!
[SAIKI] The rock thing
was dumb, but fine.
And just like that, I've got
the perfect idea for us.
--[BOY 2] Yeah, what?
--[HAIRO] Each one of us
will make 1,000
paper cranes, cool?
That comes out to 36,000 cranes
for the entire class.
Actually, let's round up to 50.
1,389 per person
in a month
shouldn't be hard.
[SAIKI] Even Hairo
can't sell 'em on this.
[BOY 2] Yeah, that's
an idea we could think about.
[GIRL 2] What about we just
do a food truck?
[BOY 3] I like that.
Would get people talking
more than
a display would.
I thought the cranes
were a good idea though.
[ALL] Phew!
[SAIKI] We dodged a bullet
on that one.
--[HAIRO] Still gonna write it.
--[ALL] Of course.
So anyone else have an idea?
Yeah, me.
[TAKAHASHI]
Thousand cranes? No way!
[TAKAHASHI] Heh!
I'm embarrassed to say this,
but what if we did
a maid café?
[SAIKI] We did that
last episode, idiot.
Well, that's an idea.
[YUMEHARA] Heh, heh!
Wait, what about this!
A cross-dressing
maid café,
where the guys wear
the costumes.
What? You're gonna make me
shave my legs?
[SAIKI] Your negative reaction
is fooling no one.
I don't know how to put on
a bra or wear makeup.
[SAIKI] If you worked at
a cafe, it'd be in the back.
Got any other suggestions?
[ALL] You're not writing that?
[HAIRO] What do you think,
Teruhashi?
[TERUHASHI] What? Ideas?
Don't look at me!
Well, maybe we could, um,
set up our very own
planetarium
by using
one of those at-home
starry night
sky projectors.
[BOY 2] Great idea,
Teruhashi! You're amazing!
That's pretty original, but
the machine's doing the work.
We need an idea that demands
actual effort from us!
Shut up, dude.
We're doing the planetarium.
[SAIKI] Well, this settles
who's more charismatic
between Hairo and her.
That's enough!
[HAIRO] Ooh, what is it, Mera?
We'll do an authentic
barbeque dinner!
Because it's
my favorite food.
[GIRL 3] This isn't supposed
to be just for us.
Barbeque can be
pretty pricey too.
[MERA] Let's combine it
with the planetarium.
Gaze upon Orion's belt
while eating meat.
Not bad. Got any more ideas?
[ALL] Write that one down!
If it's good,
write it down!
[HAIRO]
Kuboyasu, anything?
What? You wanna know
what I think?
[Kuboyasu scoffs]
[KUBOYASU] I think helping out
could help me blend in more.
How about a haunted house?
We could even dress up
like zombies.
That's a dumb idea.
It's not Hallo-- Aah!
[SAIKI]
He's got the part down.
You have no idea about
the true nature of zombies.
[SAIKI]
Kaidou's here too?
[BOY 3] I don't know. Zombies
are too slow to be scary.
True, but if there're enough
of them to form a horde,
running away is pointless.
Slowly but surely,
they will corner you,
and then suddenly,
they stop slacking
and start attacking!
[all scream]
Slacking, what?
[BOY 4] Attacking?
Oh! It's just
a lazy rhyme.
[BOY 2]
Kaidou is so stupid.
[SAIKI] Well, my favorite show's
about to start, so I'm leaving.
This sounds like
it's gonna take a while.
All right,
since no one can decide...
[SAIKI]
I better stop this.
What the heck was that?
[AIZAWA] Is that--?
[KAIDOU] A meteorite?
[BOY 2]
From outer space?
[SAIKI]
I used psychokinesis
to pull one down
to Earth.
This should settle
things.
Let's make this
our attraction!
[BOY 3]
Now that's an awesome idea!
[SAIKI]
Good job.
Even if it is from space,
isn't having
just one rock boring?
That's it!
Class 3 will display
the meteorite
and interesting rocks
found in the schoolyard!
[ALL]
Yay!
♪
[BOY 1]
You find a rock yet, Hairo?
Sort of. I found
a couple I like,
but nothing worthy
of our display.
[BOY 1] You found those
lying around?
This idea was dumb
and easy,
but they're
actually into it.
[TORITSUKA] Saiki!
[SAIKI] Hm?
'Sup?
[SAIKI] Oh.
What's Class 3 got planned
for the PK Festival?
We're doing
a cross-dressing
maid café.
Not my thing,
but whatev.
[SAIKI]
We almost did that too.
Anyway, buddy,
I want you
in our band
on festival day.
Hell, no.
[TORITSUKA] Here's our lineup.
On lead guitar,
Takeru.
Takayuki,
thunder broom.
Shinya,
keeping the beat.
And me, lead vocals!
But when assembled,
you can call us,
Eternal Diamond Veronica!
[silence]
[SAIKI] That's nice.
Wait, bro, we need you
to perform with us.
[SAIKI] Not a chance.
Why not? Do you prefer
a different kind of music?
[SAIKI] I prefer
a different kind of person.
Besides,
five's too crowded.
Band size might be
the least of our problems.
[SAIKI] None of you know
how to play?
[TORITSUKA] When we started,
Takeru was the singer,
but since he dislocates his jaw
on high notes,
we moved him to guitar.
Takayuki doesn't even know
what a bass is.
He tried to blow in it.
Shinya's only played drums
in that one video game
no one plays anymore.
[SAIKI]
You're all delusional.
I can't play anything,
either,
but that's no problem
when you're the front man.
[SAIKI]
That attitude is a problem.
[SAIKI] Why even bother forming
a band if none of you can play?
To rock the sheets with girls!
What other reason is there
to start a band?
[SAIKI]
The only thing rock about you
is your confidence.
[TORITSUKA] Anyway,
since we get worse
every time we practice,
you could use your powers
to make us awesome.
[SAIKI] You're pathetic
and naïve.
Why should I use
my powers to help you?
Wow. That school trip
to Okinawa sure was nuts.
Would suck for
the school to learn
they almost all died
thanks to a sleeping psychic.
[SAIKI] What? Are you trying
to threaten me?
You're certainly
courageous.
[squeals]
I was just talking to myself.
[SAIKI] Still,
he's got a point.
I do owe him for
helping me on Okinawa.
[plays discordant chord]
Now. The newest member
of Eternal Diamond Veronica,
Psi!
You're awesome!
A rock star?
You're in, bro.
[SAIKI]
You should be out.
Can you
help us out, Saik--
I mean, Psi, now that
you're in the group?
[SAIKI] Yeah, but I'm
just helping, not joining.
What? Play that?
You know I can't.
[SAIKI] I'm giving you
a lesson.
Dude, I barely know
how to hold it.
[SAIKI]
Just play.
[plays chord]
Oh! He can really play now!
Just the other day,
he sounded like
a cat drowning
in a washing machine!
[gasps]
[notes playing]
Whoa! That is one smooth
bass line
I'm feeling it
in my gut.
The other day,
he sounded like
a hippo drowning
in a washing machine!
[TAKERU] Whoa! Sounds like
he's done it for years!
[TORITSUKA] The other day,
he sounded like
zebras drowning
in a washing machine!
[singing]
[TAKERU] I can't believe
the notes!
[SHINYA] The other day,
he sounded like a washing
machine in a washing machine!
Let's all do a song!
[all] Yeah!
[TORITSUKA]
♪ I don't wanna be caught ♪
♪ Staring at the girls ♪
♪ I'm gonna check out
Their bath anyway ♪
♪ So much steam coverin' up
All that sweet skin ♪
♪ I'll have to feel
My way inside ♪
♪
[TORITSUKA] Guys!
We're rock stars!
So dope. Dude,
you sounded
just like
Natsuki Hanae.
Let's do
a concert!
We owe you big,
Psi!
Hey.
Where'd he go?
No problem, just means
there'll be more groupies
for us
to get in trouble with.
Hey, who am I to argue
with you, Hanae?
Cut it out.
I don't sound anything like him.
[TORITSUKA]
Saiki's the best.
Not only did he turn himself
into an ace axeman,
he made us rock stars.
I can't believe we're friends!
[SAIKI] We're not friends,
and none of us are rock stars.
That was all just
an illusion.
My playing was terrible.
My telepathy sent
the sounds
of real rock music
to everyone else
in the group
each time
one of us played.
If you try to play now,
you'll find that
you can't actually do it.
I gave you
a rock star moment, Toritsuka.
We're even.
Now go practice
so you can improve
for the festival.
I'm motivated to practice...
my autograph.
Seriously? Shouldn't we actually
be practicing even more?
What are you
talking about?
We sound great.
We don't need practice.
[SHINYA] Yeah, I wanna save
my energy for the live shows.
[TAKAYUKI]
I guess you're right.
[SAIKI]
Well, the PK Festival is here,
and Eternal Diamond Veronica
still hasn't practiced once.
Hardly seems like
my problem.
[TORITSUKA]
We're gonna be legends!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[VOICE]
Come on!
[SAIKI] What goes
in the box?
♪
[HAIRO]
Okay, guys! Are we all set up?
My entry
is an enchanted geode
with the power
to seal away evil.
Mine is way cooler!
[SAIKI] You stole a statue.
Mine's heart-shaped.
Cute, huh?
Yeah, totally.
[TERUHASHI]
But it's completely broken.
[giggles]
Yours is pretty too.
Thank you.
Kuboyasu,
what's that?
I found it behind a dumpster.
Someone hid it there.
[SAIKI]
Because it's a murder weapon.
Nice. Thanks to you guys
finding weird rocks,
Class 3 has a great
display.
[SAIKI] Only you could find
a rock shaped like that.
I heard the class with
the best festival display
wins an award.
Let's make sure
it goes to us!
Class 3 rules!
[ALL] Yeah!
All right!
[SAIKI] What was
the point of that huddle?
Well, my friend, let's enjoy
this brief respite while we can.
[NENDOU]
Yo! Teruhashi,
come see the other
classes with us!
[TERUHASHI] What? You mean
with you and Saiki!
I'd love to, but there's
somewhere else I have to be.
I'm Contestant Number 5,
Moriko Utsukushino,
from Class 1.
And I like to visit
art museums.
I never knew
we did this.
Hah, hah!
Oh man,
I bet Teruhashi
wins this bad boy,
no problem,
am I right, guys?
What? Uh. Sure,
whatever.
[SAIKI]
Why are you with us?
[KAIDOU]
Wait, Teruhashi's not in this.
That concludes
contestant introductions.
[NENDOU]
What?
Which of these
lovely ladies
do you think
will win, sir?
It would be
inappropriate of me
to pick a favorite.
Each girl shines--
Let's ask someone who knows
all about shining,
our reigning Miss PK,
Teruhashi!
All the girls look so
beautiful this year,
I couldn't possibly
judge them.
[KAIDOU] You wanna go?
[KUBOYASU] Yeah, sure.
[NENDOU]
A haunted house, a café,
a haunted house, a café.
Whoa, so many choices.
[SAIKI]
Define "so many."
Let's just pick one
and go in.
[SAIKI] Oh, man. Haunted houses
are never fun for me.
[NENDOU] I'm hungry.
Let's eat first.
[SAIKI]
Same with these cafés. I mean,
the food's made
by high schoolers-- Ahh!
Hey! Let's go to that one!
[SAIKI]
For once, we agree.
[NENDOU] The haunted house café!
[SAIKI] Wait, what?
But I don't wanna
look at ghosts
while I'm drinking
coffee.
[SAIKI] He's right.
[BOY] Not scary.
What kind
of haunted house
has people yelling,
"boo"?
PK Academy sucks
balls.
Where'd they
come from?
Probably from another
school
[DELINQUENT 1]
Let's do this one.
[DELINQUENT 2] We'll mess up
the haunted houses.
[KUBOYASU] Go ahead
without me.
I'm gonna check out
this haunted house too.
I get a real kick out of
watching people get scared.
[clattering, screaming]
[NENDOU] Whoa!
They're really screaming.
That one must be
good.
[SAIKI] Good place
to get beat up.
Now I'm curious
to check it out myself.
[NENDOU] So dark.
Like there's no light.
[SAIKI] Heh!
I see everything.
Including the guy waiting
to jump out at us.
[KAIDOU] Go on.
[NENDOU] Your idea. You go.
[Kaidou gasps]
[KAIDOU] Very well,
you timid mice.
I shall lead you through
the labyrinth of Hell
and into the light.
[KAIDOU] I've never been
more scared--
Aah! Aah!
Boo!
[screaming]
[SAIKI]
That's a sign.
[pants]
Now. Follow me, as I take you
into the light.
[SAIKI] That's the entrance.
Stop spazzing out
and screaming everywhere.
We're going without you.
[KAIDOU] Don't leave me!
Bye.
[STUDENT] I'll scare 'em
so hard
they wet their pants!
[moans]
[NENDOU] Hey.
[NENDOU] He looks real.
[SAIKI] He is real.
Yeah. Even a man
like me would faint
if I saw your face
in the dark.
What do you mean?
Now what are we gonna do?
You ruined their haunted house.
[girl screams]
Quick, hide this guy
before someone sees.
We'll dress up
and scare 'em ourselves!
[all moan]
[MIDORI] Hey.
Aah!
Oh, hi, Mom!
[KAIDOU] There are
two Nendous?
Should've told me
you were coming.
I had a break,
so I came by.
We befriended Nendou's mom
on our way in,
and we've been seeing
the class displays.
[SAIKI] This is the friendship
I wish you hadn't made.
Now that I saw your class's,
I better get back.
Good luck with
your haunted house.
We're not doing
a haunted house.
[MIDORI]
You're not?
Our class is showing off
funny-looking rocks.
[SAIKI]
I'll go wash up.
What a pain.
This is why school events
are such a pain in the neck.
Lots of
minor characters always
showing up,
causing trouble for me.
Oh, well. At least I can get
some peace and quiet in here.
Or maybe
I'll just go home now--
These aren't mine.
Hah, hah!
Do I look cool in these?
Give those back--
Damn it!
I have to wear those glasses
to block a very particular
and very dangerous
power I have.
When I look
at living things
with my naked eyes,
they turn to stone.
[shatters]
♪
I don't wear glasses
for my sight,
or to look cool.
I wear them to block
my gaze
from turning people
into stone.
Now those glasses
are broken,
and my
super-powered stare
created the ugliest
statue ever.
So what do I do?
My first thought
was to restore Nendou
by turning back time
one day.
But when you're stone,
you're dead.
Even if time is turned back
on the dead,
they don't come back
to life.
Better just to wait it out.
After a day, he'll come back
to life, good as new.
The only problem is
if he then
asks questions
about his missing time.
[NENDOU] Whoa! Oh, well,
time for ramen.
[SAIKI] Who am I kidding?
I don't have to worry
about him overthinking.
Kusuo? Ah! What is this?
[SAIKI]
Dad. Good timing.
[KUNIHARU] Did you carve this?
[SAIKI] Seriously?
Just give me
your glasses.
[KUNIHARU]
I just had those tightened!
[SAIKI] So long as I have
something covering my eyes,
that power will be blocked.
[KUNIHARU]
Give me back my glasses!
[SAIKI] Worst that'll happen is
your eyes'll look like threes.
No, I'm blind
without my glasses!
So that's why Nendou
turned into stone, huh?
What's your plan,
son?
His mom's outside
waiting to say bye.
[SAIKI] I'm over here, Dad.
Never make that mistake again.
I guess I'll have
to teleport stone Nendou
to my house. What?
[rock crumbles]
Kusuo, take care
of your mom for me.
Police, I'd like to report
an accidental homicide.
[SAIKI] You don't have to go
to the police. It'll be fine.
You're sure?
[SAIKI] In this case,
I actually can
just turn back time.
[MIDORI]
Nendou, what's that noise?
Crap. Nendou's mom's coming in.
Dad, block the door!
No prob--
What's going on?
[SAIKI]
Doesn't anyone knock?
What? Oh my God.
This is great!
Why didn't you say
your rock display
was based on my boy!
[SAIKI]
I guess that's fine.
What mom would believe
her son got turned
to stone?
Have you guys seen
where my son went?
Uh, I think he went
to the restroom.
[SAIKI]
We're in the restroom.
[KUNIHARO]
He said he had somewhere to be.
[MIDORI] It's always something.
I'll help move it.
You're taking this
to your class, right?
Come on, let's go!
What the hell.
[BOY 1]
Why Nendou?
[BOY 2]
How'd they even carve this?
[SAIKI]
Now we're really in trouble.
It's so obvious high schoolers
couldn't carve this.
Everyone's getting
suspicious.
In addition-- Oh, wow!
[BOY 3] Mr. Principal!
[PRINCIPAL] The detail here
is amazing.
Is it based on a gorilla?
[SAIKI] You're half right.
[PRINCIPAL] I'm very impressed.
In addition.
This year's award
for best exhibit
goes to Class 3.
[BOY 4] Whoa, so is this
what won them the Class Award?
[SAIKI]
It's become the showpiece.
This has gotten
out of hand!
Can't you
teleport it?
[SAIKI]
Too many people will see.
Break it
and turn back time
until it's back
in the other room?
[SAIKI]
That's not how it works.
I can only do it once a day,
per target.
[KUNIHARU] What?
[SAIKI] There have to be limits
in this universe.
Otherwise I could rewind time
as much as I want.
What if it breaks again?
[SAIKI] Then he'll be dead.
[BOY 3]
Crap. His hand broke.
Wait, it was his sleeve.
His ears are really ugly.
[BOY 3]
His face is harder to break.
Don't touch!
[BOY 3] Huh?
Who is this guy?
[BOY 1] There's a strange man
shouting at us!
[GIRL]
Someone get the teachers!
Don't touch me!
No! No!
[MALE TEACHER]
Calm down!
[SAIKI]
He better not mention my name.
Dad is right.
I have to make Nendou's safety
my top priority.
If he dies,
it's kind of
a tiny bit my fault.
[YUUTA'S MOM] Off the statue!
[SAIKI] Yuuta?
That's the last time
you ever try
to take over
the world, Baron Cola!
[SAIKI]
Stop. You'll break his face.
[YUUTA] Hey, Cyborg
Cider-man Number 2!
Look! I caught
Baron Cola for us!
[SAIKI] No, that's
a gorilla statue. Get off.
[YUUTA] Don't worry! I'm
holding on so he can't escape.
[SAIKI]
I wasn't worried about that.
[YUUTA] Give up,
Baron Cola!
Hairo! Did you hear we won
the award for best display?
I just found out!
I gave all those
pep talks,
but to be honest,
I never thought we'd win.
The Principal loved
our Nendou statue,
but I don't remember
having one of those.
Don't know what
they're talking about.
[crash]
[both gasp]
[HAIRO] Saiki!
[KAIDOU] You okay?
[BOY 3]
Saiki sacrificed himself!
[BOY 2]
It didn't crack!
[SAIKI] What a pain.
It happened so fast
I didn't have time
to use my powers.
Are you okay, Sai--
You get new glasses?
We'll get it off--
Wait, are those new glasses?
[SAIKI] Does that really matter?
The bigger problem is
my classmates
have now seen the statue.
[BOY 2]
Your statue rules! Who made it?
[SAIKI] How do I get out
of this one?
Clearly Saiki!
Who else but the sculptor
would risk a back injury
to save it!
[BOY 3]
Really? Saiki?
I guess he is pretty
close with Nendou.
[BOY 4] That's quite
an affectionate gesture.
Almost even romantic.
[BOY 2]
Saiki could do better.
[SAIKI] It'd be easier if
I just let the statue shatter.
[VOICE]
Come on!
[SAIKI]
Fill in the blank.
[NENDOU]
Let's go have some ramen!
[SAIKI] You don't need
telepathy for that.
♪
I'm sure it's fine
if we're late,
but they should've picked
a closer restaurant
for the party.
[SAIKI] What's the point
of a party?
[NENDOU]
Are we there?
[KAIDOU] Map's a little
hard to understand.
Once we turn the corner,
the restaurant's--
[SAIKI]
Not here.
[Hairo's ringtone]
Show more enthusiasm!
Where are you guys?
The class is already here!
We got lost. Have you
started eating yet?
Of course we haven't.
We're waiting on you guys.
I'll have the Japanese Style
Hamburger Steak
with Mushrooms.
[KAIDOU] I just heard you..
Since we're such a big group,
the waitress wanted to get
my order early.
[KAIDOU]
Oh, okay.
Can you tell us
where it is?
I don't see it.
I followed your map.
[SAIKI]
You didn't.
[SAIKI] Should've turned
at the second light,
but we turned at
the first.
I didn't bother
telling him though.
I don't wanna attend
any parties.
I'd rather we just
stay lost all night.
Looks like we went the wrong way
and have to double back.
Don't worry, boys, the party's
right around the corner.
[NENDOU] You have the worst
sense of direction.
[KAIDOU] If you're not helping,
you can't complain.
Behold,
we should arrive--
[SAIKI]
At the wrong place.
[KAIDOU] It appears
I'm being sabotaged
by a supernatural power
known as a Stand.
[SAIKI] You're not.
We're lost again!
No! That can't
be right!
[SAIKI] He seems to have
a real problem with directions.
After turning
at the second light,
we were supposed to make
another right.
Instead we went left.
Which means
the restaurant is actually
behind us.
[KAIDOU] All right,
you lead the way!
[SAIKI]
I'll keep that to myself.
Kaidou's bad with maps
and keeps getting lost.
Can you just tell me
where it is?
[HAIRO]
Where are you right now?
See anything
you recognize?
[NENDOU]
Uh, a big tower.
[HAIRO] That's no help.
Do you see any signs
for a restaurant?
A Todoroki?
[NENDOU] I see "Sha, Sha, Sha."
Sha-Sha-Sha?
[NENDOU]
Three "Sha" Kanji characters.
[HAIRO]
That doesn't sound familiar.
[SAIKI]
Nope, that's Todoroki.
--[NENDOU] Yo. Hairo wants you.
--What?
As expected,
you came crawling back
for help from
the Jet Black Wings!
What?
[HAIRO] I'm the one
helping them.
[KAIDOU] Seriously, have
you guys started eating yet?
Of course not. We're still
holding off till you guys--
[STUDENTS]
Cheers!
I just heard everyone
do a toast.
[HAIRO]
That's another group.
Go back to the last
spot you recognize.
We're back at
the train station.
[HAIRO] I'll give directions
from there.
Do you see a hospital
building nearby?
[KAIDOU] Yeah, I see it.
Good.
Now just walk directly
toward it.
Okay, done.
[SAIKI] He thinks a hair clinic
is an actual hospital.
[HAIRO]
You're almost here.
Keep going down
that street
until you see a post
and then turn left.
What? A post?
--Oh, host!
--[SAIKI] Nope.
[KAIDOU] Found it--
Get off the phone
and come play Bingo!
Okay, I'll play.
I'm almost done.
Sorry 'bout that.
Are you back on track?
[KAIDOU] Sure. You haven't
started the party yet?
Of course not.
Did you turn left?
Just like you said.
This doesn't look right.
You should be passing a school.
Do you see it?
A school? In a neighborhood
as bad as this one?
Wouldn't this lead
to genocide?
[HAIRO] Really?
Wait, here's a school.
No way! This can't be
what he's talking about!
[NENDOU]
Then double-check with him.
[KAIDOU] Is the name
of the school--
Uh-huh...
[GIRL] Next: I-16!
[HAIRO] Oh! Bingo!
Bingo-bingo-bingo!
Guess it is. Why host a party
on this street?
[HAIRO]
You turn at the school?
[KAIDOU] Yeah, we turned!
[HAIRO] Then keep walking,
you can't miss it.
I gotta jet. See you soon!
Oh, look! I think
we finally made it.
No, something's wrong.
[SAIKI] For you,
or for the people inside?
[THUG 1] Ugh! What are you kids
doing here? Scram!
Uh, sorry!
We'll get lost!
Hey! You can't talk to
your customers like that!
[Kaidou screams]
What did you say, brat!
[NENDOU]
What did you say, jerk!
The gang's inside!
You better let us in, or else!
[SAIKI]
"Gang" meaning Class 3.
[THUG 2] We'll show you
what's what.
[KAIDOU]
No! Let us go!
[SAIKI]
I better wrap this up.
No, please don't!
Cool.
You finally made it.
What? Seriously,
I found it?
[SAIKI] No.
I teleported us here.
I wasn't planning
on helping Kaidou tonight,
but when it looked like
they might hurt us,
I had no choice. Plus,
I respect his persistence.
Now that we're here,
let's party!
Yeah,
I'm ready to go!
The Class 3
wrap party, Hairo!
Can you get us Bingo cards
and an appetizer menu?
[SAIKI]
About that...
[BOY]
Let's have a big cheer
as we mark the end
of another party!
[SAIKI] The party's over.
[NENDOU &amp; KAIDOU] What?
[STUDENTS]
Class 3 rules!
[KAIDOU]
Let's do an after party!
[BOY 1] I'll pass.
[BOY 2] Me too.
[SAIKI] I'll give you
30 minutes,
'cause I feel bad.
♪
[man singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
Once again I somehow
got through
another school event.
But honestly,
has anything at PK Academy
ever gone off without
a hitch?
Next time, on The Disastrous
Life of Saiki K.:
What? It's Christmas
and New Year's again?
Didn't we just do
this episode?