♪
--Tell him you have a crush.
--Oh, no, I can't do that.
Popular guys like him
aren't single for long.
[SAIKI]
Romance, huh?
While not my priority,
it is, unfortunately,
all my classmates
seem to think about.
[RINATIE]
There he is. Good luck.
[MIIKO]
Hey, Toritsuka.
Wanna go to the movies
with me tonight?
[SAIKI] Wait. You like him?
Yeah, sure, I'm down.
You promised
you'd go with me.
[GIRL]
Tonight's my date with him.
[SAIKI]
Rethink your choices.
I don't know which chick
to go out with.
Who knew being a popular piece
of man-meat was so difficult?
[SAIKI] Don't act like
you're not loving this.
[TORITSUKA] In a weird way,
I owe all this to you.
Remember that rock show I did
at the school festival?
Turns out we're the biggest
hit of the year!
[SAIKI]
What?
[TORITSUKA]
First, we sounded terrible.
Shinya even made a boink sound
with the drums.
I don't know how you do that.
Anyway, I was about to leave,
when the ghost of
you-know-who showed up.
[KOMATSU]
Are you troubled?
[TORITSUKA] He was a ghost with
a mop top and round glasses.
A bigger star
than anyone ever.
Bigger even than that guy
in the Bible!
And he was tragically
killed at age 40.
[SAIKI]
Wait, do you mean--?
[TORITSUKA]
Yep. John. John Komatsu.
I'll give you a little help,
my friend.
[SAIKI]
Wait, who?
[TORITSUKA]
Once John possessed my body,
he instantly won the
audience back over.
Spirit-summoning
is the best power ever.
[SAIKI] I'm sure it'll bite you
sooner or later.
--Are you talking to that guy?
--Ow, let go!
Hey, get your hands
off her, buddy.
I'll do what I want
to her, punk!
It's no wonder she wants
to go out with me.
--Eat this!
--Possess!
[girls cheering]
Hey, Saiki,
you see that move I just did?
Got it from a Hong Kong star
who died young.
[SAIKI]
No way.
[TORITSUKA]
Bruce. Bruce Scorpion Junior.
I spirit-summoned
the legendary king
of direct-to-video
kung fu flicks.
--[SAIKI] Never heard of him.
--Saiki, with this power,
I'll become the most
popular man ever!
[SAIKI] Spirit-summoning may be
convenient for him now,
but I'm sure it'll have some
big drawbacks down the line.
[TORITSUKA]
All right!
--Yeah! Movie time!
--[ALL] Yeah!
[TORITSUKA] I've put together
a real harem. Thirteen girls,
which means 26 boobs
ripe for the squeezing.
[laughing]
Let me possess you again.
Hey, it's still my turn,
right?
[TORITSUKA] Settle down.
I got a lot to think about.
Like who's gonna be
the first girl I make a move on.
--Who is that?
--I mean, she's cute,
but she's got those crazy eyes
that say,
"The second you lay hand on me,
I'm ripping off your head
and spitting down your throat."
[KUSUKO]
That's exactly right.
Will you tell me a story
about being a rock star?
I wanna hear one too.
You guys want a story?
I was watching this porno--
Aah! That was close.
I almost told them a story
from my own life, when
I should let a ghost handle it.
[KUSUKO]
You sure that's what you want?
[TORITSUKA] Why talk when I can
get someone who commands a room,
--like, a tech CEO--
--[KUSUKO] It's not Jobs, is it?
[TORITSUKA]
Montecarlo Sudou.
I upgraded my flip phone
the other day to an iPhone.
But it turned out to be
just an iPod Touch.
[KUSUKO] Montecarlo's terrible.
What a pain.
I was worried, but it seems
I didn't have to be.
All right, Montecarlo.
That's enough. Let me back in.
What gives.
Is he switching personalities?
I should be the only one
who's allowed to do that.
Back up
and watch me work, lads.
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
[TORITSUKA] Komatsu,
I didn't spirit-summon you.
[MONTECARLO]
I had no problem coming.
--♪ La, la, la, la ♪
--What the heck is going on?
[KOMATSU] Maybe your psychic
entrance stretched out too wide
with all the spirits
going in?
[TORITSUKA] Like the waistband
in a pair of underwear?
Makes sense, but I don't get why
I can't switch into my own body.
[KUSUKO] That's because
it no longer is your body.
--[TORITSUKA] Saiki! That girl!
--[KUSUKO] You've been having
spirits use your body more
than you've used your own body.
It's like when you go
on vacation
and your pet ends up more
attached to his sitter than you.
[TORITSUKA] Are human bodies
really like that?
They can forget
who their original spirit was?
[KUSUKO] He's even controlling
your hair now.
[TORITSUKA] No! Not my hair!
Help me, Saiki!
[KUSUKO]
Yeah, no.
[TORITSUKA]
He hasn't just stolen my body,
he's turning off
all the girls!
Damn it! I thought ghosts
were supposed to be kind
and helpful!
[KUSUKO] Ghosts have nothing
to worry about,
so they merely look kind
and content.
But they are
whatever they choose to be.
In this case,
these ghosts have chosen
to be grabby
with your body.
Hey, switch back with me,
hippie.
Sharing is caring, love.
[yelling]
[KUSUKO]
Fine. Guess I will help.
[grunting]
[screams]
[both screaming]
[KUSUKO] Being a human
can't always be fun and games.
I think those ghosts forgot that
when they were using his body--
Saiki, you got my body back.
And you taught me
a lesson today. Thank you.
I won't depend on ghosts
so much anymore.
I'll start doing things
for myself again.
Well, girls, let's go.
[GIRL] One second he's singing,
the next he's doing karate?
[TORITSUKA]
Quick question:
are those boobs real?
[KUSUKO]
I'm gonna turn you into a ghost.
♪
[STUDENT]
How many people you get?
[SAIKI]
The new semester's started,
and that means all the school
clubs are competing for members.
Saiki! Good timing, buddy--
[SAIKI]
Don't care.
I need to ask you for a very
important favor, Saiki.
[SAIKI] I'm not joining
your dumb club.
I'm starting my own club
and I need your help.
--Still not happening.
--[TORITSUKA] Everyone in school
is joining clubs right now,
and I have an idea
to get in on the action.
[SAIKI] You're doing this
to hit on girls, aren't you?
I've been feeling out
the students for interest,
but I want your opinion.
I don't know what club
--I should really start.
--[SAIKI] A Loser Club?
To be honest, I tried to join
some of the other clubs,
but none of them
would accept me.
All right,
what have you got?
Manami Nakamura,
--and I'm good at freestyle.
--I'm Minako Tagami.
I've taken swimming lessons
for six years.
--I'm Reiko. My big boobs float.
--[CAPTAIN] Beat it, creep!
[TORITSUKA] So the girls
swim club passed. I wonder why.
--[ALL] Defense! Defense!
--Who is this pervert?
[TORITSUKA]
Girls basketball said no too.
[SAIKI] You're the one
they need to defend against.
I tried a handful
of other clubs.
Put your dirty skirts in here.
[TORITSUKA] I still
couldn't find the right fit.
So I have no choice left
but to put one together myself.
My very own harem!
[SAIKI]
A club's not a harem.
I just got it! I know the exact
club I should start.
--[SAIKI] Great.
--The Occult Club.
[GIRL]
Occult Club? That's weird.
They're taking the bait. Look.
[SAIKI]
No way this gets him girls.
Did you ever hear
of this one theory?
Misattribution of arousal.
It's when you mistake
your feelings of fear
for love.
[SAIKI]
His grades are terrible,
but suddenly he's an expert
on psychology?
With the Occult Club, I can put
this theory to the test.
I bet girls are lined up
already.
Or we might just have to wait
a little.
[SAIKI]
No, there is someone here.
[MAKINO]
Um. Id like to join Occult Club.
Hey, a girl!
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Aah! Aah! It's a ghost!
Save me!
[SAIKI] Don't you see ghosts
all the time?
Plus, she isn't one.
I'm Arisu Makino.
Since middle school,
I've read 3000 books
on the paranormal,
black magic,
ley lines, Satanism,
and witchcraft.
This club seems like a fun way
to find the six blood sacrifices
I need to summon
the dark lord.
[TORITSUKA]
Oh, man, this chick is whack.
Aah! But wait!
Usually, the crazy ones
turn out to be
the hottest ones.
Yeah, the Occult Club people
--are meeting over there.
--[MAKINO] Oh, okay.
[SAIKI] But you're
Occult Club president.
--Welcome to Occult Club.
--[MAKINO] What?
Well, hello there,
Occult Club.
My name is Jet Black Wings,
an exorcist,
--answering your call.
--[SAIKI] Oh, you.
--[KAIDOU] Hey, Saiki.
--Hey, you know this weirdo?
--Wait...the Chihuahua guy.
--[KAIDOU] Don't call me that!
[TORITSUKA] Sorry, Chihuahua,
no dudes allowed in this club.
--[KAIDOU] What?
--Hello.
I'd like to join
the Occult Club, guys.
[whistling]
Oh, wow!
Hey, Kaidou,
I didn't know you were here.
I'm so surprised.
[SAIKI]
Your acting needs work.
It's obvious you were
following Kaidou.
[TORITSUKA]
A cute girl did come.
But wait, why does it feel like
I've run into her too?
Oh, right. Takeru's ex.
I can't make a move on her,
that'd be wrong.
Hello there, gorgeous.
Ready to get scared
--out of your skirt?
--Uh..
--But you said guys can't join.
--Yeah, that's right.
Girls have way more
spiritual sensitivity than guys,
so that's why
you can't join.
The thing doubles as my harem.
Lock the door behind you.
Kaidou's not gonna be in this
club? I'm not joining anymore.
[CHIYO] Kaidou, let's create
our own Occult Club instead.
Do what? Okay, I guess.
--[MAKINO] May I join?
--Aah! Everyone, wait, wait!
You can join, Kaidou.
--[TORITSUKA] A two-man harem.
--We're gonna have so much fun.
[TORITSUKA] Is it possible
she likes the Chihuahua?
Hmph. No big.
After a couple meetings,
she'll fall for me.
I'm way cooler.
[SAIKI]
Nope. But I do wanna see
if this misattribution
of arousal thing works.
[CHIYO]
A blackout? Kaidou, hold me!
[KAIDOU]
Look at the TVs!
--They're on!
--And broadcasting static,
even though everything
is digital now.
Aah! The door won't open!
[MAKINO]
Everyone calm down
and do some ancient chanting
with me.
[chanting in foreign language]
[SAIKI] That's enough.
Let's see if all that fear
really did make people
fall in love.
It's back.
[SAIKI]
Her love for Kaidou is 95.
It was high
from the start, though,
so that doesn't mean much.
And Kaidou's love
for her is 52.
--Ouch. This didn't work at all.
--[gasps]
[SAIKI]
Oh, no. Hers just went down.
I guess being afraid of the dark
isn't sexy.
[TORITSUKA]
My heart is beating so fast.
[SAIKI]
Huh?
[TORITSUKA] No misattributing
this feeling.
I'm in love with Makino!
[SAIKI] Misattribution
of arousal is real.
--[BOY] Come on!
--[SAIKI] Use telepathy
to play rock, paper,
scissors.
♪
[STUDENT]
What's our next class?
[SAIKI]
I don't hate school.
I just think it's boring
and I would rather watch TV.
Home Ec. Today we're supposed
to be making crepes.
Oh, man, I hate Home Ec.
[SAIKI]
That's my cue. Chef Saiki.
[MATSUZAKI]
All right, kids, listen up.
Today we're making crepes.
[SAIKI] Why are you teaching it?
I don't know how to cook,
but I printed the recipe,
so I should be fine.
[SAIKI]
What's with the cute apron?
I wish they'd teach us...
[SAIKI] Your apron's
also ridiculous.
The important thing here
is I actually like crepes.
They're delicious
on their own,
but they go well
with all sweets.
With crepes,
you have an infinite variety
of infinite combinations.
[MATSUZAKI]
Commence cooking.
[SAIKI]
Since I like crepes,
I won't be phoning in
this assignment.
The real problem is gonna be
my two kitchen teammates.
Don't worry, dude,
I got you.
[SAIKI] Well, at least Nendou's
not in my group.
Hmm. For three people
we should use two eggs.
Oh, check it out, Saiki.
I got a special way
to crack eggs.
I can crack one
with just one hand.
[SAIKI]
I know how this ends.
--Oh, no, the shell fell in!
--Use both hands, like me.
[SAIKI] This is bad. These guys
are worse than I thought.
Now you just whisk it.
Make sure no lumps left...
[SAIKI]
Nendou's good at this?
My mom is always working.
Means if I wanna eat
I gotta cook food
for myself.
Hey, that's why I learned too.
[SAIKI]
Even Kuboyasu can cook?
Boy, did I get
two rotten eggs.
All right. We got
all the pieces of shell out.
We made a mess,
but we'll be okay.
Well, now that we finished
the eggs,
the recipe says
we have to add some flour.
Huh. How much is some flour?
What? I don't know.
Well, let's try three pinches
to start.
[SAIKI]
It's not a spice.
[HAIRO]
What's next?
[SAIKI]
Kaidou is too cautious.
Now we add some sugar.
But what is some?
[HAIRO]
Let's just do the whole bag.
[SAIKI] And Hairo's reckless.
This is bad.
If I let them keep going,
my chance to snack on crepes
will be ruined.
I'll just have to make
the whole thing my--
A whole stick of butter?
[HAIRO] When it says
"some butter," means one stick?
[KAIDOU] Looking again it
says "add some melted butter."
--[HAIRO] It does. Oh, no!
--Put the bowl in the microwave.
--Good save.
--[SAIKI] Guys, wait.
--Hairo, why is it glowing?
--[SAIKI] That's a metal bowl.
[explosion]
This is the first time
I've seen crepes
break a microwave.
I never knew you couldn't
put metal in there.
Someone really should've put a
sign on it. What shall we do?
[KAIDOU] I bet breakfast in hell
looks more appetizing.
I hate wasting food,
but we can't keep this.
--I'll toss it out.
--[MERA] I'll eat it.
Don't throw it away yet.
I can still eat that.
We've got no choice
but to start over from scratch.
At least we know
all the steps now.
[SAIKI]
As you can see, one bowl
--of perfect crepe batter.
--Whoa, it's done.
Were you following along
with us, Saiki? That's not bad.
[SAIKI]
Are you serious?
Hey, that batter
looks good, bro.
Of course it does.
We're the ones who made it.
[SAIKI]
There is no we.
We each put our blood,
sweat, tears
--into that crepe batter!
--[SAIKI] Sounds gross.
And you guys haven't even gotten
to the real hard part yet.
What could be harder than
handling a microwave explosion?
--We might blow up the class.
--[SAIKI] Don't joke about that.
Watch. I'll give you a private
lesson on what to do next.
[KAIDOU] I'll be shocked if
there's anything we can learn.
First, lightly coat
the frying pan with oil.
When does the batter go in?
Now you pour it in.
What happens
if it gets too thick?
Well, that's why
you spread it out.
Okay, smart guy,
but for how long?
--[NENDOU] Wait till...
--[SAIKI] They are learning.
--[HAIRO] How do you do that?
--Like this.
--[KEIDOU] Seriously?
--[Nendou laughs]
Good luck.
It's all in the wrist.
[KAIDOU]
We didn't need your help!
[SAIKI] You need all the help.
Like it needs a lot of practice.
Hey, she's using chopsticks.
Try that.
[CHIYO] What?
Is Kaidou looking at me?
Let's play it safe,
leave it as is.
[KAIDOU] But if we do
then we've lost to Nendou.
No, it's not about losing.
More than anything
I just wanna look cool!
No! Kaidou, don't!
[yelling indistinctly]
♪
I'll give the chopsticks
a shot.
[KAIDOU] Yeah, go for it.
Is it ready yet?
--[HAIRO] No.
--[KAIDOU] Are you sure?
--[HAIRO] It's fine.
--[KAIDOU] It's burning.
No, if anything, this crepe
needs to get even hotter.
[KAIDOU] It's a dessert
from the land of demons.
We have no choice
but to let Saiki do it.
[SAIKI] She took it
without even blinking.
Well, the key to a good crepe
begins with your batter. Hmm.
Mm.
[ALL]
This can't be good.
Here, since you guys sucked
at making yours,
I'll give you some of mine
to eat.
[SAIKI] Nendou,
I'm sorry I doubted you.
You really are
a good friend.
[NENDOU] Dig in to my
world-famous tuna fish crepes.
[SAIKI]
Tuna fish crepes?
♪
[SAIKI] Lately, some guys
have been sneaking around me.
[camera shutter clicking]
[SAIKI]
What a pain.
Seems like my worst fears
are coming true.
The secret organization
has finally started moving.
[MAN 1]
Kusuo Saiki.
Isn't he just a quiet,
average kid in his class?
[MAN 2]
He's supposed to be dangerous?
[MAN 3] He's not just quiet,
he's invisible. Nonentity.
We've received many witness
reports that say otherwise.
The danger Saiki poses
is now closer than ever before.
But we still have time
to take action.
[SAWAKITA] Her safety
will always be ensured.
By us. The Teruhashi Fan Club,
Kokomins!
[ALL]
Yes, sir.
T-R-H-S!
Kokomins Member Number 521.
Tell us Article Three
of Kokomins Law.
Oh, wow. We are to eliminate
all men approaching Teruhashi,
even at the expense
of our lives!
Right. It doesn't matter
who approaches our goddess,
we will eliminate them.
We must destroy Saiki.
[SAIKI] Too bad the secret
organization is just these guys.
I think I would prefer an evil
government cabal instead.
[BOY 1]
Look, it's Teruhashi.
[ALL]
Oh, wow!
[BOY 2]
She gets prettier every day.
[BOY 3]
My heart's bursting.
Today I'm finally
going to ask her out.
But the Teruhashi Fan Club
will get you if you do that.
An organization that includes
not only P.K. students,
but teachers, kids from other
schools and famous politicians.
[BOY 4] To talk to her,
you gotta be a member.
[BOY 1]
You're member number 36853?
[BOY 3] This lets me talk
to her about the weather.
[BOY 4]
That's all club members can do?
--[SAIKI] A terrifying power.
--Aah! Saiki.
It's nice out today.
[BOY 4] He a member?
[BOY 3] No, but she
initiated the conversation,
--so he's not breaking the law.
--[BOY 4] I hate him already.
--[SAIKI] Wanna switch places?
--Well, I'll see you later.
I just made his day.
[SAIKI] I'm sure
that made them even angrier.
I guess I'll just
let them take me.
[SAWAKITA]
We've been waiting for you.
[SAIKI]
Seriously?
[SAWAKITA]
We are the Teruhashi Fan Club.
And we will now decide
your fate.
[SAIKI]
This is way over the top.
--There's nothing to decide.
--[SAIKI] Special forces?
Wait, why does the Intelligence
leader have a stupid jacket?
And you're just a cliché.
Why is there
a brainless muscle character
in every group of bad guys?
[SAWAKITA] We'd rather not have
to hurt you. Lets talk.
[SAIKI]
We already are.
I am Sawakita,
leader of the Kokomins.
[SAIKI] I actually didn't
expect it to be a classmate.
[SAWAKITA]
Saiki, do you know why it is
that we brought you here?
It's because of Teruhashi.
[SAIKI] Oh, wow,
I never would have guessed.
[SAWAKITA] It seems
that you are very close to her.
That's something
we can't allow.
[SAIKI]
I have to give them credit
for holding on
to pointless resentment.
--[SAWAKITA] Show him Exhibit A.
--[NISHI] Oh, wow!
Why is my hand like this?
[SAIKI]
I don't care.
At P.K. Academy orientation,
I was miraculously given
a chair next to Teruhashi
and she shook my hand.
And ever since that day,
I haven't washed this hand
once.
It stays perfectly dry now
even when I shower
or use the toilet.
[SAIKI]
That stinks. Literally.
She blessed this hand
with her purity
and I won't sully it.
I can still smell her.
[SAIKI]
That's your unwashed hand.
Mishima, reveal it.
Oh, wow!
Saiki, do you understand
what you're looking at?
My love is so powerful,
I willed this tattoo onto me.
[SAIKI]
That doesn't make sense.
And here's an example
of my passion. My e-mail name.
[SAIKI] Not a lot. Especially
for the group's leader.
With that e-mail address,
he's sworn off all other women.
--He's an inspiration.
--[SAIKI] Okay.
[SAWAKITA] Let's continue. Is it
true you went on a secret date?
[SAIKI] Why does it look
like a gossip rag?
[MEMBER 1]
You're breaking my heart!
[SAWAKITA]
What about this story?
[SAIKI] Who took this picture
of me passed out?
Well, at least this gives me
a really good excuse
to avoid her.
Guys, hold on!
It gets worse.
[SAIKI]
At least they stopped talking.
--[MEMBER 1] A secret child?
--[MEMBER 2] A nightmare!
I shall purge Saiki
with the stench of this hand!
--[SAIKI] So you know it smells.
--[NISHI] Executive leader.
[SAWAKITA] Nishi, recite
Article One of Kokomins Law.
[NISHI] Maintain Teruhashi's
happiness
by all means necessary, sir.
[SAWAKITA]
That's right. And I've realized
Saiki is crucial to fulfilling
that Kokomins article.
[crying]
Even if he is human garbage,
he's still the father
of her child!
If we hurt him,
we hurt Teruhashi!
Saiki, despite your love affair,
we will always protect her.
[SAIKI]
Where are you guys going?
[MEMBER] Whatever you do,
don't break her heart.
[SAIKI]
Purge me!
--Beat Kuboyasu.
--[KUBOYASU] One, two, throw!
--A man speaks with his fists!
--[SAIKI] Settle, tough guy.
♪
--[SAIKI] Hundred yen.
--Keep that one.
There's a lost and found
over there.
[SAIKI]
Angel and demon. Weird.
A hundred, hundred yen
is a million yen.
[SAIKI]
No, one-hundredth.
Anyway,
instead of their ideas,
I'll just find
its last owner.
Let's check out
the hundred-yen store,
--100 meters ahead.
--Hundred-yen store?
Let's go to that 100-aisle
megastore 100 yards up.
--It's been open for 100 days.
--[SAIKI] Why say "yard?"
[NENDOU] Ooh,
it's 100 stories tall, right?
--Are you coming, Saiki?
--[SAIKI] I'll pass.
An exhibit of 100 sweets.
[SAIKI]
I'll stay 100 minutes.
Pictures worth 100 words
times 10.
[SAIKI]
Why do I feel so strange today?
Hey, that was more
than 100 yards!
Who cares if you had to walk
longer than you wanted?
What are you,
100 years old?
--There must be 100 people here.
--I'll clear them out
--with 100 sumo slaps.
--[SAIKI] Please don't.
Your ugly-times-100 hundred face
should do the job.
[MAN 1] Entrants in the 100-Word
Poem Contest please enter.
[MAN 2]
The winner gets $100!
[SAIKI]
This just keeps getting weirder.
[MAN 1] Congratulations
to our hundredth customer!
[SAIKI]
Great. Now what.
Customer 100, here is your
100th customer prize
of 100 lilies,
each with 100 pebbles...
[SAIKI]
That's a lot of words.
I feel like 100 bucks.
[SAIKI]
He does look good.
Anyway, I'm not crazy,
right?
Something really weird
is going on in this episode.
[MAN 1] You get this
King of 100 Animals plush
and 100 cartons
of 100-percent orange juice...
[SAIKI] One hundred.
It's appearing more often
than it normally should.
That's what's wrong.
We'll even add 100 points to
your store reward card.
[SAIKI] He said it again after I
said it.
So, what does it all mean?
[MAN 1] And look at our top 100
products and take one home.
Can I have 100 hours to decide?
--We pick one?
--[MAN 1] Of course.
--[SAIKI] I'm at a loss.
--Look at that encyclopedia set,
with 100 articles
and 100 photos inside.
--[SAIKI] Is it fun to say?
--Hey, hundred-proof sake.
Sake is top ranked
of 100 medicines,
but a cold can lead
to 100 diseases.
[SAIKI] What does that
have to do with anything?
A 100-gallon water heater that
can hit 100 degrees Celsius.
--[SAIKI] That's a reach.
--The coolest: this Blu-ray set
of 100 horror movies, including
The Parade of a Hundred Demons,
Screaming
at a Hundred Decibels,
and The Fiend with a Hundred
Faces for 100 total scares!
--[ALL] Thank you! Come again!
--[SAIKI] Why this number?
And now I'm seeing it everywhere
too. What's going on?
What was that
Mizuki Kawashita manga
--that used to run in Jump?
--Strawberry 100%.
--[SAIKI] That was random.
--Yeah, that's the one.
[KAIDOU] Know your enemy
and know yourself,
and you'll survive 100 battles.
You boys
are 100 percent alike.
Who wants to feel
my 100-percent-real boobs?
[SAIKI] Who are you? I'm out.
This is too weird, even for me.
Driver, stop the car! Feels like
it's been 100 years, pal.
--[SAIKI] Teruhashi's brother.
--You have 100 seconds
--to explain what happened.
--[SAIKI] What a pain.
I should punch you 100 times,
or maybe tie you to this car,
drag you around
at 100 kilometers per hour,
and then have my men
do a 100-man kumite on you.
[SAIKI] You're obsessed
with that number too?
I can't believe
you went on a date with her,
and when she came home
her smile was at 100 percent.
It's turning my love for her
into a hatred
that's cranked up to zero!
[SAIKI] I was ready for you
to say "100" again there.
Crap, now you've got me
saying it.
Kokomi is in 99 percent
of my thoughts,
--99 percent of the day.
--[SAIKI] Dancing around it.
My men have a grip strength
of 100 kilograms
and know 100 tortures,
like the dreaded hundred lashes.
--Who's that weird guy?
--That guy's in 100 TV shows.
--[SAIKI] Not that successful.
--You're the best.
I'd watch you a hundred hours
a week if I could.
That's great.
I have very few male fans.
The girl-to-guy ratio
is a 100 to 1.
[MUGAMI] I can't believe I'm 100
centimeters away from a star!
[SAIKI] Your 100-percent love
will drop fast
once you get to know
the real him.
I bought 100 copies
of your book and your movie.
--R-One Hundred.
--[SAIKI] He was in them?
Can I ask you a favor,
though?
Say Detective Joker's
catchphrase?
--[SAIKI] Your favorite show.
--Out of a hundred cases,
I'll 100 percent solve 100.
I'll catch a hundred crooks.
I'm the 100-million
horsepower detective!
[SAIKI]
I don't remember that phrase.
[KAIDOU]
It's just like on TV!
You know, I can do more
requests for you.
This is 100-percent bold,
but do your line
from Hundreds of Hundreds
of Hundred Dollar Bills.
--[SAIKI] Dumbest title ever.
--This 100-mile journey
will take a lot more
than 100 steps.
The Hundredaire.
Do that one.
I'd give 100-million-volt shock
to 100 ladies' hearts,
before I'd give you
a hundred chocolates.
--[SAIKI] That's horrible.
--Hundred-Handed Fighter.
A hundred men, 100 times,
under 100 stars on 100 nights.
--[SAIKI] What is that about?
--[KAIDOU] Now do the big one!
The era of 100 flowers blooming!
[SAIKI] Enough.
One hundred yen, 100 men,
100 percent, 100 million.
[MAN]
You still don't get it.
--[SAIKI] Who said that?
--[MAN] I shall explain.
[SAIKI]
Hundredth episode?
[MAN]
That's right. This episode
is actually the 100th
of those we've done.
In order to make you
aware of it--
[SAIKI] But it's not
a hundred episodes.
I know we did this
for the 99th week of the manga,
but the anime
is only 20 weeks in.
Uh...
[SAIKI]
And he's gone.
Wait, who was that?
♪
[SAIKI] In case you've been
wondering, even if you haven't,
the town I live in
is called Hidariwakibara-cho.
I may have mentioned it,
I'm not sure.
Maybe go back and rewatch all
the episodes to double-check.
Anyway, next time on
The Disastrous Life of Saiki K.
I don't really want to, but
we'll go visit him in London.