[SAIKI] When you have
supernatural powers,
the impossible becomes possible.
[GOOD-LOOKING MAN A]
Whoa! Look at this little guy!
So cute. I'm a huge dog lover.
[GOOD-LOOKING MAN A] But I'm
way more into girls, heh.
[GIRL A]
No! Pochimi, come back!
--[GIRL A] Pochimi!
--[GOOD-LOOKING MAN A screams]
That was weird.
So, you wanna go out sometime?
[GIRL A] Ew, are you
trying to pick me up?
[SAIKI]
My name is Kusuo Saiki.
And I have psychic super-powers.
Sixteen years ago,
an ordinary couple gave birth
to a not-so-ordinary baby boy.
[KUNIHARU] So cute.
Almost as cute as Mommy!
[KURUMI] So cute.
Almost as cute as Daddy!
[KUNIHARU]
Oh, you.
[SAIKI] Wow. So I guess
I'm still only second place.
[SAIKI] I started talking
when I was 14 days old.
Without using my voice.
Soon afterward...
I started walking when I was
one month old... in the air.
And at one year old...
[KURUMI] We're out?
I can't cook without rice wine!
[gasps]
Kusuo?
[SAIKI]
...I ran my first errands.
[KURUMI]
Oh, Kuu.
[SAIKI] And my mom finally
started to worry about me.
Now, you'd think after
a year of this weirdness,
they'd take me to get tested.
But my folks are
kinda weird themselves.
I'm pretty sure he
stole the rice wine.
Well, I'll go pay 'em back
tomorrow, if there's time.
[SAIKI]
Not to mention lazy.
Our little psychic
boy did pay, after all!
I don't know how he paid...
[SAIKI] They can still
act like lovebirds.
And they take
everything in stride.
Including me,
and all my weird powers.
[KURUMI]
Such a talented artist!
[SAIKI]
So time rolled on.
[SAIKI] I became
the person you see now,
a high school student.
As you saw with
the floating car,
I still have my super powers.
I can bend spoons,
like any good psychic.
And I can win any
corporate give-away I want.
My life is a dream come true.
[SAIKI] That is what
you're thinking, right?
Well, let me drop
some truth bombs.
Bending spoons
makes it harder to eat,
and winning free popsicles
just leads to stomach aches.
"He's the happiest boy alive!
That boy can have anything
and do anything."
Well, that's dead wrong.
I'm the unhappiest boy alive,
a boy who has nothing.
Telepathy, Psychokinesis,
X-Ray Vision,
Precognition, Teleportation,
Clairvoyance, etc. etc.
Sure, I can do all those things.
But having powers
like that also means
having something taken away.
Sort of like how
because we feed our pets,
they've lost
the ability to hunt.
Or when a mother
spoils her child,
he loses the ability to
become a functional adult.
In this way, there are some
key experiences
I've missed out on.
Hard work culminating
in a sense of achievement.
The thrill of being
thrown a surprise party.
They're both totally
foreign to me.
Sure, I never get angry
or sad about anything,
but that just means
there's no joy or thrill
in my life, either.
[SAIKI] Maybe I should focus
on the bright side, though.
No drama means things
are always peaceful for me.
--And that's not so bad.
--[KUNIHARU] Where is he?
[SAIKI]
Hmm?
Huh? Kusuo!
Welcome home, my son!
You're running
kinda late today, huh?
[SAIKI] Why's Dad sitting
in front of the house?
I'll get right to
the point, Kusuo.
I'm locked outta the house.
Can you open it up
for your ol' pop?
[SAIKI]
Are you kidding? Again?
[KUNIHARU] Whoa! I love
those psychic powers of yours!
They're just so sneaky! Yeah.
[SAIKI]
Don't call them sneaky.
[KUNIHARU] Kusuo.
With those kind of powers,
think of all the
things you could do.
[SAIKI] Keep your dark
thoughts to yourself, Dad.
[KURUMI] Kuu, is that you?!
You're back?
Ah! We'll talk more later!
[SAIKI] I guess there
is one thing in my life
that's decidedly un-peaceful.
I can't believe you changed
the locks on me again!
[SAIKI] That would be my
parents' current relationship.
I hope you're hungry, Kuu-Kuu.
I'm making you breaded
pork chops for din-din!
Hang on, and now you're
choosing to ignore me?
Besides I told you I wanted
to have steak tonight!
I'm sorry, I forgot.
But I can boil you
a leather shoe.
[KUNIHARU] I don't want
a shoe, leather or not!
[SAIKI] I wonder when
it went wrong for them?
They used to be so passionate.
I love you like
a fish loves water.
Oh, you.
My hate for you's become
as wide and deep
as the Pacific Ocean!
I hate you like
a fish hates air!
You suck.
[SAIKI] Well they're
still passionate now,
but it's a little different.
[KURUMI]
Gorge yourselves, guys!
I made a ton!
[KUNIHARU]
Hey! Hey! Hey!
[KURUMI]
Is it good, Kuu?
Oh, honey, would you
like something else?
No, because I bet
it's just the other shoe!
[KURUMI]
Bon appetit!
[KUNIHARU] That's not
even from the same pair!
[SAIKI] They've been going
at each other for a year.
Hey. Kusuo.
Use your powers to turn this
old shoe into a steak for Daddy.
[SAIKI]
So in case you forgot,
this pathetic dude's
my dad, Kuniharu Saiki.
He's lazy and irresponsible
and asks for help with
everything in his life.
But, surprise-surprise,
the more I help,
the more useless he gets.
So, lately, I've stopped
doing him any favors.
What? How dare you take
your mother's side in this!
Do you have any
idea how many shoes
I have to lick each day to buy
that food you're eating now?
[KUNIHARU] Nothing better
than Italian. Loafers that is!
[SAIKI]
So, you do like to eat shoes?
All right! I'll eat it!
It stinks! What did you
do to this shoe?
Are you trying to
poison your father?
[SAIKI] I'm pretty sure that's
how they always smell, dummy.
[KURUMI]
Hey, Kuu.
Now, just remember
what I've always said.
Please don't use
your powers for evil.
[SAIKI]
This is my mom, Kurumi Saiki.
[KURUMI] You must only use your
powers to help those in need.
Or those people who you are
certain are genuinely nice.
[SAIKI]
She's a big reason why
I haven't let my gifts
turn me to the dark side.
She's a caring soul,
well, to me.
But feel free to use your
powers to hurt your daddy.
[SAIKI] She kinda has
a dark side herself.
Stop eating Kusuo's dinner,
you thieving son-of-a-bitch!
That's it.
--We're taking this outside!
--[KUNIHARU] No way.
[SAIKI] In truth,
I could break up this fight
whenever I feel like it,
ut this is something
they're going to have to
work out themselves.
Hmm? Coffee-flavored jelly?
Hm. Doesn't taste bad.
Earthy, with a slightly
citrus-note finish.
Don't let the name
fool you, folks.
This jelly is a mature,
dignified treat.
Better still, when you add
just a splash of whole milk,
it becomes an entirely
new flavor sensation.
And that hint of
decadence
is everything I ask
for in my dessert.
You wanted to
eat jelly that bad?
Forget the jelly,
we got bigger problems!
Your mother's turned
into a monster!
[KURUMI] Stop running
from me, you coward!
You gotta help me, son!
You're my only hope
to stop her reign of terror!
Do it! Slay the demon!
[KURUMI] You're not
leaving till I say so!
[KUNIHARU screaming]
[KUNIHARU]
Oh God! Ah!
Huh? What?
Hey! Kusuo?
[SAIKI] I've got the weirdest
parents. I really don't care
about stopping another pointless
fight, but I can't help myself.
[KURUMI] So now you're
on your dad's side?
But I even made you pork chops!
[SAIKI] Why do I say
it's pointless? Just wait.
I want nothing to do
with either of you again!
[KURUMI] That's a lie.
Truth is: I love them.
[SAIKI]
No matter how hard they try,
the voices in their
hearts always bubble up.
In other words, all these
fights they have are a sham.
[KUNIHARU] All right, well,
I hate you both, too.
So there! Yeah! I said it!
[KUNIHARU]
Just kidding!
You know, I love you guys!
I wanna snuggle!
Oh, honey...
[SAIKI] Like I said:
Another pointless fight.
There is one person here who
has real reason to be upset: Me!
Those weirdos
interrupted my dessert!
I guess only a
psychic can fix this.
--[KUNIHARU] Love you!
--[KURUMI] Love you!
Wait. Did you just
say you love me?
[KUNIHARU] Is it really
possible she loves me back?
What? No, it's you who said it.
[KURUMI]
Oh, no.
I thought I just thought
that, but did I say it?
And what does
"she loves me back?" mean?
He loves me?
So you did say it!
You just admitted
to thinking it out loud!
[KUNIHARU] Is it possible
that I love her so much
I've started hearing things?
[KURUMI]
He loves me "so much"?
[KUNIHARU]
Huh? She can hear me, too?
What? Yeah.
[KURUMI]
He did say it!
Not out loud.
[BOTH]
What?
Kusuo!
[SAIKI]
Forced shared telepathy.
I used my psychic powers to link
their minds at the neural level.
In other words, thanks to me,
they can now hear
each other's thoughts.
Turn it off right now!
I don't want your dad finding
out that I still love him!
Her finding out that I still
love her is my worst nightmare!
I love you, dear.
I love you, too.
[SAIKI]
Cool. The end.
[KUNIHARU]
I'm sorry, honey.
[KURUMI] No, I'm sorry.
It was all my fault!
[SAIKI] What a pain,
normal people are complicated.
At least now I can finish
my dessert in peace.
...eating your coffee jelly
would have trapped us
in this cycle of violence,
I wouldn't have done it!
You did nothing wrong, honey.
It was all my fault for
getting so angry with you
and breaking all the doors
and windows in the house.
Let's set things right!
A token of our renewed passion!
Whoa!
[KURUMI]
Is it good?
[KUNIHARU] Mm-hm! It's a mature,
dignified treat. Delicious!
[SAIKI] This is my
high school, PK Academy.
Five hundred forty-two kids
walk these hallowed halls.
[BOY STUDENT A]
The Principal will not shut up.
[SAIKI] Despite the school's
relatively small size,
no one knows about my powers.
If they did know,
all hell would break loose.
Back when I was
in kindergarten.
I was undefeated in
rock-paper-scissors.
Which shouldn't surprise you,
since you know that I can
hear people's thoughts.
--Rock-paper-scissors-
--[SAIKI] Some kids would cheat,
--Colt-45-shoot!
--so I'd just tie them,
so they'd never win.
In lawless kindergarten,
all battles are fought with
rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, Kusuo, let's
play rock-paper-scissors.
If I win, you have to share
your treat with the
other students.
[SAIKI]
Even against a teacher,
--I always won.
--How 'bout best of three?
--And won.
--Uh, best of nine?
Tradition says teachers just
need to win once, right?
[SAIKI]
And won.
Let me show you,
--[SAIKI] It's quite the streak.
--here comes rock!
[SAIKI]
After that,
she disappeared from
the school, entirely.
I followed up that incident
with even more success.
And it took a while for
things to finally die down.
So, I learned it's best to stop
using my powers in public.
Now I only do it when
it's absolutely necessary
and when I'm sure
no one else is looking.
And the way I do that,
is to use my telepathy.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[SAIKI] Within 200 meters,
I can sense anyone.
[NENDOU]
Guess who!
[SAIKI]
Well, that used to be the case.
There's one guy my
powers always fail to spot.
Hey there, buddy!
[SAIKI]
Riki Nendou.
The guy no one likes, but who's
strangely taken a liking to me.
But that doesn't bother me.
What does bother me is the fact
that no matter how hard I try,
I can't read this
guy's thoughts.
And believe me, everyone
has thoughts I can read.
Like this guy.
[ONIGAWARA] I don't
wanna go to the dentist.
[SAIKI]
Or this guy.
[MONK A] Mu, mu, mu, mu,
mu, nose hair, mu...
[SAIKI] I can even read
the minds of animals!
But when it comes
to Nendou, forget it.
I finally figured
out why that is.
Nendou is a moron.
You can't read a mind if there's
--nothing on it,
--Who is this old guy
--which is scary.
--who keeps talkin' to us?
--[thud]
--Uh?
[BOY STUDENT E]
He passed out!
[NENDOU screams]
[NENDOU]
What happened, buddy?!
[SAIKI] Well, he's not
a bad person at least.
I mean, I don't think so.
Okay, I take it back, he's evil.
[IGARASHI] Nendou,
what do you think you're doing?
Take him to the nurse!
Uh? What? The nurse?
Okay, right!
Hey Saiki, why don't you
go with the two of them?
I don't trust Nendou to find it.
[SAIKI]
Dammit.
Huh? Is the nurse
dead, too? That's weird.
Guess I'll have to do
mouth-to-mouth on you myself.
[SAIKI]
Please don't.
[grunts]
I don't need mouth-to-mouth,
you stupid idiot!
You're better.
Well that's nice to see.
[TAKAHASHI] 'Course
I'm better! I was faking!
[TAKAHASHI retches]
Wasn't worth it though,
since I got kissed by you!
Well, if it makes you
feel better, I'm sad, too.
You were my first kiss.
[SAIKI] You're only
making it worse, Nendou.
Now everyone's gonna
think Nendou and I are in love!
[SAIKI] I absolutely guarantee
no one is thinking that.
Hey! You better not tell anyone
my fainting spell was a fake.
[TAKAHASHI] I can't count
that as my first kiss, right?
That was terrible!
[TAKAHASHI]
Don't tell anyone!
[SAIKI] Don't tell what?
That you faked being sick?
Or that now I know you shared
your first kiss with Nendou?
If it's the sick thing,
you're too late.
I heard it all!
[TAKAHASHI]
Matsuzaki!
So your fainting
was a con job, huh?
[TAKAHASHI] Crap!
It's Gym Teacher Matsuzaki!
That's not what
happened, sir!
It's his fault!
He forced me to collapse,
so we could skip out
on the principal's speech
and my sickness
is actually a ruse.
Nendou, is that all true?
[NENDOU]
Wha--?
[SAIKI] Pinning this on
Nendou isn't a half-bad idea.
Huh? Saiki?
What're you doin' here?
[SAIKI]
What?
Takahashi, is he
also a part of this?
Who? Uh, yeah, sure.
That's it! I want
you both, in my office!
[SAIKI] Dragging me
into this is a bad idea, pal.
[NENDOU]
Hold on a sec, teach.
His fainting was real.
Didn't you hear him say it?
Root sickness.
[SAIKI]
Holy crap he's dumb.
How could anyone
mistake "ruse" for "roots"?
What? Isn't that right?
What in the holy heck?
What's "root sickness"?
[NARRATOR A]
Root sickness is a deadly virus
that infects the victim
through his follicles.
Oh, that one.
[TAKAHASHI]
Huh?!
[SAIKI]
He's dumb, too.
Let's take your temperature
to see if you have a fever.
'S what my mom
always does for me.
[TAKAHASHI] C'mon, dude,
I don't have a fever.
I'm not even sick!
[MATSUZAKI]
Ninety-two point-eight Celsius.
Huh?
Go call an ambulance now!
[NENDOU]
You can beat this thing, man.
[MATSUZAKI]
We'll save what hair we can!
[SAIKI] Pyrokinesis:
My ability to manipulate fire.
Oops, I melted the tip.
Better hide the evidence.
Whoa.
[SAIKI]
He saw!
You... have the fever too?
You can beat this thing, man!
[SAIKI]
Like I said, Nendou's a moron.
[KAIDOU] I'm Shun Kaidou,
an 11th grader at PK Academy.
At least, that's my cover story.
In reality, a force
called "Black Beat"
dwells in my right arm.
But they are trying to
steal this power from me
and create a new world order.
I'm referring to
the Dark Reunion!
But with my power,
I will protect the world.
I, the Jet Black Wings!
[chuckles]
[SAIKI] His body's grade 11,
but his mind's grade 8.
[BOY STUDENT J]
Did ya hear?
A deadly snake escaped
from the local zoo.
There's a poisonous
snake on the loose?
[KAIDOU]
Are you boys sure it escaped?
An animal attack is
just the kind of plan
they'd come up with.
But fear not, I,
the Jet Black Wings,
am never fooled by
their evil deception!
Someone must've set
that snake free on purpose!
Hang on. You know the
guy who did this, Kaidou?
Some wannabe supervillain
called the Black Wing?
[KAIDOU] No, I'm
Jet Black Wings, the hero!
The villains are a
secret organization
named "Dark Reunion."
And this escaped snake
thing is the first step
in their evil plot
to sort mankind!
[STUDENTS]
Dark Reunion?
Who? Jeez. Never heard of them.
Heh! Once again, the fate
of the world has fallen
into our super-powered
laps, eh, Saiki?
[SAIKI]
Oh, boy. He doesn't realize
I actually do have superpowers.
This is all just
play-acting for him.
[KAIDOU]
Saiki, what's your read?
I don't like this one bit.
This snake, which I've named,
"Murder-Dragoram-Snake,"
is likely no ordinary snake.
[SAIKI]
That's quite the dramatic name.
[KAIDOU] It's also likely
that Dark Reunion genetically
engineered Murder-Dragoram-Snake
specifically to kill people!
[SAIKI]
He's fond of saying "likely."
We're running out
of time here, Saiki.
the world's counting on us
to stop that slithering--
Hey! Good news,
they caught the snake.
Well, that's a relief.
Where did they find it?
[BOY STUDENT M]
At the school's front gate!
It was just kinda laying
on the ground, half-dead.
[KAIDOU]
Is it possible Saiki and I
aren't the only students
with superpowers?
[GIRL STUDENT G]
'Kay, why was it half-dead?
[BOY STUDENT M]
Some first graders had been
whipping it around.
[SAIKI]
That's one weakass murder-snake.
Sounds like we beat
Dark Reunion this time.
Be careful what you say!
They're an all-powerful
secret society.
[GIRL STUDENT H]
Who knows what they'll do to you
when they "sort mankind"!
[STUDENTS laughing]
Hah. Go ahead and laugh!
This is the calm
before the storm.
Dark Reunion is coming.
I tried to warn
you all, I swear.
[SAIKI] He's going
to the bathroom to cry.
Whoa. I'd better go with him.
[BOY STUDENT N]
...pretends he's a super hero!
It's like he's in
elementary school!
One time, he said there's
a monster in his arm!
[BOY STUDENT N gags]
You guys, it's starting to
take over my whole body!
[BOY STUDENT P laughs]
Watch out!
There's something in there!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[BOY STUDENT P]
Ah! Snake!
[BOY STUDENT Q]
Get out!
[BOY STUDENT R]
It's blocking the door!
[SAIKI]
I saw that snake coming.
Y'know, because I'm psychic.
I could help them,
but I'd have to out myself.
So, I'll just stay here
until things calm down.
Speaking of calming down,
Kaidou should stay
here for a while, too.
Now, back to that snake attack.
[BOY STUDENT S]
Did someone see where it went?
[GIRL STUDENT I] Somebody
break out and get a teacher!
[BOY STUDENT T]
And risk being bitten? No way!
What a bunch of dorks.
[BOY STUDENT T]
When did you get in here?
Are your guys'
balls still attached?
[BOY STUDENT T]
Worry about yours!
[NENDOU]
'Cause mine feel weird.
Well, obviously they do.
The snake's on your crotch!
[STUDENTS]
Nendou!
[NENDOU]
I'm dead.
[SAIKI]
Calm down.
It didn't bite
through the fabric.
[BOY STUDENT S]
It's coming toward us!
[NARRATOR B]
The power of Clairvoyance!
By crossing his eyes,
Kusuo is able to remotely
view distant locations.
[KAIDOU]
Everybody, get down!
I'll take care of this snake!
Kaidou, what're you doing?
All right,
Murder-Dragoram-Snake.
It's time you face me,
the Jet Black Wings!
Let's go!
[BOY STUDENT V]
That's a real pose!
Let's get outta
here while we can!
So we're having a fake superhero
fight a real
poisonous snake now?
[SAIKI] Kaidou may look
confident right now,
but he has no idea what to do.
[KAIDOU] Why did I think
I could fight a snake?
I'm so stupid!
[STUDENTS screaming]
[screams]
[KAIDOU]
Oh, no, I'm screwed.
I love you, Mommy!
Take this!
Judgement Knights of--
[SAIKI]
Sorry, Kaidou.
I'll be handling
this part myself.
[KAIDOU]
Thunder!
[SINGING VOICES]
♪ Judgement Knights of... ♪
[STUDENTS cheering]
[SAIKI] I'm sorry I said
you had the body of
an eleventh grader and
the mind of an eighth.
You don't have real powers,
but you certainly
have real courage.
[KAIDOU]
I really do have super powers!
[NARRATOR B] Thus, the Great
Snake Attack came to an end.
I don't care for this new
attitude of yours, Kaidou!
You better watch
what you say, teach.
It ain't a pleasant
thing to get blasted
with the "Judgement
Knights of Thunder."
[MALE TEACHER A] That's it.
Go to the principal's office.
[NARRATOR B]
He's gotten more immature!
[SAIKI] I take back
everything I just said.
[NARRATOR B]
Hey, a pretty girl!
There's no one better at
getting people's attention.
[TERUHASHI]
My name is Kokomi Teruhashi.
And not to sound arrogant,
but I'm an example
of a perfect pretty girl.
Again, I'm not
trying to be a jerk.
I'm just stating a fact.
For the most part,
I don't make a habit
of boasting about
my flawless good looks.
Hey, you wanna go out
with me sometime?
[TERUHASHI] Now, if I were
your average, pretty girl.
How 'bout you go to a
pig farm and kiss one of them?
[TERUHASHI] I'd probably
say something like that.
But I'm perfect.
I'm sorry, but I have
to study for a test tonight.
[giggles]
Oh, good luck!
[TERUHASHI] So, not only
am I beautiful on the outside,
I'm beautiful on the inside.
And you know what
that means, right?
It means I'm invincible.
That guy's in my class.
What's his name?
Sega?
Sakè.
Saiki!
Kunio Saiki!
Aw, he looks so alone.
Poor thing.
I should go say hi
and brighten his day.
Remember?
I'm not just pretty
on the outside,
I'm also perfectly
pretty on the inside!
[TERUHASHI]
Saiki! Hi!
I couldn't help but
notice you looked sad!
[TERUHASHI] Perfect!
Now he has a memory of me
to cherish for
the rest of his life.
Not only did you
get to be seen talking
to the prettiest girl in
school while out in public,
she's the one who
rushed over to you!
I bet you've fallen in love.
That's okay.
Even though we're on
separate social levels,
it's a natural response
to my beauty.
How else are you supposed
to react to perfection?
[TERUHASHI]
That's it?
You're supposed to panic at the
mere thought of touching me!
Oh, I get it!
He's uncomfortable showing
his emotions in public.
That's the only way to
explain his non-reaction.
I bet he's just beating
himself up for being
so bashful around me.
Okay, then, shy guy.
I'll give you another chance.
Because I'm not
just beautiful, I'm nice!
I'm the perfect pretty girl!
Saiki! Silly!
You know it's not polite
to ignore a girl--
[TERUHASHI] He didn't
even stop, let alone bow!
Am I invisible? Am I dead?
Oh! I know!
He's so used to being
alone and miserable,
he's probably convinced himself
that any pretty girls who talk
to him are just illusions.
Well! I'm gonna have
to prove to him I'm real
and give him the
happiest day of his life.
[TERUHASHI]
Saiki! Don't leave me alone!
He dodged?
But if he thinks
I'm an illusion,
why would he have
to step around me?
Is it possible
that he's so in love,
even touching my illusion
would be too much?
Even though she's a figment...
[TERUHASHI] It's very flattering
to know that I mean so much
to this poor, pathetic boy.
[SAIKI]
Oh, brother.
Why does this chick from
school keep following me?
Saiki! Hi!
[SAIKI]
Here she comes.
The one thing this
arrogant girl won't consider
is that I'm ignoring her.
Though, to be fair,
if I was the kinda
guy she thinks I am...
Oh, wow, it's Teruhashi!
[SAIKI] ...I probably
would be just like that.
Nendou, too.
Oh, wow, it's Teruhashi!
[SAIKI]
She is very pretty.
In fact, everything Teruhashi
thinks about herself
is actually true.
That's what makes
her so dangerous.
She really does
attract attention.
And because
I don't like attention,
I don't want her around me.
Do you mind if I
tag along with you?
I promise it'll be fun, Saiki!
[SAIKI]
Nendou!
This is bad.
She thinks I think she's fake,
but if he acknowledges her,
--I have no choice but to
--Hey, buddy,
--acknowledge her, too.
--and girl from school.
[SAIKI] I'll be checkmated
by social convention.
Oh wow! I didn't
know you were there!
[SAIKI]
I simply can't let that happen.
I'll disappear into the crowd.
Huh. He didn't see me.
That was a close--
[NENDOU] Hmm? I could swear
I just saw my best friend.
[TERUHASHI]
Huh?
Oh, no! Where did Saiki go?
Huh?! What's going on?
[SAIKI] Whoopsie.
I accidentally teleported.
[TERUHASHI]
Saiki!
[SAIKI] The people around
me didn't seem to notice
my vanishing, but of course
Teruhashi knows
something is off.
Well, maybe it's best if
you think I was the illusion.
[TERUHASHI]
Nendou?
Oh, wow! Hey there, Teruhashi!
[TERUHASHI]
Do you know where Saiki went?
What? Buddy? Nope.
Haven't seen 'im.
[TERUHASHI]
It's... like he disappeared?
Is it possible he was a
figment of my imagination?
You're so much in love with me
that you see illusions of me?
Oh, my gosh. No. It can't be.
Don't tell me that I'm...
Wh-What're these
feelings coming over me?
I think I'm falling
in love... with Saiki?
[SAIKI]
Oh, wow.
Teruhashi.
[SAIKI] Because it's critical
to your enjoying the show,
I'll remind you again that
my name is Kusuo Saiki,
and I'm a psychic with all
sorts of crazy mental powers.
This is annoying.
This season, on The Disastrous
Life of Saiki K. :
Each chapter of the
manga gets an episode!