♪
[man singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
Uh-oh.
I face a difficult decision.
This is the coffee
jelly I normally buy.
This brand is 183 yen
for a three-pack,
which is a great deal.
If it's that much for three,
then each one's just 61 yen.
Eating two would
only cost 122 yen,
which is still less than
one of my usual jellies...
Mommy, look, that weirdo's been
there for a long time.
...which option
promises satisfaction?
[SAIKI]
Gotta be this kind.
I'll get two times as many.
And quantity beats quality.
Net weight?
Ugh, that's right!
Just as I thought,
each container
in the three-pack
is smaller.
So it's not double
the amount after all.
Sneaky.
In this case,
this brand's quality
makes up for slightly
reduced quantity.
And obviously quality
beats quantity.
I got 3000 yen
for my allowance, so, heh,
I can buy 21. Enough to cover
the surface of my desk.
But wait, if I go
with the other brand,
I can buy 16 packs.
And that times three is 48!
I could make a bed
out of 'em!
Or give one to every member
of a certain overpopulated
idol group!
[GIRLS] Thanks for
the coffee jelly, Saiki!
[SAIKI] Should I get
the three-pack after all?
It's just one serving?
And they're charging almost
3000 yen for it?
That's obscene.
Who would spend that much
money on a coffee jelly?
I would.
What was I thinking?
Not to mention,
it's only 55 grams.
Could the taste of this one
really be more satisfying
than eating 48 cups
of the kind in the three-pack?
I mean, coffee jelly
is coffee jelly.
One kind can't be that much
better than any other.
Though, with that price tag,
it's gotta be pretty good.
And if it's not,
well, considering
that I just blew my entire
monthly allowance on it,
I could just destroy
their factory.
Anyway, I need
to get home fast.
Walking around with a
3000 yen coffee jelly,
I'm practically begging
to get mugged.
Should I teleport?
No, people would notice.
I could teleport
just the coffee jelly
back to my house,
but that can get
a little complicated.
When I wanna
transfer an object
to another location,
in return,
I have to apport
something of equal value
from the same place.
Oh, no! The jelly!
Psychokinesis!
[ball whistles]
[sighs]
You're safe.
[BOY] I'm real sorry, sir.
Are you okay?
[SAIKI]
Yeah, I'll be fine.
But I can't
say the same for you,
after what you did.
Sorry, the kid doesn't know
his own strength.
[SAIKI] I'll let you off
if you go away.
What, you know this guy?
[SAIKI] How do you always
show up at the worst time?
Hey, did you see
where my ball went?
♪
[NENDOU]
Hm, no luck.
But it can't have gotten
too far, right?
[SAIKI]
Actually, it did.
Which is why
I'm looking for it
using clairvoyance.
--Ooh?
--Find it?
[SAIKI]
It's not working.
Can't locate it.
Sorry, kid, I give up.
True, I'm the one
who sent it flying.
It was your fault for throwing
it at me in the first place.
I'm gonna head home now
and enjoy this coffee jelly.
[NENDOU] I can buy you
a new one.
[BOY] No, it has to be
that ball.
Wha--?
My grandpa gave it to me
right before he died,
so it's
really special to me.
I see.
Well, in that case,
we're sure as heck
gonna find it!
And I promise you,
we'll all keep looking
till we do!
Thank you, sir.
Oh, but it looks like
your friend
already left.
What?
[SAIKI]
What a pain.
This thing's so lost,
I had to use
thoughtography.
Ah, it's in the water.
Clairvoyance won't
help me get it then.
Gotta try something else.
Maybe I can apport it.
To bring the ball here,
I'll have to exchange
something of equal value.
Think this stuff
ought to do it.
Apport!
[BOY] You know, that ball
was signed by Negishi.
[NENDOU]
Who's Negishi?
[BOY]
He's a baseball player!
[NENDOU] You serious?
That's awesome!
Is it worth a lot?
[BOY] Grandpa said
he saw a ball
just like it on the Internet
going for 3000 yen.
[SAIKI] I see.
So that's why.
[BOY] Ha, you found
my baseball?
Oh, there you are, buddy!
Wow, thank you, mister!
I can't tell you how glad I am
to get it back!
It's my most
prized possession!
[SAIKI] I can always buy
coffee jelly some other time.
For him, there'll never be
another ball like that.
[doorbell rings]
[KURUMI] Ooh! Coming!
[Saiki gasps]
[KURUMI] A boy
and his older sister
came by
and dropped these off.
They said they wanted
to thank you
for the other day.
Did you do
something nice for them?
[SAIKI] I guess it's good
to do good sometimes.
♪
[GIRL]
You went to the House
of Fortune-Telling, Chiyo?
It was amazing!
They told me I'd finally
be able to break up
with Takeru
and find a new boyfriend!
Takeru, you been to the House
of Fortune-Telling?
Yeah, it was great!
They said me and Chiyo
would make up
and find happiness.
[SAIKI] Both fortunes
can't be true.
How naive. Fortune-telling's
a ridiculous fantasy
concocted by false prophets
trying to prey
on the weak-minded.
[SAIKI]
Wow, for once you and I agree.
Anyway, forget about that.
There are more
important things.
Come with me after school.
Haven't you noticed?
There's a strange aura,
and Dark Reunion's
behind it.
I know they're
up to something...
[SAIKI] That's fantasy. You
have anyone else to go with you?
Buddy, did you hear about
the Telling-Of-Fortunes...
[SAIKI] It's all in the "House
of Fortune-Telling."
and I'm sick
of hearing about it.
[SAIKI]
They shouldn't do that. Hm?
So that's the House
of Fortune-Telling?
[GIRL]
Well, how was it, Kiyomi?
[KIYOMI]
Okay, get this!
They said
Kento Yamazaki's fate
is destined to be intertwined
with mine!
[SAIKI] Well, if it
makes them happy... Hm?
Kaidou?
What's he doing here?
[KAIDOU] I don't care about
fortune-telling,
but if this person
is a prophet,
then it's possible Dark Reunion
would target them.
I've gotta scope out the
situation for the greater good.
[SAIKI] Their fortune-telling
seems suspicious.
They said I'm gonna
go out with Kento!
[SAIKI] Kento's
got two girlfriends now.
[FORTUNE TELLER]
Next in line.
[SAIKI]
Well I'm already here.
Might as well check
the place out.
Welcome to the House
of Fortune-Telling.
Please, have a seat.
Okay.
This place is so cliché.
My name is
Mikiko Clairvoyance.
It is a true pleasure
to read you today.
[SAIKI] Even her name
is sketchy.
[KAIDOU]
Uh. Your advice?
[thinking]
She seems kinda shady.
Maybe she is
just a normal person after all.
[SAIKI] Looks like he's
not impressed either.
Oh, my. I'm getting a very
special aura from you.
[gasps]
[MIKIKO] You're no
ordinary boy. You have talents.
[KAIDOU] This woman's
the real deal!
[SAIKI]
Since you reacted like that,
now she sees right
through you.
[MIKIKO]
He's got a hero complex.
This'll be almost too easy.
I'm picking up there's
something troubling you. Right?
[KAIDOU]
How did you know?
[SAIKI] People without troubles
don't come to places like this.
Ha, let me tell you
what it is.
A romantic dilemma...
is not the problem,
so concerns about school
or your future...
are also not
what is troubling you,
but a relationship
with your friends...
[screams]
I'm getting a strong sense
that the source
of your distress
has to do with friendship!
[KAIDOU]
How did you know?
[SAIKI]
You make it easy.
[KAIDOU]
That is absolutely
the source of my distress.
You see, I'm secretly
a super-powered assassin...
[MIKIKO] What is
this idiot blathering about?
[SAIKI] I ask myself that
every day.
[KAIDOU]
I discovered the truth.
Yes, I understand.
[KAIDOU]
I'm used to fighting evil.
But fighting the solitude,
that's the hardest part.
I have no frien--
I mean comrades
that I can rely on.
[MIKIKO] He kept spouting
nonsense. The gist is--
[SAIKI] His problem is
he can't make friends.
[MIKIKO]
You're searching for someone
who can understand you.
But that's
the wrong approach.
[SAIKI] Huh, she makes
some valid points.
I may have
judged her prematurely.
[MIKIKO]
This will help.
[SAIKI]
What's she giving him?
[MIKIKO]
This will change your life.
[KAIDOU]
No way!
[MIKIKO]
If you wear that,
you'll be able to make friends
with 100 people,
including Kento Yamazaki!
[SAIKI] Is "Kento Yamazaki"
her word of the day?
[MIKIKO] I'm willing
to sell it for 30,000 yen.
What. It costs how much?
[SAIKI] Seriously?
What a scam.
Why do I even
bother with him?
[KAIDOU] Will this make
Saiki my friend too?
As long as you wear that,
this Saiki person
will always be your friend
and greet you with "Hey, pal!"
[SAIKI] Which Saiki are you
talking about?
[KAIDOU]
I'll take it!
[MIKIKO]
Ha, what a moron.
Going on about some shadowy
organization.
All right, next in line!
[SAIKI] I don't really care
what happens to him,
but she made a mistake
dragging me into this.
[KAIDOU]
A hundred friends?
I gotta remember
all their names.
[MIKIKO]
Kaidou!
[KAIDOU]
My first new friend!
Take your money back.
I don't want it!
Everything you said
was real!
[KAIDOU]
The necklace?
Keep it! I bought it at a
street fair for 500 yen!
[KAIDOU] What?
[SAIKI] I don't want him
thinking that necklace has
the power to make me his friend.
He should learn to make
friends on his own,
without relying on trinkets.
Oh?
Oh, hey, buddy!
And hey, runt!
It works.
This is great!
[SAIKI]
Another plan ruined
'cause you showed up.
[grunting]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
Hey, are we there yet?
[SAIKI] Somehow, I'm stuck
with these guys again.
Oh? Fancy meeting
you here, Saiki.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow! Teruhashi!
[TERUHASHI]
What are you boys up to today?
Nendou said he knew
of a good ramen shop,
so he's taking us there now.
We're gonna pig ou--
I mean eat like gentlemen.
Oh, ramen sounds good.
Do you guys mind if I invite
myself to tag along with you?
Oops, I hope I'm not being
overly pushy.
I don't have a problem!
I think that'd be great!
[SAIKI] Seriously?
[MAN]
Oh, wow, look at her!
[SAIKI]
I let my guard down.
Teruhashi's my most
formidable opponent.
Normally, Nendou
just stands around
with that stupid look
on his face, but--
I must admit. I never
pegged you for a ramen girl.
[SAIKI] Who are you?
And Kaidou's even worse.
[TERUHASHI]
Say, Kaidou...
Yeah?
Why do you have
those bandages
on your hands?
It's to keep my powers
under wraps!
Uh, powers? Sorry, I'm afraid
I don't understand
what powers you're
referring to.
It just something
that happened...
[SAIKI] He's suddenly cured
of his hero complex.
It's really creepy,
but this is the reaction
Teruhashi always
elicits from people.
[TERUHASHI] They're excited.
It's natural, given that
they're about
to have a meal with me,
the cutest girl in the world.
Why is he still acting
so blasé about it?
Kunio Saiki!
Why don't you say
"Oh, wow!"
When you see me,
your reaction
should always be, "Oh, wow!"
[MAN] Oh, wow!
[SAIKI]
What does that mean?
[TERUHASHI] There's no way my
wiles wouldn't work on a dork
who's always got
that annoying far-off look
and probably has
a scary dark side,
that intriguing air
of mystery
with a penetrating gaze
that can see through you.
Something wrong?
[TERUHASHI]
My face gave me away!
That's it.
I'm making it my mission
to turn up the charm
and get him to say "Oh, wow..."
[SAIKI] Great, I'm drawing
her attention.
Don't want her
following me around,
but don't wanna give in and say,
"Oh, wow!" either.
Hm, I think I might
have a solution.
[NENDOU]
Ah, we've arrived.
There's the ramen shop.
[SAIKI]
Stop making that face.
Oh, wow.
We're not going in there,
are we?
[NENDOU] I hear their ramen's
crazy good!
[TERUHASHI] No! No way!
I can't!
My friend's cousin's
ex-dog-walker
said it's good,
so it's gotta be good.
[TERUHASHI] Is this like
an urban legend?
I can't go in there!
This is me we're talking about!
Of all the places they
could've brought me...
[SAIKI] Just as I thought.
She'll split without going in.
Something urgent just came up,
so I'm going home!
[NENDOU] What?
[SAIKI] Because of that
she'll be less likable.
They'll stop saying, "Oh, wow!"
What's her problem?
She thinks she's too good.
I guess she's not
like us common folk.
[SAIKI]
Once her pride is wounded,
Teruhashi will leave
me alone.
[TERUHASHI] What's with them?
They're impossible!
[SAIKI]
That's how it'll go.
I'll tell 'em
something urgent came up.
Something urgent
just came up, so--
Are you out of your mind?
She's got class.
No way she's gonna
eat at a place like that!
You don't really wanna eat in
this rundown rat hole, do you?
I'm okay with this place.
I can't go home now.
They'll think I'm stuck-up.
[SAIKI] Kaidou, why'd you
have to push her?
Her commitment to playing
the perfect woman is impressive.
♪
[TERUHASHI] Ha, there's no way
the inside could be clean.
What was I thinking?
What is this place?
It's filthy!
Hey, seriously,
don't feel pressured to stay.
I'm fine.
Taste is what matters.
[KAIDOU] She's so cool.
She doesn't look disappointed.
She's perfect!
[TERUHASHI] "She's perfect!"
You're totally right.
I've spent 16 years
carefully crafting
the image of a girl
with perfect appearance
and personality.
I can't burst that bubble
in front of him!
Besides I have
to keep alive the dream
of all 7 billion people
on Earth.
Yo, mister Manager!
Four ramen, please!
Four ramen comin' up.
[TERUHASHI] Oh wow.
That slob is
the manager here?
That monster who possesses every
trait I find repulsive?
Is he gonna prepare our food?
No, it can't be!
He's just giving our order
to the first-class chef!
[SAIKI] Quit dreaming.
[MANAGER] Here you go.
Ah, noodle time!
[bubbles]
[in unison] Oh, wow.
[SAIKI] What you'd expect
from the shop's appearance.
There goes my plan
to tank her likability.
She can't eat this.
No one can.
[TERUHASHI]
I have to eat it!
They won't call me the perfect
woman if I leave the food
that's been served to me
untouched!
And I can't disillusion
7 billion people!
[gasps]
I don't think you
should eat that.
[NENDOU] Hey, pops! Even pigs
wouldn't eat this slop!
[KAIDOU] Teruhashi eats
stuff like this?
[SAIKI]
The perfect woman, huh?
Hm, if she'll go that far
just to play
the perfect woman,
then maybe she actually
is perfect.
[TERUHASHI]
I feel sick.
♪
[TORITSUKA]
My name is Reita Toritsuka,
and I'm a psychic medium.
From the time I was born,
I've been able
to see ghosts.
People think ghosts are scary,
but they're not.
[GHOST] Hey.
[TORITSUKA]
They're actually nice.
Have a good day
and watch out for cars.
[TORITSUKA]
And helpful.
Thanks! See?
Ghosts are
completely harmless.
I guess what I'm trying
to say is,
the powers of a medium
are pretty great,
and if you
play your cards right,
they can lead
to world domination!
Hey, you there!
Are they searching bags
at the school today?
You mean PK Academy?
In fact, they are!
[TORITSUKA]
Knowledge is power.
With ghosts as my
eyes and ears,
there's no information
beyond my reach!
And he who controls the
information, controls the world!
[GHOST] What kind of filth are
you bringing to school?
[TORITSUKA]
I'm using my natural gifts
to get ahead in life and achieve
a little happiness.
It's no different than what
rock stars and athletes do.
Hey, can I ask you
to do one more favor for me?
Sure, you name it.
There! Tell me what color
her panties are!
I can't do that.
It's an invasion of privacy.
And creepy.
Well, see you around.
[TORITSUKA] Like I said,
ghosts are really nice.
So of course, they refuse
to take part in dirty deeds.
[bell ringing]
[TORITSUKA] In any case,
the benefits
of being a medium
don't stop there!
[ARIYOSHI] I'm at a loss.
Hello, ladies!
I've got some time
if you wanna hear about
guardian spirits!
Chicks are totally
into this spiritual crap.
Huh, maybe I should start
a business with these powers.
I could make a fortune!
This is a ceremony
to exorcise evil spirits.
For your own safety,
please remove all your clothing.
[GIRL]
Whatever you say.
He's already told me
everything about mine.
Oh, you should
have him do yours.
[KANAZAWA] I'm not into
spiritual crap.
Forget spirits. There's
something we wanna ask you.
Her gym clothes went missing.
Do you know anything?
No, no! I don't know anything!
It wasn't me! I swear...!
[YABE] I was just asking
if you'd seen 'em.
That's it! I'll find
those gym clothes for you!
[in unison] What?
I don't get it.
How, guardian spirits guy?
Yeah, how?
Do you have any leads,
With guardian spirits?
Well, first,
the name's Toritsuka.
And I do have leads.
There are ghosts
all over this school.
They know everything
that happens. I can ask them.
[TORITSUKA] Hey, ghost.
Let me ask you.
I'm looking
for this girl's gym clothes.
You know where I might
find 'em?
Huh? What kind
of sick stuff
you gonna do with those clothes
when you get 'em, perv?
[TORITSUKA] You got
the wrong idea! She asked me!
Oh, whoops, sorry about that.
Then yeah, I saw 'em.
When and where?
Not long ago.
Think it was when I was
goofing off,
floating inside
your Vice Principal.
[TORITSUKA] Is that fun?
[GHOST] Eh, not really.
Anyway, I saw a boy walk by
carrying a girl's gym bag.
Seemed odd at the time.
[TORITSUKA]
The clothes were stolen?
This story just got a whole lot
more exciting!
When word spreads that I solved
a robbery, I'll be a hero!
[GIRL 1] I heard he
caught a thief by himself!
[GIRL 2] That's amazing!
I hope he's single!
[GIRL 3] All that,
and so handsome!
[TORITSUKA] Ha, my dream
knows no bounds!
That's him!
[GHOST] Stop right there!
You're the guy
from this morning--
I'm that troubled boy's
guardian spirit! Leave him be!
So you're okay aiding in his
dirty deeds, but not mine?
I beg you!
[TORITSUKA] You really gonna
stand in my way?
[GHOST] As his guardian--
[TORITSUKA] Okay.
[GHOST] No, stop!
I'll do anything you want,
please, just leave him alone!
Anything?
[GHOST] That's right!
I can tell you people's
weaknesses, help you cheat,
get you whatever information
you desire!
All you have to do
is look the other way!
Thanks, but no thanks.
[gasps] Really, why?
[TORITSUKA]
I was tempted.
But there's this super
scary psychic
roaming the halls.
He's kind of
a goody two-shoes.
He sees everything
that goes on,
even in people's heads.
If he found out
I let a creep
get away with that just so I
could do bad things myself,
he'd blow me up
with his mind.
I know you're
doing whatever it takes
to protect the kid
you watch over,
so I'd feel guilty
taking advantage of you
and making you
compromise your values.
Plus, I really
wanna be a hero!
Come out, you perv!
[GHOST] Wait! He's a good kid!
Huh? He's not here.
But that girl's gym clothes are.
He probably jumped out
that window there
when he heard you coming.
[GIRLS] Ah!
Those are
Ariyoshi's clothes!
It was you who took
them all along!
We thought
it was suspicious,
you freaking out
earlier, you perv!
No, wait!
You've got it wrong!
Sorry, I really appreciate
you taking the blame for him.
[TORITSUKA] What was I
thinking? My powers suck.
Being a medium is the worst!
Aw, cheer up.
Just this once,
I made a point to check
the color of those
poor girls' panties
for you.
That's probably small
comfort to you.
[TORITSUKA] Being a medium
is awesome!
[SAIKI] Why wasn't I
in this episode?
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
[SAIKI] Within 0.2 seconds
of waking up,
I realized that my
supernatural powers were gone.
First off,
I don't hear voices.
Normally,
as soon as I wake up,
people's thoughts
come flooding into my head,
making me wish I could sleep
through the rest of my life.
I can't float
in the air either.
[SAIKI] Ow.
My punch didn't
even make a crack.
Usually, it would
obliterate the wall
and everything else seven
kilometers in that direction.
I've been freed from the curse
that is my psychic powers!
Finally! I'm free--
Uh...
And 0.2 seconds later,
I realized it was all a dream.
[MAN] Morning already? Well,
another day closer to death.
♪
[SAIKI]
Well, of course.
Nah, I probably shouldn't.
What a disappointment.
This morning is the worst.
Plus, I had that dream and now
I've got a killer headache.
Whenever I have a dream,
followed by a headache,
my precognition powers
kick in.
They allow me to see
what happens in the future.
And by "allow,"
I mean "force."
Unfortunately,
that dream wasn't foretelling
that I would
lose my powers.
No, it foretold
the explosion.
Fine. I guess I'll have to save
some lives before breakfast.
This must be the place
that blew up in my dream.
My house is right around
the corner.
I only take action when
things are gonna personally
cause me harm
or inconvenience.
If my actions happen to also
save other people, so be it.
But generally speaking,
that's never my goal.
I've saved the world
and mankind six times so far,
though only because my own
existence was threatened.
But back to this explosion.
Well, there you go.
Crisis averted.
You may think I'm kidding,
but I'm not.
An accident usually happens
as a result
of a specific
series of events.
So one tiny change can lead to
an entirely different outcome.
Let's look into the future where
I didn't change the rock.
One minute from now, a high-
school girl will run this way.
She's wearing a miniskirt even
though it's the dead of winter.
She'll slip on the rock and
tumble violently into the air,
almost like she's doing
a somersault kick.
This maneuver will send
the rock flying
straight towards
an oil tanker.
At that moment, the driver
will lower the window
to talk to the gas station
attendant,
and the rock'll hit
him in the head.
He'll fall forward
as he passes out,
His foot'll press
the gas pedal.
The tanker will move forward,
crashing into a gas pump.
Gasoline will
leak everywhere.
Meanwhile,
the girl who slipped
will have landed
in a less-than-ladylike pose.
That hurt.
[SAIKI] Just then,
a man on a scooter
will pass by,
his attention diverted.
[MAN] Ha, ha.
[SAIKI] As a result, he'll wipe
out on the spilled gas.
The scooter will slide
into the gas station,
which'll lead
to a big explosion.
So that's what
would've happened.
You get it now?
The accident
was gonna be caused
by a series of unlikely
coincidences,
like the kind
you see in manga.
If the schoolgirl
wasn't running,
then she wouldn't have
tripped on that rock,
landing bottoms up.
If she'd worn sweatpants
under her skirt,
the perv on the scooter
wouldn't have wiped out.
[MAN]
Nothin' to see here.
[SAIKI]
There's the truck driver,
who, if he'd rolled down
his window a second later,
wouldn't have been hit
by the rock.
Or if he'd had
even a modicum of skill,
he could've caught it.
[MAN] Nice try.
[SAIKI] No matter how big
an accident is,
it's always triggered
by something minor,
and so a minor change
is all it takes to prevent it.
It was easy this time,
since I saw the whole thing
in my dream.
But normally,
I only see a part of it,
which can make my job
much harder.
[grunts]
I had another
premonition just then.
And this time, all I saw
was the end result.
Seriously?
[NENDOU] Ouchy!
Where'd this rock come from
all of a sudden?
Huh? Could it be?
Yes! It's definitely a meteor
from outer space!
♪
[HAIRO] Sir! I brought all
the kerosene for the heaters
in from the shed!
[TEACHER] Oh, thank y--
We don't need all that!
We're not trying to turn
the teachers' lounge
into a sauna!
[HAIRO] Sorry!
Lemme take some back!
[TEACHER] That's not necessary.
Leave 'em in the hallway.
I'll take care of it.
[HAIRO] You got it!
[NENDOU] Hey! Check it out!
Ya ever seen a meteor before?
Isn't it amazing?
It's from outer space,
you know?
It's not a meteor, stupid,
it's just a plain, old rock.
[NENDOU]
Hey! What're you doing?
You mighta hit someone!
[KAIDOU] There's no one.
[TAKAHASHI] I overslept! I've
got class assistant duty today!
I've gotta book it
if I'm gonna make it!
I know they say never to run
'cause we might trip and fall,
but I have no choi--
And I tripped!
[SAIKI] See? It's always
something minor
that triggers an accident.
♪
[woman singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
Seriously, I could talk about
how good coffee
jelly is for days.
It's just so good.
Whoops, I let myself
indulge in happiness.
How unlike me.
Next time on
The Disastrous Life
of Saiki K,
if you ask me if I'm
a cat person or a dog person,
the answer is,
"I don't care."