♪
Huh? Is that Kuboyasu?
I don't care for the way
he's standing there all creepy.
It's no biggie.
He still shows a lot of promise
for someone so frail.
If he were properly motivated,
I could turn him into
a first-class soldier.
Dark Reunion
won't know what hit 'em
when I lead my righteous army
into the final battle.
Hey.
[THUG]
Show some respect, kid.
A simple "sorry" don't cut it
when you bump into us.
I think you broke my arm. That's
like a million yen to fix.
--Did you hear that?
--Give me a million yen.
Oh, crap. Those guys
are shaking down Kuboyasu.
But I can't turn a blind eye
to evil,
especially in my neighborhood,
so I will...
go find a hero
who can actually help.
[THUG 1]
Aah! We're sorry!
Hey, wait.
I'm a hero who can help.
[THUG 2]
Forgive us.
Let go of his throat.
You're gonna kill him.
[whimpers]
[grunts and groans,
punches landing]
What? What the heck
just happened?
I had no idea he was like this.
Oh, man.
Did this morning
really happen?
I knew he had promise,
but I never thought
Kuboyasu had such
fighting skills.
Thinking back, lots of little
things have been weird with him.
When he arrived, he introduced
himself with phrases like,
"S'up, homeys,"
and "Aren was here."
On Festival Day, he said
he got ketchup on himself,
but it didn't smell
anything like ketchup.
I also think that "huh" that
sometimes appears over his head
is really weird.
[SAIKI]
You can see that?
What's going on, little guy?
Aah! What? Don't sneak up on me
like that!
Well, you can always come to me
for advice.
[SAIKI] I can't think of
a worse guy to go to for advice.
--Well, it's...
--Wow, you really are.
Do you think something's up
with Kuboyasu?
Huh? What about me?
Aah! Nothing.
--S'up, new guy?
--What are you guys doing?
I want in on it.
Has he always been this scary?
It's not important, sir.
Sir? What's with
the formal talk, dude?
[whimpers]
You're acting kind of strange.
Did something happen?
Did you maybe see something
you shouldn't have?
What's wrong, stupid?
You scared?
You're the stupid one.
I got a little dizzy is all.
--He's a weirdo, right?
--I guess.
Get off it, Nendou.
What are you going on about?
All I hear is crazy talk.
[sneezes]
Ooh, that was a wet one.
Nendou! You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. No big deal.
Apologize to him.
Hold on.
My nose is still itching.
Oh, you got some on your face.
That's full of snot too!
Really, I'm fine.
It's just a sneeze.
After all that, he's not mad.
Can someone so level-headed
really be a juvenile delinquent?
I said...
[SAIKI] You're barely
holding it together.
We take showers
after P.E., anyway.
Guess I was wrong about him.
He's so shy
about changing his clothes.
Heck, maybe that wasn't even him
I saw beating up those guys
this morning.
Yeah, I was mistaken.
[NENDOU] Dude, why do you
take off your shirt like a--
Hey, give that back to me.
He's totally ripped
from the neck down!
I heard we're playing
baseball today.
Maybe he just likes
to lift weights.
Plenty of normal
non-delinquents do that, right?
Why is he looking at that bat
like it's an old friend?
Could he be thinking,
"I never thought I'd use you
for an actual baseball"?
Oh, crap. I think Kuboyasu's
really a delinquent.
Even the way he squats
is vaguely thuggish.
--[grunts]
--Kuboyasu, are you okay?
If he's a delinquent, there's
about to be a huge fight.
--Watch where you're throwing.
--You hit him, you hit us.
There's not gonna be a fight.
That's just baseball.
Now, where were we?
No outs. Runner on first.
Now he sounds like
a reformed delinquent
in a teen sports drama!
Whoa, thunderstorm.
Everyone inside.
Damn. We could've won that game.
Are you a loner too?
Why is there suddenly
an abandoned puppy
after it started raining?
I'm certain of it now.
He's definitely
a delinquent.
All these weeks, he's pretended
to be a normal kid
while hiding
a powerful dark side.
[SAIKI] Isn't that how
you imagine your own life?
[KAIDOU] I'll have to keep
my distance from him now.
More for his good than mine.
If he ever messed with me,
I could go full Jet Black Wings
and turn him into ashes.
Yeah, I'd like to see that.
Oh, hey, Saiki,
do you want to go--
--Afternoon, fellas.
--There's a new rule.
You got to pay the toll
if you want to walk through.
[whimpers]
Get back here.
We can't have you forgetting to
pay now, either.
What? Oh, no.
Saiki and I are
getting shaken down for money.
♪
If you want to get through, pay
up. Whatever's in your pockets.
Looks like trouble
found us again, huh?
These juvenile delinquents are
from the worst school in town.
Saiki's scared, always is.
I'd use my power,
but it's just too dangerous.
--Pay up, dumbass.
--Shun, no!
--[THUG] Take that.
--[SAIKI] Shun!
What's with this kid?
We must've punched him
a hundred times.
How the hell is he standing?
Is he superhuman?
[HYAKKIMARU] Well, what's this?
[THUG]
Hyakkimaru.
Looks like you started
the party without me.
Well, now I'm getting in
on the fun.
We just roughed him up. You hit
him with that, you'll kill him.
[laughs]
Good point. I'll hit him.
[gasps]
[snickers]
Oh. Hey,
what happened to my arm?
[ALL] Hyakkimaru!
So if you like to
shake down innocent kids,
then you have yourself to blame
for what happens after this.
As a parting gift before
I send you to the Netherworld,
I'll show you the power
of Black Beat--
Hey. Hey, are you listening?
Feeble-minded fools.
It's far too late
for you powerless weaklings
to escape from me.
[THUG] I said give us the money
if you want to get through.
[SAIKI] Time to come back
to Earth, Shun.
What's that?
Didn't I take all you guys down?
What? Stop screwing around
with us, losers.
Where's Hyakkimaru?
Never heard of him.
Now give us our money.
Hyakkimaru might show up
in delinquent manga,
but not in this anime.
Wait. All of that before
was my fantasy?
[THUG]
You think you're better than us?
Wait. If Hyakkimaru
doesn't exist,
I can stop these small-timers
easily using my normal powers.
This is your last chance, buddy.
What? You're gonna hit me
with that?
I won't if you give us
your wallet.
I'm outnumbered. Of all
the times to get mugged,
it had to happen
when Saiki was around.
If he wasn't with me,
I'd just hand over everything.
--You would?
--But Saiki looks up to me.
I have to take on
these delinquents
and show them my cool side.
You don't have
a cool side.
My wallet isn't here!
[wimpy voice] There it is,
in my back pocket all along.
--Who would've thought?
--You're exhausting.
[THUG 1] Whoa, you carry
a lot of cash.
[THUG 2] Your daddy
rich or something?
[SAIKI] That could pay for
a lot of coffee jelly.
Now it's your turn, pal.
Hey, you got enough for today.
Shut it,
unless you want to get hit.
Your friend finally gave us
his wallet.
Now you're gonna do the same,
okay? Hey, knock that off.
All right,
you're finally playing ball.
That wasn't so hard, was it?
Too bad I cursed your body
so that in three months,
blood will come out of
every pore.
Consider this wallet my apology.
--Then I guess we're done--
--Aah! Let's go!
Hey, hold it!
--[KAIDOU] Aah! Unhand me!
--[THUG] This kid's really slow.
He's so slow, you wonder
if he's trying to get caught.
Oh, well. Sorry, Kaidou.
I'm gonna keep running
and just go home.
[THUG] You're not coming back
for your friend?
He's not really my friend.
You do realize we're gonna
beat up your pal, right?
Oh, good. I'm glad at least
you managed to get away, Saiki.
Seriously.
I can't leave him now.
He stopped. So he does
have a heart after all.
I've hidden it for long enough.
Time to reveal my true powers.
Or I can just leave you
to this guy.
--It's easier for me, anyway.
--Hey, what's going on here?
What? A shakedown.
Kuboyasu's here.
Excellent timing.
He's a lot stronger
than he looks.
I bet he could save me.
Oh, hey. Are you friends
with these losers?
Kuboyasu,
don't just stand there. Run.
--Get out of here now.
--I can't ask him for help.
I'm just messing around.
It's fine.
I can't make him fight for me.
after I've spent the last day
trying to avoid him.
You run away with Saiki
while you still can.
These guys aren't a big deal,
so I can handle them.
[THUG 1]
Are you threatening us?
[THUG 2]
Not too bright, is he?
Whoa. Hold on.
We can't just let you go.
[KUBOYASU]
I was once a delinquent too,
but when I transferred schools,
I decided to give the
straight and narrow a chance.
Bastard!
It's not always easy leaving
that old life behind, though.
Hard to hold back
when someone picks a fight,
whether it's with me
or with one of my friends!
Aah.
Kuboyasu, you saved me.
[SAIKI] This would be
more heart-warming
if he hadn't left
a trail of bodies in his wake.
[KUBOYASU]
You knew about me.
Of course I did. No one can hide
from my divine magic eyes.
I thought I blended pretty well
as a normal kid.
Even though he knew my past,
he still told me to run.
[KAIDOU]
I don't care about your past.
All that matters to me now
is the present and the future.
--Right.
--Aah!
[SAIKI]
He's so weak.
Which card has Yumehara?
Use your x-ray vision.
♪
[NENDOU] They're closed?
Well, that's weird.
I can't believe you made us
walk 30 minutes for this.
Hey, don't blame the manager.
He's got hay fever.
That's serious stuff, dude.
Can't be sneezing around
exposed noodles. Ahchoo!
Aah. I'm mad at you for not
picking a closer ramen place.
Well, I'm going home.
Fine. Let's go find
somewhere else to hang out.
Hey, an arcade. Let's go there.
How are games
a replacement for ramen?
It's not my fault
the guy has hay fever.
Do you have any idea how
terrible that disease can get?
My point is, we need to find
a new food place, not an arcade.
All right, then, Kaidou.
Let's settle this beef
between us once and for all.
Fine. I was getting bored
of having this peaceful
everyday life, anyway.
[BOTH]
To the video arcade!
[SAIKI]
Hey, you agree on something.
Anyway, it's been a while
since I been to an arcade.
I liked it as a kid,
so my mom always took me.
My favorite game
was Whac-A-Mole.
I know it's simple, but I liked
that it just let you focus on
doing that one thing very well,
which I did.
When I hit those moles,
they never came back up.
All right.
I'm way ahead of the other cars.
Hey, how come
it's not turning right?
[SAIKI] Put a coin in.
I picked a broken machine again.
[SAIKI] It's your brain
that's broken.
Is that the best
you can do, zombies?
If you couldn't handle
the pressure,
you shouldn't have gone against
Kaido, the double bullet.
No, I'm all out.
Let me reload. Don't eat me.
Give me a fighting chance.
Oh, right. Then I'm done playing
your stupid zombie game.
--It's totally rigged.
--Well, it is a game.
[laughs]
You suck at games, dude.
Fine, then let's start
this duel.
I'm ready when you are, runt.
Just pick a game so I can start
beating the crap out of you.
Yeah, right.
You couldn't beat me
at a single game in this arcade,
but since it's closest,
why don't we go with
this quiz one?
[SAIKI] Wow, you really
want to win this.
If you just want a game
that's close to us,
what about the one
you're leaning on?
[SAIKI]
And you dug your own grave.
Uh, maybe it's better
if we let Saiki choose.
Oh, no. If you're not
gonna pick, I will.
Just play something, seriously.
[MAN] Air hockey.
First man to nine points
is the winner.
Yeah! Air hockey is awesome!
[KAIDOU] I can hold my own
against most,
but Nendou's
got the strength of an ogre.
If I don't play flawlessly,
I'll get smoked.
I need to outthink him
with strategy.
--[MAN] Game start.
--If I hit the puck straight,
he'll just block it
with his wild reflexes.
Just start.
I'll confuse him
with a rare bank shot.
--[SAIKI] Everyone does that.
--Tall hammer shot.
--Bam!
--What the...? How?
That was so fast,
I barely saw it.
[laughs]
What's wrong, short stuff?
Hmm. I actually did
pick this game randomly,
but Nendou might have too much
raw strength over Kaidou.
I can't believe
it's come to this.
That's the same attack you tried
last time, only way slower.
How'd you get two
of those hitty thingies?
Behold the impregnable wall
of double mallets.
That's cheating,
but it doesn't matter,
because Nendou still scored.
Ha! You haven't seen
anything yet.
Damn.
--Huh?
--What's up?
Can't find the puck. Can you
check if it's on your side?
Uh...
--Meteor smash!
--Aah!
[SAIKI]
That's dirty.
Looks like it was on
your side after all.
Sorry to interrupt
your victory pose,
but you cheated again.
I'll let it slide to keep you
from losing so badly.
[MAN]
Kaidou kept confusing Nendou
with more illegal,
but sneaky, plays.
--Teruhashi.
--Uh, wow.
Oh, that's weird.
You cracked the puck.
Yo, manager. We need a--
Triple mallets.
Triple mallets featuring bag.
[MAN] Kaidou ran up his score
despite lacking skill,
but Nendou
was not going away quietly.
And so it came down
to the final point.
The air-hockey battle
had reached its climax.
[pants] I will say,
you played a pretty good game,
but it's over now.
Zig-zag attack!
It's too fast.
He'll win the game with this.
All I can do is--
Oh, it's slowing down.
Well, take that.
Ha-ha! Piece of cake.
He fell for it.
Mallet bullet attack.
[SAIKI]
Play dirty to the end.
[MAN]
Game, set, match.
All right, I actually won.
How do you like me now?
And don't say I played dirty,
because no matter what,
a win is a win.
Oh, now I get it. I didn't
realize until just now
I could use those little hitty
thingies to block the puck.
Oh, why do I feel so guilty?
So in a way, Nendou wins.
Hey, I just realized
I didn't use my powers.
Oh, well. No reason to meddle in
such a hallowed sporting event.
Hey, buddy, let's get a shot
to remember this.
Hurry up. We're waiting.
[SAIKI] Do I have to?
These guys are hopeless.
♪
Where'd that idiot go?
I haven't seen Nendou all day.
Wait, I forgot to buy
this week's Jump.
Let me pop in there quick.
Welcome, friend.
--Nendou?
--Oh, hey, guys.
Wait. You have a job?
I didn't say anything because I
only started yesterday.
He's in the workforce.
That's bad.
[groaning]
--Is he gonna be okay?
--Of course not.
This is a convenience store.
It can't be that hard--
Hey, just because it's small
doesn't mean that it's easy.
There's always something to be
done in a convenience store.
Selling lottery tickets,
running copies,
stocking shelves,
topping off the deep fryer.
--It's overwhelming.
-Oh, you're smart.
Have you worked in one before?
Yeah, after I wrecked
my motorcycle.
Hey, he got a customer.
Looks like 500 yen
worth of stuff.
What? You're guessing at it?
Use the register!
Use the register.
I'd like to,
but I couldn't open the drawer,
so I tried some stuff,
and now it's broke.
[KUBOYASU] Use the other one.
Here, watch and learn.
Sir, I'll ring you up over here.
That comes to 777 yen, please.
Oh, three sevens.
That's lucky, sir or ma'am.
For a prize, please enjoy
this free box of fried chicken.
[KUBOYASU]
Don't give away product.
Your change is 333 yen.
Thank you. Come again.
[SAIKI] But that wasn't
the correct change at all.
--an I get this issue of Jump?
--Beep.
Why do you need to check my age?
It's just a copy of Shonen Jump.
Hey, Nendou, are all these boys
friends of yours?
--Yes, Mr. Manager.
--Sorry for using the register.
It's fine. A long as you're
Nendou's friends, I trust you.
This might sound crazy,
but I owe my life to Nendou.
He helped me a few weeks back
when I collapsed on the street
with severe heart palpitations.
I offered to repay him
however I could,
and he said
he was looking for a job.
That's how we got
where we are.
[SAIKI]
Yeah, that makes sense.
Nendou, I am so grateful
for everything you've done.
Thank you.
--Aw...
--And you're fired.
What?
You broke the register three
times and the copier twice.
Your tills are short 33,000 yen,
and we've gotten
27 complaints from customers.
Sorry, Nendou, but I'd rather be
indebted to you forever
than have to employ you
in my store.
[SAIKI] That was
the kind of a sped-up plot
that only happens in fiction.
Don't go crying for me, guys.
At least I have my other job.
--What?
--Other job?
Oh, hey there, Riki.
You're early.
--A ramen shop?
--It's his favorite food.
I got fired from my other job,
so I figured I'd come in early.
It was a convenience store,
and I made a lot of mistakes,
and I scared shoppers.
I want you to put
all that crap behind you
and get ready
so you can work for me.
Listen good, kid.
Everyone makes mistakes.
And looks don't matter.
What's important
is you're enthusiastic.
Be like that,
you'll always have a job here.
Or not, yeah.
You're fired.
[wind howls]
Here. You were holding two jobs
so you could earn enough
to buy these for yourself.
--You like them, don't you?
--That's not what I wanted!
My mom's birthday is next week.
That's why I was trying to
save up some money.
[KAIDOU] Oh, I didn't know.
See, since I don't have a dad
no more,
my mom has to work all the time
to support me.
She holds down
three different jobs
and still finds time to cook
for me and clean all my clothes.
That's not an easy life,
so I wanted to show my love
by buying her a present
with my own money.
Hey, what are you guys
crying about over there?
[SAIKI] Ignore those idiots.
--I'm not crying.
--If you want another job...
the diner by the train station
is hiring.
We could all go apply together.
--[NENDOU] Yeah, cool.
--I'm going home.
[MANAGER] I'd like you meet
our new waiters--
Kaidou, Kuboyasu,
and Rikii.
[BOTH]
Nendou didn't get the job?
What's the point of working here
if Nendou's not gonna be here?
We forgot that no restaurant
would ever hire
someone as ugly as he is
to be a waiter.
All right, guys,
let's make some money.
Wait. Who the hell
do you think you are?
Let me explain.
I knew Nendou's looks guaranteed
he wouldn't get hired,
so I took action.
Hey, I didn't see you there.
[SAIKI] I made it so he appears
handsomer than he really is.
Riki Nendou is now
just Rikii with two "i"s.
--Of course Nendou has no clue.
--Hey, Rikii.
Don't call me by my first name.
It's weird.
[SAIKI] I even changed
the spelling on his application.
Rikki!
You're pouring water
on that customer.
I'll let you guys
clean this up.
[BOTH] I'm sorry.
Please forgive us, sir.
How'd we get stuck cleaning some
random employee's mess?
Aah! I'm sorry!
Kaidou,
you're screwing up now too?
Part-timer, get us some ketchup
for these french fries.
[CUSTOMER]
Lickety-split, dumbbell.
[FRENCH FRY CUSTOMER]
You ain't getting no tip.
Oh, I'll get you some ketchup...
out of your nose.
Here's a tip.
Don't mess with me!
How are they so hopeless?
[BOY] Come on.
[YUMEHARA] You mean Saiki
does like me?
Nope, not a chance.
♪
[SAIKI] At least once a winter,
it happens:
a gym class so cold,
it makes you want to strangle
any teacher in a jacket.
All right, get it together.
Time for the winter marathon.
[SAIKI]
That's right, marathon.
But, actually, this is easiest
of impossible for me.
All I have to do is run,
and I can even use
my pyrokinesis to stay warm.
--You'll warm up once we start.
--Where's your jacket?
--Hairo, aren't you freezing?
--Ha! Not at all.
--See, look. I've got sleeves.
--[SAIKI] Does that help?
It drops a few degrees,
and you wimps all start whining?
Hairo, is that all
you're wearing?
He's cheating
with fleece bandages.
Man, I'm tired...
Let's ignore Nendou
in this video.
Hey, Nendou. Would you like
to be running buddies today?
Yeah, that sounds fun.
Time we settle this and see
who's the better athlete.
I will have revenge
for the physical fitness test.
--It's getting warm here.
--Like a furnace.
This is a 10K race. Every 2K,
you'll cross a checkpoint
with a teacher at it making sure
there's no funny business.
Well, sorry about this, but
I'm gonna let out my true power.
See you at the finish line.
Ready? Start.
Ha-ha! So long, mortals.
Hey, wait, Slow down.
You fools. Running fast
from the start will...
tire you out.
I'll be waiting for you
at the finish line,
even after throwing the race.
Right now, I'm in 45th place
out of 90 students.
At this pace, I'll finish
without drawing any attention
to myself.
[huff and puffs]
He's nowhere in sight.
All I got to do is stay at
this pace, and I'll finish--
Hey, you're fast. I went to buy
a drink, and you were gone.
Wait. You stopped at
a convenience store,
and you still caught up with me?
It's important to stay hydrated
when you're running a marathon.
Corn potage?
Oh, yeah.
This warms me right up.
Damn it! Sweet.
Eight kilometers left.
Huh? Guess I should
get a sweat going
so they don't become suspicious.
[pants]
Saiki, you're going too fast.
I'm impressed
he made it this far
considering how weak he is.
--Get in.
--But what if we get caught?
Don't worry. We'll get out
before the checkpoint. Hurry up.
[SAIKI] Three idiots.
--Where to?
--Eight kilometers towards the--
School. Start the race
from the beginning.
[all gasp]
[SAIKI] So there's a go-back-
to-start square in real life.
[MAN] So Saiki passed the second
checkpoint without incident.
He's now closing in on
the 6K mark,
still in the middle of the pack.
Four more to go, kiddos.
How is he at
every checkpoint like that?
Hmm? A lot of guys
are dropping out now.
What's going on?
See, Saiki? I warned them
if they went too fast
at the start, they'd just--
[throws up]
[SAIKI]
At least they're not puking.
I can't do this.
I got nothing left in the tank.
Now I have to try to keep pace
with Hairo and Nendou.
Oh, I see. Were all these guys
try to keep up with those two
idiots? That's pretty reckless.
[winded] Saiki,
if everyone's taking a break,
there's no shame
in us resting too.
As it stands,
I'll finish with a high rank.
Well, desperate times.
What's happening?
I don't even feel tired anymore.
Saiki, I've been reborn.
I'm back in the hunt.
First place is--
I turned back time on your body.
Oh. Well, I could run
another 10K.
All their energy
is coming back in a rush
because I'm basically resetting
their exhaustion levels to zero.
Come back to life, zombies.
Look, our first finisher's
coming in. It's Hairo.
No, wait. Who's that?
No! What the heck
is fueling this guy?
He's running backward,
and I still can't pass him.
It's like he's not even human.
I can't keep up.
I'm barely moving my legs.
I'm gonna lose.
I'm gonna... win!
Hey, look. It's manga author--
Shuichi Aso!
What? Where? Wait. Hairo.
Hey, where's that Aso guy
and who is he?
Second place: Nendou.
--I won.
--[SAIKI] But did you really?
[indistinct chatter]
Huh? Saiki?
I thought there was a bigger gap
between me and everyone else.
The gap would've been
much larger
if I hadn't restored them all,
but the real winner
is Matsuzaki.
--He was everywhere.
--Yeah!
--That's some good running.
--[SAIKI] That's impressive.
At least I got my boring
45th-place finish like I wanted.
Forty-four.
Weird. I could swear
there were 44 ahead of me.
Did I pass someone and forget?
I'm tired again.
[MAN] In case you're curious,
the girls' marathon
was held later in the week.
The checkpoints
will have snacks and stuff.
[GIRL] Never too early
to start work on my beach body.
When you're a perfect pretty
girl, marathons also come easy.
♪
Hi. I'm Kokomi Teruhashi.
Thank you so much for watching
the hilarious anime
The Disastrous Life
of Saiki K.,
short for Kunio.
Wait. It's Kusuo, and you're
saying I visit his house
and do karaoke next episode?
Everyone'll say, "Oh, wow,"
when they hear me sing.