♪
[man singing in Japanese]
--[GIRL 1] He is so cute!
--[GIRL 2] Come here, kitty!
[SAIKI]
People often like to ask:
"Are you a cat person,
or a dog person?"
My answer is, "I don't care."
No matter how cute the cat is,
or friendly the dog,
to me they just look
like this, and this,
so if I asked you,
"Do you like
the bones on the left,
or the right?"
Your answer would
be like mine:
"I don't care."
You might choose a pet
based on the
impression they give,
like, "This dog seems loyal," or
"This cat seems really loving."
But that's just you projecting
your own desires.
[CAT] Don't touch me so
casually, female homo sapiens.
[SAIKI] That's what
he's really thinking.
See, since I can also read
animals' minds,
I have no preconceived notions
of their feelings.
Summer or winter? Winter.
Mushrooms or bamboo shoots?
Mushrooms.
But with cats and dogs,
it's like asking whether
I like the name Sato or Susapee.
I just don't care
one way or the other.
[gasps]
[ANP] Hey, hey! Stop,
get back here, human!
I need your help!
[SAIKI]
Seriously?
[ANP]
Man, that is one cold human.
Sees a cutie like me in a bind
and totally flakes!
Wait. He's coming back!
Yes! Now get me out,
and I might let ya pet me.
[ANP] Don't you dare
walk away from me again!
[SAIKI]
All right. Fine.
[ANP]
Stupid-dumb human.
Maybe he's a dog-lover?
[SAIKI] I wasn't before.
Now you're making me
lean toward them.
Anyway, do you want my help,
or do you want to keep
insulting me?
[ANP]
What is with this dude?
His mouth doesn't move,
but I keep hearing him.
[SAIKI] Of course you do.
I'm speaking to your brain
since I don't know
how to speak cat.
--[ANP] Is he part cat? Meow?
--[SAIKI] I'm not.
[ANP] What? So then
you're just a cruel human.
[SAIKI] No, I want you
to say "please"
instead of ordering me around.
[ANP]
Okay, okay. Help me!
Do a good job, and I might
even be your friend!
What? Wait, hold on!
I'll make another offer!
[ANP] Get me out
and I'll let you pet me
wherever you want
for three whole minutes.
You can even touch my paws,
and he's gone?
No! Come back!
You didn't hear the part
about getting to
scratch my chin!
[SAIKI] How can someone
in your position be so stuck up?
Can't you just be humble
and say, "Please, help me"?
[ANP] "Please, help me"?
Are you joking?
Don't you know
who you're talking to?
I am the mighty cat!
The proudest,
most elite creature
on the Earth! When
you're at the top,
you don't need to
beg or be polite
with lowly humans!
[SAIKI] What is he
talking about?
[ANP] Just because
you walk on two legs
doesn't mean you get
to ignore reality!
If you haven't noticed,
it's you guys who give us food
while we lie around all day.
And that's not all.
When we mess up the house?
We're forgiven.
We turn off your Super PlayBox?
We're forgiven
Even when we spill ink
on your manga
the day before it's due,
we're forgiven!
The world revolves
around us cats.
I am your Mighty Pharaoh!
Now do as I say!
Hey! Wait! Get back here!
[SAIKI] How many times
are we gonna repeat this?
Just leave me alone.
[ANP] It's your fault
for disrespecting me.
[SAIKI] I'll only say this once.
You're not getting
another chance.
Say "please" or else I'm leaving
you stuck here forever.
[ANP]
I just can't get through to him.
Who does he think he is,
speaking to me that way?
Doesn't he want to pet me?
I bet this guy's bluffing.
He wouldn't leave a cute
little kitty like me
trapped between two buildings.
He wouldn't.
He would? He is!
All right, all right, you win!
I'll say it!
Please.
Please help free me.
Are you happy now, jerk?
[SAIKI] There is nothing
cute about this cat.
[Anp yells]
[SAIKI]
All right, you're free.
[ANP]
What's this guy's deal?
No. What's he doing?
Is he gonna hurt me?
Oh, he's gonna pet me.
They always end up petting.
You may pet-- What?
He's leaving?
I'll never forgive you for this!
Stupid human!
[KUNIHARU]
Hey, I'm home.
Welcome back, honey.
Your dinner's
already on the table.
[KUNIHARU]
Oh. Great.
[KURUMI]
What's with your belly?
[Kuniharu grunts]
What are you hiding?
Take it out!
It's nothing! Leave me alone!
It's something dirty,
like an adult magazine?
Aah!
[KURUMI] A cat?
[meow]
Oh! So cute!
Where did you find
this furball?
In front of our house,
so-- Can we keep him?
--I'll take care of him.
--[SAIKI] Seriously?
[ANP] Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You humans are so stupid.
Soon this house will be mine,
and I'll have stolen your
place in their hearts.
Honey, I'm sorry, but I'm
allergic to cats, remember?
[SAIKI]
Nice try, pal.
♪
[SAIKI]
Christmas, I hate it.
At first, it's fun to see
all the pretty lights
and the smiling masses,
I grant you that.
But where there's light,
there's also shadow.
So even Christmas
can be easily shrouded...
in the darkness bubbling up
from people's hearts.
They may look happy
on the outside.
--Yeah!
--[WOMAN] Gotta string him along
until I get my present.
Then it's Splitsville.
[SAIKI] But deep down, this
is how they really think.
The only people who seem
to genuinely love Christmas
are either little kids
or couples madly in love.
Unfortunately, my parents fall
into both of those categories.
It's like this every year
at my house.
I have a bad feeling.
Why're you so late?
Let's get this party--
[KURUMI] I ran into
your best friend at the store
so I invited him.
When it comes to parties,
the more the merrier, right?
[SAIKI]
Someone please end my misery.
Not that I play them,
but this feels like
the Christmas scenario
in a dating simulator.
I wonder if I can avoid
triggering any flags.
Oh, right. I forgot we were
still missing one weirdo.
Merry Christmas!
Santa's here with presents.
I thought this was supposed
to be just family.
--Now I look like a fool.
--[SAIKI] Because you are.
Who's that guy?
[KURUMI]
He's Kuu's friend, Nendou.
Kusuo has a friend?
Oh, dear!
[SAIKI] You too?
[KUNIHARU] But how?
Kusuo's such a jerk.
If I went to school with him,
and he didn't have powers,
--I'd punch him in the face.
--[SAIKI] Wow. Thanks, Dad.
Hello, Nendou!
I'm Kusuo's dad, Kuniharu.
I've heard so much about you!
Oh, it's so nice
to finally meet you,
Mister Kusuo's Dad.
[KUNIHARU]
He seems like a thug.
Is he really Kusuo's friend?
He seems more like
the dumb bully type.
--[KURUMI] He's a good kid.
--[SAIKI] We can hear you.
This is a great costume.
I thought you really were Santa.
What? Oh. Thanks, kid.
[SAIKI]
Now you like him?
[ALL]
Merry Christmas!
Well, Nendou!
I get the feeling
you're just a big kid
under all that beef.
[SAIKI]
You're acting like
the host family
foreign exchange student.
[KUNIHARU] Before Kusuo
turned 1, he was already
treating his old man like
something found in his diaper.
[SAIKI]
You should have taken that hint.
I can tell by the way
you listen, you're a good kid.
Ha, oh? I don't know
if I'm that good, sir.
When I was little,
Santa never visited my house.
No way!
Why would your dad
deprive you like that?
Well, my dad's dead.
He passed away before
I was even born.
[KURUMI]
What?
I had no idea, Nendou.
[KURUMI]
I'm sorry my husband said that.
[NENDOU]
Heh. Why? Doesn't bother me.
I've still got my mom.
And I'd rather have her
than Santa once a year.
I see. Um, would
you please excuse us.
You two keep eating.
Huh. That's odd.
Anyway, that's pretty cool
your dad still comes home
in a Santa costume
every Christmas.
[SAIKI]
I have a feeling
this night's about
to get more uncomfortable.
I'm back!
Sorry for stepping out.
[NENDOU]
No prob! Where's my buddy's dad?
[KURUMI] He had to leave
for a work thing.
Something about clients needing
their shoes licked.
Anyway, let's eat!
Huh--?
Aah! Oh, no!
There's a man dressed
like Santa trying to break in!
[KURUMI]
Oh, my!
I told you
to unlock it for me.
[KURUMI] I'm sorry.
But I didn't think you'd be
so fast getting to the door.
[SAIKI]
You're so sloppy.
Hey, Nendou! I'm Santa Claus.
It's nice to meet you.
[SAIKI]
That's worse than I expected.
Pulling the exact same stunt
twice is bound to fail.
Even Nendou will notice.
The real Santa Claus is here!
Aah!
[SAIKI] Then again. This is
Nendou we're talking about.
[NENDOU] I can't believe it! I'd
be honored to shake your hand.
Ho-ho-ho! Of course!
[SAIKI]
He's getting carried away.
Oh, hold on!
I just remembered
you fly around with reindeer!
[KUNIHARU]
What? What?
[NENDOU]
I've always wanted to see
a reindeer in person!
They're grazing just outside
on the lawn. Go look.
[KUNIHARU]
Kusuo, help me out!
[SAIKI]
You're on your own.
[KURUMI] Kuu, please.
It's Christmas. Be giving.
[SAIKI]
Seriously? Fine, here goes.
[NENDOU]
Whoa! That reindeer is awesome!
[SAIKI]
It's just a normal deer.
Here, Nendou. It's for you.
Whoa, a present?
[SAIKI]
Isn't that my present?
Yeah! That's two presents!
What? You have two gifts?
I thought you said you'd
never gotten one before?
[NENDOU]
Yeah, nothing from Santa.
But I still get one from my mom.
Every year, while I'm asleep,
she comes in and puts a present
right next to my pillow.
I wonder why she doesn't
just give it to me herself?
Oh, well.
[SAIKI]
Your mom is a saint.
[man sings in Japanese]
♪
[KUNIHARU]
Ugh. It's so crowded!
[KURUMI] Well, it is New Year's
Day, what do you expect?
[SAIKI]
I expect to be able to stay home
and enjoy the day in peace.
I wish for another
happy year with you.
Oh, no. Why are you doing
your New Year's prayer to me?
Oh, but Kurumi,
don't you see.
the goddess I pray to is you.
[SAIKI] Ugh. He gets so smug
when he charms her.
[SAIKI] Wishes, huh?
I can make my own come true
whenever I want,
so I don't have any.
Besides, I'm not religious.
God, Buddha--
All the same to me.
[KUNIHARU]
Please let me win
200 million
in the lottery.
[SAIKI] That's not what you
wished for earlier.
[KUNIHARU] I beg of thee,
oh, Great Kusuo!
[SAIKI] Wait. You're
praying to me now?
Oh, well.
Might as well kill time too.
"Please let the rest of
my New Year's Day be quiet."
Thank you.
[SAIKI]
Well, guess I'll go home now.
[KAIDOU]
Whoa. Hey there, Saiki.
[SAIKI]
See? There is no God.
[SAIKI] This year
is already off to a bad start.
Also, his scarf is dragging.
[KAIDOU] Visiting the shrine
for New Years?
That's nice.
I only happen to be passing by.
I'm not really
the superstitious type.
Huh?
I'm Kusuo's Father, Kuniharu!
And I'm his mother.
You are such a handsome boy!
Thank you for being friends
with our grumpy little Kuu!
What? Um. Yeah, well, sure!
Greetings! Sir and ma'am.
I'm-- Jet Bla--
Uh, Kaidou!
Oh, hi, so your
name is Kaidou?
[KAIDOU] Uh, Kusuo is
one of my greatest allies--
I mean, friends!
Ha, ha. Yeah.
[SAIKI] Boy, you are really
struggling to interact
like a normal person. Oh,
and Nendou isn't my friend.
Yeah. I know.
Who would've thought
Kusuo was able
to make two real friends.
Honey, no, I didn't
mean it like that.
My prayer was for Kuu to make
lots of friends this year.
Don't you see?
The year's barely begun
and it's already been granted!
[SAIKI]
Then grant mine already!
Neat. You know, I prayed for
the exact same thing.
We're on the same page, honey.
Always thinkin' alike.
[SAIKI]
You wanted money.
So, Kaidou, have you gone
and said your prayer yet?
[KAIDOU]
I should! Indubitably!
[SAIKI]
"Indubitably"?
Well, time for me to
go converse with the heavens.
[SAIKI]
So you do believe there's a god?
[KURUMI] Kaidou seems
like a good kid.
[KUNIHARU] Yeah, he does. Even
if he is dragging his scarf.
[SAIKI] You guys have
such low standards.
[KAIDOU] Saiki's parents are
a bit on the strange side,
but I guess
they seem nice enough.
Please let me have
more friends this year.
[SAIKI]
You too, huh?
[Kaidou laughs]
I didn't expect to engage
in a battle with God today.
[SAIKI]
Why did you bow so low?
[KURUMI] So what was
your prayer about, Kaidou?
[KAIDOU] Well, it's
a secret. Indubitably!
[SAIKI]
Sounds like you decided
to kind of play
your character part-time.
Now you really sound weird.
--[HAIRO] What's up, Kaidou?
--[KAIDOU] Huh?
Oh, wow. Saiki's here too?
How you doing?
Happy New Year, guys.
[SAIKI]
What are you wearing?
[KAIDOU]
If he's here,
does that mean
my prayer was heard?
Oh. Uh, thanks.
You do the shrine thing?
To be honest, I-- Saiki,
who are these people with you?
[SAIKI]
Ugh.
[HAIRO]
Oh, you're his parents!
Good to meet ya! An honor.
Kusuo may have mentioned that
I'm the class three rep.
Name's Kineshi Hairo.
Your son is always quick to help
me out at school.
[KUNIHARU &amp; KURUMI]
He's a good kid!
[KURUMI] And Hairo is such
a well-mannered young man.
[SAIKI] Who dresses
like he's at the gym.
To think that my little
Kusuo has so many nice friends!
Your mother is
just so very happy!
Yeah. You've turned into
Mister Charisma, son!
[SAIKI] They're not my friends,
they all just follow me around.
Although, I am curious
to hear what he's praying for.
[HAIRO] A friend and rival who
will get on the court with me
and push me
to become a stronger man.
That's what I need
in my life.
[SAIKI] That's a
passionate request.
So, Hairo,
what did you pray for?
Ha-ha-ha. It's a secret.
[SAIKI] What is the deal
with everyone praying
at the shrine for more friends?
--[NENDOU] Oh, hey guys!
--[ALL] Hm?
Wow. Why you all
at the shrine today?
[KUNIHARU]
Nendou?
[NENDOU] Oh! Hey,
buddy's mom and dad!
[HAIRO]
Is-- Is it possible?
The man destined to become
my rival is Nendou?
Nendou! Do you play tennis?
[NENDOU] Never! But I'm
probably pretty amazing at it!
[SAIKI] Does make me wonder
why so many of their prayers
are getting answered today.
Oh, well.
Probably just a coincidence,
because my prayer,
to be left alone,
hasn't been answered at all.
♪
So, Nendou,
have you prayed yet?
Oh, you mean like
ringing that big bell?
Sure, I'll do it.
[SAIKI] Ugh. Now he's going?
I hope for all our sakes
that Nendou doesn't
pray for anything weird.
[NENDOU]
Unh. All right! Ha-ha-ha-ha.
[gasps]
Okay, now it's time for ramen!
[SAIKI]
What was that about?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Nendou, you're funny.
You only rang the bell once.
I'll show you how
to do the whole ritual.
[KUNIHARU] First, you
throw the money in there.
Then, you ring the bell.
After ringing the bell,
you have to bow twice. And then
you clap your hands twice,
like this, and say a prayer.
[KUNIHARU] I hope Kusuo
finds a girlfriend next!
[SAIKI] Wait, what did you
just ask for?
I must be hearing things.
Even if he did say it,
and this was all real,
he already prayed once before.
No way it'll happen.
[TERUHASHI]
Is that who I think it is?
[SAIKI] You've gotta be kidding
me. I'm not gonna turn around.
Oh! It is you, Saiki!
[TERUHASHI] Running into him
at a special place like this
--has to mean something, right?
--[SAIKI] Why is everyone here?
[gasps]
What the--?
Who is this girl talking
to my son?
Does Kusuo know her?
Who cares! My wish
has been granted!
Though I hate him
for getting attention
--from such a hottie.
--[SAIKI] I don't want it.
Oh, wow! It's Teruhashi!
What? Who is this lovely lady?
Hey, what's up, girl?
Want me to show you
how to ring the bell?
[KUNIHARU]
Kusuo's dad! Nice to meet you!
And I'm Kuu's mother!
[SAIKI] Why are they
all acting like this?
I just want some
peace and quiet.
Kusuo!
You going home now?
I know, why don't you all come
back to our place to celebrate.
We got a big spread!
Yeah, please come!
[NENDOU]
Great! I'm hungry!
[SAIKI] Hey, God,
grant my wish already.
[KAIDOU] Teruhashi, you didn't
pray! Is that all right?
I'll come back later.
[TERUHASHI] I don't have
anything I need to pray for.
I just came so my presence
would bring a little more joy
--to the masses waiting in line.
--[SAIKI] You're not God.
[TERUHASHI] All the boys in line
can see me and go, "Oh, wow!"
[SAIKI]
What are you talking about?
[KUNIHARU]
Everyone, follow me!
[NENDOU]
Whoa! Mashed chestnuts!
[KUNIHARU]
Have more!
[HAIRO]
Piggin' out rules!
[SAIKI] They've overrun
my only sanctuary.
This food is amazing!
Would you please teach me
how to make it sometime?
Oh! I'd love to!
Ha. You're gonna make
a great wife, Teruhashi!
[SAIKI] What a terrible way
to start the year.
[KURUMI] No, thank you.
All of you,
for being friends with Kuu!
You don't have to thank us
for being his friends.
We're here
because we want to be!
Hm. That's right.
You're sincere.
I'm just so grateful for you.
[SAIKI]
Uh...
My Kuu's always had
a really hard time
making friends, what with him
being a psychic and all.
[SAIKI] Well.
At least it's finally quiet.
Um. You may have said too much.
What?
[SAIKI]
Now would be a good time
for divine intervention.
What do you mean
by he's a "psychic"?
Uh.
Honey.
You should say something.
Oh, dear.
[SAIKI] Calm down.
There's nothing
to panic over.
For example, if your
friend's mom had said...
"My little Ken
has psychic powers!"
[SAIKI] How do you
think you'd react?
I'll tell you,
'cause it's not exciting.
You'd make the face
these guys are making now.
You'd never take it seriously.
I mean, my mom says
all kinds of crazy things.
It's only if you panic that
it sounds suspicious.
All you need to do is calm down
and change the subject.
Right. Ahem. Hey.
You know, that one manga logo,
the pirate face on Shonen Jump?
Yeah. Kinda, sure.
Get this. If you turn it ninety
degrees, it looks like
the profile
of a little girl's face,
and uh, I just thought
I'd point that out.
[All]
Uh...
[SAIKI] How you gonna come back
from this, Pops?
You just made this party
even more awkward.
Oh! He's right! It really does!
Guys, look!
[TERUHASHI] I see her!
[SAIKI]
Nendou, I'm somehow grateful.
You successfully
changed the subject.
--[NENDOU] Never noticed that.
--[KAIDOU] Me neither.
--So my buddy's a psychic?
--[SAIKI] Get out.
Did you know a female sunfish
lays up to 300 million eggs
for each spawning?
[SAIKI] You get out too.
Fine, I'll do it.
[TERUHASHI] Ah! Sorry!
I must've bumped into it!
[HAIRO]
Are you okay?
[SAIKI] Hopefully one situation
will distract from the other.
But I worry that I'm too late.
[man sings in Japanese]
♪
Well!
Thanks for the dinner!
We're forever in your debt,
thanks.
You kids drop by
anytime, okay?
[KAIDOU] I didn't expect Saiki's
parents to be so friendly.
[NENDOU]
Yeah.
[KAIDOU] You sure took
advantage of them.
You made yourself right at home!
[NENDOU] Me? What about you,
talking all fancy.
What was that all about?
Inbubitably.
[HAIRO] It's still New Year's.
Don't ruin it by fighting.
Oh, by the way, anyone figure
out what his mom meant,
when she said he's a psychic.
What was she talking about?
[HAIRO]
Oh, yeah. I don't know.
[SAIKI] Oh, man. I didn't
undo the damage after all.
Dad made it even worse.
Figures.
[KAIDOU]
It was such a weird moment.
His mom is weird though,
so it was probably just a joke.
[SAIKI]
Yes, my mom is weird,
but I don't want to hear that
from you guys.
Ha. You fool.
--You read too much manga.
--[SAIKI] Look who's talking.
[HAIRO] I'm just playing.
Well, I live down here.
See ya at school.
[TERUHASHI]
I gotta go this way.
[KAIDOU] I'm going this way.
So I'll bid you adieu.
[NENDOU] Huh. Which
direction is my place?
[KAIDOU] I don't know.
[TERUHASHI] See you at school!
[SAIKI]
So what's my next move?
None of them really believe
I'm a psychic, which is good.
But thanks
to my mom's big mouth,
the idea's been implanted
in their heads, which is bad.
It already hurts my conscience
to think about
what I have to do,
but I see no other way.
I'll use this thing that looks
like the TV Tokyo mascot
--to make it all disappear!
--[NENDOU] Ow!
Uh. What the--
[SAIKI] Things should start
getting back to normal now.
I erased part of his memory.
A very tiny part.
In fact, just the key word
"psychic."
The trick is channeling
my powers through this thing
that looks like Nanana,
the TV Tokyo Mascot. But isn't.
It's a complicated bit
of psychokinesis,
so I won't explain it here other
than to say I can only erase
up to one minute of memory.
Now I have to repeat this
procedure three more times.
It's such an imposition.
And I haven't even had a chance
to tell you about the biggest
drawback to this ability.
--[GIRL] Happy New Year!
--[BOY] Gonna be a good one!
Hey, Saiki.
Back to spending our days
at this boring school again,
huh?
[gasps]
[KAIDOU]
He's probably still embarrassed
with how awkwardly
dinner ended at his house.
I never would have
expected it.
Kuu has had a hard time
making friends,
because he fantasizes
about being a hero.
[KAIDOU] Ignorant idiots often
accuse me of having
the same problem.
I know exactly how it feels.
So don't you worry.
I'll support you as only someone
who shares your pain can.
[KAIDOU]
Saiki!
This is our friendship sign,
cool? Never forget it!
[SAIKI] Don't worry. Can't
forget what you don't remember.
So here's the drawback
I was talking about.
When I erase a memory,
a blank space appears.
And when that happens, the
brain's natural repair mechanism
kicks in and fills that void
with a different memory.
The replacement memory varies
for each person,
so I don't know what they think.
[TERUHASHI]
Ooh, it's Saiki.
I haven't seen him since New
Year's Day. That was fun.
But it was surprising to hear
what his mom said about him.
Kuu has a hard time
making friends
because
he doesn't trust people.
[TERUHASHI]
Saiki has trust issues.
[SAIKI] Like I said,
each of my friends
now has a different memory
of that dinner.
[TERUHASHI] I bet he liked a
girl once who broke his heart.
That would explain why
he's all "No, wow" around me
instead of going,
"Oh, wow!" Ha, ha.
Don't worry, Saiki. This goddess
will melt your frozen heart.
[SAIKI]
When a memory's replaced,
sometimes things turn out good.
Or, in the case
of Teruhashi, bad.
[Teruhashi giggles]
[HAIRO] Hey, Saiki!
So about New Year's... Uh.
[HAIRO] Well, you can't blame
him for being cold.
If something like that happened
to me, I'd be messed up too.
Kuu used to be captain
of the tennis team.
He was competitive
and obsessed with winning,
but the other members weren't
into it. They quit.
That's why he has such
a hard time keeping friends.
[SAIKI] That's a long
replacement story.
--[NENDOU] Oh. Aah.
--[SAIKI] Nendou.
I don't know what his
replacement memory is,
and frankly,
I don't want to know.
Somehow he's ended up more
attached to me than ever before.
[NENDOU] Come on!
Kusuo!
Wanna come whack
some tennis balls?
[KAIDOU] Saiki, do you sense
a disturbance in this hall?
Oh, Kuu.
Heh. I sound like your mom.
[SAIKI] So there is a God.
He just hates me. Hmph.
♪
[woman singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
That's weird.
I just realized Hairo was
the only character today
who said, "Happy New Year,"
even though most of this
episode was about New Year's!
Next time on
The Disastrous Life of Saiki K,
if you thought
New Year's was strange,
you haven't seen anything yet.
We're introducing
an all-new character.