♪
You really don't have
much time to practice,
your next show's
about to start.
[chuckles]
Oh, Michael, a magician
can never stop
trying to improve.
In magic, what's important
isn't the reveal,
it's how you keep
the audience from noticing
the misdirects
you do along the way.
That's why I practice
every chance I get.
[MICHAEL] Wow. You've come
so far, Mister Chouno.
You too, Michael. No more dove
tricks in the park for us.
Well, I still like
to keep them around,
just in case you ever
need to fill time.
Don't worry,
we're fine.
[MAN] Mr. Chouno,
they're ready--
Whoa, what's with
the doves?
We've got a whole, new act.
Our best one yet!
Kusuo, hey! It's tres bien!
Hm?
Did you hit your head?
It's fine.
I can fix that for you.
Ah! No, I'm fine!
You haven't heard this
catchphrase?
Everyone's saying it!
[SAIKI]
Don't know, don't care.
I'll do it again.
It's tres bien! Eh? Hey?
[SAIKI]
Go to work.
Look? This is the guy
I'm doing.
He's the magician
on all these ads now.
Those guys? Chouno and his
assistant, Michael.
It's surprising
you don't know them.
Or rather,
"it's tres bien"!
Stop that now.
I know
that catchphrase!
I've seen them
on TV, too.
I hate those
dumbbells.
Wow. Hard to believe
when I first met them,
they were just
a homeless magician
and his smelly assistant
in the park.
I never thought
they'd get this big.
I don't understand life
sometimes.
Kuu. You actually
got something
in the mail from the guy
we're talking about.
Uh, it's so
tres bien.
[CHOUNO]
Master. It's been a while.
I'm writing to let you know
that I'll be performing
my new magic show in your area.
I know I've caused you
trouble before,
so I'd love for you
to see me now.
I think you'll find
our updated act
pretty exciting.
Hope to see you there.
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen--
[SAIKI] I'm interested to see
where he's at.
[audience applauding]
It's tres bien!
[SAIKI] What? People actually
like this?
Maybe he's just doing that
catchphrase
to get their attention.
Hey, Michael! Where are you?
Sorry I'm late!
Hey, what took you
so long!
It took me a while
to find
the right brand
of chainsaw.
[CHOUNO]
We don't use that in our act!
[MICHAEL] It'll make my job
so easier. Let me show you!
You'll cut me in half!
Aw, let me try it!
I'm not gonna
let you kill me!
Too late!
No!
[audience gasps]
Ugh! Wow.
Tres bien!
[audience laughing]
This is their new act?
They've really moved away
from stage magic.
A quick trick.
With a ball.
Ugh...!
[MICHAEL] Ladies and gents,
he's levitating the ball!
He's sticking
his thumb in it!
It's tres--
Bien!
Well, if the audience likes it,
who am I to argue.
[CHOUNO] So what do you think
of our new stage personas?
We merged a comedy double-act
into our old magic show!
If you remember, we used
to make mistakes all the time.
Then I realized
that it was our mistakes
that always got a reaction
from the crowd.
I said, "let's make those
funny mistakes part of the act."
And now look:
We're doing well!
Sure, I never reached your
skill level,
but all the money and fame
makes this a good trade off.
I see.
Well, good luck.
Wait! Master!
Let your past go, son.
[SAIKI] I didn't have to stick
around any longer.
I knew what he wanted to say.
He's self-conscious
about using his mistakes
to make people laugh.
He wants to make sure
I don't think
he's avoiding
the hard work it takes
to become a great magician.
Heck, being a popular comedian
might be an even bigger
accomplishment.
[MAN]
I hate this!
Why do I have to be
the warm-up act
for a couple
of no-talent clowns!
They're not fit
to do magic
at a kid's birthday!
Who was that guy?
[MAN 2] Some guest
I had to let in
for them, earlier.
They call him, "Master."
Hey, wait, kid, explain to me
how you're Chouno's master.
You're even younger
than him.
I wanna see what
magic chops you got!
I'm not his
master.
Show me that ball trick
he does.
Hey, come back!
Do a trick for me!
No, don't!
What? It's floating.
What the...?
[SAIKI]
Why are you so surprised?
You asked to see
a magic trick, right?
Here's another one.
Free of charge.
[both gasp]
Who is this guy?
Wow, Master!
All right, that was childish
of me, I admit it.
Master! Once more, you've
motivated us to do even better!
The comedy-magic thing's got
potential. Bye.
We're losing the
comedy from our act!
What.
Your floating ball trick
made me love magic again!
We wanna do what it takes
to reach your level, Master!
Seeing as how
you're not psychic,
just stick
with the comedy.
Eh, do whatever.
You don't really have
the talent
for comedy, either.
[CHOUNO]
Tres bien!
♪
[YUMEHARA]
Good morning.
Oh, Chiyo,
it's been a while!
[gasps]
What happened?
We see each other
every day, silly.
Yes, of course.
I was just distracted.
You okay?
I'm fine, thanks.
Ugh... Should I say
something or not?
Wow. Winter's here.
Yeah, but I swear--
She has to know,
right?
But, maybe she needs
to hear it
from someone else
to realize how bad it is?
Are you sure,
you're fine?
What?
No, I'm always perfect.
Ever since I said
hello,
you've been acting strange.
I'm gonna tell her.
Sometimes people don't notice
how much they change,
because they see themselves
in the mirror every day.
Is she letting me know
she knows?
It's the best
opening I'll get.
What about your weight, Chiyo?
[chomping]
Ow! What are you doing, Mera!
That hurts!
Darn, I missed my chance
to slip it in naturally!
You have no right to eat me!
Sorry, I didn't think you'd mind
if I took a little.
[TERUHASHI]
Mera, that's way rude!
Yeah, but why was I the first
thing you tried to eat?
It's not like I'm--
Huh? What?
Uh-oh. When'd I gain
this weight?
So, she didn't
know.
[SAIKI]
It's nice to get outside
every now and then and read--
[YUMEHARA] Gotta lose it!
--or not. Seriously.
So much for quiet time.
I'm hiding because
that sounds like Yumehara.
[panting]
Or not! That can't be her.
It's like a totally
different person!
The Yumehara I know
never wheezed like that.
[YUMEHARA] I gotta lose it--
[soft thud]
She didn't trip
as much, either.
No, that's
definitely her.
You jerk-ass writers!
You run out of ideas
or something?
So you have to pull from a bin
of old tired tropes instead?
[SAIKI]
Who is she even talking to?
Oh, she calmed down.
Why's it so hard for me
to lose weight?
Mm-mm!
[SAIKI] I found your problem.
Ah! I was snacking
without thinking!
I didn't even realize
I'd opened the bag.
Don't bring junk food
to a work out!
Ah!
Cardio's too hard!
I'm switching
to bodyweight exercises.
First, I'll do 30 sit-ups.
No, 50! Here we go!
All right, let's go!
Whenever you're ready, Chiyo!
She literally
can't get off her butt.
'Kay, now, I mean it!
Three-two-one!
[groaning]
Ahh!
That's even worse!
I'm so heavy I can't move.
Seriously?
That sort of reasoning
doesn't make any sense.
I could try putting snacks
on my knees
and use them to lure
my head up.
[SAIKI]
That's a terrible idea.
She's never losing
this weight.
Looking at her brain
right now,
all she's thinking about
is food! That's no good.
What a pain.
I guess it can't be helped.
I'll give her some extra
motivation.
Yumehara! Why have you
gained so much weight?
No, Kaidou!
It's not that I gained weight,
I just got
a little bit bigger is all.
Oh! Hm? Was that a dream?
Hey! I sat up!
[SAIKI]
I knew you had it in ya.
I also know that you
like Kaidou,
so I used his voice and talked
to you, via telepathy.
I can't let Kaidou
see me like this!
[SAIKI] If people hear a voice
while they're fantasizing,
the person that voice
belongs to
automatically pops
into their fantasy.
Yumehara, there's nothing
I hate more than fat chicks.
He hates me!
After this,
she'll have no problem
staying motivated.
Well,
lost track of time.
It's getting late,
so I better head home
and finish it there--
What!
1005, 1006--
Whoa, she's still going?
And she's done
over a thousand sit-ups?
I believe it. She looks like
she's lost a bit of weight.
I knew my trick with
Kaidou's voice would work,
but I didn't think
it would work this well.
Better check inside her head
for an update.
Ugh...!
Kaidous everywhere!
[KAIDOU] Don't slow down--
[SAIKI] He's her trainer!
Sorry,
Lord Kaidou!
At that pace,
you'll be a piggy forever.
[SAIKI] Imaginary Kaidou
got an unexpected upgrade.
[YUMEHARA]
I'll try harder!
[KAIDOU] Turn yourself
from a pig into a human!
Once you've returned
to your other form,
I'll hold you in my arms
the entire night!
[SAIKI]
I like this Kaidou even less.
Scold me more,
Kaidou!
[SAIKI] It's not scolding
if you enjoy it!
[NENDOU] All right, that's
enough! It's time to chow down!
[SAIKI] Not him, please.
[YUMEHARA] Stay away from me!
Don't let them tempt you!
Kaidou!
Don't give up!
We can fight that food devil
with the power of our love!
Yes, Kaidou!
Well, it's weird,
but it is working.
Wow, you've lost
it all!
You're skinnier
than before
Aw, thanks.
And she has the hardest abs
in the world.
[giggles]
That's the power of love.
And now it's given me
the strength
to tell Kaidou
how I really feel!
Yumehara, do you have time
to do a favor for me?
Yes, sir, whatever
you want, sir!
I don't think that'll get
the reaction you want.
♪ C'mon! ♪
The last match
is against me!
Can you read
my mind?
♪
[GIRL]
Did you do your homework?
I didn't know we had any!
[SAIKI] At mid-morning,
there's a 10-minute break.
For normal students, it's
a time to relax and gossip.
But for me,
it's the most painful part--
Saiki!
--of the school day.
So you're the first pest.
The function
we learned about
in Trigonometry has me locked
me in a mental prison!
I need to defeat
this conundrum
by sneaking a peek
at your homework.
[SAIKI] Just get to the point
next time.
Oh, that's how
it works.
As I'm sure
you've guessed,
every nuisance will
visit me during this break.
Saiki!
And who is this?
Dodgeball, let's go!
[SAIKI] Hell no.
It's beautiful outside.
It's gonna be a blast!
[SAIKI]
It's a 10-minute break.
How much dodgeball
can we cram in?
Saiki, early lunch?
[SAIKI] Go away.
I think it's time you and I
have a little meeting
in the parking lot.
[SAIKI] Or we could talk here.
Hey, buddy! Buddy!
Hey, Buddy!
[SAIKI]
You're just bored.
I hear poor people
don't have free time,
so me being here tells you
just how rich I am.
You could try studying.
Crap. Someone's at the gate.
My show's taping in the area.
I thought I'd come see Kokomi.
[SAIKI] Yeah, I'm calling
the police on you.
This isn't my Kindergarten.
Where am I?
[SAIKI] You're here 10 years
too early, now beat it.
I'd like some advice
from Yumehara, please.
[SAIKI]
Then go see her.
Saiki, I'm in love.
I need to see this girl now!
It's annoying to see
Toritsuka happy,
but since he's not causing any
trouble, I'll let him be.
[SAIKI]
When did you record that?
Saiki!
Do you need help with homework?
You want some juice?
Can I be your human umbrella?
[SAIKI]
Her break's worse than mine.
You haven't seen a bike lock key
around here, have you?
[SAIKI]
Who are you? And no!
Saiki! Please, tell me!
How come I haven't been on
in a while?
[SAIKI] You haven't had
anything funny to say!
Kusuo! What's up, bro!
Can you hear me okay?
[SAIKI] This cameo's a stretch.
Not in the AV club to see him!
Bring me food, human!
[SAIKI] Who let you in?
Saiki, I need you
after school.
We're going on a hunt
for a suspicious man
who's been skulking
around town.
[SAIKI] You all ready made
your appearance!
Okay. Please take
your seats.
[SAIKI] She doesn't show up
often enough
to have a consistent design.
Class is in session.
[ALL] Yes, ma'am!
[SAIKI] Finally. I get a break.
[SHIMA] Who can solve this
question? Saiki?
[SAIKI] Oh, right.
Class is no break, either!
Lately, people have been acting
even stranger than usual.
C'mon, buddy!
Walk home with us.
The nerd says he wants
to talk about tomorrow.
Nendou!
You idiot!
[KUBOYASU]
Told you not to talk!
[NENDOU] He's my buddy!
[KUBOYASU] We're leaving!
Sorry. We've got plans
with just the three of us.
Nothing important!
[NENDOU GRUNTS]
[gasps then whistles]
This must be some
brand new type of bullying.
[KAIDOU] Man, Nendou almost
gave me a heart-attack.
[KUBOYASU] He was this close
to ruining our big hustle.
[TERUHASHI] You almost tipped
him off, too, Chiyo.
[YUMEHARA] Sorry! I promise
I'll be more careful.
Wait.
Where is Nendou?
Played it safe
and sent him home.
There's no way
his pea brain can keep up.
Good call.
When you've honed a plan
for as long as we have,
you can't afford to fail.
Now let's start the meeting!
At last, Operation: Surprise
Saiki" is kicking off tomorrow!
See? They're even
ganging up on me.
So, after school, Aren and I
will go up to him and say--
Wanna hang?
Sure!
We'll then go to my house.
We won't mention his birthday.
When we get there, I'll say--
I'm getting a drink.
That's Aren's cue
to take him
into the room.
Hey, why is this room
so dark?
Aren will then set off
a party cracker.
[pops]
Aah! Then you'll all say:
[ALL]
Happy Birthday!
Then, I'll bring the cake
and the surprise will be
a big success!
[TERUHASHI] I can't wait to see
the look on his face!
[SAIKI] This. The look on
my face will be this.
Seriously.
What am I gonna do?
I bet he'll look
something like this!
[SAIKI] Pretending to be
surprised?
I bet he freaks out,
just like this!
[SAIKI] Now they're one-upping
each other.
No! He'll scream
like I'm doing!
[SAIKI]
Dial it back, buddy.
His glasses will shatter!
How'd you do that?
Honestly,
I am pretty surprised.
[MERA] I'm impressed you
knew his birthday,
considering how private
he is.
I only knew about it because
I bumped into his mom.
She mentioned it in passing
[SAIKI]
Ah, got it.
Mom's the one who got
the whole ball rolling.
Tomorrow's gonna be
such a surprise,
There's no way he knows
that we know his birthday!
[SAIKI]
Oh, I'm surprised.
I'm surprised because
my birthday isn't tomorrow.
It's in August.
♪
So, like I said
10 seconds ago,
my birthday isn't
tomorrow.
That's why I didn't stop
their party plans until now.
I didn't consider anyone would
try to do something like that
three months ahead
of time.
Kaidou and the others
have planned a surprise party
for a middle aged man
who barely knows them.
Not only do I know
about the surprise,
they got my birthday
wrong.
This whole thing's a disaster
before it starts.
Hopefully, they'll realize this
and just cancel everything.
I'd rather this not be
my problem.
Did everyone remember
to get Saiki a present?
Kokomi and I got something.
It'll blow his mind!
It's gonna taste delicious!
Yeah!
I should stop this
before any of them
try to give me
a present.
[KAIDOU]
Huh? Hairo what'd you buy?
[HAIRO] It's a wooden Buddha
statue I made by hand!
I thought about Saiki
with every cut!
Took forever
to get right.
I'd never carved
anything before!
[SAIKI]
I really don't want that.
We're putting more than that
into ours, aren't we?
[giggles]
That's right.
[YUMEHARA]
Ta-da! Here's our plans
for our finished Saiki
Tribute Cake!
[SAIKI]
Well, there goes my appetite.
[KUBOYASU] Awesome!
[HAIRO] Incredible!
[SAIKI] It's my severed head
in frosting.
I'd be crying tears of joy
if I got that cake!
Nada sou sou.
Teruhashi's cake rules!
How is she so damn perfect?
It's my cake, too!
I better tell them
the truth
before they actually
make that monstrosity.
[KUBOYASU]
Look what we did.
What now?
We put a new spin
on the old birthday card.
He's gonna flip out
when he sees it!
[SAIKI]
What did you do!
Happy Birthday to the man
who inspired my career!
A video birthday card?
[MERA] We gotacquaintances
to wish him well!
[KAIDOU]
Awesome!
[SAIKI]
They got the Principal?
Who couldn't even
get my name.
The musician from the manga
who didn't appear in the anime!
He doesn't have a voice
because we never cast him.
You're turning 17, huh?
[SAIKI] Wait, who're you?
That's all the acquaintances
we could find.
They were hesitant
to go on camera.
[SAIKI] Why would this gift
make me happy?
[KAIDOU] I think the gifts are
great. My gift's pretty boring.
[SAIKI] Oh, good. Why couldn't
you all have done boring gifts?
Those other ones
almost qualify as harassment.
All I did was write
a silly letter from the heart.
[SAIKI] Now I'm worried.
[YUMEHARA] Read it!
[SAIKI] This is going to be
over dramatic, isn't it?
Ahem! "Dear Saiki.
"I know you'll think
it's over dramatic of me
"to write you a letter,
but that's okay.
"You're a great friend
I share memories with.
"I can't believe
it's only been six months
"since we met at the start
of the anime series.
"Anyway, thanks to you,
I met everyone else,
"and they've brought joy to my
life in so many ways too.
"I know it's sappy,
but it's true.
"It's good to know that you're
looking out for me,
"and I wanna be a better person
because of you .
"Thank you for being born.
Happy Birthday, from Kaidou."
[SAIKI]
Where'd that come from?
[KUBOYASU] Great work, Shun!
[YUMEHARU] You moved me!
Hmph.
What a pain.
I guess I can't
stop them after all.
What? He went home early?
Yeah.
How are you gonna get
him over to your place?
I don't know! I didn't
plan on him leaving early!
I think we gotta
call it off!
No! We've come too far!
We'll switch to Plan Beta!
[ALL]
Plan Beta?
I'll keep this
short.
First, we ring the doorbell
from a safe distance.
When Saiki comes out,
we set off the party crackers.
He'll be so surprised
and happy. And that's it!
[HAIRO]
Let's do it!
[KUBOYASU]
What if someone else answers!
[KAIDOU] We'll ask them
to let us in!
[doorbell rings]
[hearts beating]
[popping]
[ALL] Happy Birthday, Saiki!
[TERUHASHU] Are you surprised?
What are you doing this for?
Today's your birthday,
silly!
Yeah, it is.
Surprised you, dude!
Look, he's in shock!
Wait. So, you came here
to celebrate my birthday?
[ALL] That's right!
What a pain.
I guess that was fun to watch.
Because that Saiki
standing in the door
is not me.
It's my dad.
I didn't think you'd care.
'Course we would, Saiki!
[SAIKI] I've hypnotized them
into thinking Dad looks like me.
But I didn't tell him, so his
reaction would be genuine.
That's done. I'll go tell Dad
the truth before he makes a--
[NENDOU] They're doing the
thing. Happy Surprise, buddy!
What?
Why're there two buddies?
Surprise.
Huh? Wha--?
[groans]
What the heck's
goin' on here?
Oh. A mirror!
Anyway,
hey, birthday boy!
Yeah, thanks, Nendou.
It's been great!
Finally made it.
I'm so glad he's dumb.
♪ Come on! ♪
Can you beat me?
One, two, throw!
You're a hundred years
too early to beat me.
♪
[SAIKI] My wrong-day
birthday surprise party,
courtesy of Kaidou and Company,
is still going.
[laughing]
Thank you so much!
[KUNIHARU] I can't believe
Kusuo's friends would
celebrate my birthday!
It touches my very soul.
That's sad.
Such an honor
to call myself your friend!
You rock, Saiki.
[KUNIHARU] Weird, but I love
the attention!
I don't know
who these girls are.
I guess they think
I'm a cool dad.
[SAIKI]
Of course you're not.
Any minute now,
they'll all get suspicious.
I have to find an opening
to tell Dad.
Hey, Saiki, what time
are your parents coming home?
[SAIKI]
Uh-oh...
What? My folks
don't live here.
Are you sure?
My Mom's at her house
and Dad's dead, so, that's that.
Oh, no,
your dad is dead?
[SAIKI]
You just killed yourself off.
I'm sorry.
No, my Dad died
a long time ago.
[KAIDOU]
You sure get over it fast.
[SAIKI]
Come upstairs.
What? Kusuo?
Kusuo?
Kuu-rap-so.
So I have to go upstairs
and take a crap. Be right back.
[SAIKI] Don't change
my name to crap!
I knew something
must have been going on.
They were acting
a little too strange.
No you didn't.
You bought into it.
Now you'll switch in
and be you, right?
No, you'll stay on as me.
What? I don't wanna act!
[SAIKI] I can't convincingly
pretend today's my birthday.
[KUNIHARU] Why're you confident
I can pretend to be you?
You'll be fine.
Ugh...
I just feel
so uncomfortable
around their relentless
good cheer.
Be Kusuo, be Kusuo.
What a pain, what a pain.
Toilet problems.
What a pain--
[SAIKI]
I don't say it that much!
What's wrong?
We feel bad for making
such a racket
in your
dead father's house.
[KUNIHARU]
He's not dead!
What? Your Dad's not dead?
I was just joking to get you
back for surprising me.
You shouldn't be joking
about death.
Yeah, parents dying
is totally not cool!
Just forgive him.
This is a bit much.
Guys, c'mon,
let's have some fun.
It's time
for Saiki Cake!
It turned out
so perfect.
We spent a long time
on his face.
♪
[ALL]
Oh wow.
But why? It must've gotten
smashed on the way here.
With candles,
it'll be fine.
I'll eat the whole thing--
Is this made of poop!
Shut up, Nendou!
[YUMEHARA] I'll make another!
Seriously? Fine. Psychokinesis!
Everyone,
stay calm!
[TERUHASHI] Look! The cake is
going back to normal!
[MERA] It's like the sponge
is springy again!
[SAIKI]
What a pain.
Whoa! Awesome cake, guys!
Kokomi and I baked it!
Man, Kusuo's got great friends.
Kusuo?
I mean I! Me!
I'm Kusuo!
And in my, Kusuo's,
perspective,
Kusuo is very happy to have
such great friends.
[SAIKI] Great. Now I talk about
myself in the third person.
Heh. You're gonna love what's
next even more.
Mera and I
made this for you.
[SAIKI] My video letter.
[thud]
[groans]
[camera thuds]
Oops, looks like
it broke.
I'm sorry, Saiki.
Punch me so we're even.
[SAIKI]
There's nothing to settle up!
[KUBOYASU]
You guys can hit me, too!
[SAIKI
Seriously?
If we didn't have--
[KUBOYASU] Hey, it's playing!
[NENDOU] Must've healed.
[MERA] Saiki, watch it!
[SAIKI] I still have no clue
who that guy is.
Let's get this party
started for real!
Cheers to Saiki!
[ALL] Cheers!
[all laughing]
♪
Oh, there you are!
I was so popular in there
I didn't know what to do!
Good for you.
Those high school girls even
hand-fed me a piece of cake!
But the guys made you
kneel on the floor.
Let's switch now,
so you can have fun.
Yeah, I'll pass. If I go down,
I'll just kill the mood.
Who cares about that?
Those kids like you, Kusuo.
And deep down,
you like them too.
After all, you asked me
to take your place
so they wouldn't
feel bad
about getting
your birthday wrong, right?
But, they didn't come
to spend time with me.
Even if the mood
does change,
I think they'd rather
be with you.
Go down there, son.
[SAIKI]
Who are you to give me advice?
[KUNIHARU]
I'm your Dad!
[KAIDOU]
Well, it all worked out.
Saiki looked so happy
and full of life.
I've never see him
that social!
How can I get them
to leave?
But I have this weird feeling
something's wrong.
Like what?
Like he wasn't being himself.
[HAIRO]
Yeah, he seems pretty distant.
[MERA]
Yeah, I know what you mean.
[TERUHASHI] I wonder if
he's forcing himself
to get along with us.
[YUMEHARA] That'd be awful!
[KAIDOU] He should feel
comfortable around his friends!
Fine. Normal Kusuo Saiki
it is.
[NENDOU]
Hey, you're back!
[SAIKI]
Let's keep this party going!
[ALL]
Yeah!
♪
[woman singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
What a pain.
My disastrous life
in the anime is over.
What? Another season?
No, no, no!
No one told me
anything about more episodes.
I'm tired of having adventures
with all these people.
Mostly.
Sometimes they're okay.
Well, that's it for now.
See you next time!