♪
[man singing in Japanese]
[TERUHASHI]
Ah, Saiki got the wrong idea!
Because I was with teen actor
Toru Moogami,
he assumed we were
dating!
I should have just come
with a non-famous hottie.
Everyone knows
I only date the best. Aah!
[MUGAMI]
What's wrong, Kokomi?
Don't scare me!
[MUGAMI] I knocked!
Why's your head
in the clouds?
It's both none of your business
and, at the same time,
all your fault,
stupid big brother!
[MUGAMI]
Huh?
Aah! Everyone, look!
Toru's on TV!
What-what-who?
Hon, don't tell me you
haven't heard of Toru Mugami!
He's the hottest,
and therefore best,
young actor today!
I love him!
So who do you like more,
him, or your husband?
That's a no-brainer! Of course
I love you more, dear!
You make silly Toru
look like a fly on dog poop!
--[KUNIHARU] Honey!
--[SAIKI] That's a little harsh.
Kurumi, I feel the same way!
Compared to you, other women
are poop on porcelain!
Honey,
I so heart you!
[SAIKI] Their metaphors
need some serious work.
[doorbell ringing]
Oh! We have a visitor.
Hey, but we're having
a moment!
Coming! Who is it?
Aah!
[Kurumi screams terrified]
No! What's wrong?
It's the poop-fly!
--[MUGAMI] Good evening.
--[KUNIHARU] Ahh!
I'm sorry to pop in
unannounced like this,
but is this Kusuo Saiki's home?
--Huh?
--[music on TV]
Huh?
[KUNIHARU]
It's the guy you like on TV!
[SAIKI]
Quiet!
You're scaring the neighbors!
--[KURUMI] Here you go.
--[MUGAMI] Thanks.
Remember how we
bumped into each other
at the movie theater?
[SAIKI] I don't wanna deal
with this guy in my home,
but it beats him
ambushing me on the street.
People assume two hotties
like us are dating,
but Kokomi is actually
my younger sister.
--You're related!
--[SAIKI] I knew this.
Toru Mugami's a stage name.
I'm actually
Makoto Teruhashi.
Anyway, Kokomi's super freaked
that Kusuo's got the
wrong idea about us,
and so I came over here
to smooth things out.
Wow. She wants Kusuo
to like her! Totally--
[SAIKI] Please stop saying
stupid things.
[KURUMI]
I haven't even started dinner!
Man, I wish our parents
were as chill as yours are.
Probably best
they leave, though...
I have one more message
to give, and it's serious.
Stay away from my sister,
you piece of filth.
I don't know if you're
crushing on her at school,
but shut it down.
She's way out of your league,
--pink-haired four-eyes.
--[SAIKI] Wow.
I all ready knew
he felt this way,
but I never thought
he'd tell me to my face.
Even I'll admit this
stings.
You're just a fly
hovering over poop.
[SAIKI] Wait. Is Teruhashi
the poop in this metaphor?
[MUGAMI] You really think
you have a chance?
[SAIKI]
I'm not thinking that.
[MUGAMI]
Since you see her every day,
and say hi to her
in the hall,
you probably think
you'll have a courtship
and then marry her,
huh?
[SAIKI] Nope.
Don't dream, pervert.
How many times
do I have to say this?
She's so pretty,
you're drawn to her
like hyenas to a rotting
zebra carcass.
[SAIKI] Now you're saying
she's rotting flesh?
Kokomi is no normal
pretty girl.
She's a masterpiece,
painted by God!
[SAIKI]
That's an exaggeration.
The only man suitable
for Kokomi is her brother.
[silence]
[SAIKI]
Did he just say that?
[MUGAMI] You're just
her loser classmate.
I've been with her
since she was born!
[SAIKI]
Because you're siblings.
That's why
I'll be the man
--to marry her!
--[SAIKI] He's a pervert.
I'll never let some
ugly nobody have her!
The only man allowed to touch
her perfect body's me!
[SAIKI] How could his parents
let him get this bad?
Oh, Kokomi!
No one else in the world
has the passion for you
that I have!
[SAIKI] Wow, obsession
doesn't even
begin to cover this.
Don't dare come
near my future wife.
Don't look at her,
don't breathe the same air,
--got it?
--[SAIKI] What a pain.
I've caught the attention
of a nut-job.
Time to send him home.
[doorbell rings]
Who is--
Oh, hello!
[SAIKI] You got a guest.
Huh?
[MUGAMI]
Kokomi?
What're you doing here?
[MUGAMI]
[SAIKI] I called her.
Huh?
[SAIKI] Your brother's
at Saiki's house! Hurry!
I talked to Teruhashi
using telepathy.
[SAIKI]
Take this perv home.
I'm here
'cause you thought
he got the wrong idea
about us.
How did you know
that bothered me?
I'm your bro.
I always know
what you're thinking.
Anyway,
you don't have to worry,
I explained it all.
[TERUHASHI]
That's so sweet. Wait!
No! If he explained it,
Saiki knows
I was worried
he got the wrong idea.
Teruhashi
was thinking about me!
I'm always here for you.
Why?
Why'd you have to stick your
nose into my personal life!
I hate you, big brother.
I hate you!
I'm never talking
to you again!
[groans]
Oh, wow...
[SAIKI]
Don't leave him here.
♪
[TEACHER]
You have 50 minutes.
No talking.
No funny business.
And I'll be watching you
the whole time!
And start!
[SAIKI]
Final exams start today.
Every student dreads it,
but to be honest,
I never lose a second
of sleep over them.
And that's because--
[BOY] The answer
to question-1 is "A." Next!
[GIRL 1]
It's totally "B," right?
[GIRL 2]
It's "A." I'm positive.
[SAIKI] I'm free to cheat
as much as I want.
With my psychic powers,
cheating is as easy
as breathing.
First off,
I can read everyone's minds.
Or, I can look through
the person in front of me
to see his answers.
If I use "thoughtography,"
I can quickly copy them,
too.
But don't get
the wrong Idea.
If I wanted to,
I could score 100
on all these tests,
without cheating.
No, I cheat
to get an average score,
to make sure I don't
stand out.
So my goal
during test day
is to mix in
plenty of wrong answers.
This way, out of a class
of 181 Students in my grade,
I'll still end up smack dab
in the middle.
The answer's "A,"
but I guess I'll say "C."
[school bell chimes]
[GIRL]
I totally bombed that one.
[BOY]
I don't even know
what it was about?
--You don't look happy.
--[SAIKI] Kaidou.
I don't wanna brag or anything,
but I totally aced it.
Mad respect, bro!
Thank you.
And did you do ok, Hairo?
If I didn't fail,
I'd be shocked.
My fault, though.
I didn't study.
[SAIKI] Just a hunch, but I bet
his score beats Kaidou's.
Guys, I didn't study
for that stupid test, either.
[SAIKI] Shocker.
I'm not surprised.
Heh! You take this stuff
too seriously, man.
Nendou, listen up.
Flunk three more tests,
and the school will be
dragging you down a grade.
Dragging!
Down?
Uh...
Don't worry. You won't have to
treat us like upperclassmen.
We'll spare you the shame.
There's still time
to improve your grades.
[SAIKI]
Yes-- And pigs will fly.
We'll save you!
What do you mean
by "dragon down"?
[SAIKI]
I rest my case.
[NENDOU]
Oh. The test thing, right?
Eh, don't worry about that.
I got a plan.
This!
With this trick pencil,
I can't lose!
[ALL]
He's toast.
And. begin!
[SAIKI]
Well, that's that.
After this term,
I'll never see him again.
'Kay, this one's "E."
[SAIKI] But even
with his pencil dice,
there's one way
he can avoid flunking.
I can use my powers
to roll it
to the right answers for him.
But do I really
wanna help someone
who won't even make
an effort?
The answers are
"E-I-E-I-O."
Like the chorus
in "Old Macdonald."
[NENDOU]
Come on, "O--" Yes!
[SAIKI] What?
He got them all right.
Hey, quiet!
[SAIKI]
What the heck's going on?
Ugh...
[TORITSUKA]
Hey. You listening?
I'm all ready stuck
on question-1!
Wait. Where'd you go?
I brought you back here
to help with my test.
[SAIKI] Now I get it.
Nendou's doing well on this test
because he's getting help
from his father's ghost.
Now I'll get
question-5.
[SAIKI]
Ghosts don't recall their lives.
How would he know
Nendou's his son,
let alone
that he needs help?
Weird. For some reason,
I feel compelled
to keep helping this kid.
[BOTH]
Out of 181 students,
Nendou ranked 90th?
You're usually
at the bottom. Explain!
I don't take it serious.
You cheated, admit it!
No, dork-face.
I used my bean.
I'm assume that means
someone hit you on the head.
Congrats, Nendou!
In my book,
beating 90 other students
makes you a national hero!
[KAIDOU]
Don't patronize him.
[HAIRO]
No, I'm being nice!
High scores don't equal
prowess on the battlefield.
[KAIDOU
I studied all night.
Hey, guy, nobody likes
a sore loser.
I didn't lost to you!
90 is a terrible--
[KAIDOU]
Oh. Sorry.
[SAIKI] Don't be.
This is the exact ranking
I was aiming for.
Mission accomplished.
[KAIDOU]
That score isn't that bad!
[SAIKI] Don't try to comfort me.
I don't need it.
The big thing we learned today
is that this trick pencil
my dad once had
really does work.
Wait, your dad left behind
that lucky pencil for you?
Yep.
[KAIDOU]
How'd you score that high
just by rolling a pencil?
Are you psychic?
[NENDOU]
Probably!
I don't see
your name on this.
It's there...
right near the bottom.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
[MAN] So down the drain.
My life is over. What a pain.
[SAIKI] The second I take off
the telepathy blocking ring,
I hear this stuff.
Peoples' thoughts
are always so exhausting.
This guy's got it
pretty bad.
Wait-- I could swear
I've heard that voice before.
[MAN]
Floating in the water.
[sobbing]
[SAIKI] Nope.
False alarm,
and I'm going home now.
--Master?
--[SAIKI] Wrong guy.
Oh, Master, I've never needed
your help and wisdom
more than I do
right now!
[SAIKI]
I said "wrong guy"!
Master! I beg of you!
Join my magic act
as my new assistant!
[MAN]
Ladies and gentlemen,
our next performer's been on
Miraculous Magic Show --
The illusionist you've all been
waiting for: Uryoku Chouno!
--Tres bien!
--[audience cheering]
[MAN]
What a response!
[SAIKI]
How's he more popular than ever?
His act seems just as terrible
as I remember!
Of course, the real question is
how did I get talked into this?
[CHOUNO]
I have a show booked tonight,
but my assistant, Michael,
got in an accident.
[SAIKI]
What? Did he die?
[CHOUNO]
Fortunately, he didn't die.
But he did say he
couldn't do tonight's show.
I asked anyone I could think of
to be my substitute assistant,
but they all said no.
When I needed them most,
my friends vanished
into thin air.
It feels like
a really bad illusion.
[SAIKI]
That's sad. I guess.
[CHOUNO] I got so desperate,
I even asked my mom.
It wound up looking
really terrible.
[SAIKI]
Don't say that about your mom.
Please, master,
can you just help me out
with tonight's show?
I'm busy.
[CHOUNO] This is the biggest
show of my life!
Please! My love,
my darling wife who left me
is coming to see it!
This is my last best chance...
to win back her love...
[sobs]
You're not listening?
[CHOUNO]
Because you're annoying.
What kind of master
are you?
[SAIKI]
When you referred to her
as your "darling wife,"
I cringed.
[CHOUNO]
How could you ignore the needy!
This is the classic
body-cutting trick.
I put all my savings
into this box.
A new one would cost
1.2 million yen,
so I bought
this used one for 1.18.
[SAIKI] You should've
bought it new.
But it came with
no instructions!
Michael and I tried
doing the trick
dozens of different ways,
but we couldn't' get it right.
[SAIKI]
Was that his accident?
[CHOUNO] Fortunately, he only
needed a couple stitches.
No, the real problem
came two days after that,
when a motorcycle hit him,
throwing him 30 meters.
[SAIKI]
Holy crap.
I still don't know
how to do this trick.
Now that the world's
abandoned me,
I have to figure out
some way to use it--
[SAIKI] There's actually nothing
to figure out here.
There are no moving pieces
or hidden compartments,
just partitions.
It's a box.
[chainsaw turns over]
[CHOUNO] I'm thinking of using
this in tonight's show
then picking a random assistant
from the audience!
[SAIKI]
No! No! No!
That's how I became
a magician's assistant.
[CHOUNO] Midori,
where are you?
No.
That's not her.
No. Ahh...!
Definitely not.
[SAIKI]
What does his ex even look like?
[CHOUNO] No, I have to focus
on my performance.
My master is helping,
and I have to impress him, too.
Now, for my next
illusion.
I'll move Saichael
from here--
[SAIKI]
"Saichael?"
[CHOUNO] --over to this box
on the other side
--of the stage!
--[audience gasps]
I'll lock both boxes
to keep "Saichael" in
and keep everyone else out.
All right, crawl inside.
[SAIKI] Okay, but I still
don't know how this works.
When I say so,
pop out of the other box.
Got it? Good!
[SAIKI] No. I do not.
[CHOUNO]
Ladies and gents, I'm closing
and locking the box.
Music, please!
[SAIKI]
Seriously? He didn't even
bother to explain it.
How am I supposed to--
Well that answers that.
Secret tunnel.
I gotta hand it to him,
this is a pretty involved trick.
This must be where I crawl
into the other box.
[creaks]
And it won't open.
I'm not surprised.
Let's open the box.
And it's tres bien time!
[SAIKI] Fine.
[audience cheers]
[MAN 1]
He just appeared out of nowhere!
[MAN 2] Yeah.
[GIRL] How'd he do that?
[CHOUNO] Master came through
for me, but how?
So far, tonight's gone
perfect!
Did she come?
Is that her?
Ahh!
Huh...?
[SAIKI] Nendou?
What are you doing here?
She's here.
You came back.
You came back for me!
Midori!
[SAIKI]
Huh...?
♪
[CHOUNO]
My named used to be
Kouta Nakanishi.
I was an office drone
for a book publisher.
About a year into the job,
I met Midori.
She worked at the café
one block over.
I still wasn't
very confident at work,
so she was the highlight
of my day.
[sighs]
Kouta, welcome!
[CHOUNO]
I went as often as I could,
until we grew close.
She would smile and listen
as I complained about my job.
Then, one day,
I realized I was in love
and wanted
to take care of her.
Her first husband had died
and she had a son at home.
Anyway, I proposed!
But then--
One month later,
they fired me!
I started drinking
and she took her son and left.
It's important
she see everything
I've accomplished
in the last two years!
That's why today's performance
means so much to me!
[SAIKI] Yeah, I get all that,
but in the end,
this Midori person,
never show up.
[NENDOU]
Cool, magic knife!
I have a magic pencil.
[SAIKI] Instead,
we got this idiot.
Riki, that's not a toy.
--[CHOUNO] Midori!
--[SAIKI] This can't be real.
It's been a while, Kou.
[SAIKI]
She's nothing like his memory!
Meet my wife.
[SAIKI] These plot twists
are giving me whiplash!
I wish the writer would stop
making stuff up on the fly.
--You look familiar.
--[SAIKI] Shoot!
The glasses are all wrong.
For a second
I thought you were Saiki,
my best buddy.
[SAIKI]
He's so reliably stupid.
Well, that's my cue
to leave.
Whoa, don't go
anywhere yet, Saichael.
We've still got
half of the show!
--[SAIKI] Just my luck.
--[CHOUNO] My sweet,
watch the rest
of my performance...
then give me
a second chance?
[SAIKI]
This is unfathomably weird.
Yes. It's a drive for me
and Riki,
so at the very least
we'll watch you.
But don't expect any more
from me than that.
It feels like our relationship
ran its course a long time ago.
[SAIKI] Why do you and Nendou
have the same face?
Master,
let's get the box ready
Presenting, my all-new
body-cutting trick!
My lovely assistant
will get inside the box,
then separate the box
into parts with a chainsaw!
Then I'll move the parts
around stage--
[SAIKI] If you explain
the whole trick
before you do it,
where's the surprise?
[MAN 1]
You think this'll really work?
[MAN 2]
It's gotta be a trick box.
[SAIKI]
It's actually not.
This box is literally
just a box.
No gimmicks.
Which, would suck for me
if I wasn't a psychic.
I've come up with 13 ways
to avoid getting chainsawed
to death.
First, I'll bend the blade
when it cuts into the box.
Then, right before
he pulls it out,
I'll turn back time on the blade
to put it back to normal.
When he moves the parts around
I'll use my super flexibility.
Are you ready, Saichael!
Let's go!
[NENDOU]
Hold on!
I wanna be your helper
and get in the box!
Try to cut me up
with whatever, I'll be fine!
Riki.
You idiot.
--Wait. No.
--[SAIKI] Sit down!
That's enough, Riki.
Let's go!
No! Midori, don't go!
[SAIKI]
And just like that,
the wheels came off.
Now what's he gonna do?
With Nendou in there,
he's likely to send
the audience home screaming.
[CHOUNO]
The blade won't touch him.
The gimmick will trigger.
My love is watching!
Don't kill her son!
[NENDOU] Hit me with
that chainsaw, bro!
Riki's my name.
Riki Nendou.
I know I look cool.
You just don't get it
'cause you're nothing
but an old grandpa.
I'm dropping out of
high school.
I gotta earn some cash
to support my mom.
I'm sorry! I can't go through
with this trick!
I violated the Code
of Stage Magic.
I wanted this trick
to be a hit so badly,
that I brought it out here
even though
I hadn't figured out yet
how to do it, safely. Sorry.
I knew they'd be mad,
but not that mad.
[SAIKI]
They full-on rioted.
But, I think you made
the right decision.
Usually, I can find
a ton of different ways out,
but this time, I only saw
four ways to save Nendou.
--What do I do now?
--[thud]
Hey, my old bank account.
[MIDORI]
It had gotten lost in my stuff.
I never spent one cent from it.
[CHOUNO] Midori!
I thought you left!
Well, that was
a really bad show.
You got the crowd
so excited
then you didn't
deliver the goods.
Is it any wonder
they rioted?
But don't worry.
When you've got
that trick down cold,
I'll come see it
again.
[CHOUNO]
Thanks for my bank account!
I promise I'll do it right
next time!
With this,
I now have the money
to buy a brand new,
1.2 million yen box!
[MIDORI]
One-point-two million?
[thud]
Ugh!
[MIDORI] On second thought,
give that back, loser!
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
Hey, we're all going to karaoke
after class, you wanna come?
--[BOY 1] Heck yeah!
--[GIRL] I want in!
[BOY 2]
Let's make it a party!
[BOY 3] Hairo! You down
for some karaoke?
Now that exams are done,
sure, bro!
--[GIRL] Yumehara, coming?
--[YUMEHARA] Sounds fun!
--[BOY 3] Uh, hey.
--[NENDOU] What?
[BOY 3]
Yoshida, are you in?
What are they
talking about?
[SAIKI]
It's better that you don't.
[GIRL]
What about you, Mera?
Yeah, I have plans later,
sorry.
[GIRL]
Interesting. Is it a date?
[MERA]
Maybe. Something like that.
[BOYS]
Oh, wow! Teruhashi!
What's up, guys.
[BOY 3]
Wanna come to karaoke?
[BOY 1]
Most of the class is going.
Us and the other guys
over there.
[TERUHASHI] Doesn't look like
Saiki's coming, so, no.
I'm sorry, I can't. I have
a koto lesson after school.
--[BOY 3] Okay.
--[BOY 1] Let's call it off.
[SAIKI]
Wow, that sure killed the mood.
This is Café Mami.
It's quiet,
out of the way,
and very relaxing,
which makes me a regular.
Most importantly,
they serve great coffee jelly.
Since this is a coffee shop,
it puts the store bought
ones to shame.
It is one of life's
great pleasures.
Unfortunately,
I may have to stop coming here.
[MERA]
Sorry, to keep you waiting.
Ahh! Saiki?
[clatter]
[SAIKI] What a waste.
And it was such good coffee.
At least I was able
to catch my coffee jelly.
Why not, she'd just
have to throw it away.
Sorry! I'll clean up
and get you another one,
just hold on--
Hey, where's the jelly?
[SAIKI]
No idea.
I'm sorry.
I can be a bit of a klutz.
[SAIKI]
No complaints here.
[MERA]
Here's an extra, free of charge.
[SAIKI]
Are you a god?
Um, by the way,
Saiki?
[SAIKI] Mera Chisato, I know why
you panicked when you saw me.
I'm begging!
Please don't tell anyone
that I've got a part-time job
as a waitress!
If the school finds out,
they'll make me quit.
[SAIKI]
Student jobs are forbidden.
[MERA] Not just this job,
but my morning paper
milk-delivery routes,
my night job
at the gas station,
and the restaurant.
Not to mention my gigs
as a baby-sitter, tutor,
and flower arranger!
[SAIKI]
Making her quit seems humane.
To be honest,
my family's poor.
[SAIKI] I think everyone
all ready knew that.
Her lunch is always just rice
with a pickled plum.
Her gym clothes have
someone else's name on them.
And, if you look closely,
her glasses are missing a lens!
And right now,
she's literally drooling
over my coffee jelly.
Oh, it's fine.
You can go ahead and eat.
[SAIKI] You're hard to ignore.
Besides, your drool ruined it.
Mm!
Saiki, it's so good!
I feel like I owe you my life.
All I've had to eat since
yesterday morning is ice!
[SAIKI] If coffee jelly's the
price of survival, so be it.
I'm supporting everyone!
So that's why you can't blab
about me working.
Is that okay?
Ugh! Three-second-rule!
[SAIKI] Okay. I promise
not to tell anyone.
[MERA]
Thank you, Saiki!
[SAIKI] Keeping her secret
benefits me, too.
It means I get
to keep coming here.
[door opens]
--[MERA] Welcome!
--[SAIKI] Huh?
Wait.
[Mera groaning]
[MERA]
Mister Matsuzaki?
Young lady,
are you working here?
[SAIKI] It is him.
Sorry, I don't think
there's anything
I can do to help you.
Don't take it personally.
Are you working here,
yes or no?
[MERA] N-no.
[MATSUZAKI]
You know the rules.
No matter how good
your reason--
[MERA] If they won't let
me help my family,
I'll have to quit
school!
Nothing to worry
about, Mera.
You're working hard,
huh?
Thank you so much,
sir!
[MATSUZAKI] Well, I'd
like to order a parfait.
[MERA]
Coming right up!
[SAIKI] Well, I said I'd keep
my mind control powers sealed,
but I guess I made
another change in the world.
Not a big one, though.
Hopefully it won't affect
too much.
[PEOPLE]
PK Academy students
are now allowed
to have after-school jobs.
[SAIKI] Consider this thanks
for the coffee jelly.
Hey, we're all going to karaoke
after class, you wanna come?
Now that exams are done,
sure, bro!
Sounds like fun!
What.
[BOY]
Hey Mera, are you in?
Thanks, but I have work
after school.
Instead of karaoke,
how 'bout we all go
to your work
to keep you company?
[MERA]
That'd be great!
[BOY 1] We're going
to Mera's work.
Do you wanna come?
Well. Today, I might be.
Saiki's not going, is he?
[BOY 2] Saiki says
he wants to come!
Aah! Saiki? Yeah, sure!
I'm in, let's go!
--[BOY 1] Really?
--[BOY 2] Suh-weet!
Oh, hey, what's going on?
We finally gonna get together
after school and hang?
[BOY]
Nendou wants to come?
[GIRL]
Let's just cancel.
[SAIKI]
Wow, that sure killed the mood.
♪
[woman singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
We introduced so many
new characters this episode.
I'm exhausted.
I think I'll unwind with--
Surprise!
--a coffee jelly!
Next time, on
The Disastrous Life of Saiki K:
Hoo, boy. I just foresaw
what'll happen.
What a pain.