♪
[man singing in Japanese]
[indistinct chatter]
[SAIKI]
Four o'clock.
If I leave now,
I'll be home with time to spare.
Which is good,
because there's a TV show
I absolutely cannot miss
airing at 5.
[TV ANNOUNCER]
Healthy Warriors. Specializer.
[SAIKI] Don't think anime
is just for kids.
This is mature animation
for a discriminating viewer
like myself.
Uh-oh. Kaidou's up ahead.
Better double back.
I can't find Saiki anywhere.
Huh.
I found a really cool
abandoned building
that I've turned into
my Jet Black Wings lair.
He'll love seeing what I've done
with the place.
My own hideout.
I mean, a super-secret base.
[SAIKI]
I'd rather not.
Saiki, where are you, bro?
Since he helped me
the other day,
I thought I'd repay
the favor
by inviting him
to the gym.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Muscle.
[HAIRO]
We can spot each other.
[SAIKI]
Yeah, pass.
If you wanna repay my favor,
Hairo,
you can start
by leaving me alone.
[TERUHASHI]
Where is Kunio Saiki?
It's not like I really care
about him or anything,
but the teacher said that I had
to bring him this form.
Although it could be fun
to ask him out to tea,
just to watch him get
all nervous and flip out.
He won't be able to think
I'm an illusion if I corner him.
[SAIKI]
Yeah, whatever.
Why is today's episode
so important?
Because it's
the season finale--
Hey, buddy! Wanna go get some
ramen with your best friend?
[SAIKI]
Leave me alone.
Huh? Hm?
♪
[SAIKI]
I'm trapped at school.
Every route's blocked by someone
I want nothing to do with.
I could teleport,
but then I wouldn't get to stop
at the locker and take off
my school shoes.
Hm. Well, I only need
30 minutes
to get home.
I'll wait them out.
No one is leaving.
Hairo's at the front gate.
[HAIRO] I won't leave
till I get to thank him.
[SAIKI]
Kaidou's at the shoe locker.
When Saiki's taking off
his shoes,
I'll jump out and scare him
as a test of his reflexes.
[SAIKI]
As for her.
Excuse me.
Hm?
Oh, wow! Hey, Teruhashi.
Can you please help me
find Saiki?
I've been looking,
but there's just
too much ground to cover
for a girl like me.
[TAKAHASHI]
Yes, yes, of course I'll help!
[SAIKI] Teruhashi and her
worker drones are everywhere.
Now I'm really screwed.
Leaving is suddenly
near impossible.
If you're wondering why
I don't record this show,
it's because the moment
it's over,
spoilers will flood into my head
from people who have seen it.
[MAN 1]
Who knew it was a dream?
[WOMAN 1] I called
that guy dying.
[MAN 2] Too many montages.
[SAIKI] It can't be helped.
My only choice
is to become invisible.
This only makes it
so people can't see me.
I'm still here, physically,
able to interact with things.
But there are some
pretty big drawbacks.
I can only do it
for 10 minutes,
and if anyone touches
me while I'm like this,
I'll become visible
immediately.
I've got to handle this
carefully.
[toilet flushes]
Ah, that hit the spot.
Better get back
to finding my buddy.
[SAIKI]
Ah. That was almost game over.
But knowing Nendou's location
is a big help.
His unpredictability is the
biggest threat to this power.
Now I just go in the other
direction and lay low.
Ugh, where in the hell
is that damn Saiki?
[SAIKI]
Right here.
For the sake of everyone
watching at home,
I'll make myself
visible to you.
How cute, the locker where
Kaidou's been hiding.
[Kaidou screams]
What's wrong, Kaidou?
[KAIDOU] Ghost just lifted up
the locker I was hiding in.
No, wait. It wasn't a ghost,
it was Dark Reunion.
[TERUHASHI] Slow down, nothing
you're saying makes sense.
[SAIKI]
Now's my chance.
Hold on, I'll save you!
What happened?
I heard a scream.
It's Dark Reunion.
They found my hiding spot.
Oh. Okay. Yeah.
Oh, of course.
[SAIKI]
Nendou's on the other side
of the building,
and the rest are right here.
Now to just
switch my shoes and--
[TORITSUKA]
Finally heading home, Saiki?
I'll walk with you, pal.
[SAIKI]
You idiot.
[ALL]
Ah! There he is!
Uh...
Saiki, I need to repay
your favor.
Our teacher asked me
to give these to you.
I have a lair now.
[ALL]
You're not busy, are you?
Uh...
Ah, Teruhashi.
[SAIKI]
So it's not just ghosts.
He can see anything
invisible.
[TAKAHASHI]
Saiki? Hello?
♪
[SAIKI]
Sports Day.
[HAIRO] Listen up, guys.
Today's about one thing:
us being number one!
[ALL] Let's do it!
[SAIKI] I was all set to skip
school today, but...
But you can't miss
Sports Day.
Yeah, I bought a camcorder
just for the occasion.
[SAIKI]
...they guilted me into coming.
That's right, look over
this way. Just like that.
Oh, crap, the battery died.
[KURUMI] Oh, no.
[SAIKI] Go home.
Class three, go!
[SAIKI] Boy, those "yeahs"
are getting annoying.
Sports Day is so stupid. Heh.
My skills are best used...
[SAIKI]
Hey, for the first time ever,
Kaidou and I
agree on something.
You're just saying that
'cause you suck at sports.
[KAIDOU] Shut up!
[SAIKI] Wow, Nendou's headband
seems completely at home.
Oh, right, it looks exactly
like the grooves in his hair.
Yo, Saiki, hey.
[SAIKI] Oh, great.
You pumped?
[SAIKI] The opposite of pumped.
[HAIRO]
And Nendou, you're a fit guy.
I expect big things
out there from you too.
That's right.
You're not beating me this time.
[SAIKI]
We're all on the same team.
[HAIRO]
And Kaidou, my man.
Just do whatever it is
you can do.
I'm sure you're gonna try
really hard.
[KAIDOU] What's that mean?
[HAIRO] Don't fight with me.
Fight with our competition.
They look tough this year.
First, Class One.
[SAIKI] Their symbol's a circle.
[HAIRO] Every student in this
class is an intellectual.
That's right!
[ALL] Yeah!
[HAIRO] Class 2...
[SAIKI] Their symbol's a plus.
[HAIRO] Everyone in this class
is an athlete.
[OOSHIMA] Class Two's gonna
curb-stomp you.
[HAIRO] Class Four.
[SAIKI] Their symbol's a square.
[HAIRO] More intellectuals,
led by Tanihara,
who aced his midterms.
We compete for
immortal glory.
[SAIKI]
They'd rather be reading.
[HAIRO] Class Five.
[SAIKI] They got the star.
[HAIRO] Intellectuals
who wear glasses.
They match
our hair and face types.
[SAIKI] Is "intellectual"
your word of the day?
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Our first event:
boys' hundred-meter dash.
[SAIKI]
Great. I'm gonna have to run.
Make them eat your dust, Kuu.
I'm recording you, son,
to a tape called "my heart."
You can do it, Saiki.
Win it for Class Three.
[SAIKI]
I don't care about winning,
because I don't want
to draw attention to myself.
I'm in second place right now.
That's a little too conspicuous.
I'll just fall back
into the pack.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
That's the finish line.
[SAIKI] Perfect.
Saiki. Holy crap, dude,
you got third.
[SAIKI]
Why is everyone so excited?
All the other racers are on
the track-and-field team.
The fourth-place guy
has a school sprint record.
[BOY] You should join track.
[SAIKI] I wish I knew before.
Not bad, though I'm certain
I could smoke you one-on-one.
Wait, that guy's running?
[SAIKI] Kaidou's up next?
[MAN] On your marks.
[KAIDOU] I am the wind.
I am the gale!
[laughs]
You need to go back
to running school.
We wound up tying
for fifth place.
We gotta get a win on the board
in the next event.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
...Three-legged race.
Ooh, it's time for me
to go to work.
[SAIKI] No, it's not.
[SAWAKITA] I'm up.
I'm running in the three-legged
race, not you.
[SAIKI] And who are you?
[SAWAKITA] My name is Sawakita.
But you don't have
to bother remembering it.
I'm just here to play
a supporting role.
[SAIKI]
Now he's narrating?
[SAWAKITA]
From my grades to my looks,
everything about me
is average.
I was born average.
But then, winning a single
rock-paper-scissors game
brought a ray of hope
into my life.
I'm running the three-legged
race with Teruhashi.
It's a memory I can cherish
for the rest of my average life.
[SAIKI]
You're especially dramatic.
Try your best, Sawakita.
From grades to looks,
everything about me is average.
But winning a single
rock-paper-scissors game
brought a ray of hope
into my life.
I'm running the race
with Teruhashi.
It's a memory I can cherish for
the rest of my life.
I bet that's what he's thinking.
[SAIKI] Amazing.
She got it.
Certain you're not psychic?
[TERUHASHI] I hope he's not
so focused on me he loses.
Let's win this together.
[SAWAKITA] Yes.
[TERUHASHI] As sweet as I am,
I'm also very competitive.
If we win this,
we should celebrate.
Alone. Together.
[MAN]
On your marks. Set.
[screams]
[BOY] Hey, this was supposed
to be the three-legged race.
[SAIKI] I'm so honored to have
witnessed your cherished memory.
Yeah. Let's keep that momentum
going, guys.
A scavenger hunt race?
I wonder which one of us
is gonna do that.
[SAIKI] You are.
Oh, yeah, it's my turn.
Come on, Nendou.
[KAIDOU] Lose, lose, lose.
[NENDOU]
Nendou is hot out of the gates.
He's coming home.
[SAIKI]
You didn't win yet, Nendou.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] Now go find
what's on that paper.
That's right. Ah...
All right,
he's figured it out.
Must be over here.
[NENDOU] Here, let me have this.
Yeah, sure.
No, not the racket. This.
Thanks.
[all gasp]
[ALL]
Saiki!
[man sings in Japanese]
♪
[KAIDOU]
Saiki, wake up.
Kaidou, what happened?
I don't know.
He just fell over.
Wake up, Saiki.
[HAIRO]
No, wait, don't move him.
[both gasp]
--[HAIRO] Saiki?
--[KAIDOU] Saiki!.
[NENDOU]
Oh, my bad.
[KAIDOU] There's something
wrong with his face.
[WASA CREWMAN]
Status report, ISS.
We're in trouble. The main power
system suddenly went down.
I've never seen anything
like this happen before.
[WASA CREWMAN] What?
[MAN] Oh, no. Oh, my God!
[alarm blares]
No. It can't be.
Get me the President
of the United States now.
[TRIBE CHIEF]
What do you mean, elder?
I have had a vision
of the future,
and the world will soon
come to an end.
Are you feeling okay?
We were worried.
You fainted when Nendou took
that thing out of your head,
so I tried to put it back.
[SAIKI]
He pulled out my antenna?
[WASA CREWMAN]
Is it back?
The power came back
when I smacked the generator.
[WASA CREWMAN]
Did what?
Now all of our readings
are normal.
[MAN] Director,
the president's on the line.
Whoops. Sorry, kids.
False alarm.
[BOTH]
What?
[sighs]
[SAIKI] Since the antenna
was only out for a bit,
the doomsday scenario
didn't happen.
--I almost lost my buddy.
--[SAIKI] The real bad news
is that Nendou's the one
who did it.
That makes him a danger.
I'll have to eliminate him.
Nothing I could have done
about that one, guys.
I mean, when your best buddy
passes out,
there are more important
things than Sports Day.
We'll get the next one.
[TAKAHASHI] He passed out
because of you!
[MALE ANNOUNCER] And that's
the end of our morning events.
Well, pal, sounds like
it's time for food.
Hey, where'd Saiki go?
Saiki?
Where are you?
Tres bien!
[SAIKI]
I'm not feeling so hot.
It doesn't matter if it was
only out for a second,
it's causing me
all sorts of problems.
The antenna Nendou removed
is a kind of control device.
The psychic superpowers
I was born with
have only gotten stronger
as I've grown older.
By fifth grade, I could already
lift a high-rise with my mind.
I probably could've blown up
the moon if I wanted to,
but all that psychic power
is that much harder to control.
Blowing up the house in my sleep
is a best-case scenario.
What's most worrisome
is my mind-control power.
I could accidentally destroy
the world with a single thought.
It would make explosions
seem like a day at the beach.
So to restrain those powers,
I wear these on my head.
But it can only restrain
my ability, not stop it.
Underneath, it's always
growing in strength.
Once these antennae come off,
I have no idea what will happen.
My body's not
listening to me.
At this rate,
I could really hurt someone
if I keep participating
in Sports Day.
I've got to go home.
[NENDOU] Saiki!
You playing hide-and-seek?
[SAIKI] Crap.
Well, that's my cue. Teleport.
Hello? Huh?
Doing some private
stretching?
[SAIKI]
It's not working.
My powers are messed up.
[NENDOU]
Hey, you all right?
Maybe you should
go home early.
[SAIKI]
That might be my opening.
Sorry to hear you're sick.
You need help getting home?
[GIRL] How are you feeling?
[BOY] Drink lots of liquids.
Yeah, we're gonna win the
afternoon events in your honor.
[SAIKI]
Don't say that.
[HAIRO]
No way we're losing now.
--Let's win it all for Saiki.
--[ALL] Yeah!
[HAIRO] Never forget
what he did for us!
[SAIKI]
Now I can't leave.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] Let's hear it
for the Amazing Chouno.
No one watched us today.
We've been on a losing streak
ever since that TV special.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] ...tug-of-war.
All right, guys and gals,
these are the team events.
While we may be
at the bottom...
[SAIKI] He didn't do any
individual events, did he?
...that's about to change!
Pull, pull, pull!
Clench your teeth
and pull that rope!
Squat and lean back!
[SAIKI]
Stop talking and pull.
I don't even like gym
when I'm healthy,
and now I've got to do
a tug-of-war like this?
Oh.
[TAKAHASHI]
It suddenly got light.
--[SAIKI] Gotta stall.
--[TAKAHASHI] Whoa!
Now it's heavy again!
[SAIKI]
Why did it snap so easily?
Oh, well, I bet I can fix it
before anyone notices.
All right, this shouldn't
be too hard.
Oh, crap, again?
The friction tore my gloves.
I don't know what'll happen if I
use psychometry now.
[all yelling]
Oops.
[bodies crashing]
[JUDGE]
Uh...Class Three wins.
All right, we won!
[people cheer]
[SAIKI] I knew I should have
skipped school today.
Sports Day is the worst.
♪
[BOY]
Class Three is crazy.
We're not crazy, we're just
the kings of Sports Day.
Battling real people's
kind of fun.
I don't remember
eating lunch.
It's torn where I was
holding it? Am I that strong?
[BOY] I've never seen them
so cocky.
[SAIKI] They're not cocky
so much as stupid.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
After tug-of-war,
Class Three moves up
to fourth place.
[SAIKI]
Still two more events.
Even if you did, you would still
be doing terribly.
Class Two is gonna beat you
hands down.
[SAIKI]
Eh, couldn't care less.
Hey, you respect us
for being number one!
[SAIKI]
Again, I don't care.
I came in last
in the race,
but it was worth it.
[SAIKI] I can't believe
you're bragging
about how that went down.
Just don't hold a grudge
when we win.
[SAIKI] For the last time,
I don't care about who wins.
Sorry, groper,
but Class Three's winning this.
In fact, if we lose to you,
I'll buzz-cut my hair.
--There's no way.
--[HAIRO] Yes, way.
That's how much I believe in us.
[SAIKI] Please don't.
[BOY] Yeah, if we lose....
--[ALL] We'll get a buzz cut.
--[SAIKI] Slow down.
You can count me in too.
There's no way
I'll let us lose.
[SAIKI] Where are you getting
this confidence?
I want in on this
buzz cut bet too.
[SAIKI] In your case,
a buzz cut's an improvement.
I know what's next.
We all share in the glory,
or every guy in Class Three
will get a buzz cut!
[SAIKI]
We are gonna look so dumb.
[ANNOUNCER]
Now for the beanbag toss.
[SAIKI]
If we're gonna turn it around,
it's gotta be at this event--
Our comeback starts now!
[MALE ANNOUNCER] All the classes
are tossing bags.
There's a time limit.
Hold them all at once.
You're not getting anywhere
near the hoop.
[SAIKI] I'll stop the beanbags
right above the basket
for a split-second
and drop them.
He is still throwing them,
and the rulebook says nothing
about using psychic powers.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
All right, that's time.
Class One, 33 beanbags.
Class Two, 28.
[BOY]
We're still winning overall.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Class Three...
[ALL]
We tripled them!
[SAIKI]
I might've overdone it.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Class Four has 100.
It's not that difficult
if you use your head. Just look.
[HAIRO]
What the hell is that?
[TANIHARA]
Well, what does it look like?
Everyone in Class Four put all
his bags in one larger bag.
That way, we threw a hundred
in the basket with one toss.
[SAIKI] Wow. That's not smart,
that's just cheating.
Now, now, guys,
don't go using the C-word.
The rules say nothing about
putting all your beanbags
--in one big bag.
--[SAIKI] Well, they should.
But there's still
one last event.
The inter-class relay race.
And whichever team wins this one
will get a whopping 500 points
added to their overall
total score.
Saiki, I want you
running the anchor leg.
[SAIKI] If I say no, things will
only get more difficult.
I'll just finish third again,
like I did in the first race.
On your marks.
Set.
--[starter pistol fires]
--[HAIRO] Go, Kaidou!
[KAIDOU]
I am not gonna lose.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] Class Three
has already fallen behind.
They're the last
to pass...
[KAIDOU]
I tried.
[TAKAHASHI] Thanks for nothing.
Looks like it's time for
Takahashi to take the lead.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] And again,
Class Three's the last
to pass the baton.
But Nendou's unusual stride
is closing the gap.
Class Three is winning the leg.
[SAIKI] He's even creepier
at high speed.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] Running
the next leg is Teruhashi,
the running goddess.
[TERUHASHI]
That's right, boys.
I can run fast too.
After all, I'm the perfect,
pretty girl.
[NARRATOR] And so, Class Three
maintains their lead,
finally passing the baton
to Hairo,
their last runner
before Saiki.
[HAIRO] Great work, guys.
Now to just get this to Saiki.
What are you doing?
Not a good time for this!
[SAIKI] I knew he'd show it
at some point.
At least it won't look
suspicious when I finish last.
We're totally gonna win now
Nothing wrong with tripping
someone, if no one sees you.
[SAIKI] Well, now that
changes everything.
You should have kept quiet.
Sorry! I fell!
[SAIKI]
It's not your fault, it's his.
[all gasp]
--Payback time.
--[BOY 1] What the heck?
[BOY 2] This guy's flying.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Class Three has once again
come back from
last place to first.
[SAIKI] I hate the attention,
but this way,
I at least avoid
getting a buzz cut-- Uh!
[SAIKI] Oh, right. I'm having
trouble controlling my body.
[NARRATOR]
And so, the next morning.
[SAIKI] My name is Kusuo Saiki.
I have psychic superpowers.
--Looking good, buddy.
--[SAIKI] Shut up, Hairo.
--[KAIDOU] Hey, Saiki...
--[SAIKI] Boy, you went all out.
What's going on with your hair?
It looks so weird.
[SAIKI]
We have the same cut.
[HAIRO] What's up?
Where are your buzz cuts?
We only had to do it
if we lost to Class Two,
and we beat them, right?
[ALL]
Oh, wow.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
[HAIRO]
All right, everyone, listen up.
Today we're doing
a safety drill.
[SAIKI]
Safety drill? Okay.
I don't need a drill.
I'll be fine.
Nendou, you need
to take this seriously.
Imagine this room's on fire.
White-hot flames
are everywhere.
The smoke makes it impossible
to see, let alone breathe.
So what then?
You got an escape plan?
How will you know
what decision to make
if you don't participate
in this drill?
Preparation is the key
to survival!
[SAIKI] You're as hot
and smothering as a fire.
So when the alarm goes off,
follow my lead
and evacuate to the courtyard.
[ALL] Okay.
[HAIRO] Here's an easy
way to remember
the correct procedure
in any emergency.
What's "SOS"?
[SAIKI] If I remember correctly
from grade school, it means
"Slow," "Orderly," and "Silent."
I know what that stands for.
"Save Our Selves." SOS.
[SAIKI]
That's terrible.
Yeah, that's the plan,
but it doesn't mean that.
If it's not that, how about,
"Someone. Over here. Save Me."
[SAIKI]
You're on your own, pal.
heh, heh. Each of your guesses
is dumber than the last one.
[NENDOU] All right, do you know
what it means, smart guy?
Of course I do.
It stands for
"Scorching
Oblivion
Smackdown."
Hey, I'm joking.
It stands for "Slow,"
"Orderly," and "Silent," right?
Yeah, you got it.
Now, everyone just remember
those simple rules
and we'll ace this drill.
[alarm bell rings]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] First-floor
science lab is on fire.
That alarm always makes me
nervous.
[SAIKI]
We should pay attention.
Stay calm, everyone.
Open your bag and get
your safety hoods.
Stand in line
after that
in order of
student number.
[BOY 1] Where's my hood?
[BOY 2] Is this it?
Oh, crap. I'm pretty sure
I left my hood at home.
Seriously? If this was
an actual fire,
obviously you'd be
smoldering ashes!
[SAIKI] Don't be dramatic.
I can't find
my safety hood, either.
What? Oh, come on,
not you too.
Use my hood, Teruhashi.
If I take all of yours,
then you'll die.
She's right.
This is not a safe plan.
Sacrifice...
Ourselves
to...
Save her.
Oh. Okay.
[TERUHASHI] Saying nary a word.
Offering theirs to me.
Slaves of love.
[HAIRO]
Okay, let's move out.
Hold on.
I forgot my phone.
Stop, Takahashi.
Out of line
is too dangerous.
Stay in place.
[SAIKI]
Everyone's trying way too hard
with these SOS abbreviations
now. It's all I'm hearing.
Stop it, guys. Obviously, it's
not the time for stupid fights.
[SAIKI]
See? They're everywhere.
[gasps]
Chiyo, hi.
Hey, wait.
[YUMEHARA] Splitting up with
a guy in the same school
is overwhelmingly awkward
and tough.
[SAIKI] This doesn't have
to do with the drill.
[TAKERU]
The ex-girlfriend
I can't forget.
She's oblivious
to my suffering.
[SAIKI] Why are
you doing this?
[HAIRO]
Okay, gang, we're almost out.
Stop! Stop, everyone!
Our path
leading out,
shuttered before us!
[BOY 1] Seriously?
[GIRL 1] Oh, come on.
[BOY 2]
Screw it, we'd be dead.
[NENDOU]
That's weird.
Now we're completely trapped.
I guess someone closed it
by mistake.
[SAIKI] No. This route has been
closed with good reason.
The science room
is directly in our path.
Remember the intercom
announcement from earlier?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] First-floor
science lab is on fire.
[SAIKI] In this drill,
the lab is on fire.
If this was real life,
the hallway would be impassable.
They're testing to see
how well we paid attention
and if we made the safer choice
of going down the back stairs,
which we didn't.
Stay calm. Obviously, there's
a solution to get outside.
Yes, that's it. I understand
why they locked us in.
[SAIKI]
Well, better late than never.
They're testing
our physical strength.
Yeah, that's the only
explanation.
We don't have
to send out an SOS
if we can overcome obstacles
by ourselves.
Which means to get out,
we must break down that shutter.
[SAIKI] This is a fire drill,
not a movie.
All right!
Let's break it down, boys!
[yells]
Bash it with whatever!
[SAIKI] In a real fire,
they'd be the first to die.
[MATSUZAKI]
So you wrenched open
a metal shutter and ran out
the front door?
I see. Why would you animals
break our new shutter?
We literally installed it
last week, losers!
What are you
gonna do?
Obviously
you're idiots!
Shutters are
expensive to fix!
[SAIKI]
I tried to warn them.
Well, not directly, but still.
Anyway, this school doesn't
actually even need
to bother with
emergency drills.
After all...
[MAN]
Life sucks.
♪
[fingers snap]
[SAIKI]
So long as I'm here,
ordeals like fires
simply won't happen.
[MATSUZAKI]
As punishment,
you're all getting
buzz cuts.
♪
[woman singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
You might not realize it,
but I've been talking
this whole time.
I actually just send my words
directly into people's brains.
The end result is the same
as normal communication.
Next time, in
The Disastrous Life of Saiki K,
a 3000 yen coffee jelly?