♪
[man singing in Japanese]
[gasps]
[SAIKI] Oh, no. I already regret
getting that kid's balloon.
[giggles]
Hey, mister, are you
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2?
Because I think you are.
[SAIKI]
Sorry, but I am not
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2.
[YUUTA]
Your secret's safe with me,
Cyborg Cider-man Number Two.
[SAIKI]
Wrong. I'm not a cyborg,
a Cider-man, or a Number 2,
or any other number.
But I just saw you do the
Soda Jump to save my balloon.
It's too late
to try to hide it now.
[SAIKI] I'm not a superhero.
I'm a high school student.
Can I have your autograph?
Here.
[gasps]
[SAIKI]
I don't have time for this.
[wailing]
[YUUTA]
Whoa! Thank you!
I'll never wash this bag
again.
[SAIKI]
He can't be more than 5.
Where's his mom? Is he lost?
So can you please do
the Soda Jump again?
[SAIKI] I can't believe
this is a real hero.
Is there
a Cyborg Cider-man Number 1?
I always drink Energy Cider
to support you.
[SAIKI] His entire comic's
just an ad for some gross drink.
So it's just sleazy marketing
tactics to rip off kids.
[YUUTA]
Come on. Do the Soda Jump.
The carbonation from the soda
shooting out of the bottom
of your feet
is what makes you jump
so high in the air, right?
[SAIKI]
That's a lot of carbonation.
[YUUTA]
Jump! Do it! Do it!
[grunting]
Whoa!
[SAIKI]
Idiot. Psychokinesis.
[MAN]
Whoa! What?
That was close.
That was the Soda Air Cannon.
The Soda Air Cannon is real!
I know that move.
It's like you use
the amazing power of carbonation
from the soda out of your hands
to blow away your enemies.
[SAIKI] Soda shoots
out of his hands and feet?
That's not a great power
for a cyborg.
We're raising
a generation of kids
with unrealistic
soda expectations.
[YUUTA] I know everything
there is to know about soda
and Cyborg Cider-man
Number 2.
[SAIKI] Have they even replaced
his blood with soda?
I know you're Cyborg Cider-man
Number 2. I'm sure of it.
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2,
I love you so much!
[SAIKI]
Does he really need to say
that stupid full name
every time?
It's so annoying.
Good motivation to find
the kid's parents ASAP,
though.
Hey, a policeman.
That was easy.
This little boy lost?
[Yuuta laughing]
Suspicious.
Why does this kid
love this teen so much?
[SAIKI] Isn't that better
than the opposite?
[OFFICER] Thirteen years on the
job and my gut says this is bad.
[SAIKI] Find a new job.
Anyway, the kid's all yours.
I'm out of here.
All right, son, are you friends
with that big kid?
Yes, sir. He's a superhero
with a secret identity.
You should've seen him
shoot a car.
Hey hold it right there!
Where'd the policeman go?
[SAIKI]
Oh, just a little
soda-infused
obstruction of justice.
This kid's parents
could be anywhere.
My telepathy hasn't picked up
their voices,
so they're outside
my 200-meter radius.
[exhales audibly]
Question.
Is your archenemy
Baron Cola really strong?
[SAIKI]
Yeah, he's strong.
You'd think being lost
would scare this kid.
[YUUTA] It's getting dark,
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2,
so it's time to go home.
Right, Mommy?
Hmm. What?
My mommy's gone and I'm scared!
[SAIKI] You just realized this?
[wails]
Somebody help me!
My mommy got lost!
[SAIKI]
No, you got lost.
I thought she was right
behind me all this time,
but it turns out
it was just a balloon.
[SAIKI] Are 5-year-olds
always this stupid?
Oh, Cyborg Cider-man
Number 2,
please go find my mommy
for me.
[SAIKI]
I don't think I have a choice.
What do you want? What--?
[SAIKI]
Get on. I'll do the Soda Jump.
Whoa! I'm flying
with a superhero! Best day ever!
[SAIKI] Quiet down,
you'll draw attention.
[YUUTA]
Mommy!
Oh, Yuuta.
Where have you been?
I was about to call the police.
Heh. Don't worry, Mommy.
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2
rescued me,
and then we flew here.
Right?
[Yuuta gasps]
[MOM] Honey, I don't see anyone.
I think this hero
was in your imagination.
[SAIKI] Cyborg Cider-man
Number Two's fate
is to remain hidden
in the shadows.
[YUUTA]
I did, I really met him.
I even got his autogra--
It's gone.
[SAIKI] Forget this happened.
It was all a dream.
[MOM] I'll chalk all this up
to you being stressed out
over moving into the new house.
[gate squeaks]
Oh, hello there, neighbor.
We're the Iridatsu Family.
We just moved in next door
today.
Aah!
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2.
It's him. I told you, Mom.
I told you he's real.
[SAIKI]
He's my new neighbor?
♪
[KUNIHARA]
Aah! Look at the time!
I just woke up
and I'm already late for work.
How did this happen?
[SAIKI] Summer vacation's here,
but now I have to wake up
to this guy every day.
Aah! Help me out, Dr. Kuu.
Make that blue box
that teleports me to--
[SAIKI]
Not a chance.
No, Kusuo,
don't make me beg you.
[screaming]
[SAIKI] You're being
too dramatic.
Don't use me,
use your own two feet.
Take me and I'll bring you back
a coffee jelly when I come home.
[SAIKI] We're here.
[KUNIHARA] What?
We're already on the roof
of my office?
Thank you, Kusuo.
Now my boss'll slap me just
four times instead of five.
[SAIKI]
That's practically the same.
Since you're here, why
don't you check out the office?
[SAIKI] Yeah, I don't even know
what you do.
You switch jobs so often,
it's hard to keep straight.
You clean shoes or something?
[KUNIHARU] I work for
a publishing company
called Shuensha.
[SAIKI]
Shueisha? They're huge.
One of the leading publishers
in Japan,
and a magnet for the best
and brightest in the industry.
No, you misheard me.
Not Shueisha. Shuensha.
[SAIKI]
Shuensha?
You're not the first person
to mix us up.
It's a real problem.
[SAIKI] Seems intentional
more than anything.
They're written
totally different. Look. Huh?
[SAIKI]
You know shuen means death?
You might be excited to learn
that your old man's job
is to edit manga.
[SAIKI] Manga?
[KUNIHARA] Here.
Editorial department
for The Weekly Shonen Cognac.
[SAIKI] Come again?
What's with the blank stare?
Don't tell me
you've never heard
of Weekly Shonen Cognac manga.
[SAIKI] Never heard of it.
Jump Magazine, Sunday
Champion, and Cognac, right?
[SAIKI]
I know those first four.
[Kuniharu whimpers]
[ONIMATSU] About time.
[yelps]
Did you get here late because
you like getting slapped?
[whimpering]
[ONIMATSU] Who's that?
This is my boy, Kusuo.
Huge fan of the magazine,
collects the whole run.
For weeks he's been begging me
to bring him by
so he can meet
the great chief editor.
Well, I never wanna disappoint
a fan.
I'm Onimatsu,
the great chief editor.
You're addicted to Cognac.
[SAIKI] Dad just wanted me
as cover to get his boss
off his back.
[ONIMATSU]
Give your boy the full tour.
Just make sure
you get your work done.
[door closes]
All right, thanks to you,
I got off with no slaps
at all.
One coffee jelly
isn't enough for this.
[KUNIHARU] This is where
the magic gets edited.
[SAIKI]
This place looks pretty sad.
Seeing how manga
gets made could be interesting.
[EDITOR] How much longer
do you expect me to wait?
A deadline isn't a suggestion!
What? More time?
[KUNIHARU]
Being a writer
can be difficult
and time-consuming.
So every morning, we editors
call them up to check in,
chat, and offer
friendly encouragement.
I will beat this script
out of you, if I have to.
[SAIKI]
A lovely group of men.
Check out
our most recent issue.
You at least recognize
the logo, right?
[SAIKI] No.
[KUNIHARU] Here.
You don't want it?
But this is our top character,
The Ever Optimistic
Santarou.
In fact, every issue's loaded
with great manga.
[SAIKI] The editors
need to edit the titles.
[KUNIHARU]
They're good. Read it.
You won't even open it?
[EDITOR]
Mr. Saiki, you got a visitor.
I almost forgot.
I'm scheduled
to hear a new pitch
this morning.
Don't cause any trouble.
[SAIKI]
Unbelievable.
My dad's a manga editor.
How weird is that?
I've caught him
reading manga,
but at home he never mentions
or even thinks about his work.
[KUNIHARU]
Aw. My Kurumi is such a cutie.
She's washing dishes.
[SAIKI] Though, to be fair,
the only thing he
thinks about is Mom.
I wonder how his meeting's
going. Better check in.
♪
You've addressed
all of my notes.
I like how you've cut way back
on the dialogue
and are letting the art
and layout create the tension.
But the characters
could use some work.
[SAIKI] He actually sounds
like he's good at his job.
Have you thought about
making the main guy a psychic?
[WRITER] What?
[SAIKI] Hey.
But it's supposed to be
a realistic sports drama.
[KUNIHARU] Yeah.
Maybe add some dry wit too.
I'm sorry, but your notes
don't make any sense.
[KUNIHARU] Look, to be safe,
bring me something like Naruto.
[WRITER]
I can't do that.
Sorry about that.
[SAIKI] Don't apologize to me.
Apologize to that writer.
[cell phone rings]
Sorry. It's another one.
Yeah, Saiki here.
What's up? Oh, that?
Yeah, you got it.
[SAIKI]
I've never seen him like this.
Thanks for touching base.
[SAIKI] Well.
You don't have to go home, son.
[SAIKI]
I don't wanna get in your way.
This job's not as fancy
as it sounds.
And let me tell you,
when it's crunch time,
there's no superhero
coming to save us.
But every time I see
those finished manga pages
printed with a story the
writer poured his heart into,
it makes all the stress
and boss slapping worth it.
[SAIKI]
Hmph. Thanks for working hard
to provide for us, Dad.
Ha-ha-ha. Bye, son.
Right. I've gotta send
yesterday's finished pages
to the printer-- Ugh.
Kusuo! Kusuo, help me!
[SAIKI] Nope.
You already said no heroes.
[man sings in Japanese]
♪
[SAIKI]
Summer break's the best.
Once I'm done
with my homework,
which I can knock out
in a few hours,
I can just hang out and read,
and no one will care.
Best of all, today no one's even
home. When you're a psychic,
this is pretty much the
only time in the entire year
when you can relax.
[doorbell rings]
And now Nendou's here
to ruin that.
Wait. It's even worse.
Hello and good morning,
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2.
[SAIKI] Right.
Mom mentioned this earlier.
That neighbor boy,
Yuuta's home alone today.
so be nice and spend some time
with him, if he stops by, okay?
[SAIKI]
But being nice is so hard.
Whoa! So this is Cyborg
Cider-man Number 2's
secret base.
Hold on. Why's there
no soda coming out.
[SAIKI] It's a sink.
What? According to the comics,
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2
uses soda
everywhere in his life
where we would use water.
[SAIKI]
Wouldn't he get sick of that?
[YUUTA] At least tell me the
water in your toilet is soda.
The bubbles clean stains.
[SAIKI] That's convenient.
Oh, well. Who cares about
all of the soda in your home
when I've got
the latest Blu-ray of you
kicking bad guy booty.
Watch it with me.
[SAIKI] Uh...
Awesome!
Watching Cyborg Cider-man
while sitting
next to Cyborg Cider-man
is like eating ramen while
watching a TV show about it.
[SAIKI] That only makes sense
if you don't think about it.
Whoa!
♪
[NARRATOR]
Cyborg Cider-man.
Number 2!
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
[SAIKI] Can't you just
sit quietly and enjoy it?
[NARRATOR] Episode 10:
The Lemonade Fiend Appears.
[MAN] The Lemonade Fiend
has appeared!
Aah! It burns, it burns!
You jerk!
Ow! My eyes!
[Lemonade laughing]
Whenever we hit him, he just
squirts lemon juice on us.
He's taking over the world!
[SAIKI] A giant lemon?
[both gasp]
[MAN] An empty soda bottle.
[CIDER-MAN] Hold it
right there, Lemonade Fiend.
Huh? That voice!
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2
fizzes onto the scene!
Whoa!
[SAIKI] Keep it down.
What do you think'll happen?
Will he win?
[SAIKI] If you stay quiet,
he'll win.
Take this, Lemonade!
Soda Punch!
Wait! Don't punch him!
The impact will spray the city
with lemon juice!
Fizz!
[WOMAN] Oh, no!
He's become more
citrus sourness
than man now!
[WOMAN] Earth is doomed!
Wait, hold on!
[Woman gasps]
[MAN] It's having no effect
on Cider-man!
He looks like
that was nothing to him!
That was nothing to me!
[MAN] My God, he just said it!
[LEMONADE]
No! Impossible!
Heh. You just made lemon soda.
What? Lemon soda?
[CIDER-MAN] That's right.
When you add lemon to soda,
you're adding a sour kick to
that great, natural sweetness.
Not to mention a whole lot
of vitamin C.
It's the perfect
summer thirst quencher!
You see, your lemon juice
has actually powered me up!
Ha! Take this!
Lemon Soda Attack!
Find it wherever food
and drinks are sold!
Aah! It's only 148 yen
after tax?
[SAIKI]
That thing was just an ad.
Yeah! Cider-man won!
[SAIKI]
Could it get more blatant?
That was fun
sitting next to you
and watching you beat
Lemonade.
Now take me to the store
to get a lemon soda.
[SAIKI]
You lost the real battle.
Show me
your Lemon Soda Attack now,
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2
or get me a lemon soda.
[SAIKI] You'll get nothing
and like it.
[MAN] Here you go.
Lemon soda!
Hey. Good thing I bought
three of these, huh?
Now my buddy's kid bro
gets one.
[SAIKI]
Lemon Soda Attack!
[NENDOU]
Lemon what?
Why'd you hit me?
[SAIKI] He's not my brother,
and get out of my house.
No fighting in the Soda base!
Are you okay, mister?
Yeah. Thanks for asking me,
little boy.
[whimpering]
[Yuuta screaming]
[NENDOU] What's wrong?
[SAIKI]
Your face is terrifying.
This big guy is your archenemy,
Baron Cola!
[SAIKI] Baron Cola?
[LEMONADE]
Baron Cola,
my humblest apologies.
Next time--
[BARON COLA]
There will be no next time.
But I will gladly add
your lemon juice
to my Bad Cola power.
When life gives you lemons
after all.
[SAIKI] That's totally Nendou.
Oh.
[SAIKI] You got a point, kid.
Don't let him pickle me,
Cyborg Cider-man Number 2.
[SAIKI]
I can't believe the resemblance.
What's going on?
[NENDOU] Baron Cola.
[SAIKI]
You know this show? Figures.
Baron Cola's my favorite
comic book super villain.
He was even the inspiration
for me growing
this thick mustache.
[SAIKI] Thick?
[NENDOU] I get it.
That's why you're scared.
Look. There's nothing
to be afraid of.
See? I'm not scary, right?
[whimpering]
Aah!
He's gonna pickle me in cola!
[SAIKI] Oh, man.
I can see how if you're a kid,
he's pretty traumatizing.
I can't see too well
when making this face.
How's the little kid?
[SAIKI] Soda, get out!
[Nendou screaming]
♪
[SAIKI] I see. I was wondering
what all the commotion was.
Turns out it's some kind
of summer festival.
Usually crowds bug me,
but I'm actually okay
with these things.
[boy cheers]
[bell ringing]
[VENDOR]
Congratulations!
You just won a generic knock-off
of a popular toy!
[BOY] Yay!
[SAIKI] My parents used to take
me to festivals all the time.
I was obsessed with winning
this one prize,
but I never got it.
Sorry, kid.
Better luck next time.
[SAIKI] Years later,
it still bothers me.
But all in all, I have
good memories of the fair.
Man, what a big crowd.
[indistinct chattering]
My telepathy's gonna be
pretty much useless here.
Gotta keep my eyes open,
make sure I don't run
into anyone I know.
[NENDOU] For the last time!
There's no octopus
in these takoyaki.
I'm returning them for a refund!
[MAN 1] You can't...
[SAIKI] That was close.
Time for an alternate route.
Twenty-two caliber. Not a bad
weapon for hunting small game.
Hair trigger's always nice,
and I like having
that bolt-action for durability.
[MAN 2]
It's just a cork gun.
[KAIDOU] Ready, fire!
[MAN 2] Sorry, you missed.
[ALL] Heave-ho!
[MAN 3] Everyone out of the way!
[MAN 4] The festival mikoshi
is coming through!
[ALL]
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
[SAIKI]
That's a sore sight for eyes.
I should go before I start
hating festivals.
I'll get one of these
for the road.
[MAN 5]
That'll be 300 yen.
[SAIKI]
Hmm. My wallet's gone.
[MAN 5] Something wrong?
[SAIKI] Did I drop it?
No, I don't make mistakes
like that.
And it couldn't have been
a thief.
[MAN 6] Easy to pick pockets
when there's so many people.
[MAN 7]
I could go for another hot dog.
[SAIKI] With so many people,
I can't tell who's saying what.
[TAKAHASHI] It's gone!
[YOKOTA] What?
My wallet!
Someone must've taken it!
That's a drag, dude.
How much cash was in it?
On the way over,
I remember you saying
you put every last penny
you earned this summer in there.
[SAIKI] Sounds like Takahashi
got pick-pocketed.
Like I say,
you gotta pay attention
at all times in crowds
like this.
What a joke.
Pick. Pick-pocketed?
I can't deny it anymore.
That must be what happened
to me.
I got ripped off.
I, an all-seeing psychic,
got ripped off.
[babbling]
[MURATA]
Whoa! Takahashi just broke.
[SAIKI] I can't laugh.
I feel the same way.
[both babbling]
[MAN 1] Cool, fireworks!
[WOMAN] Didn't know it was time.
[MAN 2]
Not for another hour.
[SAIKI]
I've never felt so humiliated.
[laughs]
Festivals sure are fun,
aren't they?
Well, guess what,
Mr. Pickpocket,
now I'll make you pay...
with interest.
Only problem
is it's gonna be hard
to find him with telepathy alone
in a crowd this big.
I'll have to lure him out.
This should work.
[man chuckling]
[MAN] One night's work
and I made enough
to carry me through summer.
Thanks for donating
to my personal charity.
Huh, my backpack's heavy.
[screaming]
[grunts]
[MAN 1]
What the hell?
[MAN 2]
A motorcycle fell on him!
What the hell happened?
Get this thing off me.
[MAN 3]
Hey, you left your bike.
Ow! Stupid tree!
[screams]
[SAIKI] Did you enjoy
the little trade I made?
I found
an abandoned motorcycle,
and after fixing it up,
I realized
it was worth the same
as my wallet,
so I switched the two.
All I had to do then
was use my clairvoyance
to find a big commotion,
which led me right to you.
[whimpering]
All you need to know
is that you should never steal
a psychic's wallet.
Because there are
grave consequences.
♪
[man screaming]
[sighs]
This night's a total loss.
Wait.
What?
[MAN 1] I found my wallet.
[MAN 2] Really?
[SAIKI] Three to go. I could've
had the police handle this part,
but it would've taken longer
for everyone
to get their wallets back.
And that would ruin
the fun of the festival.
Besides, with psychometry, I can
easily find the owners myself.
So it's no big deal. Hmm?
My wallet's gone!
Dark Reunion stole it!
[SAIKI] Is this it?
Huh? What?
[SAIKI] Everyone I know
looks like an idiot tonight.
Well, two more.
My wallet! It's gone!
It was here a moment ago!
[SAIKI] In your loincloth?
Aah!
[SAIKI] Now whose is this?
Hey, buddy,
is that my missing wallet?
Big surprise.
Whoa.
Saiki's at the festival too.
Saiki. Nendou.
What's up, guys?
[SAIKI] What a pain.
They found me, after all.
Hmm. Which reminds me, I didn't
find Takahashi's wallet.
[babbling]
[MURATA]
Let's just go home.
[man sings in Japanese]
♪
[NARRATOR]
Here we find a beautiful girl,
this one with much on her mind.
[Teruhashi sighs]
[TERUHASHI] Why can't I
get him out of my head?
[NARRATOR]
Kokomi Teruhashi, 16 years old.
[TERUHASHI]
Is it true love? No!
I just can't believe
that a boring guy like him
is all "no, wow!" around me
instead of "oh, wow!"
I swear, I will make
Kunio Saiki fall for me,
no matter what it takes.
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere.
[YUMEHARA] What am I gonna do?
[NARRATOR] We find another,
not as attractive girl,
with much on her mind.
[YUMEHARA] How come I haven't
been in any episodes lately?
[NARRATOR]
Chiyo Yumehara, age 16.
[YUMEHARA]
What I'm worried about
is my relationship
with Saiki!
Whenever I wanna get close
to him,
it's like there's some invisible
force pulling us apart.
[NARRATOR] And so right on cue.
[both gasp]
Kokomi?
Yumehara?
[NARRATOR] They meet.
[YUMEHARA] Is this the first
time we've met outside school?
You know,
I think you're right.
I wish I knew before that
you liked to come to this place.
Yeah, it's quiet.
Makes a good place
to study or read.
[YUMEHARA]
Neat.
[TERUHASHI] This is awkward.
If we never talk at school,
what are we supposed
to talk about here?
[YUMEHARA] Do we know
each other enough
for me to just call her Kokomi
like that?
Hey.
So...
♪
[both sigh]
So excited for that
school field trip coming up?
Yeah, I'm super excited.
I love Okinawa.
Mm. It's gonna be so fun.
[YUMEHARA]
A three-day trip with Saiki.
Heaven.
[TERUHASHI]
A three-day trip with Saiki.
The only thing hotter than
these Okinawa beaches is you.
[NARRATOR]
Love fantasy.
You're more worthy
of an "oh, wow"
than the Okinawan sea.
[YUMEHARA &amp; TERUHASHI]
The dream.
[both gasp]
Were you saying something?
What? No, nothing at all.
What about you?
Uh, no.
I wasn't thinking
about any boys at school.
Kokomi, do you have a crush
on anyone?
[gasps]
What? You do?
[TERUHASHI] No! No, no.
I just wasn't expecting
such a private question.
There's no way
you'd have a crush.
Someone as pretty as you can
have any guy she wants, anytime.
Well, thank you,
but what about you?
Do you have a crush?
Yeah. Heh.
[TERUHASHI] Really, who?
[YUMEHARA] Promise not to tell?
[TERUHASHI] Is he in our class?
[YUMEHARA] Yeah.
Heh. Oh, that's nice.
[TERUHASHI]
It can't be Saiki, can it?
I'm dying to know.
[YUMEHARA] My psych--
[TERUHASHI] What'd you say?
Well, my psycho ex
is finally out of the picture.
[TERUHASHI]
Aah! Ha, ha. Psycho. Got it.
[YUMEHARA]
My crush is actually
someone I liked
before I met my ex.
[TERUHASHI]
Oh, wow. I had no idea
Yumehara had
so much experience with boys.
Maybe I should just ask her
for advice.
[TERUHASHI]
Um, well, the truth is
there is someone in our class
I like.
[blowing]
Tell me! Tell me! Tell me!
Is it a French guy? No, Russian!
[TERUHASHI] Bring down
that volume. You're drooling.
[YUMEHARA]
All right, I'm calm.
Now, please give me a name?
You're surrounded by
so many guys, I have no clue.
I'm not always around boys.
The last time I did that
was New Year's Day
when me, Hairo
and the others
went to Saiki's house
to celebrate.
[YUMEHARA]
Oh, Saiki, huh?
[YUMEHARA] I wasn't expecting
to hear that name
come out of Kokomi's mouth.
[TERUHASHI]
What was that about?
Was she reacting
to hearing Saiki?
[YUMEHARA] Could it be that
[TERUHASHI] Does that mean
[YUMEHARA] Kokomi's crush...
[TERUHASHI] Yumehara's crush...
[YUMEHARA &amp; TERUHASHI]
is Saiki?
[NARRATOR] Little do the girls
know the man of their dreams
sits next to them.
[KAIDOU] What's wrong, Saiki?
You look sick. Oh, no,
is Dark Reunion behind me?
[SAIKI]
What do I do?
If they end up
fighting over me,
they'll be in my life
all the time,
scheming to win
my affection.
That'll be worse
than having to deal
with Kaidou and Nendou.
The girls are this close
to realizing
that each of them
has a crush on me.
I have to nip this in the bud
before feelings get hurt
and my life gets ruined.
Hey, sorry, I blew my wrapper
over there.
Oh, wow, it's Teruhashi.
What? Nendou?
[SAIKI] Idiot.
Aah! Oh, no.
Did he hear us?
Kokomi.
She's blushing.
I was right.
There's no doubt.
[YUMEHARA] Kokomi likes...
[TERUHASHI] Yumehara likes...
[YUMEHARA &amp; TERUHASHI]
Saiki.
[SAIKI]
Don't jump to conclusions.
Huh?
[gasps]
[KAIDOU] My bad.
My deepest apologies.
[TERUHASHI]
She's blushing more than before.
Which means
the boy Yumehara likes is...
[SAIKI] Your turn, Teruhashi.
Oh, sorry.
Wow! She's so red.
Means the guy she likes
isn't Saiki. It's--
[SAIKI] I'm warming the girls'
faces using pyrokinesis.
[SAIKI] That was close.
[TERUHASHI] It's cute
that Yumehara's secret crush
is Kaidou.
[YUMEHARA]
I never would've guessed
Kokomi has the hots for Nendou.
[SAIKI] I may have just
made things even worse.
♪
[woman singing in Japanese]
[all singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI] Okay, folks, one
last time, so we're all clear.
I'm not a cyborg, a Cider-Man
or a Number 2 anything.
Next time, on
The Disastrous Life of Saiki K.
The big school trip
that everyone's
been looking forward to,
except the writers.
There are so many characters
on this show
and no one ever stops talking.