♪
[BOY] Little help with that!
Thanks, man!
[SAIKI] I've gotten much better
at controlling my throw.
I used to have problems because
I couldn't regulate my strength.
But those 300 practice throws
I did every day really paid off.
Of course, I still can't take
this thing off.
It's a device
that keeps my powers in check.
If something were
to ever happen to it, then--
[BOY]
Sorry! Can you throw it back?
[SAIKI]
Seriously, again?
Where'd that ball come from?
[BOY] Throw it back!
Is that any way to ask
for a favor? Fine, here you go.
That sparkle effect's
pretty old-school.
But never mind that!
What just happened?
I used the same amount
of strength as before.
[beeping]
It's missing.
I won't be able
to control my powers.
Right, the ball I saw earlier.
I have to fix it. Whoa!
See? This is bad. Very bad.
I can't modulate my powers.
So if I lean on a wall,
it'll shatter like a wafer.
If I bump into someone,
it'll send them flying.
If I run past people,
the wind pressure
will tear all their clothes
to shreds.
In this state, I've got
the power of a giant robot.
Every move I make
could flatten an entire city.
Going home like this
will be dangerous.
I have no choice. I've gotta
use my restoration ability
to put it back together.
That'll turn back time
on the device by one day.
Turn back time.
♪
Okay, problem solved.
Ugh. What?
Since my powers
are no longer constrained,
they're a lot stronger now.
Turning back time by seven
years?
That's trickier to use.
I should use telepathy
to ask my parents to get me.
[people speaking
in foreign language]
What's with
the other languages?
Of course, it's because
my telepathy's amped up.
It was limited
to a 200-meter radius before,
but-- Everyone shut up!
This is bad.
I can't pick up mom and dad's
voices like this.
What do I do--? Oh, crap!
What was that?
Turn back time!
[MAN 1] I thought I heard
a noise over there.
[MAN 2]
Was that wall always clean?
[SAIKI]
Phew, that was a close one,
but luckily I was able to hide
behind the wall.
Should be safe for me
to teleport without being seen.
What are you doing there, buddy?
[SAIKI] Nendou? Why's he here?
[NENDOU]
Why you lying down in our yard?
[SAIKI]
This is your house?
[NENDOU] Huh, doesn't that wall
look cleaner somehow?
Hasn't looked nice
in seven years.
[SAIKI]
He's being perceptive, scary.
Seriously, looks cleaner, right?
[SAIKI] What was that?
Don't you think so?
[SAIKI]
I'm seeing through flesh?
Damn it,
even that power's intensified.
He's got one crazy chinbone.
[NENDOU] Ain't it clean?
[SAIKI] I don't have time
for this. Gotta get home.
Hey, wait.
I'm not letting you go
till you say
how clean our wall is now.
[SAIKI] Why do you care?
[NENDOU] Aw, I'm just playing.
You gonna get some ramen?
Sure, I'll come with you!
[SAIKI] Why's he make it sound
like I invited him?
I'll have to lose him somehow.
That trick ought to work.
Might look weird
with me suddenly disappearing,
but it'll be okay,
he's an idiot.
A big, dumb idiot.
Hey, let's go already.
[SAIKI] Okay, now.
Something shot out.
Did you see that just now?
[NENDOU] Hey,
where'd you go, buddy?
[KURUMI] Don't you have to get
to work? You have that meeting
with the new manga author
you're handling, right?
[KUNIHARU]
It'll be fine.
I'll handle him later on,
but first, I need to handle
my beautiful wife.
But Kuu will be home soon.
Don't worry.
[SAIKI]
I'm home.
[KUNIHARU] Kusuo?
[KURUMI] Kuu?
You teleported back home?
But why?
Oh, no!
Kuu, your hairpin is missing!
[SAIKI]
Good, saves me the exposition.
[KURUMI[ Kuu?
[KUNIHARU] Kusuo, what's wrong?
--Are you okay?
--[SAIKI] Of course.
I'm just relaxing my body,
that's all.
If I don't do this, the room
might get a little chaotic.
[KUNIHARU]
Oh, your control device.
What's wrong?
[SAIKI] It broke.
But you like building stuff.
So fix it.
[KUNIHARU] I'd need
instructions, with pictures.
[SAIKI]
Please. I beg you.
[KUNIHARU] You don't look
like someone begging.
[KUNIHARU] Guess I could try.
We could use something else.
Ooh, what about a lollipop?
It basically looks the same.
[SAIKI] How would that work?
[KUNIHARU] Done!
I'm surprised I was able
to do it, I do build a lot.
[SAIKI]
It shouldn't look like a toy.
I pulled it back,
it started rolling. Redo it.
[KUNIHARU] This is too much.
We're gonna ask who
originally made it.
[SAIKI] I created it.
You didn't do it yourself.
Kuusuke's pretty much
the only one
who could fix this.
I'll try giving Big Kuu
a call now.
[SAIKI]
How could you?
[KUUSUKE]
Hello?
Oh, hi, Mom. Been a while.
Yep, I'm doing fine.
You're calling about
the control device, aren't you?
Come by any time.
Can't let down my baby bro.
[SAIKI]
This is the worst.
Can't believe I have to go
beg him for his help.
♪
[JAMIE] Mr. Saiki.
[KUUSUKE] You need something?
This thesis you let me copy--
I mean, gave me advice on,
got the most insanely glowing
evaluations from the professors.
You really are brilliant,
you know? You're a genius.
I'm no genius, Jamie.
Just an ordinary man.
Someone who makes all
of modern science
and common sense irrelevant,
now that's a genius.
Yay! We're here!
The Saiki's are in London!
[KURUMI] London! So debonair!
Love, take a picture!
You look like James Bond!
[SAIKI] The reason we're here
is to make him fix my device.
Did you remember to bring it?
[KUNIHARU] Yes.
We're not here to sightsee.
[SAIKI]
That's not how it looked.
All right, let's go!
Next stop, Cambridge!
♪
[SAIKI]
Hey, we're not here for fun.
Now, let's hurry and get
on the train to Cambridge.
Oh, right, of course.
[KUNIHARU] Mind the gap!
[SAIKI] Good grief, finally.
This is the London Eye!
What a lovely view.
[SAIKI] I'm going by myself.
[KUNIHARU]
Whoa, Kusuo! We're so high up!
If you can't control
your powers, we're goners!
[SAIKI]
You brought me up here!
[KUNIHARU] Fine.
We can go see Kuusuke now.
[SAIKI] Sheesh.
I didn't even wanna see him
in the first place,
but here we are.
Yoo-hoo!
Long time no see!
Oh, Kuusuke!
Big Kuu!
[SAIKI]
Seriously? Quite an entrance.
♪
Good to see you!
Kuusuke!
It's been so long!
I missed you, Mom.
Hey, Kuusuke! How's it--?
Hey there, Kusuo.
Looks like
you're doing well.
[SAIKI] If I were,
I wouldn't be here.
[KUUSUKE] Been a while, Dad?
What? Yeah!
[KUUSUKE] Did you gain weight?
[KUNIHARU] I'm here.
Just kidding. How've you been?
Oh, fine.
[SAIKI]
Look at him toying with Dad.
I really hate being
around my brother.
Kusuo's control device
is completely broken now.
[SAIKI] At first glance,
he doesn't seem so bad.
Well, even if I manage
to fix it,
that's never gonna resolve the
underlying problem with him.
[SAIKI] My brother isn't worried
about me one bit.
The reason I don't like him
is that he doesn't like me.
...slip up in there
since I don't like Kusuo.
[SAIKI] But it's only natural
that he resents me.
Eighteen years ago,
an ordinary couple
welcomed a baby boy
into the world.
You're so darn cute.
[SAIKI] The reason why
my parents weren't surprised
when I was born was because
they already had my brother.
See, when he was only
a month old--
I grasp it.
[SAIKI]
--he spoke his first words.
By age 2, he'd mastered
simple calculations
and could read and write.
A test said his IQ was 218.
Basically, he was a genius.
But at the age of 3,
that genius would already hit
a big wall.
I'm bored of this puzzle now.
I think I'll read
Young Jump instead.
[crashing]
[SAIKI] That wall was none other
than me.
He felt humiliated.
As he projected his jealousy,
inferiority complex,
and hatred onto me,
I started to dislike him too.
Then, when he was 14...
A younger brother never
surpasses his older brother.
...he uttered that phrase
and left to go study in the UK.
It's been four years
and I haven't seen him
even once since then.
[chuckles]
I'm kidding.
I could never hate
my precious baby brother.
You brought the parts.
Let me have a look.
[SAIKI] I'm wearing
my telepathy-blocking ring.
I don't know if he means that.
[gasping]
[KURUMI] What's wrong?
[SAIKI] Don't tell me.
[KURUMI]
You lost your bag?
And I'm guessing
all of the parts
for the control device
were in it?
[KUNIHARU] And the travel guide
with the tourist spots! No!
[SAIKI] Why does that matter?
I know for sure I had it
when we arrived in England.
[SAIKI] In other words,
you don't remember anything?
At least we know
it's in London.
That's all the information
I need.
[KUNIHARU] What's that?
[KUUSUKE] From the city's CCTV.
The UK is a total
surveillance state now.
They've got cameras installed
in every nook and cranny.
They even caught you picking
your nose an hour ago.
[KUNIHARU] Don't look!
Wait, I still have the bag!
Where'd we go after that?
Maybe the souvenir shop.
[KUNIHARU] How'd you know?
What you're wearing.
You had on a different one
an hour ago.
You must've bought it some time
after that and changed.
But you don't have the clothes
you were originally wearing,
which means
you still had the bag then.
So the only possible place
is here at the London Eye.
They check bags
before you get on,
so if you had it here,
it should be at the bag check.
[KUNIHARU]
Woo-hoo, I found it!
Now then, get to it,
Kuusuke.
Well, I'll try my best.
[KURUMI] Please do.
Hm. Here, this should be
all good to go now.
[KUNIHARU]
You fixed it already?
Yeah,
wasn't too complicated.
[KUNIHARU] Whoa! Kusuo's back
on his feet, good as new!
[SAIKI] Huh, he fixed it
without making a big fuss.
But a superficial gesture
of good will won't work on me.
Huh? Wait, what's going on?
What's wrong?
Is something not working
for you, Kusuo?
[SAIKI] I'm not able to read
his mind at all.
[MAN]
Come on!
[SAIKI]
Which card has my dad on it?
See through it!
♪
[KUUSUKE]
My name is Kuusuke Saiki.
I'm an ordinary person
except for the fact
that I have a little brother
who's a psychic.
The oldest memory
from my childhood
is a feeling of defeat.
[KUNIHARU] Wow, Kuusuke.
Great,
you can ride a bike already.
It's like taking candy
from a baby.
[KUNIHARU] You were a baby
till like a week ago.
[KUUSUKE] I don't need
the training wheels anymore.
Take them off.
What? Sure you're ready?
[KURUMI]
Kuu, no! Get off!
It's not something
a baby should be riding!
[KUUSUKE]
My little brother was a genius
and I was just
an ordinary kid.
That's what I realized
that day.
Older brothers aren't supposed
to lose to their younger ones.
[KUNIHARU] This is phenomenal.
Hundreds on all your tests
and straight 5's
on your report card!
Like I was taking those tests
with monkeys.
[KURUMI]
Nine hundred million points?
You manipulated your teacher's
brain again. No more...
[KUUSUKE]
My bro was always topping me.
Whoa, what's that?
My summer break project.
Made with materials
I found in the trash.
[KUNIHARU]
Incredible.
Oh, you made one too?
[KUUSUKE] What is that?
Looks like I came out
on top this--
Ah! Kuusuke Number One!
[KUUSUKE]
I lost again.
I refused to give up,
challenging him over and over,
yet still, I was never able
to win even once.
When I was in the seventh grade,
I created a device
that would weaken
my brother's powers.
But even with that,
I couldn't win.
So at 14, I,
an ordinary boy,
lost all hope,
skipped several grades
and escaped to the University
of Cambridge in England.
There I lived
a self-indulgent life
and just last year
received a master's degree.
Since then, I've spent
all my time researching
in order to earn a PhD.
That's when the idea hit me.
A way to block
Kusuo's telepathy.
[KUUSUKE] You can't hear
my inner voice?
That's all because
of this thing.
I call it
the Telepathy Canceler.
Telepathy Canceler?
Whoa!
Another brilliant invention.
So Kuu can't hear
your thoughts
if you're using that device?
I assumed you wanted
a unique character design.
[KUUSUKE] Well, that too.
[SAIKI] Seriously?
Great, now there are two people
whose minds I can't read.
There's a fine line
between genius and idiot.
Hey, Kusuo, why don't you come
check out my lab after this?
I wanna show you something.
What? You don't want us
to tag along with you?
As long as we're in England,
I was really hoping
that we all could see
where you live too.
[KUUSUKE] You two should go off,
enjoy London on your own.
I made a reservation for you
at a roast beef restaurant.
Well, shall we go on a date?
I don't mind going if you don't.
Well, I guess I don't mind
either or whatever.
[SAIKI]
Why are you acting like that?
[KUNIHARU]
Well, see you!
Heh.
Those two never change, huh?
[SAIKI]
What are you up to here?
I'm not interested
in visiting your lab.
Let's play
rock, paper, scissors.
[SAIKI] Don't ignore me.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Oh, look at that.
I lost, huh?
[SAIKI] Are you happy now?
I'm going back.
[KUUSUKE] I'm zero
for 725 against you
in rock, paper, scissors.
You've thrown rock less often
than the other two.
Now I think about it, that's
because I used scissors least.
A hundred four times,
to be exact.
I lost 31 times in shiritori,
59 times in shogi,
10 times in chess, 189 times
in various video games,
six times in sugoroku,
four times in mahjong,
seven times in Yamanote Line.
There were other games too.
In total, how many times
do you think I've lost to you?
[SAIKI] He remembers every loss?
He really creeps me out.
Zero wins, 4254 losses.
[SAIKI]
Seriously, what is he up to?
[KUUSUKE] Teleporting really
is incredible!
[SAIKI] What is this place?
A hotel room?
Are we still in London?
No, it can't be.
I must be hearing things.
Oh, I see you've noticed.
That's right.
They're in the next room.
[NENDOU]
Whoa! Check it out, runt!
The buildings look
like the kind in manga!
Why were we brought all the way
here for some surprise?
Ah! Could be a trap set
by Dark Reunion?
[SAIKI] Ugh. What the hell
are they doing here?
I invited them. I called the day
before you arrived and said,
"Kusuo's coming to London.
How'd you like to go too
and surprise him?"
I sent plane tickets
and everything.
[SAIKI] They'd never fall for
something obvious-- Actually.
So why'd you bring them here?
Play a game with me, Kusuo.
[SAIKI]
A game?
[KUUSUKE]
A game of tag across London.
I lost at rock, paper, scissors
so I'll be it.
Time limit's three hours. As
long as you don't leave London,
take any mode of transportation.
Bus, taxi, subway.
What do you think? Fun?
[SAIKI] You'll never win.
London's bigger than all 23
of Tokyo's wards combined.
Take those two so you can't use
your powers so freely.
[SAIKI]
Not happening
[KUUSUKE] Guess you don't care
what happens to those guys.
On my signal,
they'll be whisked away
to sightsee around London,
and then sent back to Japan.
[SAIKI]
Take me too.
Did I mention
that if you win,
I'll treat you
to afternoon tea and desserts?
Okay! Tag starts now!
♪
Hey, buddy!
You surprised to see us?
Bet you never expected that!
[SAIKI] Don't bother
with the surprise.
We're gonna play tag now.
[BOTH] We're doing what?
[KUUSUKE] Yeah, I'm gonna be it
and Kusuo will be running.
You two can help him get away.
[KAIDOU] The surprise?
He was surprised.
It was a success.
[KAIDOU] That's it?
The game will last three hours.
Stay within city limits,
go anywhere you like
and use any public transit,
including bus, taxi
and subway.
[both groan]
Okay, ready and go!
I'm giving you
a 30-minute head start
so run while you can.
[KAIDOU] Wait.
See you.
And now, at last,
the game begins.
[KAIDOU] What's going on?
This makes no sense.
[SAIKI] Sorry for dragging
you guys into this,
but just go along with it.
Something very important
is at stake.
[KAIDOU] It's folly to challenge
me in this child's game,
I'm used to being pursued
by Dark Reunion,
but it could be interesting,
so I'll play.
I'm game. People don't call
me Nen the Awesome Tag Champ
for nothing.
[SAIKI] They're into it.
[KUUSUKE] It's about time to go.
Let's see how they're doing.
It looks like
they still haven't noticed yet.
[KAIDOU] Doesn't this seem
a little too easy?
London is bigger than all 23
of Tokyo's wards put together.
[SAIKI] There are probably lots
of cameras in the subway too,
but it is efficient
traveling long distances.
Hey, where we going?
We're gonna use the subway.
[NENDOU]
Huh. The gate's closed.
[SAIKI]
So this was his plan.
[gasps]
I didn't know about the strike.
You can take any mode
of transportation.
Bus, taxi, subway.
[SAIKI] He knew the whole time.
How about a bus or taxi?
The bus line goes on
forever.
If we don't move,
we'll be caught.
[SAIKI] Yeah, probably sooner
than you think.
But where should we go?
[SAIKI] If he's gonna watch us,
then I'll watch him too.
Clairvoyance!
He's heading this way.
He's close. He'll be here
in less than five minutes.
What do we do, Saiki?
Stand in line or run?
What's wrong with your eyes?
[SAIKI] What do we do now?
Well, well, it looks like
I might be a little too late.
I see. They opted for those.
Boris Bikes.
[SAIKI] What a pain.
[panting]
We've gone pretty far.
[SAIKI]
You're pretty out of breath.
[gasps]
[crashing]
Maybe a short break?
We've only been biking
for about 15 minutes.
But I tried to avoid
all the cameras,
so we should be okay.
In fact,
moving around haphazardly
can only help him find us.
Staying put here--
[KUUSUKE] Best course of action.
Oh, come on! How'd he find us?
That was awesome!
Now's not the time!
He means business!
[NENDOU] Huh?
[KAIDOU] Let's go!
[SAIKI] I don't understand.
How did he find us
when we were avoiding
the cameras?
That was fast.
Maybe he's got psychic powers.
[SAIKI] No, that's me.
Maybe he planted a transmitter?
[SAIKI] A transmitter!
How stupid could I be?
The control device has
a transmitter. He tricked me!
Guess I have to wrap things up
quicker when dealing with Kusuo.
[Kaidou gasping]
Are we
in a department store?
[SAIKI] Since he knows
where we are now,
I figure it's better
than walking around outside.
We should be inconspicuous.
Outrun him in these cars!
[SAIKI]
Less conspicuous than that.
[KAIDOU] A game console that
hasn't been released in Japan.
[KUUSUKE]
Bing, bing, bong, bong.
Attention.
[SAIKI] That voice.
We have lost children
in the store.
They're three Japanese boys.
First one has pink hair,
he tried to climb Big Ben.
Second is a youth
with evil eyes who insists
on calling football "soccer".
And lastly, the serial killer
who looks like a gorilla.
Oi, it's them!
Let's nab them!
[KAIDOU] Uh...
Ha-ha-ha.
Things are getting wild.
Don't climb Big Ben!
It's a national treasure!
[SAIKI] Seriously?
What do we do now?
Okay, everyone.
It's all right.
That announcement was part
of a big misunderstanding.
[MAN 3]
Misunderstanding?
[MAN 4]
If a Cambridge man says so.
Well, that's that.
Sorry, Kusuo,
but it's checkmate.
I know that you're in there.
Zero wins, 4254 losses.
This was a long time coming.
It's all over now!
What?
[SAIKI] GPS transmitters
can identify your location,
but not your elevation.
Yes, we are in a restroom,
it just happens to be a floor
above the one Kuusuke's in.
I also used a little hypnosis.
While running,
I made a few of the guys
we passed look like us.
Temporarily, of course.
With them as a distraction,
we took the opportunity
to run upstairs.
[beeping]
Time's up.
I lost yet again.
Ah,
so that's what happened?
Ever since he was a kid,
Big Kuu has always been
so competitive.
[KUNIHARU] He might be feeling
a tad down after losing.
[SAIKI] Yeah, not likely.
This guy hasn't given up
after losing 4255 times
in a row.
If anything,
it's the other way around.
I lost again.
[SAIKI] He's a total masochist.
You truly are the only one
who can defeat me, Kusuo.
And now you see
why I don't like him.
[MAN]
Come on!
[KUNIHARU] Kusuo, can't
that power be used for--
[SAIKI]
I refuse.
♪
Dark Reunion? What kind
of organization is that?
Better you don't know. Knowledge
of it will cause you harm.
[KUUSUKE] Whoa, how do you fight
against people that dangerous?
The ominous power living
in my right hand
is more than enough.
Wait, what kind of power?
Can I see?
[KAIDOU] Uh, well, uh, that's--
What?
You can't do that either?
No, it's just
the power is too enormous.
If I release it here,
the building will implode.
[KUUSUKE] If that's all it is,
there's a lab with protective
walls. We can go there.
Well, I'd love to,
but it's sealed now, so--
[KUUSUKE]
You mean those bandages?
You saying without them,
something bad will happen?
But you didn't
have them on yesterday.
[SAIKI] What are you doing
up early?
Oh, hey there, Kusuo.
Good morning.
I was taking out
some of my frustration
from yesterday's loss
on your little friends here.
[SAIKI]
Stop tormenting him.
[KUUSUKE] I feel better
now thanks to them.
[SAIKI] Whoa, I've never seen
Nendou like this.
What'd my brother say to him?
That jerk said my mom's
belly button is an outie.
[SAIKI] That's it?
[KUUSUKE] I could only get
you an afternoon flight.
[SAIKI]
Was hoping sooner, but...
Since we have a few hours
before our flight,
we can check out
Kuusuke's place.
[SAIKI] They're leaving.
[KUNIHARU] You are students.
Go in there and learn.
[NENDOU] Eh?
[SAIKI]
An art museum, huh?
Not the kind of place
I'd choose to visit.
Because while it may appear
quiet to you,
for me, having people around
always means this.
[MAN 5] I don't get it.
[MAN 6] Ah! I don't get it.
[SAIKI] On top of that, to be
honest, I don't understand art.
This is good art.
[SAIKI] Hate to admit it,
my reaction's the same.
We'll do a lap, then leave.
I see conflict. Fretfulness?
[SAIKI] Hm?
The feelings put
into this painting.
It sublimates the conflict
towards life and a fretfulness
about death as art.
One might call it a rebuttal
to modern art,
which has become too focused
on originality above all else.
[SAIKI]
What's he talking about?
You know about art?
[SAIKI] Conflict, fretfulness?
Hm...
[SAIKI] Looks like
an ordinary landscape to me.
Oh. What about this picture
here? What's it mean?
It's creating rhythms by
carefully calculating the layout
of geometrical patterns
and color schemes.
The circle in the middle
breaks them,
and feels foreign
to the painting.
Thus, it succeeds in fostering
an entirely new
visual experience.
[SAIKI] Who the heck are you?
Hm.
♪
[gasps]
What the--?
How long was I standing there?
Oh, about 10 minutes
I guess.
Oops, it happened again.
I was drawn into the painting,
so overwhelmed by it
I lost myself.
[SAIKI]
Ugh, he's so annoying.
If this is what he talks about
with art
then I'd rather it not speak
to me.
Forget that.
Check out this room.
Isn't it weird?
[SAIKI] Contemporary art?
[NENDOU] And get a load of this!
The elegant harmony
of an every-day folding chair
juxtaposed with an object
that one can only call "art".
[SAIKI] Never at a loss
for words, are you?
To me, it looks
like a chair and... that.
[NENDOU]
Hm...
So they just put a pile of poo
on a chair, is that right?
And what's this?
[SAIKI] Just a string phone.
This is the sort of layout
that could only be created
by injecting a splash
of randomness
into the concept
of a classic string telephone.
It advocates that anyone can
establish their own originality.
[SAIKI] No, it doesn't.
[NENDOU] What about this?
[SAIKI] Just a doodle.
Distance of soul!
The neo-iconoclastic combination
of material and function
stimulates our inspiration
and teaches us
how uncertain this world is!
[SAIKI] We already learned
that lesson earlier.
Oh, really?
I'm glad you liked it.
I mean, I drew this thing
in like three seconds.
[SAIKI] You baited him.
What is it
teaching us again?
Excellent!
[SAIKI] Who are you?
What is this?
[SAIKI] He seems excited.
Hey, dude!
[ENGLISH MAN] Did you draw that?
My name's Michael Scofield. I'm
the director of this gallery.
[KAIDOU]
You're the director?
Yes, it's my job
to select pieces for display.
[SAIKI] How did someone with
your questionable taste in art
get this position?
[SCOFIELD] That drawing there
is quite interesting.
Huh?
Yes, wonderful.
[SAIKI] He keeps it simple.
If it's all right with you,
my boy.
[all cheering]
You gotta be kidding me!
I could draw something better!
Please, sir,
look at my drawing too!
Oh, you draw, too?
I'd love to have a look.
[KAIDOU] So, what do you think?
No.
[SAIKI] Doesn't get any simpler
than that.
[SAIKI] In a certain sense,
this one looks more art-ish.
Does he really get it?
What's all this fuss
about then?
[SCOFIELD] It's the master
of contemporary art ,
John McMahon!
[SAIKI] Looks like another
art expert has appeared.
Wow, this is bloody bonkers!
Yes, isn't it?
[MCMAHON]
There's no other word for it.
[SAIKI]
See? I could apport the drawing
since there're both
worth nothing.
This drawing's the best,
innit?
[SAIKI]
I really don't understand art.
♪
[KUUSUKE] Well, Kusuo, Round Two
of tag is about to begin.
[SAIKI] There is no Round Two.
Go back to Cambridge already.
[SAIKI] Next time on
The Disastrous Life of Saiki K,
summer break
is already approaching
and I plan to keep my schedule
completely and utterly blank.