[SAIKI] Kokomi Teruhashi
is universally acknowledged
to be the absolute,
perfect pretty girl.
[TERUHASHI] Heh. Won't you be
surprised to see me?
No, I can't do it!
Come on,
get it together, Kokomi.
After all, you didn't
come here to see Saiki.
You came to get cooking lessons
from his mother.
Oh, no, I rang
the neighbor's bell.
[SAIKI]
However, there is something
that even
she can't deal with.
[TERUHASHI] I'm sorry,
I rang your bell by mistake.
Hey, who are you?
[SAIKI]
And that would be children.
[TERUHASHI]
I'm sorry.
I went to the wrong house.
He saw me
and then ran away?
[SAIKI] Her beauty has
no effect on children.
Hey, what are you--?
Here, come quick,
Cyborg Cider-man Number Two.
[SAIKI]
Hey, let go. Seriously.
[YUUTA] Look, there's
a strange lady here.
[TERUHASHI]
Saiki, what are you--?
[SAIKI]
Everything goes her way.
I sensed her coming,
so I fled next door.
I never thought
she'd show up here.
[KURUMI] Oh, hi there, Kokomi.
Nice to see you again.
Sorry it's been so long.
Aw, and you've got Yuuta
with you.
You two look like
a married couple.
Huh? What? No!
What are you trying to say?
[SAIKI]
Give it a rest, Mom.
[KURUMI] So, do you have a date
with Kuu today?
No, no, no.
Remember, a while back
you offered to give me
a cooking lesson, so here I am.
Just for lessons.
[KURUMI] You came to see me?
That makes me so happy.
I'll go set up then.
I'm sorry
to just barge in.
Married couple?
Yeah, right.
There's no way a girl like me
would ever wind up
with a guy like Saiki.
I mean, give me a break.
Why's that kid
staring at me?
Oh, of course,
I must be his first crush.
Well, hello, Yuuta.
[shudders]
[TERUHASHI] You little brat!
Oh, right,
I've got this.
I brought cake.
Does that sound like something
you might like?
Cake?
[TERUHASHI] He took the bait!
There's an extra one for Yuuta
if he wants it.
[YUUTA] Yay! Cake! Cake!
[TERUHASHI] Good thing that guy
at the pastry shop
threw in a free one.
Wow, they look delicious.
[TERUHASHI] What?
That's what he gave me?
I guess this one must be
for Kuu, huh?
No, no, no! I just told them to
give me whatever they had.
I didn't pick it out,
so it doesn't mean anything.
[KURUMI]
Oh, all right.
You can have whichever one
you like.
[YUUTA] Yay!
[TERUHASHI] Of all things,
I can't believe they gave me
a heart cake.
Still, I hope that's the one
that Saiki chooses.
Yummy. It's my favoritest kind.
[scoffs]
Boy, that was great.
[KURUMI]
As delicious as it looked.
[SAIKI] Wasn't bad.
[TERUHASHI] Glad you liked it.
Did you enjoy that, Yuuta?
Yep, it's the kind I like most.
Then you should say thank you
to Kokomi.
Okay. Thank you
for the cake, ma'am.
[TERUHASHI]
Ah! Who are you calling "ma'am?"
Me? How old do you think I am?
[SAIKI] You're overreacting.
[TERUHASHI] This rude little
pipsqueak just said number four
on my list of things no one
will ever say to me!
[SAIKI]
That's a weird list.
[phone rings]
[KURUMI] The phone's ringing.
[TERUHASHI]
This will not go unpunished.
I'll get my revenge
10 years from now,
when you can appreciate
my beauty.
Oh, man, I'm so bored.
[TERUHASHI] I'll strut up
to you, all sexy-like.
[YUUTA]
Who's that beautiful goddess?
I-- I love you.
[TERUHASHI]
And then I'll whisper softly.
Oh, no, we can't be together.
After all, I'm an old lady.
In your face!
[SAIKI] I really don't enjoy
seeing Teruhashi like this,
but I might be able to use this
as a weapon against her.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I forgot that I had to go
to the Neighborhood Association
meeting.
[TERUHASHI] That's okay,
I'll come back some other time.
If you don't mind waiting, it
should only take half an hour.
Kuu, entertain her
while I'm gone.
[TERUHASHI] That means
I'll be all alone with Saiki...
except for the brat.
Hey, can we watch some TV now?
[TERUHASHI] Watch at your house.
Oh, nothing. Come on,
let's watch some TV, okay?
I need to be careful.
Can't get worked up
over a child.
Now we can have
a grown-up conversation
while the twerp's busy
watching TV.
So, do you like children?
I love 'em.
You're watching it with him?
Seriously,
what are you doing, Saiki?
So much for our
grown-up conversation.
He's pretty cool, huh?
Be quiet,
I'm trying to watch.
[TERUHASHI] He just said
number 31 on my list!
[SAIKI]
How long is this list?
Um, I just remembered something,
so I'm gonna go home now.
Okay, bye.
Please apologize
to your mom for me.
[SAIKI]
I feel bad, but it worked.
I owe Yuuta a coffee jelly.
You just leave the protecting
to me, Cider-Man.
[CIDER-MAN]
That sweet scent, it must be--
Go on ahead and take care
of Baron Cola.
[CIDER-MAN] I'm counting on you,
Peach T Girl.
[SAIKI]
Hey, what are you thinking?
They're two totally
different people.
[YUUTA] That's the girl
who was just here!
[SAIKI] They look nothing alike.
[YUUTA] Come back, Peach T Girl!
[SAIKI] Looks like Yuuta
has a new obsession.
[SAIKI]
I forgot my wallet at home.
A normal person would be
freaking out right now,
but I'm a psychic.
All I have to do is duck into
the bathroom and teleport home.
Not a problem.
There are plenty
of other ways.
I just thought of 182.
Only problem is,
they're all either illegal
or highly immoral.
So I won't be doing
any of those.
Causing trouble for others
goes against my principles.
Unfortunately, I can't think
of any safe methods
given where I am.
There are people everywhere,
and they all have a clear view
of my table.
Plus, of all days, I had to pick
today to wear this.
It makes me stand out,
which means I can't teleport
from here.
And making myself transparent
takes at least a minute.
Maybe I can use telepathy to ask
someone to bring me money.
I could ask Mom.
Kuu, you need money?
What happened?
Are you all right?
I emptied out our bank account--
[SAIKI] No, I don't wanna
worry her. What about Dad?
Kusuo, you gotta be more
responsible, kid, you big goof.
[SAIKI]
No, that'd be annoying.
What about Nendou,
Kaidou, or Toritsuka?
Out of the question.
It's not that I mind
bothering them,
it's just that I'd rather die
than ask any of them
for a favor.
That leaves only
one method: apport.
The perfect solution
for this situation.
But I need to send something
of equal value
in exchange for what
I apport here.
And even
in a post-apocalyptic world,
these wouldn't be worth
980 yen.
But there's
a loophole I can use.
See, what you send doesn't have
to have the exact same value
as what you get.
There's a little wiggle room,
so you can exchange
a 100-yen item
for something anywhere
in the 90-to-110-yen range.
If I start with 100 yen,
I can get to 980
in as few as 25 exchanges.
That's a lot.
How many times will it take
if I start with 2 yen?
I need something
of higher value.
Clothes could work,
but can't use my pants.
Can't use this cardigan either.
Too noticeable.
[WAITER]
How about "Zebra Cardie"?
[SAIKI] Waiters are already
coming up
with a nickname based on it.
They'd definitely notice.
Not wearing a shirt
would be awkward too.
Can't even imagine the nicknames
they'd come up with then.
Guess I'll have
to lose those.
Feels breezy down there
without my socks.
Oh, what did you think
I was talking about?
There's no way
I'd do something as stupid
as exchanging
my own underwear.
The last time 500 yen seemed
this valuable to me
was in second grade.
Now to exchange it for something
worth 550 yen.
Apport.
Okay...apport.
That's odd.
Why is there underwear in here?
[SAIKI] Okay. I've increased
the value by 100 yen.
Now let's keep going.
Apport.
This is The Disastrous Life
of Saiki K.
Extra Story of Psychics.
I bought it on impulse,
since the name matches mine.
Weird coincidence, huh?
But wait, this was on
my bookshelf, which means...
Eh, probably best
not to think about it.
Next is...oops.
There's nothing at home that
cost between 650 and 715 yen.
I have no choice. I have to
cause trouble for them. Apport.
You called about pitching
your manga, right?
Right, that's me.
[KUNIHARU] Then let's see
what you've got.
Um, I don't really wanna see
[SAIKI]
So this is Dad's belt.
I guess he did buy
a pretty cheap one.
But moving on. Apport.
Alrighty, it's chow time.
This meat's kind of leathery.
[SAIKI]
Before it gets cold. Apport.
[MALE LECTURER] Let's review
integration by substitution
using pi.
Hey, Kaidou, what are you doing
with your lunch out?
It's not time!
[SAIKI]
Apport.
Whoa, check this hot mama out.
Her booty and boobies are
spectacular, and her-- Huh? Pi?
You pervert. Are you really
from the Editorial Department?
[KUNIHARU]
What? Of course I am.
Here, look at this.
[SAIKI] Apport.
I'm definitely an editor here.
See?
Sure doesn't look like it!
[SAIKI]
This is the last time. Apport.
All right.
The Straw Millionaire plan
worked.
Like I said, that situation was
nothing for a psychic to fear.
[MAN 1] Where's Crappy Dresser?
[MAN 2] He left.
[SAIKI] Well, for once,
my friends and family
helped me out,
though only about 2 percent.
Guess I'll help them
next time I see them.
[MALE GUARD] How'd you get
in here, you creep?
I swear, I'm telling the truth!
I work here!
Eating during class?
Unbelievable.
I'm going to have a good talk
with your parents about this.
Hey, wait, this is a belt.
No wonder it tasted funny.
And why did I eat
so much of it?
Where'd my girls go?
[ALL] Somebody, help me!
[SAIKI] Never mind.
It would've been easier if
I'd just washed dishes instead.
[GIRL]
Come on!
[SAIKI]
Who on earth will win?
Foretell it.
[KUNIHARU]
It's finished!
I finished building this awesome
one-hundredth scale
Destruction Weapon Libeon model
I've been working on.
Look how perfect it is.
[SAIKI]
Yeah, yeah, that's great.
Why don't you go show Mom.
[KUNIHARU]
It's even got a cockpit.
Isn't that the most amazing?
Aah! My Destruction
Weapon Libeon.
[SAIKI] More like
Destroyed Weapon Libeon.
Kusuo, what'd you do that for?
[SAIKI] Wasn't me.
Though in two more seconds,
it would have been.
He did it.
It's been a while,
so I thought you might
be missing me.
My Libeon. Please, Kusuo,
can't you put it back
to how it was
with one of your powers?
Aah! Don't ignore me!
[SAIKI] Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
[KUNIHARU]
Whoa, really?
[SAIKI] Well, I put it back
to how it was. Good luck.
I guess I should've known
something was up
when you were so quick
to help me.
Now I have to start over.
[meowing]
You're the only one on my side,
aren't you, Anp?
[ANP]
Hurry up and feed me, will you?
[SAIKI]
Did you forget he's the one
who broke it in the first place?
[KUNIHARU] I'll go get you
some food, okay?
[snickers]
[ANP]
Humans really are simple.
But the boy
hasn't budged at all.
Normally when a stray cat
shows up,
people flip out and cater
to our every whim.
Hello, kitty-witty.
Where'd you come from? Meow!
[ANP] When will he finally
bow to my will?
What? He's holding me.
I knew his heart
would melt.
No human can resist
the undeniable cuteness
of cats forever.
Hey, let me in, you jerk!
[SAIKI] He's as loud as ever.
[ANP] Come on, open the door!
At least let me eat!
What is that?
Looks like it's edible.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's your food.
Huh? Kusuo,
where did Anp go?
[doorbell rings]
That's a lie.
[SAIKI]
Mom's allergic to cats,
so we can't let him
inside the house.
Well, yeah, I know that,
but still-- Wait, what happened?
Come here, Kusuo.
Anp is unconscious.
[SAIKI] Looks like it.
Call an ambulance.
No, that won't work.
What's the number
for a pet ambulance?
Is it different?
Meow, meow?
Do we have to call
nine-meow-meow?
[SAIKI] Calm down.
I know what happened.
He choked on one
of the model pieces.
Seriously?
Well, can't you take it out?
Turn back time on him
or something.
[SAIKI]
That won't work.
Since I already used my
restoring power on the model,
even if I turn back time on Anp,
the piece will be there.
Well, we have to do something!
[SAIKI] Don't worry.
There are still two ways
to get it out.
I don't care! Just save him!
[SAIKI] Sure.
Then I'll go with Plan A.
I'll just cut off his head and
then take the model piece out.
[KUNIHARU] Let's do Plan B.
[SAIKI] I'd prefer Plan A,
'cause it's easier,
but oh, well.
Wait. Where'd you go?
[SAIKI] I'm here.
What just happened to you,
Kusuo? You're so tiny now.
[SAIKI] Keep it down.
I'm one-hundredth size now.
This way I can enter his body.
You really can do anything.
This is freaky.
[SAIKI]
Don't touch me.
You're not gonna get eaten
while you're in there, are you?
[SAIKI] Even if that happens,
I'll just teleport back out.
What happened?
Is there a problem?
[SAIKI] His breath stinks.
There's nothing cute about it.
Don't just stand there!
[SAIKI] You're right.
It's as bad outside
as it is inside.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
[SAIKI] I took it out.
[KUNIHARU] Whoa, nice work.
[ANP] Gasp.
You did it.
Look, he's coming to.
[SAIKI] He actually said
the word "gasp."
[ANP] My dead grandmother
was beckoning me
from the other side
of the river.
[SAIKI]
Talk about a lucky cat.
[KUNIHARU] Look at him.
He's so cute when he's sleeping.
Why don't you--
Wait, why are you still small?
[SAIKI] Once I shrink,
I don't go back to normal
for at least an hour.
Hey, where are you going?
[SAIKI] Bathroom.
Hey, don't just go off
on your own.
I don't wanna step on you
by mistake.
Hang on.
I've gotta be stronger
than him now, right?
This is finally my chance
to show him
his father
is the bigger man.
[SAIKI]
Don't fall by mistake.
After all,
you're the bigger man.
Oh, you're right.
Of course I am.
[SAIKI] The bathroom seems
so far away when I'm this size.
Might as well teleport.
Hm, probably wasn't even
a drop's worth.
Man, being this size
is a pain.
Hey, I found some money
under the fridge.
Guess being this size
isn't all bad.
[MALE NARRATOR] At that moment,
the darkest of fears
entered Saiki's mind.
It was a sense of dread
unlike any
he had ever
experienced before.
[SAIKI] He's following me.
I can't lose him like this.
I need longer legs.
What's happening?
Libeon!
[SAIKI]
Do something, bigger man.
Cockroach! Help me!
[SAIKI] It's flying right at me.
This is it!
Chow time.
Hey, what's with
the sudden affection?
[SAIKI] I've changed my mind
about you, Anp.
[Kongou laughing]
[SAIKI]
That's Kongou from Year Three.
[KONGOU] I'm gonna bump into
that kid and steal his money.
[SAIKI] I can read people's
minds using telepathy,
and predict their moves.
Why'd you move around like that?
Give me your money.
[SAIKI]
What a pain.
Even when I read his mind,
it ends this way.
Are you trying to make me look
bad here, you little jerk?
[SAIKI] I've already
set a plan in motion
to deal with this
Neanderthal.
See, there's more than one way
of using telepathy.
Hey! What are you doing?
[SAIKI]
Sending telepathic messages.
Knock it off, Kongou!
You're graduating soon,
aren't you?
Or would you rather
repeat Year Three?
Oh, come on, man.
That's unfair.
This has nothing to do
with me graduating.
[SAIKI]
I beg to differ.
You want to graduate,
change your attitude.
And you can start by fixing
your hairstyle and clothes!
Shut up, okay? I know all that.
I'm planning to clean up my act.
That's why I was trying
to shake this loser down.
I need cash to pay
for a new haircut.
[SAIKI]
Your logic's a little off.
[KONGOU] I'll get you for this!
[MATSUZAKI] Hold it!
Sorry about that.
That kid's a former student
of mine.
Despite his flaws,
I'd like to see him graduate.
[SAIKI]
That's impossible.
[clock bell ringing]
Man, I'm so pissed off
right now.
[SAIKI]
Him again?
If that stupid four-eyes had
just given me his damn money...
[SAIKI]
Sorry for not being a victim.
Hey, good timing.
Give me all your money.
[SAIKI]
He's doing it again.
The guy's a disgrace
to our school.
[WOMAN 1] What's going on?
[MAN] Looks like he's wearing
a PK Academy uniform.
[WOMAN 2] What are his teachers
teaching him?
[SAIKI] I don't really care
if he repeats Year Three,
but I can't let him tarnish
our school's reputation.
Hurry up and give me
your shiitake.
I know you have shiitake.
What shiitake?
[KONGOU] No, not "shiitake."
I said "shiitake."
What's going on?
This is crazy.
I can't think of anything
besides shiitake.
[SAIKI] I can disrupt
someone's thinking
just by sending a torrent
of thoughts into their mind.
By the way, "shiitake" was just
off the top of my head.
You know, there's a grocery
store just down the street.
[KONGOU] Hey, hold it.
Shiitake. I want shiitake.
[WOMAN 1] Oh, he was just asking
for mushrooms.
[WOMAN 2] Nothing wrong
with mushrooms.
[grunts]
[KONGOU]
What the hell was that?
Just have to use
my own money.
[SAIKI]
Hm? Barbershop? Oh, right.
That's the excuse he gave
for shaking me down.
So I guess he was serious about
fixing that terrible hairstyle.
What would you
like today?
[SAIKI] Hey, your hair
doesn't look half bad that way.
I'm gonna be graduating soon,
so I wanna have
a respectable haircut.
You know, something really
classy, like a punch perm.
[BARBER]
Absolutely.
[SAIKI] There's nothing
respectable about a punch perm.
He'll look like a gangster.
As it stands, he has no chance
of graduating.
Telepathic Lullaby.
[WOMAN]
♪ Sleep, sleep... ♪
[SAIKI]
That was fast.
Actually, I want
a different look.
[BARBER]
Sir. Sir. We're all done.
Oh, yeah? That was quick.
Cool. Let me have a look.
[screams]
What'd you do?
Where'd my hair go?
[BARBER]
You said you wanted a buzz cut.
[KONGOU]
I asked for a punch perm!
Huh, this kind of looks
that celebrity ABZO.
Wait, no!
I'm gonna give you
a reverse Mohawk!
[SAIKI]
ABZO.
[KONGOU]
Huh? ABZO?
That's right!
You look just like
that celebrity.
[KONGOU] Really?
[BARBER] Really.
[GIRL] Good morning.
[BOY] Morning.
Huh, so you got
a buzz cut, huh?
Well, don't think that's enough
to help you graduate.
Your uniform violates
the dress code.
Fix it by tomorrow.
[KONGOU]
Just you wait.
I'll get you back for this
after graduation...
[SAIKI] He shouldn't be allowed
to graduate.
He's still
the same delinquent inside.
You're that four-eyed jerk
from yesterday!
[SAIKI]
You're so clueless.
Immediate telepathy.
By touching him, I can send
images telepathically.
[groans]
[SAIKI] Every time the school
receives a complaint about you,
Mr. Matsuzaki
has to apologize.
And he always stays late
after school
so that the other teachers
won't pick up the phone instead.
Then yesterday, after receiving
no complaint calls
for the first time ever,
he saw you with a buzz cut
and now he's got a lump
in his throat.
I hope that knowledge
helps you.
No way.
Is that really Kongou?
[BOY]
What happened to him?
Wow, Kongou, is that...?
[KONGOU] Yes, sir.
And I'm grateful to you for
everything you've done for me.
I'll be sure to remember you
after I graduate this year.
Kongou, I'm afraid you have
to repeat Year Three after all.
They said that you missed
too many days.
But if you work hard now,
then next year.
[KONGOU]
No!
[MATSUZAKI]
Kongou!
[SAIKI]
Now who's gonna win?
[NENDOU]
See you at the finals.
[SAIKI]
There are no finals.
[upbeat music plays]
♪ We all have a-- ♪
[music stops]
Hey, who hit cancel?
What are you gonna sing, Saiki?
[SAIKI]
I didn't come to sing.
I came to eat this.
Grand chocolate parfait.
Dazzling.
Okay, it's been ordered.
Hey, Saiki, since this is about
making memories as a class,
we have a rule that everyone
has to sing at least once.
[SAIKI]
People have that attitude
when they do karaoke as a group.
I hate it, but oh, well.
I'll eat the parfait and leave
before my turn comes up.
I'll just enter
a random song number.
Some crazy song got reserved,
but I won't be singing it.
I'll relax and wait
for my parfait.
[BOY 1] The moment we've been
waiting for!
[BOY 2] Our class idol
is singing!
I'm a little embarrassed.
[BOY 1] We get to hear
Teruhashi sing!
[BOY 2] Her singing voice
is as pretty as she is!
[SAIKI]
She hasn't sung yet.
[TERUHASHI]
I see you out there, Saiki.
Welcome to my concert.
[SAIKI]
It's not your concert.
[TERUHASHI]
I know what you're thinking.
She's that pretty
and has a great personality.
There's no way she could be all
that and great at singing too.
Maybe she'll turn out
to be a horrible singer.
♪ I'm super-duper good
At singing ♪
♪ 'Cause I am the perfect
Pretty girl ♪
♪ You know I'm awesome
At everything ♪
♪ Don't bother trying
To resist me ♪
♪ I'm such a cute and kind
And pretty girl ♪
♪ But soon enough ♪
♪ You're going to say it to me ♪
♪ Oh, you'll say it to me ♪
[SAIKI] Ignoring her singing,
those lyrics are awful.
Well, then,
guess I'm up next.
Wow, you could definitely
be a pro singer.
That really moved me.
You should become a pro singer,
Kokomi.
[TERUHASHI]
What? No, I'm not that good.
♪ The lost sheep stands
Before the corpse... ♪
[SAIKI] Somebody pay attention
to the lost sheep behind you.
Nice bloody.
[WAITER] Thanks for waiting.
Who ordered
the grand chocolate parfait?
[SAIKI] It's here.
[BOY] That's mine!
[SAIKI] Someone else ordered one
before me?
Wow, came right after
I ordered it.
[BOY]
Has it even been a minute?
[SAIKI]
Hey, that's mine.
I've been waiting
for 15 minutes.
This is ridiculous.
I just wanna take it,
but no.
It's good.
[SAIKI]
When it's your turn to sing,
I'm gonna create feedback
during the absolute best part
of the song.
Enjoy the awkward moment.
I have to wait
another 15 minutes?
At least there are nine songs
reserved before mine.
It'll come before then.
[MAN] Okay, who's next?
Oh, I am, I am!
[SAIKI] You? Seriously?
I'm just gonna block my hearing.
Hey, buddy,
let's sing a duet.
[SAIKI]
What's the gorilla saying now?
Nendou and Saiki
are doing a duet.
I think it'd be fun to see that.
[SAIKI] Shoot.
We're drawing attention.
[BOY] Do it! Do it!
[SAIKI]
I have no choice.
Everybody calm down.
It'll be-- It's back.
All right. We're back, buddy.
Huh? Buddy?
[SAIKI] Pretty scary you can't
predict things like that.
But I can't give up now.
I'm gonna eat
that grand chocolate parfait
no matter what obstacles
stand in my way.
Should be okay now.
Hm? Why is it so quiet?
Hey, Kaidou,
what happened?
Oh, no, he's dead!
Saiki. Help.
[SAIKI] Oh. He's alive.
So, what happened?
[KAIDOU]
After the lights came back on,
Nendou decided
to sing alone.
What followed was pure hell.
It's as if we were forced
to listen to an orchestra
of the world's
most unpleasant sounds
playing as loud
as humanly possible.
Just before
I lost consciousness,
I remember thinking,
"If Death really does exist,
this must be what it
sounds like."
[SAIKI] Now I'm really curious
to hear it.
[NENDOU]
Huh? What's wrong?
Oh, you fell asleep listening
to my gentle singing voice.
In that case, I'll sing
something up-tempo...
[SAIKI]
I wonder how bad it really was.
Oh, are you the one who ordered
that dessert, Saiki?
One of the waiters brought it
here earlier,
but nobody claimed it,
and then he couldn't escape.
[SAIKI]
Thank you, brave waiter.
Your death will not
have been in vain.
Now to--
[HAIRO] Hey, you're up, Saiki.
[SAIKI] What?
My song's the eighth one down.
You picked "Go, Go, Go,
Wild Samba," right?
[SAIKI] How?
[HAIRO] After the blackout
erased all the reserved songs,
I re-entered what I remembered.
- [SAIKI] Damn it.
- Look, it's Saiki's turn.
- "Go, Wild Samba"?
- Seriously, that's his pick?
[GIRL] Crush it, Saiki.
[HAIRO] Go, go, go on.
[SAIKI]
This is bad.
Looks like my first real
line will be,
"Oh, yes, go wild."
No thanks.
[BOY]
Hey, where you going?
Are you trying to sneak away?
- [SAIKI] I'm not doing this.
- A duet?
[all scream]
[BOY]
I gotta go to the bathroom!
[GIRL]
Me, too. I'm about to burst!
[SAIKI]
Finally I can eat.
Yeah, buddy, let's jam!
[singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI] To recap,
I forgot my wallet,
shrunk down to tiny size,
and almost went wild.
Another crazy episode.
But I got to eat
a grand chocolate parfait,
so it wasn't all bad.
On the next Disastrous Life
of Saiki K.,
we'll go to the countryside, and
you get to meet my grandparents.