[SAIKI] When I woke up,
our hotel had vanished!
Is this all your fault, Saiki?
What happened to
everyone inside the building?
Did you just kill an
entire high school class?
[SAIKI] Shut up. I have
to concentrate on bringing back
the hotel exactly how it was.
Looks like it came off the
foundation in one piece,
so everyone should be alive.
Had I used psychokinesis,
they'd all be dead.
I must've just teleported
it somewhere else.
Hey, Saiki, I see
something down there!
How can you be sure
everyone's still alive?
[SAIKI]
Well, I'm pretty sure.
I mean, in all
likelihood they're fine.
Look, there's nothing there.
Aaaah! They are dead!
You killed them, you jerk!
And not just the dumb guys,
but all the hotties, too!
[SAIKI] Calm down. These aren't
our classmates from the hotel.
High school girls are
a treasure that... Uh?
Augh! What the hell is that?
[SAIKI] An old shipwreck,
and if it's here,
it must contain treasure
equal in value to the hotel.
In paranormal terms,
the two objects switched places
or "apported," which means
the hotel is now--at sea!
Weird. Guess the power
was out. That sucks.
I don't sleep well
if it's pitch black.
[KASHIMURA] Maybe they turn
off the power for "lights-out"?
[ZOLBE] Whoa. Do you
think they would do that?
[MATSUO] Power-schmower,
let's talk about girls!
[ZOLBE]
No! The AC's off, too!
[MATSUO]
Don't change the subject, Zolbe.
You're the only one here
who hasn't said who he likes!
[ZOLBE] Hairo never
answered you, either!
[MATSUO] We couldn't ask him,
'cause he went to bed at eight!
You can say any girl you
want, except Teruhashi.
I mean, she's the obvious
choice, so that's dumb.
Has to be from school.
Aren't you guys hot in here?
I'm gonna open the window.
Um, what's with the water?
What? Earlier you
were complaining
we couldn't see any of
the ocean from our hotel!
But now it's like,
there's water everywhere.
[MATSUO]
What're you saying,
there's been a
tsunami or something?
No, it's like our room moved.
[MATSUO]
What water?
[ZOLBE]
We were just in the ocean!
[MATSUO]
You really do need a nightlight.
Hey! Right on cue!
[SAIKI]
What a pain. That was close.
Holy crap! It came
back instantaneously!
So everything's
fixed now, right?
[SAIKI]
Not yet.
Huh?
[SAIKI] Give me back
the antenna you pulled out.
What? Oh, your little
barrette thingy's gone?
I didn't notice.
[SAIKI]
Give it.
Hey! Don't hurt me. I didn't
take your pink head ball,
I swear!
[SAIKI]
Eh? What?
With ghosts-as-my-witness,
I don't know anything
about your antenna!
I'm telling the truth!
[SAIKI] I actually do believe
him now. So who did take it?
[YUMEHARA] Kokomi still
isn't back, and it's already
lights out! She's broken
curfew and then some!
I hate to tattle, but
it's time to tell a teacher.
I agree.
Plus, Kokomi isn't the type to
just disappear without telling.
I'll go find someone!
[SAIKI]
So it was Teruhashi!
She's the one who
took my control device,
and now she's vanished!
Well, more like, my powers
made her disappear.
Just like the hotel
and the ship,
she must've switched
with something.
But what? Nothing
suddenly appeared over here.
Okay, calm down. I can use
clairvoyance to find her.
[gasps]
[SAIKI]
Good! She's okay!
Oh, what kind of face
is that supposed to be?
[TERUHASHI whimpers]
[SAIKI]
She's not okay!
It'll get stuck that way.
Hey, where did you go?!
Saiki?
[SAIKI] Uh-oh. I don't have
any cover story this time.
I guess I'll have to tell
Teruhashi about my powers.
Is this a dream?
[TORITSUKA] Hey, Saiki!
What is wrong with you, man?
You disappear more
than the ghosts I see.
[YUMEHARA]
There you are!
Where on Earth have you been?
You had us so worried,
we broke curfew
and snuck outta
the room to find you!
[TORITSUKA]
You're worried about me?
I'm so glad!
Me, too!
[TORITSUKA]
Whatever's going on here,
it looks like the
chicks finally dig me!
But... never scare us
like that again, Kokomi.
[MERA] And you know, you still
haven't told us where you went.
You think I'm
Teruhashi? Serious?
[YUMEHARA]
Did you lose your memory?
[MERA]
I bet she's sleepwalking.
[TORITSUKA] No. Saiki
must've done something!
[SAIKI]
Indeed, mass hypnosis.
To the girls, you appear
and sound like Teruhashi.
I would've used it
for myself, but I can't.
Trust me, this was the best way
to keep things from
getting out of hand.
[TORITSUKA] Now all the guys
are gonna be drooling after me,
and I want the girls! Why do I
get stuck being your guinea pig?
[YUMEHARA]
Well, let's go.
What? Go, where?
Where else, Kokomi?
Back to our hotel room!
We gotta be back in
time for bed checks!
[TORITSUKA]
Saiki. Thank you so much!
[MERA] Teruhashi,
your nose is bleeding!
[SAIKI]
So long as he doesn't ruin this
by doing anything stupid,
I've got things back
there cleaned up.
Now, I just need to swap him
with the real Teruhashi.
[TERUHASHI]
Oh, Saiki.
[SAIKI]
Provided I can get her off me.
[SAIKI] What a pain. How'm
I gonna get outta this one?
Oh, wow, I've never had
a lucid dream before,
it feels so realistic!
[SAIKI] In a lucid dream,
you're asleep,
but you're still aware
that you're dreaming.
This means that you
can do anything you want.
Teruhashi has mistakenly
convinced herself
she's in the middle of one.
Saiki.
[SAIKI] Normally, I could
turn this to my advantage.
What do you think of
our dream date so far, Saiki?
[SAIKI]
But there's one problem.
Wow, everything feels
like it's really happening!
I'm playing with
your face because I can!
[SAIKI] I still don't have
my control device back.
And that means I can't use
any of my psychic powers
without hurting her.
For example, normally
I'd just chop her on the neck
to knock her out and then
take her back to the hotel.
That sounds creepier
than I meant it to.
Anyway, without that device,
it doesn't matter
which power, I use.
Anything I touch
could be destroyed,
so knocking her out
is a definite no-no.
Even the slightest tap
could pop her head clean off!
And as for the arm
I mentioned earlier,
the tiniest muscle
spasm could rocket her
into the upper atmosphere.
Heck, she might even go into
orbit. So because of all that,
I've got one option:
Get her to fall asleep for real.
--[SINGER] ♪ Sleep, sleep, ♪
--Do you hear a weird song,
--♪ go to sleep... ♪
--or is that just me?
[SAIKI] Only thing that
won't kill her is to repeat
this lullaby in her head,
over and over.
[TERUHASHI]
Wait! Where am I anyway?
This is weird,
and I don't like it anymore.
[SAIKI] I didn't like
it from the beginning.
Wait, I can just use the
power of lucid dreaming
to pick a new spot for us!
All right, get ready for a
fairy tale castle! And go!
Huh? It's not working.
Wait, does that mean
that I'm not lucid dreaming?
Wow! This is amazing!
The interior's not quite
as pretty as I imagined,
but it'll do for now.
[SAIKI]
Don't be so picky.
It's the best I could
do on short notice.
I like being able to do
whatever I want in my dreams.
Although I pretty much do
whatever I want
in real life, already.
[TERUHASHI]
Whatever I want.
I know! Saiki! Look at me,
and say, "Oh, wow."
As part of my dream,
you must do as I say.
And I'm commanding
you to look at me
and finally say, "Oh, wow."
[TERUHASHI] Oh... Why do I
suddenly feel so tired?
I'm already sleeping
in order to dream this.
Maybe my body's just
switching from a light sleep
to a deep one.
[SAIKI]
It's 2 am our time.
No! I won't sleep till
Dream Saiki says, "Oh, wow!"
[SAIKI]
Don't you need your beauty rest?
Now, kneel down, Saiki,
and say, "Oh, wow."
Oh, wow.
[squeals] That's it!
Saiki finally said it!
I'm so happy! And he bluuh...
Ah! I was just in the girls'
hotel room, now where am I?
[SAIKI]
I made him appear as me to her,
and now I can get some sleep.
Uh, Saiki, you wanna avoid
saying, "Oh, wow" that badly?
[SAIKI]
Yes.
[alarm clock ringing]
[SAIKI]
Man. I needed that.
Even just three hours in
your own bed is better
than eight in a hotel with
people you can't stand.
All right.
[SAIKI] Guess I'll have
to work hard today too.
[KAIDOU] When did you
go back to the room?
I don't remember
seeing you at lights-out.
Did you go somewhere?
[SAIKI]
Nowhere interesting.
Just a little trip abroad.
[TERUHASHI sighs] After that
strange dream last night,
I can't even look at Saiki
without feeling weird,
but was totally worth it
to hear him say, "Oh, wow."
By the way, you were
acting strangely last night.
As soon as we got back to
the hotel room, you yelled at
all the girls to take off their
clothes so you could wrestle!
What?! I didn't do that!
[SAIKI]
That idiot!
Right! Finish up breakfast,
and get on the bus!
We're going to the
pineapple farm first,
and then the aquarium, right?
Yep, and those are just
the warm up activities,
because this afternoon is
when we go to the beach!
[YUMEHARA]
For a whole month,
I've dedicated my life
to this very moment.
To get bikini-ready,
I haven't eaten any sweets!
And I've worked out every
single day to lose weight!
Since we got here
I've cheated on my diet
a little tiny bit, but the fact
remains--I did it all for you.
Yumehara! Or should I say,
my sunshine baby doll?
[MALE VOICE A]
Sunshine. Crazy.
[YUMEHARA] On top of
all the dieting and training,
I even bought a new
swimsuit just for today!
I'll do whatever it takes
to get Saiki to notice me!
[SAIKI] Oh, man. I have
to worry about you again?
[SAIKI]
Which card is Kaidou?
What do your psychic
senses tell you?
[SAIKI]
Day two in Okinawa,
and the excitement has
reached a fever pitch,
with a trip to a pineapple farm.
I always thought pineapples
were shaped like a donut!
[YUMEHARA]
No, Mera! Don't gorge! Take one!
But I want them all!
[TORITSUKA]
Perky pineapples.
[SAIKI] Why does this creep
turn everything into that?
On to the aquarium.
[NENDOU]
Whoa! It's huge!
I bet this thing's Capture
Level is twenty, at least!
Ha! So your world is shrouded
in darkness too, huh?
Wow, even the fish
are attracted to Teruhashi!
[BOY STUDENT A]
Bet they think she's a mermaid!
[SAIKI] And now we get to
Yumehara's ultimate destination.
Emerald Beach, whoo!
[SAIKI]
Hey, move!
[NENDOU] Whoa! Ain't got no
beaches like this back home.
Where're the girls? Hmm?
What do you think
that's all about?
The beach is great,
but wait until you see
these natural wonders.
I wouldn't miss this
moment for anything!
It's the only reason
I came on this stupid trip!
Here she comes!
Thanks for waiting!
[ALL gasping]
[NARRATOR A]
And it wasn't just the boys,
but the entire beach
that erupted in applause.
[TERUHASHI] I had a
hard time finding a locker.
No prob! We're happy to wait!
That's right. It's no biggie!
[TERUHASHI]
Ugh! What's it gonna take
to get the real Saiki
to go, "Oh, wow"?
Well, all right then.
I think it's time for a swim.
Wait, Yumehara and
Mera aren't here yet.
Well, that's weird, I just
saw them in the locker room.
Hey! Yumehara, let's go!
[YUMEHARA]
I-I can't do it!
How'm I supposed go
out there after Kokomi?
Get a grip, Chiyo.
You've worked too
hard to give up now.
Your weight's never been lower
and your swimsuit's
never been tighter!
Kokomi's reign is over!
It's my time!
Sorry for the wait!
I had trouble
finding my sunscreen.
Wait, I don't even
get a camera pan?!
Move this word!
[YUMEHARA] And why don't
I get any sparkles?!
Now we're just waiting for Mera.
Oh, right.
[YUMEHARA]
What? What is this?
No reaction?
They've already moved on?
[MERA]
I'm sorry!
My suit shrank in the dryer,
so I had trouble putting it on.
[YUMEHARA] Mera gets a
sexy camera tilt close-up,
and you let her stand and pose?
She's got a pretty rocking body.
Yeah, even in that grandma
one-piece she looks hot.
[BOY STUDENT R] Oh, mama,
I'd love to go downhill skiing
on those mountains.
[MERA] Wish I ate that
extra bowl of rice at lunch!
[YUMEHARA]
They're still gawking at her?
[MERA]
I'm so hungry.
[BOY STUDENT L]
Wait, her name's Nakao?
[YUMEHARA]
Why does it say that?
Who cares, as long as Saiki
notices me, today was worth it.
Nendou, where'd Saiki go?
Oh, he said he was
goin' up ahead to do stuff.
[YUMEHARA]
He didn't even check me out!
Well, it's all over now.
All that sacrifice for nothing.
Trip's a total waste.
Hey. Aren't you
gonna go swimming?
No. Go away, I don't feel good.
Um, are you saying
that you can't swim?
Because I know someone
with the same problem.
I can swim,
I just wanna be alone.
Go without me.
I would, if I hadn't been cursed
by mighty Poseidon,
God of the Ocean!
Whenever seawater
touches my chaste body,
it burns like a thousand suns!
Curse those petty
tyrants of Olympus!
That sounds like a stupid way
of saying you can't swim.
[KAIDOU]  Huh...? That's
not true, I can swim!
[YUMEHARA] Wait. Did he just
blush when he saw my body?
He did, didn't he?!
And now he's looking away in
shame at how I made him feel!
[TERUHASHI]
Kaidou!
Hey. Did a ball roll over here?
[KAIDOU] No! No, I didn't
see anything! I'm innocent!
[YUMEHARA]
He rolled backwards three times?
I can't believe how
much bigger his reaction is
to her than to me!
Life is so unfair! Someone!
Please say I'm cute!
[MAN A] Dude.
That girl over there's cute!
What's that?
[MAN A]
Hey! You in the blue!
Huh?
Whoa, you look pretty hot.
Come with us, and we'll
buy you a shaved ice.
[TERUHASHI]
What?
These beach bros really think
they have a chance with me?
[MAN A] What are you waiting
for? We'll cool you off, hottie.
[TERUHASHI]
Got more muscles than sense
if they think
I'm in their league.
I know I'm every
guy's dream girl,
but going after a
perfect ten-plus like me
makes them seem like idiots.
Then again,
just 'cause they look dumb
doesn't mean they're poor.
If one of them has a net worth
of at least 40 million yen,
I'll look the other way
on this pick-up.
[SAIKI]
Who are these two idiots?
[TERUHASHI] Yeah, what
if their families are rich?
[SAIKI] Fine. I'll help
before she gets hurt.
[KAIDOU]
Let her go!
She's doesn't want it,
now get lost!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[SAIKI]
We're halfway through day two
of our big school
trip to Okinawa,
and there's a situation
with Teruhashi
and some "guys"
on Emerald Beach.
She's doesn't wanna!
Now get lost!
Huh?
Who the hell are you?
Uh, I'm just saying
she doesn't wanna go,
so leave her alone.
[MAN A] No, you leave,
this ain't your scene, bro!
No, she's my classmate, and
if you don't leave her alone,
I'll be forced to get
physical with you and stuff.
[MAN B]
Huh?! "Physical" with us?
Yeah. You guys'll
really regret it.
[YUMEHARA]
Cut it out, jerks!
[MEN]
Huh?
We're a group of students
on a school trip,
and if you don't stop putting
the moves on my friend,
I'll have no choice
but to tell a teacher!
Wow. I'm shakin'
in my boat shoes.
No one was talking to you, girl.
[MAN A] Yeah, we're
not interested in talking
to an ugly chick like you.
Bet you don't even
care about her.
You're just jealous
she gets hit on.
[MAN A laughs]
Take that back!
Apologize to Chiyo!
[MAN A]
The hell was that for?!
[KAIDOU] Say you're sorry,
or I keep punching!
Oh, you are really
asking for it now.
That hurt-- Huh?
Actually it doesn't hurt at all.
Did you even make contact?
From this angle, it looks
more like a tiny mosquito bite.
First I was mad you punched me,
but now I'm madder at
what a weakling you are!
[KAIDOU squeaks]
[SAIKI]
No, it wasn't a weak punch.
Owwww!
What's wrong?
[SAIKI]
Delayed pain.
Courtesy of the
"Jet Black Wings Fist of Rage."
[KAIDOU]
Uh... Is this my fault?
Ha-ha! Those guys really
weren't so tough, after all.
Are you okay?
I can't believe some
people are that rude.
[NARRATOR A]
What Yumehara sees.
Yumehara, don't
let them bother you.
[NARRATOR A]
What Yumehara hears.
[KAIDOU] You're lookin'
kinda cute today, Chiyo.
[YUMEHARA]
Kaidou. You're amazing!
[SAIKI]
Good job, Kaidou.
[NARRATOR A] And with that, the
second day of their trip ended.
And their final day
on Okinawa began.
Hard to believe this
trip's almost over, buddy.
It felt like we were
here just a few days.
That's 'cause we were
[SAIKI] It's felt like
a few weeks to me.
[KAIDOU yawns]
Hey! You need more sleep, man,
that's why you're so short.
It's your fault I didn't
sleep on this trip!
[SAIKI] This is how Kaidou
remembers last night.
You snore as loud
as a lawn mower!
You sounded so bad I got worried
and went to check on you,
but that's when...
...you scared the hell outta me!
Why do you sleep with
your eyes rolled back?
Hey, look who's talkin', pal,
you were pretty noisy yourself!
[KAIDOU]
No way!
You've been muttering in
your sleep every night here!
[SAIKI] Great.
Now you're doing a flashback?
[KAIDOU]
What's this power?
It's out of control!
[NENDOU] I wanted to shut you
up, but then I saw your face!
I can't breathe.
[NENDOU]
Creepy!
[KAIDOU] I can't sleep
without a blanket on my head!
At least my sleep talking
is better than your snoring!
Yeah, but it's even
louder than my snoring!
[SAIKI] I had to
sleep through both of you.
I'm the real victim.
Well, that's in the past.
Let's enjoy our last day here.
Yeah! It's time to
buy some souvenirs!
[SAIKI]
You buy your knickknacks.
I've still got something
far more important to do.
On the way here, I read--
Oops, I guess I'm doing
a flashback now, too.
Anyway, I read a magazine
and I discovered this!
That's right. The best and
rarest dessert available
on Okinawa's
International Avenue:
Coffee Red Bean Anmitsu .
They only make five
of them a day,
at one hole-in-the-wall joint.
Although, after
it's been featured
in a major airline's magazine,
it can't really be called a
"hole-in-the-wall." Anyway!
I vowed right then and there
I wouldn't go home
until I try this dessert.
But in order to do so,
I need to split from the group.
I mean, you've seen
what those two are like.
They'll ruin the
whole experience.
Hey. Where'd the ladies go?
Yeah, I haven't seen 'em today.
[SAIKI]
Thanks to a certain stomach,
the girls never get
anywhere on time,
which is good for me.
[YUMEHARA] Mera! We're late
meeting up with the guys!
Chinsuko is so good!
C'mon, it's our
last day, let's go!
You really have to
learn some self-control
when you see a
"free sample" sign, Mera!
Y'know, I can't think
of a moment this trip
when she hasn't had
food in her mouth.
Uh! We'll never catch up
with the guys now!
Yumehara, if you're that bored,
why don't you go ahead,
and I'll stay with Mera?
What?
[TERUHASHI] I want you
to have fun with them.
Especially Kaidou.
[YUMEHARA]
What?! Uh... No!
I don't have a crush on
Kaidou, don't be silly...
Oops! I'm sorry.
I've been under the impression
you had feelings for Kaidou.
[SAIKI]
All right, so I'm not gonna have
to worry about the girls,
but as for them...
[NENDOU] Do I like bitter
melon? Or do I hate it?
[KAIDOU] You ate
a whole plate at the hotel!
[SAIKI] I gotta ditch
them no matter what
if I wanna get one
of those Anmitsu .
[KAIDOU] I take it you sensed
my powerful wave energy?
[SAIKI]
Oh, shut up!
[SAIKI] We're right
back where we left off:
The last day of the
school trip to Okinawa.
And there is only one thing
I want to do, or rather eat,
before I go home:
Coffee Red Bean Anmitsu .
But to eat that,
I need to lose them...
...because they
are complete idiots.
[YUMEHARA] Ah! I can't
believe Teruhashi figured out
I like Kaidou so easily!
I didn't know I was
so obvious about it.
Sort of, yeah.
But don't worry,
I won't tell anyone!
No, you certainly will not,
because I know
who you like, Kokomi.
What?
You like Nend--
No, stop! Don't say it!
I won't tell who you like,
so long as you
never tell who I like!
[TERUHASHI]
If she says his name out loud,
I think I'll have
a total meltdown!
[YUMEHARA chuckles]
'Kay, deal.
Then whaddaya say we catch up
with the boys, together?
Yeah, and let's grab Mera
before she ends up hurt.
[YUMEHARA] She really
abused the free sample policy.
Hey, um, shouldn't you call
me by my first name now?
Huh?
Yumehara, sounds
kinda formal, right?
You know who my crush is,
for crying out loud.
Call me Chiyo!
We've totally bonded this trip.
Um, sure... Chiyo.
[YUMEHARA]
Doesn't that feel right, Kokomi?
That's so sweet.
I said stop eating!
[SAIKI] So, the girls are still
fine, but as for these two...
[POPS]
Hey, you! Cool guy!
Cool?
You like this purple t-shirt?
Yeah, I've been lookin'
for more purple!
[POPS]
It's cool, right?
Well, there's your souvenir!
Wow, are you sure?
Thanks for the shirt, Pops!
[POPS] I appreciate
your business-- Hey!
You didn't pay!
[NENDOU] Sounded like
you were givin' it to me!
[POPS]
I was givin' you the pitch!
I'm not handing away
my best inventory for free!
[SHOP OWNER B]
I'll give you a discount, kid.
[SAIKI]
Hm?
[KAIDOU]
Hmm.
I already bought snake powder
with my souvenir money.
It's normally 28 thousand yen,
but just for you I'll knock
it down to three grand.
Wow, you mean it?
Well, I'll take it!
Look, kid, how about I just make
it, "buy one, get one free."
Whoa! So, if I buy this one,
you'll make this one free?
That's not how it works!
[KAIDOU]
Hey Nendou, where'd Saiki go?
Huh? Hey! Buddy! Where are you?
[SAIKI]
Yes! I escaped!
No one stands between me and
my Coffee Red Bean Anmitsu .
Plenty of time.
I'm all but guaranteed
to score one of the five.
All I have to do is walk there.
[TAKAHASHI groans]
[YOKOTA]
What's wrong?
[SAIKI]
Hm?
My... My stomach hurts!
[SAIKI]
Takahashi's still here?
I could swear that stomachache
sent him home yesterday?
Wait, now I remember.
Ow!
[SAIKI] Just like on the plane,
I turned back time.
My stomach... is fine?
[SAIKI] But we're going home
soon, no point in helping again.
[MURATA]
Hey, Saiki!
Get a teacher before he spews!
[SAIKI]
Get one yourself.
Man, this is annoying.
Thanks, man.
I knew you'd help.
Just go find anyone!
You're saving a life!
[SAIKI]
You're so dramatic.
Hang in there, Takahashi!
[SAIKI]
Seriously?
I just wasted precious time
on an upset stomach.
Oh, well. At least there's no
one left to stand in my way.
[MUGAMI]
There you are!
[SAIKI]
Right on cue, the pervy brother.
Where's my Kokomi?!
[SAIKI] He came all
the way down to Okinawa?
Your famous big brother
skipped the filming
of Jump Police
just to be with you!
[SAIKI] You skipped out
on TV Tokyo again?
[MUGAMI]
Now, where is she?
Kokomi! I missed you!
[TANNED GIRL A]
Huh?!
Who are you?
[TANNED GIRL A] Oh my God!
You're like Toru Mugami!
I'm a totes huge fan!
[SAIKI] Hypnosis might be
my most underrated power.
I finally made it!
[MALE SHOP OWNER C]
Good afternoon!
Hey, we've been
looking for ya, buddy!
Saiki, here!
We haven't seen you all day!
I'm surprised that
you found this place.
Now everyone in our
travel group is here!
[SAIKI] I knew it right
when I opened the door.
Take a seat anywhere.
Oh, you're here for
the red bean anmitsu ?
You sure picked the right place!
But I just sold today's
five servings to them.
[WAITRESS A]
Thank you for waiting.
All right!
[MERA]
Whoa, it looks delicious.
I wish they served
more than five a day!
[SAIKI]
So this is how my trip ends.
[NENDOU]
Come on! Sit down!
You can have some
of mine, buddy!
Yo! Give my friend a bowl!
[TERUHASHI]
Here. Have some of mine, too.
[MERA]
And mine!
[KAIDOU]
Mera's giving up food?
[MERA]
I ate too many samples earlier.
[NENDOU]
There! Your very own bowl!
[TERUHASHI, YUMEHARA]
It's huge!
[KAIDOU] Now Saiki has
the biggest serving!
Wait. Give some back.
Chow down, folks!
It's the last memory
we'll make on Okinawa!
[GROUP]
Cheers!
[SAIKI]
This isn't bad at all.
After three days of drama,
the Okinawa trip
ended without incident,
and we're settling back
into our old routines.
Next time, on The Disastrous
Life of Saiki K. !
Seriously?
Another transfer student?
Just what we didn't need.