♪
Who's ready for another
tres bien trick by me--
master illusionist
Uryoku Chouno?
Hey, Pink Hair, join the fun.
I'll do a trick to put
a smile on that face.
Ha, ha!
[SAIKI]
No, thanks. Already seen it.
Oh, I see you're a skeptic.
Well, once you see my show,
you will become a believer
in my powers to amaze. Ha, ha!
[SAIKI] Fine. I'll watch.
Just so he leaves me alone.
Right. I hold here
an ordinary cardboard box.
[SAIKI] Nope. There's nothing
ordinary about it.
[CHOUNO] As you can see,
it's empty inside.
[SAIKI] At that angle, they
can't tell there's a partition.
But watch.
Just a couple taps,
and it's party time.
Aren't they amazing, folks?
Hey there, kid.
Tres bien. Am I right?
[SAIKI]
It's not tres bien.
If anything,
I'm worried about that dove.
And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
please turn
your attention here
for the main event of our show,
my super illusion.
Magically teleporting
from one box to another
will be my lovely
assistant Michael.
[SAIKI]
Lovely is a stretch.
The beautiful Michael
is entering the box.
And drumroll.
[imitates drum roll]
[SAIKI]
This is so sad.
[CROWD murmuring]
[SAIKI] What expression am I
supposed to be making right now?
La, la, la, la!
[SAIKI] His overconfidence
makes me cringe.
I'm still worried
about this poor guy.
Does that hat have air holes?
All right, let's open the box.
[SAIKI] Uh-oh. Lovely Mike
isn't done teleporting yet.
[CHOUNO]
Three. Two. One.
It's party time.
--Yay.
--[CHOUNO] Tres bien.
[SAIKI] Now I really don't know
what sort of expression to make.
Yeah, that one
seems appropriate.
[MICHAEL]
That was the trick.
[CHOUNO] Why should I pay
you for ruining the illusion?
I moved at the normal speed.
It was your darn patter
that got too fast.
Now you hand over
that 500 yen.
No one tipped me
for this performance,
so I couldn't pay you,
even if I wanted to.
Hey, why are you
hanging around? What?
Oh, you want to give
me a tip? Heh heh.
I could never take
money from a kid.
The look of joy
on your face is--
Piko!
I completely forgot
she was up there.
[PIKO cooing]
[SAIKI] How can you forget
there's a dove on your head?
So you weren't trying to tip me.
You were trying to remind me.
Wait. Does that mean
that you're a magician?
That's how you knew
she was up there.
[SAIKI]
I should have kept walking.
With instincts that good,
you must've hated my show.
Maybe I'm not cut out for
the magician game after all.
Until a few months ago, I was
just your average office drone.
--Then I made a small mistake.
--[SAIKI] Oh, boy.
[CHOUNO]
Corporate fat cats laid me off,
then my wife skipped town.
[SAIKI]
Is it too late to walk away?
[CHOUNO] With no job, I couldn't
pay the mortgage anymore.
One little mistake,
and my career, wife, and home
had all disappeared.
And then it dawned on me.
I should become an illusionist.
--Yeah.
--[SAIKI] Wait. What?
Because so many things
had vanished from my life,
I thought it must mean that
disappearing them was my talent.
[SAIKI] Your only talent
is self-delusion.
So even though I'd been
offered another office job,
I turned it down to start
my new life doing street magic.
[SAIKI]
Again, what?
If I can save up
one million yen,
I can buy the
sawing-a-body-in-half trick.
Then my wife is
sure to come back.
[SAIKI]
Don't be so sure.
But then I wonder if
I chose the wrong path.
[SAIKI]
Yes. Yes, you did.
Now quit street magic
and get a real job.
Sorry. Didn't mean
to get so gloomy.
[SAIKI] What'll it take
for him to give up?
Let's get back to your
background as an illusionist
and how you knew
I had a dove up there.
[SAIKI]
That's it.
[CHOUNO] Whoa, gonna pull
something out of your bag?
[SAIKI] I'll do a trick that's
so beyond his ability,
he'll realize how far
gone he is and give up.
You're gonna pull out a dove.
Well, I'll have you know
that I can do a bowling ball.
[SAIKI]
Hm.
[MIKE]
Hey, hey.
[gasping]
That's impossible.
[SAIKI] Aren't you supposed
to say, "Tres bien"?
At least this'll
make him give up.
[CHOUNO]
Thank you. Now I can see.
If your talent was hair,
it'd be a flowing mane,
while mine is just an eyelash.
[SAIKI] I don't quite understand
using hair for that metaphor,
--but at least he's finally--
[CHUONO]
Make me your apprentice.
[SAIKI]
Should've seen this coming.
♪
[SAIKI]
I like watching TV.
It's one of the few things
that can surprise me.
Because I can't hear
the actors' thoughts,
I don't know what's coming next.
Speaking of next,
that new mystery show's
supposed to start soon.
[ANNOUNCER] Tonight you will
witness a miracle.
[SAIKI]
What?
[ANNOUNCER]
A stupendous, amazing illusion
performed by former homeless
man turned master magician,
Uryoko Chouno.
Now that's tres bien.
[SAIKI] What'd I tell you
about TV surprising me?
After losing it all,
he became a street magician
and mastered tricks
that others can only dream of.
[SAIKI] This isn't just
a surprise. It's unbelievable.
How is a man who
almost killed his dove
good enough to be on TV?
What I'm attempting tonight
is the most dangerous
escape you'll ever see.
[SAIKI] No way he's this good.
But live or not,
they'd never put someone on
TV who might get hurt, right?
[ANNOUNCER]
As you can see, folks,
Chouno's hands and feet
are both shackled
as he makes his way to
the crate-- Oh, no, he fell.
[SAIKI] Just a trip.
He should be fine.
He's safely inside the box.
And with that, Mr. Michael,
Chouno's formerly homeless
assistant, will lock him in.
Wait. I'm not ready!
[SAIKI]
Him screaming isn't a good sign.
Neither is all that
banging he's doing.
[ANNOUNCER]
The Amazing Chouno
needs to escape
within five minutes,
or he'll be destroyed
right along with the box.
[SAIKI]
I'm skeptical he can do this.
[ANNOUNCER] He's got
three minutes left to escape.
[SAIKI] Should I help?
I don't even think I can.
I'm not close enough to jump in
and save him without being seen.
[ANNOUNCER] Two minutes.
Just two minutes left.
[SAIKI] Then again, if he fails,
he dies, and I can't have that.
There's been an accident.
This isn't part of the show.
Chouno is burning
alive in that crate!
We'll pre-empt all other
shows until we can save him.
[SAIKI]
It would ruin my night.
If he fails, the coverage
will cut into my mystery show.
Is there a way to teleport
in without getting on TV?
Yes. The one place
no camera can find me.
That's right,
inside the box itself.
Now stop banging.
I'm here to get you out. Hmm?
[CHUONO] Yes. The trick's
going perfectly.
Not only was I able to escape,
I was able to make it seem like
I'm in there about to die.
[SAIKI]
Wow, he really has improved.
[ANNOUNCER]
Time's up.
Mr. Michael will
now use the swords.
[SAIKI] I got to think fast.
I can't just teleport back out.
That power needs to be
recharged for three minutes
before I can use it again.
[ANNOUNCER]
Seventeen swords to go.
[SAIKI]
Oh, crap.
[ANNOUNCER]
This is the last one, folks.
How could anyone
survive this?
[SAIKI]
No one could, except me.
I dislocated almost
every joint in my body.
I'm not gonna lie. It hurts.
[ANNOUNCER]
Now a construction crane
is hoisting the box
30 meters in the air...
...and dropping it.
[SAIKI] The only way to
avoid certain death...
...is...
...to jump.
Flawless timing.
That box has sustained
catastrophic damage,
but we have more
in store for it.
We're lighting it on fire.
[SAIKI] Didn't even get a
chance to catch my breath.
At least with all the
hot weather lately,
I've been able to hone my
psychic powers over temperature.
[ANNOUNCER] And now we're
running over the crate.
[SAIKI]
There's more?
[ANNOUNCER]
With a steamroller!
Chouno's box is
as flat as a pancake.
How could he survive that?
Hold on. Who's that I see?
It's the miraculous
illusionist himself,
Uryoku Chouno. He's alive.
[crowd cheering]
[SAIKI]
How annoying.
His wasn't the only
great escape, but I got lucky.
The soil was extra-soft.
I know. I said I like TV because
it can still surprise me,
but this is too much.
Well, folks, that sure was
some first-rate escape artistry.
Tres bien, right?
[SAIKI] Time to go home
and watch my show.
Hey, stick around
for what's next:
the world premiere of a mystery
called "Love Fantasy."
My character will try to
uncover the mystery
of his girlfriend's death.
[ACTOR A] Viewers are
gonna love that the twist
is I'm the killer.
[ACTOR A]
Enjoy the show.
[SAIKI[
Never mind.
♪
[bell chiming]
[SAIKI]
Hm?
Guess what. I've been summoned.
If I told you why,
I'd have to kill you, Saiki.
But for now, let's just say
the world's in store for
some pretty big changes.
[SAIKI]
What? Did he make a friend?
[MAN]
Thurisaz, isa, hagalaz.
Sowilo, um, gebo, fehu.
[MAN]
Eihwaz. You made it.
I hope no one
has followed you,
the Jet-Black Wings.
Not to worry, Jade Eyes.
I'm tail--
[JADE EYES] Wait.
There's something important
you've forgotten.
I'm sorry. sir. You're right.
An energy field
surrounds this room.
If one doesn't perform
the Holy Grail ceremony
within 66 seconds,
they'll vanish.
[JADE EYES]
That's right.
[no audio; swishes]
[string plucks]
Laguz.
[JADE EYES] So have you come
to terms with the truth?
It's not that easy for me.
It's like everything
I ever knew was a lie.
You say in a past life,
I was a top soldier
in Dark Reunion?
But then after discovering
their plan to sort mankind,
I stole the mystical stone,
Panalize, and went rogue?
And then, when they cornered me,
I performed the
Phantom technique
and became a
disembodied soul?
And then I entered the
unborn body of Shun Kaidou?
It's not easy
to believe all that.
[JADE EYES]
You seem excited by it.
I'm not, really.
[JADE EYES] That's fine. So long
as you're realizing the truth.
I have always felt like
there's something different
about me from other kids.
[JADE EYES] The powers
of the spirit within you
are absolutely vital to
destroying Dark Reunion.
That's why we'll do what we can
to help you regain
your memories.
What "we"? Who else is here?
[JADE EYES] There are four
others at this table besides me.
Of course, they are
all phantoms.
[gasps]
[JADE EYES]
I take it you don't see them.
If so, then you have
no chance to help us.
No. No. I see them fine.
They're just not here
physically, right?
[JADE EYES] Ah.
Yes, they are here in spirit,
but not body, like myself.
Unfortunately,
they don't trust you.
Why's that?
[JADE EYES] Because you
haven't yet presented the
Sworn Ally Absolution.
Oh, I got that right here.
[JADE EYES]
Oh... such detailed answers.
It's everything we
expected and more
from the Jet-Black Wings.
With this, they're sure to
accept you into the group.
Great. If that's all it takes--
--[JADE EYES] Duck.
--What?
[JADE EYES]
Mannaz. Ingwaz. Wunjo.
Um, what was that?
[JADE EYES] Dark Reunion
has found out about this room.
[gasps]
[JADE EYES]
We are under attack.
Attack?
[JADE EYES] They just
killed the four phantoms.
What? Phantoms can die?
[JADE EYES] Yes, even phantoms
can be killed.
If we want to make it out of
here alive, we need to act.
Now help me create a barrier.
Yeah, sure. So what do I do?
[JADE EYES]
Well, first things first.
I need you to put any and
all metal objects on you
into that special bag.
Metal can interfere with
the barrier magic.
Right. Even change?
[JADE EYES] Yes. You know what?
Just put your whole wallet in.
Right.
[JADE EYES]
Great. Now repeat my movements.
Okay.
[JADE EYES]
Ansuz jera.
Uh, ansuz jera.
--[JADE EYES] Eihwaz.
--Eihwaz.
[no audio]
[JADE EYES] Looks like we got
up the barrier just in time.
Yeah, that was close.
[JADE EYES]
Now it's time for us to go home.
Oh, okay. Then can I
have my wallet back?
[JADE EYES]
The barrier's still unstable.
It's much too risky to
remove it from the bag.
But it's got my train pass--
[JADE EYES]
If it wasn't for you,
I would've died today
with the phantoms.
Jet-Black Wings,
you're our savior.
Oh, well, sure. No problem.
[JADE EYES]
Come back same time tomorrow
and keep doing the
Sworn Ally Absolution.
[KAIDOU] Yes. Hm. Savior, huh?
I like the sound of that.
I'll have to bring
Saiki with me tomorrow.
Man, Kaidou's stupid fantasies
are the best thing ever.
He couldn't tell the absolution
was my homework.
All I had to do was
play along with him.
I even got the idiot
to give me his wallet.
[SAIKI]
What a pain.
[JADE EYES]
Ha, ha. Dark Reunion...
[SAIKI]
Kaidou, as your one friend,
I'm telling you
to do a better job
choosing your other friends.
What the... ? Who did that?
--[SAIKI] Dark Reunion.
--[gasps]
[JADE EYES screaming]
Don't tell a soul, okay?
This meeting involves
the fate of the world.
Oh, it's open.
Ah! What's going on?
That's the logo
for Dark Reunion!
Could it be they're only
one step behind me?
[SAIKI]
Pretty much.
♪
[NENDOU]
Hey, buddy. Ready for the beach?
I was walking by and saw the
last name Saiki on the mailbox,
so I figured this must be
where old Kusuo lives.
K-K-Kusuo, is this
boy your friend?
[SAIKI]
He's not my friend.
Oh, dear. My little boy
finally has a friend.
I'm so happy.
Sorry, girly-girl, but me
and him ain't friends.
We're best buddies.
Oh, dear.
My little boy is finally
getting a normal life.
I never knew you
had a sister, pal.
Oh, dear. He thinks I look
young enough to be Ku's sister.
[SAIKI] How many times
are you gonna make her cry?
I didn't know you
were Saiki's mom?
Guilty as charged.
What brought you here, big guy?
I wanted Saiki to come
with me to the beach.
Oh, that's so fun.
[SAIKI]
Uh, yeah, I'm not going. Sorry.
Your best buddy went out of
his way to ask you in person.
You're going to
the beach, Kusuo.
[SAIKI]
Oh, dear.
And that's how someone like me
ended up at a place like this.
What's wrong, Kaidou?
You afraid of the water?
Why did Kaidou come, too?
[KAIDOU] No. No, that's not
true. I know how to swim, jerk.
I am not afraid of the water.
[SAIKI] Oh, he's turned
on the waterworks.
[KAIDOU]
Uh, water.
[SAIKI] Drowning in inch-deep
water isn't easy.
[HAIRO]
I'll save you!
[SAIKI]
I know that butt.
[NENDOU]
Hey, it's Hairo.
Oh, hey, Nendou. Hey, Saiki.
You getting some sun, too?
[HAIRO] Actually, I volunteer
as a lifeguard.
[MALE SWIMMER]
Aah! I'm drowning.
I'll save you!
I can't believe he does
that job for free in this heat.
Huh. When you gonna
get in the water, buddy?
[SAIKI]
Just forget I'm here.
[NENDOU]
You guys are no fun.
I don't want to go
swim in the ocean
all by myself,
so to the ladies.
[SAIKI]
That sounds ridiculous.
[KAIDOU] With a face like that,
you don't have a chance.
[SAIKI] Why don't you try
walking on water instead?
You'll have better odds at that.
Oh, ho ho.
My looks don't matter.
It's about attitude.
[WOMAN A] I'm sorry.
I find your face repulsive.
[WOMAN B]
Are you joking?
There's no way I'm giving
my number to that face.
[WOMAN C]
Ever hear of a mirror?
You should look at one
before leaving the house.
[NENDOU screams]
Hey, don't run away.
[SAIKI] I don't want people
knowing I'm with him.
Unh. Girls are stupid.
[WOMAN D] Ha ha. You're such
a little cutie pie.
[NENDOU]
Wha... ?
Aw, I love his spikey
hairdo, don't you?
Stop touching my hair
and leave me alone. Go away.
[NENDOU groans]
[WOMAN D] I just remembered
I have to move my car.
[WOMAN E]
Yeah. Me too.
I'll save you.
Why'd you do this
to me, Nendou?
[NENDOU]
Where'd my bro go? Bathroom?
[SAIKI]
When I want to be alone
or get some serious
thinking done,
I like to come down here.
I find the sea floor relaxing.
Granted, there can be
weird stuff lying around,
but it's not important.
[NENDOU]
Saiki, you going pee-pee?
[SAIKI] Oh, man. Next time,
I'll have to go deeper.
Better go back
before they start looking.
[NENDOU gasps] What's that girl
doing? I think she's drowning.
Kaidou, I'll go rescue her
and you go get Hairo.
[KAIDO]
Hurry up!
Oh, so you can swim? Huh?
[gurgling]
[NENDOU]
Kaidou?
No, don't. Save her.
I'll take care of myself.
No way. I'm more than
strong enough to save you both.
[NENDOU]
Yaah. I rock!
Hey! Need help?
Can't take both.
Can you bring one back?
Yeah. That's my job--
Leg cramping.
[NENDOU]
Hairo!
Now I got to do all three?
[coughs]
I'm sorry, dude.
[SAIKI] What a pain.
Everyone around me is so needy.
So heavy.
Don't cramp, bro.
--Leave me here.
--Shut up.
Oh, crap. Now we're sinking.
[NENDOU]
Huh?
[HAIRO]
Nendou, you're walking on water.
[KAIDOU] Where'd you
learn how to do that?
[NENDOU]
Whoa-oa-oa.
[SAIKI] See? I told him
he'd have more luck
walking on water
than picking up girls.
Thanks for saving my life.
[NENDOU] Hm? One of
the babes from earlier.
Sorry I joked about
how ugly your face is.
Hmm. I'm glad you didn't
ask for her number
in return for your heroics.
Hm. I try to be a gentleman,
but if that hottie
fell in love with me,
I'm not gonna turn her down.
She wouldn't.
What'd you say?
[SAIKI]
But he did get a secret admirer.
[HAIRO]
Riki Nendou, you're my hero.
I love everything about you.
[SAIKI]
This guy.
♪
[SAIKI]
First day of a new term,
which means now I got to
see those guys every day.
Hairo, you got tan.
Yeah. I volunteered at
the beach as a lifeguard.
[BOY A]
You got a crush on someone.
[BOY B]
Teruhashi, is it one of us?
It's someone I ran
into over vacation.
[TERUHASHI chuckles]
You know who I mean, right?
I know he wasn't a
figment of my imagination.
It was the sixth of August when
I first fell in love with him.
[TERUHASHI] That's a day you'll
never forget, either, Saiki.
I remember seeing
you that day, too.
And the guy you were
talking with...
...was Nendou!
[TERUHASHI]
You are way off, idiot. Uh...
Yeah, his name's Uri Offidiot.
He's a Russian exchange student.
[SAIKI]
Nope.
[KAIDOU]  Hey, Saiki, just me,
or is Nendou acting weird today?
[SAIKI]
You're the one being weird.
Like usually
he's always saying,
[MOCKS] "We should do stuff
after school, buddy."
[SAIKI]
He is quieter than normal.
Oh, my look? Don't worry
about it. It's a long story.
[SAIKI] I'm not worried about
it. I just think it's stupid.
[grunting]
[SAIKI]
What's that all about?
[KAIDOU]
Pretty fishy, right?
[SAIKI]
My interest is piqued.
All right, all right.
I'll tell you. It all started--
[SAIKI] Stop it. I don't
care about your new look.
[KAIDOU]
His house isn't this way.
He's got something
going on. Heh, heh.
[SAIKI]
Why are you so excited by this?
Heh heh.
[SAIKI] And why are you so
good at tailing people?
Hey, Saiki, check it.
What's Nendou looking at?
[GIRL laughs]
[chuckles]
[BOTH]
Creepy.
[KAIDOU] Nendou has a
thing for little girls?
[SAIKI]
Doesn't look good.
We should probably
call the police.
[KAIDOU]
He's going into a store.
Looks like a flower boutique.
Don't tell me he's got a girl.
[SAIKI, KAIDOU]
No, not Nendou.
Huh?
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH]
Another one.
[KAIDOU]
That's just gross.
[SAIKI] We'll confirm it
after we call the police.
No, we need more
proof than this.
I mean, lots of people
like sunflowers,
and it's natural to smile when
you see a cute
little kid, right?
[SAIKI]
Good point. Let's not be rash.
[KAIDOU]
Hm, another shop.
Cakes!
Women and children
can't resist sweets.
When you combine a woman and
a child, you get a little girl.
[SAIKI] Now you're
jumping to conclusions.
[KAIDOU] Have you ever
seen Nendou eat that?
Or like flowers?
It's all meant to
be given to someone,
but he has no girlfriend
to give them to.
That can only mean
that they're bait
and that he's using them
to lure away little girls.
[SAIKI] Any girl it works
on has her own problems.
[NENDOU] Bummer. They were
all out of shortcake.
Oh, well. It's not like
anyone will ever eat this.
[SAIKI, KAIDOU] If it's not
for eating, it must be bait.
--[KAIDOU] Nendou.
--Huh?
Your secret's out. How dare you
hurt little kids, you monster.
[SAIKI] Is that what
his punches sound like?
Wait. What secret?
You mean my dad? Wha... ?
[KAIDOU]
He's dead?
I visit on the anniversary
of his bus accident.
But the flowers and the cake?
Respectful offerings
to the dead.
It's normal to bring cakes
and flowers to a family grave.
[SAIKI] To think Nendou's
lecturing us on normal.
I get it now. Those weren't
creepy looks he was giving.
Seeing kids with their dads
just made him think of his own.
Nendou has a very
misleading face.
When did your dad die, Nendou?
Well, it was before I was born.
He died trying to save
a little girl
who'd run in front of a bus.
Huh. Maybe that means
he was into little girls?
[KAIDOU]
Uh, hope not. Heh, heh.
[SAIKI]
That's a dark joke.
So if he died
before you were born,
he must've been pretty young.
He was only 18 or 19 years old.
Here, look. I got his picture.
Hey. This is just
a picture of you.
No. It's him.
My mom says I look more
like him each year. Weird.
You don't just look like him.
You're the same.
[SAIKI] I've seen pictures
of Nendou's dad before,
and they really do look like
they could be identical twins.
The only difference is that
while Nendou has a
scar over his left eye,
his father had one
over his right.
Cake, mmm.
[SAIKI] Uch. That's not
a real ghost, right?
Wanna go get some ramen?
[SAIKI] I know my powers
are literally supernatural.
But personally
I don't believe in ghosts,
so I'll pretend today at the
graveyard never happened.
Hmm?
It's for me. Weird.
I never get mail--
[SAIKI]
What?
♪
[SAIKI] I can't believe we
ended with a cliffhanger
and right after
I received a creepy letter.
But don't worry.
We're just following
how the manga plays out.
Next time on The Disastrous
Life of Saiki K,
each chapter of the manga
gets an episode.