[SAIKI] Ah, phys ed.
My least favorite class.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm good at sports.
Like, medal-in-just-
about-any-event good.
But that's exactly why...
[BOY STUDENT A]
What the hell was that?
[BOY STUDENT B]
Was that a meteor?
[SAIKI] ...it's so hard for me
to play at a normal human level.
[MATSUZAKI]
All right, losers, listen up!
We're playing dodge ball!
Dodge ball in high school?
Aw, what about soccer?
Hey, quit complaining! Let's
give it everything we've got!
So what if it's childish? It'll
be fun to relive our youth!
Let's go out there and
dodge till we drop! Eh?
Well, if Hairo really
wants us to, then I guess.
Yeah, we gotta give
it a shot, right?
[SAIKI] That's Kineshi Hairo,
our class rep.
He's a little too relentlessly
gung-ho for my taste.
But the rest of the class
seems to respect him.
[HAIRO] Okay, who wants
to be on my team?
[MATSUZAKI] We'll decide
teams with rock-paper!
[HAIRO] All right!
We're gonna win this thing!
Yeah!
[SAIKI]
I'm on Hairo's team.
Beats the alternative.
[NENDOU chuckles]
[MATSUZAKI]
We'll start with a jump ball.
[SAIKI] And with that.
The game is on.
[yelling]
--Yeah!
--We got one out!
We got one out!
[SAIKI] Getting one player out
is worth that much excitement?
And how is he sweating
that much already?
We just started.
All right, guys,
we got the ball this time.
Hey there, Saiki.
We're takin' you first!
[SAIKI]
Already?
Might as well go with it.
Dude, are you okay?
[SAIKI sighs]
[SAIKI] Least I can sit out
the rest of the game now.
The more time I spend
on the bench, the better.
[HAIRO]
Hold it, Saiki!
Were you actually trying
to get hit by that ball?
[SAIKI]
Guess I made it too obvious.
[HAIRO]
For real? Well...
Hey, where you going?
You're not out.
Face-safe rule. Hmph.
[SAIKI]
Seriously, that's the rule?
Great. And now I've
gotta throw the ball?
This is ridiculous.
Throwing balls is where I have
the most trouble
masking my power.
Saiki! Give it all you got!
[SAIKI]
I'd rather not do that.
You say it like
it's no big deal,
but if I really
gave it all I've got,
somebody'd wind up dead!
Forget the face-safe rule.
They won't have a face anymore!
I'll try my best to throw it
weakly, but just in case...
...I'll aim for Nendou.
Uh.
[NENDOU]
Huh?
[SAIKI]
Too weak, maybe?
What the heck kinda
wussy-ass throw was that?
This isn't a game,
kid, it's serious!
Put some heart into it!
[SAIKI]
'Kay, I get it. Calm down.
Hey now, buddy, thanks
for goin' easy on your boy,
but right now, we're
s'posed to be enemies.
Did you really go easy on
him 'cause he's your friend?
[SAIKI]
No part of that is true.
All right!
Heh, they don't call me "Nen
the Dodgeballer" for nothing!
Take that! And that!
Bam! Boo-yah! Twofer!
[KIJIMA] Whoa, he took
out six players at once!
[BOY STUDENT G] The Paper
Team's only got two guys left!
[HAIRO growls]
Obviously gotta
save my pal for last.
Which makes you my
next target, captain!
Dodge ball!
[screaming]
[HAIRO]
I'll catch it!
For my brave teammates
who sacrificed themselves,
I'll catch it even
if it kills me!
[BOY STUDENTS]
Whoa. Saiki?
[SAIKI]
I should go out before you.
Sorry I couldn't play harder,
Hairo, but I've got my reasons.
Hey, don't give up now!
We're still in this! Let's go!
[KASHIMURA]
Whoa! Look!
[UKAI]
He caught the ball!
[BOY STUDENT H]
He saved Saiki's butt!
[SAIKI]
You've gotta be kidding me.
[YUASA]
Oh, no! Hairo's knee is busted!
[UKAI] That means Saiki's the
only one left on Team Paper!
[SAIKI]
You have got to be kidding me.
[HAIRO]
Looks like this is it for me.
[SAIKI]
Don't you give up!
[HAIRO]
I entrust this ball to you.
I know that you're
hiding something, Saiki.
You've got a power deep inside
you that you're not using.
What's stopping you?
Now's the time!
I wanna see you let
loose and unleash--
[SAIKI] You do realize you
only scraped your knee, right?
[HAIRO]
Help us, Saiki.
You're our only hope.
[HAIRO retches]
Yo, Saiki. I believe in you!
[BOY STUDENT I]
We're counting on you, Saiki!
[KIJIMA]
Kick their butts, Saiki!
[SAIKI]
You have got to be kidding me.
There's nothing I hate more
than being the
center of attention.
And yet here I am,
all eyes on me.
So what do I do now?
Looks like Saiki's found himself
in a difficult spot here.
Uh-huh.
Saiki's on the Paper Team,
which originally had the upper
hand when they started playing,
thanks to Hairo's killer
opening attack,
but then Nendou took out
six players with one shot.
Then while trying to save
Saiki from getting out,
Hairo got hurt and was
forced to leave the game.
So now Saiki's the only
one left on Paper Team!
That's right.
[SAIKI] Wow, thanks
for that detailed recap.
Though what makes this
situation difficult for me
isn't that I'm one
man against seven.
Not to brag, but winning
this would be a breeze.
Problem is, if I do,
my likability will skyrocket,
and everyone's gonna be
watching me 24/7, which sucks.
On the other hand,
if I throw the game and lose,
I'll be about as
popular as a stinkbug.
In which case, I'll attract the
merciless attention of bullies.
Either way,
I'm in the spotlight,
so I'm not really concerned
with winning or losing.
For me, it's all about
getting out of this
as unremarkably as possible.
That's the challenge.
[SAIKI]
Forty-one? That's a tad low.
[NARRATOR B]
Likability Meter.
It is an applied
telepathic ability.
By reading the minds
of everyone around him,
it calculates his likability
and quantifies it!
[SAIKI]
My goal here is 50.
To get that,
I have to at least...
...take out one guy!
[BOY STUDENTS]
Stop screwing around, you jerk!
[SAIKI]
Twenty, huh?
Well, that went down fast.
[NARRATOR B]
With that score,
a girl would scream if
assigned the seat next to you.
[SAIKI] Figuring out how
hard to throw is tricky.
[KOBAYASHI]
Put some muscle into it!
[SAIKI] If I really tried,
it'd break the sound barrier
and do catastrophic damage.
But this slow ball's
different than the last one.
[TAKEDA]
Got it!
Ugh, Saiki is so the worst.
Try harder, bro!
[SAIKI]
This time I threw...
Got it. Got it!
[SAIKI]
...a spin ball.
Whoa!
[SAIKI]
Nice. My likability's back up.
Even if I get out now,
I can end up around 50.
Just gotta get hit next time.
[KAIDOU] Hmph! Finally
it's my turn to show you
what I've got.
Do you have any idea what
that means for you, Saiki?
It means that
you're in big trouble!
[SAIKI] Jeez, I have to
let this kid take me out?
Here's my Meteor
Spark Genocide Ball!
Ow!
[BOY STUDENTS]
You call that a throw?
[TAKAHASHI]
What the hell was that, Kaidou?
It looks like Saiki got lucky.
If he can't catch that,
that's just sad.
[SAIKI]
If I don't catch this one,
my likability's gonna plummet.
[NARRATOR B] With a score
of 36, the students won't put
your chair down when
they're done cleaning.
[FURUKAWA] All right!
We got the ball again!
--What's wrong with you, Kaidou?
--[SAIKI] If I throw another
--spin ball,
--My wrist is acting up.
--that'll look suspicious.
Hey, Saiki, over here I'm open!
Toss it here! Bring me in!
[SAIKI] If I pass the ball to
the outfield and gain a player,
then I'll stand out less!
Gotta make sure
it gets to him, though,
so I'll put a little
strength behind this one.
[BOY STUDENTS yelp]
[SAIKI] Shoot, that was
a little too much strength.
[NARRATOR B]
With a score of 73,
peers will reciprocate
nonsensical greetings.
[TAKUMI]
Chori-Chori-Noon!
Sorry, buddy!
[SAIKI]
Time to end this.
[KIJIMA]
No!
Guess he couldn't pull it off.
Well he gave it his best.
[SAIKI] Fifty-five.
I can live with tha--
[HAIRO]
I got it!
[BOY STUDENTS]
Ah! That butt. It's...
Just in time.
[BOY STUDENTS]
...Hairo!
[SAIKI]
Not you again.
[BOY STUDENT T]
Hairo's back!
Saiki, I saw the spirit
you put into that throw!
It really moved me!
[SAIKI] Yeah, I don't
care about your likability.
[HAIRO]
I'll handle things from here!
[yells]
Direct hit! Bull's-eye!
Yeah, suck it!
Sorry, but your little
comeback ends here.
I won't be dropped as
easy as those puny wimps.
Yeah, me neither.
Fine, let's finish
this then. Bring it!
[SAIKI] With that injury,
Hairo probably
can't catch Nendou's
ball right now.
[NENDOU]
Take this!
[SAIKI]
I've got no choice.
The kid wounded
his knee 'cause of me.
Much as I hate
to draw attention...
...I hate being in debt
to someone even more.
No, you take it!
[BOTH yelp]
[BOY STUDENT T]
He did it! It's a miracle!
[SAIKI] Oh, great.
It wound up at eighty-two.
I'll just have to chip
away at it over time.
Saiki's so amazing!
Nice job, Saiki!
[NENDOU]
Buddy!
That was a really
great match, man.
[SAIKI]
Likability...
It can free-fall in
the blink of an eye.
[BOY STUDENT V]
What? Minako said yes?
[SAIKI] In high school,
love is always in the air,
which is something
I consider entirely pointless.
These romantic
feelings elude me.
Take Teruhashi for example.
Every boy in school wants her.
[GIRL STUDENT D]
Come on, Teruhashi.
When are you gonna
get a boyfriend?
Well, I guess I just think
I'm too young to be dating.
[GIRL STUDENTS]
Seriously?
[SAIKI] Meanwhile,
I have zero interest in her
because I know
who she really is.
So when she says something like:
Studying should be
our focus as students.
[SAIKI]
The only thing I hear is:
[TERUHASHI]
Actually, I don't get involved
with immature brats.
[SAIKI] And this is
how she looks to me:
[TERUHASHI]
His annual income should be
at least 40 million yen.
[SAIKI] Oh yeah, I can't
control this ability to see
through objects, just like
I can't control my telepathy.
To find out more,
please read The Disastrous
Life of Saiki K .
Anyway, that's the main reason
I'll probably never wanna
be in a relationship,
and it's why I'm currently
facing a serious dilemma.
Yup.
[sighs]
[YUMEHARA]
Saiki always looks so dreamy.
[SAIKI] Meet my dilemma,
Chiyo Yumehara.
[YUMEHARA]
Oh, Saiki.
Lately, I just can't
stop thinking about you.
[YUMEHARA] Sweet Saiki,I have
such a huge crush on y--
What? What was that? Huh?
[SAIKI]
No, this won't work at all.
I'll stand out as a freak.
I know I'm repeating myself,
but I really don't
wanna stand out.
[YUMEHARA] I wonder
what he's thinking right now.
[SAIKI] I just need
her to give up on me.
And to do that...
[YUMEHARA] I just need
to know more about him.
And to do that..
--[SAIKI] ...I have to get
--[YUMEHARA] ...I have to get
--away from her immediately!
--closer to him!
[YUMEHARA]
Here he comes!
And he's all by himself!
Now's my chance!
Just remember the plan!
First, Saiki and I will
bump into each other
at the corner,
papers flying everywhere.
Are you okay?
Here, lemme help
you pick these up.
Oh-uh. Yeah. Thank you.
[BOTH gasp]
Ah, sorry!
Oh, that's okay!
[giggling]
You've got small hands.
--[NARRATOR A] Love fantasy.
--[YUMEHARA] It's perfect!
[YUMEHARA]
Okay, here we go!
Uh... Wha--? What the--?
What the--?
All right, next up.
The handkerchief plan!
First, I casually drop this
handkerchief by Saiki's feet.
Then, he sees it and says:
Hey, I think you dropped this.
[YUMEHARA]
Oh.
Smells like a sunny day!
[NARRATOR A]
Just in love.
[YUMEHARA giggles]
Best thing about this plan is,
even if he doesn't
notice the handkerchief,
I still have an
excuse to talk to him.
You can do it, self!
[YUMEHARA] Now to see
if Saiki takes the bait.
[YUMEHARA]
Hmm, he's not saying anything.
Oh well, that's okay.
On to Plan B!
Oh my goodness,
that's really bizarre.
My pink handkerchief is...
Right here?
How'd that happen?
[YUMEHARA]
Another disaster!
[NARRATOR B] Undeterred,
Chiyo continued on her mission
to engage Saiki, however...
Did someone knock?
I made way too many
cookies in home ec.,
and I was wondering
if you wanted s--
Yeah, I'd love some.
[YUMEHARA]
Who's this guy?!
[NARRATOR B] Every single
one of her plans failed.
[YUMEHARA]
Maybe Saiki and I just
aren't meant to be together?
Great, on top of everything,
I forgot my umbrella.
That's it!
[GIRL STUDENT G]
See ya!
[BOY STUDENT Y] Man, it's
raining cats and dogs out here!
[YUMEHARA] I bet Saiki
brought his umbrella.
He seems like the
responsible type.
Wow, it's really
coming down. Huh? I, um...
Hi, would you like to
join me under my umbrella?
[YUMEHARA sighs]
[YUMEHARA] His smile is as
warm and as bright as the sun.
Finally, the perfect plan!
Huh, the rain just stopped?
Ah... Saiki.
[YUMEHARA]
I give up.
It seems Saiki and I are
destined to always be apart.
Goodbye, Saiki.
[SAIKI]
Goodbye, Yumehara.
Please forget about me
and find somebody else.
I'm sure another guy
will come along soon, so--
[TAKERU]
Wanna share my umbrella?
[YUMEHARA]
But the rain stopped.
[TAKERU] Not the rain of tears
falling inside your heart.
Please, let me be the umbrella
for your overcast heart.
[YUMEHARA] This boy!
I just met my soul mate.
[SAIKI]
Okay, that's a little too soon.
[KUNIHARU]
Kusuo!
Gimme a hand
moving some furniture.
Won't take long
with your powers.
[SAIKI]
Move it yourself.
[KUNIHARU] Huh? I would, but
I've got other things to carry.
Ah!
[KUNIHARU]
See, like your mother!
I've got my hands full
carrying her around!
You're so strong, honey.
[SAIKI]
I repeat. Move it yourself.
[NARRATOR A]
Due to a marital spat,
this couple has been sleeping
in separate bedrooms.
However, that's
all about to change,
thanks to the help
of a craftsman who--
[SAIKI]
I'm not a craftsman.
[KUNIHARU]
Whoa!
[KURUMI]
You really are amazing, Kuu!
Yeah, seriously, what do people
without a psychic son do?
Woo-hoo! Flying bed!
[grunting]
Oh my.
[SAIKI] Some of you,
like this idiot here,
may be getting the wrong idea,
so let me clear a few things up.
If you think my power's always
convenient, you're wrong.
Most of my abilities come with
limitations and drawbacks.
For instance,
some can only be used
under certain circumstances.
Oops, I don't know how
that picture got in there.
So yeah, I'm not all-powerful.
[KUNIHARU]
Hey, look at me!
I'm the strongest man
in the world!
[KUNIHARU groans]
[KURUMI]
Oh, my goodness!
[SAIKI] See? Lost my
strength for a second.
[KUNIHARU]
Phew.
Well, that's the last of it.
I'm all done now.
Good job.
Here, you must be thirsty.
[SAIKI]
Don't act like you did anything.
I moved everything myself.
[KUNIHARU groans]
[KUNIHARU] The bed's blocking
access to the balcony.
[KURUMI]
Oh no, you're right.
I'd love to move it,
but it's too heavy
to move by myself.
[KURUMI] Hmm, if only
there was someone
who could move it really easily.
[KUNIHARU]
Well, to do that,
they'd prob'ly need
psychic powers.
[KURUMI] Yeah, I wish
there was someone
--with psychic powers around.
--[SAIKI] Stop this farce.
[KUNIHARU]
Is there anyone like that here?
[BOTH gasp]
[SAIKI]
Just stop.
[KUNIHARU]
Ah, this is perfect!
[KURUMI] Now we can
get to the balcony again!
How can we thank you?
How 'bout we give you
a little brother or sister?!
Which would you prefer?
[SAIKI] Please don't imply
whatever you're implying.
Anyway, if that's all,
I'll be in my room.
[KURUMI]
Uh-oh.
Now we can't get
the closet door open.
What a travesty!
[BOTH]
Ah!
Wow, that's so much better!
Oh yeah, this time
it's definitely perfect!
Now let's go have some...
Huh?
[BOTH]
Ah!
[SAIKI]
Are they stupid or what?
[KUNIHARU] Maybe we should
knock this wall down?
[KURUMI]
Let's do it!
[KUNIHARU]
Kusuo!
Make it happen!
[SAIKI] Just remember,
you asked for this.
[loud crash]
[SAIKI]
All done.
Okay.
Uh. Thanks, I guess.
[SAIKI]
Hey, what did you expect?
[KUNIHARU yelps]
[SAIKI]
Yeah, that's a good reaction.
[KUNIHARU]
This is nice!
Knocking it down
was the right call!
[KURUMI] The room's
a lot more spacious now!
[KUNIHARU]
Yeah, it really is!
All this space overwhelms me!
[SAIKI]
I'm about to lose it.
[KURUMI] This emptiness
right here bothers me.
[KUNIHARU]
Then let's put something there.
[KURUMI]
What about a TV?
[KUNIHARU]
That's not quite right.
I'm thinking... tiger rug.
[SAIKI]
Disgusting.
Well, all we have
in the house is a sofa.
Let's bring it in here, Kusuo.
That's a terrible
place for a couch!
Who's gonna wanna
sit in the corner?
We can't have our
heads facing north!
What the hell is that?
[KUNIHARU grunting]
[KUNIHARU]
Too humid!
What do we need two beds for?
I've never seen
that ceiling before!
Something feels off!
This isn't working!
Let's take a break.
Honey, look at this.
The room on the
left is our bedroom,
and we tore down the wall
'cause it was too small, right?
But it looks like
the room on the right
was already much bigger.
So instead of tearing
down the wall,
maybe we should've just made the
one on the right our bedroom?
[KUNIHARU]
That's it!
[KURUMI]
Really? I did good?
[KUNIHARU]
Oh, you did very good!
Right, you heard the woman.
Put the wall back up!
We're counting on you, Kuu!
[SAIKI]
Huh?
Do it for her.
Oh, honey, please!
Son, I swear, this really
is our last request!
[SAIKI]
It better be. 'Cause I'm done.
Wall, resume
your original state!
[KURUMI]
Kuu, you're incredible!
[SAIKI]
You're on your own now.
Our sweet castle of
love is finally complete!
I love you.
[SAIKI]
I forgot to mention,
my restoration ability
has a drawback, too.
[KUNIHARU]
Huh?
Where's the bed?
[SAIKI] See, it doesn't
actually revert things
to their former state.
All it does is turn back time
for that object by one day.
Problem is, time rewinds for
things that are nearby, too.
In this case,
we're dealing with a wall,
so, the whole house might've
gone back to the way it was.
[KUNIHARU]
What happened?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[SAIKI]
Hey, what can I say?
My powers aren't perfect.
[KURUMI cries]
[MATSUZAKI]
Hey! You!
[BOY STUDENT Z yelps]
What's up with the
sloppy school uniform?
[BOY STUDENT Z]
Uh, sorry, sir.
Tuck in that shirt, and pull up
your damn pants right now!
[BOY STUDENT Z]
Oh, yes, sir.
Higher!
Looks like Matsuzaki's on
the warpath again. Great.
[SAIKI]
A surprise inspection.
Lemme ask you.
Think I can pass the dress code
check, looking like this?
The answer, of course, is...
Hey, stop right there!
[SAIKI]
...obviously.
[MATSUZAKI]
That hair is unacceptable!
Oh?
[SAIKI] It's to be expected,
since, by all accounts,
I'm a perfectly normal student.
The other day,
I received some fan mail,
asking the question, "If Saiki
doesn't want to stand out,
why is his
appearance so strange?"
Well, here's the answer.
In "this world,"
my look is natural.
Now of course,
when you think about it,
I'm not normal at all.
Yet, I'm the most
inconspicuous kid in school.
How? I'll tell ya. Mind control.
I can alter people's thoughts,
at least to some extent.
I mean, I can't completely
control somebody's actions.
If I could, this guy
would shut up already.
Right?
[SAIKI] But what I can do
is make others perceive
"unnatural things" as
something "totally natural."
Antennae? Huh.
Wait is it possible
they're just hairclips?
Oh, yeah, sure.
That's what they are.
[SAIKI] Thus, I can go
through life and not stick out.
Simple, right?
But I've gotta use
this power sparingly,
'cause if I change
someone's way of thinking,
it'll affect the people
around them, too.
Take a look around.
In "this world,"
you almost never see
people with black hair.
This phenomenon,
believe it or not,
is all due to my psychic powers.
For some unknown reason,
I was born with pink hair.
Meanwhile, all the
other kids had black hair.
Or, on occasion, brown.
Since I didn't wanna stand
out, I used mind control.
As a result, pink became
a common hair color,
and it's pretty normal now to
see hair in all sorts of colors.
And their hair is natural.
I altered human biology, right
down to the genetic level.
Are you starting to get the
potential risk of my power?
Hey, wanna get some ramen?
[SAIKI]
To tell you the truth,
that's not the only
thing I've changed.
[crack]
[NENDOU]
Uh? Agh!
[BASEBALL PLAYER A]
Oh man, it hit Nendou!
[BASEBALL PLAYER B]
Sorry! You okay?
Watch your aim, punks!
[BASEBALL PLAYER A]
Sorry, Nendou.
[SAIKI]
Don't you think it's strange,
how his injury healed
so abnormally fast?
That's right.
As you've no doubt guessed,
this is the result of
my psychic powers, too.
When I was little,
a kid skinned his knee,
I healed it.
Needless to say,
he was surprised.
So I used mind control.
[SAIKI] Since people stopped
suffering from mild injuries,
they started to
think it was natural
for them to heal right away.
As a result,
people's ability to self-heal
increased dramatically.
Maybe you've noticed other
freakish behavior, like this.
[BATTER A] Here it comes!
Is it a fastball?
Or his favorite, the curveball?
According to his stats,
he usually throws
a curveball first.
I should adjust my angle.
[SAIKI]
He thinks too fast, right?
[UMPIRE A]
Strike!
[SAIKI]
Yup, that's all because of me.
Humans have evolved
to think fast
when they need
to react instantly.
Now clothes can be torn off,
while the crotch
remains covered.
Tiny folks can be super strong.
You can knock someone
out with just a chop.
All these unnatural phenomena
were caused by me.
And yeah, sure, I feel some
guilt for changing the world
like I have, but it's too late
to change things back now.
Still, at the same time,
I've shown some restraint,
and things haven't
gotten too out of hand.
[KONGOU]
What was that?
Wanna tell me which
rules I'm violating?
You do not wanna mess
with me, you bastard!
[BOY STUDENT DD screams]
[yells]
[BOY STUDENT DD]
That's his legendary
planet-destroying attack,
Galactic Magnum Flavored Punch!
[yells]
[BOY STUDENT DD]
Mister Hatakeyama!
--[KONGOU] Hey, how dare you
--[HATAKEYAMA] Kongou, you're
--interrupt me in the middle
--so blinded by rage, you've
--of a good butt-whooping!
--left yourself wide open.
[BULLY A]
Uh?
[HATAKEYAMA]
Chop.
Whoa, that was a "chop."
Mister Hatakeyama "chopped" him.
Well, are you doing
all right, Mister Matsuzaki?
Yeah.
Thanks, you really
saved my bacon.
[SAIKI] You'll notice
his clothes are un-torn.
Of course, that's another
of the changes I've made.
See? This isn't too bad, right?
[SAIKI]
Since the show's called
The Disastrous
Life of Saiki K. ,
I'll try to
realistically present
the many disasters I face.
[SAIKI] Next time, on The
Disastrous Life of Saiki K. :
Each chapter of the
manga gets an episode!