♪
[REITA]
"To Mr. Kusuo Saiki.
"I am someone who knows you have
psychic powers, but don't worry.
"I intend to tell
no one about you.
"I'm writing this letter
"because I wanted to tell you
that I'm not your enemy,
"and that I want to be
your apprentice.
"To tell you the truth,
I also have unique abilities.
"It is because of
those abilities
that I came to know
about you, master."
[SAIKI] He's all ready
calling me master?
[REITA] "I'll come to greet
you in person sometime soon.
Sincerely,
Your Faithful Servant."
[SAIKI] He's gone from
apprentice to servant.
But the real news is there's
another psychic out there.
Wonder what he's like.
I should find out
before he shows up.
Psychometry--
the ability to read
a person's feelings and memories
that have been stored in
an inanimate object,
like, for example,
this Shonen Jump.
The printing process.
Major story spoilers.
Overworked writers.
Just touching it,
I'm overwhelmed with all this,
which is why I always wear
extremely thin
transparent gloves
that help to keep
this power in check.
My psychometry only works
when I touch things directly,
but now the gloves are off,
so I can see what this guy is--
[doorbell rings]
Wow, your house
is really normal.
This is too soon. Why
even bother sending a letter?
Ah, sorry.
Where are my manners?
My name's Reita Toritsuka,
and it's a pleasure
to meet you, master.
Let's see, I'm 16 years old--
Ah, but you know all that
'cause you can read my mind.
Anyway, feels like I know you.
I've heard so much about you
from people. From dead people.
Did I forget to mention
that part?
[SAIKI] That explains it.
He's a medium.
You can't see spirits, master?
Not unless you're one.
Oh, good for you.
I see about 15 right now.
Really? That sounds like a lot.
What, are they having a party?
Nothing draws a crowd of spirits
like a psychic. They're curious.
There's an old lady hanging out
up in that corner there.
And right next to you is a guy
bouncing his bare butt.
But forget about that.
The reason I'm here
is I wanna be your apprentice.
Wait. He's doing what
with his butt now?
[REITA] Don't worry.
It's totally harmless.
Harms my peace of mind.
Oh, looks like he's gone now.
Nope. he's rubbing his butt
on his face.
You know I hear your thoughts,
right?
I'm sorry. I don't really have
any control over these guys.
You're a psychic medium.
Can't you just...
Be gone.
or something?
Yeah, well, my abilities
are pretty much limited
to seeing ghosts
and talking to 'em.
I've had this gift since birth
when I was born into a temple.
From birth?
We're the same in that manner.
[REITA] When I was little,
I couldn't tell the difference
between people and ghosts.
Then my beloved grandma
told me that spirits
can't take on physical form,
so that's a good way
to identify 'em.
I was so relieved,
I went to give her a hug,
and that's when I discovered
Grandma was a ghost.
[SAIKI] That's dark.
[REITA] Yeah,
I was pretty bummed,
but my grandpa came
to cheer me up,
except he was a ghost, too.
After that, I just started
hugging people at random.
A lot of 'em thought
I was being creepy and gross,
but, really, I was just checking
to make sure they were alive.
[SAIKI] That sketchy grin
says otherwise.
When it comes to powers, I drew
the short end of the stick.
It's more of a burden
than a gift with no upside.
That's not true.
By communicating with the dead,
think of all the people
you can bring closure to.
Yeah, but is there any way
I can get rich off of it?
Uh, got you.
When I heard about you
from my ghost friends,
I knew I had to meet you.
He said there was a guy
with all kinds of powers
like telepathy, x-ray vision,
teleportation, clairvoyance,
and psychokinesis.
But you still cared more about
the ladies' bath, didn't you?
Please, Saiki,
make me your apprentice
and teach me how to do all of
your tricks. I'm begging you.
Even if I could teach you
these abilities,
you'd just use 'em
to do gross stuff, right?
Look, I'm not gonna lie to you,
because I respect you and also
because you can read my mind
and would know that I was lying.
To be honest, I mostly want to
see through girls' clothes
and predict lottery numbers.
Tell me, is that so wrong?
That was too honest.
I think clairvoyance
could help with peeping, too.
Plus, I want to lift skirts with
psychokinesis and teleport...
Never seen a scumbag
with such pure eyes.
But these powers
don't work how he thinks.
People's voices
flood into your head constantly.
You see through things
too well
and can't touch anything
without gloves on.
You have no idea how hard it is.
Being a psychic is suffering.
Uhh. Guess I should be
going now.
[SAIKI] Don't tell anyone
about this, okay?
But can I come see you again?
Just get out of here all re--
Psychometry? I forgot
to put my glove back on.
When I touch other people,
it's like their senses
become my own.
Uh, master?
[timer dings]
[REITA] Master,
is something wrong?
[SAIKI] Well, I guess
we're both suffering.
♪
[SAIKI] Last night, I had
a surprise drop-in from--
what was his name--
Toritsuka?
You hear about the cool
new transfer student next door?
Really?
♪
Ooh, can you tell me
what my guardian spirit is like?
She looks like
a noblewoman,
and she's stunningly beautiful,
just like you are.
Oh, stop it.
Ooh, do mine next.
Uh, master.
Could this be any more cliché?
Hey, change schools.
Wait. Hold on a sec.
Chill out.
Why are you upset?
Didn't I tell you...
I was gonna be
transferring to your school?
No.
Well, I assumed you'd know
what with you being a psychic.
Wrong.
Oh, I think I get it.
Are you worried I'm gonna
tell people about your powers?
First, quit calling me master.
I won't tell anyone, I swear--
[flushes]
The perfect weapon.
It dissolves in water
so there's no evidence.
[stammers] I feel like a kid
who just got beaten up by the
school bully on his first day.
I don't get why
you'd rather hide your powers.
If you showed off what you do,
you'd get so much attention.
That's exactly why.
Then again,
I guess it's kind of creepy
to know someone's
peeking into your brain.
Wait. Hold on. Forget brains.
You can peek at
other body parts, too, right?
Wow, so that means
you can see all the girls naked
any time that you want.
Oh, my God. Ahh.
[giggles]
Ahh...
Yep, another boy
in love with me.
Oh, who is that beautiful angel
who just glided past us?
That's Teruhashi.
She just walked by you
for no reason whatsoever.
You should thank her.
Did you see all the nooks
and crannies on her body?
Gimme some details here.
[SAIKI] Please
don't be weird.
Look, there he is.
You can see guardian spirits?
Come read our minds.
Well, Saiki, I guess
I can make do with this.
Ladies, I'll get to all of you.
One at a time.
Hey, so what is
a guardian spirit?
Like it sounds.
A spirit that always
watches over and protects you.
Cool. So can you
tell me who mine is?
Your spirit is a samurai
who looks like he can
really keep you safe.
Wow.
Yours is a fancy lady
from Europe
or somewhere else
with lots of blonde people.
--Really?
--Me next. Do me.
Yours is-- Aah.
Um, he's like a bard maybe?
Could be from France.
--Oh, my.
--Hey.
He might be in his mid-twenties.
Has long hair.
You see me, right?
And he's really handsome.
Hey, tell me about mine.
--Yeah, me too.
--No, me first.
[REITA] All right, ladies.
Who else wants to talk to me?
[BOY] Hey, what about us?
Uh, let's see now.
Old dude, old hag, old hag,
really old hag.
Now yours is a--
[STUDENT]
At least pretend to care.
Have him check yours, Hairo.
No, I don't have to.
Aw, man. Your guardian
spirit's incredible.
He's an intensely
passionate man.
Plays tennis.
He's got boundless energy.
I think maybe his name's Shu--
He's not dead yet.
Guardian spirits? Sounds dumb.
Still, suppose it'd be rude
not to hear you out,
so tell me about mine
or whatever. Don't care.
[SAIKI]
He totally cares.
Your guardian spirit--
Oh, wow, it's kind of abnormal.
Huh? What does that mean?
Is it some kind of demon
or monster or dark spirit?
So what is it,
not that I care--
--A Chihuahua.
--A Chihuahua?
[GIRL]
A Chihuahua, he said.
How dare he insult me like that.
This guy's a fraud.
Hey, now. What's goin'
on here, a festival?
[SAIKI]
Now here's someone abnormal.
New kid says he can see
guardian spirits, but he lies.
Oh, cool. What's that?
Now no pushing.
Everyone just wait your turn.
Hey, what's my guardian spirit?
Nendou's guardian?
Now that I am curious about.
Okay, let's see.
Yours is a politician.
What? Really?
Aw, denied.
[bell chimes]
Got to say. I'm really happy
I transferred to this school.
I can already tell I'm gonna
have an awesome time here.
Say, wanna hear about
your guardian spirit, Saiki?
Me? I couldn't care less,
but tell what him his
'cause he's getting
really annoying.
Aw, just shut up.
I've told you not to follow me
everywhere. I hate you.
[SAIKI]
Whoa. What got into you?
Ow.
[gasps]
[groans]
[REITA] What?
You're not a ghost?
[SAIKI]
You really didn't know?
But all this time
he's been following us,
you never once
acknowledged his presence.
I thought you
couldn't see him.
[SAIKI]
I just ignore him.
--What was that all about?
--No way.
It's true. I see
an old hag behind him.
He can't tell the difference
between the living and the dead.
Psychic mediums
sure have it rough.
[REITA] Hey, Saiki, there's
something I've got to show you,
but you'll have to touch me
using your psychometry power.
I think when you see this,
you'll understand why
I was so confused before.
Is that--?
[snores]
Allow me to introduce
my guardian spirit.
[SAIKI] I'm sorry.
You really do have it rough.
Wow.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
Uhh, I can't.
It's too heavy. Aah.
Whoa. You okay? This is heavy.
Where are you takin' it?
The teachers' lounge.
Kineshi Hairo--our class rep
and pillar of the community.
Due to his kindness
and strong leadership,
everybody looks up to him.
Although...
But... first I want you
to bring it this far.
We can only get stronger
by pushing past our own limits.
Come on. Great job.
Don't give up.
Keep going. You can do it.
[SAIKI] He's so positive,
it falls more on
the side of obnoxious.
Good hustle. Now it's time
to push myself.
I'm gonna carry it
the rest of the way
while doing bunny hops.
What?
Still, as tough
as he is on others,
he's even tougher on himself.
That's probably what inspires my
classmates to follow his lead.
Ooh, we should
hop along with him.
We don't have stuff to carry,
but we could pretend.
Aah. I'm coming for you,
teachers' lounge.
[SAIKI]
I don't hate him as a person,
but the two of us
probably wouldn't mix very well.
[bell chimes]
Hey, Saiki, did you know
that scientists say
the average person sweats
about 300 milliliters
every night
while they're sleeping?
You're telling me why?
Well, the school's
Sports Day is coming up,
and I'm working on building
the entry gate for it now.
Kudo was supposed to help me,
but then he went
and came down with a cold.
You can't quit on me now.
Beating a cold
is just a matter of willpower.
You show that stupid virus
who's boss. Never give up.
[SAIKI] Are you a monster?
[HAIRO] Really,
it's almost done.
All we have to do is connect
the arch to the pedestals.
So if you just give me a han--
[screams]
Pedestal? You were standing
just fine yesterday.
Hey, come on, get up, pedestal.
[SAIKI] Pep talks
don't work on pedestals.
What a pain. This is more than
we can fix ourselves,
--so I'm gonna go now.
--Hold it there, Saiki.
We can do this.
If we work fast,
we'll finish before
the last train leaves.
Gimme a break.
Waah. You can do it.
I believe in you.
Don't give up.
Give it all you've got.
Please stop. What a pain.
Why am I even here?
[HAIRO] Never give up.
Hard to figure out
how much strength to use.
Damn it. This is a catastrophe.
We ran out of lumber.
[SAIKI] So we should
give up? Give up already.
Saiki, keep it up.
I'm counting on you.
Waah.
Seriously? I could just go home,
but then I'll have to deal with
a guilt trip from him tomorrow.
How could you just abandon me?
What part of "never give up"
don't you understand?
[SAIKI] It'll be a lot easier
if I work without tools,
seeing as I'm not used to them.
But it'll look suspicious
if I finish too much.
[hisses]
Might as well read a book
while I wait.
It's taking a long time.
What's he doing?
Is he slacking off?
No, that's not like him.
Guess I should try to find him.
Clairvoyance.
Ah, there he is.
What's he doing? Uhh.
[groans]
[SAIKI] Where the hell
did he get that?
The lumber shop
may have been closed,
but there are always logs
on the ground.
[GIRL] What's wrong with him?
Did somebody tie him
to a tree or something?
I will never, ever give up.
You know, sometimes it really is
better to just give up.
Saiki's working hard right now,
all by himself.
I can't give up.
I have to do this for him.
I'm fine. Please give up.
Uh. What the hell?
What now?
[HAIRO] The log. There's--
It's covered in fungi.
Then just ditch it.
[HAIRO] No, I can't give up now.
[Hairo screaming]
That's some slimy fungus.
Sorry I took so long,
but don't worry.
We can still finish by morning.
[BOY] Oh, you'll finish
sooner than that.
[HAIRO]
What're you guys doin' here?
We were doing
after-school activities
and saw you sliding by
on an out-of-control log.
[GIRL] Since you
always help us out...
[BOY] We wanted to help you.
Wow. 'Kay, let's do it.
Huddle up, guys.
--Let's go, team.
--Can we get started now?
Stop the fungi from breeding.
Saw like crazy.
Hey. No slacking off.
[strains]
[BOY]
We're finished. It's done.
[SECOND BOY]
Oh, it looks pretty good.
[SAIKI]
What a pain.
I didn't think
it'd take this long.
Normal people
have it rough, too.
Though doing this kind of thing
isn't so bad once in a while.
Hey, but wait.
Why are we preparing stuff
for the Sports Day now?
It's still
a month away, right?
Are you kidding?
A month will pass in no time.
[SAIKI]
Yeah. We don't mix at all.
♪
[WOMAN] We're leaving, Kuu.
Hold down the fort, okay?
We'll be back around nightfall.
They're going to a wedding.
Someone from Dad's work.
I don't understand why Kirishima
is having his wedding
smack in the middle of summer.
This heat is unbearable.
I mean, honey, don't you agree?
It's even hotter outside.
[SAIKI] You guys are hot because
you're clinging to each other.
Anyway, Kusuo, are you sure
you don't wanna come with us?
You've met Kirishima before,
right?
Not interested.
On the surface, it seems like
a happy occasion full of joy.
But underneath...
Welcome to my misery.
It's a hotbed of schadenfreude,
pity, and jealousy.
You know, a wedding.
Uch, marrying her? Poor guy.
I'm not in the mood
for any of that.
Aw, well, that's too bad.
You know, your psychic powers
would've livened up
the reception.
Those things are stuffy.
My powers
aren't for your amusement.
Finally, it's quiet.
Maybe I'll watch some TV.
Hmm, this place is a mess.
Well, I guess I could help with
the cleaning now and then.
♪
There's so much dust
under the furniture.
Seriously, how could anyone
have let it get
this dirty in here?
I mean, really, it's a wonder
we don't have bug--Unh.
[screes]
[SAIKI]
There was a cockroach.
For the most part,
I'm unshakeable,
but there's one thing
I can't stand--bugs.
And it's not because
they're gross or anything.
Okay, well, maybe a little.
But the real reason I hate bugs
is I can't predict their moves.
When it comes to telepathy,
I can communicate with
most of the animal kingdom,
not just humans.
But bugs are so small that
I can't read their thoughts.
Just can't get inside their
tiny little bug brains.
And sure,
if I used psychokinesis,
I could catch 'em easily,
but I don't even want
my psychokinesis
to touch those icky critters.
Okay, so teleporting to Texas
may have been
a bit of an overreaction,
but as long as there's
a roach in that house--
Zuzuya's delivering some
Yukimi Garlic Chives Daifuku.
Be sure to answer the door.
That's right.
Mom's expecting a package,
and I've already been gone
five minutes.
I have no choice.
Got to go home.
The roach was downstairs,
so I should be safe up here.
What do I do
when the delivery guy shows up?
I'll have to go down there.
I wish Dad was home.
Aah, it's a roach.
[SAIKI] Right. Dad's useless
when it comes to bugs.
What's that? There's a roach?
[SAIKI] Mom, on the other hand,
would scoop it up
like an ace infielder
catching a ground ball
--and toss it outside.
--You're out of here.
Maybe I should bring her home
using teleportation.
--[doorbell rings]
--He's here.
Why'd he have to come now?
No, wait. This is actually good.
Once I get the package, there's
no need for me to be home.
Soon as they leave,
I can teleport far, far away.
Only question is,
how to get to the door?
Oh, yeah, nailed it.
[cicadas humming]
[hisses]
Russia
St. Petersburg
There was a Nendou.
Okay, maybe
I overreacted again.
But first a cockroach shows up,
then Nendou.
Two small-brained creatures
whose actions I can't predict.
Can you blame me
for freaking out?
I just can't seem
to catch a-- Of course.
Why didn't I think of that?
Granted, I only saw him
for a second,
but he had some kind of a net.
Ah, no problem.
Leave it to me, pal.
Doesn't matter
if it's one roach or a hundred,
--I'll get rid of 'em all.
--Great.
Well, I'll be in Brazil,
so let me know when you're done.
There they are.
There's two of 'em under there.
That's even worse.
Can I lift this thing?
Huh. Lot lighter than it looks.
If it helps get rid of those
monsters, I'll lend a hand.
Ah, now there's
nowhere to run.
You're not supposed to let go.
Anyway, take 'em outside--
[splatters]
[NENDOU] Hey,
you got any tissues?
Well, do you want to
go get some ramen?
I hate to say this
after all your help,
but could you, leave, like, now?
[KURUMI] We're home.
Whoa. It's so clean here.
Wow, Kuu. You tidied up
while we were gone?
You're welcome.
Thank you. It looks great.
Here, as a reward, have these
chocolates they gave us at--
Aah. Oh, no,
they went everywhere.
[sighs]
Uh... where's Kuu?
[water running]
Republic of Palau
Babeldaob Island
Mount Ngerchelchuus
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
[BOY] What? Minako dumped you?
[BOY 2] Hey, keep it down.
--So you're single again?
--Welcome back.
In high school,
love is always on the rocks.
Another reason
I don't get romance.
The whole thing's
a mystery to me.
Oh, no. I'm back to staring
at Saiki again.
Chiyo Yumehara.
I don't know why...
but a couple of months ago,
she had a crush on me
and wouldn't leave me alone.
I managed to evade
all her advances,
and eventually,
she gave up on me.
Thought she was going out
with some other guy, but--
He's got such kind eyes,
the cheekbones of a prince,
and fair skin
that just glistens.
I can't take my eyes
off of him.
--Get them checked.
--No. Bad Chiyo.
You have a boyfriend.
But lately, the thrill is gone.
We've lost our spark.
Those beautiful words that first
made my heart skip a beat.
There's a rain of tears
falling inside your heart.
Please, let me be the umbrella
for your overcast heart.
[overlapping chatter]
[YUMEHARA] Takeru says it
so much, I wanna scream.
And when he finally gives that
stupid metaphor a rest
and says something else--
Baby, let me be
the little blue kickboard
for your swimming heart
so it doesn't drown
in the great big ocean
we call life...
It sounds ridiculous.
I see. Breakup season's
come for you, too, huh?
And that's not even
the half of it.
His feet smell horrible.
He chews food as loud as a cow.
The way he holds chopsticks
is totally weird.
He's always a jerk
to store clerks.
He's got the worst
fashion sense.
And every time he laughs,
he dislocates his jaw,
which is a total buzz kill.
These days, all I see anymore
are his many, many, many flaws.
Ordinarily, I couldn't care less
about people's relationships.
But considering her history,
she may set her sights on me
again if they break up,
so I have no choice.
I'll be the stand
that protects their umbrella.
So this guy's Takeru?
[laughs then jaw snaps]
[screams]
Are you okay?
[sighs]
Yeah, I'm fine. My jaw
got dislocated. Sorry.
No, we're sorry
for making you laugh.
That really is a buzz kill.
Oh, hey, by the way, Takeru,
how's everything been going
with your girlfriend lately?
--Great.
--Nope, wrong answer.
[bell chimes]
Ahh, I feel awful.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
but now that I'm here...
Yeah, it's fine. I just
got here, too. Don't worry.
--So, want to do something?
--Whatever.
All right, then let's do
something.
I can't stay out too long.
He thinks this is going great?
Wanna hit the arcade?
Nah.
Is there someplace
you'd rather go?
No, not really.
This relationship's
in worse shape than I thought.
Yumehara's affection for Takeru
is already down to 57.
And it just dropped
three points.
Naturally he forgot that today
is our three-month anniversary.
Ah, girls make a big deal
out of anniversaries.
Even after all these years,
Mom still wants
something special every month.
So did Takeru remember?
I feel so relaxed
when I'm with you.
You're like a massage chair
for my heart.
That's even worse. But I have
no choice, so three months.
--Huh? Three months?
--Wait? What?
Wow, you remembered
our three-month anniversary?
I'm so touched.
[SAIKI] Good.
Yeah, of course,
and I got you something.
--Really? How sweet.
--His likability shot up.
Does he have something for her?
[TAKERU] Crap,
I don't have anything.
--Of course not.
--Score. I've still got...
some of that squid jerky
I was eating in class.
[SAIKI] What girl
wants squid jerky?
--Can I look now?
--I'm ready.
No, you're not.
Oh. How cute. A bunny.
She was eying it
in the window earlier.
Good thing I bought it,
just in case.
Don't worry.
I'll take the money...
out of your wallet later
to reimburse myself.
I smelled squid jerky,
and for a second,
I was afraid
that was gonna be my gift.
Like, I would do that.
[NARRATOR] Saiki
continued to help Takeru out,
trying to boost
his likability score for Chiyo.
And finally, it hit 90,
a major milestone.
[YUMEHARA]
I'm having the best time today.
--Right? Let's grab dinner.
--Sounds good.
--The burgers there are--
--Okonomiyaki.
--No way.
You must've read my mind. I was
thinking about Okonomiyaki.
His score's so high,
I wouldn't be surprised
if she married him.
There's no way
they're gonna break up now.
[MAN] Welcome. Party of two?
Oh, wow, you can count. Now
take us to our table, dumbass.
Man, I'm starving.
This is great.
[talks with mouth full]
Uch...
I can't take it anymore.
Goodbye.
Huh? Hey, wait.
Oh, right.
Likability can plummet
in an instant, too. Ahh.
♪
[woman singing ending theme
in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
Sports Day.
My least-favorite school
event is approaching.
And as Hairo said,
a month will pass in no time.
Next time on The Disastrous
Life of Saiki K.,
I'll live every day
to the fullest
by being extremely cautious
and never letting my guard down.