♪
[SAIKI]
People aren't born equal.
[MAN]
Are you really changing schools?
This will be a step down
from your father's
--prestigious alma mater.
--I've made my choice.
[MAN]
I'll make the arrangements.
[SAIKI] I was born a winner.
Is it talent? Looks?
No, nothing so meaningless.
I was born
with a far greater power.
By which of course I mean,
money.
[STUDENT 1] Heard there's
a new transfer student.
Heir to the famous
Saiko Group.
[SAIKI] Seriously, another
transfer student?
[STUDENT 2]
Saiko Group?
They're a super-huge
conglomerate.
[SAIKI] So he's one of those
rich guys you see in manga.
[STUDENT 3]
Why would a rich kid come...?
Okay, kids, take your seats.
Before we begin,
let me introduce
our new transfer student,
Metori Saiko.
[STUDENTS] He's just throwing
his wealth in our faces!
Yes, I'm the Metori Saiko.
And let's get
something straight.
I'm not here
to befriend peasants,
so know your place
when you speak to me.
Right, well, you can take
that empty seat there.
No, no, I'll take
that weird-lipped urchin's seat.
Weird-lipped urchin?
Don't act all high and mighty
just because you're rich!
Who's acting?
I am high and mighty.
How dare you look down on me,
you jerk!
--[STUDENT 1] Just calm down
--[STUDENT 2] Hey. Takahashi?
Miss Shima,
I'd like to change seats.
[STUDENT]
Did he buy you off?
[TAKAHASHI]
Of course not, Mr. Saiko and I
just came to an arrangement,
that's all.
This guy seems
like a real piece of work.
[SAIKI]
Really? I welcome any student
who wants nothing
to do with me.
What do you thing you're doing?
--[KUBOYASU] Force of habit.
[SAIKI]
Yeah, punks habit.
[METORI]
Cheap-ass middle part.
Hey, why'd you come
to our school anyway?
It's a fair question.
Ordinarily, I'd never set foot
in such a filthy school,
but I have a good reason.
And that reason is you,
Kokomi.
I saw you in town
and had to track you down.
--I like you. Be my girl.
--[ALL] What?
[GIRL] Saiko Group's
heir transferred here
because he's got a crush
on Kokomi.
Of course he's the talk of the
school. He thinks he's so great.
I just wanna beat the crap
out of him.
Try not to let him
get to you, Aren.
The guy lives
in a different world.
I mean, look. It's like
he's living in some manga.
Always surrounded by butlers
and bodyguards.
--Better stay away.
--[SAIKI] I spy a familiar face.
That's not an excuse.
I still think
we should beat him up.
He's got bodyguards, though.
[KUBOYASU]
Then we'll beat his bodyguards.
[KAIDOU]
If his parents get involved?
[KUBOYASU]
Beat his parents too.
[SAIKI]
Who aren't you beating up?
[METORI]
What are you yapping about?
Not that I have any interest
in the problems of poor people
like you.
So have you guys seen Kokomi
anywhere?
Huh? Kokomi? Let me give you
a piece of advice.
Teruhashi's got
a very passionate fan club,
--so you'd better watch--
--Mr. Saiko! I'm so sorry,
but we couldn't find
Teruhashi anywhere.
She may be hiding
in the ladies'--
[KUBOYASU]
What do you think you're doing?
Did you all pull
a Takahashi?
[METORI]
That's right. These gentlemen
gave into the power of money.
For, you see, no one can resist
its awesome sway.
And soon, Kokomi too will fawn
over me and yes, become mine.
Watch your mouth!
She's not that kin--
[STUDENT]
Fight! Someone get a teacher!
What? They own that
company too? Aah.
His family is like super-duper,
out-of-this-world loaded!
[NARRATOR]
She is that kind of girl.
[KOKOMI] Metori Saiko.
Status-wise, he's perfect.
The only problem is that
my married name, Saiko, Kokomi,
would be hard to pronounce with
those three "ko's" all in a row.
No, what am I thinking? How
often does a girl get a chance
to marry a guy
who's this stinking rich?
--So this is where you've been.
--What? Saiko?
But this
is the ladies' room.
Are you sure? Well, let's
fix that. Chop-chop, guys.
So then,
will you be my girl?
You couldn't ask
for anything more, could you?
Let me rescue you
from a life of poverty.
[KOKOMI]
What is with this guy?
[METORI]
You'll never find a man
worthy of you in this run-down
slum of a school.
Screw you!
[GRUNTING]
--[KAIDOU] Aren! Are you okay?
--Huh, I never expected
a run-of-the-mill,
muscle-for-hire
in a stuffy black suit
like him
to pack such a mean punch.
A pathetic kid like you
can't even lay a finger on me,
let alone our young master--
Ha. I wouldn't be so sure.
[SAIKI]
If this brawl gets any bigger,
I could get dragged into it.
And more importantly,
this isn't a
fighting show, so...
--[GRUNTING]
--Take that!
[SAIKI]
Hey, where is the young master?
--Shoot!
--[ALL CHEERING]
Come on, you know you want this.
To be the wife of Metori Saiko,
heir to the Saiko
Conglomerate fortune--
--Sorry, but no.
--Excuse me?
The old me would've accepted
his proposal right away,
but now I can't forgive
this arrogant snob
for mocking my friends.
For mocking him.
It's just that I already like
somebody.
I like Saiki.
[GASPS]
Saiki?
[SAIKI]
I'm too late.
♪
I like Saiki.
Saiki? Why'd Saiki have
to show up now, of all times?
Did he hear me? Am I safe?
Is my secret out?
And just what is he doing
in the girls' bathroom anyway?
Huh? When did this become
a men's room?
Never mind that,
I have to cover somehow.
Look, it's not what you think.
That was just an excuse
to turn down his proposal.
Please, let him buy this.
Better yet, please let him
be sleepwalking. He's asleep!
Which means he couldn't
have heard what I said earlier.
--Thank goodness, I'm safe.
--[SAIKI] That was easy.
[KOKOMI]
What I was saying to before
that is the reason why I
can't go out with you now.
--I'm sorry.
--[SAIKI] Can I wake up now?
You're picking
this penniless buzzkill over me?
[GASPS]
Oh, good. He's still asleep.
Yeah.
So you're just a peasant girl
living in a fantasy land
after all.
Whatever. There's plenty
of other chicks out there.
He gave up easier
than I expected.
[SAIKI]
What a pain.
I hope I don't
get dragged into this.
Welcome home. Your father has
something important to tell you.
[SAIKI]
Why so formal all of a sudden?
Work's decided
they're gonna transfer me.
[SAIKI]
Transfer you? To where?
[KUNIHARU]
Siberia.
[SAIKI] You work for a
publishing company. Why Siberia?
Shonen Cognac is planning
to expand abroad soon.
They want their first
international
editorial department
to be in Siberia.
[SAIKI]
Why Siberia?
[KUNIHARU] They chose me
to be chief editor there.
I'll be the only editor,
so it's a ceremonial title.
[SAIKI]
That's just cruel.
We're talking about us
moving there together.
You'll come with us, right?
[SAIKI]
Are you nuts? I've got school.
You can transfer there.
They probably
have a great private school,
Like Siberi-Academy.
That sounds fun.
--Super fun.
--[SAIKI] I'm not going.
[NEWSCASTER]
Our top story tonight,
popular actor Toru Mugami
has been caught
in a torrid love affair.
--His paramour is a...
--It's not true!
--[REPORTER 1] Talk to us.
--[REPORTER 2] Can I ask you
about your son's love life?
Bet he did this.
[MAN]
I made the arrangements,
--as you ordered.
--[METORI] Do you little peons
now have at least an inkling
of what happens
when you defy the chosen one?
[MAN] Master, please try
not to bathe in money.
You'll get paper cuts.
[KOKOMI]
Kuboyasu got arrested?
Yeah, for assaulting
Saiko's bodyguard,
even though that jerk
started the fight.
Oh, no.
Saiko's putting
the squeeze on us.
My dad suddenly
got a job transfer,
totally out of the blue.
I'm moving to Siberia.
[SAIKI] Hey, maybe we'll
be in the same class.
It happened to me too.
Yesterday they cut off
--our water and power.
--[SAIKI] You don't pay bills.
He got to me too.
The Jump I bought last night
had boogers
on three pages in a row.
[SAIKI]
I don't think that was him.
[METORI LAUGHS]
Heard cheapo middle part
got locked up.
--You monster.
--[METORI] That broke buzzkill
and broke pipsqueak
are moving to Siberia.
We're changing schools
together?
[SAIKI] Decide what clubs
you're gonna join yet?
[METORI]
And you, balls-chin,
did you enjoy the book
you bought last night?
[SAIKI]
So the booger thing was you?
[METORI]
Hey, super-broke girl,
you like that
laxative-laced bread?
Oh, yes, it was delicious.
Some kind-hearted stranger
--must've left it there.
--[SAIKI] Didn't work on her.
You picked the wrong man
to defy.
If your stubbornness
persists,
more misfortune
will befall you
and the people
you care about.
Weigh your options carefully.
Huh! Don't worry about it.
Yeah, we all can
handle boogers,
Siberia and jail.
They're no big deal.
Equating boogers
with Siberia's absurd,
--but he's basically right.
--[SAIKI] I'll show you
who picked the wrong person
to defy.
[METORI LAUGHING]
Kokomi's backed
into a corner now.
[MAN 1] Please don't sit
on the stacks of cash, sir.
[MAN 2] Young master,
you have a visitor.
--So she came to grovel, huh?
--[MAN 2] Well, actually...
[MAN 3] Hey, do you have any
idea whose house this is?
I've never seen our Teruhashi
look that sad before.
If we don't protect her,
who will?
Come on, guys,
let's get him!
[METORI]
What's going on?
--Get rid of them now.
--[BOTH] Sir!
Damn riffraff. Maybe I'll call
for reinforce--
Aah! Who the hell are you?
[SAIKI] You've caused me
quite a bit of trouble,
so now you must be purged.
Wait, calm down.
I'll give you all the money.
--[SAIKI] Money, huh?
--Even if you give some
to those losers out there,
you'll have plenty.
[SAIKI]
Oh, no, my hand slipped.
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
If you're right
them being swayed by money,
--this ought to stop them.
--Huh?
Hey, we're not done
fighting yet!
Now's our chance, boys.
They're wide open.
Why? I don't understand.
[SAIKI] Turns out there are
some things money can't buy.
--[GRUNTS]
--Going after Teruhashi
was a bad move,
and if you wanna buy me off,
it'll take a mountain
of coffee jelly,
not a mountain of cash.
Kokomi Teruhashi.
Oh, wow.
[SAIKI] What goes in
the question mark box?
♪
Hey, have you seen Kusuo?
Oh, he went out earlier.
I see. That means we've got
the house to ourselves now.
Not exactly,
because the reason he went out
was to get my parents.
Oh, hey there, Dad.
It's been a while, huh?
You really want those to be
your dying words?
Well, I wasn't expecting
a visit.
--Oh, I didn't tell you?
--Nope.
It was last-minute.
I'm sorry.
I was opposed
to this little trip,
but she insisted,
so I had no choice.
[SAIKI]
My grandfather is tsundere.
I just wanna go home
and go to bed.
I'm at my daughter
and grandson's house,
and it smells amazing!
[SAIKI]
Inside, he's super affectionate,
but he can't bring himself
to admit it out loud.
Well, since you've come
all this way--
--You go home and go to bed!
--[KUNIHARU] I'm sorry!
[SAIKI]
But when it comes to my dad,
he's only tsun.
Still, I'm glad we came,
because I'd like
to do some shopping.
Sugamo and Asakusa?
I'll show you around.
--Mm-mm. Nope, Shibuya.
--[SAIKI] Isn't that for kids?
--Just go on your own.
--Are you sure?
Hey, what's he really
thinking?
I wanna be out
with my family!
[KUMI] Ah! Shibuya gets me
so super psyched!
Oh! We should totes hit up
the Mickey D's!
[SAIKI]
That's not how kids talk.
I'll go park the car
and be right there.
Thanks for dropping us off.
We'll call you when we're ready
to be picked up.
Yeah, but I want to go
shopping too.
Watch the house
while we're gone.
[KUMAGOROU] Aah! Now that pest
is finally out of the way!
Oh, this is just
what I wanted.
I'm so happy,
I feel 40 years younger.
That wasn't very nice.
Yeah, I feel bad for him.
Let's ditch your dad
and do some shopping.
Do whatever you want.
No! Wait! I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
Don't do whatever you want.
Right. Kusuo, you get it.
You can read my mind,
can't you?
[SAIKI]
I do get it,
but I'm gonna keep on walking,
because you're being a jerk.
--[GIRL] Check out that old guy.
[KUMAGOROU] They left me behind.
I'm all alone in this strange
and frightening town.
[NENDOU]
What's wrong? You lost?
--[KUMAGOROU] Am I being robbed?
--Hurt yourself?
He think I'm some weak old man
he can take advantage of?
You don't know how the war
toughened up this man.
I'll straighten you out,
whippersnapper!
[NENDOU]
Oh, you wanna fight?
[SAIKI] I just had a
bad feeling all of a sudden.
Is something wrong?
[SAIKI]
I feel grandpa's in trouble,
but I'm probably
just imaging things.
Yeah, let's go with that.
Thanks for waiting, guys.
What do you think?
Not a bad look?
--[GIRL 1] For reals?
--[GIRL 2] A party girl.
[GIRL 3]
Gotta get a shot.
[SAIKI]
I should check Grandpa.
Nendou? What are you doing here?
Go find a vacant lot
and play with some drainpipes.
Seriously. What a pain,
--but I have to put a stop--
--[KUMAGOROU LAUGHS]
You know, you're pretty
sensible for an old man.
Yeah, well, for a youngster,
you sure have got guts, kiddo.
[SAIKI]
How'd they hit it off?
--Hey, hey!
--Hoy, hoy!
[SAIKI] This is the strangest
thing I've ever seen.
What was that?
I don't know what happened,
but now I'm even more worried
about Grandpa.
So you had a fight
with your grandson?
Aw, man, I'm sorry.
That's not good.
He's 17 years old and he's got
the biggest, brightest eyes.
His skin's so fair,
it's almost translucent.
In my eyes he always helps me
see things more clearly.
--He sounds weird.
[SAIKI] I'm not a contact lens.
I don't know how to make
things right with him.
In situations like this,
a present does the trick.
I'll help you find one.
You think you can figure out
what my grandson might like?
[NENDOU] Of course, I can.
I'm 17 too, you know.
[KUMAGOROU]
What? You sure you're not 37?
[SAIKI] Nendou actually had a
pretty solid idea for once,
but can he pick out
a good gift for me?
--[NENDOU] This is the one.
--[SAIKI] That's a no.
--Hmm.
--Any 17-year-old
--would want a dumbbell.
--[SAIKI] Except for most of us.
[NENDOU] Then how about this?
You see those coffee jellies?
--[SAIKI] Ooh.
--[NENDOU] The push-up bars.
[SAIKI] I don't want those.
And what kind of store is this?
--Hmm.
--Maybe those'll work.
-Your grandson's a contact lens.
--[SAIKI] I'm a human being.
--Every 17-year-old wants these.
--[KUMAGOROU] Absolutely not.
[SAIKI] I could use a spare
pair of glasses,
but what should I do?
Oh, right.
[KUMAGOROU]
You have a minute?
I bought these earlier
on impulse.
A spur-of-the-moment thing.
It's nothing special,
but I know I caused some
trouble, so here's an apology.
Ah, I'm so nervous,
I can't even look him
in the eyes.
Great. I mustered up the courage
to give it to him.
--Aw, thanks, Dad.
--Huh?
Mine just got broken
so I needed a new pair.
--[KUMAGOROU] How you get there?
--[SAIKI] Body replacement.
[KUMAGOROU] You've got it
wrong. Those aren't for you.
--Give them back!
--[KUMI] How sweet.
Oh, that's great.
You apologized and made up.
A stubborn old man
like you apologizing.
[KURUMI] We're sorry, too,
for ditching you earlier.
[KUMI] I'm so impressed
by you right now.
[KUMAGOROU]
I guess this isn't so bad.
♪
Well, guys, it's about
that time of year again, huh?
--Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
--Huh?
--[KUBOYASU] The Emperor's Cup.
--[KAIDOU] No!
--[HAIRO] ATP World Finals?
--My mom's birthday?
--[SAIKI] That's not it.
It's Halloween.
And we'll commemorate it
with a ceremony
at my place this weekend.
[HAIRO]
Oh, you're throwing a party?
[NENDOU] Sounds like fun.
Let's get nuts!
Not sure that's the right tone
for a day
honoring the souls of the dead,
but that's okay.
--I'll see you all this weekend.
--[HAIRO] Okay, see you then.
[KAIDOU]
The wind is calling me.
[SAIKI]
Halloween. In the West,
I think it's a big holiday,
like Christmas.
But I'm not really sure how
we're supposed to celebrate it.
Do these guys know?
Is that
the trick-or-treat thing?
--Do we wear costumes?
--Or pumpkins?
[ALL]
What do you do on Halloween?
[SAIKI]
None of us are clear.
Great. The decorations are
perfect and so is my costume.
I bet they're all
gonna be impressed.
Only thing is jack-o'-lanterns
didn't turn out so great.
But I did my best on them.
--[DOORBELL RINGS]
--Oh, they're here.
I wonder what kind of costumes
they're wearing.
I've been waiting for you--
You dressed normal?
Where's your costume?
[SAIKI]
You should be happy I showed up.
Oh, come now, Saiki.
Halloween without costumes
is like Christmas
without a turkey.
[SAIKI] Plenty of people have
Christmas without a turkey.
Well, you can wear one
of my backup costumes.
[SAIKI] It's a good thing
I arrived first.
That way I could help spare the
other guys from embarrassment.
Uh-oh, we were supposed
to wear costumes?
--This is bad.
--Yeah, I'm just wearing
my regular clothes]
a tank top and shorts.
Same here.
I've just got on the outfit
I usually wear to a party.
[BOTH]
Wait, that's not a costume?
[KUBOYASU]
Let's try the hundred-yen store.
--[HAIRO] Yeah, good thinking.
--[DOORBELL RINGS]
They're here.
I'm still working on your blood,
--so don't move.
--[SAIKI] Isn't this enough?
You guys are late, but--
Those are the worst costumes!
Where's your holiday spirit?
Hairo, you're just wearing
a trash bag!
[HAIRO]
I've got a claw too.
[KAIDOU]
That's for picking up trash!
Are you the ghost
of a garbage man?
And, Aren,
that mummy costume is pathetic!
You're just wrapped
in toilet paper!
[KUBOYASU] Don't bother
recanting those words.
They are but
a beast's ramblings.
[KAIDOU]
That guy wasn't a mummy!
Dang it, no one bothered
to prepare.
[HAIRO] So Nendou's not
wearing a costume either?
Well, he's not here yet.
I bet he won't be.
[NENDOU]
Who's not wearing a costume?
--What? Really?
--Yeah, you got me.
--[KAIDOU] Go home! Do you
even know what Halloween is?
Why am I the only one
wearing a costume?
--Whoa, look at him!
--Wow, his costume.
--[KAIDOU] They noticed?
--[GIRL 1] High quality.
--[GIRL 2] Those pointy ears.
--[GIRL 1] That crazy butt-chin
--no human could ever have.
--[GIRL 2] That hairdo screams
--"I'm a total weirdo!"
--[BOTH] Can we get a selfie?
Well, well, looks like
I showed you up, Mr. Cosplayer.
So suck it.
That's it!
Halloween's officially canceled!
[KUBOYASU]
Hey, Shun, wait!
--Aah!
--[SAIKI] Scared of your work?
[KUBOYASU] Come on. You can't
pout in there forever. Get out.
Sorry we messed up. Don't you
wanna get out of this thing?
It's not like it's nailed shut,
you know. Just lift it.
[KUBOYASU] That's not the point.
--[HAIRO] Let him come out
--when he's ready.
[KUBOYASU] He's not coming out.
[SAIKI] He's like a child
who cries at his own party,
--then hides in his room.
--Start the party.
Maybe he'll be lured out
if we're all having
--a good time.
--[SAIKI] Like a child.
So, what do you do
at a Halloween party?
That's a good question.
That reminds me,
I brought something
we might be able to use.
[HAIRO]
What is it?
[KUBOYASU]
I kind of thought that Halloween
was something like this,
so I brought a pumpkin.
[SAIKI]
That is a pumpkin.
Actually, I didn't wanna
show up empty-handed,
so I brought something too.
You know how they say,
"trick or treat," right?
If you don't give them
something, they'll prank you.
--So I brought a pumpkin.
--[SAIKI] Now there are two.
I didn't know anything about it,
so I brought roasted pork.
[SAIKI] Can't follow your logic.
--Wait, why roasted pork?
Not that everybody
bringing a pumpkin
--would do us much good either.
--I saw something on the news.
There's this annual event
where everybody brings a pumpkin
to see whose is the biggest,
and then they get a ribbon.
--[SAIKI] That's something else.
--[KUBOYASU] It could be.
[NENDOU]
My pork's at a disadvantage!
--[SAIKI] This is dumb.
--[DOORBELL RINGS]
--What do you want? Huh?
--Trick or treat, sir.
Hey, there are a couple of tiny
people here for some reason.
That's not it.
They said, "Trick or treat."
It means they're gonna prank us
if we don't give them something.
Here you go!
[ALL GRUNT]
--[NENDOU] What was that for?
--[KUBOYASU] It stinks!
[HAIRO] Those pumpkins were
the wrong answer!
--Hey, there. Trick or treat!
--[KUBOYASU] Try giving them
the roasted pork.
--[HAIRO] We got it wrong again!
--[GIRL] Trick or treat!
Too bad, guys.
That's what you get
for not taking
Halloween more seriously.
[SAIKI]
Give them a break.
You just spent
two whole hours pouting.
Trick or treat.
--[SCREAMS]
--Huh? What's that?
[KUBOYASU]
Why's he throwing candy around?
The kids want us
to give them some candy.
Oh, I see.
So this is Halloween.
--[HAIRO] I finally get it.
--[SAIKI] Well, I got my candy.
Guess it's time
to head home.
[SAIKI]
What goes in the box?
[TORITSUKA] I wish something
naughty would happen.
[SAIKI]
Is that all you think about?
♪
[BUTLER] So, young master
isn't coming out again?
[MAID 1] He's locked himself
in his room for a week now.
[METORI] Who knew poor people
could be so much trouble
when they band together.
What a drag.
[FATHER] Buck up, son.
I heard what happened.
[METORI]
Father! It's too bright
from all the gold he's wearing,
not to mention his halo.
I'm his own son and yet
I can't even see his face.
The only thing I can make out is
he's stroking his Siamese cat.
[FATHER] I won't allow you
to just turn tail and run.
You represent the Saiko Family,
so start acting like it.
Has anyone seen that fancy kid?
You know, the new transfer?
Wasn't he mobbed
by Teruhashi's fan club?
Ha! Those guys
were merely a distraction.
In reality, it was I
who was pulling the strings.
I took advantage
of the commotion to unleash
my sealed power
Dark Dragon Cannon,
which brought an end
to his oppressive--
[METORI]
Oh. So that was all your doing?
Then you might wanna say
your prayers.
Hold on, I was just--
[SAIKI]
I'm rooting for you.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Oh, hey, wanna come
get some ramen with us?
Why are you inviting him,
moron?
[METORI] That guy's name
was Nendou, right?
He's being nice to me.
Maybe he's after my money?
[KAIDOU] If that jerk's going,
then count me out.
--[KUBOYASU] Let's go, Saiki.
--[METORI] I guess he'll do.
Once I have one of them
in my pocket,
the rest will follow suit
soon enough.
Hey, I know a place even better
than a ramen shop, okay?
[NENDOU]
Wow! This is awesome!
--It's okay for me to eat it?
--Eat whatever you like.
[NENDOU]
Yummy. This is yummy! So yummy!
You know, Nendou, you're
a lot smarter than you look.
--[NENDOU] Huh, you think?
--A shrewd move you played,
angling to become
my lackey first.
Huh? Your lackey?
Not a chance.
[METORI]
This guy. He's clearly no dummy.
I mean, we haven't even
discussed moolah yet.
[METORI] For now,
here's a million yen.
Just a small gift. Take it.
[NENDOU]
You're just giving it to me?
And every time
you follow my instructions,
you'll be compensated.
For real? You're a good guy.
It looks like
we've got a deal.
You are officially
my lackey now.
Your lackey? No way.
Absolutely not.
[METORI]
He's a tough negotiator.
I think that you're missing
a zero here.
[METORI]
How about 2 million?
[SAIKI]
You're wasting your time.
There's an old proverb that
describes what you're doing.
--Casting pearls before swine.
--Dessert menu, sir?
[SAIKI] Definitely. And put
my bill on that guy's tab.
--For 150 million yen?
--[SAIKI] Rapid inflation.
I don't really get
this lackey thing,
but I'm more than happy
to be your friend.
[METORI]
What's he saying?
I can't make you
my best buddy,
because I've already
got one.
[METORI] He wants a
relationship where we're equals
and he's free to obey or disobey
my orders as he pleases?
--Is that what he means?
We have to be total equals here.
You're not gonna be
the boss of me.
[SAIKI] You've had him
wrong this whole time.
[NENDOU] Man, that steak
was really yummy.
Like, seriously yummy.
And those shrimp
were super yummy.
And the garlic rice
was yummy.
And that dessert at the end
[SAIKI] Can you say
something other than "yummy"?
[METORI]
What's with this guy?
I feel bad
you paid for all that,
so let's go somewhere else.
It'll be my treat.
[METORI] So you don't
wanna owe me anything?
Enough! I don't beat
around the bush, so here.
150 million yen if you agree
to be my lackey right now.
No more games, Nendou.
Just say yes.
There's nothing money
can't buy.
[FATHER] Son, there's nothing in
this world that money can't buy.
[METORI] I've lived my life
based on my father's words.
[SAIKI]
What a horrible parent.
[NENDOU]
Thanks, but no thanks.
No matter how much money
you give me,
--I'm not gonna be your lackey.
--[METORI] Are you insane?
There's no amount of money
that can sway you?
[NENDOU]
For me to be your lackey,
you'd have to buy me
at least 100 ramen.
[METORI]
This could buy that easily!
[NENDOU] Really? You can eat
that much on this kind of cash?
[METORI] This is 150 million
yen we're talking about.
[SAIKI]
Nendou has no concept of money.
For him, it was like being
offered 15,000.
--[BOY SCREAMING]
--What do you say?
Are you going to agree
to be my lackey or not?
Yeah, sure.
Give that case to me.
[METORI]
Once he understood its value,
he sure changed his tune.
Well, that settles it.
There truly is nothing
money can't-- Huh?
Are you crazy?
It's blowing away!
Hey, kid!
Can you hear me?
Here! Hold on to this!
Don't move, okay?
What the--? Seriously?
He gave up all that money
just to rescue a kid?
Guess he didn't understand
how much it was worth after all.
No, he knew.
He sacrificed it,
despite knowing.
And all for some kid
he's never even met.
Oh, hey, buddy.
[SAIKI] Seriously, you can be
so reckless sometimes.
I'm glad Saiko had something
I could toss in that floats.
[SAIKI]
There's no way an aluminum case
is buoyant enough
to keep a child afloat.
[NENDOU] Of course, now I
gotta become Saiko's lackey.
[SAIKI] I don't think you
have to worry about that.
I can't believe it.
Father lied to me.
There are some things
money can't buy.
♪
[SAIKI] My high school
life's been pretty stressful,
and when the tension builds
for this long,
even a psychic like me
can feel like
he's on the verge
of a breakdown.
But that's where coffee jelly
can be a big help.
Mm, it really relaxes me.
Next time on
The Disastrous Life of Saiki K,
well, it all comes
to an end.