♪
[man singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
It's that time of the year
when excitement runs through
every school.
That's because it's
time for
one of high school's
biggest events,
The school trip.
[GIRL] I've never been
to Okinawa before.
This year we're going on
a 3-day trip to Okinawa.
You think
it's hot there?
It's a southern
island!
Seriously?
I don't get the appeal
of these trips at all.
I can go to Okinawa
and come back
within three minutes.
Saiki, have you picked
your group
for the trip?
It's gotta be a total
of three boys
and three s.
Let everyone else
decide.
I'll just go
with whoever's left.
Looks like
the only ones
besides you
are Nendou and Kaidou.
Guess the best weren't
saved for last.
That's three boys.
Perfect!
I'll mark you down
as a group.
Let me know once
you find three s.
Now I'm even less
excited about going.
Especially since--
Saiki's gonna be with
those two guys after all.
Just as we suspected.
The only thing that
we have to figure out
is how we're going
to join up with them.
I'd be way too embarrassed to
ask them directly.
Oh, I know!
Why don't we have
Mera do it!
Chisato's out today.
[YUMEHARA]
I heard she's working
to earn money for
the trip.
[TERUHASHI] Ugh,
sounds rough.
[YUMEHARA] Got a postcard from
her yesterday. See?
[TERUHASHI] Tuna? Whoa.
So what should we do?
There's no other
option.
I'll have
to ask Kaidou myself!
[TERUHASHI] Whoa, she's gonna
ask the guy she likes?
That's pretty
forward.
[NARRATOR]
Teruhashi's under the impression
that Yumehara likes Kaidou.
She could not be more wrong.
Oh, no, I don't see
Kaidou anywhere.
That's okay,
I can ask Nendou.
He's right over
there.
Whoa, she's asking
the guy she likes?
[TERUHASHI] The 's got
guts!
[NARRATOR]
Yumehara thinks Teruhashi
likes Nendou.
She is also very wrong.
[YUMEHARA] Hey, Nendou, wait!
[excited chatter]
[giggles]
I can't ask
to join Nendou's group
with all these guys around.
[SAIKI] Hm! If you did that,
Yumehara wouldn't be
the only one
with the wrong idea.
Uh, what's goin' on?
[SAIKI] Teruhashi's too popular
for her own good.
I have relatives in Okinawa.
I can show you around!
I used to live in Okinawa
and they called me
"Islanders' Treasure"
when I was little!
I'm friends with
Bi Kyo Ran's bassist!
[BOY 1] Liar!
[BOY 2] They're from Shizuoka!
We have no choice.
We'll decide
the boy/girl match-ups
via random draw.
Teruhashi, you're up.
[TERUHASHI] Aw, this stinks.
I have to depend
on blind luck.
Then again,
God does adore me.
A one-in-six chance
tipped in my favor
isn't too much to ask.
Just gotta use
those puppy-dog eyes.
Please let me pick
Saiki!
Okay!
I've got this in
the bag!
[SAIKI] It's truly frightening
how she always gets
what she wants.
Too bad for her, though.
Puppy-dog eyes don't work on me.
[TERUHASHI] I pick this one!
So then,
Teruhashi's group
will be joining
Takahashi's group!
[group giggling]
[TAKAHASHI]
If you wanna talk to Teruhashi,
you'll have to go through me.
Guess we can play
board games or something
when we're at
the hotel.
Yeah, I'll bring
Uno with me.
We know which guys
Teruhashi is going with,
but what about the rest
of the s' groups?
Shall we keep drawing
names?
[muttering]
[HAIRO] Talk about a drop
in enthusiasm.
[SAIKI]
The groups were set
to be paired
by lottery, but--
[GIRL 2] Nendou's group?
Ew.
Can we, like,
pick again or something?
This totes bums us out and ruins
the whole trip for us!
That's kinda harsh.
That's
going far.
[SAIKI] I don't care
who we wind up with,
as long as it's not
Teruhashi's group.
I want to switch!
Teruhashi!
[SAIKI] Damn it.
If Nendou and the others
don't mind.
[TERUHASHI] This is perfect!
Normally, wanting to join
Nendou's group
would seem strange, but--
Come on, stupid,
don't you get it?
[SAIKI] Yeah,
in this situation...
She's sticking up
for Nendou!
So selfless!
That's Teruhashi
for you!
[ALL]
That's our Teruhashi,
you're a benevolent goddess!
This doesn't just
make sense,
it actually makes me
more likable.
We're gonna have fun
together!
[SAIKI] God loves her
way too much.
We just dodged
a major bullet, s!
We can dig holes in
the sand during our downtime.
All day long.
Hairo, can we talk?
Ms. Shima?
[HAIRO]
Who's in Mera's group?
Oh, right here!
That'd be us!
Sorry, but she can't go
on the trip.
What?
They couldn't catch
as many tuna
as they'd hoped.
An unfortunate setback.
[GIRL 3] Tuna?
[BOY 3] Seriously?
[GIRL 4] Too bad.
Oh, I see.
That really is a shame.
That means
we'll be forming
five groups
of seven instead, okay?
[both scream]
[HAIRO]
Let's have each member
of Teruhashi's group
join another group.
[BOY 4]
Please pick us, Teruhashi!
[BOY 5]
Please, I need this!
[SAIKI] Looks like God's on my
side this time.
♪
[KUNIHARU]
Your school trip's
next week, huh?
I want you
to be careful, okay.
Nendou and Kaidou
will be with you,
so there's no
cause for concern.
[SAIKI] They're the definition
of concern.
[KUNIHARU] Two nights?
Try not to use
your powers in your sleep.
[SAIKI] I won't.
Remember
how you did that
up until
the fourth grade?
We had to clean up
after your
nighttime accidents.
[SAIKI] Don't make it sound
like I wet the bed.
Anyway, I'm glad things
worked out
and my group got
split up,
though I do feel
kind of bad for Mera.
[doorbell rings]
Wonder who that
could be.
I'll get it.
[SAIKI] Oh, come on.
Are you going on vacation
with Kokomi?
[SAIKI] This is Makoto,
Teruhashi's older brother.
Hey, what are you
looking at?
[SAIKI] He may be a big star,
but he's also a big perv,
so I don't wanna
talk to him.
Answer me! Is it true
that you're taking
my sister on a three-day,
two-night trip!
[SAIKI] A school trip.
She's only
in the 11th grade!
[SAIKI] Hence the school trip.
[MAKOTO] There's gonna be
other guys?
[SAIKI] School trip.
What will you do
to my Kokomi,
you pervy
four-eyed freak?
[SAIKI] You're the perv.
Shut up! Stop trying
to mess with me!
[SAIKI] You're the one
messing with me.
Fine, if you guys
insist on going,
then I'm going,
too.
Hah-hah-hah! It's too bad
for you, four-eyes!
Bet you were hoping
to spy on her bathing,
but now you won't get
the chance!
[SAIKI] I had no such plans.
Can't fool me!
I know you were planning
to sneak into the girls room,
and then,
when a patrolling teacher
comes by,
try to hide,
only to find yourself
under the covers
with Kokomi!
My presence there means
you're out of luck!
[SAIKI] That was a little
too detailed.
I'm going, even if it
means skipping Oha-suta
and World Business Satellite!
[laughs]
[SAIKI] TV Tokyo won't be happy
about that.
Here I was relieved
when the groups
were changed up,
but if he tags along,
the trip'll be ruined.
I'll just have
to let his manager know
about his plans
to miss out on work.
[LITTLE GIRL]
Cheer up, sis!
But I really wanted
to go on that trip.
You can
go next time!
[MERA] This trip's
once-in-a-lifetime.
Please don't be
so sad.
At least they let you
take this fish home!
I guess, but it's the ugliest
fish I've ever seen.
[MERA]
Wish I could go to Okinawa.
[SAIKI]
All right, Teruhashi. You win.
[MERA]
Huh? Saiki?
[SAIKI]
There's a saying:
"Trips and troubles
go together."
What are we
gonna do, sir?
This doesn't
look good.
[SAIKI]
We learned that the hard way.
[LADY]
Due to a typhoon,
the 10 o'clock flight
to Okinawa
is temporarily
suspended.
[SAIKI]
That's right. Our school trip
may be over
before it even begins.
Not 10 minutes ago,
these kids
were experiencing
pure joy--
[STUDENT] I can't wait
to get there!
[SAIKI] --then we heard about
the typhoon, and boom,
those same kids were
like this.
I've never seen
extreme joy
turn to extreme sorrow
so suddenly.
They're in the depths
of despair.
And just when
I was finally able to go.
[TERUHASHI] I was finally
able to be in Saiki's group.
[SAIKI] And look at this guy.
[scoffs]
School trips are so lame.
We should skip it.
Whaddaya say?
[SAIKI] That was him bluffing
earlier.
But really,
he's been dying to go.
You can clearly see
the circles under his eyes.
I bet he was too excited
to sleep last night.
And take Yumehara.
I bought snacks
for the trip!
[GIRL 5] That's way too much!
[SAIKI]
Before, she showed off
all the food she brought
to eat on the plane.
Now she's eating everything
with a blank stare on her face.
Then there's Nendou.
Blonde babes everywhere
and shooting guns!
[SAIKI] Putting aside
that he thinks Okinawa
is a foreign country,
he was pretty excited.
But now look at him.
Temporarily suspended?
Tem-poo-rarily
rear-ended!
[SAIKI] He still can't face
reality.
If the flight's canceled,
will the trip be postponed?
No! It'll be canceled.
You may not care,
but we've been
looking forward to this
forever and--
[ALL] Uno?
I do want you kids to go,
but it's out of my hands now.
[GIRL 6] Mister Matsuzaki,
no!
[SAIKI] This is brutal.
Don't give up hope, guys!
The flight's not canceled yet!
Come on, sun!
Give it all you've got!
[sobs]
Hey, get over here
and do it with me!
[SAIKI] Wow, they aren't
even responding to Hairo.
They must really
be taking it hard.
[HAIRO] Where's your spirit?
[GIRL 7]
We're not in the mood.
[SAIKI]
Ouch.
Even I can't bear
to watch this.
[wind rushes]
Hey, the flight's
back on!
[BOY 6] The typhoon
just disappeared!
[all cheer]
[BOY 7] Okinawa, here we come!
Oh, hey, Saiki,
where have you been?
Uh, you're
soaked...
[SAIKI] Never mind that.
I just paid a little visit
to a typhoon in Okinawa.
♪
Now, let
the school trip begin.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
[HAIRO]
Liftoff!
[SAIKI]
It took some work,
but the plane finally left
for Okinawa
with all the kids
on board.
[STUDENT 2] I was worried
there for a sec.
It'll make
a good story.
I'm glad the flight
wasn't canceled.
Yeah.
I almost started crying.
Hey, Teach!
Let's play Uno!
I'm pretty tough
to beat.
Oh, yeah?
I bet I can beat you!
Whoa, we're in
the sky!
Hey, how do I open
the window?
[SAIKI] I'm just glad everyone's
in good spirits again--
[groaning]
[SAIKI]
Well, almost everyone.
Kaidou,
are you all right?
[groans] Hold it together.
Yeah, I'm fine.
You need
motion sickness pills.
The flight attendant
gave me some earlier,
but they didn't help
at all.
I thought
I brought mine,
but I left them
at my desk.
The flight's
two and a half hours.
I'll manage.
[KAIDOU] Just seeing
Teruhashi smile
made me feel better.
You okay, runt?
Why'd you start
puking
as soon as you
looked at my face?
[Saiki sighs]
[SAIKI] Just listening to that
makes me sick, too.
Good, I don't see
any here.
He's at that age,
so I feared
he might be
hiding dirty magazines,
Looks like I was worried
for nothing.
[SAIKI] Don't mind me.
Now what's this
about?
[KAIDOU]
I found 'em!
Didn't think they were in
the pocket
of my other clothes!
I feel
much better now!
That's a relief!
So you got a weak
stomach, runt?
[KAIDOU] Your face
makes me puke!
[SAIKI] If you knew what
your mom just found
in your room,
you'd be sick again.
I'm exhausted.
Two round-trip
teleportations,
plus I wrestled a typhoon.
Time for a nap.
Oh, my!
Sir, are you all right?
[man groans]
What's with him?
[SAIKI] Seriously.
What now?
We've got a passenger
in distress here.
My stomach's
killing me!
You okay,
Takahashi?
[SAIKI] Oh, it's just
Takahashi.
Well, then,
goodnight.
[ATTENDANT] Help! Is there
a doctor on board?
[STUDENT 3]
No! What'll we do?
[ATTENDANT] We can land at
Fukuoka!
Like hell we will!
We've come too far.
[SAIKI] One way or another,
we're making it to Okinawa.
I can't take it!
Get me off this plane!
[BOY 8] Just hold on!
[SAIKI]
Restore!
This pain!
It must be something serious--
Huh?
The pain is gone.
[SAIKI] I didn't cure him.
I used my
restoration ability
to set his body
to yesterday's state.
Which means he'll get the same
stomach pain again tomorrow.
I'm gonna have
a great time in Okinawa now!
[SAIKI]
Yeah, good luck with that.
[sighs] Had to use
my powers yet again.
Now I really need
a nap.
[REPORTER]
Breaking news!
We have reports
of a terrible accident!
A plane carrying students
on a school trip
had to make an emergency
water landing.
The downed aircraft
is Flight ASO-815.
[SAIKI] They say that when
it rains, it pours,
but this is just
getting ridiculous.
The plane is going to crash.
That was a prophetic
dream.
Should I try
my restoration power?
No, the plane may have had
the problem yesterday.
I've gotta find out
what causes the crash first.
Gotta pee again?
So we'll be landing soon?
Yeah.
Hm... Oh no,
that doesn't look good!
The needle on that gauge
is spinning like crazy!
[CAPTAIN] What? You mean
that gauge there?
What's happening?
Try pulling that lever
there or something?
[grunts]
It's not working!
It's not doing
anything!
Try clicking those buttons
over there really fast!
Click, click, click!
We're losing altitude!
Oh, this is bad!
This is really bad!
If we don't do something quick,
the plane's gonna crash
in the water!
What's wrong?
That was a heck
of an earthquake.
Captain,
we're gaining altitude!
Really? Guess banging
stuff at random works!
Weird, the problem
isn't fixed, but...
[SAIKI] Oh, man.
This was easier than trying
to find the cause,
though it is kind of heavy.
Don't know how,
but we're flying.
Let's land
while we can!
♪
[NENDOU]
Woo-hoo! We're here!
Hey, you don't
look so good, pal.
Perk up bro.
[laughs]
So planes make you
motion sick, too?
How many troubles do I have
to deal with on this trip?
♪
[SAIKI]
Okinawa.
The westernmost prefecture
in Japan.
It's one of the country's
top resorts,
with beautiful views,
rich cultural heritage,
and fantastic tourist spots.
And now our school trip--
[indistinct conversations]
[SAIKI] --can finally begin
for real.
♪
[SAIKI] I sure hope this
three-day trip goes smoothly.
Whoa, cool!
Look, it's green!
[SAIKI] So far I've seen
nothing but sea.
Somebody's
been dumping
green paint
out there, right?
[SAIKI] Seriously?
Unfortunately,
Nendou's not the only one
who's excited.
Okinawa!
Crank up the heat!
[in unison] You're sweating
like crazy, Hairo!
[SAIKI] Since we're on
vacation,
everyone's
obnoxiously loud
[YUMEHARA] Tada!
Whoa, hey!
What're you doing?
No worries. I'm wearing
a bathing suit underneath!
Soki soba,
Aguu pork,
goya champuru,
red bean soup.
[SAIKI] At this point, Kaidou's
the only one keeping quiet.
Hey, runt,
you've had your nose
stuck in
that dang book
this whole time!
Try livin'.
You sure are
kashimashii today.
Wow, you weren't kidding!
The sea is quite chura.
Chura?
[KAIDOU] Let's get some air.
Oh man, it's
ippee achisan outside!
Huh?
Ippei who?
I know! You're using
Okinawan dialect.
Chimu dondon!
[YUMEHARA] I forgot
my shirt was open!
I'm speaking uchinaa guchi,
the Okinawan dialect.
Oh, that's right,
they use funny words
like "salsa"
and "menthol."
[SAIKI] Pretty sure
you're wrong.
I think you meant "mensoore,"
which means "welcome."
"Kashimashii" means "noisy,"
"chura" means "pretty,"
"ippee" means "very,"
"achisan" means "hot,"
and "chimu dondon" means
"my heart goes pitter-patter."
You know a lot of words.
[KAIDOU] Wow! Teruhashi--
[TERUHASHI]
Will you teach me a few?
Yeah, of course!
[SAIKI] Great, now Kaidou's
the most excited kid of all.
[TOUR GUIDE]
Everybody, time for lunch.
[NENDOU]
Uh, so this is Okinawan soba?
It don't look
like soba.
They call it "soba,"
but they don't use
buckwheat flour.
Whatever it is,
looks good! Let's eat!
Kuwacchii sabira.
[groans]
Oh, wow! This is maasan!
This soba is ippee maasan!
[SAIKI]
Teruhashi complimented
his language skills earlier,
so now he's going overboard.
[KAIDOU]
Eat up, guys! It's maasan!
[BOTH]
That's getting really annoying.
[KAIDOU] Whoa, Mera,
you're a gachimayaa!
Hm? Hm!
This soba's so darn maasan
that nada sousou.
For those who don't know,
"maasan" means "delicious,"
"gachimayaa" means "glutton,"
and "nada sousou" means
"tears trickle down."
[SAIKI] The kid's trying
way too hard.
Uh, wow, that's
impressive, Kaidou.
I can't even keep track
of them all.
No need to worry.
Even if you don't get
uchinaa guchi,
nankuru naisa!
[SAIKI] "Nankuru naisa" means
"it'll work out."
He's been dying
to use that.
[NENDOU] I ate a lot!
That was good!
Kuwacchii sabitan.
[YUMEHARA] Hey, we have
some time left.
Wanna check out
some souvenir shops?
Yeah, let's go!
[gasps]
Habu vs. Mongoose?
Ultimate death match
in Yanbaru?
[SAIKI] Looks sketchy.
[TERUHASHI] Sounds scary.
Come on.
[MERA] Yeah, let's look
at souvenirs.
They're such fools.
You can buy souvenirs any time.
How often do you get to
gaze upon
the fiercest creatures
in Yanbaru?
[SAIKI]
This mode's annoying, too.
Whoa!
What's this place?
It looks pretty sweet!
Hah, hah!
[SAIKI] Not interested.
Maybe I'll join up
with the girls.
[Yumehara screams]
Chisato, you're not
supposed to eat
that many
of the free samples!
But this pineapple
is so juicy!
Gachimayaa!
People started
gathering around
for some reason.
[MAN 1] Chura Kaaghii!
[MAN 2] Chee-moo dondon!
[SAIKI]
The ultimate death match
in Yanbaru
sounds pretty good.
[OWNER] Howdy, and welcome to
the Habu vs. Mongoose show!
[NENDOU] Snake!
Oh, don't worry.
This snake is my friend.
He would never bite you.
Ah! Snake!
Get it off me!
It'll bite!
[SAIKI] Nankuru naisa.
[OWNER] If you encounter a habu,
you'll wanna run away fast.
Can you guess
where they'd bite ya first?
The legs?
That's right!
They want their fangs
in your shanks.
Just a little rhyme
I made up.
If you run into a habu snake,
ask if it has poison.
It'll tell ya,
"yes, I snake it in."
[OWNER] Just kidding.
[all groan]
How about this one?
What makes a habu
so charming--
[SAIKI]
He doesn't know when to quit.
Its poise!
Poisonous? You get it?
♪
Well, here's the Habu
Versus Mongoose match.
What?
You mean they're not here?
[OWNER]
Ain't like the old days.
Got animal protection
laws now.
So the outcome's
already decided?
[SAIKI] It was a 3-minute
video.
And as expected,
the mongoose won.
I wanna go.
Me too.
[OWNER] Wait,
not so fast.
Ippee maasan
makes a great souvenir.
[SAIKI]
Should've seen that coming.
I don't wanna
carry it around.
Nankuru naisa. How 'bout
habu powder and oil?
[SAIKI]
The guy continued his pitch
for 20 minutes.
By the end--
[KAIDOU]
Nada sousou.
[SAIKI] --Kaidou walked away
with all of it.
♪ Come on! ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
♪
[HAIRO]
Dinner's at 18:00
in the first floor
dining hall!
Each class has 20 minutes
to take a bath.
After, we'll have free time,
but don't leave the hotel.
[STUDENT 4] This is a swanky
hotel.
[SAIKI] Thank goodness
the first day's almost over.
Wish I could relax,
but the real hell's
about to start.
[NENDOU]
We can see the sea from here!
Huh. Wow, this room
isn't so bad.
[SAIKI] Least I don't
see bugs.
Don't block
the entrance way.
First, Teruhashi
ditches our group,
then we get stuck in a room with
you losers. Sucks to be us!
We're putting
our stuff here.
[SAIKI]
Old guy got to you, too?
Don't get down,
Takahashi.
We can still
have fun here.
Oh, yeah, I forgot
about the great views.
What's with them?
Are they up to something?
[SAIKI] Yeah, something
stupid.
Mm-mm!
[KAIDOU]
You sure like to eat, Mera.
She ate
all my snacks, too.
More rice,
please!
So where are we
going tomorrow?
Let's see, first up
is the pineapple garden.
[MERA] Drool.
Pineapple garden?
How are you hungry
while eating?
Then after,
the famous aquarium!
[MERA] Fish? Drool.
[SAIKI]
Those fish aren't for eating.
[TERUHASHI]
The first day's almost done.
Feels like the trip
will be over in no time.
[YUMEHARA]
What are you talking about?
It's barely even begun!
Yeah, you're right.
Shall we go
take a bath now?
[giggles]
Sounds good.
They're acting weird.
What are they up to?
[SAIKI] Something stupid.
[TAKAHASHI]
Hah, hah! Now this
is what a school trip's
all about!
[ALL]
Looking at girls!
What's the plan?
I scoped the place
out last week.
You flew
all the way here?
They swap
men's and women's baths
every other day.
I have a good grasp
of the other side.
That's dedication!
Yeah,
I don't know what to say.
It'll all be worth it soon
as we catch a glimpse of her!
Best place
to sneak a peek is there.
We can sit on each other's
shoulders!
[TAKAHASHI] I don't want you
on my shoulders naked!
I brought three.
[BOTH] Whoa!
[TAKAHASHI] All right!
Let's do this!
Steamy Reality
Scope!
[all scream]
Why are you showing up
in our view?
Let's try again!
What are those?
[TAKAHASHI]
What the hell is wrong
with these stupid
periscopes?
[SAIKI] That's what you get
for trying to peep on girls.
Not taking
your glasses off?
What's so great
about seeing naked bodies?
[KAIDOU] They're foggy.
[SAIKI] I see 'em
all the time, and they
don't seem that special.
[NENDOU]
This thing is amazing!
[TAKAHASHI] Shut up, Nendou!
And get your grubby--
[all gasp]
[TAKAHASHI]
It's not possible.
[YOKOTA] I'm never gonna make
fun of Nendou again.
They ain't looked at me
since the bath.
[SAIKI]
They're idiots. Just ignore 'em.
[YUMEHARA]
One, two. Good evening!
Let's play Uno!
A bunch of guys showed up
at our room for some reason,
so is it cool
if we hang out in yours?
[YUMEHARA]
That was perfect!
[TERUHASHI]
Yeah, we nailed the timing!
[YUMEHARA] That's enough
practice, let's go for it!
[SAIKI] Sorry, girls,
but I'm not really into Uno.
[sighs]
I should be safe here.
Man, I'm beat.
When I made
that typhoon disappear
and when I carried
the plane,
I removed my
control device both times,
so it's gonna be
a long trip.
[TERUHASHI]
Seriously, where could
Saiki have gone?
And why am I,
the most perfect girl,
wandering around sear--
Oh! Saiki!
Is he asleep?
Yes!
This is my chance!
Before he wakes up.
Wait, what was I just
about to do?
How could I, the world's
most perfect pretty girl,
do the kind of thing
a creepy, gross, unpopular guy
would do to a girl
like me?
[KURUMI]
Wonder if Kuu's doing okay.
Why is that?
He might have an accident.
He hasn't done that
since fourth grade.
[KURUMI] Was it
the fifth grade?
Around the time
he started wearing
that thing on his head.
[KUNIHARU] You're right.
If that's what's preventing him
from having an accident,
what'll happen
if it comes off?
Heh, heh! You worry
too much, honey.
Guess you're right.
[TERUHASHI] Here we go.
Hope it's okay
I took it off
without asking.
But if he fell on it,
this hairpin
could really
hurt him, so-- Huh?
Saiki, wake up!
We got a big problem!
[SAIKI] What?
I must've fallen asleep.
This is no time
to be taking a nap!
[SAIKI] Stop yelling in my ear.
What time is it?
We have to return
to the hotel.
You mean
return the hotel!
[SAIKI] What? No, I meant
return to the hotel.
Now calm down.
[TORITSUKA] Calm down?
Are you out of
your mind?
The hotel we were
staying in is gone!
And I've got
a pretty good feeling
that you're
behind this somehow!
[SAIKI] Oops,
I had an accident.
♪
[woman singing in Japanese]
[SAIKI]
Our school trip has been
one disaster after another.
Then I had to go
and have an accident,
making it even worse.
Next time on The Disastrous
Life of Saiki K.:
Our Okinawa adventure
continues.
Unfortunately for me.