♪
[FEMALE STUDENT 06-A]
Bye!
- Ren!
- Hm?
[FEMALE STUDENT 06-B]
Brave Star at your place again?
[chuckles]
Sure I'm down.
- Huh?
- Everyone wants to come!
- [gasps]
- You gotta show them
how good you are at it!
Sorry, but I'm busy.
[FEMALE STUDENT 06-B]
What?
That's not what you
were about to say earlier!
Can't believe you're friends
with that guy.
[MALE STUDENT 06-B]
Yeah, I've never even
heard him speak.
♪
[screaming]
- [explosion]
- Huh?
Did you finish
off the others?
[grunts] Yeah.
We just barely managed it.
Wow you're
amazing, Sir Ren!
You took down this dragon
all by yourself?
The dragon's weak spot
is its stomach.
Focus all your attacks there
and it's laughable.
[PARTY MEMBER 06-A (M)]
Sir Ren knows everything
- doesn't he?
- That's why he's a hero!
[REN] I knew this world
like the back of my hand.
Because it was exactly
the same as the VRMMO
I used to play
called Brave Star Online.
[grunting]
[REN]
Okay, let's go!
But it's huge!
Can we beat
something that big?
Yes. I doubt this will be
any trouble.
[chuckles]
[REN] At the time
I felt strong enough
to speed run the world.
I really believed it.
Until that moment.
♪
[REN]
Why? Why couldn't I win?
I followed
the online guides perfectly.
They said it should be
beatable at level 60.
And all of us
were above level 80!
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[gasping]
This is impossible.
Level 80 should've been
more than high enough.
My companions were weak.
That's why we lost!
It's not my fault!
[thumps]
[NAOFUMI] [grunts]
Ren, I'm sorry
you had to
go through that
but it doesn't mean
you have to give up.
It's only a matter of time
before the Phoenix revives.
When it does, we heroes need
to fight against it together.
Please, fight with me.
[REN] All right.
[thump]
[MYNE] How dare you put
your trust in the Shield Demon!
[REN] To be honest, I didn't
believe her either at first.
But, her tears
were real.
Not to mention.
Her slave crest.
[gasps]
I care about you more than
anyone in this world, Ren!
Everyone else may think you
to be a criminal
but I know with all my heart
you're a hero.
I believe you fought
for the sake of the world
that day, Ren.
[REN] That's right.
I didn't do anything wrong!
[panting]
[NAOFUMI]
If that's how you're gonna be
I've got some shit
to say to you, too.
This world isn't
some game.
You had loyal followers
who believed in you.
Shut the hell up!
[REN] From now on
everything's going
to be just fine!
I was just
unlucky until now!
It's not my fault.
And unlike the others
she's a true comrade
that's worthy of me.
[chuckles]
[rain splattering]
[grunts]
[gasping]
Where'd all my equipment go?
[gasps]
- [thuds]
- [gasps]
Huh?
[MYNE] Seeing as you're useless
to me now
I figured I'd go
ahead and take
what useful things
you had left.
[REN] Huh!
No way.
Me? Useless?
[gasps]
[shuddered breathing]
♪
[grunts]
[laughs]
Well, would ya look at that.
It's the Sword Hero.
Here, just like
that woman said he'd be.
[Ren gasps]
♪
[grunts] Again.
[laughs] Too slow!
[panting]
[REN] What's going on?
Why are they after me?
♪
[panting]
- [door creaks]
- Hm.
Mommy, help!
- A bad guy got in the house!
- No wait, I'm a hero!
- [gasps]
- [child crying]
- [MOTHER 06-A] The Sword Hero?
- Huh?
[sighs]
That's right. Forgive me.
I'm being chased.
So it's dangerous
out there.
Stay inside
and you'll be safe...
Get out of my house.
Huh?
We counted on you
to protect our village
from the
Spirit Tortoise.
How dare you show
your face around here!
[gasps]
Get out of here
before you bring
another disaster
to our village!
[thuds]
[door slams]
♪
[panting]
[MAN 05-B]
There he is!
[grunts]
[panting]
[thuds]
[coughing]
[grunts]
I'm... I'm a hero, dammit!
[BANDIT 06-A]
Well, well, well
if it isn't the all mighty
Sword Hero.
What are you doing
out here all alone, huh?
Where are your
other party members?
Oh, I remember now
[all laughing]
[BANDIT 06-D] What happened
to your clothes, Sword Hero?
They're covered in mud!
[BANDIT 06-B] Maybe he's not
the Sword Hero then.
- He's the Mud Hero!
- How did this happen to me?
[REN] These losers
are laughing at me.
And that woman took every piece
of gear that I owned.
I don't need companions.
I can get by fine by myself.
After all, I know everything
about this world!
I was chosen
to be a hero!
[grunts] This wasn't how it was
supposed to be, dammit!
[bandits gasp]
[whooshing]
♪
I'll kill you all.
[thunder rumbling]
[bandit 06-B screams]
[BANDIT 06-C] Wait! Stop!
Please don't hurt us!
[BANDIT 06-D] Boss, quick!
What do we do?
[BANDIT 06-A] Don't just
stand there, go kill him!
[bandits screaming]
[thuds]
[bandits whimpering]
[thunder rumbling]
♪
[explosion]
[chuckles]
♪
Out of my way.
Prepare yourself!
- [both grunt]
- [laughs]
- [NAOFUMI] Ren?
- Huh?
[gasps]
[MOTOYASU]
Oh! Greetings, father!
Motoyasu?
What are you doing here?
Defeating these bandits
before they attack
your village!
Think of all trouble
they would cause you!
I figured I'd start
by luring out their leader.
Only to find
that their leader
is someone that we know
Ren, are you?
Maneater. Meteor Slash!
[grunts]
[NAOFUMI]
I know this feeling.
- [sword clangs]
- [grunts]
The Curse Series?
[grunts]
[exhales]
You think I'm a failure too
don't you, Naofumi?
I'm going to be stronger
than everyone.
That's right.
There's no one left
to hold me back anymore.
I'm going to awaken
an even greater power here
and defeat both of you!
[screams]
- [sighs]
- [sword clanging]
I'll awaken
all of my abilities
defeat every enemy
Master every power!
And become the strongest
in every world that exists!
[NAOFUMI] He's reduced himself
to a bandit.
But his greed's
driving him
to seek more
than just treasure.
What he wants is victory.
What he craves is power.
This curse is... greed!
- [grunts]
- [NAOFUMI] But I don't get it.
Why does he still feel
so weak and pathetic?
Stop looking
at me like that!
[NAOFUMI]
Whatever the reason
the Curse Series has skills
that make you pay a price
each time you use them.
I need to stop him!
You'll never defeat me
[NAOFUMI]
I got a question!
Why isn't your comrade witch
with you?
[gasps]
[grunts]
Careful, father!
You're only making him angrier!
Ren, I swear
I'm not your enemy!
- Shut the hell up!
- Oo! Oo!
Don't forget that I'm here
if you need me, father!
Shall I kill
him for you?
No, just let
me handle him!
Ren, you gotta
calm down!
Being a bandit leader
isn't going to help you
get back what you...
I call upon thy
twisted power.
Let this sinner
pay for his misdeeds
with an execution
by beheading.
[gasps]
[REN]
Let him writhe in despair
as his head is separated
from his body.
- Guillotine.
- [chains rattling]
[groaning]
I've had enough
of this shit!
[shattering]
- [Naofumi grunts]
- Ha!
Are you okay?
Keep your
distance from him!
I'll be fine,
don't worry!
All of these
teams and guilds.
You're all worthless when it
comes to fighting on your own!
Let this foolish sinner
standing here before me
pay for his transgressions
by being crushed to death
in the name of a God!
Take my riches
and deliver a divine strike
that will purge my enemies
from this world!
Witness Gold Rebellion!
- [growling]
- [gasps]
[Naofumi grunts]
[groaning] Hold him off
for me, Raphtalia!
[REN] Damn it!
I'm not done yet!
I can still
get stronger!
I'm stronger alone than
any number of these cowards
who need to gang up
on me in order to win!
I'll show you how limitless
my strength is!
[panting]
[grunts]
Hm.
Hey, S'yne
so the curse doesn't consume
any more of him.
After that, we
can restrain him
and take him back
to the village with us.
[ECLAIR]
Pardon me, Sir Naofumi.
But if you'd permit me
to do so
I'd like to duel
the Sword Hero alone.
[NAOFUMI]
Are you serious?
Yes.
I am. I can bring him
back to his senses.
[grunts]
[NAOFUMI]
Now that I think about it
Eclair is far better
with a sword than Ren is.
She can win this.
He has more
buffs as a hero
so I'll cast
support magic on you.
My only condition
is I get to intervene
if things start
to look bad.
- Is that all right with you?
- Yes. Thank you.
[NAOFUMI]
Zweit Aura!
- [shuddered breathing]
- [ECLAIR] Sword Hero
- I challenge you to a duel.
- Hm.
My name is
Eclair Seaetto.
And if you wish to fight
the Shield and Spear Heroes
you must defeat me!
I don't care who you are.
You'll fall like all the rest!
[both grunt]
I dunno about this
can she really take him
in a one-on-one duel?
She's strong,
but he's a hero!
She'll be just fine.
This is Eclair
that we're talking about!
[grunts]
[RAPHTALIA] In a way I think
I might understand
how Eclair
feels right now.
When he swings his sword
Tell me Sword Hero
what do you seek
to gain from all this?
And why do you wish
to get stronger?
I refuse to accept anything
less than being the strongest!
Strongest in the world
the strongest
out of all the dimensions!
- That's why I have...
- [ECLAIR] And then what?
Hm?
Once you have become
the strongest
what will you do then?
After I become
the strongest
I, I'm going to...
To save the world!
That's right!
I'm the chosen hero!
The Sword Hero that's
going to save this world
from despair!
Now die!
- [sword clanging]
- [Ren gasps]
That was a task that
someone else thrust upon you!
I'm asking
what you yourself want!
[grunts]
Decide what you wish
to aim for
then fully commit
to your attack.
It's obvious that
you're not committing
to anything right now.
And you cannot defeat me
with your heart
in such a
state, can you?
You shut up.
Shut up!
♪
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
I am the strongest.
[panting]
[crackling]
To gain the strength
to be the strongest.
To gain everything.
♪
[burbling]
Devour all.
"Devour."
[NAOFUMI]
My curse is wrath.
So Ren has two.
Greed and gluttony?
It's like
the seven deadly sins!
[ECLAIR]
You're suffering, aren't you?
[thudding]
I'll put an end
to your pain.
Hengen Muso Swordcraft
Multistrike Crumble!
[groaning]
[thudding]
[laughs]
Huh.
[laughing]
There you are, Sword Hero!
[REN]
I've seen those two before.
What the hell
And the Shield Hero's
here, too!
We're gonna make you regret
killing us earlier!
[NAOFUMI]
Damn, why now, of all times?
They're gonna try
to crush us again!
All right! Time to die
♪
[chuckles]
- [groans]
- [gasp]
Eat this, I say!
♪
No way! How
is this possible?
- [both gasp]
- Motoyasu.
Any last words,
assassin?
- [screams]
- He's fast!
- [grunts]
- [slashing]
[blood splatters]
[thudding]
[both gasp]
Raphy.
- Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Ah, I see.
Those must
be their souls!
- Finish 'em.
- Spirit Blade, Soul Slice!
Oh, wow. You
defeated them.
[sighs]
He's really something.
I'll see to it that all
your enemies lie dead, father.
Motoyasu, where is your
strength coming from exactly?
I just followed
your advice
Seriously?
You made use of the power-up
methods I told you about?
[REN] He's strong.
Huh?
Why don't we get
stronger together?
[gasps]
I now know why it is
you were suffering back there.
You didn't want to die
in a place like this
with all the things
you've done.
However, you didn't know
what else to do.
Even if you did manage
to find a way
to change and
get stronger
the things you've lost
wouldn't come back.
And that's exactly why you
should live and keep fighting
to make up for the things
you've lost.
[grunts]
[ECLAIR] I know that
right now you feel weak.
But I'm sure
within you
lies a sliver
of strength.
[gasps]
♪
[ECLAIR] Together...
We can be stronger!
[REN]
This whole time
I thought I'd be
better off on my own.
- [ECLAIR] Hm.
- [Ren gasps]
[grunts]
You'll find your reason
to get stronger eventually.
[chuckles]
And while you're at it, I could
really use a training partner.
- Huh?
- [both chuckle]
You're not hurt
There you are, Filo!
[screaming]
[ATLA] That was an
incredible scream she let out.
The Spear Hero sure
is a weird guy, isn't he?
Raphy.
♪