[MC 01-A (M)]
Ladies and gentlemen
we will now begin the match
between Rishia Ivyred...
[ITSUKI] I needn't worry.
Everyone wants my help.
Everyone believes in me.
[MC 01-A (M)]
and the unstoppable
Perfect Hidden Justice!
Who will emerge
victorious?
[ITSUKI]
I have to win that money
so I can save
the slaves.
Save everyone.
I need them to understand
that I'm the one in the right!
That I'm not inferior
to anyone else.
I'll show them.
I'm on the
side of justice.
[RISHIA] Sir, Itsuki!
I see. Are you
my opponent today, Rishia?
[ITSUKI]
If so this will be easy.
Sir Itsuki
you saved me from a despair
I can't put into words.
[ITSUKI] Is that what you
came here to tell me?
And so this time.
- [sword schwing]
- Gah!
It's my turn to save you
Did you just say
you're going to "save me?"
That has to be
some kinda joke.
[KEEL] You're gonna eat
those words, Mister!
Rishia is gonna
kick your butt!
That's right,
she'll show you!
[ALL] Don't let
this guy beat you, Rishia!
[KEEL]
You can do it!
- [cheering]
- [indistinct chatter]
[grunts]
[ITSUKI]
Now I get it.
This whole fight
was a setup, wasn't it?
You lied to me.
You tricked me
just like you do
with everyone else!
I see now why fate
brought me here!
[gasps]
It's time I show the world
how evil you really are.
And as an instrument
of justice...
I'll bring you
to the truth!
Sir Itsuki,
don't do this!
The hell is
wrong with you?
What does shooting
at harmless children
have to do
with this justice of yours?
[ITSUKI] I'm...
I'm punishing
an unforgiveable evil!
[grunts]
Please stop.
[Keel gasps]
Dammit,
Itsuki, you fool.
Sir Itsuki, I'm begging you
to listen to me!
The Phoenix
will be reviving soon
so you're in
danger, too!
Naofumi!
Rumor has it that you've been
buying up child slaves.
[ITSUKI]
Forcing them to do heavy labor
and then keeping all the money
that they earn for yourself!
- Huh?!
I even heard you gave
rare medicine to a slave
to help his sick sister
just so that you could
exploit him forever!
And even now
you're using them
as human shields
to protect yourself!
You filthy coward!
That's not
even the worst!
[ITSUKI]
A mother came to me and said
that the life of her son
depended on you
but no matter how much
she begged and pleased
you refused to help her!
You forgot the part
where her son was already dead.
Why didn't you use your
miraculous powers to save him?
That's just
unforgivable!
[sighs] I shouldn't have
to explain this to you
but even a
shield like this
can't bring people
back to life.
[NAOFUMI] You have some nerve
standing there
and making me out to be
the worst person imaginable.
Especially after you failed
to defeat the Spirit Tortoise
which cost the lives
of countless innocents.
Or does it not count
when you're the one
who's responsible?
[chuckles]
Changing the subject
won't help you avoid punishment
for all of the evils
you've done.
[Itsuki sighs]
[ITSUKI]
This is a waste of my time.
If you have no intention
of repenting for your sins.
Then I won't show you
any mercy!
♪
That power again?
[ITSUKI] Allow me to introduce
you to my new weapon.
The Justice Bow!
With the full power
of this unlocked bow.
I'll show you just
how evil you are!
Prepare to be judged!
[gasps]
Stop, Sir Itsuki!
Now, you'll see for yourself
just how right I am!
♪
[grunts]
Meteor Shield!
[gasps]
[RISHIA]
A-Are you all right?
♪
[gasps]
Sir Itsuki!
Huh?
As the referee for this
underground coliseum
I must confess I was secretly
aiding the Shield Hero
behind closed doors
this whole time!
How forthcoming.
If you change your ways
then you will be forgiven.
[MC 01-A (M)]
Oh, thank you
[NAOFUMI]
This power
is Itsuki being affected
by the Curse series?
That weapon
[ITSUKI]
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's a bow that's been infused
with holy power
and given to me
by Princess Malty herself.
With this, I
have the power
to make the ignorant
understand me.
[ITSUKI] Now I can put them
on the path of justice!
Looks like
we're too late.
I think losing to
the Spirit Tortoise broke him
and then Bitch
got into his head.
The arena isn't
safe anymore.
I need you to get
everyone out of here.
Got it.
Hey, guys, everyone follow me!
- [SADEENA] Mm.
- [S'YNE] Mm.
[SADEENA]
Come on children
I'll take you all on!
Once you fight me
you'll finally understand
who's truly in the right!
[IMAGINARY CROWD (5M)]
Perfect Hidden Justice!
Sir Itsuki!
[sighs]
Yeah, well I think
you're full of shit.
Your new bow hasn't got
a damn thing
to do with justice.
It just brainwashes
people!
That's not true!
This bow is an instrument
of justice!
[ITSUKI] Yes.
And justice means power!
It means proving
you're right!
Lending aid to the weak
and humbling the strong!
And as a Hero of Justice
I have but one job to do.
To destroy every evil
that plagues this world!
He's lost it.
[RISHIA] Sir Itsuki!
I refuse to accept
your twisted justice!
[ITSUKI] I'd almost forgotten
you were here, Rishia.
Ever since the day
I met you Sir Itsuki.
I've been asking myself
[RISHIA] I wanted more
than anything to be someone
who could save
those in need
the same way
you saved me that day.
I wanted to follow
in your footsteps!
But you're not the same person
you were back then.
The justice I learned
from you, Sir Itsuki.
The justice I know
[scoffs]
You leave me no choice.
I'll prove my actions are just
and save you once again
'Cause no matter
what anyone says
I stand on the
side of justice!
[RISHIA]
Muso Activation!
Hengen Muso Swordcraft.
Shining Arrow!
Spiral Rush!
♪
[grunts]
Hengen Muso
Thrusting Swordcraft!
[RISHIA] Circle!
Huh!
So that's how it is.
I guess you have gotten
a little tougher after all.
[ITSUKI] Which makes it
all the more important
that you understand me
and awaken to justice!
- [ITSUKI] If you do...
- [RISHIA] No!
[RISHIA] I refuse to accept
the person that you've become.
Even if that means
I die by your hand!
Hengen Muso
Secret Technique.
First Stance.
- Sun!
- Meteor Shot!
Second Stance.
Moon!
That shouldn't
be possible!
My justice can't be felled
by the weak!
Now, Third Stance!
[RISHIA] Star!
That's enough! Now die!
♪
[ITSUKI]
Law Fanatic!
He must have boosted
his own stats!
Please, Sir Itsuki!
You mustn't allow that power
to corrupt you!
[RISHIA]
You don't need it to be strong!
Itsuki, you idiot.
[NAOFUMI] He's so drunk
on his own justice
it's blinding him!
Which means his deadly sin
must be pride!
That's enough, Itsuki!
Keep using the Curse series
like that and you'll regret it!
I will not be lectured
by sinners!
Shadow Bind,
ensnare my target!
[grunts]
[gasps]
Bind Arrow!
[grunts]
I-I'm not giving up yet!
Sorry, but this
fight is over.
[ITSUKI] I call upon thy power
and request this foolish sinner
pay for her misdeeds
by means of a fiery inferno
worthy of thy power!
May she writhe in agony
as her dying screams
are converted
into the cries
of a raging beast!
Bull of Phalaris!
[gasps]
Rishia!
My victory is absolute!
[shattering]
Fourth Stance!
Demon!
My eye!
[ITSUKI] Why? Why do you have
to keep getting in my way?
I'll never forgive you!
You don't mean that.
[ITSUKI]
I'll never forgive you.
♪
No, Itsuki! You
can't give in!
Fight back!
I will never
forgive you!
[ITSUKI] Any who stand
in my way must die!
Sir Ituski! Stop using that
power before it's too late!
Die in the
name of justice!
This world is stained
by your evil!
- Master Naofumi!
- Right, I'm on it!
[NAOFUMI]
Rishia, use this!
I can't do that.
This battle is solely
between me and Sir Itsuki.
If I accept your weapon
Be careful, Rishia.
[chuckles]
Looks like our fight
is all but finished.
I'm just
getting started!
[ITSUKI] Oh, really?
And how exactly do you plan
on fighting me
without a weapon?
♪
Admit you're outclassed
in every way and surrender.
[RISHIA] No matter how much
I suffer or despair...
I will never give up!
Huh?!
[RISHIA]
I learned that from you.
That's what you taught me
when you saved me
from the depths of despair
that day.
You taught me that justice
never gives up!
Don't twist my words!
[ITSUKI]
Everything about you is evil!
The opposite of justice
isn't evil!
It's my justice!
After all, everyone holds
their own ideals
their own
form of justice!
Shut up! You're a wicked stain
upon the world.
And I am justice!
Using my power to rid
the world of darkness!
Then I'll fight you
with my own justice.
Sir Itsuki
Don't go spouting
your lies at me!
- What the...?
- Master Naofumi, is that...?
[ATLA]
I was able to sense it.
The evil ki
from Itsuki's bow
A pure ki.
The Cardinal Weapons still have
some kind of hidden power?
[gasps]
What the hell just happened?
I see even your own bow
rejects the perverted justice
you cling to.
Huh?!
Your bow gave
me this strength
as if pleading for me to put
an end to this battle.
That's not possible!
[ITSUKI] My bow would never
betray me like that.
This isn't possible.
This can't be happening.
This can't be happening!
[ITSUKI]
I won't accept it!
Hengen Muso
Secret Throwing Technique!
Rolling.
Spin.
Air Strike Throw!
[RISHIA]
Second Throw! Dritte Throw!
Tornado Throw!
♪
[screams]
[gasps]
My power.
My new power that was
supposed to save the world.
[ITSUKI]
Class 3-3, Itsuki Kawasumi!
And my dream is
to be a brave hero
who fights for what's right!
And saves everyone
who's in need of help!
[applauding]
[STUDENT 11-C]
With your power
[STUDENT 11-B]
You're going to a middle school
that only kids with powers
can go to, right?
[STUDENT 11-C]
That's so cool!
[chuckles] I'm so proud
to be able to call you my son.
This can't be happening.
[ITSUKI]
I've been placed in Level E?
Level A's are
just amazing
With power like yours you can
do anything you want!
[STUDENT 11-F]
You've practically won at life!
[gasps]
Screw this.
- [rain drumming]
- [Itsuki's mom sobbing]
[ITSUKI]
I refuse to accept this.
I'm not inferior
to anyone!
[grunts]
[MYNE] I'm the only one
who understands you.
[Itsuki gasps]
That's right.
I still have someone
by my side
who chooses to believe in
who I am.
Sir Itsuki, I...
Princess Malty
is the only one left who...
Sir Itsuki, wait!
Hey, get back
here, coward!
[ITSUKI]
I'm sure Princess Malty
will understand
everything.
And that I'm on the side
of justice!
[MYNE] I'm the only one
who understands you.
I can tell that you care
deeply for this world
and all the innocent people
that live in it.
[MYNE] But everyone else
only cares about themselves.
Everyone except for you
No matter what
anyone says
you always charge ahead
to save people in need
and stand for justice.
The way that
every hero should.
Yeah, but I...
You've been
through a lot
[Itsuki grunts]
This is a gift for you
[gasps]
[ITSUKI] That's right.
I'm not the one in the wrong.
But I need to take it
upon myself
to save the
ignorant that are.
Because I am justice!
I'll save them!
Huh?
Sir Itsuki.
Seems like Witch
left you a letter.
[NAOFUMI]
Itsuki, you oughta read it.
[grimacing]
All right. I'll
do it then.
If what I'm reading here
is the truth
Bitch spent all
the prize money he won.
[grimacing]
[MYNE] Tell me, was it fun
pretending to be a hero?
You looked like you were having
a grand old time
imagining you were
saving people.
Well, it was a lot of
easy money for us
so I really should be
thanking you.
Oh. If you
see the Shield
please do me a favor
and kill him.
Do that and we'll see
each other again.
One last thing.
I left you another
little present.
She says that she left him
some kind of present.
And to have fun
paying it back.
All of these
are debt notes.
And each one of them's
marked with Itsuki's stamp.
[ITSUKI] I am.
[gasps]
I am.
[shatters]
[ITSUKI] I am.
I am.
[RISHIA] Sir Itsuki!
[crows cawing]
Huh?
- [Grandma 11-A laughs]
- Huh?
[GRANDMA
11-A] Oh, Itsuki
[laughs]
Huh?
[RISHIA] This is Naofumi
and his party's village.
He generously agreed
to help you pay off
all the debts
that you owe.
And don't you worry.
I'll be by
your side too!
Once they're paid off
we can go on a journey
together again!
[gasps]
[RISHIA] Sir Itsuki.
♪
[kids giggling]
Wait up! [Giggling]
[DEMI-HUMAN KID 11-A (M)]
Come on!
[NAOFUMI] The translucent
weapon Rishia used back then.
[NAOFUMI]
Unfortunately, even the Queen
didn't know what it was.
Either way, the Phoenix
will be reviving soon
and all four heroes
are finally together
we've even shared methods
to make us stronger.
All that's left is to make
my lands better protected.
Do you think the Bow Hero
will eventually be okay?
[Naofumi sighs]
[NAOFUMI] He succumbed to
the power of the Curse series.
His companions betrayed him
and his bow rejected him.
Itsuki may have had his
own idea about what justice is.
[NAOFUMI] But "justice"
is a complicated thing.