♪
Take 'em all!
I'd rather you fight with
our weapons than those fools.
[sponsor 02-A
(M) laughs]
I see.
He must be a sponsor.
That girl has already
mastered it?
[MC 01-A (M)] And now.
It's time to announce
the newly formed
Team Rock Valley's
next opponent!
- That was awfully quick.
- Yeah.
For their next opponent...
What's this?
It appears several teams
have forfeited!
You'll just have to wait
till next time!
[crowd screaming]
- Forfeited?
- Why would they do that?
Clangkity clang.
[NADIA] Congrats on winning
your first fight, Rocky.
The prize money
wasn't enough?
Boy, you must really be
strapped for cash
if you have to
bet on yourself.
[NAOFUMI]
So what if I did?
You gonna rat me out?
Your little secret
is safe with me.
In exchange for that.
[smiling]
You have to spend the night
drinking with me.
[sighs]
[exhales]
It's not half bad.
Tastes like
a whole rukor fruit is in it.
You can handle
a whole rukor fruit?
Yup, I could down
a dozen glasses of that.
Now, what info
you got for me?
Hmm.
Huh?
Can I help you?
Why don't we get some
fresh night air while we talk?
Up next
a round-robin
tournament.
[NAOFUMI]
That's interesting.
Oh, are teams typically told
who their next opponent is
right after the battle?
Yes. And if the teams forfeit
like today
then you win by default
and find yourself waiting
for a worthy challenger.
[NAOFUMI]
Makes sense.
And the reason
there were all those forfeits.
Was because of this?
Payback time
for beating our teams!
Prepare to
die, bastards!
Hold on
these aren't your men?
Ah.
You think so little of me.
Source of thy power
- Decipher the laws of nature.
- Magic?
Let thunder strike
each and every one of my foes
who is before me!
All Drifa!
Come forth
Chain Lightning!
♪
That's some power!
So, is this why enemies are
forfeiting before the fights?
Your enemies will do
whatever it takes
to come out on top.
Like how you put rukor fruit
in my drinks at the bar?
[smiles]
[giggling]
- Get off of me!
- [giggling]
I pray that we don't fight
one another in the coliseum.
You're better off giving up
before that.
[NAOFUMI] The next day
Aah!
They ended up matching us
against some monsters
so we used
illusion magic
to make it look
like we struggled.
And the winner is
Team Rock Valley
who defeated the three griffins
after a fierce battle!
We're witnessing the birth
of a new star!
[CALL OUT 02-A (M)]
Nice one, Rock Valley!
[CALL OUT 02-B (M)]
This is bullshit!
[NAOFUMI]
With each victory
And since we were using
illusion magic
to make it look like
we were struggling to win
the betting odds
just got better and better.
[RAPHTALIA]
The Slave Merchant said
this is the biggest
department store
in the capital city.
Happy!
I bet we could get more armor
and weapons
for our matches here.
Aah! Master, look!
There's lots and lots of food
here too!
Yeah. Let's buy enough food
to last us a while.
We should avoid going out
at night.
[FILO]
Yay! Let's go! Let's go!
[JEWELRY SELLER 02-A (M)]
Savior of the Heavenly Fowl!
- [gasps]
- Or wait
should I say
Mr. Rock Valley?
The underdog
of the coliseum!
Oh, yes. I thought
that I recognized you
from the sponsors section
back at the coliseum.
Please know
I'm cheering you on!
Everything you see here
is part of my store.
I'm willing to
invest in you
Looks like you're doing
pretty well for yourself
And thanks for the offer
but I don't wanna be
in your debt.
Come on don't say that!
You can pay me back
by giving me
joint rights to all the profits
of the land you own.
[Rishia and
Raphtalia gasp]
I'm willing to let you open up
a store at most.
Sounds like
a deal to me!
Now please, enjoy your time
at our fine stores!
[gasps] If I'm
not mistaken
I should've figured.
[RISHIA] I've heard
if he doesn't like you
he'll drive you
out of business.
[NAOFUMI] I wouldn't worry.
Well, for now at least.
We are his customers.
[FILO]
Master look at this!
- [ALL] Huh?
- We just have to buy it!
♪
Hmm?
They announced the name
of our next opponent!
They're fighting
us alone?
[exhales]
That's right!
And it's someone who wins
almost all of their fights
or places in
the top ranks!
They're either strong
or they have a lot of support
from their sponsor.
Maybe a little
bit of both.
There are more
powerful fighters than them
but this time I hear
they're not participating.
Well, we're not
fighting them.
So what is our
opponent's name?
Um, let's see.
The only name that
it has listed here is Nadia.
Nadia?
It says here
she uses lightning magic
and fights up close
with a big harpoon!
Lightning? Harpoon?
- What's wrong?
- [gasping]
Oh, it's nothing
important.
And listen to this.
Due to the forfeits, this will
be the championship match.
The championship.
Hmm.
Right then
This one's gonna be
our toughest match yet.
I say we hit the bed early
and get some rest.
[FILO] Wait! But we still
have to eat dinner!
[MC 01-A (M)] And now
that you've
all been waiting for!
This season's
championship match
at the coliseum!
Will the winner be the newly
formed Team Rock Valley?
Or the Drunken Lightning
who's consistently
one of the top-ranking fighters
each season!
Will you bet
on the new kids
with horrifying
10-to-1 odds
or play it safe
and bet on the nigh-undefeated
goddess of victory!
The choice is yours!
It's time for our fighters
to enter the arena!
Team Rock Valley!
And Nadia!
[Fan 02-A (M)]
Nadia!
[crowd cheering]
- [sighs]
- Good grief
I warned you
to forfeit this match
but you just
didn't listen.
No, I heard you
but I've got more than money
on the line
- so I have to win.
- [gasps]
Naofu... I mean, Rock
Yeah, a little bit.
[giggling]
- [giggles]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
Hey, Get off!
You're trying to get money
to buy the slaves
from Lurolona village
aren't you?
- How kind.
- [Naofumi gasps]
This might be a great way
to get a lot of money fast
but I do not lose to people
who are only here to fight
in the coliseum
to get rich quick.
Don't hold
back against her.
[MC 01-A (M)]
Team Rock Valley versus Nadia!
Let this season's
championship battle, begin!
Source of thy power
Decipher the
laws of nature.
Don't let it hit
you directly.
You might die!
Drifa. Thunder Burst!
[Naofumi grunts]
Oh!
Time for my
special attack!
Huh? Source of thy power
I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature.
You're going down, lady!
Lightning, become a power
which protects me!
Drifa. Lightning Speed!
Spiral...
Air Strike Shield!
Second Shield!
- Dritte Shield!
- [gasps]
Oh, my, you're just
one surprise after another!
[screaming]
[both gasping]
[MC 01-A (M)]
Amazing!
The two sides
moved so fast
that a field change spell
has just taken effect!
Boundless Sea
is a choral magic spell
that temporarily submerges
the entire area.
They want me
to put on a good show.
What?
How the hell's that fair?
You have to give the people
what they want, don't you?
It's time for me
to take this seriously.
Mm.
[indistinct chatter]
[MC 01-A (M)]
Hang on tight, folks!
It looks like
Nadia is about to transform.
[NAOFUMI]
"Transform?"
[MC 01-A (M)] Try not to get
caught in the waves, everyone!
♪
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] Is that
a killer whale Demi-human?
Here I come!
[grunts]
- [gasps]
- Shigaraki! -Sis!
[NAOFUMI]
Run! You'll die!
Is that you? Sadeena?
- Oh, my?
- [both gasping]
[indistinct chatter]
It really is you.
It is you, right,
Sadeena?
If you're calling me
by that name then
that means.
You're Raphtalia, right?
Yes, I am.
I can't believe it.
It's really you!
[smiles]
If you're Raphtalia
that means Rocky is...
The Shield Hero
[NADIA] Oh, my.
[crowd shouting]
[CROWD 02-A (M)]
What's wrong?
[NADIA] Uh.
Sadeena, wait!
[NADIA] You were gathering up
the children from the village
for Raphtalia's sake
[grunts] That's right.
I see now.
I think it's time
I put an end to this!
I'll finish you off
with my signature move!
Master Naofumi
Sadeena's a Demi-human
she can take it.
[grunts]
Here I go!
Zweit Tornado!
Illusion Sword!
[Nadia, Filo
and Raphtalia screaming]
♪
They're too strong for me
to continue fighting.
I surrender.
[crowd cheering]
[laughter]
[grunting]
[sighs]
The sponsors might sell
the kids from the village
that I was working so hard
to buy back all this time.
No need to worry.
I'll deal with
that issue.
[MC 01-A (M)] The winner
of the championship
is none other than...
Team Rock Val...
S-Sorry, folks
but it seems
the sponsors have declared
that this
final championship battle
will be
declared invalid.
Wait, what?
Instead, there will be
an exhibition match
between the two fighters
who participated
and a brand new fighter
who has yet to make
an appearance here with us!
- Oh, my.
- Damn it.
Your sponsor's a real pain
in the ass.
I understand
his reasoning.
[MC 01-A (M)]
So now...
Team Rockvalley
and Nadia join forces
in order to
wage a war against...
Careful, Rocky
[NAOFUMI]
The clown is dangerous?
[gasps] That's them!
[MC 01-A (M)] Their opponent is
the Murder Clown!
Betting will be available
for the first 10 minutes
after the match starts.
And we will be
refunding your money
for the finals
right away!
So we have to fight
the clown, huh?
Indeed. We can worry about
everything else after we win!
Ladies and gentlemen
I'll end this quickly!
Here I go.
Instant Blade Mist!
[MURDER CLOWN]
Spider Net.
[gasps]
[MURDER CLOWN]
Bind Wire.
- [gasps]
- The hell?
[groans]
It's too strong!
- Damn!
- Hey, Rocky
cast a choral spell with me
and we can end this!
Sorry, but I've never cast a...
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] Is it like what Ost
did back then?
[NADIA]
There's no time to hesitate!
Your Birdie and Raphtalia
are counting on this!
Hmm.
Two powers, imbued with
strength to give them succor.
Strength to overcome
destined defeat
and lead them
to a victorious future.
- [NADIA] Dragon Vein.
- [NAOFUMI] Dragon Vein.
[BOTH] We ask you to hear
our desperate wish!
[BOTH] Source
of thy power
[BOTH] Decipher the laws
of nature
and grant me the power
to overcome
the obstacles before me!
[gasps]
Oh, my. So then that's
the kind of spell we get.
[BOTH]
Descent of the Thunder God!
Hey, Rocky, Just so we're
on the same page
you know
who our target is, right?
Yeah!
[Raphtalia screaming]
Sister.
[gasps] Huh!
Raphtalia
we gave you
a choral spell
- Got it!
- I won't lose.
It's over.
Brave Blade: Mist!
[Murder Clown groaning]
♪
You're finished!
Fusion Technique.
Blade of the Thunder Emperor!
[explosion]
[sighs]
[gasps]
- [MURDER CLOWN] Scape Doll.
- [gasps]
♪
[gasps]
[MURDER CLOWN] I'm guessing
you have four buffs
applied currently.
You'll only get yourself
killed.
Your base strength
is far too low.
Say what?
[MURDER CLOWN]
Unless you're a hero
no one can
stand up against
the other world
will surely destroy you.
Especially, if you're having
trouble with me.
[NAOFUMI] What in the world
is she talking about?
[MURDER CLOWN]
I fought enough to earn my pay.
Therefore, there is no reason
to continue this fight.
Let us meet again.
Try not to get
yourself killed.
A clown who's
also a ninja?
[MC 01-A (M)] Um. It seems
Murder Clown has disappeared!
And so, the winner is
Team Rock
Valley and Nadia.
[sponsor 02-A (M)] Give me
a break. This doesn't count!
How could it
when there's foul play at hand?
Team Rock Valley
bet on themselves
under a fake name
to win more money!
They should be disqualified
for cheating!
And so, I ask you to declare
this match as invalid!
[JEWELRY SELLER 02-A (M)]
You're wrong!
This match goes to none
other than the Shield Hero.
And as victor
of the championship
he will receive his fight money
and bettings as he deserves.
- [YELLOW SHIRT 02-A (M)] What?
- [RIGHT MAN] The Shield Hero?
- I had a feeling it was him!
- You're kidding.
The Shield Hero?
One of the
Cardinal Heroes
was competing
in an underground arena?
You are correct, sir!
And Nadia is the rightful owner
of the Lurolona Village slaves
which she was
able to purchase
with her prize
money from here.
So no one will be allowed
to take them.
[gasps]
[grins]
[crowd cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
I get the slave merchant
but what's the jewelry seller
doing here giving orders?
In case you've forgotten
he also owns
the largest department store
in the capital.
[gasps] You mean he
owned that entire building?
Which means
it all worked out
- right, Master Naofumi?
- Hip-hip Hooray!
[crowd cheering]
- It's good to see you again.
- [gasps]
You too, Sadeena.
[smiles]
My how you've grown.
I'm glad to
see you're safe.
I can't believe it.
It really is you.
I'm so happy.
I really am.
I heard rumors
that the Shield Hero
had one of the Lurolona Village
Demi-humans with him.
I never thought
it'd be you!
Let's start over.
I'm Sadeena!
I'm Naofumi Iwatani.
Nice to meet you.
And thank you
for watching over Raphtalia.
Now please
take care of me
the same way, Naofumi.
[grunts]
♪
Oh, hey, there Fohl
do you want the usual?
[coins clinking]
I hope that you're able to
get them better medicine soon.
Here, take this too.
♪
Atla, I'm back.
[gasping]
[ATLA] Oh, good.
Welcome back, brother.