[grunting]
[ITSUKI] Rishia,
be honest.
I need to know if you're
the one who broke my bracelet.
[grunts]
[MALD] There's no point
in coming up with excuses.
All of us saw you break this
with our own two eyes.
[grunts]
But I promise I didn't!
[MALD] Your lies mean
nothing to us.
[RISHIA] I really don't know
anything about it!
Not even an
apology, huh?
All right.
Then I'm afraid I have
to ask you to leave our party.
[gasps] But Sir Itsuki.
- I didn't, I'm telling the...
- That's enough, Rishia.
- [gasps]
- [ITSUKI] It doesn't matter.
You've been nothing more
than a burden for us.
[swishing]
♪
[RISHIA] Sir
Itsuki, I promise.
I promise I'll
become stronger!
And prove I
can be useful!
[screams]
[panting]
[ELRASLA] Your ki isn't
focused at all, Rishia.
Huh?
[ELRASLA]
Your technique needs work.
[RISHIA] Master!
How about some training
to iron that out?
Huh?
Sure! Thank
you so must...
Hm.
[bird chirping]
Now then
This is gonna
hit our budget hard.
- You can say that again.
- Raphy.
- [Gaelion squeaking]
- Hm?
I'm the only one here allowed
to give rides to master.
- [squeaking]
- No, I'm the only one!
That's enough.
It doesn't matter
you can both do it.
It definitely matters!
[sighs]
I'm sorry, Gaelion
but you're going to timeout
for a while.
- [squeaking]
- [gasps]
What's the big idea?
Don't bully
Gaelion like that!
It's not bullying
Well, he did cause
a lot of trouble for us.
Raphy.
Hm. Hm.
[NAOFUMI] And Filo
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
We got lucky
'cause whatever happened
broke your curse.
You got it!
Hey Melty!
You should come with me
so that we can level up
together!
- Huh?
- It'll be fun!
We can get strong
and have Master play with us!
But I can't Filo!
I don't have
time to level!
And there's so
much work to do.
I have to catch up on what
I missed while I was away.
What? Come on, Melty.
You were just saying
you wanted a higher level!
Well, yeah, but
not right now!
[gasps] Remember, Melty
when you got mad before
and said
"If you can't
do it today
[MELTY] I know but...
[FILO] You said that
even if you're busy...
How typical.
She's not going to give up
until Melty gives in, is she?
Definitely not.
[MELTY] But I'm telling you
I can't do it Filo!
[FILO] Why?
[NAOFUMI]
Everybody's here now, right?
Princess Melty will be gone
for a while.
She left to go
on a journey
to become stronger
Raphy.
[all gasp]
Hooray!
"Left on a journey?"
I never agreed to this!
That's what we're
telling people.
Make sure everybody in town
knows it. Okay, Éclair?
Y-yes, right away.
Hey, hold on a second!
You can't just
decide that!
[NAOFUMI] I got permission
from the Shadows.
Believe it or not
[MELTY] Huh?
Look, you've got plenty
of magical potential, Melty
but they've been worried
for a while
that your
level's too low.
For someone running
the country at least.
He's correct,
I dare say.
But leaving like this
so suddenly is...
[NAOFUMI]
All right then, Filo.
I'm counting on you
to level up with Melty.
- Wait!
- Hooray!
Are you ready, Melty?
♪
No, I'm not ready!
- And I never said anything...
- Off we go!
-Raphy -Naofumi!
[MELTY] I promise
you're gonna regret this!
A leveling journey, huh?
What of it?
Princess or not
And kids need to play
every now and then.
And with Filo and Raphy
there with her, she'll be safe.
I hope she
manages to have fun.
I'm sure they'll
all be fine.
If you've got work to do
- Eclair.
- Huh.
[NAOFUMI]
While Melty's gone
I'm going to need you
to act as ruler
and handle her
day-to-day duties.
A-are you
sure about that?
I mean, after all
Who do you think's
been picking up the work
while you've
been slacking off?
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] You've been relying
on Melty too much, Eclair.
Hm.
[REN] If there's something
I can do to help.
Huh?
Am I allowed to do so?
[chuckles]
If that's what you
want to do, then sure.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
What's wrong?
[RAPHTALIA]
Are you okay, Sadeena?
I'm fine! It's
nothing! [Gasps]
[gasps]
Is something the matter?
Do you have to show up
out of nowhere?
[S'yne's
stomach growling]
[chuckles] Guess that means
it's time to eat.
[giggles]
[birds chirping]
[S'YNE]
Thank you kindly.
[DOLL]
It was delicious!
So then
We sure had a hell of a time
while you were gone.
Well, if I'm
not mistaken
S'yne was busy doing
some work underground.
Hm.
Underground?
She means
the underground arena.
[DOLL] And of course
half of what I earned
down there, Sir Naofumi!
[coins clinking]
Nice! Keep the
money coming!
That's not very nice
Just what I expect
from Master Naofumi!
[RAPHTALIA] Why would you
expect that from him?
I'm impressed you managed
to make this much!
And in such a short period
of time too!
Somebody made
even more than me.
[DOLL]
There's a rumor going around
about an archer
who's been seen fighting
at a different
arena every day.
An archer? Could it be?
Hm. From what I heard
their name is
"Perfect Hidden Justice."
[all gasps]
Hold on, there's no way.
I mean with a ridiculous name
like that
who else could
it possibly be?
Who you're talking about
While it's possible
But it's worth
us checking out.
You're going
back to the arena?
Then I want
to go this time!
[NAOFUMI]
We're not going to goof off.
I know that!
Come on!
It'll help me get stronger!
Hm?
[ELRASLA] You know you really
should take her with you.
- Hm.
- She'd do well
fighting mercenaries.
As opposed to fighting
the same people
all the time here
in the village.
Aah!
[ELRASLA]
I can confidently say
she's more than strong enough
now to fight there.
- [swords clanging]
- [both grunt]
[audience cheering]
[KEEL]
Wow! This is awesome!
Are we really gonna get
to fight in here?
[NAOFUMI] Yeah. Just don't do
anything dumb, okay?
[KEEL]
All right, all right!
Fohl decided
not to come with us?
I think he realized
how weak he was
and stayed behind
with the old lady to train.
[NAOFUMI] The two of them
were both really fired up.
So I can't imagine how hard
she's gonna be on him.
- [audience cheering]
- Hm.
[SALVE MERCHANT 01-B (M)]
How good to see you.
Welcome back
Shield Hero!
I take it the little ones
before you here
are today's
entrants, yes?
They look exactly
how I pictured slaves
of the Shield Hero
to look like!
After all, each one of them
has a fire
- burning in their eyes!
- [ALL] Hmm.
Oh, not to worry!
I can safely assure you
that today's tournament
is more for sport
than anything.
I promise
there's no need to worry!
Sadeena, you're
in charge here.
Sure thing.
I promise
everything will be fine!
Listen up, make sure
you're careful
when you're fighting
down there.
[ALL] Okay.
All right! Let's
get going!
[DEMI-HUMAN BOY 10-A]
All right.
Now then.
I've been told you have
a question for me Shield Hero.
Yes. Do you know if one
of the contestants here today
is an archer named
Perfect Hidden Justice?
Hm.
[gasps] Sir Itsuki!
- Huh. Wait, Rishia!
- Where did she go?
♪
[RISHIA] Sir Itsuki.
Wait. Sir Itsuki!
[panting]
What was that about?
- Sir Itsuki!
- Huh?
[REN] Hey, isn't that.
It really is him.
[grunts]
[RISHIA] Sir Itsuki!
[SLAVE MERCHANT 01-B (M)]
My oh my.
You all started running
so quickly
I thought I'd never
catch up with you!
Is that man with the bow
the one you're looking for?
Since the match
hasn't started
Yes. I suppose
just for you
I could bend the rules
and make a small exception!
Go on!
[grunts]
♪
[RISHIA] Sir Itsuki.
Its, uh, been a while
- You see, I've...
- [ITSUKI] Everything's fine.
[ITSUKI] I... Yes.
Everyone is...
Is everything okay?
[ITSUKI] Hm. Yes.
Everyone wants
the Bow Hero's help.
And the prize money
I win today
- will save lives.
- [gasps]
Sir Itsuki!
What's going on?
[ITSUKI] That's right.
I'm just as strong
as I used to be.
I'm a servant
of justice!
[grunts]
[both grunt]
- Rishia!
- [RAPHTALIA] Are you okay?
- [Rishia whimpering]
Hey, Itsuki.
So, Naofumi.
- [ITSUKI] She told me you know.
- [gasps]
Princess Malty
told me everything
about what you've done!
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] Why the hell
am I hearing Witch's name
from your lips?
Don't tell me.
She's traveling
with you now?
[ITSUKI]
And so what if she is?
Who's in my party
is none of your business.
Trust me, Itsuki
[REN] ] Do what he says.
Nothing she says is true.
She's feeding
you lies, Itsuki.
How can you
even say that
when you don't know
what it is she said?
Because I know her!
[REN]
I know her too well.
"Whatever you're doing
is right.
I'm the only one
who believes you!"
She's saying exactly
what you want to hear, right?
They're all lies!
To manipulate you
the way she did with us!
[grunts]
I'm clearly
wasting my time.
[ITSUKI]
My round is about to begin.
Huh. Itsuki wait!
Itsuki.
[gasps]
[SLAVE MERCHANT 01-B (M)]
Ah, participant number 982.
If I recall correctly
that's Perfect
Hidden Justice
I believe if I'm
not mistaken
it was right after you left
the arena last time
that I first saw him enter
my arena as a participant.
[NAOFUMI] It's just like
the rumors S'yne heard, then.
Mm.
Naofumi, I'm glad
we found him, but what now?
From the look of it.
Yeah. We're not gonna
be able to have
a productive
conversation.
[sighs]
What if we knock him
unconscious and capture him?
That would
work, wouldn't it?
- Huh?
- Or simply speak to him
using our fists.
Why are both of those choices
equally violent?
- [RAPHTALIA] Goodness.
- I'd rather work
things out
peacefully, but...
If Bitch
is travelling with him
then there's
not much time.
Yeah. And also
there's those enemies
S'yne talked about.
- [NAOFUMI] What do we do?
- [gasps]
♪
[ITSUKI] They're wrong.
I'm not being
lied to here.
I'm not in the wrong.
I'll never forget
all the looks of disgust
I've gotten
since that day.
The words
they've said to me.
That's right.
They're the ones in the wrong!
Not me!
And that's what
Princess Malty said
so it must be true.
Although we parted ways
once before
Mald and the others
came back to me again.
[door creaking]
[ITSUKI] That's right.
Everybody wants me
in their party.
That's why I fight.
So for the sake
of Princess Malty
and my comrades
who believe in me
I'll continue
pushing forward!
[door creaking]
[audience cheering]
[spear swishing]
[screams]
[audience cheering]
[NAOFUMI] I knew it.
He hasn't powered up
his Cardinal Weapon, either.
And that bow he's using.
I don't like the feeling
it's giving me!
- [blood splatters]
- [grunts]
[gasps]
Rishia, are you're okay
watching this?
Mm-hmm. I'll be okay.
Though it is a little...
[gasps]
[audience cheering]
[grunts]
[panting]
[screams]
[shuddered breathing]
[whimpering]
[Rishia grunts]
I beg of you!
Let me be the one
to fight Sir Itsuki!
Please, Sir Naofumi?
You want to fight him?
[RISHIA] Yes!
I want to talk to him.
You see, I've always wanted
to repay him
for saving my life
but I just haven't
had the chance to yet.
[RISHIA] Back when
we were in the same party
I was completely
useless to him.
I wasn't allowed
to fight with them
so I just did
menial jobs.
Because I was weak
I was nothing
but a burden to him.
I had no idea.
To be fair though, my stats
were actually really low.
But in the time that
I've spent alongside you
I've seen you
and your comrades
save each other
again and again!
And so now.
Unlike before
when I see him
suffering like this
I feel I can help, so...
Look, I understand
how you feel.
But he's not going to listen
to reason right now.
[Rishia] That's why
I want to fight him!
If it's a fight
[SLAVE MERCHANT 01-B (M)]
Pardon me, Shield Hero.
But I think I might have
just the thing
to help you
in your fight.
Yes.
[indistinct chatter]
[ITSUKI]
Here's the money I made today.
[MALD] Nicely done.
Even more than last time!
[SPEARWOMAN]
Right? I'm so impressed!
Thank you for doing
all this, Itsuki.
- Hm.
- Hm?
What, is
something wrong?
No. It's just
we still don't have enough.
Not if we want to rescue
the slaves.
And when I think of the kids
we can't save...
[ITSUKI]
Don't you worry about that.
Just leave
everything to me.
[gasps]
[ITSUKI] As long as
I have you by my side
along with this bow
you gave me
I'm sure. No.
I swear. I'll
save all of them!
Sir Itsuki.
[ITSUKI] Oh, and I ran
into Naofumi there.
[all gasp]
[ITSUKI]
It's exactly as you said.
He has slaves
there with him.
And... he said
I was being lied to.
[MALD] D-do you think
that we're lying to you?
[ITSUKI] Of course not.
Why would I?
But don't worry
will come around
in due time.
I'll make enough prize money
to free all of the slaves.
And show him
we're the ones in the right.
Good.
[HOODED MAN 10-A]
The Shield Hero's here?
[MYNE]
Sorry to disappoint
but we won't be able to sell
the boy into slavery after all.
[HOODED MAN 10-A] Yes.
He's young enough
to be worth a lot
but he's already made us
a lot of money.
We've made enough.
[MYNE] I don't think so.
I had to put
up with listening
to his childish ideas
of justice
so I'm going to squeeze
every last drop out of him.
I mean
it's my job to teach him
how the world works.
[audience cheering]
[grunts]
[panting]
[Itsuki screams]
[coins clinking]
[MAN 10-A]
Here's your prize money.
And also.
[ITSUKI] What's this?
[SLAVE MERCHANT 01-B (M)]
While he's in the arena
I'm going to have
one of my men
send an invitation
to the Bow Hero.
And then tonight
I'm going to lure him
into a secret underground arena
where the ritual
magic sanctuary has been cast
in preparation
for his arrival.
Once it falls into place
we will have captured
the Bow Hero!
- Yes!
- [NAOFUMI] Hm.
[SLAVE MERCHANT 01-B (M)]
Oh? Is there a problem?
I wanna know what you gain
from doing this.
[NAOFUMI] I'm sure if you
were to help us
capture the Bow Hero
that the Queen
of Melromarc
would be willing to pay
a healthy reward but...
Just as I'd expect
of the Shield Hero!
I truly am in awe
of your unshakeable ability
to sniff out my intentions!
Yes!
[NAOFUMI]
So what else are you after?
You're not
trying to profit off
selling tickets
to the match
But of course.
I just haven't invited
the audience yet!
- Huh?
- [whispering]
I've just been informed
that the Bow Hero
has now arrived.
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] He's not as strong
as he could be
but it's possible he's affected
by the Curse series.
Hm.
Don't worry.
We'll be there the entire time.
If things go bad
[Keel giggles]
Everyone.
Now then, go show Itsuki
the woman you've become!
Let him see just
how strong you are now.
[giggles]
Okay! I'll do
my blesh...
Hm.
[chains rattling]
[gates rumbling]
♪
The Bow Hero really is
someone important to her.
She's willing to fight him
for their bond.
Without any further ado.
We'll now begin our match
between Rishia Ivyred...
And her opponent
Let the battle
between them begin!
[gong dings]
[audience cheering]
- I haven't done anything yet.
- [RISHIA] Sir Itsuki.
Hm?
I see.
Are you my opponent
today, Rishia?
If so, this
will be easy.
[RISHIA] You saved me
from a despair
I'm unable to
put into words.
[Itsuki sneers] Is that
what you came here to tell me?
And so this time.
- [sword clangs]
- [grunts]
It's my turn to save you
♪