♪
[NAOFUMI] There are just
two months left
until the
Phoenix revives.
In order to defeat it
the four Heroes
are going to need to learn
how to work together
as a team and fast.
We also need
to fortify our defenses
to protect the village.
♪
[NAOFUMI] Hopefully, everyone's
ready when the time comes.
♪
[both grunt]
- [thudding]
- Hm.
♪
Well, that should do it.
- [stomach growling]
- [gasps]
Looks delicious.
The food'll
be ready soon
so just wait
a little longer, okay?
[KEEL] Aww, yeah!
I knew I smelled
something
good over here!
C'mon, you guys.
Hurry up, I'm starving!
Hold up, is that Keel?
- I think it is!
- [laughs]
Pretty cool, huh?
Sadeena's the one who taught me
how to turn into this.
[Sadeena giggles]
Well, Keel always
had the talent
I just showed him
how to do it is all.
And how does this affect
his abilities?
Well, it typically depends
on the race
but usually
they just get stronger.
[panting]
[SADEENA]
By the way
Fohl's capable
of transformation as well.
[RISHIA]
Aw, look how cute Keel is!
Hey! Cut it out, that tickles!
[laughs]
- [RISHIA] You're so adorable!
- [KEEL] Stop!
All right! Now
who's hungry?
♪
Hey, Ren, come
here for a sec!
Something wrong?
What do you need?
All yours. Give it a go.
Huh?
[gasps]
Instead of Sir Naofumi
serving us
the Sword Hero will be
helping out for today.
So gather 'round!
Hurry up, Sword Hero!
We're starving!
I'm getting to it!
Uh, the food
is ready, right?
[NAOFUMI]
I remember that girl.
Her name is
Wyndia, right?
[birds chirping]
[FILO]
Master, get her off!
Help me!
[RAT]
Stop running away already!
[both gasp]
- [FILO] No!
- [both gasp]
[screaming]
Master, get her off me!
[crying]
- Filo!
- Huh.
- Master, please help me.
- Hm.
♪
Who is that, Filo?
I don't know, she just
showed up out of nowhere
and grabbed
onto my back.
I'm guessing that you
must be the Shield Hero?
Yeah.
♪
My name is
Ratotille Anthreya.
But all of my friends
just call me Rat.
Nice to meet you.
I can understand
why you're cautious.
But I have a feeling
this might ease
- your worries a bit.
- Huh.
From the Queen?
What's it say,
Master Naofumi?
[NAOFUMI] It says
that she's an alchemist
who was exiled from Faubrey
for causing trouble
but that she's also
more than talented enough
to help my lands prosper
if I'm able to put her to use.
There is one part of that
I'd like to correct.
The only reason I was exiled
was because the idiots there
refused to understand
my research.
And what's
your specialty?
I research monsters.
My job is to alter their beings
and make them even stronger.
Well, it was my job before they
started spreading rumors
about how I was a devil
and then slaughtered
all of my research subjects!
It was just
ghastly back there.
- But...
- [whimpers]
Maybe it was for the best
that it happened.
After all, I have
a mutant filolial here
that's capable of
human speech!
[Filo screams]
Melty! Help me!
Aw, and there goes
my valuable test subject!
Ratotille, was it?
Just call me Rat.
What is it that
you're after exactly?
Well, if I were
to put it simply...
The filolial.
Wait, you mean Filo?
The Queen mentioned
in legends is one example.
That being said
a great help to humanity
by taking us places.
That's the kind of monster
I intend on making.
Speaking of which
If you don't mind, I'd love
to go and check it out.
I'm quite curious to know
what you've raised as a Hero.
Hmm?
Should we show her?
[NAOFUMI] Yeah.
I say we give her a chance.
♪
Aw! My goodness.
I've never seen a caterpilland
so big at this level.
[NAOFUMI]
One, two, three? Wait.
Yeah, I thought
we only had two of them.
Where'd the
third come from?
- [WYNDIA] No!
- [gasps]
Come on you're not supposed
to be here!
[gasps] There's two!
There isn't a
third one, okay?
Why is she
acting so strange?
No clue. [Gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
What is this?
[all gasp]
Master Naofumi,
look here!
- [gasps]
- [chuckles]
[kids gasp]
[FOX EAR KID 07-A (F)]
I promise we'll take
good care of them!
Just please
I'm sorry, you guys.
But we really don't have
the resources
to raise that many.
I can take care of them
for you.
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] I guess
we do need a specialist
who can make
our monsters stronger.
[sighs]
I don't like
being lied to.
So unfortunately
a slave crest from me.
Is that all
right with you?
Yes, anything
to do my research.
[NAOFUMI]
Then it's settled.
Excellent.
I won't disappoint you.
[WYNDIA]
Um, Mr. Shield Hero.
- Huh?
There's something else here
that I think
you should see that
Siltvelt sent us.
[RAPHTALIA]
Siltvelt?
[NAOFUMI] Whoa, what's that
big black egg there?
Looks like a dragon egg.
Is it really?
I've always wanted
to raise a dragon!
Filo won't be
happy about that.
No, probably not.
More powerful dragons
will breed
with creatures
from any species
which can
cause problems.
They can easily destroy
a whole ecosystem.
That's not true
dragons are
strong and awesome
I'm talking about the integrity
of ecosystems here!
I can create something even
more powerful than a dragon
as well if
you'd like me to.
Yeah, well
it would be the strongest one
in the whole wide world!
I guess we can try
raising it here.
- [gasps]
- Rat, do you think
you can handle it?
Of course. Let's start
with a monster seal.
Then there's
something else
that I would like
your help with, Count.
Hm.
[indistinct chatter]
[chuckles] What the hell
are you doing with that, kid?
Master Naofumi is trying
to keep the egg warm.
We were told
that it's healthy
for boosting
the dragon's stats.
Why'd it have to be me?
Ren, think you can you look
after this thing for me
while I'm gone?
I would, but due
to the curse series
every single thing I touch
begins to rapidly degrade.
- [gasps]
- No way! [Panting]
- Huh.
- [WYNDIA] I refuse to let
the Sword Hero touch it!
[ELHART] [laughs] Guess you're
stuck with it then.
[sighs] Can't Raphy
take care of it?
What does Raphy know
about raising a dragon egg?
- [sword thunks]
- [gasps]
[ELHART] Here it is.
This is the Siderite Katana
you asked for, Raphtalia.
It's been a while
since I've made a katana.
I guess I'm still not as good
as my teacher, huh?
It's perfect.
May I hold it?
Sure thing.
I'm all finished.
It's skill is called
Stardust Blade.
It might be a skill kinda like
Ren's Meteor Slash.
- We can try it out a bit later.
- Sounds good!
Thank you
for your work, Elhart.
I'm happy I could help.
Now, is that all
you need for me?
[NAOFUMI]
For now. We'll be back.
Oh, as for that equipment
you gave me
I'll let you know
when it's repaired.
Huh?
[sighs]
[chuckles] They certainly
don't waste time.
[crickets chirping]
[door creaks]
Huh.
[FOHL]
Having trouble sleeping?
Hm.
[bed squeaking]
Go and tuck yourself in.
Hm.
Hey, brother
Mom's lullaby?
That one?
[ATLA] Yes.
♪
Goodnight, Atla.
Have sweet dreams.
I'll see you in
the morning.
Goodnight, big brother.
Pleasant dreams.
[chuckles]
[birds chirping]
[gasps]
Really? Again?
♪
Oh, good morning, Master.
How did you sleep?
- [sighs]
- Hm.
How many times
have you done this?
I think it's the third time
I've shared a bed with you.
I mean, wandered
into your bed.
Yeah, I'm sure.
How's your slave crest?
My heart feels more warmth
than pain right now.
[NAOFUMI] Why isn't Fohl
keeping watch over you?
At the moment, he's most likely
sound asleep in his room.
[grunts]
Master Naofumi!
Good morning.
Really, Atla, again?
You're not welcome
to sleep in this room.
How many times
do you have to be told that?
But I am
Master Naofumi's shield.
I need to be by his side
If you're his shield
and stay in your own bed
It's up to Master Naofumi
if I'm disturbing him.
[FOHL] Atla!
I'm pretty sure I told you
not to come over here.
- So then why did you...
- Don't tell me what to do!
[gasps]
[thuds]
Enough, Atla, it's time
for you to go back now!
But I don't wanna!
[grunts]
[gasps] Can't I just stay
with him a little longer?
[sighs]
♪
[NAOFUMI] That was a hell
of a way to start the day.
[birds chirping]
- [giggling]
- Hm? Huh.
Hm. What is it?
You're looking great
with that egg, Naofumi!
Who knew you'd be a great cook
and a great caretaker?
I'll bet you'd make
a wonderful dad someday.
You're interrupting my work.
Get lost you two.
[MELTY] Hey, I've got
a busy schedule, too
and I still made time
to come see you!
- [door opens]
- [gasps]
[DOLL] Hi, Sir Naofumi.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Hey, that stuffed animal
looks like me!
- Wow, it's so cute!
- Thank you!
I based it off of how Keel
looks when he transforms.
Wow, you're a whole lot easier
to understand with that.
The reason is
I was able to...
I was able
to repair an accessory
that one of the enemies
we defeated had.
It has a translation ability
that I can use.
[NAOFUMI]
You can't just use it yourself?
[sighs]
[DOLL] It reacts poorly
with my vassal weapon.
So I am unable to.
Ah, I see.
So, what
brings you here?
- [stomach growling]
- [gasps]
We should
probably eat first.
[chuckles]
♪
Hmm.
[ECLAIR]
Melromarc's language, huh?
[gasps]
Let's see.
The spelling here
[scribbling]
[gasps]
Hm?
- What's wrong?
- It's nothing.
[RAPHTALIA] Thanks
for cooking this morning.
We're getting more
and more therianthropes, huh.
Yeah, we'll have to come up
with something for them, too.
Well, what if we went
and got a new pot for them?
I saw a store in Zeltoble
that had one.
[gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
When did that...
♪
[hammering]
- [NAOFUMI] Rat!
- Hm?
Is it finished already?
Yes, I've been here
waiting for you, Count!
These giant trees
are called camping plants.
Just plant the seed
and before long
you'll have
a brand new place to live!
It stores sunlight
during the day
and when night comes
That's real impressive.
[chuckles]
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
It just feels like
we're getting
further and further away
from the village
I know and love.
Well, I've got plenty
of weed killer to remove it
if you'd like me to.
If it makes life easier
for people in the village
then I'm okay with it.
- [egg crackling]
- [all gasp]
It cracked!
- [wind whooshing]
- [birds chirping]
[panting]
Oh, good
Hey, what exactly do
dragons eat anyway?
Dragons eat just about
anything, really.
- They are omnivores.
- [crackling]
[gasps]
[all gasp]
[chirping]
Well, I can't say this is
quite what I had in mind.
I can't believe
it's so cute.
It reminds me of back when
Filo was just a little chick.
- [Naofumi gasps]
- Well then.
Looks like a healthy
dragon pup to me.
- Hmm.
- And a male one at that.
[NAOFUMI]
What kind is it?
A wyr, I think.
And luckily for you
they're one of the most loyal
types of dragons.
[both gasp]
- Hmm.
- [chirping]
From here on out
Yeah, your
name's Gaelion!
[chirping]
You like that, don't you?
[chuckles]
Are you sure you don't want
to name the dragon yourself?
He seems to have taken
a liking to that name
so it's fine with me.
Wyndia, since you're
the one who named him
it's up to you
to take care of him.
Hm.
♪
- [knocking on door]
- Huh?
- [thudding]
- [gasps]
What's going
on over here
All right
Wait, you triggered it?
[RAPHTALIA]
Gaelion?
[NAOFUMI]
Where's Wyndia?
Somebody's been
knocking on my door
and then running away
for the past few days
so I set up a trap.
Turns out it was
him all along.
Why Gaelion?
He says that he just wanted
to play with the Shield Hero.
So you were just
playing a prank on me
'cause I wouldn't
play with you?
I know! This might be
a perfect opportunity for us!
Huh?
He could certainly help
with Atla.
We could have him stationed
outside the door
to drive her off, so that she
doesn't wander in here.
- [squeaking]
- [gasps]
So, he'd be like
a guard dog, huh?
What is that? An orb?
It's a core.
The Emperor
Dragon's Core.
I had them turn into a jewel
for me in Kizuna's world.
[both gasp]
[SADEENA] Stop! Get that away
from him, quickly!
[squeaking]
Gaelion! Spit
it out already!
[whimpering]
Quick, Raphtalia, water!
- Huh.
- Right!
Gaelion, are you okay?
Hurry, stand back!
What happened?
What's going
on with Gaelion?
[growling]
- [WYNDIA] Gaelion?
- [fire roaring]
- [Naofumi gasps]
- [explosion]
- [gasps]
- [both gasp]
♪
- Damn it!
- This is bad.
We need to deal with him
before he harms the village.
Just tell me how we can
save him and I'm on it!
- Please! Gaelion!
- [fire roaring]
[growling]
[roaring]
♪
[fluttering]
[panting]
[swooshing]
[gasps]
♪
[Naofumi gasps]
Gaelion.
♪