♪
[flag fluttering]
[NAOFUMI]
Motoyasu?
[MIRELIA] He's searching
for his comrades
who split up with him
after the Spirit Tortoise
fight.
We have located
one of them.
If our intel's correct
then they're in small town
near Melromarc.
Near Melromarc?
Right. And the whereabouts
of the others?
We haven't got a clue.
Mal...
Bitch hasn't shown herself
since we last talked.
The last sighting
reported of her
was near the
northern border.
[NAOFUMI] You can't use
her slave crest to find her?
[MIRELIA] We've tried
but she's somehow
blocking our attempts.
It's no use.
And the other heroes?
Ren and Itsuki
remain to be seen.
However, one thing
about the Sword Hero's
been confirmed.
His companions have been
pronounced dead.
[gasps]
Sir Naofumi
it won't be long
before the Phoenix revives.
I know that
you're often at odds
but please persuade
the Spear Hero
while there's time.
♪
[NAOFUMI]
Persuade him, huh?
No matter
how many times you ask
I'm not gonna make nice
with those idiots.
[FITORIA ] If the heroes
are busy fighting each other
then you leave
me no choice
I must kill all
four of you.
[sighs]
[inhales]
[NAOFUMI] I suppose
I could leave Eclair
in charge of my lands.
Then start
with Motoyasu.
- [wind whooshing]
- [leaves rustling]
[indistinct chatter]
[panting]
[MOTOYASU]
Where'd you all go?
Come back.
Please.
I need you.
Elena. Myne.
♪
[OLD LADY]
Hai! Hai!
Haaah!
Keep your
breathing steady now!
Hone your focus
[screams]
[ALL] Hai! Hai!
Haa!
[children giggling]
[NAOFUMI] Hm.
- Thank you!
- How's over there?
- Looking good!
- Let's pick some from there.
- Okay!
- Huh.
Oh, Mr. Naofumi!
Hey, You're to call him
"His Lordship!"
Hey, when's breakfast?
I'm getting hungry!
Yeah, and my
tummy is rumbling!
- [clamoring]
- Fine.
I'll get on it, relax.
[cheering]
[RAPHTALIA]
It seems like everyone's
settled in nicely here.
Yes. And thanks to that
we should have
the outer walls built soon.
Our problem now
is getting enough money.
There's a lot
here to keep up.
Can't Melromarc help us?
I wouldn't count on it.
Every nation
is still rebuilding
from the
Spirit Tortoise.
I see.
Hm.
Oh, how'd it go?
Resetting Fohl
and Sadeena's levels?
We managed
to get it done.
They need to do some rehab
to make up for lost levels.
But from the look of it
[RAPHTALIA]
Both of them have come so far
and in such a short amount
of time.
[NAOFUMI]
Unlike your stats
whatever skills
you obtain from training
aren't lost
during a reset.
[grunts]
But we gotta get their stats
back up for the Phoenix.
The real problem comes
once they hit their limits.
If they do
[sighs]
Yeah, probably.
Hey, is the
food ready yet?
I'm so hungry
Food will be ready
in a few minutes
go work up an appetite.
Fine.
I wish we could
just eat right now.
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
♪
[drooling]
My goodness!
I could eat all the food
on this table!
It's too early
to start drinking.
You don't think
I know that?
♪
- Hm.
- Uh...
Sorry, but who are you?
My name is S'yne.
Hm?
Hey! You're
the clown girl
- Clown girl?
- Filo, you know her?
We both already
know her, right, Master?
This should remind you.
[both gasp]
You're Murder Clown!
Why're you here?
- I walked.
- That's not what I asked you.
- Did you come here to eat?
- Yes.
Just so you know
At least for
you it's not.
[S'YNE]
I understand.
Is this enough?
For food?
[Filo gasps]
I'm not interested
in taking all your money.
What I'm
trying to say is...
[sighs]
Please, just
leave the village.
But it was me who protected
everyone from slavers?
- So why?
- Master Naofumi?
Don't care. I
can't trust you.
I see.
♪
[sighs]
Hm.
Oh, right, Filo, I have
some good news for you.
I'll tell you
after we finish breakfast.
Huh?
Carriage! Carriage!
Carriage! Carriage! Carriage!
It's my carriage!
Hooray! Hooray!
[chuckles] Right.
Remember to
raise your levels.
- I know, I know.
- Yes, sir!
We'll train our
very hardest!
Hm.
And in the meantime, you'll be
training with me, Rishia.
- [gasps]
- I'll help out, too.
[crying]
And most importantly
don't let anyone
suspicious in.
Just leave it to us.
- Let's go.
- 'Kay!
- Good luck, you guys!
- Bye now!
[RAPHTALIA]
We'll be back soon, everyone!
[humming]
[wheels rattling]
It's been so long
since we've been
on a journey like this.
It reminds me
of when we met.
I know what you mean.
Maybe we can do some trading
on the way back.
- [FILO] Yay!
- [RAPHTALIA] Great!
[door creaks]
[sighs]
How on Earth
did I ever end up like this?
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[RAPHTALIA]
This is...
[NAOFUMI] Yeah.
But we need to find
the Cardinal Hero.
[SHOPKEEPER 04-A (M)]
Oh, you'll want to go
to the next street over.
Thank you so much.
Yes, I think
I saw a hero
at one of the taverns
on the outskirts of town.
Thank you.
This should be
the one, right?
[MOTOYASU]
Elena, you're alive!
Thank goodness.
I thought I lost you!
Oh, well
I-Is something wrong?
I'm not sure
what to tell you.
Listen, Elena.
We've had a lot
of adventures together
haven't we?
So come on!
Let's team up again!
I'm sorry, but
I can't do that.
- [gasps]
- I had to take over
the family business.
- Good day.
- [gasps]
[grunts]
If it's party members
that you need
then go to a tavern.
No, see, it
has to be you!
Sir Motoyasu.
Sorry, I mean,
Spear Hero.
I can't bear the idea
of traveling with you
another day.
Elena.
The days when you had
fame and riches
to your name are gone.
And without all that
What do you mean?
I'm a hero!
Please, you're nothing
but a vagrant.
If you want me to return
then make something
of yourself.
The same way
the Shield Hero did.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Huh. N-Naofumi!
Looks like we've
finally found you, Motoyasu!
[grunting]
Hey, wait!
Just hear me out!
Motoyasu!
♪
[indistinct chatter]
Argh, damn it.
Where do you think
he ended up going?
I don't really know.
But there's someone else here
we can talk to.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
I take it you're paying
for all of this, right?
If you tell me
what you know
I will, just relax.
What Sir Motoyasu wanted
was to find the Spirit Tortoise
and beat it before you did.
[rumbling]
[MOTOYASU] [laughs]
No need to run, men!
I, the Spear Hero
See how much stronger I am
than the Shield Hero!
Time to destroy
this beast!
- [ALL] Right!
- [MOTOYASU] Let's go!
Zweit Hellfire!
[fire roaring]
[sword clanging]
You're mine
for the taking!
♪
Here goes!
Thunder Spear!
[thunder rumbling]
- [electricity crackling]
- [chuckles]
♪
[gasps] Wait, what?
- Sir Motoyasu!
- Uh, right!
Meteor Thrust!
[MOTOYASU]
Lightning Spear!
[Motoyasu grunts]
- [rumbling]
- [MYNE] Hey.
I don't think
it's working.
[all gasp]
[grunts] Take this!
[grunts]
There you have it.
I picked the wrong guy
to suck up to.
Oh, and don't even bother
trying to have me arrested.
I already gave all this info
to the authorities.
What? I told you
everything I know.
Yes, and I do
appreciate that.
Now where are the taverns
in this town?
[indistinct chatter]
[gurgling]
Hm.
Huh?
[gasps] Naofumi.
It's been a while
Hey, relax.
I'm here to talk.
I'm not trying
to arrest you or anything.
[sighs]
Filo, Raphtalia.
Sorry, but can you two
look for Motoyasu?
Are you sure?
[NAOFUMI]
Leave us alone for a bit.
Very well, then.
[FILO] Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
Sit with me
for a second.
I just ran into
Motoyasu.
I think he was here meeting
with an old party member.
But he ran off
before we could even talk.
I see.
So his comrades
are alive.
I heard that
all of yours are.
They're dead.
Every last one of them.
♪
It's not my fault.
I lost because
they were weak.
It can't be helped.
[gulps]
[thuds]
It's not, it's not my fault.
Ren, I'm sorry you had
to go through that
but it doesn't mean
you have to give up.
It's only a matter of time
before the Phoenix revives.
When it does
we heroes need to fight
against it together.
Please, fight with me.
[REN] All right.
[sighs]
Now then
It...
How dare you put your trust
in the Shield Demon!
[gasps]
Bitch is here?
You told me
that you would trust me!
And that you would believe
what I said, right?
[gasps] I never said
I'd believe you.
And Motoyasu is still looking
for his comrades.
The Spear Hero
is a scumbag
Forget about
him already.
The moment I
laid eyes on you
I knew you were the hero
destined to save the world
unlike the others.
The Spear
just like the Shield.
Motoyasu. That bastard!
Ren, come on
don't tell me
you believe this nonsense.
Remember the trial
at the castle?
Enough with your lies
- Huh?
- That trial was nothing
but a farce
that had been conjured up
to steal the
throne from me!
My mother joined forces
with the Shield Demon
just to humiliate me
in a position
to take the throne!
And the Shield
Demon here
was secretly controlling
the Spirit Tortoise
all so he could gain
the people's trust!
Meaning!
He killed your comrades!
[grunts]
Take that back.
[REN]
Is that true Naofumi?
[NAOFUMI]
Seriously?
I can prove to you
I'm not lying.
If I were, my
slave crest
would be activating
[gasps]
How is that possible?
Please, you have
to believe me, Ren.
I do, but...
I care about you
more than anyone
in this world, Ren.
Everyone else may think you
to be a criminal
but I know with all my heart
you're a hero.
- [grunts]
- I believe you fought
for the sake of the world
that day, Ren.
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
You wretched.
♪
Even if the whole world
were to turn against you, Ren
I would stand
by your side.
My allegiance
is only with you, Ren
the great Sword Hero.
- Shut the hell up!
- [MOTOYASU] Wait!
- [panting]
- Motoyasu?
[both grunt]
What are you
doing with Ren?
I've been looking for you
this whole time!
Please, Myne
Sword Hero!
You heard him just now
He told me he's
looking for me
but called me a whore!
- [gasps]
- That's proof
that he forced
himself on me!
And he told me he'd kill
my father if I tried resisting!
No, that isn't true!
[REN]
You really did that?
Of course not!
She's lying to you!
I swear!
[REN]
Why should I trust you?
[MOTOYASU ] Listen to me, Ren!
I never laid a hand
on her or anything like that!
If she hadn't asked me
to wait till dawn
and call the knights
I would've
gladly cut you
- down myself!
- [REN] So you're gonna run away
as soon as things start
to get tough?
You really are scum!
[grunts]
I'm impressed.
Who knew one human being
could lie so much, witch.
Hey, stay away
from Myne!
Ren, please.
Don't tell me
you believe a word
coming out of that
lying bitch's big mouth.
Enough!
Myne's right
from the very beginning!
The reason my party died
and I'm being
blamed for it now
is because of
you, Naofumi!
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Oh, so that's how it is, huh?
If that's how
you're gonna be
I've got some shit
to say to you, too.
Your friends are dead
because you're
treating this
- like a video game.
- What?
But it's not
your fault, right?
Because it's easier to blame
someone else, isn't it?
This world isn't
some game.
You had loyal followers
who believed in you.
And yet...
You're not just a failure
as a hero
but as a human being!
You're wrong!
It's not my fault
they died, dammit!
Stop, Ren! You can't let
the Shield Hero
get in your head!
Get lost, witch!
Before I kill you
where you stand!
You know exactly
what you should be
doing right now.
But here you are
refusing to do it
because it would require you
to admit that you screwed up.
Am I wrong?
How dare you
say that to me?
Need me to say it again?
You know
exactly what to do.
Your conscience
is screaming at you.
But I guess
you're too damn busy
listening to that
lying whore run her mouth
so you can't
hear it, can you?
Shut the hell up!
[gasps]
It's not my fault!
You're using a skill
in a tavern?
I'm going to
fight for Myne.
For the one person
who still believes in me!
- Stop!
- Meteor Slash!
[grunts]
[clamoring]
Master Naofumi!
♪
[clamoring]
Huh?
[gasps] Impossible!
Sir Ren, hurry
[REN]
That's not possible.
You have to be cheating!
Face reality, Ren.
[grunts]
Flashing Sword!
Wait, hold on!
- Get off me, coward!
- [grunts]
Yeah, that's for
abandoning me!
Huh.
- Do it, Ren!
- Portal Sword!
[gasps]
[snickering]
- [grunts]
- [fire roaring]
You're the one
who abandoned him.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi!
- Hm?
- Are you okay?
I am
but he's not.
What did I do?
- Why are Bitch and Elena both?
- [NAOFUMI] Motoyasu!
- [NAOFUMI] Hey, Motoyasu!
- I trusted them with my life.
Why's this happening?
Why is everyone
so cold to me?
I'll never trust
- another woman again.
- Is he going to be okay?
- I don't care.
- Why?
- Can you guys check...
- Why am I the only one stuff
- like this keeps happening to?
- If anyone here is wounded?
[indistinct chatter]
[NAOFUMI]
I'm exhausted.
[indistinct chatter]
[MOTOYASU]
Why am I the only one
this happens to?
Why did this
happen to me.
I never want to talk
to a woman again.
♪
[audience cheering]
Is that Filo?
What is this,
Master Naofumi?
Maybe something
she gained
from her time
as a Humming Fairy.
[chomps and chuckles]
[gasps]
Here, take
a bite of this!
It'll cheer you up!
[screaming]
Filo!
- [Motoyasu grunts]
- [Filo gasps]
Motoyasu...
Glad to see
you're feeling better.
Believe in the method
I gave you to get stronger
and work to get ready
for the fight.
[MOTOYASU]
Understood!
♪
This is
everything, isn't it?
What about
the Spear Hero?
From the look of it
to come back with us.
I'll explain what happened
to the Queen
and head back
to the village.
Hey, I want to head back
- [door opens]
- [both gasp]
Good morning, Father!
How are you?
- [screams]
- [door closes]
[sighs]
What the hell?
Sir! [Thuds]
Your daughter saved me
at my lowest
and she taught me
about true love!
I will give you my word!
I'll keep her happy
forever.
May I have
your blessing?
[sighs]
[laughs]
Let's be happy together, Filo!
- [Motoyasu laughing]
- [Filo shrieking]
- [moaning]
- Hey.
Stop it, you're
scaring her!
Stay out of my way
Huh?
[grunts] Pig?
- Huh?
- [thumps]
- [groans]
- All right, let's get going.
- [Filo] 'Kay!
- [Naofumi] Y-Yeah.
[groans]
[gasps]
Filo! Filo!
Don't leave me behind!
[crying] Filo!