♪
[straining]
[shouting]
[grunts]
This isn't good.
I can't block
what's next!
[crackling]
[ATLA]
Leave it to me!
- [shouting]
- Atla!
[gasps]
Atla!
Atla...
Master Naofumi!
[water trickling]
[panting]
[NAOFUMI]
Stay with me.
[coughing]
I didn't know
you couldn't swim Sir Ren.
It's not one of
my strengths.
[hissing]
Sorry, Atla,
was that painful?
A little, but I'm okay.
[FOHL]
Ow, that stings!
Stop whining.
It's not that bad.
[squirming]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi.
How's Filo?
She's still
hanging in there
but her levels are
going down rapidly.
I see, that means...
We don't have
much time left.
Yeah, I think
you're right.
By tomorrow morning
he'll have drained away
every last level.
[NAOFUMI] The most effective
attack we've got right now
is Atla's which scales off
the enemy's defense stat.
But...
[sighs]
[WYNDIA]
How're you feeling?
[ATLA]
Much better now, thanks.
[WYNDIA]
That's a relief.
Oh, by the way
there's something I've been
meaning to ask you, Wyndia.
What is it?
I was just wondering
is that giant dragon back
there really your father?
[crackling]
Yes.
He's the one
who raised me.
[panting]
[crying]
[birds fluttering]
I'm sorry
but can you watch over
my daughter?
[roaring]
I thank you.
My daughter's
name is... Wyndia.
[crying]
[hissing]
Huh?
[crying]
[thudding]
[wailing]
[clattering]
♪
[roaring]
[crackling]
This is super yummy
Huh?
Why is this one
upside-down?
[roaring]
[gasps]
Dad, what's wrong?
I'm sorry! I didn't know
that it would hurt you!
It was an accident! I promise
I didn't mean to do it, really!
That's right.
I'd almost forgot!
Huh?
The upside-down scale.
Is something wrong?
I have to go and tell the
Shield Hero!
This is a good ways
out from the village.
If we can lure
the dragon here
we can attack
him from above.
Not only that
the dragon vein is
especially strong here
so we'll have the
protection of the land as well.
I think this is a great place
to fight him.
But why would he
willingly come out here?
I'm gonna use
the Wrath Shield.
No matter what it takes
[SADEENA]
Well then, everyone
we better start
getting ready!
[MELTY]
I'll hide all the magic water
and healing potions
that I can find in the forest.
[ECLAIR]
We still need to repair
our weapons
and equipment.
What's our attack
plan, though?
Well, for starters...
[WYNDIA]
There you are, Shield Hero!
[panting]
Everyone, listen!
I figured it out!
I know its weakness!
A scale?
That's right.
One of the
dragon's scales.
It's upside-down
on its chest.
That scale is the
dragon's weak spot.
Least I think.
But what do we do
if it flies up into the air?
I'll attract its attention
and coax it to land.
Can anyone pin it down
before it starts flying again?
Leave it to me.
I've got just the
Choral spell for that.
But Wyndia and
Melty can help
in case I'm not able
to handle it on my own.
Huh?
[SADEENA]
Can I count on you girls?
Not to worry.
The two of us have your back.
I'm gonna
give it my all!
As for Raphtalia
and Eclair
I need you to use attacks
that'll shatter his defenses.
Ren and Sadeena
can work together
to pierce the
weak scale.
I feel that's the best
course of action we've got.
♪
You sure you're okay?
Yeah, why?
Well, we're about to go
fight your dad.
It's gotta have you
a little worried, right?
Sure.
But I promise you
that I'm all right!
The reason I
came back here is
so I can finally say
goodbye to my dad.
Huh? Wow, you've got quite
the strong spirit, Wyndia.
You must love him.
Aw, look at this!
You're such good little kids!
Is now really the time
to be drinking?
It's the perfect time
to be drinking!
Don't you worry kids.
No matter what happens.
I swear I'll
protect you.
'Cause look at you!
You're both so adorable.
- You're so cute!
- You reek of alcohol!
Are you gonna be able to fight
while you're drunk, Sadeena?
Huh? Don't
worry about me!
I feel like the
more I drink
[groans]
- [chuckles]
♪
Grant me the power to overcome
the obstacles before me!
Hang on, Filo.
♪
[RAPHY] Raphy.
You need to go and hide
with the other kids.
Please, Master.
Let me fight with you.
- Atla.
- Please.
We need you
as our last resort.
And we can't have you
getting injured before that.
I want to have
an ace up my sleeve.
I'm your ace?
Fine. If it helps you
Hey, big brother!
[ATLA] Guess what
Master Naofumi told me!
[NAOFUMI]
I still don't fully understand
the ins and outs
of Atla's power.
So it's too risky to try
and rely on it.
We'll end this
before sunrise.
Let's go, Raphy.
[RAPHY] Raphy.
Come forth!
Wrath Shield!
♪
- [grunts]
- Raphy!
- [straining]
- Raphy.
Stay back!
I'm all right.
There he is.
[SADEENA, MELTY, WYNDIA]
Dragon vein
We call out so that
you may hear our wish!
As source of thy power
Impart to me
the laws of the nature
and grant me
the power to
overcome the
obstacles before me!
[EMPEROR DRAGON] If you
sacrifice yourself to me
Shield Hero
then you have my word
that I will do all in my power
to exact revenge on the
humans who made you suffer.
[scoffs]
Don't make me laugh.
[MELTY, WYNDIA. SADEENA]
Choral Magic!
Boundless Sea!
♪
[grunts]
[SADEENA]
Dragonfury Dual Blades!
And one more.
Orca Strike!
[grunts]
Not good, we need her
to keep the barrier up!
There's no time
for weakness!
We'll just have to
try it again!
Right!
Eclair! Now!
Multistrike
Crumble Attack!
[NAOFUMI]
If he raises his defense
we use attacks
that scale.
If he lowers it, then we
use our strongest moves.
We can do this!
Meteor Shield!
[grunts]
♪
[shouting]
Now, Raphtalia!
Life Force Blade
♪
[straining]
Master Naofumi,
I'm sorry.
[EMPEROR DRAGON]
Shield Hero
your folly demands a death
ripe with suffering!
[groaning]
[WYNDIA, MELTY]
Oh, tainted land
alter the flow of your
accursed dragon vein.
[crackling]
Not yet.
We still... need more.
[FOHL] Hey, Atla.
What do we do
if their plan doesn't work?
As Master
Naofumi's servants
we have a
duty to carry out.
In order to help
the plan succeed
we have to do
whatever it takes.
Atla...
♪
[shouting]
[ATLA] A wall?
I can't break it!
[grunts] [screaming]
Big brother!
[roaring]
[gasps]
Atla!
You've gotta break it!
Damn it!
[grunts]
[ATLA]
This is my last attack.
Even if it costs
me my life.
I'll remove any obstacle that
stands in my Masters way.
After all it's my duty!
♪
Because I...
Am Master
Naofumi's Shield!
[gasps]
[roaring]
[crashing]
[thuds]
You did great.
Thanks.
[crackling]
There they are!
[straining]
[cooing]
[RAPHTALIA, MELTY]
Filo!
Gaelion!
Please wake up!
I'm begging you
[muttering]
Melty's here?
And Raphtalia too?
Thank goodness!
I'm so glad you're safe.
Gaelion, you're okay!
[cooing]
Huh?
[crumbling]
Huh?!
♪
[gasping]
[bubbling]
[chuckling]
[splashing]
[chuckles]
Dad, can we
go fly over there?
♪
Sweet dreams, Dad.
Sleep tight, okay?
I'm... glad I got to
be your daughter.
Goodbye, Dad.
[roaring]
[thudding]
[SADEENA, WYNDIA, MELTY]
Hear me tainted land
for our desires and our
wishes to save the world
are akin to a
pure stream
washing away
all hatred and anger.
Dragon vein, we call upon thee
to grant us a miracle!
Erasing Aqua Splash!
♪
[shouting]
Oh, no, you don't!
Air Strike Shield!
Second Shield! Dritte Shield!
[grunting]
Here goes.
Instant Blade, Mist!
♪
Is it all over now?
Yeah.
[chuckles]
Master Naofumi!
[EMPEROR DRAGON]
Wrath will always dwell
within the depths
of your heart.
[birds chirping]
Huh?
[MAYOR]
Goodness.
I can't tell you just
how thankful we are
you came, Shield Hero.
If it weren't for you
the Sword Hero would've gotten
us killed by that plague.
[NAOFUMI] Don't blame Ren
for what happened.
You're responsible.
You manipulated him
just so you could steal
the dragon's treasure.
You got what
you deserved.
[groaning]
Please forgive me.
I've done something
that I can never atone for.
[WYNDIA]
I already knew.
Huh?
I also knew that
the villagers had
manipulated you to
get what they wanted.
But, I still couldn't
forgive you.
Thank you, Ren.
Huh?
You saved my life
Uh...
♪
[FATHER DRAGON ]
I must say, Shield Hero
it's a wonderful thing to
watch one's daughter grow up.
[gasps]
Wait that voice. No way!
[FATHER DRAGON ] It seems
this body became a vessel
allowing me to
escape annihilation.
[NAOFUMI] Huh.
You sure you don't
wanna say anything to her?
Not when Wyndia is trying
to overcome my death.
I think it'd be best to
keep it a secret for her sake.
Agreed.
♪
- Hm?
- Huh?
Give back the experience
points you took from me!
[scoffs]
[grunting]
Give them back!
Give them
back right now!
[NAOFUMI]
Wait, Filo's curse is gone.
Did the Emperor Dragon
absorb it?
All's well
that ends well
Raphy.
[gasps]
- [roaring]
- [whimpers]
Let me ride, too!
Huh!
♪
[exclaiming]
- [FILO] Wait!
- Huh?
I'm the one
who gives Master rides!
Me and nobody else!
[laughing]
Listen up Gaelion!
Grow up to be
a great dragon.
Just like my dad was
[screeching]