♪
[SADEENA] Unfortunately
there's a good chance
the Emperor Dragon has
taken over Gaelion's mind.
What do you
mean by that?
To put simply
that contains
their mind.
You're able to use that core
to improve your abilities
or even inherit the memories
that reside in the dragon.
Oh, so basically
the dragon zombie's mind
absorbed
by the Emperor Dragon's core
caused Gaelion to
lose control of himself.
[SADEENA] Yes.
No way. It's
like I thought.
Hey, Ake, the old lady
and Rishia are out right now.
Bring 'em back here!
On it.
Rat, I want you to protect
the village in our absence.
[NAOFUMI] I'll send S'yne too
if you need her.
Keep an eye on the monsters
till we're back.
Right. Leave it to me.
I'll go after Gaelion
along with Raphtlaia
Sir Naofumi!
[ECLAIR] I need you to
come with me.
Filo suddenly collapsed
in pain.
- [NAOFUMI] Filo?
- The healers are doing
everything they can
but it's not helping.
Master Naofumi.
Raphtalia and I will
go ahead and check on Filo.
The rest of you should
prepare to go while we're gone.
Understood.
Allow me to
come with you.
I feel like I maybe able to
help somehow.
I'll go too!
Me too!
I'm too worried about Filo
to stay!
Hm.
[sighs]
Let's get going.
♪
Naofumi, quick!
Where's Filo?
This way! But hurry!
[whimpers]
- Are you okay?
Master, you came for me.
Thank you.
Don't you worry.
I'll fix you up right away
Master
Naofumi, this is...
It's worse than
what the Curse Series did.
[NAOFUMI]
Her levels are dropping?
What's going on?
[RAPHTALIA] It's too odd to be
a coincidence
could Gaelion have
something to do with it.
I'm able to sense
a terrible power
flowing out
from within Filo.
Could it be
that her experience points are
being transferred to Gaelion?
[whimpers]
Hang in there!
Oh.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi
Atla?
[ATLA] I'll try to dampen
the flow of power.
Ah. That's strange.
[FILO] For some reason
I feel a little bit better now.
Thank goodness!
Raphy.
That's a relief!
[sighs]
It's not much but I think
this should buy you
a little more time.
Thanks, Atla.
[NAOFUMI]
Even at this slower speed
she won't last two days.
She'll drop
to level one.
No, we'll be lucky
if it stops there.
At this rate
[NAOFUMI]
I want you to stay here
and take care of Filo.
[gasping]
I'm going to break the curse
that was laid on her.
Let's go, Raphtalia.
[FILO] No!
Please don't
leave me here
[NAOFUMI] You need to stay here
and rest.
But if I stay here
then who's going to
pull your carriage, Master!
[NAOFUMI] Enough.
You're not in any shape to do...
Well, if Filo's going with you
then so am I!
[NAOFUMI]
Melty, you're a princess!
I may be a princess
but more importantly
[whines]
[sighs]
At the first
sign of trouble
I'm sending you back
to town with a portal.
Yay! I feel fine now!
Ah.
Atla, can you keep
slowing down the curse?
Yes. I'll do my best.
If Atla's going
I'm going too
no matter what.
All right, all right
Everybody,
get ready to go.
[NAOFUMI]
After that
Filo raced to the village to
the east as fast as she could.
[Filo panting]
You did great, Filo.
I can fight too, Master.
I just need a nap.
It'll only be a minute.
- Ah!
- Savior!
- The Shield Hero has come!
- Our hero!
[NAOFUMI] Make sure
Filo gets some rest.
- [ATLA] Right.
- [MELTY] Right.
♪
She must be exhausted
right now.
I might need
your help here.
Very well!
Fast Aqua Heal!
I'll help too!
And go get something
for her to eat!
Thank goodness you've come
to help us, Shield Hero.
Yet another dragon has found
its home near our village.
Where did it go?
[VILLAGER 08-A (M)]
Our best guess is
that it went
to the Dragon's Den!
Dragon's Den?
There's a huge cave just beyond
that mountain over there
the same one where that
horrible dragon once lived.
But please be careful
as our village won't survive
another plague.
Save our village!
We beg of you!
We don't have time
to waste on courtesies.
We should get going.
Agreed.
♪
[SADEENA] If we want to
put an end to this
we'll need to first
weaken Gaelion
and then make him spit up the
Emperor Dragon's Core, right?
[NAOFUMI] Yes
but what if it's taken over
Gaelion's whole body by now?
[SADEENA] If so, then we'll
have a tough call to make.
I see.
[Monster 08-A roars]
[gasps]
[roars]
[grunts]
Dark Fire Palette!
[roars]
The hell?
Since when could you use magic?
I'm able to fight
if I have to, you know.
Oh, my, you mean
you didn't know?
Wyndia is able to use
the Way of the Dragon Vein.
What kind of
magic is that?
She can take power from the
Dragon Veins beneath the Earth
to power her magic.
[SADEENA]
Once she masters it
she'll be able to use both
Choral Magic and Jamming Magic.
She can use
Choral Magic?
Wyndia, you're
incredible.
My dad taught me
everything I know.
[whimpers]
[MELTY] You okay?
[ATLA]
How do you feel, Filo?
[FOHL]
You're in luck!
I got a lot of fish
for you, Filo!
Raphy.
Thank you so
much everyone.
- I'm feeling, ah..
- Filo!
[groans]
Filo, Hang in there
a little longer!
[MELTY] Poor Filo.
It's gonna be okay!
[screams]
[fire crackling]
[REN] So this is where it
became a dragon zombie?
When I think about the people
who suffered because of that
I feel as if I
can never atone.
[Ren grunts]
[Ren sighs]
[NAOFUMI] If a hero wants to
save the world
he has to get stronger
even if it means sacrificing
something dear to him.
Stand strong, Ren.
[sighs]
[NAOFUMI]
This must be the spot.
Look over there.
[NAOFUMI]
That's the Dragon's Den.
[NAOFUMI] Raphtalia
[RAPHTALIA] Yes.
Drifa Light!
Just how deep
do these caves go?
Do you really think
Gaelion is down here somewhere?
[Wyndia scream]
[rumbling]
[RAPHTALIA]
Ren, Wyndia!
[Ren grunts]
Wyndia, Ren!
[REN] We're fine.
Are you okay?
I am.
That's a relief.
[NAOFUMI]
Air Strike Shield!
Will you wait
outside for us?
Mm-mmm.
I'm coming!
If you say so.
[NAOFUMI] What in the world
is this place?
Even the light can't reach
all the way back there.
[WYNDIA]
Give me a second.
Wyndia, what
are you doing?
Dragon Vein
♪
Whoa!
It's beautiful.
[NAOFUMI]
Have you been here before?
[WYNDIA]
Yeah, long ago.
[grunts]
Master Naofumi!
[roaring]
Gaelion, stop!
Filo, no!
[all screaming]
[MELTY] Filo!
[NAOFUMI]
What happened?
Filo went crazy!
[MELTY]
No matter what we try
she just won't listen to
anything we to tell her!
[growls]
What's gotten into her?
Don't do it!
Did it just...
[growls]
Filo, no!
[NAOFUMI]
She's still there!
Filo's still alive!
If we get the core back from
Gaelion then she'll be fine!
[NAOFUMI]
Don't let him absorb her!
- Right!
- [grunts]
♪
Meteor Slash!
[SADEENA]
Zweit Thunderbolt!
[crashes]
[roaring]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[all gasping]
[growling]
That thing's gigantic.
I'll stop it!
Stardust Blade!
Meteor Slash!
[grunts] It's tough!
Lightning
Strike Harpoon!
[zapping]
It's tough indeed.
Not even my strongest attack
works.
I'll use magic to make you
stronger.
All Zweit Aura!
♪
Light Stardust Blade!
It worked!
[roars]
[ECLAIR]
Over here!
[roaring]
♪
[screaming]
You better
give back Filo!
Drifa Aqua Slash!
[roars]
They did it!
[Wyndia gasps]
[weak growl]
It's working!
Now let's finish this!
[WYNDIA]
Wait don't!
That's enough,
everybody!
Please stop it.
[WYNDIA]
Stop all this, Dad!
[voice echoes]
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Please, Dad.
Please don't fight anymore.
Wyndia, what are you
talking about?
[WYNDIA]
My dad is..
My dad was the dragon
that lived in this area.
[Wyndia crying]
[laughing]
[WYNDIA]
No! Let go of me!
Dad, help!
[WYNDIA]
Dad, help me!
Does that mean
I was the one.
[NAOFUMI]
So that's it.
He became a dragon zombie
to try and protect her.
[grunts]
[WYNDIA]
Ever since my dad died
I hated them
with all my heart.
I told myself I couldn't
forgive the heroes
for destroying my life.
However
the Shield Hero was kind to me
when no one else was!
He's not like everyone else
here
who mistreats
Demi-humans!
Or the villagers who
stole your treasure
and turned your body
into a spectacle for others!
Please, give little Gaelion
back his body.
You hear that?
He's even got the same name
as you.
And he's still
alive, Dad.
[sobs]
You can't stay
here anymore!
Not when you're acting
like this!
[growls]
[roaring]
[gasps]
[Ren groans]
[groans]
No, Ren!
Wyndia, are you hurt?
No.
Are you okay?
I'm fine
[NAOFUMI]
Drifa Heal!
Ren, can you fight?
Yeah, just barely.
Who're you?
You're nothing like my dad!
♪
Wyndia, get back!
[EMPEROR DRAGON]
I am the Emperor Dragon
ruler of all monsters
beneath the stars!
Him again?
[NAOFUMI]
So that's it.
Combining the cores of the
zombie dragon from this world
and the Emperor Dragon
from Kizuna's
caused their souls
to mix into one!
[EMPEROR DRAGON]
My festered rage
craves to take control
of this world
from you
pathetic humans!
And once I do.
I'll kill the Hunting Hero
and her comrades
who crushed
my burning ambitions.
[ATLA]
Master Naofumi!
An incredible amount
of power is flowing
from your shield
into the Emperor Dragon.
[NAOFUMI] It's fine.
Stand back, Atla.
But you?
Right.
Just what did
you do with
[EMPEROR DRAGON] I take it
you're referring to the monster
they call a Filolial
in this world?
Filo, no!
- [Sadeena gasps.
- Filo!
[EMPEROR DRAGON] I'm sure
she's more than happy
to serve as
part of my flesh!
[grunts]
[NAOFUMI]
Zweit Aura!
Raphtalia!
On it!
Air Strike Shield!
Light Stardust Blade!
[grunts]
♪
[grunting]
Drifa Aqua Slash!
This isn't working.
My attacks aren't
even affecting him!
[MELTY]
He's nullifying my magic, too!
There is still one way.
[NAOFUMI] I think he's getting
his massive defense stats
from my shield.
Which means
a power-up attempt
on the Wrath Shield
it should weaken him.
But still, that'll just end up
weakening you too, won't it?
There's no
time for caution!
Filo won't
last until then...
[EMPEROR DRAGON]
You really think I'll stand by
and let you do
such a thing?
[whimpers]
[NAOFUMI]
He took it over?
[beeping]
[fire roaring]
Get back!
[explosion]
[all screaming]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Raphtalia!
[WYNDIA] Please, Dad!
Stop this and come back!
[whimpers]
[NAOFUMI]
Damn it!
[NAOFUMI] Meteor Shield!
Air Strike Shield!
Second Shield!
Dritte Shield!
E Float Shield!
[explosion]
[screaming]