[wind whooshing]
[fire crackling]
No I'm fine!
It's just that, I'm a...
Bit tipsy?
I bet you are!
Sorry, Master Naofumi
[thudding]
[GAELION]
Me too. Good night.
My goodness!
Well, these sakes are called
Tanuki and Dragon Killer.
I guess they were
a little too strong
for Raphtalia
and Gaelion, huh?
You know
why you'd wanna keep a place
like this a secret.
I know, isn't
it wonderful?
Yeah, it's nice
and secluded.
Atla, can't bother us
and I can learn the
Way of the Dragon Vein here.
Since Gaelion's proven himself
to be a great teacher
I'm sure you'll have it
mastered in no time.
Oh, is he now? Says who?
[underwater explosion]
[GAELION] Stop
firing off your magic power!
Instead of unleashing
all your power like magic
envision yourself
as an empty vessel
one being
filled with power!
[sighs] I don't know
what to make of any of that!
[NAOFUMI]
You mentioned Raphtalia
already had a blessing
which makes it tricky
for her to learn it too.
[SADEENA] By the way
that Gaelion
is able to talk!
[snoring]
[SADEENA] So, what's the deal
with you two?
Huh?
I mean you and Raphtalia.
What exactly is she to you?
[waves crashing]
It's funny really
[chuckles]
I'm in her debt.
Raphtalia and her parents
gave my life meaning.
If it weren't for them.
I don't know where I'd be.
Gave your life meaning?
That's right. So if you intend
on marrying her someday
you'd better be
especially careful.[Sighs]
- Huh?
- That's not it.
I've only ever thought
of Raphtalia
as a daughter of mine.
Are you being honest
with yourself right now?
Master Naofumi.
Oh, you're awake!
C'mon, you'll get a cold
if you sleep out here.
[SADEENA]
Let's head back now.
You hear that, Gaelion?
It's time to wake up!
[GAELION]
Huh? Did I fall asleep?
[SADEENA] [giggles]
I'll tell you when we get back
to the village, okay?
[GAELION] Fine.
[SADEENA] [giggles] We should
drink like this more often!
♪
Ahh!
Looks like you've been
busy here.
[grunts]
I've thought about it
and I think it might be best
to put Gaelion's blessing
on all the villagers.
I agree, the more people
who can use
the Way of the
Dragon Vein
[soft roaring]
[ELHART]
Hey, kid! How are ya?
- Mister Elhart!
- [ELHART] Whoa!
How you been holdin' up
here, missy?
- [RAPHTALIA] Good!
- Well, well.
To what do we
owe the pleasure?
Thought you'd want to see
what I finished for ya.
♪
[ELHART]
It sure was a lot of work
but I think
it turned out nicely.
Thank you.
Sorry for making you
come all the way out here.
Oh, dear, is that?
[NAOFUMI] It doesn't seem
all that different
from what you're wearing now
if you ask me.
I did what I could.
Sorry it's not my best work.
It's great! And it's not like
I could've done better.
[DEMI-HUMAN GIRL 12-A]
Hey, what's going on?
Are those clothes
for Raphtalia?
Try 'em on we wanna see!
You heard the crowd!
You gotta give the people
what they want, right?
So why not
try go try it on.
Master Naofumi
- [door opening]
Huh?
Hey.
Wow.
You look beautiful, Raphtalia!
Do you really think so?
[gasps] Oh, wow!
You look incredible Raphtalia!
[KEEL] Those clothes
are awesome on you!
Well, seems
everyone likes it.
That settles it then
From now on you're wearing
the miko outfit.
- Hey! I wanna wear one too!
- Okay.
[DEMI-HUMAN GIRL 12-A]
I don't think I've ever seen
clothes like that!
I can't say I understand
what's so special
about this though.
[DEMI-HUMAN BOY 12-A]
I'm so jealous.
How come Raphtalia
gets all the attention?
Ya know, since you're
already here, Elhart
you oughta
go visit Tolly.
Yeah! Since you mentioned it
I'm gonna do just that.
You can teach him
some things while you're at it.
And feel free to stay
the night if you'd like to.
[ELHART]
I'll think about it. Later!
[NAOFUMI]
Elhart helped Tolly
and Raphtalia got comfortable
in her new miko outfit.
As for me
with her paperwork
for the rest of the day.
Things are tough
without Melty here.
I don't know where Motoyasu is
or what he's doing
but at least Ren and Itsuki
are still accounted for.
We've got two months.
Two months to make sure
we're ready
for our upcoming battle
with the Phoenix.
We're back, Naofumi!
Hope you're hungry!
Hey, welcome back!
I pulled in a big catch!
So whip up something special
for dinner!
Sure thing.
We can try frying them
with salt!
You're back, Sadeena
Dinner's going to be splendi...
[gasps]
Are you okay Sadee...
Raphtalia, you have to take
these clothes off, right now.
Hey, what are you doing
I could ask you
the same thing!
I said to be
"especially careful"
- You have to change out of this! Quickly!
- Sadeena.
- What are you talking about?
- That hurts.
Is everything
okay, Naofumi?
[NAOFUMI] Yeah.
You need to calm down.
Tell me what's happening.
I will as soon
as she changes her clothes!
[NAOFUMI] Fine.
Raphtalia, go and change.
Right.
Aw, but it looks
good on her.
[DEMI-HUMAN GIRL 12-B]
That's no fun.
[DEMI-HUMAN GIRL 12-A]
Why can't she wear it?
What has
gotten into you?
Wearing that outfit
is the same as
painting a target
on her back.
It tells the world she's next
in line for the throne.
[gasps]
Wha... Hey!
[explosion]
I was too late!
As source of thy power
Decipher the
laws of nature.
Raphtalia!
A kunai?
[gasps]
- It's an ambush!
- Damn it!
Eclair and the old lady
aren't around either!
[MONKEY 12-A (M)] Die!
Lightning strike those
standing before me
All Drifa Chain
Lightning!
Are you okay?
[RAPHTALIA]
Yes, thank you!
Sir Itsuki we have
to help them fight back!
I'll see what I can do.
[RAPHTALIA]
She's badly wounded.
[SADEENA]
Rishia, please!
[RISHIA]
Leave her to me!
[ELHART]
What's going on over there?
[ATLA]
Was that an explosion?
I don't know
I came as fast as I...
[FOX 12-A (M)]
Don't try and deny it.
We saw your declaration!
We'll do whatever it takes
to stop you
from taking the throne!
Who are these people?
And what is this 'throne"
they speak of?
First thing's first.
We must protect Raphtalia!
[NAOFUMI]
Meteor Shield!
What the!
I'll use my
Hundred Swords!
And I'll use Arrow Rain!
Air Strike Shield!
- Now, Raphtalia!
- I'm on it! Brave Blade Mist!
[RAPHTALIA]
He's tough!
[NAOFUMI]
That worked?
[grunts]
Don't tell me.
They're only immune
to Hero attacks?
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia!
I don't know if
this will work
Understood!
Oh, Power of two
bewilder the enemy
with an illusion!
Spin the threads of fate
once more.
[RAPHTALIA, NAOFUMI]
And thereby turn
our defeat into victory!
[RAPHTALIA, NAOFUMI]
Dragon Vein
hear our plea
and grant us your power!
As source of thy power
Decipher the
laws of nature
and create an illusion
to deceive my foes!
[RAPHTALIA, NAOFUMI]
Form is emptiness!
♪
Huh?
What just happened?
We used some
Choral magic.
It's not much but it'll keep
them busy for a little while.
[REN] For whatever reason
they seem resistant
to Hero attacks.
[ITSUKI] We'll just have
to use our big moves
to overwhelm
their defenses.
[NAOFUMI] Exactly.
[REN] All right, then.
Here it goes!
Meteor Slash!
Eagle Piercing Shot!
Eight Trigrams
Blade of Destiny!
♪
[ORCA 12-A (M)] Glory be to
the Heavenly Emperor!
Get to cover!
[explosion]
What's happened?
Hyah!
I think you owe me
an explanation.
Those assassins
came here from Q'ten Lo.
From Q'ten Lo?
[fire crackling]
[DEMI-HUMAN GIRL 12-C]
Here!
[KEEL] Got it!
[SADEENA] You see
about Raphtalia.
She was born
into a royal family.
The family of Q'ten Lo.
She's a descendant
of the Emperor.
Huh?
And what does that have to do
with the miko outfit
she was wearing?
[SADEENA] The robe you refer
to as a miko outfit
it's a special attire
only the Heavenly Empress
is allowed to wear.
This is...
[SADEENA]
And so, when Raphtalia
who is royalty
born wears it
it's no different than
declaring herself Empress.
Since Q'ten Lo already
has an Emperor
this is akin to
declaring war.
This isn't over.
They're sure to send more
assassins in the future.
That's horrible.
Sadeena, Raphtalia's parent
died in this village.
In the midst of
the First Wave.
[NAOFUMI] Why would
descendants of an Emperor
be in Lurolona Village?
[SADEENA]
Because of a war over
who would be
the next Emperor.
Her father grew tired
of the endless struggles
in the royal family
over who would be the heir.
So he and his wife
fled the country
to come to Melromarc.
My family has served
as bodyguards
for the royal family
for generations.
But I decided
to abandon my mission
so I could follow them
and stand by their side.
After Raphtalia was born
But then... on that day
when the first Wave hit
I was out at sea fishing
and was attacked
by the Wave's monsters.
I couldn't protect
the three of them.
♪
[SADEENA] And by the time
I finally made it back
the slavers had already come
and left with her.
In an instant
the family
I had sworn to protect
with my life
was no more.
Raphtalia
is being the Heavenly Empress
something you want?
No.
The fire has
settled down.
Is the child okay?
I wouldn't say
she's out of the woods yet.
[fire crackling]
I see. It was Q'ten Lo.
[NAOFUMI] The reason
they picked a fight with us
was idiotic.
Not quite.
[ECLAIR] Just because it might
seem stupid to us.
Doesn't mean it's not a matter
of life or death
to another country.
[NAOFUMI]
Sadeena, there were times
when you were acting
like there might be someone
on the outskirts
of the village.
Were you
looking for them?
- Yes.
- Then how long
have they been
watching Raphtalia?
They've been watching her
since before she was born.
- I'm sorry.
- [gasps]
Seriously?
So when the First Wave hit
and the slavers came
when she was nearly
auctioned off
when she became my slave
and nearly died.
You mean to tell me
this entire time
they've been
watching her
and did nothing about
any of that?
Can't say I'm surprised.
I hate to say it
but from their perspective
they'd be better off
if she died.
She threatens
their throne.
Yeah, you're
probably right.
But if they'd been
watching that closely
they'd know she wasn't aware
of her royal blood
meaning that
she had no intention
of ever taking
the throne.
[NAOFUMI] They're just using
that miko outfit
as an excuse
to finally kill her.
To eliminate any threat
to the Emperor's rule.
They don't give a damn
whether she wants
the throne or not.
They want her dead.
They sent assassins
before even sending messengers.
They see no need
for international formalities
since we're a tiny territory
of Melromarc.
[ECLAIR]
Good point.
They probably assumed
attacking us
wouldn't result
in a war for them.
And I'm gonna make certain
they know
they were
wrong about that.
They're sure as hell
getting a fight!
Master Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI]
They tried to kill Raphtalia
they gravely wounded
one of my citizens
they waged
war on my lands!
[grunts]
It's a declaration of war
against one
of the Cardinal Heroes.
With that in mind
We can't get ready
for the Phoenix
if we're constantly
watching our backs.
There's only one thing
that all of us can do.
[gasps]
Only one thing. You mean!
We're gonna go and have
a little chat with them.
And if that doesn't work
♪
[both grunting]
Atla, we don't have
to do this here, you know.
Regardless of
where we are
we have to continue
our training. [Gasps]
[ATLA] Hello there.
[MIRELIA]
Leave all of the preparations
for the battle
with the Phoenix to us.
I wish your party
a safe journey to Q-ten Lo.
[NAOFUMI]
Thank you.
I will also send knights
to Lurolona Village
guarding it in
your absence.
I don't get it.
Why are you being
so helpful right now?
I don't know
how you did it
but you managed to bring
the four Heroes together
in time for the Phoenix.
[MIRELIA] It would be an insult
to not reward you for that.
In that case, I'd like to know
the fastest route to Q'ten Lo.
We don't have a lot of time
to spare at the moment.
Sadly, it's as
the Knight Eclair said
Q'ten Lo has
isolated them self
and we don't have
any relations with them.
However, there
is something.
A ferry that goes to Q'ten Lo
from Siltvelt.
I'll see if I can arrange
for you all to be
on the next one out.
Sounds great.
Back to Siltvelt, huh?
That's the place where we
picked up Fohl and Atla.
How are those two?
Are they doing well?
Sure are.
They're here right now.
They insist on
following me
whether I really want them to
or not.
I think that's lovely.
[MIRELIA] I suppose they'll be
going to Siltvelt too then.
[FOHL]
Hey, old man!
What're you
doing out here?
I suggest that you watch
your tone, boy! This here is...
Silence. I'll
hear no more.
Yes, sir.
Are you
feeling all right?
Have you had
enough to eat?
Yes. Thank
you for asking.
[FOHL]
She can eat all right.
Atla eats enough food
for the both of us!
Yes. I'm full of energy.
Ah, I see!
The Shield Demon hasn't done
you any harm, has he?
[BOTH] Huh?
Did you say, "Demon?"
Please don't use such
a terribly cruel word as that.
I mean after all
it's thanks to Master Naofumi
that I'm even alive right now.
[FOHL]
Yeah, that's right.
Atla was getting sicker
by the day.
She never would've
recovered without his help.
She was so sick
But look at her now!
[ATLA]
Oh, there he is!
[gasps]
[grunts] Farewell.
[ATLA] Oh! Um, will we ever
get to see you again?
Yes. I'm certain of it.
[NAOFUMI] And so...
I left Queen Mirelia
in charge of
preparations.
And headed for Q'ten Lo.
First, we'll head to Siltvelt
where the ferry departs.
I'll fly there
with Wyndia and Gaelion.
Once we're in a safe
enough location.
[NAOFUMI] I'll use a portal
to summon the rest of you.
Be careful flying there!
Take care of
him, all right?
We're all
counting on you!
[soft roaring]
Just leave it to me!
You all hang tight.
♪
[NAOFUMI]
We have less than two months
before the
Phoenix revives.
What I'm doing now
might be irresponsible
given the time
we have left.
However... this is a battle
I have to fight.
After all, this will decide
Raphtalia's fate!
♪
- [giggling]
- Raphy.
[panting]
Slow down, Filo!
You're too fast!
[FILO] Here we go!
Just wait and
see, Master!
I'm gonna come back
ten times stronger than before!
Ra-Raphy.
- Wait, before we go.
- [FILO] And we're off!
[NAOFUMI] Even though
I'm the Shield Hero
I shouldn't interfere with
the fates of my party members.
But they're my precious
comrades.
And for the sake
of those comrades
I'll fight the Waves
and anything else
that comes my way!
♪
Worry not. For the sake
of my precious Filo
I will fight
by your side
[NAOFUMI] I'll fight
an entire country if I must!
♪
[thunder rumbling]
[NAOFUMI] Because
the Shield Hero,
must follow!
[thunder rumbling]