This story
is one that only she and I can tell.
It is the story of the secret of this world.
It was just there,
like a pool of light.
Without even thinking, she ran out of the hospital.
Praying with all her heart,
she crossed the shrine gate.
Are those fish?
Even now, I wonder
if everything I saw that day
was all just a dream.
But I know it wasn't.
On that summer day,
up in that sky,
we changed the shape of the world.
Attention, all passengers.
We will be expecting very heavy rain shortly.
It's gonna rain again?
I thought it was finally clearing up.
There was a typhoon on the island, too.
It was still fun.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
We may as well get lunch.
We ask that all passengers
who are out on the deck to please go back...
Whoa.
So cool.
Huh?
Thank you.
Yeah. That was a pretty intense storm, huh?
This is shockingly delicious.
You, uh, want to try, little man?
Nope. I'm not that hungry.
Last chance. 'Cause I'll just dig in.
Thanks for treating, by the way.
Oh, don't mention it.
It's the least I could do since you saved me.
Oh, I did, didn't I?
It was a close one, too, huh?
Oh.
Hey, wait a minute.
Huh?
Yeah.
This is actually the first time I've saved a guy's life.
Well done, me.
Oh. Okay.
Come to think of it,
I think I deserve a beer.
Do you want me to buy you one?
That's...
so expensive.
I can't believe a grown man is mooching off of me.
Tokyo sure is scary.
Ugh. It's raining again.
So, tell me, little man, what brings you to Tokyo?
Oh, uh, I'm just here to visit some relatives.
Uh, 'cause, uh, at my school,
uh, s-summer break starts early.
I see.
Well, if you ever need help, feel free to reach out.
See you around, little man.
In the baggage claim area.
Again, thank you for riding the Salvia Maru,
operated by Tokai Kisen...
Yeah, right.
Huh?
The shower's 280 for 20 minutes max.
Here.
That's crazy.
It started pouring out of nowhere.
You should know better by now.
Not my job to clean up after you.
I'm sorry.
Last year's record instances
of sudden torrential rain were exceeded this year,
with more frequent occurrences expected in July.
It is advised to take extreme caution...
Yes!
Not just to the mountains
and beaches, but also throughout the city.
In order to prevent accidents
and potential disasters, it is imper...
Seriously?!
You sure you're in college?
Let's see your I.D.
No I.D.?
How we supposed to hire you?
This job some kind of joke to you?
As you can see, sudden downpour...
Huh?
Tokyo sure is scary.
Can't keep spending money like this.
You can't sit here. You'll have to move.
Right. Sorry.
All you can drink for 18 yen!
Hi there, big guy. Would you like to come inside?
Hang on, buddy. Can you spare a minute?
Please beware of solicitors.
You are not obligated to give them any money.
They may or may not be telling the truth.
Hey, hang on there.
What are you doing out here?
You in high school?
Hey, wait!
Hey, come back here!
What the hell?!
This has been a public service
announcement from the Shin...
Huh.
Tokyo sure is scary.
You know what?
I just...
I don't want to go home.
Not ever.
Seriously?
Who is this kid?
He sleeping?
Out here?
Hey, kid.
You can't be out here.
Oh, sorry.
God, is he okay?
Ah, he's fine.
So, you would make way more with us.
Pardon me.
Gross.
It's got to be a toy.
Uh, s-sorry. Wh-What... what's this?
It's for you, but don't tell.
Uh, but wh-what for?
Take it, unless you want to have chowder for dinner again.
I think that was the most delicious
dinner I've had in all 16 years of my life.
Hey, so when can I see you again?
Uh, how about the day after tomorrow?
Great. I discovered this cute new café.
I'll book us a table.
Bye, Nagi. See you then.
See you then, Ayane.
They're in elementary school?
Nice!
I was hoping I'd see you.
Hi there, Kana.
Hello, Nagi.
What a player.
Oh, did you curl it?
Do you like it like this?
I do. It's super cute.
Tokyo sure is amazing.
This should be it.
Yeah?
Hmm?
It's not working. Ugh.
Excuse me.
I called earlier.
Hello? Is anybody here?
Mr. Suga...?
Mr. Suga?
No, I shouldn't be doing this.
Mm. Hello.
I-I'm so sorry.
Oh, you're the new assistant.
Kei told me about you.
What? No, I haven't...
I'm Natsumi. Welcome.
Huh?
Finally, he's found someone to do all my grunt work.
So, uh, kid...
Uh, yeah?
I saw you checking out my boobs.
No, I wasn't.
Okay, kid, what's your name?
Hodaka Morishima.
Hodaka, huh? That's interesting.
Are you one of Mr. Suga's employees?
Oh, so you want to know the truth about us?
Yeah.
Hilarious.
I know what you're thinking, and you're right.
I don't believe it.
I've never met a mistress before.
Huh.
Long time, no see, little man.
Did you lose weight?
For me?
Let me guess... This from playing pachinko?
So, little man,
you came for a job... am I right?
This is basically what we do here.
We write articles for time-honored, prestigious magazines.
We're doing a piece on urban legends.
All you got to do is talk to a
few people who have witnessed some.
It'll be a piece of cake.
Huh? I'm not...
It can be on anything.
Doomsday predictions, abductions, you know.
Whatever you kids are into these days.
Here. I got one.
"The girl who brings sunshine wherever she goes."
S-Sunshine girl?
Bring that sunshine!
Yeah, it's been raining so damn much this year.
She's got to be in demand.
Right?
Okay.
Come on, little man. Where's your hustle?
She's already got a thing set up.
Tag along. Take notes.
Huh?
Wait, what? Like, like, now?
Oh, it'll be like an audition!
A what?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Of course.
Sunshine girls do exist.
I knew it!
But rain girls exist as well.
The former are protected by a fox spirit,
and the latter are protected by a dragon god.
Uh, what?
Those who are protected by the
dragon god tend to drink a lot.
They yearn for water.
They're strong-willed and competitive,
though careless and unreliable.
That kind of sounds like me.
Those protected by the fox spirit are hardworking
but too timid to be leaders.
Though many of them are quite beautiful.
That's totally me.
The four spirits of weather are off-balance, so
more sunshine and rain girls are born these days.
It's the homeostasis of Gaia theory.
That's how it works.
But one must be careful.
Whenever we mess with nature, we will always pay a price.
And they say whoever uses too much weather power
will get spirited away.
I see.
Huh?
Don't worry. I'll be careful.
So...
how did it go?
The so-called psychic went on about mystical
stuff that came straight out of a fantasy novel.
Weather power making you disappear.
Yeah, sure. Typical.
Weather isn't controlled by girls with powers.
It's a natural phenomenon
having to do with pressure fronts.
I know that, but we're not doing a research
paper. We're just providing some entertainment.
Is this all you've written so far?
Damn, you're slow.
I'm sorry.
Well, at least your writing style's not too bad.
All right, fine, you're hired.
Huh? Hold on a minute. I wasn't looking...
We need you on-site, so your room's included.
Meals, too.
Really?
Yes. I'll take it.
That's more like it.
Now, what's your name again?
Hilarious.
It's Hodaka.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Dinner's ready.
Here.
Hmm?
I'm underage, r-remember?
Now, here's to our new hire,
Hodaka.
Bottoms up.
Slow down, Hodaka.
It was the first meal I had shared
with anyone since I came to Tokyo.
And that is how my new life began.
The place was a small publishing
company run by Mr. Suga and Miss Natsumi...
Hey, guys.
Good morning to you.
Where I pretty much did all the chores.
Starting with Mr. Suga's personal care,
to answering the phone, filing
receipts, transcribing interviews.
Is this seriously all you've written?
This isn't mine.
Sorry, but Mr. Suga's out right now.
Sometimes, I got to ride around town with
Miss Natsumi to assist with the interviews.
They're looking for a real-life sunshine girl.
That's so hilarious.
My little sister's friend's a real sunshine girl.
People will call her up right before they go on a date.
We really don't do those kind of interviews.
After that, the balloon's particle
imager picked up something really strange.
A swarm of moving objects from among the cumulonimbi.
Is this seriously all you've managed to write?
You should wait for these to go on sale.
Mr. Suga's out right now.
This paragraph's crap.
But this one here's not too bad.
Oh.
Come on, Mr. Suga. We got to go.
Wake up.
My days were, well, hectic.
But for the first time in my life,
someone counted on me, and it was nice.
Those rainy days in Tokyo seemed to just fly by.
Rain. Rain.
There you are.
Hey there, Rain.
Are you good?
Is that so? Here.
Don't you worry your pretty head.
I'm telling you, it's an easy job.
We'll see.
Just try it and see how you like it.
You'll get paid immediately after.
Our club's right over there.
I know her.
You might as well give it a go
and earn some quick cash, huh?
It's just right through that door, okay?
Come on, let's go.
But...
Hey!
Let's go!
What? No, no, no, no.
Where are they going?
Hey! Wait, please!
Just keep running!
No, wait!
Punk!
Hey. Where you think you're going, buddy?
What in the hell do you think you're doing?!
You were about to force her t-to... to...
Huh?
What are you, dumb?
Hate to break it to you, but she and I made a deal.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a second. You look familiar.
You were squatting in front of our club.
What is this, some kind of payback?
Please, stop hitting him.
I said stop!
Damn you!
Get off me!
What do you got there? A toy?
You really are dumb.
Get up.
Come on!
Hey!
What'd you do that for?
Paying me back for the burger?
Huh?
Who are you?
And where'd you get that gun?
That was just...
I-I found it. I-I thought it was a
toy, and it brought me luck, so I kept it.
That's your reason?
How could you point it at someone?
You could have killed him!
Seriously, who does that?
It's messed up.
So, uh...
I ended up getting fired.
'Cause of me?
It didn't have anything to do with the burger.
Since I got fired, I needed the money,
so, um...
I'm sorry. I-I shouldn't have...
Hey. Does it hurt?
No, not really.
Let me guess... You ran away from home?
Huh?
It's pretty obvious.
Too bad you can't enjoy Tokyo with all this rain.
Uh, yeah.
Come with me.
Uh...
Whoa.
Watch.
It's gonna clear up.
Huh?
Hey. What do you mean by...
What?
You're a sunshine girl.
My name's Hina.
And you?
Hodaka.
How old?
Uh, 16.
Mm...
You're younger than me.
Huh?
I'll be 18 in, uh...
approximately a month.
You-you look younger.
So you should treat me with respect.
What?
Mm...
Nice to meet you, Hodaka.
Huh?
Mommy, I saw a fish.
Oh, yeah? That's nice.
You better not be making this up.
I'm dead serious. Come on, this way.
Look. It's over there.
What am I looking at?
It's right over there.
Just trust me, will you?
Huh?
Mm.
What the heck is that?
And in our storm watch series,
the Kanto region is experiencing a
record-breaking amount of rainfall this summer.
It has been raining continuously
for more than two months now.
And our 30-day forecast predicts more
heavy rain for at least another month.
The Meteorological Agency is calling for strict
alerts on landslides and other related disasters,
as these are extremely unusual
weather patterns for this season.
Is that too expensive?
Oh, my God. Come look at this.
Huh?
It's amazing.
It's so weird.
Hmm.
I mean, they do kind of look like fish.
Except these things come from the sky,
and it's not like they leave behind evidence.
I know. They just instantly disappear. Look.
Huh?
And remember what that guy we interviewed said?
The sky's a more vast unknown world than even the sea.
A cumulonimbus can hold as much water as
an entire lake. Which means it's possible
that it could hold a whole unknown ecosystem.
Something like...
like these fish.
Yeah, totally.
That's so cool!
If we write about it...
oh, maybe we can make good money from it.
Huh? What's...
Huh?
- Oh, come on. You're starting to sound like Kei.
You don't want to wind up a boring grown-up.
Careful, or that sunshine girl is gonna lose interest.
You two are going on a date, right?
It's not a date. I'm just confirming if...
Well, I got a job interview, so...
What? Don't you work here?
This is just a temporary thing.
I told you guys, it's not a date.
I understand how you feel, Keisuke.
But we've finally gotten to the point
where she isn't asking about you constantly.
It would be too cruel to her to
allow you to meet with her now.
That's not... It's well within my rights to see her.
Well, let me ask... You still smoke, right?
Huh?
She has asthma.
You know that.
Selfish, don't you think?
Actually, not anymore.
I've already quit.
Perhaps.
Still, that doesn't address your lifestyle.
Huh?
Besides, with all this rain now,
she can't play outside.
It would be bad for her asthma.
I feel sorry for children nowadays.
We used to have such beautiful springs and summers.
They can't go on living there unsupervised like that.
I completely agree.
Wait a minute.
Could this possibly be...
the first time I'm visiting...
a girl's home?
Welcome to my place.
Was it hard to find?
Uh, I just stopped to, uh...
It's-it's not much. Here.
That was very sweet of you.
Welcome.
Thanks.
Sure thing.
Hodaka, have you had lunch yet?
No, not yet.
But you don't have to.
Uh...
You just sit right there.
Hey, mind if I use these?
Yeah. No, sure.
Thanks.
So, do you live all by yourself here, Hina?
With my younger brother, due to some circumstances.
Circumstances?
How about you? Why did you run away?
Truth is everything was suffocating.
That town, my parents.
I see.
You should go back, don't you think?
No, I don't want to.
I see.
Here you go. Lunch is served.
Whoa.
I forgot the spring onions. Where'd I put them?
So, how do you feel now, living in Tokyo?
Huh? Uh...
I don't feel like I'm suffocating anymore.
Well, that's great, right?
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Wh-What's that? An earthquake?
No. No.
It's just the train.
Hodaka,
are you serious?
Why not?
I mean, you're a real sunshine girl, right?
Mm-hmm.
You can clear up the sky simply by praying.
I guess.
Then why not?
You said you needed a job, right?
I really do. But I feel weird charging.
Well, would you rather go back to that club? 'Cause
I don't think you're cut out for that kind of work.
Hodaka.
What are you looking at?
I'm not looking at anything!
Sorry.
Isn't 5,000 yen too expensive?
Okay. Uh, how about 3,000?
Hmm, but in order to cover my living expenses...
We should have some artwork.
Oh, I can draw something.
What is that?
A hippo?
It's a frog.
S-Seriously?
It's done!
All right, I'm uploading.
Everything look good?
Yeah.
I'm home.
Hey, the sardines were on sale, so I...
Oh.
Who are you?
Uh, y-you're that kid!
From the back of the bus.
Huh?
You guys know each other?
Hodaka, this is my brother Nagi.
Nagi, this is Hodaka,
my brand-new business partner.
Huh?
Whoa! We've got a response already!
What? You actually uploaded it?
And they say that... that they
want good weather for a flea market.
Uh, and it's tomorrow!
Hang on a minute.
Am I really going to do this?
And tomorrow, it looks like more rain.
And it's gonna rain!
Yeah, but isn't that, like, the whole point?
What do I do?
Ugh, who is this guy?
It will be fine.
I'll be there to help you.
How?!
Here. I brought you this.
Thanks, but no.
Uh, th-that's okay.
I have another secret weapon.
Sorry, but no.
I told you, Hodaka!
Who called these guys again?
What a bunch of weirdos.
Uh, we figured it couldn't hurt.
Don't worry about it, kids.
I don't think it's working.
We can do this. We're-we're almost there.
Do you... do you need some water, Hina?
Uh, how about some candy?
Just tell 'em to go home.
Okay.
The sky!
Huh?
It's been forever since I've seen the sun.
It's so pretty.
Huh. Will you look at that?
How'd I do?
That was truly amazing.
You are a sunshine girl.
I can't believe that actually worked.
You kids did great, even if it was a coincidence.
It wasn't!
How does 20,000 yen sound?
It's too much.
It's a bonus.
For a job well done.
Thanks again.
People will come out now, and we'll
be... we'll be able to sell more.
Yeah!
That was amazing, sis!
All right!
I can totally do this!
Yeah!
Let's make some money off of the weather!
Yes!
Yeah!
The human mind works in mysterious ways.
Sometimes, you just need to see the sun
shining in the morning to feel energized.
A blue sky can make you feel happy that you're alive.
It makes you feel more in love with
that someone special by your side.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime event,
and it better be under a blue sky.
The meteor will be passing Earth tonight.
He can't run well in the rain, so he's losing.
I've been working so many hours, saving up just for today.
We want to play outside.
Everyone had their own reason to want a
little sunshine in the constantly rainy Tokyo.
Hina was only able to clear up small
areas and only for a brief amount of time.
But it didn't matter.
The sky would always answer her prayers.
She was 100% a real-life sunshine girl!
It was like the whole city was
putting its best foot forward.
It made me think...
what a wonderful world I was born into.
Here we go. Big smiles.
That's it! Go, go!
Look, there's another one.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
Thank you so very much.
It's amazing how a simple thing
like the weather can affect our moods.
That was when I realized for the first time just
how much the human heart is connected to the sky.
All right, I'm off.
Huh?
To where?
Ugh. Five more minutes.
Five more minutes... That's all I'm waiting.
Is it canceled 'cause of the rain?
When was it actually supposed to start?
And I got all dressed up.
There's no way it's happening.
It's too crowded here anyway.
I read online that your sunshine girl is amazing.
100% success rate.
Uh, yeah.
It's true, but d-do you really want to
rely on just that for such a huge event?
Well, it's supposed to rain all week
long, so I can't exactly postpone it.
I would say we're in a unique situation.
The door is opening.
May as well rely on luck.
Uh...
Huh?
The Jingu Gaien fireworks will start
promptly at 7:00 p.m. as scheduled.
I think that I'm in love.
Huh?
This job, the sunshine girl.
It's like, for the first time in my life,
I've found a purpose.
And you know what?
That's not not not such a bad thing.
Wait. How-how many "nots" is...
Is it bad or not?
Lighten up a little.
And so, thank you, Hodaka.
Weather is such a mystery.
Seeing a beautiful sky can really make you feel things.
Just like Hina.
She really makes me feel things.
Yesterday's Jingu Gaien fireworks were
blessed with sudden miraculous clear skies.
But as if to make up for it, the rain
is back again today with a vengeance.
The temperature in central Tokyo is now at 70 degrees,
much lower than average for this time of year,
making it an unusually chilly August.
Make sure to bring a light jacket when going out.
You're my first choice, of course.
You're my first choice, of course!
Getting a flu shot may not be a bad idea.
In other news, the record rainfall and
low temperatures are driving food prices up.
A head of lettuce will cost you three
times more than this time last year.
This abnormal cold snap is affecting agriculture.
Oh, that submission?
Yes, we received it.
Look, I'm sorry, but we decided to pass.
I see. Thank you, and, uh...
we have other pieces in the
works for, you know, next time.
Hmm.
Yeah, what?
Hello. Mamiya residence.
Hi. It's Keisuke.
I'm sorry to bother you, but it's regarding my visit.
You're late again, Kei.
And this is an important interview.
Bad mood?
Did you get rejected? Meow.
Where's the kid?
What do you mean, busy with his other job?
No wonder he's been slacking.
Just leave him alone.
It's not like we're busy.
He took in a stray cat without asking.
Like you took him in?
Huh?
I know why you did it.
He reminds you of yourself.
Plus, how much could it be costing
you to pay the kid each month?
What, 30,000 yen?
Cheapo.
Actually, 3,000.
Uh... what?! Are you serious?! That's slave labor!
Is that even legal?
You're gonna get sued by the Department
of Labor. Young people love suing.
You know what? Actually, I-I
think I'm gonna report you myself.
One, he gets to live with us for free.
Two, we pay for his food and his phone bill.
It's a sweet deal.
Oh, God.
Well, no wonder he got another job.
That's incredible.
It really cleared up.
You kids are amazing.
It's a shame you're planning to quit.
Since she was caught on camera,
we've been flooded with requests.
We can't handle them all.
We have one more scheduled, so we'll
do that, and then we'll stop for a while.
And besides...
All right, good job, sis.
Hey, Grandma. I see you got people over.
I wasn't expecting you.
Just stopped by to see if you needed help.
You've got some really young guests.
Are you friends of Grandma's?
Hello.
I wanted nice weather for Grandpa's Hatsubon.
Ah. Nice.
Well, it did stop raining.
It'd be hard for him to come back
with all the rain we've been having.
"Come back"?
The Obon,
the day the dead come back from the sky to visit.
His first Obon?
So, then your grandpa died about a year ago?
That's right.
Yeah, same goes for my mom, too.
Oh, did you lose your mother this past year, sweetie?
Uh, yes.
Then let's light a welcoming fire for her as well.
I know she's watching over you.
Thanks.
The spirits follow the smoke,
and that's how they come back.
Back from where?
From Heaven.
There's always been another world up there in the sky.
This painting is apparently
of what the Weather Maiden saw.
It sure is mysterious.
I mean, there's a flying fish and a dragon?
Absolutely stunning.
Isn't it, though?
So, this Weather Maiden, what is she?
Like a shaman or what?
Huh? What?
Oh, he...
Is the Weather Maiden like a shaman?
Uh-huh.
Mending the ailing weather is
the charge of the Weather Maiden.
So, is it like her job?
Sounds like a scam.
Does that mean she could fix
the abnormal weather we're having?
Huh? There's nothing abnormal about the rain.
The news makes a big deal about everything.
They always say things like "record-breaking,"
but when did their records start?
100 years ago?
How old do you think this painting is?
800 years old, at least.
800?
Hey, you're getting yourself all worked up.
Oh, oh, is he...?
My point is the weather can suddenly change on a whim,
regardless of our human needs.
So we cannot tell what is normal and what is not.
We merely have been allowed to stay in this shifting space
between the heavens and earth, clinging for our lives,
trying our best not to be shaken off.
This is something we humans were
much more aware of in the past.
However, there's a thin thread
binding us humans to the sky.
And that is the Weather Maiden.
A special girl with the ability
to gather the people's wishes
and deliver them to the heavens.
In ancient times, there was one
in every village in every country.
Hey, Kei. Sound like anyone you know?
You know, you don't have to
listen to everything Grandpa says.
No one actually believes in that stuff.
No, no, I love it.
We're grateful for all of your insight.
Just remember, though,
everything comes with a price.
This is no exception.
A tragic fate awaits the Weather Maiden.
One, two, three.
All right, it's your turn, sis.
Thanks for keeping Grandma company.
- It's really kind of you.
Oh, we're actually here 'cause she hired us.
You have to. Come on.
Well, they're having fun.
How old are you guys, anyway?
Oh. I'm 16, but she's actual...
She mentioned that she was turning 18 next week.
18, huh?
Have you thought about what to get her?
Hey, you guys, I brought out some watermelon.
Oh, nice. Thanks a lot.
Okay.
Hey, wait. I said wait!
Just great.
Ah, what the hell?
I said wait!
Whoa, guys. You got to cut me some slack.
I didn't know she was a minor. I swear.
Huh? Wait, so this isn't about the girl?
That's what we've been trying to tell you.
You made us run for nothing.
This is you, is it not?
What?
Take a good look.
What do you know about the boy in the video?
So, the kid's about high-school age, huh?
Maybe he picked up the gun
Shibata threw away by pure accident.
If that's the case, then the
kid might have posted about it.
Oh. You mean online.
Yeah, nothing is private.
Kids post everything on social media these days.
Go, Nagi, go!
Yeah!
That was amazing, Nagi!
Yeah! Great shot!
A ring. Definitely a ring.
What? You sure it's not too much?
We're talking about my sister's birthday, right?
I did ask a woman for ideas, but...
I know what I'd like.
Hugs and kisses, money,
boyfriend and a real job.
But she wasn't very helpful.
See you later, Nagi.
See you around, Nagi.
Mm-hmm.
Just admit it. You're in love with my sister.
Huh?
No, it's-it's noth-nothing like that.
Uh, oh, wait. What if it is? Then what?
You know...
Being ambivalent is the worst thing as a man.
Uh, is that true?
Be clear before you start going out.
Then you can be vague. Those are the basics.
I should call you "Sempai."
Ever since our mom died,
my sister's been working nonstop.
I know the reason she's doing it is for me.
'Cause I'm still a kid.
So that's why
I want to see her get to do more teenage stuff.
But you're gonna have to prove
you're the guy for the job, okay?
Here you go. Enjoy.
Thank you.
But, uh...
do you think she'll like it?
Huh?
Don't worry.
We spent three hours picking it out.
If it were me, I'd be very happy.
Good luck, okay?
Tomorrow's sunshine girl job will be our last.
Our customer is a man who requested good weather
at the park so that he could play with his daughter.
After that appointment,
I plan on giving Hina the ring.
Daddy, can you do it one more time?
Okay. Are you ready?
Oh, man.
That was tough on my back.
Of all the people that could have hired us.
Did you already know I was doing this as a side job, huh?
I bet you knew this entire time and said
nothing. And since when have you had a daughter?!
Well, I'm impressed.
The forecast said it'd be 100% rain today.
Yeah, unfortunately, my daughter has asthma.
And she lives with her grandmother, who
won't let me see her if it's raining out, so...
it's been tough lately.
There's nothing more gorgeous than a beautiful, clear sky.
I concur.
I take it you're Hodaka's boss, then?
Yep. I also saved his life.
Hey, does your friend always speak so formally?
Huh? Well, Hina is a whole two years older than me.
What? Ridiculous.
16, 17, 18... There's no difference.
Yeah, there is!
Yeah, you're right.
Ugh! There you are.
Hey!
Did I miss anything?
Wh-What are you gonna do about her?
Aren't you gonna be in trouble?
Hmm?
I mean, does Natsumi even know that you're married?
What's wrong? You okay?
Hodaka, he... he actually thought you were my...
Mistress?!
Hang on. You never mentioned that she's your niece.
So, this whole time, you had disgusting fantasies?
That is so perverted.
Classic Hodaka.
Hmm.
Are you looking at my boobs?
I am not!
Natsumi!
Hey, Moka. What do you got there?
Daddy, look! A flower crown.
I made it for you!
Yeah? Let me see.
Hodaka, join us.
Uh, Sempai calls.
Hodaka is such a riot.
He is such a child.
They're like the older and younger
versions of each other, don't you think?
Hodaka and Mr. Suga?
Yeah.
Kei ran away from home and came to
Tokyo when he was a teenager, too.
Then he met and fell madly in love with his future wife.
But then, a few years ago, she died in an accident.
He's still very much in love with her, though.
It's so good to meet you.
I've been wanting to for a long time.
You're the real sunshine girl. That's amazing!
I wish I had a special skill
to put on my résumé like that.
I hate looking for a job. Too bad I'm not in high school.
It's funny.
'Cause for me, I can't wait to grow up.
Huh.
Yeah, I understand that.
I'm glad you're
doing well, though.
Huh?
Actually, I was a bit worried about you.
You okay, Moka? You tired?
Here you go.
One, two, three.
I'm fine. I want to keep playing.
I know, but it's raining.
We're taking off. Have a good day, okay?
But I want to hang out with Nagi some more.
Then why don't we all grab some dinner?
I'm sorry, but...
Hey, how about I just go eat with Moka, then?
Would that be okay?
Great.
Yay!
Hodaka, can you take Hina home?
Uh...
Hey, whoa, uh...
Hina, thank you for bringing the sunshine today.
Thank you.
I'm happy you're happy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
This might be...
the very first time that...
I tell someone I love them.
Hina, I...!
Hodaka.
Oh, sorry.
Uh...
What is it?
Nothing in particular.
What did you want to say?
Hodaka,
so, um...
I...
Hina!
Hodaka!
Where are you, Hina?
I think I know when I became
a sunshine girl.
It was one year ago, on that day.
I spent the entire day before praying for good weather.
I wanted to have one last walk under the sun with my mom.
And then I saw it.
It looked like a pool of light.
And praying with all my heart, I crossed the shrine gate.
When I finally came to, I was lying on the ground,
and the sky was clear.
I think that's when it happened.
That's when...
I became connected to the sky.
Is it true? Connected to the sky?
Hodaka, don't come out.
It's the police. Sorry for the late visit.
The police?
Look again.
You sure you haven't seen him before?
Someone fitting his description has
been reported several times in this area.
I don't know him.
May I ask what he's done?
We just want to ask him some questions. That's all.
He's a minor and a runaway.
Additionally, his parents have
filed a missing persons report.
We've also been told that you live
here on your own with your little brother.
Is that correct?
Yes.
That, unfortunately, is another issue.
Children cannot live on their own without a guardian.
But...!
Sorry.
But we're quiet and don't cause trouble.
Hina.
She said that she was going to come back tomorrow,
bring child services.
What do I do?
They're going to separate us.
I just know it.
Hodaka, the police.
They were just...
I know.
Go inside. I'll be back tomorrow.
Mr. Suga?
Hey. Like the new look?
I'm in disguise.
Earlier today, the police stopped by my office.
They're treating your disappearance as a kidnapping.
I denied any involvement, but I
can tell they still suspect me.
Consider this your severance pay.
Huh?
I can't have you coming back to the office.
If they catch you there, they'll arrest me.
I'm in the process of filing for custody of my daughter,
so I got to be careful, understand?
If I were you, I'd head back home tomorrow.
Then everything can go back to normal.
It'll be best for everyone.
You'll see.
Time to grow up, little man. Got it?
We can't stay here anymore.
But... where will you go?
I don't know, but...
Hey, it doesn't matter where
we go, as long as we're together.
Hmm. Hodaka, you should probably go
home before you get caught by the police.
At least you've got a place to go back to.
Don't say that.
Don't worry. We're gonna be fine.
No way.
I'm not going back.
Let's run away!
A special heavy rain advisory has
just been issued in the Tokyo area.
It could be the heaviest downpour
that the city has experienced in decades.
Lowland communities should be prepared for flash flooding.
A sudden typhoon-strength low-pressure system is...
River levels rising.
Increased risk of flooding.
The dam is not going to hold!
Keep calm and slowly make your way towards the exit.
The Namboku Line at Akabane-Iwabuchi
Station, the Shibuya Metro...
Outgoing flights have been canceled from Haneda Airport.
Over six inches of rain is falling per hour, and
heavy flooding has been reported in many areas in Tokyo.
Sir, are you okay?
Kita Ward, Arakawa Ward,
Taito Ward, Sumida Ward, Shibuya...
Please head home immediately.
It's really cold, right?
It has been a record-breaking August.
The temperature in Tokyo has fallen below 50 degrees.
Cumulonimbi continue to gather above Tokyo.
In merely an hour,
Tokyo's landscape has been transformed.
I repeat, a heavy rain special advisory
has been issued for the greater Tokyo area.
This is looking to be the heaviest rainfall
recorded in the last few decades.
A low-pressure system over the Kanto region...
The stream of cold air that passed over
Kanto on the 21st is the cause of the current...
Active rainclouds will remain over
east and central Japan at least...
The Meteorological Agency has
stated that this abnormal weather
will continue for at least the next few weeks.
Experts warn that the current weather pattern we
are seeing is unprecedented and extremely dangerous.
Trains on the Yamanote Line are
indefinitely delayed due to the heavy rains.
There is no way to resume
operations until the weather clears up.
Let's just get off here.
Oh, I'll ask my mom to pick us up.
It's freezing.
What should we do?
Hey, don't worry.
Let's find a place to stay tonight.
I'm sorry, but we don't have anything available.
We're fully booked.
Do you have a reservation?
We're all full.
There's no adult with you?
One last thing... I need to see your I.D.
We can't accept unaccompanied minors.
This ain't about the money.
It's not about the money!
Be honest.
Are you kids runaways?
Hina, Hodaka, look.
Is that snow?
Could it be true?
That Hina is connected to the sky?
It's freezing.
Hey, Kei, it's snowing in August.
It's official... The world's gone crazy.
Hmm?
Oh.
It is difficult to believe,
but it is snowing here in Tokyo.
Kei, wake up. Hey, you'll catch a cold.
Asuka.
Kei, you, too. Smile!
Oh, it's cold.
Careful. You're starting to act like an old man.
That's what happens when you're old.
You have to make tough choices 'cause
you've got different priorities, you know.
What are you saying?
Where's Hodaka?
You kicked him out?!
I don't believe you.
I told you, the police showed up.
I've got to protect myself, not some stranger.
What? And how are you protecting
yourself by smoking and drinking again?
Not cool. Meow.
See? Even Rain's judging you.
Not only is it uncool; it's so last century.
Don't get near me. I don't want you to rub off on me.
Ah, you're not exactly cool, either.
What's her name... Hina?
If the story about the Weather Maiden is true,
that she's a human sacrifice, then one day she'll...
I know, but then...
what was I supposed to do?
Ah, come on, relax.
It's all bullshit anyway.
Besides, if it were true...
if you could fix this crazy weather with
one human sacrifice, I'd be fine with it.
Everyone would.
A heavy rain and heavy snow advisory has
been issued for Tokyo and its surrounding areas.
Residents are urged to stay
indoors at all times if possible.
You kids, hold up.
It's dangerous to walk around right now unsupervised.
What are you doing out?
These your siblings?
I... Yeah, we're, uh...
We're actually on our way home.
I-I'm a college student, and
these are my younger brothers.
Hmm. I understand, but...
I'm gonna need to see some I.D.
Oh, I, uh, don't have it on me.
We may have located the boy.
We think he might be carrying
a firearm. Proceed with caution.
And you... you in high school?
That's a pretty big backpack you got there.
Can you remove your hood for us, please?
Hina.
Huh?
Run for it!
Hey, wait!
Stop!
Gotcha!
Let go of me!
Will you settle down?!
Get off!
Stop struggling.
Stop it! No!
Hodaka!
No!
Stay where you are!
Hina.
Please!
Clear the area!
Hina, we've got to go.
Let's go take a closer look.
Come on.
It's 280 a night.
Uh...
So, can you pay it? 280.
Oh, y... oh, yes, uh, of course I can.
It's official.
Looks like I'm a full-fledged fugitive now.
That's so cool.
Huh?
That almost gave me a heart attack.
You totally almost got arrested.
Why are you laughing?
'Cause it was funny.
I'm glad you think so.
It's huge.
The bed's huge.
The bathtub's huge.
Whoa.
Hina. Hodaka.
Let's take a bath together.
Take it by yourself!
Fine. Then let's take a boys-only bath together,
okay, Hodaka?
Wait, what?
This is the life.
What's this do?
Huh?
Whoa!
Your turn. Tag.
My turn. Tag.
Whoa, so many.
What do you want?
How about one of each, Sempai?
Are you sure?
Yeah. I got severance pay.
Hina, we're having a huge feast tonight!
I can't wait.
Sorry I took so long.
Uh, it-it's fine.
Bon appétit.
Hodaka, you want to try some of mine?
Mm.
Mmm!
Curry's good.
So are the noodles.
I want to try.
Hey, wait. I don't think those are ready yet.
It tastes better this way... Al dente.
My fortune cookie
Speaks of love again
Future's looking, looking bright...
It's that precious thing that is in your heart
It's the same thing that will soon depart, so...
God, if you really exist,
then I beg you.
This is more than enough.
We don't need anything else.
We'll manage somehow.
See how you like it!
So, please,
don't throw anything more at us,
but don't take anything more from us, either.
I'm begging you.
Please, God, let us stay like this.
Together, forever and ever.
Hina, here.
Happy 18th birthday.
Huh?
It's not much, but, uh, it's something
that I thought would look good on you.
Thanks.
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
Would you like the rain to stop?
Uh, yes. Yeah.
I'm a human sacrifice, they say.
Huh?
Natsumi was the one who told me
about the sunshine girl's fate.
If the Maiden gets sacrificed, then her body disappears,
but after that, the weather goes back to normal.
Come on, now.
You can't believe the stuff in those weird legends.
I mean, people don't disappear.
What are you looking at?
I'm not looking at anything!
I'm looking at you, Hina.
Come on. Why are you crying, Hodaka?
The more I pray for sunshine, the more my body fades away.
But if I end up dying from this...
we'll finally get our summers back.
Take care of Nagi for me.
No!
I won't!
'Cause you're not going anywhere.
We're all gonna live together.
Hodaka.
Hina, let's make a promise to each other
to always be together.
I'll get a job. I'll take care of us.
You don't have to be a sunshine girl anymore.
Your body will go back to normal, and then...
I had a dream.
I was still on the island.
I wanted to leave.
I pedaled as fast as I could.
I was desperate, wanting to go into the light.
When I finally reached it,
I discovered I had reached a dead end.
That's when I decided
that I was gonna go into that light.
And at the edge of it,
I found you.
I had a dream...
the day I met you.
Huh?
You looked like a lost kitten.
But you helped me find a reason to live.
I continued working as the sunshine
girl because it made me happy.
I liked making people smile.
I'm really glad I met you.
So, please, don't cry, Hodaka.
Where am I?
Hodaka.
Oh, no. Hina?
Where are you?!
Hina?!
Hina!
Hodaka, what is it?
Your sister's disappeared!
She's gone.
I was just dreaming...
that she disappeared into the sky.
It can't be.
Open the door.
Open up.
What?
Are you Hodaka Morishima?
You're the subject of a missing persons report.
We also believe that you're in
possession of an illegal firearm.
I need you to come to the station.
Let go of me!
It's okay. I'm not going to hurt you.
No!
We're taking a little trip.
Sempai!
Don't make this any harder than it has to be.
Why are you stopping?
After months of intense rain, the Kanto
region is finally seeing some brilliant sunshine.
The sun's rays are making yesterday's
storms seem like a crazy dream.
In a matter of hours, the weather has done a 180.
By 8:00 a.m., the temperature was 25 degrees Celsius.
Many areas adjacent to the
Arakawa River have remained flooded.
The trains are still not running.
The extent of the damage has yet to be ascertained.
Authorities say it will take at least
a week to restore municipal services,
as long as the weather remains clear.
The sky's clear.
Oh, so sunny.
Oh, it's so bright.
The sky's actually clear.
It's making me all emotional.
Well, it took a while,
but summer has finally arrived.
Hey. Hurry up.
This is Hina's.
She sacrificed.
Hina! What happened to you?!
Hey. Where are you going?
Hina!
Calm down.
I have something I need you to confirm for me.
The girl who disappeared last
night is 15-year-old Hina Amano.
Is that correct?
Do you have any idea where she could be?
She's 15?
Hina said she was older.
Isn't she 18?
She's been lying about her age on
her résumés and job applications.
I understand she needed to make a living,
but the truth is she's in middle school.
Or at least legally she's supposed to be.
You didn't know?
I don't believe it.
I'm the one who's older?
Oh, what a pain.
This whole time.
Hey. Do you know where she is or not?
The weather cleared up
only because Hina sacrificed herself in exchange.
Huh?
No one knows the truth!
No one knows her sacrifice.
What a pain.
Should we get a psychiatrist?
It's clear.
Huh.
Daddy, did you look outside?
Yeah, I did.
I had a dream about Hina.
She's the one who brought the sunshine back.
I know it.
Yeah. I think you might be right.
Excuse me.
Detective, I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Let me go.
I need to go out there and look for Hina.
It's my turn to help her now.
I'll come back as soon as I find her.
What you need to do is step in
here and answer some of my questions.
Understood?
Tell Yasui we're about to begin the interrogation.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
Hey! Get back here!
Stop running!
Come back!
Someone stop him!
Stop! I said stop!
Do not let the boy in the white T-shirt
leave the building.
Stop that kid!
Wait! Stop!
Hey! Come back here!
What the hell?!
That little shit.
Cut him off.
You go that way.
Yes, sir.
No!
Hodaka!
Huh?
Natsumi?
What are you doing?
I'm going to get Hina back.
Huh?
Get on.
Goddamn punk!
While you were at the station, Nagi called.
He said Hina had disappeared and
that the police had arrested you.
Where is he?
At a child service center.
No going back.
We're about to become outlaws.
Breaking the law!
All right, partner, where we headed?
What? Another visitor?
Yeah, and it's another girl.
He sure is popular.
Hello, Nagi.
Ayane, I'm so glad you could make it.
Kana, this is Ayane.
Nice to meet you.
Ayane, this is Kana.
My pleasure.
And that's Officer Sasaki.
She's going to be watching over me all day.
Wow. That's so cool.
It's like you're a celebrity.
How do you do?
Nice to meet you.
Thank you both so much for coming.
I'm sure you must have been surprised by my call.
I was.
When I heard they took you in custody,
my heart almost stopped.
Me, too. Mine's still pounding.
Nagi, if you touch my chest, you can feel it.
Yeah, she's right.
Oh, I do feel it.
Um, excuse me.
Yes?
It's-it's my first time here, so I
don't know my way around, and, uh...
Uh-huh.
Uh, where's the bathroom?
Oh.
Thanks. I owe you one.
You better. I can't believe you.
Calling your ex to help you out with something like this?
Take it.
Turn around.
We still need to swap clothes.
Mr. Keisuke Suga. Good to see you again.
You again?
What do you want?
Looks like the weather's finally
back to the way it should be, huh?
I told you already, I know nothing about that runaway.
Would you mind if we took a look around your office?
What? Hey. It's not a good time.
Oh, it's really flooded, huh? That's too bad.
You're not gonna find him down there.
Yeah, we know.
This is embarrassing, but, uh, the truth is...
Huh? What do you mean, he ran away?
From the police station?
An abandoned building in Yoyogi?
Yeah. It's where she became a sunshine...
Duck!
She said she became connected
with the sky on that building's roof
and that's how she became the sunshine girl.
So, I think that's where I have to go.
Oh, great!
Hey, on the scooter!
Pull over!
Hold on tight.
Hold on!
I think that maybe...
What?
That I'm totally awesome? I know!
I was born for this stuff.
That's it... I'm gonna be a motorcycle
cop and catch anyone who speeds!
They're not gonna hire you after this!
We have a theory about why the kid escaped.
We think he may be trying to
search for the girl who he was with.
You see, he told us a few things that
frankly sounded like science fiction.
He seems to believe that the girl disappeared
in exchange for the good weather returning.
That's ridiculous.
Don't tell me you believe him.
No, of course I don't.
But what I do believe is that he's throwing his life away.
And all of it is just because of some girl.
To be honest with you,
I envy the kid to feel that passionately.
What's the point in sharing that? It doesn't change much.
Huh?
Mr. Suga, are you, uh...
Are you okay?
Why do you ask?
Well, it's just that you, uh...
you're crying.
This is bad.
We're gonna jump it.
Huh?
No. Wait.
Ugh, it's the end of the line.
Hurry. Get out of here.
Go on.
Thank you. Wish me luck.
Hodaka!
Never give up!
Hina.
Hina. Hina, Hina!
Hina?
Hina, are you there?
Hina!
Hey, Hodaka.
It's gonna clear up.
It's for you, but don't tell.
Unless you want to have chowder for dinner again.
Does it hurt? Let me guess... You ran away from home?
Too bad you can't enjoy Tokyo with all this rain.
You're younger than me.
I'll be 18 in approximately a month.
You should treat me with respect.
Hodaka, have you had lunch yet?
You just sit right there.
How do you like living in Tokyo?
Huh? Uh...
I don't feel like I'm suffocating anymore.
Well, that's great, right?
I think I'm in love...
with this job as the sunshine girl.
And so...
thank you, Hodaka.
Hey, hey, look.
There's someone on the tracks!
Who is that?
Stop!
You can't be here!
Come back! It's dangerous!
Hey, hey! What are you doing?
This place is off-limits!
What is he doing?
That's so crazy.
There's someone running up there.
He's gonna get himself arrested.
Do you see that?
Some people are such idiots.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Hina!
I made you do that sunshine girl job,
but in the end, you were the one
who had to deal with the consequences.
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
Would you like the rain to stop?
Mr. Suga?
People are looking for you, Hodaka.
How did you find me?
Look at you.
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
You don't get it. Hina's gone!
And it's my fault.
The sunshine girl job was my idea.
Hodaka, calm down.
That's why I have to help her!
I have to go.
Hey, wait.
Where are you...
I can make it to Heaven if I just go through that.
What?
Have you lost it?
She's somewhere in the sky.
I can get there if I use the stairs!
Hodaka, stop this.
There's no way she's up there.
Snap out of it!
What's gotten into you?
You have to go back to the police station.
If you explain it to them, they'll understand.
You haven't done anything wrong.
You can't keep running away from your
problems. They'll catch up to you. You know this.
We've located the vehicle. We're going in.
Look don't worry.
I'll come with you, okay?
Then we can explain everything together.
Let go of me!
I said let go!
Cut it out!
Let go!
Get off of me!
Get out of my way.
Hodaka, what are you doing?
Let me go to Hina. I have to see her!
Hodaka Morishima!
Drop the gun!
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Everybody, calm down.
This is a misunderstanding.
Don't shoot. I can explain.
Hodaka, come on.
Huh? What are you...?
Don't do this. Put the weapon down.
I don't want to shoot you.
Hodaka.
It's gonna be okay.
Just do what they say.
What's wrong with you guys, anyway?
Give him a break.
He's just a kid. It's...
Why can't you leave me alone?
Why are you standing in my way?
You don't know anything,
because you choose to ignore the truth.
So, please...
All I want is to see her again.
I have to see her!
Stay down!
Let me go!
Get your hands off Hodaka right now.
Get off of him!
Son of a...
Hodaka, go!
What the...
Hold it!
Hodaka!
Nagi?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
This is your fault, Hodaka, so you have to fix it!
Go and bring my sister back!
God...
please, please.
Please!
I beg you!
Is that fish?
In the sky?
Hina!
Hodaka!
Just jump!
Hina, I found you.
Hodaka. Hodaka!
Don't let go of my hands.
Hina!
Hodaka!
Let's go home.
But if I do, the weather,
it-it will go back to...
Let it.
I don't care. You've done enough.
You don't have to be the sunshine girl anymore!
I don't care if I ever see the sun again.
I care about you. I don't care about blue skies.
It'll be okay.
Let the weather stay crazy.
Pray for yourself...
Hina.
Huh?
Hodaka.
The rain started falling again that day,
and since then, it hasn't stopped.
Slowly, it sank Tokyo, where it remains,
submerged in water.
The rain's still falling three years later.
The garden where we've grown
When we look back
It went so fast
Now we must Say goodbye
We're leaving here
After all this...
What's left for me to say?
Excuse me. Hodaka?
Uh, i-is it true that you're moving to Tokyo?
Uh, yeah.
Just ask him already.
It's your last chance.
Mm...
Wait a minute. Could this be...
Um, I just... I...
Well, there's something that
I've always wanted to ask you.
I don't believe it.
My first love confession?
Uh, Hodaka...
Huh?
I...
I heard you were wanted by the police in Tokyo.
Is it true?
Huh?
That same summer,
three years ago,
I ended up getting arrested.
They charged me, and I stood trial.
I had to be on probation until I graduated high school.
The island, my parents' house, school...
They were all the same old places where I spent my life.
But, actually, I was just biding my time,
waiting for graduation to come.
That day...
was the last time I saw Hina.
I have no idea what I'll think.
I haven't seen Tokyo since after it changed.
And I have no idea what I'll say to her.
Here's tomorrow's weather forecast for the Kanto region.
A full day of rain is predicted.
Now if I could just find a job.
Heavy rainfall in the mountain
regions. Lower, in the metropolitan areas,
there is a chance of the rain letting
up periodically throughout the day.
The high will be 59 degrees Fahrenheit, with the
same or slightly hotter temps in surrounding areas.
Oh, right.
Speaking of jobs...
Now for the forecast for the rest of the week.
It looks like rain is expected every day.
The site's still up.
There was still one unanswered request.
It was from two years ago.
Next stop: Takashimadaira.
Takashimadaira.
Oh, it's you. Are you alone?
Where's your sunshine girl?
Oh, she's no longer a sunshine girl.
Actually, it's why I'm here... To tell you that.
Uh, thanks, but I'm okay.
So, how long have you been living here?
Last time, weren't you in a house downtown somewhere?
I had to move.
The entire area is underwater now.
Sorry about that.
Why are you apologizing?
Did you know the entire area of
Tokyo used to be under the sea?
I think, until about 200 years ago.
Back when it was called Edo,
Tokyo was just a bay.
Little by little, humans... As well as
the weather... Changed this landscape.
Look at it now.
It's sort of reverted back,
back to its original self.
What is wrong with you? You've been thinking
about this crap for the last three years?
Hey, don't call it crap.
Stop acting like a kid.
You're about to start college.
You should focus on other things.
Yeah, but the two of us did something.
Did what? You think you caused this?
You really think you're
responsible for changing the world?
That's precisely why I called it crap.
You don't matter in the scheme of things.
Don't flatter yourself.
Oh. Check it out.
It's from my last date with my daughter.
Natsumi and Nagi were the third and fourth wheel, though.
Now, for crying out loud, will you stop
brooding over all this nonsense and just go see her?
I don't know why you haven't already.
I was on probation, so I wasn't supposed
to, and I didn't want to cause her any trouble.
Plus, even if I wanted to, she doesn't have a cell phone.
Also, I'm super nervous.
I don't even know what to say to her.
Rain?
You've gotten so big.
Go on. Get out of here. Can't
you see I got work to do? Beat it.
Go and find her. You know you want to.
Thank you for your time.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
Huh?
Don't sweat the small stuff, big man.
The world is crazy.
It always has been, always will be.
The next stop is Hamamatsucho.
So where do you want to go to lunch?
You're always so incredibly positive.
You really think so?
The flowers should be
in full bloom.
That's what I hear.
Used to be under the sea.
The world's crazy.
Always has been, always will be.
So that means it's no one's fault that it's like this now.
Is this what I should say to her?
I don't know.
No. They're wrong.
That day, I... No, we changed the world.
I made a choice.
I chose her.
I chose this world,
and I choose to live in it!
Hina!
Hodaka!
Hodaka, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
You know what, Hina?
We're gonna be all right.