[PLAYER 1]
He’s incredible.
That’s so odd.
I had no idea there would be
this many players
remaining in the stage.
No way that guy isn’t loaded!
What do you think about
joining up with our party?
Yo. I’m pretty certain
that he’s the guy.
How annoying.
You hear them?
Everyone can’t stop
talking about you, Suigin.
Let them gossip.
The only thing I’m focused on
is restoring my sealed memories.
Speaking of...
Aslan.
What happens to you
once your core is taken?
[ASLAN]
That doesn’t matter.
You won, I lost.
My job as a guardian
has come to an end.
As for how to use the core,
if you follow me to Stage Zero’s
entrance, all will become clear.
Before I go, there’s something
I’ve been meaning to ask you.
Why hasn’t another high-class
player shown up yet?
The only one who appeared
was Dark Tiger.
But besides him, not a single
other major player participated.
Don’t you find
that a little strange?
The mantis stalks the cicada,
unaware the sparrow
is behind it.
This would be the perfect time
for someone to steal my trophy.
Very impressive.
I was wondering
when you’d notice.
[ASLAN]
You’re an observant one.
It’s not that higher-ranking
players aren’t on the stage,
it’s just that
you can’t see them.
For your sake, I’m glad
you didn’t spend
a minute longer defeating me.
Or the one lying helpless
in a pile, would have been you.
Meaning?
Whatever you’re trying to say
doesn’t make very much sense.
Unless there’s some elite player
hiding elsewhere in the level.
[SUIGIN]
If my suspicions prove correct,
there’s only one place
they could be.
They’re in another part of the
level, busy killing each other.
My thoughts exactly.
The ten million class players
are logging off.
One right after another.
Wait.
So the only reason they came
here was to kill each other?
How come they weren’t
interested in Aslan?
Understand their motivation.
The strong have confidence
to spare.
In their minds, Aslan was
an enemy
they could defeat
any time they wanted.
[SUIGIN]
I see.
I bet they were busy
fighting each other
for a shot
at the stage’s boss.
It probably wouldn’t
have mattered who won.
I only know I was lucky to get
the chance to challenge you
before any of them got here.
Or was this a trap set up
by someone, Aslan?
There must be more
to this level.
[ELDER BABOON]
You have no idea!
[PLAYER 2]
Where’d they come from?
[PLAYER 3]
Look at their masks.
[ASLAN]
As you’ve already deduced,
they’re far from lightweights.
Which meant I had to seek
you out
before they had a chance
to fight me.
If any of them had engaged me
in combat before you,
our meeting would have
most likely never transpired.
So, basically, every high-class
player on Stage 18
wants to get a piece of me.
Guess we’ll just have to cross
that bridge
after dealing with the core.
We must hurry!
Travel to Stage Zero!
Then my mission
will be complete.
[ELDER BABOON] Shut
whatever’s left of your mouth!
The hell kind of boss
are you anyway?
Letting this no-name loser
demolish you?
[SUIGIN]
And you are?
[ELDER BABOON] Address me as the
Elder Baboon of Inbei.
Hand over the core if you want
to avoid a gruesome death.
What?
Are you sure?
You certainly sound
like a person to me,
but, if you want
to be a monkey...
Also, where’s the rest of you?
[SILVERBACKS] When you insult
our leader, you insult us all!
Silverbacks unite!
This isn’t good.
Those are the infamous
gang of thugs, the Silverbacks.
[SHOU KEI]
Who’re you calling thugs?
We’re a reputable organization,
and don’t you forget it!
Let’s give ‘em a demonstration
of our three tenets!
Teamwork, strength,
and effectiveness!
[SILVERBACKS]
Yeah!
I can definitely confirm whoever
they are, they’re not good guys.
And I’m going to have to ask you
to remove your foot.
Aslan can’t breathe with you--
[grunts]
[ELDER BABOON] You can have
that ridiculous mask
and wear it for all
I care, brat.
You think just because
you defeated him
you’re suddenly worth a damn?
When I tell you who I am,
you’ll crumble
under the prestige.
You should do yourself a favor
and grow a brain.
Bow while you still can.
You, on the other hand,
honey pie,
I’d recommend distancing
yourself from this newb
as soon as possible.
You should join the Silverbacks.
I could take special care
of every part of you.
My ID is Ryuuman.
Feel free to contact me
the moment you change your mind.
Listen up, skull heads!
Proclaim our motto.
Loud and clear!
These plebs obviously
need educating
on the rules of the game!
[SILVERBACKS]
Yes, sir!
Silverbacks!
You can’t beat us,
so you best log out!
Silverbacks!
Retaliate against society!
Well?
Terrifying, aren’t we?
Now, hand over the core already.
If there’s one thing
I can’t stand,
it’s raving morons like you.
Farin.
Hold Aslan for me.
[grunts]
[FARIN]
That’s weird.
You feel warm and look
even redder than usual.
[ASLAN grunts]
Seems like I've got no choice.
I have to fight you
before I--
[exploding]
A surprise attack?
How cheap can you get?
My bad.
I was just a hair off.
Cheater!
That was way overpowered!
You think?
Tell you what,
since you’re so cute,
how about I show you
an even stronger one?
No way!
You see that coin he’s got!
[PLAYER 4]
A one million Shinryou coin!
[PLAYER 5] Think he’s going to
spend all of it
to enhance his items?
Wow.
Didn’t know you could upgrade
your weapons with money.
[ELDER BABOON]
Hey, you bankrupt bastard!
Bankrupt?
Why’d you say that?
You think you’re fooling anyone
with your t-shirt and jeans?
You’re as broke as they come!
The only reason you beat the
boss was ‘cause you got lucky.
Hope you enjoyed it
while it lasted,
since it’s about to run out.
You’ve never laid eyes
on one of these before?
Consider it an honor!
Only players with assets
of a million
or over can access
these graphs!
You mean the beam of light
represents his assets?
That’s a real warrior!
[ELDER BABOON] Based on its
intimidating length,
you can clearly make out
my total assets
reach beyond
the five million mark!
That’s it?
I don't know if I’d go
bragging about it.
Don’t pretend like
you’ve seen bigger!
How about it, Silverbacks?
Should we show this dumbass
our Asset Graphs?
[SILVBACKS]
Yeah!
Silverbacks!
You can’t beat us,
so you best log out!
Silverbacks!
Retaliate against society!
[PLAYER 6]
Talk about legendary!
[PLAYER 7] They’ve all got a
million plus assets!
[PLAYER 8]
What a super squad!
I never thought they’d have
so many Million Players
in their party!
And they aren’t afraid
to show it off.
Huh?
You think ours are big?
Wait until you see
our leader’s assets!
His exceed well over
a hundred million!
[SUIGIN] If you like doing this
so much, mind if I try?
Oh, by the way, how do you use
an Asset Graph?
This scrub doesn’t even know
how to access the graph?
Do yourself a favor and hand
over the fruit
before you end up
hurting yourself!
Uh, Asset Graph, appear?
[energy shimmering]
What the hell?
[SILVERBACKS]
Elder, sir!
You ever seen anything that big?
[SUIGIN]
So, how’s it measure?
[SILVERBACKS]
It’s stupidly long!
Hundred thousand.
A million.
Ten million.
A hundred.
[PLAYER 9] Anyone still doubt
he’s a Billion Player!
[PLAYER 10] No wonder the dude
was able to completely
destroy the boss
like it was nothing at all!
You certain you want to take
the core from me now?
[FARIN]
All this time,
to think,
he was a Billion Player!
[ELDER BABOON] Stop acting
like this is some damn miracle!
I don’t know how the chief
is going to take this, though.
Not good.
[yelling]
[NISHIKAZE]
All right.
I know we’ve all been
having fun,
but it’s time to get serious.
Evil mirror, come to me.
Amazing.
[SUIGIN, FARIN yelling]
[yelling continues]
[SUIGIN grunting]
[SUIGIN]
Talk about whiplash.
So this is the entrance
to Stage Zero.
We should be able to get in
with no problem,
thanks to the key
we got earlier.
You’re the only one
that can enter the stage.
The rest of us will have to wait
here until you return.
Is that a fact?
Whatever lies just beyond
the gate
was meant for your eyes
and your eyes alone, Suigin.
Got it.
I’ll see you guys
when I get back.
[ASLAN]
You aren’t going alone.
Hold up!
You mean you can fly?
All right.
Here it goes.
Some kind of white void,
without sound.
What the... ?
Weird.
A feeling of nostalgia’s
washing over me.
[ASLAN]
It’s time, Suigin Riku.
Consume my core.
Your repressed memories
of this place will return,
and my mission
will reach its conclusion.
Well,
bottoms up.
What is this?
[laughing]
[YOUNG SUIGIN]
That’s weird.
The tree has a hole in it,
Gramps.
Yes, then the ceremony
is nearly finished.
[YOUNG SUIGIN]
What ceremony?
[crashing]
Damn it.
There goes my status symbol.
[phone ringing]
Who’s calling me
at a time like this?
Yeah?
What is it?
I’m a little busy so whatever
the hell you need
just cut right to the chase.
[RANDENGYOKU]
It’s me, idiot.
Or don’t you recognize my voice?
Chief! Please forgive
my insubordination!
I’ve got all the time
in the world!
How can I help?
[RANDENGYOKU] I just
finished off this small fry.
But maybe you could shed
some light on a mystery.
Seems someone already defeated
the guardian boss.
So then, who’s stolen my
rightful victory away from me?
What am I seeing?
Are these my memories?
[YOUNG SUIGIN] Who's that
girl in there, Gramps?
[YUUKI]
Someone very special.
The same extraordinary power
that flows through both of us
resides within
this child as well.
The poor girl’s parents
were murdered by him.
Despite his efforts, even
he cannot stop the ceremony.
Her powers will be offered
to this tomb.
The process is nearly
complete now.
The only step remaining
is for the tree
to entirely absorb her essence.
And in exchange, her power
will then defend this tomb.
Unfortunately, she must have no
recollection of her former life.
She’ll grow up to be
a normal girl.
Freed from the chaotic fate
she was once doomed to.
[YOUNG SUIGIN]
Hey, she fell down!
Suigin!
Hey.
Do you need some help?
Who are you, boy?
Oh, right.
My name is Suigin.
-Hi, Suigin.
-Hi!
What should I call you?
You have a name, right?
Huh? She fell asleep again.
Grandpa, why is it
that she can’t stay awake?
[YUUKI] Poor girl has lost
her strength from the ceremony.
Will she be okay?
[YUUKI] There’s nothing
to worry about, Suigin.
Actually, it’s your turn next.
My turn?
[YUUKI]
I’m sorry I have to do this.
Understand, I must take
every precaution
to ensure the enemy
doesn’t find you.
[YOUNG SUIGIN]
Huh?
As of now,
you are no longer my grandson.
[screaming]
What... the... Aslan.
Did I really just
see my memories?
[ASLAN]
Correct.
He was convinced
it was the best way
to keep you safe from danger.
He saved your memories
and information about
Stage Zero within that fruit.
Waiting until your return.
Powers residing deep
within this ancient blood,
hear me and heed my bidding.
Using this fruit,
protect the tomb from intruders.
Arise, be born
from a sea of blood.
These are your orders
from the 157th
Grave Guardian
Leader, Yuuki Riku.
Arise, so I may bestow upon you
a form and title.
Aslan.
Remember the following.
Those two precious children
are the single advantage
that we have
in this struggle.
I task you with
an important mission.
Reawaken Suigin’s memories
when the time comes.
[ASLAN]
Now do you see
who you really are?
Yeah.
I’m remembering everything.
[ASLAN]
Excellent.
Then my mission
has reached its conclusion.
Aslan.
[ASLAN]
I have one final gift for you.
[SUIGIN]
A gift?
[ASLAN] The entirety of my
powers, I transfer to you!
-What?
-[yelling]
[fanfare]
Are you seeing how many coins
we just won?
Looks like every player
that survived
the battle
is receiving prize money!
Lucky me!
Glad I showed up!
[PLAYER 11] I never thought
I’d accumulate so many
Shinryou coins!
[PLAYER 12]
Grave Buster is the best!
[FARIN] My Seabay
just got a notification.
Aslan was defeated!
Which means Suigin
should be coming back!
A little early for celebrating.
Finishing off the boss
in a stage too quickly
can sometimes
backfire on you.
[RANDENGYOKU]
What the hell’s going on?
Well, you see.
It turns out we’re kinda no
match for this player, boss.
Really.
I assume you didn’t fail
to mention my assets
or connections with Precious?
I don’t think that would have
changed anything.
[RANDENGYOKU]
Spit it out.
[ELDER BABOON]
He’s not like the others!
This one’s a Billion Player!
What?
Did you say a Billion Player?
Please don’t get emotional
until I can confirm it, boss!
Let me look into it more!
No.
I only want to know
his location.
-Well...
-Hurry it up!
Right!
Uh, his current location...
is on top of the temple
at the transfer entrance
for Stage Zero.
Not for long.
[SILVERBACK 1]
Hey, Elder.
What do you think the boss
has got in mind for him?
I don’t know, but man,
is he pissed off.
[SILVERBACK 2]
Speaking of "piss," BRB.
Like I ought to give a damn
if he’s a Billion Player or not.
Rich, poor, my Artemis Snipe
treats everyone the same way.
-Map Cannon!
-[cannon fires]
How’s it too early to celebrate?
There are certain players
who don’t think highly of those
who defeat a boss
before them.
Case in point:
a powerful energy beam
is headed right for us.
Hey, you see that?
Whatever it is, it’s bright!
[PLAYER 13]
Could it be a UFO?
[PLAYER 14]
Or a shooting star?
[PLAYER 15]
Victory fireworks?
None of the above, I’m afraid.
Looks to me like a super-long
range, wide-area sniper shot.
Based on these readings,
its power--is immeasurable!
[gasping]
We won’t be able to dodge it
in time!
[ELDER BABOON]
What a beautiful sight!
It’s not often
you get to see the boss
use his god-killing shot!
Map Cannon’s his ultimate
special move
that he can only activate
if there’s over a thousand
players on a stage!
The perfect solution for
clearing the board of pests!
[maniacal laughter]
We let our guard down
for a second!
[SUIGIN]
Both of you, stay back.
[energy bursting]
[exploding]
Damn!
This is absolute madness!
No way any of ‘em
are walking away!
[SUIGIN]
Are you all right?
How’d you stop it?
Looks like your wardrobe
got a much-needed upgrade.
[SUIGIN] Thanks, and that’s not
the only thing I left with.
A god-killing move had
zero effect on this dude.
But that’s impossible.
So, what did I miss?
Are you sure you’re not hurt?
That wasn’t some minor attack
you should be able to brush off.
I’m fine, Farin, thanks to this
new equipment of mine.
I’m guessing that stuff’s
your reward for defeating Aslan.
[SUIGIN]
Yep.
The Bloody Armor.
And apparently,
having it fully loaded
also raises my HP.
When it goes into effect,
my health increases
until it’s equal
to the combined total
of every player
on the stage with me.
What’s still pretty
amazing, though?
That attack depleted it
by nearly a fifth.
Don’t get too cocky.
Most of the HP came from the one
who fired the shot.
So glorious,
what beautiful destruction.
Who’s calling me?
Whatever it is, make it snappy.
I’m enjoying my work.
What?
You’re telling me my god-killing
attack had no effect?
An interesting turn of events.
Very interesting.
I’m headed your way right now!
I can’t remember the last time
my heart
was beating this fast
in anticipation...
for a killing-spree!
[PLAYERS shouting, cheering]
What’s your email?
Help me level up please!
Do you wanna be my friend?
[NISHIKAZE] I can't help
but feel sorry for them.
All the players here
were simply pawns.
The entire point of the battle
was to use their numbers
to lower
their collective attack power,
making it far easier to wipe out
all the low-level players
simultaneously.
But anyway,
now the festival’s over,
I think it’s time
you met my superior.
Alright, but first,
I wanna see
Rei with your mirror.
And I want to speak
with her directly.
Whatever.
Lucky for you,
I’m feeling generous.
[shimmering]
It’s you!
Do bear in mind,
withholding certain information
from her may keep her safe.
She doesn’t know about the
earlier battle or Stage Zero.
Suigin?
You really came back for me!
[SUIGIN] Of course!
I’d never forget you!
Rei.
The whole situation
is complicated
but I’ll explain
everything when we meet.
I understand. And I look
forward to hearing all about it
when we see each other again.
Soon!
And that’s a promise!
Just a little while longer!
A few days at most!
Please believe me!
Afterwards, everything
will return to normal!
[REI]
I know.
I believe in you.
Do you remember how I waited
for you exactly like this
on the last day
of Dungeon Century?
I know you’ll save me,
same as before!
I’ll never let anything
like this happen to you again!
I swear that
I’ll protect you, Rei.
And find who’s responsible
for killing your father!
I’ll be waiting
right here for you.
And look!
I’ve got upgraded equipment now.
Rei!
See you soon!
Suigin, wait!
[SILICON]
That’s enough for now.
Stage Zero will officially open
in five days' time.
If all goes as planned,
I’ll hand you over
to Suigin Riku.
That is, if he manages
to stay alive until then.
The Silver Guardian!