Who are you?
Get off him!
Did she hurt you, Suigin?
[SUIGIN]
Yeah, she freakin’ hurt me.
It appears our data was right.
You’re the player they call
Suigin Riku.
That’s one hell of a warm
welcome you got there!
Do you greet everyone
the same way or just me?
Don’t let your guard down,
Suigin.
This girl’s stronger
than she looks.
Yeah.
I have a message.
Even though my boss
clearly instructed me
not to approach you,
I’m not one
for following orders.
I imagine if you’ve
come this far,
you’re dying to see her again.
Evil Mirror, manifest.
A mirror?
Now what?
Who is she?
That’s Rei.
You don’t know how much
I’ve missed you!
[heavy breaths]
Rei!
It’s me!
Suigin!
If you hear me, give me a sign!
Wherever you are,
I’ll rescue you!
Are you close?
Tell me where
they’re keeping you!
If you’re being held
at the Totems' headquarters
I need you to tell me
where it is!
Rei!
Can you hear me?
Behind you!
Rei.
Please.
Don’t worry.
I’ll find you.
I know it’s taken me a while
but I will get you out.
And when I find the person
who put you there,
they’re gonna regret it.
Please just hang on
a little bit longer.
We’re gonna get you back home
no matter what it costs.
[REI] Poor Maki must be worried
after I disappeared so suddenly.
I haven’t contacted
the school, either,
so I definitely fell
behind in my classes.
And then I still have
to sort through
all of my father’s belongings.
None of that matters right now!
First, let’s worry
how to break you out, Rei!
Wait, do you even see me or hear
anything I’m saying?
Please don’t go, Rei!
Come back!
Suigin?
Is that you, Suigin?
I’m right here on the other side
of the mirror, Rei!
We’re on our way to save you!
[NISHIKAZE]
Enough sentimentality.
I hope you enjoyed
your brief reunion.
So you know.
My boss also said you’re quite
the exceptional player,
which I find hard to believe.
It’s time to see
what you’re made of.
[SUIGIN]
Bring her back!
Suigin!
[SUIGIN]
I’m okay, Farin.
I assume this girl’s Nishikaze.
She’s the one the guy
on the phone told me to find.
What a relief I found you.
Tell me what your group
is after!
Why won’t you let Rei go?
You’re a quick study, Suigin.
Yes.
I am Nishikaze.
I apologize for attacking you
but I needed to test
the strength of your Divine
Tomb Item
[PLAYER 1]
Hey, guys?
Where’d the boss go?
[PLAYER 2]
Not a clue.
[PLAYER 3] Has anyone
ever fought so overpowered?
[PLAYER 4]
Stay sharp.
We may not get far
with what we have equipped.
Yeah. I got it.
[whirring]
[exploding]
[yelling]
[ASLAN]
None of your blood...
is what I seek!
[PLAYER 2] We don't
stand any chance against him!
Retreat!
[PLAYER 3]
Save yourselves!
How pathetic.
I have no interest
in weaklings like you.
Time to thin the herds.
At least I can promise a show.
With my summoning attack.
Your deaths will
be spectacular.
Slash kai!
Demons in the sea of blood,
reveal yourselves!
Uh, guys.
You see what I’m seeing?
Those shapes.
There’s something alive
in the blood,
swimming right beneath our feet!
[PLAYER 5]
Don’t just stand there!
[PLAYER 6]
Move into formation D!
I saw this in a horror
movie before!
And how did it end?
They were so busy looking down
they didn’t notice
the real threat was coming
from above them!
But that was a movie.
[PLAYERS yelling fearfully]
What the hell is it?
A blood-sucking freak!
These are my faithful servants.
The Mosquito Legion.
They’ll bleed you dry.
So if you want to live,
I suggest you flee.
Anyone unfortunate enough
to get pierced by my minions,
will transform into
a droplet of blood.
Spheres of energy I absorb
and then convert into bone.
Now go.
Drain them for everything
they’re worth,
so they may merge with me!
Together, we must protect
the final tomb!
[PLAYER 7]
Make a run for it!
The damn festival was a trap!
[ASLAN]
Pity.
Despite such a generous harvest,
the blood I seek continues
to elude me.
Where is it?
Someone’s on that pillar.
Their wave, it’s so familiar.
[NISHIKAZE]
Then it is true.
I’ve seen it for myself.
That’s Yuuki Riku’s wave.
My boss sends a message.
Since I’ve confirmed
your Buster Item,
proceed to Stage Zero
as soon as possible.
I’d love to but I heard
it was supposed to open
five days from now.
A rumor, nothing more.
You can enter
if you have the key.
I can feel it waiting up ahead.
The blood of the one
I’ve long been searching for.
I’ve found you,
Suigin Riku.
[grunts]
What’s he talking about?
And what the hell is this?
[ASLAN]
We finally meet.
You don’t realize how long
I’ve waited for this moment.
Wait?
For me?
I was supposed to follow you.
To fulfill the mission.
Those were the orders given
and I intend to complete them.
[SUIGIN]
You lost me.
[ASLAN]
First off, this is yours.
The key is built to activate
in response to your blood alone.
Use it to enter
Stage Zero, Chosen One.
Once you arrive, your long
dormant memories of the Stage
will finally be reawakened.
But in order for that to happen,
you must undergo
one final challenge.
[SUIGIN]
What the--?
[explosion]
[FARIN]
He looks completely different!
Are we fighting
a separate boss or something?
[NISHIKAZE] Allow me to present
Aslan’s ultimate form.
Bloody Buddha.
[PLAYER 8]
Up there!
Those players are goners!
Look it!
There’s something inside
the boss’s stomach!
Suigin Riku, tell me
if you recognize this.
I, uh, would have to guess
that’s the boss’s weak point?
In other words, you remove
the core, you defeat Aslan.
You are correct.
Pretty sharp
for a one-eyed girl.
But there’s more to it
than that.
Before his death, Yuuki Riku
ordered part of
Suigin’s memories
be contained and sealed
in the talisman
you see before you.
Of course, that stupid
weird geezer did.
Just take my identity and stick
it inside of some blood freak!
I’m sure that it also holds
your origins.
If it simply contained
your memories
I think Yuuki would have
told you before he passed.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, maybe he did,
but without them,
I’ve been having a hard time
remembering things.
Sorry, Aslan.
But it looks like I’m going to
have to ask for those back.
They sorta belong to me.
[FARIN]
Be careful.
Raven Scarf, I activate you.
Upon summoning this Tomb Item,
seven different gems appear,
and every one possesses
a unique ability.
They randomly shuffle
when activated.
I keep forgetting
which color does what.
So please, choose me a winner.
Huh?
This one.
The time has come.
Show me the equipment’s power.
If it was worth him
becoming a Tomb Item!
[PLAYER 9] You see that?
It was some kind of explosion!
[PLAYER 10] A player must be
fighting the boss!
[PLAYER 11] Do they have
a death wish or something?
Can you tell
if Suigin’s all right?
It’s up to fate to decide
whether he’ll live or perish.
You’re more difficult to kill
than the rest.
Unleash armed skill.
The Raven Blade.
I can endlessly regenerate
any damage you deal my body.
What good do you think
a sword will serve you?
Sorry to tell you, but this
is no ordinary sword.
[yelling]
In addition to its
razor-sharpness,
the Raven Blade allows me
to triple my speed.
Opponents don’t even
have time to react.
[yelling]
[splashing]
He’s going to use the blood
droplets to regenerate.
Then, before he does,
Aslan, I want my memories!
[energy bursting, crackling]
[energy buzzing]
Not good.
This armor’s tougher
than I thought.
The blade isn’t enough
to pierce it.
If I’m going to win this,
I gotta come up with a plan B.
And quick.
[evil laughter]
[ASLAN] You immobilized me
by damaging my limbs
so I couldn’t attack,
then attempted to finish me off
with a sword stab to the head.
You must not understand,
Suigin Riku.
As long as
I’m in the ocean of blood,
I remain invincible!
Stab, slash, hack away
as much as you wish!
I’ll heal and only become
stronger!
Interesting.
Not only does it
help you regenerate,
you can use players' blood
to gain limbs
and increase your body size.
Wait, does that mean that
Aslan is literally made
from our blood, sweat and tears?
Yes.
[ASLAN]
What’s the matter, Suigin?
Too petrified to make
the first move?
Guess it’s up to me!
Seriously?
And he can shoot orbs of plasma?
[grunting]
[SUIGIN]
Not only did his size increase,
apparently, so did his power.
There’s no comparison.
He’s way stronger than I am.
Can I even win against him?
No.
I don’t stand a chance!
[attack yelling]
[evil laughter]
Your precious sword
is out of commission!
[panting]
Think, Suigin.
At this point in the match
it’s too hard
to damage him directly.
I can hold on a while longer
if he doesn’t have any other
tricks up his sleeve.
What the--?
Is that some kind of halo?
[ASLAN]
Think of it as a crown.
An emblem of those
selected by me.
This symbol is the mark
of my Snow Lotus.
The flower will gradually wilt
over the course
of the next 80 seconds.
During that time, I will gain
control of all the blood
flowing through your veins.
Once the final petal has fallen,
the curse is completed.
The blood will burst forth
from your body and you will die.
Burst out of my body?
[ASLAN]
However,
despite the odds of success,
there’s one chance
to release you from the curse.
If you’re able to steal my core
in the next 80 seconds,
it’ll be lifted.
If you win, you’ll survive.
But if you lose,
your body will shatter,
the same as your sword.
-[shattering]
-[grunting]
In that case...
No problem.
That’s plenty of time for me.
Eighty seconds is all I need
to cut you down to size, Aslan.
Why’s that smoke pouring
out of the sword?
A defensive move?
Whatever its purpose,
the cloud is engulfing
the players and the Stage.
It’s becoming obvious
the sword’s true power
isn’t for slashing.
Hey, what’s up
with the smokescreen?
Is it just me or do you feel
like you’re catching
a second wind, too?
So you’re a badass?
Then stop wasting
everyone’s time
and show us
your ultimate move, already.
[ASLAN]
I’ll oblige,
if you’re that eager to die.
What’s he thinking?
Doesn’t he realize if he loses,
the game permanently
removes his assets?
Seems confident.
Maybe he’s figured out
something we haven’t.
Like maybe some way to defeat
the boss and clear this stage!
Very well.
Since you desire
to embrace death, I summon.
Bloody Hell Crimson Dragon!
Upwards the serpent
rises to the heavens,
bringing about a storm
that will seal your doom!
The way that dragon’s flying,
swirling to the sky
in a spiral pattern.
Basically, operating
the same as a tornado.
Which means the closer
I get to the center,
the calmer the storm!
[attack yelling]
-[energy bursting]
-[yelling]
It separated itself from Aslan!
[ASLAN]
Valiant, but no use!
He’s not gonna be able
to do this alone!
Whoever he is,
we gotta help him out!
[PLAYERS]
Let’s go! Go!
[ASLAN] Pack of scavenging
grave robbers.
[PLAYERS yelling]
That ought to keep him
from moving around!
[PLAYERS]
Let’s get him!
[ASLAN]
Strike to your hearts’ content,
the result will be the same.
Or did you forget
I can regenerate?
Not that I need to bother.
Now that the dragon’s completely
immersed with the sky,
you’re in for a treat.
Experience the wrath
of my final attack, weaklings.
Crimson Dragon Blast!
-[PLAYERS yelling]
-[exploding]
[crashing]
[ASLAN]
Yet,
you still refuse to die.
It’s of no consequence.
You’ve disappointed me,
Suigin Riku.
At this rate, how do you expect
to become a Tomb Guardian?
You were too strong.
There’s no way I could’ve
defended against your attack.
[scoffs]
You freely admit
to your failure?
Just telling you the truth.
In a head-to-head fight
between the two of us,
you’d always emerge victorious.
Your move, Aslan.
[ASLAN]
While you still have time
before your 80 seconds expires,
I can’t stand to see the sight
of a defeated
would-be Tomb
Guardian any longer!
Suigin!
The battle is over.
Three, two, one...
Zero.
[ASLAN yelling]
What have you done?
Suigin Riku!
What did you do to me?
[energy bursting]
[exploding]
[grunting]
[splashing]
[NISHIKAZE]
You lost. It’s finished, Aslan.
[ASLAN]
My body.
Why is it refusing
to regenerate?
Hey, I told you I wasn’t lying.
I knew I couldn’t beat you
head-on
after what you did to my blade.
But this weapon came from my
gramp's Raven Scarf.
So,
there had to be more to it
than meets the eye.
I didn’t realize what until
after you shattered it.
Wait.
Are you saying the smoke
it released
somehow gave you the upper hand?
That vapor isn’t smoke.
It's highly concentrated oxygen
that boosted Suigin
and the other players' stamina.
I figured out if the source
of Aslan’s power is blood,
then his body must be composed
almost entirely out of iron.
I can’t say it wasn’t risky
injecting his body
full of oxygen
since it would increase
his power for a short while.
But eventually, it’d react with
the iron and make him rust.
Lucky for me,
when the blade broke,
it released even more
into the environment.
The sword itself must be
composed of oxygen
if it spread so quickly
and engulfed the battlefield.
Right.
My gramp’s Divine Tomb Weapon,
the Raven Blade.
I don’t believe you.
To reach the point
where I couldn’t regenerate,
every blood cell in me
would need to be affected.
A valid point.
Even with the hits Suigin
did manage to land on Aslan,
it still wouldn’t
have been enough.
I mean what other explanation
is there?
[ASLAN]
There is none!
It’s impossible!
Why?
[ASLAN] If his sword was
truly responsible,
I would have started rusting
as soon as I was damaged!
And that clearly
wasn’t the case.
You’re keeping something
from me.
Some additional ability used
while I was distracted!
Nothing too remarkable,
I’m afraid.
As you said, I could only apply
minimal damage
with my sword strikes.
Most of the cuts
were superficial, anyway.
You could repeatedly
heal yourself
from any slash I inflicted.
And only your blood splatter
would turn to rust.
Then I remembered
something important.
You mentioned you regenerate
using the blood
you harvest from players.
So I created an oxygen field.
That way all the droplets would
be filled with the element.
The more you kept regenerating
to increase your strength,
the weaker
you actually became.
That doesn’t explain
why my body dissolved.
I should have still retained
my form.
Remember using
your plasma attack?
That’s what gave me the idea.
If I could convince you to use
a more powerful move,
then the whole field
would be covered
in an electromagnetic wave,
resulting in the oxygen
undergoing a chemical reaction.
Into ozone.
The blood inside of you
soon began breaking apart,
and your body followed suit.
So all that ozone?
It resulted in a second
chemical reaction.
Which depleted your blood of
the necessary oxygen.
You're talking about
oxygen poisoning.
Yep. That's the reason
your cells broke apart
and became only liquid.
It's gonna prove difficult for
you to regenerate for a while.
In the meantime,
could you give me a lesson
on how to use this thing?
Journey to State Zero and you'll
receive your answer.
[PLAYER 12]
Whoever he is, he's awesome!
[PLAYER 13] He defeated Aslan
single-handedly!
[PLAYER 14] There's no way
he's not a billion player.
[ELDER BABOON]
Sure looks like we showed up
late to the party, huh, fellas?
You wouldn't believe us
if we told you.
You guys see what kind of masks
they're wearing?
I don't believe this!
Silverback!
The Silver Guardian!