[TEMUJIN]
Suigin.
I suggest you give me
your full attention.
[SUIGIN] So you’re
the one who kidnapped Rei Riku.
Who the hell is this?
If you’ve hurt her,
I’m talking to a dead man!
Oh, spare me
the heroics, would you?
If something were to
happen to her,
how would you stop it?
That’s the very reason
we’re keeping
an eye on her.
Ms. Riku
required our protection.
Though she keeps
insisting on calling herself
a hostage,
for some reason.
Where is she?
[TEMUJIN chuckles]
You really want to save her,
don’t you?
Then listen closely.
There’s a festival
being held on
Stage 18
of Grave Buster.
You should attend.
It’s a celebration
for players
who’ve completed
every level in the game.
And a provision
for conquering
Stage 0 when
the time comes.
[TEMUJIN]
If you want to beat that level,
which I know you do,
you’ll need to go
to the festival.
Once there,
you’ll have to locate a player
named Nishikaze.
Nishikaze?
And how am I
supposed to find a player
I’ve never met before?
Oh, you’ll know
when the time comes.
Give me
a straight answer!
What’s this
got to do with
getting Rei back?
[SUIGIN]
Say something!
[phone hangs up]
Damn.
I have no idea
what I’m supposed to do.
[sighs softly]
[ANNOUNCER]
He’s the mysterious lone-wolf
who never
says a word!
The no-charge-meister
that showed up
outta nowhere,
defeating enemies with
the lowest grade equipment.
Gwin!
♪
[CROWD cheering]
[CROWD chanting]
Gwin! Gwin! Gwin!
[REI]
So cool!
♪
[SUIGIN] Maybe I was cool
playing in Dungeon Century.
I’m utterly
useless, now.
[WANCHOI meows]
[grunts]
[laughs]
Hey, Wanchoi!
Feels like forever
since I last saw you.
[meows]
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
[WANCHOI meowing]
[yawns]
♪
What’re you
meowing at so early?
[meows]
Ah. Looks like some
kind of gathering.
Guess there must be
a celebrity on campus today.
[STUDENTS murmuring]
Has anyone told you
how cute you are?
You should totally join
our cosplay club!
So what school
do you go to?
I’ve never seen you
around before.
Please, date me!
Man, that poor girl.
Swarmed over
by a bunch of creeps
who won’t
leave her alone.
[STUDENT 1] What social
media platforms are you on?
Can I get
your e-mail address?
I’ll take anything!
I don’t have one,
all right?
[STUDENT 2] What?
You gotta be kidding!
You’re not online?
Do you even
have a social life?
[gasps]
[FARIN] What are you
waiting for, Suigin?
Are you just
gonna stare all day
or come down here
and save me?
[ALL]
Huh?
[STUDENT 1]
Who’s she talking to?
[STUDENT 2]
It’s that nerd, Suigin!
[STUDENT 3]
Protect her honor!
[gasps]
[STUDENT 1]
Don’t get any ideas, pervert!
[STUDENT 3]
Talk about annoying!
[STUDENT 2]
Total loser!
I should've
stayed in bed today!
-What’s the heck’s going on?
-[STUDENT 1] Bastard!
Who’s that girl and
how’s she know me?
[meows]
There’s no way.
But,
what if it is her?
Farin.
[CROWD chatting]
[SUIGIN]
Okay, it is her.
But that
doesn’t explain
why she’s
at my school.
I’m not prepared
to deal with this.
Plus, why’d she
bring a suitcase?
Makes me wonder.
Is she planning on
staying at the dorm?
Why am I being so awkward?
Come on, Suigin.
Talk to her.
[FARIN]
What are you thinking about?
What?
Oh, nothing.
Just, uh, wondering
how you found me,
I guess.
I work part-time
as an instructor
for the beginner’s
course, remember?
So, I was able to
get some
information on you.
Obviously, you aren’t
happy to see me.
So I’ll stop wasting
your time and go.
Huh?
No, I’m glad you’re here
and I get to
see you in person!
[SUIGIN]
Aw, man.
The worst part
is every word
I just said was true.
But now she’s here
and I have zero idea
what to say to her.
[bell dings]
[SUIGIN]
Come to think of it,
compared to reality,
I’m a different
person in game.
♪
[SUIGIN]
Whenever I’m playing,
I feel more confident
and always know
what to say.
But real life’s
a different story.
If I was invisible,
would anyone notice
I was missing?
Sometimes it’s like
I don’t even exist.
Then you have
someone like Farin.
Exceptional in the game
and real life.
Check her out.
Talk about
my dream girl!
I think she’s new.
A transfer student?
[SUIGIN]
At least I got it over with
and she knows
how lame I really am.
Wonder what she’s
gonna say next.
-[WAITRESS] Excuse me, sir.
-[grunts]
You’ve been
here an hour
and only ordered water.
Perhaps it’s time
you committed to
ordering food.
You do realize
we have other students
waiting to be seated?
Sometime
today’d be nice.
More like
anytime this week.
I’m starving.
Over there.
Isn’t that
the poor kid
hogging that table
and not ordering?
[yelps]
Give me that menu!
[FARIN] May I get one
to look at, as well?
Sure, here you go.
Uh, so Farin,
what are you
in the mood to eat?
It all looks
so delicious.
One avocado salad,
minestrone soup,
the escargot,
fried chicken wings,
a Teriyaki steak,
squid tempura.
[SUIGIN]
She’s bite size.
How can
she scarf down
more food
than she weighs?
Her metabolism must be
a miracle of science.
No! More importantly,
who's gonna
pay for this
mountain of food?
The only money
in my wallet right now
is too embarrassing
to mention.
You’re not
just poor, Suigin.
You are the King
of being poor!
All that money
in the game,
and it’s absolutely
useless in real life.
If only I could pay
for things with it!
[FARIN]
Chilled ham pizza.
Alfredo pasta. Oh!
-[FARIN] And the tiramisu!
-Should we dine and dash?
No! I won’t start a life of
crime over lunch!
[FARIN]
Ice cream and cheesecake.
[beeping]
♪
[WAITRESS]
Okay, sir.
If you would choose
your form of payment.
Uh...
[WAITRESS]
Before patrons get their food,
they must pay in advance.
No problem at all!
[SUIGIN]
“No problem?”
I just agreed to eat here
and I have no cash!
Sorry!
If that’s not
enough food,
we can order more.
-You want to?
-More food?
Oh, I couldn’t!
You see, I’m actually
on a strict diet!
[SUIGIN]
My wallet’s the one starving!
I’m about to go
bankrupt for one meal.
[GUY 1]
What’s a pool boy
doing at a posh
restaurant like this?
You weren’t
expecting this young lady
to foot the bill
were you, Suigin?
Actually,
weren’t you going after Rei
the other day?
Looks like something
changed your mind.
Maybe her dad dying?
Do I have to
spell it out?
Trash doesn’t belong here.
So why don’t you
give us your table?
-[FARIN] Apologize.
-What?
I won’t allow you to talk
to my leader that way.
[GUY 1]
Your leader?
Suigin’s in charge of
our party in Grave Buster!
And worth over
a hundred million.
So, he’s rich?
[chuckles nervously]
Uh, only when
I’m in the game.
[laughs hysterically]
-[ALL laugh]
-Now, that's hilarious!
The little girl’s
a comedic genius!
[GUY 1] Hate to
break it to you, honey,
but this guy’s a liar.
Look, whatever he
told you is crap.
-He wants to swindle you.
-It’s not a lie!
Oh, yeah?
Prove it.
Go right ahead
and pay your bill
using all those
Shinryou coins
you claim you have.
Huh? You can use Shinryou coins
in the game
and real life?
Sure.
We accept
that currency
as well as
several other forms
of e-money
at this establishment.
But, how?
[WAITRESS] I’ll just need to
scan your Seabay, sir.
[GUY 1] Yeah, yeah.
Hurry up and get it over with.
I wanna prove this
bastard’s a con artist
once and for all.
♪
[beeping]
[chuckles]
Thank you, sir,
for your payment.
It went through?
You sure your scanner
isn’t broken?
[SUIGIN]
I don’t believe it!
I can literally
pull money out of the game
and use it?
This has never happened.
There are
so many zeroes,
the PDT can’t display
the full amount.
[ALL]
We’re not worthy!
[laughs]
I told you so.
Suigin’s a billion player!
[gasps]
♪
-A female student.
-[STUDENTS murmuring]
Inside the guys’ dorms.
-Adorable.
-Damn his luck!
How’d he manage to score
such a cutie patootie?
-Be still my heart!
-Objection!
This goes
against the handbook!
What’s up, Suigin?
Rei’s missing and you
got a new girlfriend?
Didn’t waste any time!
Shut up!
I’m going to save her
whatever the cost!
Doesn’t change the fact
you’re a two-timer!
You heartless bastard!
[sighs]
♪
This Rei people
keep mentioning,
were you and her dating?
We weren’t.
She wasn’t my girlfriend.
Then, what did you mean
when you said
you were going
to save her?
It’s kind of a long story.
And part of me thinks
I shouldn’t even tell you
since sharing it could
put you in harm’s way.
I can tell you
this much, though.
Rei is being held somewhere
inside of Grave Buster.
I meant what I said
back there on the stairs.
I’m going to find her
and bring her home
no matter what!
That’s the entire reason
I was so grateful
you joined my party, Farin.
-[FARIN] Enough, Suigin.
-Huh?
Like you said,
we’re on the same team!
Which means
we help one another.
Now, let’s go save
your not-girlfriend!
[chuckles softly]
Logging into
Grave Buster.
[CROWD chatting]
I know this place,
but why are there
so many people around here?
[gasps]
Quit spacing!
The festival’s starting!
Festival?
[FARIN]
Just try and keep up.
[SUIGIN]
Um, sure!
♪
[SUIGIN]
Hey, Farin.
Was this
always a stage?
Sure doesn’t
look like one.
[FARIN]
After the enemies are defeated
and the stage is cleared,
it belongs
to the players.
Then they’re able to
fix up buildings
and level them up.
Open shops
and restaurants,
or use them
any way they see fit.
In short,
it becomes a spot
for the players
to commune.
This festival.
That guy on the phone.
He said something about
this the other day.
Everyone in the world
knows about it.
You see,
the festival was
created to prepare for
conquering Stage 0.
[FARIN] Defeating the stage
is a huge event
and there’s no limit
on a player’s level to join in,
meaning anyone
can participate.
So, you’re going to see
a mix out there.
You’ve got your newbies
who wanna test their luck
and also
several elite players.
In addition, there’ll be
a good number of people
who are just
curious sightseers.
Wanting to catch a glimpse
of what the mythical
Stage 0 looks like.
[SUIGIN]
Stage 0.
[TEMUJIN]
If you wanna beat that level,
which I know you do,
you’ll need to go
to the festival.
Once there,
you’ll have to locate
a player
named Nishikaze.
Nishikaze?
And how am I supposed to
find a player
I’ve never met before?
[TEMUJIN] Oh, you’ll know
when the time comes.
So, in other words,
the Totems are
gonna be close by.
I don’t know what your
relationship is with that group,
but I really hope
I don’t need to remind you
how dangerous getting
near them can be.
I don’t know my role
in this, either.
The only thing that
I can do is
keep following the clues.
And hope they
lead me to wherever
Rei is being
held captive.
I’m completely
in the dark,
unsure how powerful
their organization is,
or even where they are.
[FARIN] Why haven’t you
looked up information
on the Totems?
Good question.
I know!
Since she’s a guide
for this world,
she may be able
to tell us something
we don’t know
about their group!
Master!
It’s been ages!
How can I serve you?
Tell me
what you desire.
Well, I guess my
first impression of you
wasn’t too far off.
You got
the wrong idea, Farin!
I swear!
Twin Star’s a powerful
Tomb Beast!
I hope you’re
not gonna demand
too much outta me, master.
I’m still
pretty exhausted.
After what you
put me through last time.
You really love
going out of your way
to embarrass me,
don’t you?
So, what are you going to
command me to do?
[FARIN]
You perv!
This is not
the way it sounds!
We’re friends!
That’s it!
Only friends?
But I’ve grown
so fond of
calling you master.
For real,
she's a guide
the system gave me
to navigate the game!
Save your breath!
And to think
I respected you!
[CROWD chatting]
Take a seat!
-I’ll be right with you!
-[FARIN grunting]
Your stomach’s
a bottomless pit
in the game, as well.
Players are
psychologically connected
to the virtual world, so yeah.
I love eating equally
as much in this reality.
Also, your lack of
sensitivity earlier
depleted my
HP considerably.
[grunts]
[scoffs] Wouldn’t let me talk
then you clocked me.
What do you think
that did to my health?
Hey, waiter!
I wanna order!
I’m starving here!
-Hmm?
-[SUIGIN slurping]
Wait.
All you want is two bowls
of instant ramen?
Look at all
the delicious food
you can choose from.
[grunts]
You have no idea how vital
the existence of
instant ramen is to
poor students.
It’s our source of power!
What do you
mean by poor?
Actually, I don’t know
how much you have
but it’s gotta be
somewhere in the range of...
[SUIGIN coughing]
Chew your food.
[PLAYER 1]
You hear the news?
Another Billion
player appeared.
Be serious!
Everyone knows there’s only
five in the entire world.
[PLAYER 1]
You’re behind the times, pal.
Word on the street is
there’s a sixth
wandering around the game.
You know, I did hear about
some new player
taking on both Precious
and the Totems.
[PLAYER 1] Yeah!
And a number of
higher-ranking
players were also defeated!
-[PLAYER 2] Crazy!
-[grunts]
Wait, is that...
[PLAYER 3]
It is! Unbelievable!
[FARIN]
Huh? Am I missing something?
[SUIGIN] Sounds like
they figured it out.
What’s my next
course of action?
Stand up, admit it,
get the whole affair
over with?
-[PLAYERS gasp]
-[PLAYER 3] Let’s see!
[PLAYER 4]
Wait up!
Those guys are
sprinting over
in our direction
like they just saw
the world’s
greatest player or something!
[SUIGIN] I hate being
the center of attention.
The life style never
suited my temperament.
[SUIGIN]
But it can’t be helped.
Come on.
It’s a natural reaction
once people discover
I’m the latest
Billion Player.
I’m gonna be the first!
[PLAYER 4] But I noticed
before any of you!
[SUIGIN] Can’t keep it
a secret any longer.
Whatever it is
they’re excited about,
they’re working
themselves into a frenzy!
Farin...
You should
hear this from me
before someone else tells--
[PLAYER 3]
Hey, move!
You’re in our way,
dumbass!
[PLAYER 4]
Quit blocking the exit!
What do you
want to tell me?
There’s absolutely
nothing between
me and Twin Star!
Did I punch you
in the head too hard?
[PLAYER 5]
Look! Over there!
Sounds like something’s
happening outside!
♪
[SUIGIN] Is that
a flock of flying penguins?
♪
[gasps]
I guess they’re
dropping prizes
in honor of the festival.
Pretty fancy.
They look like rings.
What do they do, though?
They’re transfer rings
to Stage 18.
The final quest
before you can
proceed onward
to Stage 0.
Apparently,
it’s exclusive,
which means
first come, first serve.
Then I hope
I see some of you guys
over on the other side!
So then this
was the reason
behind the festivities.
[FARIN]
I hope the admins
know what they’re doing.
Sure are
a lot of participants
for such a special event.
The God Grave Tech Company.
I wonder what
they’re really up to.
If the administrators
are transferring
that many players at once,
it’s probably not
just a festival.
You game?
Could be a trap.
Duh.
If you’re going,
then I’ll be
right beside you.
All right.
Then here goes nothing.
[BASHIDA]
Everything is proceeding
according to plan,
Dark Tiger.
All of the players
are arriving
via the transfer rings
we provided them.
[DARK TIGER]
Indeed.
But like
every stage before,
there are still guards
and a boss
to contend with.
I overheard they’re a force
to be reckoned with.
[DARK TIGER]
How fortuitous
we have a shield of pawns.
♪
After this level
is cleared,
the entrance to
Stage 0 should open up.
[SUIGIN]
Hmm.
At first glance,
it doesn’t jump out at me
as being dangerous.
More importantly,
I need to figure out
how I'm going to
locate Nishikaze
among all these players.
[gasps]
It’s inconceivable this stage
doesn’t have any guards!
You guys should
go on ahead.
I’ll just hang back and keep
an eye on things here.
[yells]
What’s wrong?
[PLAYER 6 gasps]
[PLAYER 7]
Here they come!
[PLAYER 8] I didn’t expect
the place to be crawling
with this many tomb
beast guards!
How come there are
so many enemies?
I don’t know.
But if the players
don’t work together,
no one will
survive this battle.
And it’s only
just begun.
♪
What an interesting
assortment of items.
[SUIGIN] I take it that’s
the portal to Stage 0.
But who are those two?
If I had to guess,
I’d say the one on the throne
is Precious’s leader,
Dark Tiger.
[FARIN]
I didn’t think he’d be here!
[SUIGIN]
Dark Tiger.
I keep running into
Billion Players.
[DARK TIGER]
It won’t do us any good
to have our
meat shields wiped out
by the first wave.
Speed things up.
Whatever you wish
shall be done, Dark Tiger.
It’s time we
kick off the festivities
in proper fashion!
[BASHIDA]
Steel activate!
Stallion Saber!
[BASHIDA]
Centurion Buster!
Whoa. What the hell’s he doing?
♪
They defeated
all the monsters
in a single blow.
Is that Precious’s power?
It’s insane!
[DARK TIGER]
Bashida.
It’s time.
Yes.
Now that
the weaker elements
have been dispatched,
he should awaken
and the main event
can finally begin.
There’s no more
monsters to fight!
[PLAYER 9] Which means only
the boss is left!
And there’s enough of us
to clear the stage!
No sweat!
What, the?
That isn't good!
[PLAYER 10 screams]
Why’s it that color?
Uh, this isn’t
a pool of red water.
It’s blood!
-[PLAYER 11] Oh, god!
-[PLAYER 12] Watch out!
[PLAYER 13]
Something’s forming out of it!
[PLAYER 14]
What the heck is that?
I’m getting the feeling
he’s not on our side.
♪
[FARIN]
Yeah.
Stage 18’s boss.
Aslan!
[ASLAN]
Where is it?
The blood I yearn
to gorge upon.
[NISHIKAZE]
So jealous.
Looks like a lot of fun.
Think I’ll join them.
[KITAKAZE]
You know our orders.
Boss told us to wait here,
Nishikaze.
Don’t do anything
you weren’t instructed.
I don’t need
you to remind me.
But you know how much
I detest waiting.
I’ll go introduce myself.
[ALL scream]
Maximum power
and bring him down!
Magic mirror, magic mirror,
grant my wish.
Tell me where the final
Tomb Guardian is.
[PLAYER 15] Look!
The HP bar is replenishing!
[PLAYER 16]
But he’s missing an arm!
How can
it be filling up?
That’s unreal.
This boss can use
the pool of blood
to regenerate
any damage he receives.
Huh?
[NISHIKAZE]
So you’re Suigin Riku?
Ah!
[SUIGIN screams]
♪
[SUIGIN]
The Silver Guardian!