[RUDRA roars]
I now remember all
12 parts of the spell.
Rudra!
[roaring]
With these words,
I know once more who I
am and what I must do!
I am a Madou Tool,
and with my powers,
I will seal you away forever.
[RAIKOU, YASUSUKE]
Let's go!
--[SEIMEI] Yeah!
--[KINTOKI] Right!
[RAIKOU grunts]
[RUDRA roars]
[YASUSUKE grunts]
[KINTOKI]
Okay!
We'll have that giant monster
dismembered in no time at all!
[roaring]
What's it doing?
[screaming]
Huh?!
[KINTOKI]
Huh!
[CROWD screaming]
[RAIKOU]
It's consuming their souls!
[YASUSUKE] It's gonna suck up
every soul in the capital!
[RUDRA roars]
Is this for real?
How do we stop that thing?
[SEIMEI] There has to be
some way to defeat it.
[RUDRA'S LEFT ARM roars]
[RUDRA'S RIGHT ARM roars]
[YASUSUKE]
Dammit!
Until we stop it, it's only
going to kill more people.
So first, we need to isolate
it from the population.
[RUDRA roars]
What happened? The roar
destroyed my spell!
[SEIMEI, KINTOKI scream]
[KINTOKI screaming]
[SEIMEI screaming]
[KINTOKI]
You saved us!
[KAGUYA] I take it that you've
noticed as well, Seimei?
That Rudra is not the
same as it was before.
[SEIMEI]
Yeah.
This power of Rudra's--it's not
your basic regeneration.
[KAGUYA]
Precisely.
This is not the same Rudra
I sealed away in the past.
The one before us
is vastly different.
It was already unnaturally
powerful when I first fought it,
but this beast is stronger
than I ever imagined.
Wha...?
Then it probably--
No, I'm sure of it.
It absorbed Douman
into its very being
and it's using him as a gateway
to connect to Makai.
That's why new Horrors
keep sprouting up
to fill in the damage we create.
Is it even possible to
take down that monster?
Don't you worry. There
is most certainly a way.
All we have to do is separate
Douman's body from Rudra's.
Our first move is to
slice that creepy,
shattered face of his
from the main body.
And so long as a new face
doesn't grow back,
well, then we've got it
right where we want it.
Right, I see.
We cut out the power source
and it's back to basics.
The same Rudra Kaguya sealed.
Exactly.
It should be smooth sailing
from that point onward.
We'll only need the Makai
Knights to properly weaken it.
Once that has been done,
Seimei must then use
me to seal Rudra away.
Just use you, huh? You make
it sound so effortless.
Well, you are the only one
who can do it after all,
and it should come naturally.
You are the descendant of the
Abe family, so it is your duty.
It's just as
Grandfather told me.
The light will show me the way.
Now, Seimei! Invoke the
barrier spell again!
[SEIMEI]
Here goes!
[DOUMAN roars]
[RUDRA roars]
[YASUSUKE] You can leave
the rest of this to us.
All right, then.
Listen, guys. It's a pretty
straightforward plan.
The first thing to deal with is
removing Douman from the body.
Slice him out like
a deep-rooted cyst.
[RAIKOU]
You got it.
[YASUSUKE]
I think we can handle that.
[RAIKOU]
Kintoki!
[KINTOKI]
Right!
[KINTOKI] Honorable Sirs--
to the field of battle!
[YASUSUKE] Try to keep up
with me, Raikou.
[RAIKOU] I was gonna
tell you the same thing.
But, y'know--I'm proud
to fight by your side.
[YASUSUKE] It's damn
embarrassing how earnest
you are. But I like
that about you.
[RAIKOU]
Let's go!
[YASUSUKE grunts]
[RAIKOU yeling]
Man, they're so strong!
Well done. Just keep it up, now!
[RAIKOU]
You don't disappoint, Yasusuke!
[YASUSUKE] Heh. Don't you
have a head to be severing?
[RAIKOU]
I'm on it!
[RAIKOU yells]
[RAIKOU yelling]
[DOUMAN groans]
He did it!
[RAIKOU]
Kaguya! Seimei! Now!
[DOUMAN growls]
But how...?
[RUDRA'S ARMS roaring]
Oh, crap, that wasn't enough!
There's no end to it!
I don't understand this,
it should've worked!
Douman's the conduit!
You're right, and it
will still work.
The complication, though.
We must cut away Douman's
darkness from Rudra.
Not just his physical form.
But how? For all we know,
Douman's completely
assimilated with Rudra.
How are we supposed
to isolate that?
It'll be nearly impossible
to find and cut out.
[YASUSUKE]
No point in thinking about it!
Just let the swords handle it.
We'll eventually cut out
Douman's darkness!
[RAIKOU]
I'm fine with that plan!
[RAIKOU growls]
[RAIKOU groaning]
[RAIKOU screaming]
[YASUSUKE]
What's wrong, Raikou?
[YASUSUKE grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[INARI A]
No!
It appears that cracks
have formed in the barrier,
and time is seeping in!
The limit of their armor...
...is fast approaching!
[INARI A]
If this continues....
[INARI B, C] ...the lost
soul beast will roar!
[YASUSUKE]
What the hell is happening?
[GORUBA] I'm afraid the armor
has reached its limit.
At this rate, it will
consume you.
Release before it's too late!
[YASUSUKE screams]
[RAIKOU groaning]
Wha... What's happening?
Is this its true form?
Raikou, no!
[GORUBA]
Stop!
You must release yourself
from the armor!
[YASUSUKE]
Yeah, like I have a choice here.
I can't... not when I still
have to save that idiot.
[YASUSUKE grunts]
[YASUSUKE groans]
Are you all right?
Sorry, Raikou.
[KINTOKI]
Raikou!
[DOUMAN]
Where am I?
I can't remember.
[baby crying]
[DOUMAN groans, yells]
Michinaga.
[RAIKOU]
I understand your pain, Douman.
Your hateful light
doesn't belong here.
How can you still so foolishly
cling to purity and
honesty, Raikou?
The Minamoto family threw
you away like garbage.
How can you still believe
in the power of the light?
Why haven't you lost your spark?
Can't you see this world
is governed by darkness?
Salvation is nothing more
than a cruel trick.
A lie to strengthen
the eternal despair!
You're wrong!
[MASK 23A]
Join us.
Embrace the darkness
and join us.
Become the darkness,
Raiko. Such a fate...
[MASK 23AA] ...is only fit for
one who's been tossed away.
[MASK 23B]
Give in and fall from the light.
[MASKS]
Into darkness.
Darkness. Darkness.
Darkness. Darkness. Darkness.
Dark... ness...
No.
[ZARUBA] Raikou! The lost soul
beast is trying to claim you!
[gasps]
[ALL grunting]
[RAIKOU growling]
[SEIMEI gasps]
Look, it's Raikou! He's safe!
Huh?
[RAIKOU roars]
[SEIMEI] That's the armor
from when we found him!
[KINTOKI]
Seimei. I'll release the armor.
Please allow me to be
the one to free him.
I am his attendant,
so it's only right.
Why're you stopping me?
Just calm down and observe.
Remember, there is a reason why
Raikou was chosen by the armor.
[RAIKOU groaning]
There you go!
Not like this is the first time
you've fought past that line.
[RAIKOU]
I am the Golden Knight.
This blade, this power--
it's meant for salvation,
to save those souls lost
and suffering in darkness.
The capital...
everyone within it...
And the one who stands
before me now...
Douman! I will even
save your soul!
That is what it means to
carry the title of Garo!
Perfectly put!
Exactly what I expect
from my Makai Knight!
[RAIKOU]
Seimei!
I need to cut away
Douman's darkness, right?
That's what'll put
an end to all of this?
You got it, Raikou!
Here's a little help!
And he has taken flight!
Now revel within your own light!
[INARI C]
And fully blossom.
[INARIS]
Flowers of oath!
[RUDRA roars]
Go, Raikou!
[RAIKOU yells]
[MASK 23A chuckles]
[RAIKOU]
Uh!
[MASK 23A] So you've chosen
to cast away the light
and join the darkness.
It was always your fate
to become one with us.
[MASK 23AA] Nobody's heart
is without darkness.
[MASK 23B] Now embrace
and accept it within you.
[MASK 23C]
The darkness.
[MASKS]
Sorry to tell you,
but your evil darkness could
never extinguish this light.
Because it doesn't
just belong to me.
This light... it's the
hope of everyone
who continues to
fight the darkness.
The blade that protects
those without fangs.
[RAIKOU]
There you are!
[DOUMAN] It's impossible
for your putrid light
to ever reach me.
What?
There is no hope for we
minions of darkness.
We spit in the face of
your pathetic salvation!
Don't give me that!
I saw the tears that you shed!
Some part of you yearned for
the light at that moment!
[DOUMAN]
You're mistaken.
Those were tears
of blood I wept,
in gratitude for the moment
I tossed away the light
and accepted the darkness!
[RAIKOU]
Don't you get it?!
Even after being fully
assimilated into Rudra,
you still have a will!
That's all the proof you need
that there's still
light inside you!
That's an utter
load of nonsense!
I have become
darkness personified.
And I've done so by
becoming one with Rudra!
[RAIKOU]
Douman!
In the name of Garo,
I will cleanse you and
cut down your darkness!
Such hateful light.
Such hateful light!
[RAIKOU yells]
[groaning]
[RAIKOU]
Seimei! Kaguya!
It's time.
I now summon my
power of sealing.
Grandfather, I shall
cast our family spell.
[KAGUYA]
Sadness is not hopeless abandon.
[RUDRA roars]
[KAGUYA]
Anger is not hatred.
Affection is not fixation.
[yells]
[RAIKOU grunting]
Let's go!
[YASUSUKE]
Yeah!
[KAGUYA]
Disagreement is not hostility.
Gallantry is not arrogance.
Life is not an illusion.
What is she saying, Seimei?
She's reciting the 12
mantras of purity.
To cut away the darkness.
The essence of
Abe family spells.
[KAGUYA]
Death is not oblivion.
Talent is not wiliness.
Ardent longing is
not greediness.
[RAIKOU, YASUSUKE grunting]
[KAGUYA] Resistance is
not panicked struggle.
Adoration is not jealousy.
[YASUSUKE, RAIKOU groan]
[RUDRA roars]
[RAIKOU yelling]
[YASUSUKE yelling]
[RAIKOU yells]
[RUDRA roars]
[KAGUYA]
And of course,
light and darkness will
always exist side by side.
[RUDRA roars]
[RUDRA roaring]
Separation is not tragedy.
I will always be
watching over you all.
Kaguya.
I will witness every step
in the path of man.
G'bye.
C'mon. Let's go back
to our capital.
[KINTOKI]
Home sweet home.
Too bad there's not much
of it left, though.
[RAIKOU]
Just watch.
The capital will return
to what it was in no time.
[KINTOKI]
Ya really think so?
We should at least believe that.
Uh! Douman!
[KINTOKI gasps]
We're not done yet, Raikou!
Fight me now!
Just stop, Douman.
You don't even have the strength
to continue fighting.
[DOUMAN] Darkness is
the only thing I need!
My power is endless as long
as there is darkness!
[RAIKOU]
You're wrong.
If you were nothing
more than darkness,
you would have fully merged
and disappeared within Rudra.
[DOUMAN]
You are a damn fool!
You know absolutely
nothing about me!
There's light and
darkness in everyone!
And I believe that
includes you as well.
You only see the light and
you dare say that to me?
No! I also have--
[DOUMAN] These words
are getting us nowhere!
[RAIKOU]
No, stop!
[DOUMAN yells]
Douman. I only wanted to...
[gasping]
You can rest now.
I'll shoulder the weight
of your darkness for you.
It's okay.
I feel so warm.
Is this what the light
actually feels like?
[SEIMEI]
Farewell now, Ashiya Douman.
[INARI A]
Hidden Power.
Hidden Feelings.
The path chosen
is a path of white.