[YORINOBU] This mansion is truly
astonishing, to say the least.
My daughter will soon
become an imperial bride.
Making me the father-in-law
of the Emperor.
The extravagance of my home
should match my stature.
Do tread lightly, sir.
Don't let the Vice-Minister
overhear you.
He's bound to only
grow more resentful.
I'm not sure I know how
to be any more modest.
[MICHINAGA chuckles]
[HARUAKI]
I must speak with you.
Haruaki, how unexpected.
[MICHINAGA] And what
brings you here, Haruaki?
I was seized by the feeling
of an alarming presence.
Alarming enough to drag
this withered body of mine
to speak with you.
What are you trying to say?
That I've been targeted
by a sinister force?
[HARUAKI]
Correct.
What's wrong with the dog?
[DOG whines]
[ALL gasp]
Is that?
There is no misreading
the augury.
Without a doubt, somebody has
placed a curse on Michinaga.
You would have suffered the
same terrible fate as this dog
if you had stood in
its place instead.
[HORRORS howling]
Seimei, hurry! Remove the seal!
[screaming]
[RAIKOU]
Seimei!
It's far too early for
that much screaming.
A dream?
Hey, Seimei, are you
eating before you leave?
What kind of sweets
do you have?
Persimmons.
[SEIMEI squeals]
[RAIKOU]
Seimei.
Will you please do something
about the seal on my armor?
Why should I?
Did you see a Horror?
[RAIKOU sighs]
[RAIKOU]
I'm trying to cut ties with you!
Such cold and hurtful words.
When I found you,
you didn't even know
what a Makai Knight was.
I taught you everything you know
and now you just
wanna cast me aside.
All you men.
You're all the same.
You take everything an
older woman has to offer,
and then you step over her
body on the way out the door.
Hey, no. C'mon, you know I
didn't mean it like that at all!
[KINTOKI]
Crocodile tears.
[SEIMEI]
Just a little more...
...and I might really cry!
[sighs]
[RAIKOU] I should've
known better from you.
Lies. Lies. Lies!
That's all I get.
You've singlehandedly
ruined my trust in women.
Please, don't act like
you really know that many.
Here. Have some sweet persimmon.
--[RAIKOU] Get off me!
--[SEIMEI laughing]
Wait, where are you going?
[RAIKOU]
I need to cool off some.
[gasps]
We're here for
ownmyou user Seimei.
She stands under suspicion
of unlawful cursing activity.
Uhh... Hold on--
[YASUSUKE]
Find her!
[SEIMEI] Hey! Get out of here!
I'm getting dressed!
Hey, take your hands off of me!
Touching costs money!
What's happening, Raikou?
I don't know.
Perhaps she finally did
something bad enough
to get arrested.
[YASUSUKE] That's exactly
what we're going to find out.
Careful with her,
she's a natural liar.
Hey! Raikou!
You're just going to abandon me?
You ungrateful brat!
[IZUMI]
I take it you're familiar
with the name
Fujiwara no Michinaga?
It seems as though someone has
placed curses on his family.
They found a number of cursed
items inside his mansion.
Michinaga's daughter will
soon become an imperial bride.
Undoubtedly, there are many
who would be envious of the one
who controls the Light Palace.
It is a known fact, unlawful
onmyou users lack all morality.
They regularly create
and sell curses for profit.
That kind of activity
must be stopped.
Sir.
Strict new measures have
already been put into motion.
Now, any casting curses
will be punished.
Therefore, all Onmyou
users will be rounded up.
[IZUMI]
And there you have it.
If one is an Onmiogi that is
not a part of the Onmyouryo,
they're to be targeted and
apprehended for inspection.
So, then. That's it,
Ms. Shikibu?
[IZUMI]
Oh, please, call me Izumi.
That's why Seimei was arrested?
Because she's a Makai Alchemist,
and not an Onmyou affiliated
with the Light Palace?
Really? I'm surprised
you don't know.
She was born to
an Onmyouji family.
[RAIKOU]
Huh?
Princess of the Abe clan.
She surpasses most Onmyou users.
Even Professor Yasunori.
With that lineage, I have
no clue why she chose
to be a Makai Alchemist.
But I'm sure she'll be
released rather quickly.
Handshake?
[grunts]
Information fee.
[RAIKOU]
The Light Palace.
One of the most holy
places in the country.
Only nobles and government
officials are allowed to enter.
Right.
Horrors can't even come close
to stepping inside its walls.
Seimei was born there.
That's the most surprising
thing I've heard.
[OLD MAN] A mere curse would
never frighten Michinaga.
I can say with certainty,
you are his real goal.
I'm glad to hear it.
It would be my pleasure
to show him no light exists
that can pierce true darkness.
[OFFICER A]
You found him?
[OFFICER B]
Yes, sir, he's right here!
[OLD MAN] I'm interested to see
the Light Palace drop its guard
for you to pass through
its vaunted gates.
[OFFICER A]
Surround him!
Your name is Ashiya
Douman, correct?
You found me.
[KINTOU]
Hurry up!
In the cells, you damn
dirty alchemists.
Move! Walk faster!
This is wrong.
Lord Michinaga is an
official of the people.
He should not be allowed to
build his own prison like this.
He may be powerful, but he can't
simply detain anyone he wants.
Our master is the head
of the Fujiwara family.
Don't speak out against
his decisions, my brother.
So these are the scum who curse
people for financial gain.
[SEIMEI grumbles]
[YORINOBU]
Uh.
I remember that woman.
[MICHINAGA] She was actually
born of high status.
Such a waste.
Help me, please!
[OFFICER B]
Hey! Get back in line!
[SEIMEI] Please, believe me.
This is some kind of mistake!
I'm sorry to tell you,
but the Madou Ring is sealed,
along with your armor.
Seimei is the only one
who can remove the seal.
But there must be
something you can do.
It seems that someone
has placed a curse
on the Minister of the Left.
[INARI A] Pity it has
nothing to do with us.
It what? And how do you figure?
Because it's a curse
placed by a human,
which rarely amounts
to more than trickery.
They believe a curse
has been placed on them.
And so they feel sick and
become prone to disease.
It's nothing more than a
self-fulfilling prophecy,
a subconscious deception
that manifests as truth.
It is simply not the place
of a Makai Knight
to interfere with
the world of man.
But you can rest assured
I will call for you
if another troublesome
Horror emerges.
[RAIKOU] Wait, but I'm
meant to protect the people!
All of them! It's my duty
as a Makai Knight!
You take care, Raikou.
Until we meet again.
So you know your
Golden Armor, Garo?
It harnesses the power of Makai.
If you're not careful and
wear the armor for too long,
it will devour you, and
transform you into a beast.
A lost soul beast to be exact.
I had almost reached that
point when Seimei found me.
I had lost my sanity
from wearing the armor.
Now don't exaggerate, Raikou.
You weren't even close
to going berserk.
Your form may have changed,
but your soul remained intact.
That's why Seimei helped you.
By sealing away the armor,
and making me dependent on her.
Well maybe she did
it to protect you.
No, that's not her.
We'd better go. Come on.
Go where, to save Seimei?
[RAIKOU] Of course. I need her
in case a Horror appears.
[MEN chanting]
[door opens]
[footsteps]
They caught him?
I've been led to understand
that you are the
new Ashiya Douman.
Then you have adequate council.
That is the name
my teacher gave me.
I wouldn't consider
being named successor
to the previous Douman as
something to be proud of.
A variety of curses
were found in my home.
You were responsible
for them, were you not?
Not that I recall.
You were.
You're the only one
who could've made them.
Do not deny it.
You're radiating guilt.
And I'm certain you
were commissioned
by the Vice-Minister, Korichika.
He may be Michinaga's nephew,
but that changes nothing.
It's quite evident
he hungers for power.
He had you create those curses
to advance his position.
And if I were to confess
to such an egregious act.
Korichika and his
entire bloodline
would be mercilessly executed.
The prior Ashiya Douman.
A powerful Onmiyoji.
In skill my equal, who chose
to embrace the darkness
rather than the light.
Throughout the land,
people feared him
as he gained mastery
over curses.
There is no mistake here.
The one who carries his
name must be the culprit.
[DOUMAN chuckles]
And yet, I'm not the only
one you've dragged in.
You captured every single
Onmiyo user in the capital.
And you did it just to find me.
Well done, I'm impressed.
What's happening? What is
that horrendous stench?
[OFFICER C]
Is there a fire in there?
[OFFICER D]
Ugh, it stinks.
[PRISONER A]
Hey. What is that smell?
[PRISONER B]
It's unbearable!
You! Keep it down
in there, shut up!
[YASUSUKE] Where the hell
is this smoke coming from?
[yells]
Raikou! Took long enough.
[RAIKOU]
This is just pathetic.
A Makai Knight executing
a prison break.
[KINTOKI] I'm the one in
the pathetic situation here!
Ugh! This cow crap stinks!
You will not pass me!
Back in your cells,
unlawful alchemists!
That's not happening.
I busted the cell door.
And it stinks in there.
I take it you're a warrior?
Anyone who defies Michinaga must
face me, Minamoto no Yorinobu!
Yorinobu?
[SEIMEI]
Please save me, my lord!
This maniac just attacked
the jail out of nowhere!
I what?
I'm scared.
The way he was grabbing at me,
I know he's after my body.
You have to protect me!
Have no fear.
How can you say that?
C'mon, Seimei!
Your face oozes indecency.
[YORINOBU]
You won't escape!
Seimei!
[SEIMEI]
Douman. Michinaga.
What a delightful surprise.
I was unaware
you'd been captured.
Kiyome, just what are you
doing interfering here?
I have told you not to call me
by that name, Abe no Haruaki.
How nice,
a reunion between grandfather
and granddaughter.
Please, there's no reason
to fight on such an occasion.
Well, I'm curious to know
what you're planning
to do with Ashiya Douman.
This matter is no
concern of yours.
This is the man who bears
the guilt of cursing me.
He has even gone so far
as to implicate the one
who commissioned the curses.
He inherited the name
of Ashiya Douman.
He would never do
something so stupid.
Well, it's nice
of you to say so.
[SEIMEI]
Douman!
[RAIKOU yelps]
What happened?
Did you know Douman
would be here?
[chuckling]
The darkness.
These items will create
the gate of darkness
I've searched so long for!
Oh, is that so?
Listen. These cursed items here?
They were commissioned by
none other than Michinaga.
That is a blatant lie!
Those curses were placed against
the Minister of the Left!
With my own eyes
I have witnessed
a dog die in his stead!
Michinaga had scattered poison
about the garden ahead of time.
He wanted people to believe
he had been cursed.
It was all a ploy to pin
it on the Vice-Minister
and insure the execution
of him and his family.
He did it for political gain.
These worthless
scraps are untouched,
entirely devoid of any magic.
However, they have become soaked
to their core with negativity.
His ambition to destroy
his political rivals.
The cruelty to stop at
nothing for that goal.
And the relentless hunger
that drives him to rule
and stand over this world.
That core of darkness
will open this gate.
Open what?
A passage that connects
Makai to this world.
They are the dark gates that
Horrors use to pass through
to our realm.
And I am the one who
opens the gates for them.
I see.
You intentionally allowed
yourself to be captured
for this purpose.
Douman!
Hear my voice, Horrors!
Follow this acrimonious path
and feast on the humans!
[PRISONERS gasp]
[groaning]
[HORRORS laughing]
They're corrupted.
That is the very
nature of Horrors.
Consuming and corrupting
the living with darkness.
Right.
The arrogance of the Onmyouji.
It has led you
to naïvely believe
the Light Palace is protected.
But the gate to darkness
can be opened anywhere!
Don't be so foolish, Raikou.
We're outnumbered.
We need to catch Douman.
The people need protection!
[KINTOKI yelling]
[KINTOKI]
Come on, Seimei!
Release the seal on
Raikou's armor already.
[SEIMEI]
Huh.
Oh no, Seimei!
Illuminate Raikou!
The Golden Armor? But how?
[KINTOKI gasps]
[HORROR howling]
Hey, Raikou,
you do realize there will
never be an end to Horrors
no matter what you do.
[RAIKOU]
I am a Makai Knight.
[RAIKOU] I will destroy
every Horror I find.
[RAIKOU]
If that burdens you,
then you can release me
from this accursed seal!
[SEIMEI gasps]
[roaring]
[yelling]
Yeah!
[grunts]
[HARUAKI] You may have
destroyed the prison today,
but I believe this is
something we can overlook.
[SEIMEI]
Sure.
And I'll overlook the fact
that your boss faked
this curse business,
even though you rounded up
a horde of innocent people,
including yours truly.
Oh, and here's this.
I would rather you hold onto it.
I was unable to do
anything for you
when you left the house
at such a young age.
Giving you that is
the least I can do.
So please, keep it.
You may have chosen to take
the path of a Makai Alchemist,
but do not ever forget
that you hail from
the Abe family of
Onmiyoji, Kiyome.
So, Kiyome, huh?
Never call me by that name.
Why did you leave
the Abe family?
Well, it was rather
stifling there.
Hmph. Another lie.
You certainly do have
a long way to go
before you understand women.
[RAIKOU]
Uh! Quit it, stupid!
And release me, already!
Remove the seal
you've got on me!
No way.
Why would I ever let go of the
wonderful thing we've got going?
--[RAIKOU yelps]
--[SEIMEI chuckles]
[SHINBOCHI grunting]
Stay away from me.
Back, Yorimitsu!
I've come to check
on you, Father.
How are you?
Fine, Yorinobu.
No reason to worry.
Just a dream.
Tell me, Father.
The Golden Armor.
It should be passed down the
Minamoto family, should it not?
[SHINBOCHI]
Hm?
[YORINOBU] So how is it that a
man like that could possess it?
How, Father?
[INARI A]
Once upon a time,
there was a bamboo harvester
called Tahkaytori no Okina.
No, no, I'm sorry,
that's not this story.