[JIHOU]
Maka hanya haramita shingyo.
Shiki zoku zekuu.
[JIHOU coughs]
Who's there?
Are you here to rob me?
Those clothes.
Do what you must,
but I warn you,
there's nothing fancy
to steal in this shrine.
Buddha. I've no
regrets in this life.
I look forward to finally
standing by your side.
[DOUMAN]
No regrets?
Is that a joke?
Jihou. Tell us again
what you wished for?
My wish was to...
to right the wrongs of
the world with his words.
[DOUMAN]
That's right.
Unfortunately, no one
in the Light Palace
gave a damn about Buddha.
Instead, they chose to listen
to someone else's words.
[JIHOU]
The Onmyouji. You're right.
False prophets.
If only they never existed!
[DOUMAN]
Yes,
and now it's far too late
to do anything about it.
Your life's flame
is about to expire.
Just lie back and tell yourself
you have no regrets
as you wait for Nirvana
to wash over you.
You're right! I can't die!
If I could only punish
those Onmyouji
for straying
from the Buddha!
[DOUMAN]
Yes, but what if you could?
I'd sell my soul to do it!
I'd... become the devil himself
if that was the price!
That's what I like to hear.
[HORROR A roars]
[JIHOU gasping]
[JIHOU whimpering]
[gasps]
That dog! It's so tiny!
Oh, yeah.
Those guys're imported
from some distant land.
Area's full of aristocrats who
can afford stuff like that.
Imported pets. Talk
about an extravagance.
[SEIMEI]
The whole compound is!
Why, just up ahead is the
lower ranking Onmyouji's
opulent palace.
The only thing
these folks have more of
than wealth is arrogance.
[RAIKOU] Well, I actually think
it's quite nice-looking.
Good looks don't
excuse the fact
it's paid for by taxes
taken from us commoners.
[PAPER MASK A]
Hey! Stop right there!
[PAPER MASK B]
This palace is off-limits to--
Switch!
[PAPER MASK B]
Ah! Lord Michinaga?
[PAPER MASKS]
I'm sorry we were rude, sir!
Oh, it's fine. It's totally
not a big deal, you guys.
So casual.
Sounds more like
Masamune than Michinaga.
Come, servants. Let's go inside.
Wait. What about
that magic fence?!
[SEIMEI grunts]
[BOTH]
Whoa...
[PAPER MASK C]
My lord Yasunori.
There's not a single soul
left in the mansion.
It's odd, because
as you can see,
there are signs that people were
here until late last night.
But then it's like they
just vanished somehow.
Do you think they were all
stolen by an evil spirit?
What a foolish thought.
We're not so weak as to be
taken away by a mere spirit!
[SEIMEI]
You can say that again.
I hear the mighty
Onmyouji are invincible
and afraid of no man or spirit.
And they can eat
delicious sweets all day
and not gain a pound!
[YASUNORI]
Kiyome.
[PAPER MASK C] Who are you?
How did you get in here?!
[SEIMEI]
What...? Looks like...
Oh, these doll
clothes are so cute!
They look cursed.
And on top of being exactly like
the clothes normal people wear,
they're covered in
mysterious goo.
And when there's a
mystery to solve,
I can't resist getting
to the bottom of it!
[YASUNORI]
Kiyome! No, wait.
I'd forgotten you'd taken on
the name, "Seimei" now.
How many years have passed
since I saw you as the wild,
little Kiyome?
I don't know, Grandfather,
but it's been a while.
Grandfather?
The Onmyou Professor,
Kamo no Yasunori.
You heard of him at Haruaki's
house, her other grandpa.
[gasps]
[RAIKOU] Oh, this is her
maternal grandfather.
Professor Yasunori is father
to Seimei's mother,
Princess Katsurako.
I hear you're a Makai Alchemist,
serving a crafty,
old spell-user.
Your mother would cry if she
were alive to learn that.
I do hope your Makai magic
isn't behind all of
our people vanishing.
What? I resent that accusation!
Whatever mess you're in,
you can clean up on your own.
[YASUNORI growls]
[SEIMEI]
I'm going.
My friends and I have
no more business here.
Foolish girl.
[RAIKOU groans]
[PAPER MASK A]
And stay out!
[PAPER MASK B]
Common scum like you
will never step foot
in this mansion again!
[BOTH yelp]
Sorry!
My scummy, little
commoner hand slipped.
[PAPER MASK B]
Dumb girl!
You know what's dumb?
Those masks.
[PAPER MASKS groan]
[SEIMEI]
Hmph!
I'm not sure how dependable
Seimei's gonna be for us
on this case, but
there is one thing
we know for certain about it...
What happened here is
the work of a Horror.
No doubt.
I hate to be so blunt, Lord
Michinaga, but I'd be remiss
if I didn't mention there
are many aristocrats
who simply don't like you.
We believe one or
more of those nobles
is behind the mass kidnapping.
Quite possibly.
[KINTOU]
Beginning tonight,
I'll lead a police detachment
on guard duty of the mansion.
[YASUNORI]
Lord Michinaga.
There's something else
I need to ask you.
This morning, I found my
unworthy granddaughter
investigating the scene
of the disappearances.
Is it wise for us to let someone
as unpredictable as her
travel freely in this city?
[MICHINAGA]
She may be your blood,
but she's not your matter.
Yes, but...!
Lord Michinaga has his reasons
for letting Seimei
move about unmolested.
He does not have to say anymore.
Of course. I apologize, my lord.
I over-stepped my boundaries.
[RAIKOU] Well, there it is.
Just like we expected.
[KINTOKI]
Yeah, good call.
I don't recommend making
a habit of rifling through
Seimei's drawers
to grab a seal,
but in this case,
it was worth the risk!
[HORROR B grunting]
--[RAIKOU] Let's go!
--[KINTOKI] I'm on it!
[PAPER MASK C] Everything
is secure, so far, sir.
I don't want even a fly
landing on these grounds.
If you see anyone suspicious,
you cut them down!
Is that...?
[RAIKOU grunting]
Come on.
[HORROR B roars]
[RAIKOU grunts]
Uh!
[RAIKOU]
Uh...
What's happening?
Ah!
[KINTOKI]
Raikou! Raikou!
Hey, you!
Where did you send
my friend, Raikou?!
Give him back!
[BOTH grunting]
[RAIKOU]
Uh!
What the hell?!
Can you hear me, Raikou?!
Where are you?!
[RAIKOU]
Kintoki?
What! Did that Horror
turn you into a giant?
Or... maybe... he shrank me?
He did! That horror shrank me!
[KINTOKI grunting]
Don't land on me!
[RAIKOU]
Ah! Kintoki! You jerk!
Hold on.
Sounds like Raikou
screaming from far away.
Great! What's that
Horror doing now?
If you're in trouble,
yell again!
[RAIKOU screams]
[RAIKOU]
This current... it's too strong.
It's going to pull
me under, Kintoki--
[RAIKOU gasps]
Well, somehow I
survived those rapids,
so all I gotta do is float
my way back to Seimei.
And now that I've
got my bearings,
I'm enjoying how different
everything looks
when you're this little.
[RAIKOU screaming]
Turtles look like monsters!
All right.
I guess it's gonna be
survival of the fittest!
[KINTOKI] One minute he
was fighting the Horror,
the next he was gone.
I searched all night and
couldn't find a single clue.
I warned you two.
I said if something
involves Onmyouji,
don't go anywhere near it.
Right?
--[SHIKI DOLL A] Shiki, shiki!
--Hey!
[SEIMEI growls]
Not like it matters.
Guess I'm helping
you find Raikou.
Oh, thank you, Seimei!
[SHIKI DOLL A]
Shiki!
[SEIMEI]
Now what is it?
[SHIKI DOLL A]
Shiki, shiki, shiki, shiki.
[KINTOKI] What?! This
little man is Raikou?
Um. Raikou is that really you?
[RAIKOU]
Yes!
Well, it's hard
to tell, for sure.
You're shrunk,
and riding a turtle!
Oh, him?
We met down on the water.
At first we didn't like each
other and fought sword to sword,
or I should say, sword to fang,
but by the end, we became
pretty good friends!
[KINTOKI] Soft-shelled
turtles don't have fangs.
Hey! Ouch! Stop it!
Oh, wow.
You look so much cuter
when you're this small!
You're gonna rip off my arm!
I'm not joking!
[SEIMEI]
Oh!
Your weapon shrunk
right along with you!
It's all so cute!
I just want to take you
and your little sword
and put you on a shelf--
Stop it!
He may be small, but
Raikou's still a man!
Poor Raikou!
As your friend, I swear to you!
I won't rest until I've found
a way to remove this spell
and make you normal sized again!
It's fine. There's no
need to cry, Kintoki.
Yeah.
[laughs]
You're cute, too.
[KINTOKI]
Interesting.
I've never heard of a
Horror with that power.
[screams]
[RAIKOU]
Kintoki!
[KINTOKI whimpers]
Those are my only clothes.
In that size, at least.
Right. Don't worry,
I'll take care of it.
I can sew it back
together myself!
[SEIMEI]
I get it now.
[RAIKOU]
Uh?
It all makes sense.
Same size as him.
Hold on. Those are
a doll's clothes!
We're not putting
Raikou in those.
No, no.
They're from a woman who's
been shrunk, like he was!
I see!
All those Onmyouji
from the mansion
who seemingly vanished
had actually been shrunk!
[SEIMEI] Precisely. They were
shrunk by the Horror.
And then what, he just
carries them around?
That'd be weird.
The clothes were
covered in slime.
Have any thoughts on what
its origins may be?
[KINTOKI]
I don't know.
I believe that slime was
drool from the Horror.
It's Drool?
Then that means the people
it shrank were... oh, no.
Yep. It's the only explanation.
[YORINOBU]
High Monk Jihou!
[JIHOU] Hm? Oh, Yorinobu
how nice to see you!
I'm glad to see that you're
up and moving about.
I'd heard you weren't feeling
well and brought some food.
Won't you please try some?
Regain your strength.
Thank you, for thinking
of me, Yorinobu.
But I assure you, lately,
I've been eating quite well.
[YORINOBU] The prayers you
offered at my father's funeral
were very moving.
I never got a chance
to thank you for that.
I cannot remember a time
when your dear father and I
were on anything
other than good terms.
But tell me, now that Tada
no Shinbochi has left us,
what do you plan to
do with your life?
I'm not sure I understand.
Michinaga's been... corrupted.
Not by a woman,
but by the unnatural
spellcasting of the Onmyouji.
He's lost his way, and no longer
thinks of the common people.
I don't know.
If that's true,
I'm sure he has good reason
for listening to them.
[JIHOU]
Yorinobu!
[gasps]
You cannot stand by
Michinaga anymore!
That man puts us all at risk.
Not just the Minamoto clan,
but the whole capital [coughs]
will end up being destroyed.
Jihou. Are you all right?
[JIHOU]
Excuse me. I need my medicine.
[JIHOU moaning]
[SHRUNKEN PEOPLE scream]
Um. Do you need me to
take you to a doctor?
[SHRUNKEN MAN A]
No! Please no!
They give me such
great strength!
My god, what are
you doing, Jihou?!
You saw!
[gasps] He's a Horror!
[JIHOU growls]
[SEIMEI] You want us
to save the Onmyouji?
Wow, that's so unlike you.
[INARI A] The barrier they
create protects the capital.
Without them, it disappears.
And without a barrier,
it's only a matter of time
before the city's
overrun by Horrors.
[RAIKOU] Understood.
We'll save the shrunken--
There better be a good reason
why you're choosing us
for this job. If you haven't
noticed, Raikou's been shrunk.
[INARI A]
Yes, we've noticed.
[SEIMEI] There should
be other Makai Knights
you can turn to for this.
Though come to think of it,
we haven't crossed paths
with any of them.
Hell, with teacup Raikou here,
the capital doesn't even
have one to protect it!
[RAIKOU]
Seimei! That's not fair!
[laughs] You always think of
the funniest things to say,
young lady.
Seimei.
You are also deeply
connected to the Onmiyogi.
That is the reason I've
chosen you for this mission.
Yeah, but--
[INARI A]
Besides, you don't want Raikou
to stay that way forever.
Doesn't matter.
Whether he's big or small,
he's still useless to me.
[RAIKOU]
Hey!
Seimei.
'Kay, fine...
[KINTOKI]
So what's the plan?
Security at the Onmyouji mansion
is tighter than a drum now.
We can't lurk around
waiting for the Horror
without the guards
spotting us first.
[RAIKOU]
So then we have to learn
the Horror's identity the hard
way: By talking to people.
The hard way?
Fine then! Your plan is?
Hey!
Seimei!
[RAIKOU groaning]
I... can't breathe.
[Raikou!
Calm down. No use
causing a scene.
[RAIKOU]
C'mon, Seimei!
You're gonna crush me in here!
[gasps]
[YORINOBU]
Uh...
Yorinobu, why're you here?
Are you all right?
Yorinobu?
Wait. Is that Raikou?
Yeah.
It's me.
Wha... What's going on here?
Why's he small, too?
And why... is he all
nestled in your bosom?
I'm the one who should
be turning red. Not you.
So, sounds like you know
something that may help.
[YORINOBU]
I'm sure you already know
the ones who hold the most power
in the capital are the Onmyouji.
They answer to Michinaga.
Predicting disasters
and managing various
functions in court.
At Michinaga's right hand
is his closest advisor
the great Onmyouji,
Abe no Haruaki.
[RAIKOU]
Seimei, that's your grandfather.
Can't you talk
to him about this?
There are still
the Buddhist monks,
but they're impotent
and mostly ignored.
They're given no formal
power in politics.
Thanks to the Onmyouji,
the only job they have left
is praying at funerals.
And the High Monk, Jihou.
He refused to accept
such a fall from grace.
Just like my departed father.
He worried for the future
of the capital we call home.
Not your father.
Ours.
Even though I saw it,
I still can't believe it.
How could a holy man like
that become a Horror?
Seimei, please! Help him!
Turn High Monk Jihou
back into a man!
Seimei!
[exhales] Good grief.
I can't stand you two and
your big puppy dog eyes.
Shouldn't be surprised
they act similar,
they are brothers, after all.
[SEIMEI sighs]
All right, if we're gonna find
Jihou, we better get started.
[COMMONER A]
Who is that?
The only person I can think
who would ride in such
a carriage is Lord Kamo.
[COMMONER A]
You mean, the Onmyouji professor
Kamo no Yasunori?
[COMMONER B]
The one and only.
[JIHOU chuckles]
[RAIKOU]
Is this gonna work?
I don't think it's gonna work.
[SEIMEI]
Hush! You worry too much!
[YORINOBU]
What's wrong?
[KINTOKI]
If they're stopping the carriage
that means he's taken the bait.
Look!
[YORINOBU gasps]
[JIHOU growls]
Jihou! It's me!
[SEIMEI] I'm sorry you
had to learn this way.
But the High Monk is
no longer a human.
Once someone becomes a Horror,
they can't be changed back.
But, I thought...
maybe he would...
[SEIMEI] Like his victims, the
real Jihou's been eaten, too.
What you see before you
is a monster from Makai,
hiding in human flesh.
Raikou.
It's time.
I'm ready!
[RAIKOU yells]
Ah! No! Now Raikou
got eaten, too!
Do something! Please!
Save Raikou!
Don't be so dramatic!
This is all part of my plan.
[RAIKOU screams]
Oh, crap!
[RAIKOU grunts]
Seimei. Come on.
Uh! If we don't destroy him
fast, I'll end up like them!
[groaning]
[SEIMEI]
All right, Raikou! Here you go!
[RAIKOU yells]
[JIHOU groaning]
He made it out!
Sorry, brother.
Yes, I understand.
We weren't able to save Jihou.
But counting Tsuna and Father,
that's three now
who I've failed.
So what can I do?
No matter.
I'm once again thankful
for your help.
[RAIKOU]
Yorinobu!
[SEIMEI] Come on!
Get a move on, knight!
I'm tired!
That Horror's spell
really drained me.
My legs won't listen
to my brain. Ah.
Then I'll make a
special meal for you
to rebuild your strength!
Huh?
[SHIKI DOLL A]
Shiki, shiki!
[ALL]
Uh...
[SEIMEI]
I guess that's dinner.
[RAIKOU]
I guess.
[INARI C]
A light unwanted.
A power, desired.
An outstretched hand, grasping
for brilliant, white silver.