[YASUSUKE]
'Kay, guys, careful in here.
[BANDIT A]
Yeah, gotcha.
We may steal, but we don't kill.
Such is the code of
the Hakamadare thieves.
Let's go!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
You bastard!
[YASUSUKE yells]
[chuckles] A tasty treat!
What perfect timing!
Wouldn't you know it,
I just finished devouring
the last of the people
in this house.
What in the hell
happened to you?
Huh? You can't be serious.
Isn't it obvious?
The entire world
around us has gone mad.
And meanwhile,
the Light Palace refuses
to acknowledge my talents.
And that's the reason why
you just consumed all
the people who lived here?
Yes, and so what if it is?
That a problem?
Yeah, it is!
[yelling]
[grunts]
What's goin' on boss?
You run into some trouble?
No. Good work, guys.
There's just one
thing left to do.
[KINTOU]
Listen up!
We must capture these
thieves at all costs.
In the last few days alone,
they've broken into dozens
of aristocrats' homes
and stolen their valuables.
And worse, they've
won popular support
by giving much of what
they steal to the people!
They are the enemy
of the rich!
If you find these scoundrels,
you should not hesitate
to cut them down!
Now go!
[OFFICERS]
Yes, sir!
Yasusuke.
[INARI A] So, are you having
fun pretending to be a thief?
[INARI B, INARI C giggle]
Who said this was pretend?
I really am a thief now, okay?
Yasusuke.
I'm only targeting the houses
of the rotten and
corrupt aristocrats.
We may take the riches
that they hoard,
but we never take their lives.
Except for--
For what?
What're you saying here?
Sometimes, if I'm lucky,
the owner of the
house I'm robbing
might turn out to be a Horror
and then I get to kill them.
Last I checked, that is
my duty as a Makai Knight.
Am I mistaken?
I won't chastise you for it.
But have the remnants of these
Horrors been red by any chance?
That's what you've been
waiting to ask me about?
[chuckles]
Yeah. They have been red.
You gonna tell me why?
[KINTOKI] Help yourself
to some fried sweets.
Yasusuke. What you said
to Inari, is that true?
Yeah, why would I lie?
And it wasn't just last night.
I've been seeing a lot
more of 'em lately.
Why're so many
becoming Horrors?
And what's with the red?
Does it have something
to do with...
...the moon suddenly
turning crimson?
You brute! What're
you doin' to Raikou?
You're worrying too much
about what's above you.
You should look down.
Who cares what's going on
with the moon, Raikou?
I'm a whole lot more
concerned about the creatures
scurrying around
down here, you get me?
A respectable position.
Yasumasa. Hey.
'Scuse me, I need to have
a word with my brother.
[MICHINAGA]
Give me a status report.
Yes.
We're investigating
all the attacks
on the aristocrats' mansions.
They've occurred frequently
the past few nights.
[MICHINAGA]
Not that.
Sir?
The preparations for
the moon viewing.
I trust everything is
proceeding smoothly.
Yes. Just as you have planned.
Although, there are
more than a few people
who fear this red moon
may be an ominous sign.
[laughs]
The very fact that it's unusual
is what makes it interesting.
It's the reason we're
having the feast.
My Lord.
You know, I actually came
here for the express purpose
of asking Raikou if he
knew how you were faring.
And yet, you're here in person.
[YASUSUKE] You care what
I'm up to? That's rare.
The bandits who've been
running rampant in the capital,
are you their ring leader?
Right, I think I heard
something about that.
[YASUMASA]
Answer the question, Yasusuke.
I don't know.
But so what if I was?
[YASUMASA]
I won't forgive anyone
who threatens the capital.
Even you.
[yelling]
Weren't you committed
to protecting people?
Here I thought that you
had washed your hands
of this thievery business!
Hey, don't jump to
conclusions, all right!
Then show me some proof
that I'm wrong! Prove it!
Come on! Just give
it a rest already!
Well, I could say
the same thing to you!
Fine, then answer this.
Even with that fancy
uniform you're wearing,
aren't there still plenty of
lives that you just can't save?
[growls]
What happened to you anyway?
You used to be so strong.
You taught me the
way of the sword.
Brother, why did you
sacrifice that strength,
your pride as a warrior, to work
under someone like Michinaga?
And become nothing more
than Kintou's puppet?
I may have to
ignore some things.
However, that
pales in comparison
to the vital importance
of maintaining the peace.
Nothing matters more than
keeping the people safe.
If you think killing me will
help the people, then fine.
So be it.
[YASUMASA]
Hmm.
Well, unfortunately,
I don't have any proof that
you are, in fact, a thief.
Not yet, anyway.
[OFFICER B]
You all seem to be living
pretty comfortably
for commoners.
I know you didn't earn
this stuff on your own,
so don't play dumb.
Tell me everything you
know about these thieves!
Answer me now!
[VILLAGER A screams]
[YASUMASA]
Hm?
I-I don't know
anything, I swear!
Please have mercy!
Liar! I'll make you talk,
whatever it takes!
[gasps]
I believe that's
quite enough, don't you?
Oh, Yasumasa.
I'm here under direct orders
from Kintou himself!
He told us to
find the thieves
by any means necessary!
[YASUMASA] Has an official
written decree been released?
Well. No, but--
Go on and confiscate
the stolen goods
that have been doled out.
But the interrogations
must end now.
[YASUMASA]
Kintou is acting too rashly.
He must be compensating for
his failure at the Rise Gate.
No. That can't be
the only reason.
What's this about?
[BANDIT A]
So for our next targets,
first, we'll hit Fujiwarano
Yasuchika on Conoay Road.
And then there's Fujiwara
no Motofusa on the North Road.
Both of them have been using
their status in the Light Palace
to amass quite a fortune.
Hold off for now.
We're gonna have to lay
low for a little while.
What?
[YASUSUKE]
I'm going out.
[BANDIT A]
Uh, boss?
[IZUMI] Sorry, but I'm
a little busy right now.
I've been doing some research
on the Red Moon for Raikou.
What all have you
found so far?
I managed to track down
a record of the moon
turning crimson once
before, long ago.
After which, a great
disaster occurred.
Oh, really?
Bear in mind,
it happened back before
the capital was built.
So I haven't found
a lot of solid facts.
On the other hand, I did
find what you requested
regarding Kintou
and the Fujiwaras
Well, let's hear it.
It seems that Nagaske, Hirofumi,
Norinaga, and Kiyotada,
every one of them,
all of these Fujiwaras fell
out of Kintou's favor.
So much so that he
even barred them
from further social advancement.
[gasps]
What, is that important?
Thanks. That's all
I needed to know.
[YASUSUKE] So all the men I
targeted lately were aristocrats
who just happened to get
on Kintou's bad side.
And they all had become Horrors
by the time I got to them.
[YASUSUKE]
Kintou. What're you up to?
[KINTOU]
Fujiwara no Hirofumi!
Norinaga!
Kiyotada!
Fujiwara no Nagasuke!
Dare go against me?
You'll pay the price.
Divine punishment is quite
the glorious thing,
wouldn't you say?
Everyone who even thinks
about challenging me
continues to disappear.
I suppose I should
thank you for your help.
I can't afford to lose my
status at the Light Palace
with the way things are.
[DOUMAN]
Oh, is that all?
[KINTOU]
Hm?
[DOUMAN] Have you really
set your sights so low?
You should be aiming for more.
Why don't you
take down Michinaga
and seize control
of the Light Palace?
Seize control...
of the Palace myself?
[DOUMAN laughing]
[KINTOU]
I'll show no mercy today!
You must know something
about the thieves!
Start talking!
If you don't, I'll have no
choice but to kill you!
[YASUSUKE]
Damn! What a bastard!
[YASUMASA]
Hold your fire!
Brother.
[YASUMASA] Your investigation
has become pure sadism!
As a member of the police
magistrate, I'm embarrassed!
[KINTOU]
What did you say? Tell me.
Have you gone
completely mad?
I was going to ask you
the exact same thing.
I noticed something.
In the recent string
of robberies,
I've found an interesting
pattern to them.
I can't wait to hear this.
[YASUMASA] Most of the
aristocrats who've been robbed
were left unscathed, but
there have been exceptions.
The heads of certain
households went missing
and remain unaccounted for.
And all those
missing aristocrats,
it seems that they all had less
than favorable opinions of you.
Hah. That may be, but it was
thieves who attacked them.
Need I remind you,
murdering an aristocrat
and hiding their body's
a serious crime.
So we're using every
method at our disposal
to hunt down these bandits.
Sorry, but I just don't buy it.
The thieves that you're
talking about live by a code.
They don't kill.
[KINTOU]
Tch. Incredible.
Are you defending
lawless hooligans?
While casting suspicion on me?
Really? Because that sure
is what it sounds like.
I'm starting to wonder if
you're actually in cahoots
with this band of thugs.
This man right here is a
threat to the Light Palace!
A criminal turncoat!
Don't you listen to
a word that he says!
Now, cut him down!
But, Sir, are you--?
What is this? You dare
question my orders?
It's treason to disobey me!
Attack.
[OFFICERS yell]
You leave me no choice.
You might want to
brace yourselves
for a couple of broken bones.
He's not holding
anything back.
[yells]
[OFFICER I]
Die!
What? Yasuske?
You shouldn't push
yourself so hard.
You're not a young man anymore.
Ah, so it's finally
becoming clear.
The great thief Hakamadare,
or should I say Yasuske,
conspiring with his brother
to throw the Light
Palace into chaos.
He set a trap and I let
myself walk right into it.
Look, Kintou. I promise,
I will not lose to you today!
Kill the both of them!
Yasumasa.
I'm gonna need you to follow
my lead here, you got it?
Let's go!
[YASUMASA]
Hey! Where are we going?
[KINTOU]
Stop them!
[YASUSUKE] Well, you got me
mixed up in a tricky situation.
[YASUMASA]
Did I really?
You're only in this mess
because you continue to steal.
[YASUSUKE]
Hey now,
is that any way to speak to the
man who just saved your life?
Funny, I didn't hear
a denial in there.
So you basically just admitted
that you are a thief.
Did I?
Yeah, you did, without a doubt.
Tell me, why would you go
and provoke Kintou like that?
I've been looking into the man
myself and he's crooked, but...
You know, the Light Palace
is already a rotten place.
You should just
let it decompose.
Well, there are
limits to everything.
So what do you
plan to do now?
I mean, you can't go back
to the Light Palace.
I know that Kintou
is behind all of this.
The reason he's so desperate
to hunt down the thieves
is he intends to pin
the blame on them
for the robberies and
the missing aristocrats.
[YASUSUKE]
Probably.
I'll expose Kintou's sins.
And I have a good idea
where I can find some proof.
Gee, let me take a wild guess.
It's hidden somewhere at
police headquarters, right?
Then we have no choice.
After all, we have
come this far.
[YASUMASA]
Huh?
You're not seriously thinking
of sneaking into
police headquarters.
Why not? Who better
than me to do it?
I am a thie-- I mean, I'm a
former police magistrate.
So I already know
the layout of the place.
Well, I'm going with you.
You'll just slow me down.
You've been gone for a long time
and it's changed a lot
since you were last there.
You'll need me to show
you around, trust me.
[sighs]
In that case,
looks like us brothers
will be thieves together.
Security seems
lighter than usual.
[YASUMASA] I'm sure most of
the officers are out on patrol
looking for us.
Thank goodness for small favors.
[YASUMASA]
Nothing here. Any luck?
[YASUSUKE]
No. Haven't found anything.
[YASUSUKE grunts]
[YASUMASA]
What is it?
[YASUSUKE]
I wonder...
[YASUMASA]
Is-Is that?
I think we found it.
The proof we need.
[ARISTOCRAT A] True to your
reputation, Michinaga.
You truly understand
the art of elegance.
What could be more exquisite
than drinking under such
an unusual red moon?
[ARISTOCRAT B] Ooh, have
you heard the latest gossip
about Fujiwara no Yasumasa?
[ARISTOCRAT C]
Oh, it's absolutely terrifying!
For someone of such high status
to be consorting with outlaws!
[YASUMASA]
Let me through!
[OFFICER K]
Hold it there! Stand down!
--[YASUMASA] Lord Michinaga!
--[OFFICER K] Don't move!
It's Yasumasa!
You must be out
of your damn mind
to show your face
here like this!
I've come here
to offer information
vital to the security
of this capital! Hear me!
Kill him!
[MICHINAGA]
Wait!
[KINTOU]
Tch.
If you have something to
say here, then say it.
[YASUMASA] This is a letter
that was sent to you, my Lord.
In it, there's a strong
condemnation
of a particular individual
within the Light Palace.
But this letter was intercepted
before it could reach you.
And its writer was
murdered in cold blood...
...by none other than Kintou!
[gasps]
I found it stashed away
in a secret hiding place.
Along with it, were
many other documents
originally intended
for your eyes.
As well as... mementos of
the slain aristocrats.
ll displayed like trophies
from successful hunts.
Please, Michinaga.
Come see. See all the
evidence for yourself.
Oh, I think I will.
[laughing]
[KINTOU]
So this is the end for me.
Well, I'm not going alone.
Michinaga! I'm taking
you to Hell with me!
[DOUMAN]
Hmm...
[yelling]
Lord Michinaga,
please stand back!
Michinaga.
Ashiya Douman.
Those scars on your face.
Oh, don't tell me that
you don't remember.
Remember what?
[chuckles] Never mind that.
I believe that my work
here is done for the night.
Get out of here! Run!
[YASUSUKE] Hey,
I'm the one you really want!
Yasuske!
[YASUSUKE]
I'll take it from here.
[YASUMASA]
Sorry I've caused you trouble.
No more than I've caused you.
This is as far as
our alliance goes.
[YASUSUKE]
Looks like I'm the lucky one
who gets to finish you off...
...once and for all!
[YASUSUKE] You're just as
annoying as you ever were.
[MICHINAGA]
Minamoto no Yorinobu.
I want you to be the new leader
of the police magistrate.
Serve the capital honorably.
Yes. I won't let you down.
Well, look who we have here.
The magistrate? No kidding.
Jeez, they're here already?
Because now they have
a new man in charge.
Come on. Let's go.
Look. Up there! After them!
[gasps] Is that?
Did you see that man?
He looked an awful
lot like your brother.
What, Yasuske?
You're seeing things.
That's Hakamadare, the ring
leader of the bandits.
I'm absolutely certain.
C'mon, hurry!
We hafta distribute this stuff
to the villagers before morning.
Let's go!
[BANDIT A]
You got it!
[YASUMASA] Don't
underestimate me, Yasusuke.
I'll pursue you
until the bitter end.
[INARI A] The stars fade away.
The moon grows redder.
And the darkness,
it gets deeper and deeper.