[SEIMEI]
Come!
[HORROR A roars]
[SEIMEI yells]
[panting]
[gasps]
[SEIMEI grunting]
[SEIMEI]
Why you little...!
[gasps]
Summoning a Horror,
then fighting against it?
And, at such a young
age takes guts,
I'll give you that much, girl.
But you're in over your head.
All that I want is
to become stronger.
And I've given up
everything to do so.
[DOUMA]
Tell me. Who are you?
My name's Kiyome.
You know, I heard rumors
that Abe no Haduaki
had branded his own
granddaughter "filth".
And afterwards he
banished the girl.
Now I know those
rumors were true.
Do you know my Grandpa?
[DOUMA]
It's strength you seek, huh?
I want to defeat those demons!
All right, then, I would
suggest you follow me.
[DOUMA] She possesses
extraordinarily rare talent.
And such a strong will.
There's no doubt
in my mind this girl
will become an unparalleled
Alchemist. However...
[DOUMA]
Kiyome.
[SEIMEI]
Yes, Doushi?
From now on, you shall
be known to all as Seimei.
Ah, Seimei.
I'm honored to receive
such a name from you, sir.
Henceforth, whether you
shine brightly in the light,
or fall deeply
into the darkness.
That is all up to you.
[DOUMA]
Uh. Seimei.
[SEIMEI]
Oh, look how it sparkles!
It's like staring at a
completely blue rainbow!
[KINTOKI]
Jeez, another one?
[SEIMEI]
Another one? Ha!
You just do not understand.
See. This vase is a
one-of-a-kind treasure
that traveled from across
the ocean to get here.
Not what I meant.
I don't care about that vase,
I'm mad that you bought
any vase at all!
I bet you went and borrowed
money from someone again,
didn't you?
[SEIMEI]
Oh, it's absolutely beautiful!
So enchanting!
[KINTOKI] It's too bad
"enchanting" knick-knacks
don't fill the belly.
You know, I think that
this vase sparkles
even more because of my
intense love for it.
[KINTOKI]
Sheesh!
And what about the bottom
of our empty rice box?
Does that sparkle, too?!
Hey, wait a second.
Where is Raikou?
[KINTOKI cries]
He went to the Watchdog Center
in hopes of finding work.
Had to swallow his pride.
A Makai Knight
begging for a job?
How pathetic can you get?
[KINTOKI growls]
Maybe if we didn't give you
three meals a day for free!
[RAIKOU]
Seimei! Kintoki!
Whoa, what happened?
[SEIMEI]
What's wrong?
A new Horror!
[KINTOKI] Hey, so, what kind
of Horror is this one?
[RAIKOU]
I didn't get a ton of details,
but it sounds like
it could be trouble.
Yeah, well, aren't they all?
Whatever it's like,
I'm gonna destroy it.
For certain. Seimei. Hurry!
Yeah, whatever.
Could you be any less
enthusiastic right now?
[RAIKOU]
Look, there it is!
[KINTOKI] That thing?
It's definitely creepy.
Uh? But how?
There was no breeze.
Raikou. The light.
[RAIKOU]
The Horror sucks in all light,
hunts humans, and fades
into the darkness.
We won't be able to see a thing.
I guess we'll just have
to make a little light
of our own then, won't we?
How?
Some shiny Golden Armor
should do the trick.
Raikou!
[RAIKOU]
Got it!
[KINTOKI]
Raikou?
[SEIMEI]
What the...?
This thing even absorbs
the armor's light!
[SEIMEI yells]
[SEIMEI]
It's no use.
This one really is
gonna be trouble.
[KINTOKI] Great, now the
light of the armor is gone.
Raikou!
[RAIKOU grunts]
[ZARUBA]
Calm yourself.
You may not be able to see,
but you can use the blindness
to heighten your
sense of movement.
[HORROR B howls]
[RAIKOU grunts]
[panting]
[KINTOKI] You did it!
Just like I knew you would!
I mean, sure, I was a
little worried at first.
But I was always confident
you'd pull through in the end.
[RAIKOU groans]
[SEIMEI]
Raikou, what's wrong?
[RAIKOU gasping]
[KINTOKI]
Raikou?
Seimei, what happening to him?
I have no idea.
[gasps]
That's it!
[RAIKOU screams]
[RAIKOU gasps]
Uh! No, no, Raikou!
Hey, please, are you okay?
Come on, Raikou! Get up!
[RAIKOU snoring]
[KINTOKI]
He's been completely out cold
ever since he collapsed.
Oh, man you think he's
gonna be all right?
Well, we took the armor
off of him, so...
he'll probably wake
up sooner or later.
How can you be so calm
about something like this?
[RAIKOU yawns]
Told ya.
[KINTOKI]
Raikou!
[RAIKOU] Man, I'm starving.
How 'bout some grub?
[KINTOKI]
You got it! Right away!
Rice, rice, where's the--?
--[crash, glass shatters]
--[KINTOKI groans] Ow!
[SEIMEI growls]
Seconds, please!
[KINTOKI]
Coming right up!
[RAIKOU]
Second seconds!
[KINTOKI]
Coming right up!
[RAIKOU]
Third seconds!
[KINTOKI]
Coming right up!
[KINTOKI laughs]
Well, they do say
that hunger's a sign
of good health, right?
Ah!
[belches]
[SEIMEI]
Mm?
[KINTOKI] Oh no, Raikou.
I am so sorry!
We're out!
The steamed rice is all gone!
And there's nothing left in the
rice box to heat up, either!
We don't have money to buy more.
[RAIKOU] Hey, calm down,
don't worry about it.
[KINTOKI]
Uh?
Wait, Raikou,
where are you going?
[RAIKOU] Got no money,
I gotta go get us some.
[SEIMEI]
Raikou.
[RAIKOU]
Hm?
It's too soon for you to go out.
We really should monitor
you a little longer.
And besides, Zaruba is--
[RAIKOU] Yeah, well,
we're all outta rice.
So why don't you just sit there
and stare at that hair
thingy and shut up.
[KINTOKI]
Hey, wait for me!
[SEIMEI]
U-Uh...
Oh man, I can't believe you
told off Seimei like that!
"Why don't you just sit there
and stare at that hair thingy
and keep your damn mouth shut."
Y'know, I gotta say,
you're finally starting to sound
like a real man now, Raikou!
Hey, wait. Where are you going?
Don't do that!
Hey there, baby.
Wow, you are one hot mama.
[WOMAN 9]
Uh! Excuse me?
Oh, I'm sorry,
are you not a mama?
I can fix that for ya.
Oh, well, I never! How rude!
Damn. What a prissy,
stuck-up prude.
This is why I hate aristocrats.
Uh, Raikou.
[RAIKOU] See. Deep down,
they wanna have some fun.
But they're always so worried
about their "reputation."
Really, they're
annoying as hell.
[MAN A] What was that?!
What'd you just say to me?!
[MAN B] I'm telling you!
You're blind as a bat!
[MAN A]
Don't joke about that!
[MAN B] I called you blind
because you are blind!
[MAN A]
You bastard!
Fighting in the middle
of the street.
Just how inconsiderate
can you get?
Yeah, that is uncivilized.
Okay! I'll go take care of it.
Sure, he may be a little
bit rougher now,
but deep down, he's basically
still the same Raikou.
'Least I think?
[MAN A groans]
[MAN B screams]
[RAIKOU]
What's the problem?!
[MAN B]
Please forgive us!
[SEIMEI]
But why?
Because the Madou
Ring turned black?
[INARI A]
You mentioned that the Horror
stole the armor's
light, correct?
[INARI B] This is the result
of armor clad in darkness.
[INARI A] The darkness that
has collected in his armor
is affecting him negatively.
Are you saying that cleansing
the Madou Ring isn't enough?
[INARI C] You must banish the
darkness from the armor itself.
Otherwise, history
will only repeat.
If this continues, the owner
will lose his sanity as well.
Indeed, the situation
here is rather serious.
[MASAMUNE]
Come. Just a little closer now.
We're all alone.
I'll be gentle, I promise.
It'll be okay.
No, we can't.
We shouldn't.
I mean, come on.
You've got a wife
for goodness' sake.
Worst mistake of my life
was marrying a woman
who does nothing but
criticize and complain
every time she sees my face.
I'm gonna leave that harpy
for good, I swear!
But, for now, how 'bout
you start as my concubine?
Kissy, Kissy, Kissy!
Wait, no. It's wrong.
[RAIKOU]
Woo! I saw that. I saw it all!
Who's there? Show yourself!
[RAIKOU]
You're quite the ladies' man,
aren't you, Masamune?
[screams] It's you!
What are you doing in
a place like this?!
You get the hell outta here!
Hard to believe a
guy like Masamune
would ever have the guts
to abandon his wife.
Gee, you know,
I wonder how she's gonna react
when she finds out about this.
Do you think that she'll
take it lying down?
[MASAMUNE] Huh?! Wait, what?
How would she find out?
Hold on there.
Why don't you come
down here so we can talk?
Come. Come.
Let's talk. We can work
this out. [laughs nervously]
[RAIKOU laughs]
Y'see,
this is what happens when
ya put in a little effort!
What you did back there,
that was blackmail!
You don't know what
you're saying.
Look, I didn't ask the idiot
for any money, not even once.
Masamune just gave
it to us on his own.
Well, yeah, I guess that
is true, technically.
[RAIKOU]
Oh, hey, Seimei's home.
Here, check it out!
We can afford to buy
all the rice we want!
Go on, get yourself
something nice!
He's different.
He's not the Raikou I used to
know. He's like somebody else.
[whimpers]
Unfortunately, he's still being
affected by that Horror.
Well then, we've
gotta exorcise it!
Sorry, I'm afraid
it's not that easy.
[laughing] Hey! Hey, Kintoki!
We'll have a whole fish
for breakfast tomorrow!
[SEIMEI]
Raikou!
[RAIKOU]
Huh?
What the hell do you think
you're doing, Seimei?
Why'd you do that?
Damn, I can't move
at all in this!
It's tightening around me!
[SEIMEI] Kintoki, at the
rate things are going,
Raikou will lose himself.
[KINTOKI]
Oh, no.
I leave him in your care.
Watch him if you
don't want him to die.
[KINTOKI]
Mm.
What the...?!
Come on, untie me right now!
How am I supposed to
eat like this, huh?!
Hey, wait! Get back here!
Kintoki, listen,
grab that sword for me.
[DOUMAN] Ah. A visit from
you is such a rare treat.
But what's an excommunicated
student like you doing here?
Not here to see you. Sorry.
Don't get any ideas.
Well, too bad,
because you have to deal with
me before you can get to him.
[SEIMEI]
I may have been exiled,
but I've known him
for a very long time.
So step aside.
I see you're still as boorish
a nuisance as ever.
A sad, pathetic little girl
rejected not once, but twice.
[DOUMA] So, were you lured
here by the full moon?
[SEIMEI] No. I've come
to ask you something.
[DOUMA]
What is it?
[SEIMEI]
How do I exorcise darkness
once it has seeped into armor?
[DOUMA]
Ah, so you came to beg for help?
If he's affected
by the darkness,
all he has to do is accept
it and become one with it.
I won't let him slip
into darkness!
That is not an option!
It seems coming here was
a waste of my time.
[DOUMA] There are other
things you can do.
Like what? Just tell me!
[DOUMA] I see.
The one they call Raiko.
Don't you say his name!
[DOUMA] Ah. So that young
man really is your light.
You know, Seimei, it
has been far too long
since last you stood before me.
Let's have a little fun,
for old times' sake.
[DOUMA] My, my, you've developed
into quite a woman.
Go ahead and do with
me what you will.
Like you always have.
[DOUMA]
You are truly special.
One of the few who can balance
both light and darkness.
So you need only absorb
the darkness into yourself,
and seal it away there.
[SEIMEI]
Inside myself?
[DOUMA] I'll give you
the spell you need,
to pull that darkness into
yourself, as your mother did.
I wonder if you have
ever asked yourself
why I used the words
for "star" and "light"
to grant you the name
Seimei so long ago?
[gasps]
[DOUMA] A single light deepens
the darkness that surrounds it.
Though you will
be able to remove
the darkness from the armor...
[SEIMEI gasps]
[DOUMA] ...once that darkness
resides within you,
it will never be stripped away.
[groaning]
[KINTOKI]
Please, Raikou.
You gotta try to
calm down a little!
You're just gonna hurt yourself!
This is awful.
I mean, what if I never get to
see the Raikou I know again?
[RAIKOU grunts]
[KINTOKI]
Uh?
[KINTOKI screams]
[DOUMAN]
Why did you do that?
We should seize this opportunity
to crush Raikou!
[DOUMA]
Raikou is insignificant.
No, it is Seimei
who I wish to test.
Her? But why?
[DOUMA]
You still don't see it, do you?
The way the light and the
dark wage war inside her.
[DOUMAN]
I refuse to allow
even a single shining
star to burn brightly.
This world doesn't need light.
[SEIMEI]
Kintoki!
I know how to save Raikou!
Kintoki? Uh! Kintoki!
Oh, my goodness!
Are you all right?
[KINTOKI groans]
It hurts.
[SEIMEI] What's going on?
How did this happen?
[KINTOKI]
Uh... Well, uh.
[SEIMEI laughs]
That bump is huge!
[KINTOKI]
Gee, thanks.
Oh, right! Raikou!
He got away!
Go find Raikou for me!
[SHIKI DOLL A]
Shiki!
[SEIMEI] Come on.
We've gotta go get him back!
All right!
Raikou!
[KINTOKI screams]
[RAIKOU gasping]
[RAIKOU]
I can't believe I hit Kintoki.
What's wrong with me?
[RAIKOU chuckles]
[RAIKOU yells]
[DOUMAN] Oh, what a
pathetic sight you are.
Do you want to escape
this suffering?
You're turning into a beast.
Why not allow me to put an end
to the pain you're feeling,
before the darkness
consumes you.
Succumb to the
darkness, Raikou!
[RAIKOU groaning, yelling]
I'll make sure that
wretched woman
soon knows the agony of despair.
For the one who inherited
the name of Ashiya Doumahn...
is me!
[RAIKOU]
Uh!
[DOUMAN]
Feel the hate! The anger!
Drown in the darkness!
Huh?
Nice of you to come.
[SEIMEI]
Stop this, Douman!
Oh, you're far too late!
I'm afraid the boy has already
given into the darkness.
[SEIMEI]
Raikou! Summon your armor!
[KINTOKI]
Come on, Raikou!
[SEIMEI]
Raikou.
[RAIKOU growls]
The armor. Seimei, look!
[DOUMAN] Your Golden Knight
doesn't look so golden anymore.
A foolish mistake.
Now that he's put on
the Makai armor,
watch as he sinks into the
darkness even more rapidly.
[RAIKOU groaning]
Ha. It seems there's no need
for me to even finish him off.
I'll let nature run its course
and leave you to watch
him surrender to his fate.
Uh. Seimei, is...
is Raikou... going to die?
[SEIMEI]
I won't let him.
[RAIKOU groans]
Even if it means giving my life!
Seimei.
Seimei!
[SEIMEI]
Listen, Zaruba!
I'll absorb the darkness
that has infected the armor.
Don't fight against it.
[SEIMEI] This is the only
way left to save Raikou.
But Seimei!
[SEIMEI]
Oh, Raikou. Please don't die!
[RAIKOU grunting]
[SEIMEI grunting]
[RAIKOU roars]
[SEIMEI yelps]
Everything...
that I love...
shines... brightly.
Which means... you...
have to... Raikou...
You have to... shine!
Raikou.
Come back!
His light's back.
[RAIKOU gasps, yells]
[SEIMEI gasps]
[KINTOKI]
Seimei! Oh, Raikou!
Thank goodness!
You guys are all right!
Don't scare me like
that ever again!
[ZARUBA]
Did I cause you some trouble?
[SEIMEI]
Yeah. Just a bit.
[KINTOKI gasps]
Hey, you're awake.
Uh. What's up?
Have I been sleeping?
[KINTOKI]
Oh, Raikou!
Hey, what's wrong?
Wipe those tears, Kintoki.
Men aren't supposed
to show 'em, remember?
At least not in front
of other people.
[DOUMA]
Seimei, do not forget.
Though you will be
able to remove
the darkness from the armor,
once that darkness resides
within you, it will
never be stripped away.
[RAIKOU]
Whoa. Seimei.
What happened to your shoulder?
Oh. I got bit by a dog.
It was no big deal.
[RAIKOU]
It bit you?! Man.
What kinda dog was it?
Big and black, and so not cute.
Like, not even in the slightest.
[RAIKOU] Wow, sounds scary.
Glad you're okay.
[KINTOKI]
Seimei!
Come on, we're having a whole
fish for breakfast today!
[RAIKOU]
Oh, good. I'm starving!
[KINTOKI]
Really? Again?
[RAIKOU]
Oh, looks good!
[KINTOKI]
Doesn't it!
[RAIKOU, KINTOKI laugh]
[INARI B]
When your perspective changes,
so does your view of
the world around you.
Not to mention your friends.