My God. The Crimson Moon.
[HARUAKI] It won't be long
before it resurrects.
Before what does?
Rudra.
Even the powers of ancient
Makai Knights and Alchemists
could not defeat it permanently.
It is a Horror with
unimaginable strength.
[SEIMEI]
Damn this curse!
What was I trying
to do back there?
If Shiki hadn't stopped me,
my Grandfather would be--
[DOUMAN]
If you wish to know the secret
to the seal on the Crimson Moon,
you have to get through me.
A pointless struggle.
[DOUMA]
But you know this darkness
is impossible to control.
As strong as you've become,
it will devour you!
[DOUMAN]
And with this, I bid farewell
to the previous Ashiya Douman.
It's back.
[INARI B]
The catastrophe.
[INARI A]
It's begun.
I'm afraid that we don't
have any more time.
The dire threat contained
by the Crimson Moon
is the one known as... Rudra.
Rudra?
[INARI B]
A Horror so powerful
the knights of old
couldn't defeat it.
Their only option was
to seal the beast away
behind a moon barrier crafted
by highly skilled alchemists.
[INARI C] The moon turning
red was the first harbinger
of its inevitable release
upon the hapless world.
And now, it has found a
suitable vessel to inhabit.
Wait, this terrible monster
has been resurrected?
No. It still hasn't
completed the process yet.
[INARI B] At the moment,
it is gathering power
within the vessel,
building up its strength.
[INARI C] And that vessel is
most likely in the hands of...
...none other than Douma Houshi.
Douma Houshi? But why him?
'Cause he was the one
who removed the seal,
freeing the beast.
[ZARUBA] This situation
is even more perilous
than I could've anticipated.
[INARI B] If Rudra emerges,
the capital will certainly fall.
[INARI C]
Golden Knight Garo.
Yes.
[INARI A]
We hereby order you,
prevent Douma Houshi
from executing his plan.
And before Rudra's full power
can be completely restored...
[INARIS]
...eliminate it.
[YORINOBU] Michinaga has
officially appointed me
to be head police magistrate.
[COMMONER A] Yorinobu?
In charge of the police?
First, I want to apologize
for how the magistrate
has treated you in the past.
Got some nerve
after all you've done!
Quiet down! They'll kill you!
[YORINOBU] Listen, I know that
it isn't going to be easy
for us to rebuild trust.
However, without it, there's
no way the capital can prosper.
So I ask you all to
lend me your faith.
Please do.
[COMMONER A]
The police magistrate
are bowing their heads to us.
Let's work together to
make things better here!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[chuckles]
What was that?
Red lightning?
What on earth is going on?
Get all these people to safety!
Who is that?
Hold it!
Hey, wait! Who are you?
Could it be you?
Are you Seimei?
[grunts]
[DARK SEIMEI] Tell me,
where is the Golden Knight?
[YORINOBU]
Why would I...?
He was lucky enough to be
found by some citizens
who administered first aid.
Yeah.
If Yorinobu weren't so
beloved by the people,
he'd probably be--
[SUETSUMUHANA]
According to the officers,
right after the red lightning
struck the city,
he started chasing
after someone.
[RAIKOU] I never imagined things
would escalate so quickly.
[YORINOBU]
Brother...
[SUETSUMUHANA]
Yorinobu!
[RAIKOU]
You're awake!
I... saw... Sei--
[RAIKOU]
Yorinobu!
[MICHINAGA]
Yes, I understand.
So there weren't any
serious problems then?
[YASUMASA]
That's correct.
The Light Palace
sustained no damage.
Though strong, the lightning
wasn't powerful enough
to pierce the barrier.
You're in charge.
You're leaving, sir?
Not your concern. Haruaki. Come.
Yes.
I believe this world
is indeed my own,
as it was destined to be.
Like the full moon,
I lack nothing.
[gasps]
What was... that?
[YASUSUKE] Okay, so putting
aside Douman for a minute,
you wanna tell me who the
hell this Douma Houshi is?
Douma Houshi, the
previous Ashiya Douman.
[RAIKOU]
That's all I know.
The previous one?
So this Douma
is somehow involved
with that super Horror Rudra,
as well as the brutal attack
that nearly killed Yorinobu?
I have no proof,
but I believe so.
[YASUSUKE]
Well, then this will be easy.
He's been causing so many
problems, one after another.
It's only a matter of time
before he shows himself.
[RAIKOU]
How can you be so sure?
[YASUSUKE]
Just my gut feeling.
Your gut has quite the keen
understanding of villains.
He did used to be
a police officer.
Ugh, don't remind me.
Hey, you know,
it's possible the vessel may
be Douma Houshi himself.
I know that if it were me,
I would wanna keep
something that valuable
where I could see it.
Is that your thief's
instinct speaking this time?
[YASUSUKE]
Hmph.
There's simply no way
to know for certain
until we meet him face to face.
[RAIKOU]
You're right.
At the moment, there's
only one thing we do know.
If we don't stop them,
the capital will fall.
[YASUSUKE]
Ah, damn it.
Now I feel like I'm back working
for the magistrate again.
[YASUSUKE] This tiresome game
is over, Ashiya Douman.
[DOUMAN laughing]
[DOUMAN]
Oh, but you're wrong.
Things are about
to get interesting.
Are they? I think you know
what I'm here to find out.
The only way you'll get me to
talk is to force it out of me.
Well, if you insist, then.
[gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
[YASUSUKE]
Well, off to a rough start.
Come on. Let's get serious!
[YASUSUKE]
What?
It appears that the vessel
especially loathes
you Makai Knights.
Damn it!
[gasps]
Be careful, Kintoki.
Right!
[KINTOKI whimpering]
[RAIKOU gasps]
[RAIKOU]
Yasusuke!
[INARI A] And you, Golden
Knight, where were you?
Would you care to tell
us what kept you away?
We will treat Hakamadare
here and help him to heal.
He was mumbling
something feverishly before.
Indeed, he said, "If you
falter, you will fail."
[gasps]
[RAIKOU]
Kintoki.
I know that I'm not supposed
to show any weakness.
But right now, if she
were here beside me...
Hey now, that is no way for
the Golden Knight to talk!
Even though, I feel
the exact same way as you.
She may've been difficult
most of the time,
but you could always
count on her
when things got rough like this.
[KINTOKI] Raikou, maybe you
should ask for some help.
[HARUAKI] So then, you've
come to me for assistance.
Seimei must be off fighting
somewhere by herself
as we speak.
[HARUAKI]
By now, Kiyome is probably--
[HARUAKI] Unfortunately,
the power of the Golden Knight
will be necessary.
Yes, I understand. I'll try
to help you find my Kiyome.
You mean that's possible?
Yes, but it will take
some time to prepare.
Please wait here.
[gasps]
[KAGUYA whimpers]
[KAGUYA]
I am--
The pulse that I'm
about to send out
will only reach members
of the Abe family.
If it finds Kiyome, then it will
surely respond back to us.
Then please, hurry.
All right. I shall begin.
Whoa, look at
that shiki, Raikou!
Quick, let's follow it!
Thank you for all
your help! See ya later!
You take care of her!
Oh, alas. What cruel fate.
[RAIKOU]
We're coming.
No, Brother.
You don't have
anything to worry about.
Raikou's proven himself
to be quite strong.
Brother, you mustn't fight her.
You can't win against her.
She's gotta be here!
Seimei! Seimei!
[DOUMAN]
Who are you looking for?
[BOTH gasp]
[RAIKOU]
Douman! You evil bastard!
[DOUMAN] You can don
the armor by yourself now,
yet, you still
call out for your Seimei
like a child crying
for his mother.
[RAIKOU]
Shut up!
[KINTOKI] Come down here
and say that, you coward!
Or maybe you know you
don't stand a chance
against Raikou and
Seimei together!
[DOUMAN]
Oh, quiet down.
After all, we were nice
enough to wait for you.
[RAIKOU] What the hell
are you doing here?
Trust me, you'll find
out soon. Patience.
Not to ruin the surprise,
but I'm not the only one
who's been looking for you.
You mean Douma Houshi?
[laughing]
[DOUMAN] Douma Houshi is dead.
I killed him with my own hands.
He was just a helpless,
senile old man.
I am the one true
Ashiya Douman!
There is no other but me!
Wait, you killed him?
Then who--?
[DARK SEIMEI] So you're the
current Golden Knight, are you?
[gasps]
Seimei...
I was hoping to meet you.
Sheesh, you made us
worry for nothin'.
[ZARUBA]
Wait, this woman is--
[gasps]
[ZARUBA]
Watch out!
[RAIKOU]
Kintoki!
[DARK SEIMEI]
Well, he's a tough kid.
Why are you doing this?
I don't get it!
[DARK SEIMEI]
Arch-enemies face off
and fight each other
to the death.
What's not to get about that?
[gasps]
Stop this!
Why won't you fight me?
Well why do I have to?
[DARK SEIMEI] Hard to believe
you're a Makai Knight.
[gasps]
Move, Kintoki.
Look, Raikou, I dunno
what's goin' on.
I don't have any idea.
However, I do know,
if you kill Seimei...
...no matter how valid
your reason may be,
you're always gonna regret it
and you'll never be
the same again.
Yeah, but--
I get it, you're a Makai Knight,
and it's your sworn duty
to protect the citizens.
But my job... Well, it's my
job to take care of you, okay?
I mean, I am your
attendant, after all!
Kintoki.
[yells]
Kintoki!
[DOUMAN] This isn't your fight.
Stay out of it, boy.
Come on now, I can't
give up that easily.
If I do, how will I still
be able to protect Raikou?
Stop! That's enough!
[KINTOKI grunts]
[gasps]
Is he dead this time?
[RAIKOU yelling]
Seimei!
[gasps]
Poor Raikou.
[ZARUBA]
Here she comes!
Look up!
[gasps]
[ZARUBA] Put on your armor,
Raikou! Protect yourself!
[yelling]
What a miserable
sight to behold.
This is the end for
you, Golden Knight!
[KAGUYA]
Who's that?
[gasps]
[RAIKOU]
Kaguya.
You little...
[gasps]
This is...
She was the one who
sealed me up before.
I never expected her
to turn up here.
It seems we're done
for the night.
[DARK SEIMEI]
Well, Golden Knight,
I'll have to kill you next time.
[RAIKOU]
Wait!
No.
[KAGUYA] So it was you
that I heard, Raikou.
That painful cry from the soul.
Kaguya, why are you here?
Because I remember now.
[KAGUYA]
I'm the one...
...who seals away Horrors,
trapping them within
the Crimson Moon.
[RAIKOU]
Uh?
[INARI A] One of darkness.
One of pure light.
They will face each other
to the ends of untainted truth.