[NARIMICHI yells]
[YASUSUKE yells]
[NARIMICHI screams]
A Makai Knight.
I now understand the power
that I've inherited.
It's my destiny after all.
[GORUBA]
That is so,
Silver Knight Zanga.
[RAIKOU]
Yasusuke.
So you're a Makai
Knight as well.
That's amazing.
Glad you're amazed.
This makes us brothers
in arms now!
We could fight together!
You're sorely
mistaken, Raikou.
The only will I
follow is my own.
And this armor
that I've acquired,
I'll choose how I use it.
[gasps]
I will do what I want and I
will continue to do it alone.
[RAIKOU]
Hold on! Listen to me!
That's not your power,
it's for the people!
[RAIKOU grunts]
Don't you preach to me.
Tell me what the hell
you've even done
with this power to actually
help the citizens here?
Take a look around you.
Look at the capital.
It's just as bad as it was back
before I became a thief.
I don't intend to take the
easy path you have chosen.
Take that back!
Just who do you think
you are to insult him!
That's some big talk for a
self-righteous petty thief.
What could you possibly
know about being a knight?
[GORUBA laughs] You are
the only person I see here
with a big mouth, little girl.
[gasps] Well, your Madou
tool shares your manners.
[GORUBA] This man was accepted
by the armor and is my master.
He has inherited
the name of Zanga!
[YASUMASA] You could
come with me, you know.
As far as I'm concerned,
the past is just the past.
Well, I've become quite
the popular one tonight.
Return to the Light Palace.
[YASUSUKE grunts]
How long do you expect
to last as a thief?
Do you honestly think you'll
achieve your goals like this?
Let's go, then.
[KINTOU]
Impressive, isn't it?
It won't be much longer
now before it's finished
and then we'll no longer need
to worry about sickness
and evil spirits when
the Rajou Gate crumbles.
We won't know until we use it.
It's nothing to fret over.
With this gate and
Haruaki's barrier,
as well as the strength
of our police magistrate,
the security of the
Light Palace is assured.
His barrier.
Because nobody can best
the great Onmioji.
Only Abe no Haduaki can do it.
You know, I'd be
lying if I told you
that I wasn't quite envious
of your upcoming retirement.
Is there something the matter?
No. Never mind, it's nothing.
Ah! Delicious!
That's nice of you
to say, but y'know,
it would be nicer if you
didn't eat all of our food!
Oh, please, do you really expect
me to cook for myself every day?
[SHIKI DOLL]
Shiki, shiki. Shiki, shiki.
[KINTOKI]
Uh? Mm...
Tell me what the hell you've
even done with this power?
Swallow your food.
[RAIKOU grunting]
I could've choked!
Don't surprise me like that!
And just what do you
have on your mind
that's wiped your face as blank
as a piece of parchment?
What, nothing.
Ah, are you finally starting
to take an interest in girls?
I can tell you anything
you wanna know.
Oh, give me a break!
[MICHINAGA]
Looks like you've grown stronger
since last we spoke.
[YASUSUKE] Yes, well,
it has been a long time.
Yasusuke, let us not
dance around the subject.
Would you lend me your strength?
[YASUSUKE] What exactly do you
wish from a thief like me?
I'd like to see you become a
warrior for the Light Palace.
And destroy all the Horrors
threatening the capital.
[YASUSUKE]
The capital, huh?
Don't you mean the things
that specifically threaten you?
[YASUMASA]
Yasusuke!
[YASUSUKE] That huge gate
you're building out there?
It's evident that the Light
Palace is only interested
in protecting themselves.
I don't care about
your orders.
I'll destroy every single
Horror I encounter.
Because that is my duty.
Ah-ha.
So there's no need for me
to directly serve under you.
[YASUMASA]
That's enough!
I serve only the people.
If they're human, then
I will protect them.
[YASUMASA] Have you forgotten
who you're talking to?
You must be insane.
Oh, Brother.
Look at you trying to save face.
You watch your mouth!
You haven't changed
in the slightest!
You're nothing more
than a common criminal!
This is who the armor chose?
[SEIMEI]
It's not happening!
Ask all you want, I'm
not removing the seal.
[RAIKOU] But I'm not
doing enough out there!
I need to save more people!
And to do that...
You're taking the judgment of
a thief way too close to heart.
I promise you that I
can control my power!
Give it up, I'm not doing it.
Besides, don't you know it's
impossible to save everyone?
Uh! That is the whole reason
why Makai Knights exist!
Such a big hero.
Are you even listening to
a word I'm saying to you?
Quit giving me commands
like I'm your pet!
[SEIMEI growls]
Uh. Hey, Raikou, why
don't you calm down?
Wait, Raikou!
I swear that guy can be
such a hot head sometimes.
[YASUSUKE] No good will come
of working under Michinaga.
Nothing will change
while he's in power.
[YORINOBU]
Hello, Yasusuke.
[YASUSUKE] Hey, Yorinobu,
Long time no see.
[YORINOBU]
How foolish can you be?
Yeah, it's not too smart
to go against Michinaga.
[YORINOBU] And yet you still
haven't learned that lesson.
No? What gives you that idea?
[YORINOBU sighs]
Oh, a combination
of your actions and words.
The only way to truly lessen
the sadness and suffering
of the poor is for the
Light Palace to change.
I disagree.
That can't possibly be
the solution to everything.
Sure, that may be true.
But it's not enough
to stop me from trying.
Come on out.
There's no getting past you!
Don't worry about me.
I'd rather not, but you
make it hard not to.
Heh. Well since you're
here, you wanna spar?
Of course! Anytime!
I just can't understand
why she doesn't trust me.
[yells]
She trusts you just fine.
[grunts]
She just cares about
you too much.
You're special to her!
You and the Golden Armor!
[RAIKOU]
Whose side are you on?
[grunts, yelps]
--[SEIMEI] Uh?
--[SHIKI DOLL] Shiki, shiki.
[SEIMEI] We'll just have
to have faith in him.
But at least Kintoki's with him.
[SHIKI DOLL]
Shiki, shiki, shiki.
Huh?
[DOUMA] Everything
has fallen into place.
The fall of the Rise
Gate is all we need.
The perfect opportunity.
With all the effort they've
put into building that gate,
they believe it to
be their salvation.
Little do they realize, it is
in fact their destruction.
[DOUMA] We couldn't dream
of a more perfect cover,
but the key is what happens
directly afterward.
[DOUMAN] The light of the
capital will fade to darkness.
But will they really move
as you say they will?
[DOUMA]
Don't worry.
Just proceed with the plan
as I've explained it.
Now go.
[DOUMAN]
Yes.
[DOUMA] The die has been cast,
the result already determined.
[RAIKOU] So I thought
of you, Miss Shikibu.
[IZUMI]
Just Izumi, please.
[RAIKOU]
Right, Izumi.
I thought you might know.
[IZUMI] You need a method to
remove not a curse, but a seal.
I'm afraid that's
not my expertise.
Why don't you just ask Seimei?
She hasn't happened to
come by here, has she?
Are you saying she's
not come home?
Yes.
Well.
Would you like me to pass
on a message to her?
No.
Please don't tell
her I was here.
[SEIMEI]
That stupid Raikou.
He looked rather
troubled to me.
Such a fragile expression
on his face.
[SEIMEI]
He's so dutiful.
And it's suffocating him.
[IZUMI]
I'm not sure I understand.
How is that such a bad thing?
He may be a knight,
but he is still a human.
He needs a life outside
of saving people.
[IZUMI] So you think he
should take things easier?
He's constantly sticking
his neck out for others
and tightening a
noose around it.
It won't be long before
he stops breathing.
Raikou has a ways to go
before he understands the
weight of his own life.
[IZUMI]
Lost within my thoughts,
fireflies seem like my forlorn
soul leaving my body,
forever lost in the night.
Confusing your soul
with fireflies?
I suppose that's what enough
worrying can do to you.
[IZUMI]
Well,
a human would be an empty
vessel without the soul.
You really should tell him
your feelings, you know.
Raikou's not the
only one at risk
of losing the fireflies
of his soul.
Oh, be quiet!
He won't listen
to anything I say!
And quit saying fireflies,
it makes me think of b-b-b--
[IZUMI]
You mean butterflies?
Don't say it!
[IZUMI] Fine, if you insist,
but you owe me for that haiku.
I am not payin' for that!
[OFFICERS murmur]
You have all done
an admirable job.
Abe no Haruaki will
place the barrier
during tomorrow's inauguration,
and afterward, the Rise Gate
will finally be complete.
You should feel quite proud.
It's an honor.
I cannot think of
a more noble task
than helping to construct
the object that will protect
the capital and our
families from disaster.
[KINTOU]
Indeed.
Michinaga would like
to say a few words.
[MICHINAGA]
For the greater good.
[ALL]
Hear, hear!
[MICHINAGA]
Haruaki, show them just once.
That is not wise.
It is too risky,
the preparations are
not yet complete.
[MICHINAGA] It'll be fine.
They deserve to see.
If that is your wish,
I'll do it.
[chanting, yells]
[grunts]
[CARPENTERS murmur]
It's utterly dazzling!
[CARPENTER B] The capital is
guaranteed to be safe now!
[HARUAKI] I'm sorry, but that's
the most I can do tonight.
A truly impressive
feat, Haruaki.
I do believe tonight
calls for a celebration!
[BOTH gasp]
[YASUNORI] I won't leave things
like this. Abe no Haruaki.
[DOUMAN] Michinaga seems to only
rely on the skills of Haruaki.
[YASUNORI] Wha... Who said
that? I recognize you!
[DOUMAN] At this rate, your
family's name will be forgotten.
Speak no more!
[DOUMAN]
You must hate Haruaki,
but that hatred can become
your greatest strength.
With it,
you can become something that
surpasses all Onmioji.
[YASUNORI]
You shut that mouth of yours!
[DOUMAN] And at long last,
the Raise Gate is complete.
You're the one who's responsible
for that, aren't you?
Oh, don't try to tell me
you didn't find that
gate to be an eyesore.
Now tell me, Kamo no Yasunori.
What will your name
mean to this world?
Dignity? Or chagrin?
Hatred is the only
power you have left.
Hate Haruaki with
all your might.
I do hate that
pompous bastard.
I will make him understand
what true strength is.
[laughs] Beautifully said!
[YASUNORI screams]
[growls]
[DOUMAN]
Now listen.
The spell I've placed on you.
It will allow you to pass
through the barrier
of the Light Palace.
And once you're inside,
you can devour as many
people as you wish.
[YASUNORI growls]
[DOUMAN] And of course, that
includes the loathsome Haruaki.
[YASUNORI growls]
[KINTOKI panting]
Hey, Raikou!
Have you seen that?
[RAIKOU]
Uh? What is it?
[CARPENTER C]
What's happening?
[HORROR 12A roars]
[CARPENTERS whimper]
[KINTOU]
And fire!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
It's too dangerous, you must
return to the Light Palace!
[YORINOBU]
Lord Michinaga,
please allow me to stay
behind and protect the Gate.
I'll allow it.
Get as far away as
you can! Hurry!
[YORINOBU]
Just hang on!
You're okay.
[yells]
Brother!
Careful, Yorinobu!
Whoa! What is that thing?
[HORROR A roars]
[CARPENTER D]
Please save us!
Get away from there!
I won't let you
destroy that gate!
[RAIKOU]
Stop!
Oh no! Ah!
Kintoki, Yorinobu,
help as many people
escape as you can.
I'll save the people
trapped inside!
That's reckless!
[KINTOKI] Raikou, you don't
even have your armor!
Hey, I've got a duty to perform.
[KINTOKI growls]
[RAIKOU] Ashiya Douman!
I should've known.
[DOUMAN] And so the feast
of darkness begins.
Look, don't even
worry about me.
Just save everyone you can.
[KINTOKI]
Wait!
[RAIKOU yells]
[DOUMAN] I'm afraid that
I need you to stay put.
[RAIKOU grunts]
[DOUMAN yells]
[RAIKOU groans]
Kintoki!
There you are.
Was this all an excuse
to drag me out here?
Seimei!
Why don't you leave old
patchwork face to me, all right?
I'll never grow accustomed to
seeing that exasperating light.
[SEIMEI]
Go!
Raikou!
[RAIKOU]
Everyone! Escape now!
Damn! There's no end to it!
[SEIMEI grunts]
[DOUMAN grunts]
[SEIMEI]
What is this?
Why isn't he fighting back?
He really is such a poor
excuse for a knight.
This ought to whip
him into shape.
[HORROR A roars]
[SEIMEI gasps]
[SEIMEI] Raikou!
You need to stop Douman!
[RAIKOU]
I'm on it!
I'm relieved to see you're safe.
Yes.
[KINTOU]
Please, go inside.
Close and seal the gates.
[SEIMEI] I've gotta stop
that thing. [yells]
[RAIKOU groaning]
Keep struggling,
there's no escape.
[grunts]
[RAIKOU]
Sei... mei...
[DOUMAN]
You sit still and watch.
[RAIKOU grunting]
[SEIMEI pants]
Damn you!
[DOUMAN] This seems like a good
time to bring things to an end.
[RAIKOU screams]
[DOUMAN]
Hm?
He's grown stronger.
I've toyed with
them for too long!
[DOUMAN grunts]
[RAIKOU yelps]
[DOUMAN laughs] Allow me to
put you out of your misery.
This is where we say goodbye.
[SEIMEI]
Raikou!
Dammit, Douman, you bastard!
You're welcome to
delay the death
of your precious Raiko
for as long as you want.
But you have to decide
between saving him or
the people around you.
You must choose one
and sacrifice the other.
Oh, such a difficult
predicament.
Seimei. What will you do?
Please.
Seimei.
[SEIMEI whimpers]
Just forget about me.
Save the people!
[SEIMEI gasping]
We can't just let him die!
Kiyome. no!
No, I can't.
Raikou!
Seimei, no!
[HORROR A roars]
[HARUAKI grunts]
[DOUMAN laughs]
[MEN groaning, screamin]
[HARUAKI]
How could we let this happen?
[SEIMEI]
Are you all right?
[RAIKOU]
Why did you save me?
How many died in my place?
Answer me, Seimei!
How many times do I have to tell
you that we can't save everyone?
[RAIKOU]
But we could have saved them!
How much will you
make me suffer?
[SEIMEI]
I saved you!
At what cost?
You chose me and you let
all of those people die.
Now we're responsible
for their deaths.
[RAIKOU]
This is the end.
[SEIMEI gasping]
[DOUMA] The things you love
are brimming with radiance.
Douma Houshi.
[DOUMA]
I wonder...
Is it even possible for
him to forgive this?
How could he ever
partner with you again?
[SEIMEI gasps]
I should have known
this has been your
plan all along.
To separate us, so you could
seal away the Golden Knight.
That's what you wanted,
wasn't it?!
[DOUMA] Perhaps you're beginning
to see the light, Seimei.
Finally.
Raikou. Oh, no.
[INARI A] When lost within
the pitch black darkness.
You must only wait for the
starlight of dawn to guide you.