Go, Kintoki.
Right, I'm on it!
He doesn't seem to be a Horror.
You look worse than ever.
If you continue down this path,
the darkness is bound
to consume you.
[laughing]
And that is precisely my wish.
Right there.
[SAMURAI gasping]
It appeared. We've finally
found the evil spirit
that's been plaguing the area.
[laughing]
[MAN]
My, such a fine sword.
I shall take it.
That sword belongs to me!
I believe that we should
let the sword itself
choose a worthy possessor.
Hah.
Oh, who will it choose?
[SAMURAI screaming]
Lovely. So exquisite. I adore
the way it's cracked right here.
[RAIKOU]
Seimei.
Hey, Seimei.
You mind your tone. So rude.
I'm clearly busy, Raikou.
I'd rather you not interrupt
when I'm in the
middle of something.
May I see that one
as well, please?
[RAIKOU]
Who was that guy earlier?
Ashiya Douman.
So then you do
actually know him?
Well, who is he?
A Makai Alchemist?
On second thought, this
one's not to my taste.
[gasps]
[OFFICER A] Should we fan out
and search the area?
Oh, Seimei. And how
are you this fine day?
Oh, how am I?
I'd say I'm not in the mood
to be intimidated or bullied.
And no, not even by the head
of the police magistrate
such as yourself, Kintou.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
[KINTOU]
No, not so fast.
I'd like to know when
you will finally relent
and accept the
affections of Michinaga.
You cannot simply disappear
and run away forever.
Look over there, sir.
[KINTOU]
Hm?
[SEIMEI]
Run away!
[SEIMEI laughs]
Hah. Just let her run.
We will eventually catch her.
The city is plagued by Horrors
and the police chase after me.
It's like the fools
don't even care.
[INARI A] Oh, but the same
could be said of you.
[gasps]
[INARI A]
Makai Alchemist Seimei,
you are summoned to
the Watchdog Center.
[SEIMEI]
Oh. Today's not a good day.
Hey. Wait. Hold on!
Oh, really? I see they
dragged you in as well, huh?
I assure you that
I am nothing like her.
There's no need for
you to ambush me.
[SEIMEI]
Ha.
It's been quite some time.
Dear Seimei. Raikou.
You must have
information on a Horror.
That's why you called us.
Why else would you
summon us here?
After all, that is the point of
this Eastern Watchdog Center.
[SEIMEI]
We've already been over this.
You keep offering me jobs,
but I don't have the
time to take them.
Is that so? Are you too busy
hunting Horrors on your own?
That's right.
The two of us do just fine
without your instruction.
You spend all your time
searching for strange items
for your collection.
[SEIMEI grumbles]
[INARI A]
Your reluctance is a problem.
This request was
specifically made
for the two of you after all.
--[RAIKOU] I accept!
--[SEIMEI] I refuse!
[growling]
[gasps]
Is tha-that what
I think? Say no.
Yes. A butterfly.
Please! Get it
off me! Right now!
Get it off! I'm begging you!
Oh, that's right.
I had forgotten that you
don't like butterflies.
I never said that!
I said I hate them!
Ugh! No! Its pollen's
gonna get in my mouth!
That is unfortunate.
Especially since there
are so many of them.
[SEIMEI yelping]
You're actually
resorting to torturing me?
[INARI A] It's fine if
you don't want the job.
You do seem quite busy.
No, I'll do it!
I'll do any job you want,
just make them go away!
Wonderful. You are
such a selfless child.
My name is Katsuragi
no Hisayori.
[KINTOKI] So you've
been assigned to study
as Raikou's apprentice?
I guess, technically, you
already are a Makai Knight, huh?
You just haven't inherited
your armor yet.
Do you think
you'll get it sooner
by shadowing your seniors?
Is that what you're hoping
to learn from him?
Well, of course.
I'm hoping to learn everything.
With your guidance.
Uh. Well, I-I still have quite
a long way to go myself.
I'm glad to hear
you realize it.
[RAIKOU grumbles]
Oh, no. I've heard the tales
of your great achievements.
You managed to summon
the Golden Armor.
And it was believed to
have been gone forever.
Well, that's not really as
amazing as it might sound.
It's everything I aspire to.
I need to inherit
my father's armor.
Oh, wow.
So your father was a
Makai Knight as well?
A little light.
We're already struggling to
put food on the table, y'know.
Yet the great senior has chosen
to add another to our budget.
Where is the alchemist?
[KINTOKI, RAIKOU gasp]
Whoa, whoa hey! Why don't
you have any clothes on?
I'm trying to make sure
none of that loathsome pollen
was left on my skin.
[RAIKOU]
The butterfly pollen?
Don't even say the name!
[RAIKOU yelps]
Oh, he's fine.
Could you wipe down
my back for me?
Huh? Yeah!
No, not you.
Oh, sorry, you were asking me?
[SEIMEI] So, Hisayori,
the Watchdog Center said
that you requested to
apprentice under us.
[HISAYORI]
Well, your renown precedes you.
Oh, is that all? Could it be
you're interested... in me?
No, ma'am. I wish to learn the
sword style of Master Raiko.
That so?
You're just another
idiot eager to fight
because it's the so-called
duty of a protector.
A protector? Not me.
I wish I could.
But I couldn't protect anyone.
[KINTOKI] There have been
a series of brutal attacks
on warriors who
possess famous swords.
A Horror?
Now that you mention swords,
yours is quite famous as well.
I was hoping that you might
allow me to take a look at it.
That one?
[RAIKOU] It's nothing special.
I've had it for a long time.
Have you, really?
Did you happen to inherit
it from your father?
[RAIKOU]
No. I did not.
I actually never knew the man.
I was abandoned as a child.
Outside the capital.
[IZUMI] Kahtsuragi no
Hisayori, that's his name?
[SEIMEI] I feel you're the
only one I can trust with this,
Miss Shikubi.
Oh, no, please. Call me Izumi.
I must say it's rare for you
to depend on me for anything.
I have a rather bad
feeling about this one.
[IZUMI]
Oh, yes, of course.
He's the son of
Katsuragi no Chiharu.
He was a Makai Knight,
a warrior devoted to
fighting evil spirits.
He was also suspected of taking
part in a rebellion in the East.
So I'm assuming he
escaped from the capital?
I'm scared, Father.
[CHIHARU] You mustn't be,
Hisayori. You must live on!
[IZUMI]
One step outside the capital,
and you're in a world
controlled by spirits.
It is written that Chiharu
died in this savage land.
[SEIMEI] Then the Makai
Knight father fell in battle.
And only his son returned
to the capital alive.
Life can be so tragic.
[gasps]
Well, if it isn't Seimei.
Minister of the Left.
Are you still not quite ready
to accept your place by my side.
[SEIMEI]
Oh, how you jest.
[YORINOBU] That woman just now,
do you know who she was?
Someone who lives by night.
Much like those evil spirits.
[MICHINAGA] She was actually
born of high status.
Such a waste.
She chose to surround
herself with darkness.
Our informants told
me she came here
to speak with Izumi
Shikibu about the West.
Yes, of course she did.
--[thud]
--[KINTOKI] Who's there?
[HISAYORI gasps]
What do you think
you're doing in here?!
[RAIKOU]
Kintoki!
Raikou, quick, there's a thief!
It's you, Hisayori.
I don't understand.
[laughing]
That sword. It belonged
to my father.
[RAIKOU]
Your father?
My father is dead.
He was murdered.
The fact you hold his sword
is proof you're his murderer!
[RAIKOU]
That can't be.
Careful, Raikou.
He's become a Horror.
Did you hear me?
I know that you killed
him, you bastard!
[SEIMEI] To think an
apprentice Makai Knight
could be possessed by a Horror.
There's no way the
Watchdog Center was unaware.
They looked the other way
and dumped this burden on us
to deal with.
It sure would've
been nice of them
to have given us some kind of
a warning, but here we are.
[SEIMEI] Come, Raikou,
let's take care of him.
What's the matter?
I need to know.
How'd I get this sword?
Good question.
Definitely worth asking.
[RAIKOU] What if he's right?
What if I did do it?
I may have murdered his father.
Are you entirely certain
this child is his son?
[KINTOKI]
Yes.
Even though he's the first-born,
he was exiled from the capital.
Along with his mother.
We couldn't save them.
We tried, but there was
nothing that we could do.
The descendant of
a Makai Knight.
Let's hope we're lucky enough
to find him still alive.
Look. A Horror.
Not quite.
[growling]
I demand that you reveal
your true form to me!
Horror?
[SEIMEI] They flocked and
attacked in hopes of a feast,
like moths to a flame.
[SEIMEI] And what is this food
that would attract so many?
Show yourself!
[KINTOKI]
It can't be!
He must've subconsciously
summoned the Golden Armor.
And he's managed to survive.
Unless, the armor has chosen
to protect this child.
[SEIMEI]
The Madou Ring.
I am Zaruba. Who stands
alongside the Golden Knight.
The longer a Makai
Knight dons their armor,
the greater the danger.
[ZARUBA] The armor might
consume their body and soul,
preventing them from returning
to their original form.
A lost soul beast.
But this child was able
to maintain his humanity?
He is a chosen child.
It is decided.
He will be my Makai Knight.
[RAIKOU] I have no
recollection of that time.
A legion of Horrors attacked me,
and I was on the verge of
becoming one of them myself.
There's a chance I might've
killed Hisayori's father.
And what difference would it
make if you had killed him?
To begin with,
you don't even know
if that sword actually
belonged to his father.
It's never wise to believe
the word of a Horror.
So then, what will you do?
I'll return his father's
sword to him. That's what.
Remember, he is a Horror.
It would be pointless for you
to return a sentimental
keepsake to him.
He lost his father.
And surrounded by Horrors,
his only chance for survival
was to become one himself.
I was just like him.
If you hadn't found me...
Enough feeling
sorry for yourself.
On your feet!
You won't return it?!
Then I suppose we'll have to
leave the decision to the sword.
Who's the rightful owner?
Who's it going to be?
Who will you choose?
Hisayori, your old master's son?
Or Raiko, the very
man who murdered him?
[RAIKOU]
If the sword does have a will,
it will know the
truth, and then...
You better not be thinking
something so stupid
as to actually let a sword
make this decision.
I'm sorry, but I will not
allow you to do that, Raikou.
That choice is not
yours to make.
I decide whether
you live or die.
[RAIKOU] I'm the only one
who controls my life.
It would seem that the sword
has chosen to take your life!
[yelling]
Listen to my words, sword.
I've been held captive
by the darkness.
And that is why I now
yearn for the light.
So I'm asking you...
...help me to
protect that light!
[gasps]
Looks like the sword
knows what it's doing.
It chose Raikou!
But, Father... how could you?
How could you?!
Seimei.
Don't you start
ordering me around.
Zaruba!
[roars]
[yelling]
[HISAYORI]
Father... I'm sorry.
[yelling]
[OLD MAN] This Golden Knight
you encountered, Raikou.
Minamotono Yorimitsu
is his birth name.
Yorimitsu?
[OLD MAN]
You two have much in common.
You're both cursed children.
[SEIMEI] Oh, look at this.
It's absolutely splendid!
[KINTOKI retches]
[ZARUBA]
Katsuragi no Chiharu.
Obviously. I can see
the family resemblance.
[SEIMEI chuckles]
This is the Makai Knight
who owned your sword.
I don't understand. What was he
doing with his father's skull?
Simply put, Hisayori
ate his father.
[gasps]
[SEIMEI] Hisayori was desperate
to escape his guilt.
So he convinced himself the one
who carried his father's sword
was the true killer.
[ZARUBA]
But the truth,
the sword came into
your possession
in order to defeat Hisayori.
You knew all along, didn't you?
I don't understand why
you wouldn't tell me.
I was starting to honestly
believe I had killed his father.
Hisayori became a Horror,
but you were strong
enough to resist.
And that is the only difference
between the two of you.
Don't act so surprised,
you're the one who said
you were the same.
On the path of a Makai Knight,
you'll have to continue to
hunt others just like you.
I needed to confirm
your resolve.
This woman worries for you
in her own complicated way.
As to why--
You talk too much.
[KINTOKI chuckles]
What's so funny?
[KINTOKI chuckling]
[SEIMEI]
Come on, out with it!
[KINTOKI]
No, no. It's nothing.
[SEIMEI]
And yet you keep laughing.
[INARI A] Creatures
gather toward the light.
Humans and insects,
they are both the same.
But is it the same desire
that drives them?