[YORINOBU gasps]
Douman's alive. Do you see?
That's impossible!
[DOUMAN]
I am the darkness.
Killing me's not so easy.
Kintoki, I'm so sorry.
I don't think I'll be able to
do my job and keep you alive.
Don't sweat it, Yorinobu.
We got Seimei back.
[YORINOBU, KINTOKI grunt]
[DOUMAN yelling]
[BOTH gasp]
[YORINOBU, KINTOKI grunt]
Huh?!
[SEIMEI]
Thinking back now,
all this time, we were
both so stubborn.
We're not just related,
we're the same person.
Grandfather. I love you.
[SEIMEI]
Well, let's go.
[HARUAKI] Promise me that
you'll take care of Kiyome.
[RAIKOU]
I would die for her.
[bird caws]
[KAGUYA gasps]
Hey, what's wrong?
Talent is not wiliness.
[DOUMAN]
Heh.
Douman!
[DOUMAN grunts]
Watch out!
[RAIKOU grunts]
[SEIMEI gasping]
No!
Come back! [grunts]
[gasps]
[RAIKOU grunts]
[SEIMEI growls]
[chanting]
[grunts]
[RAIKOU] So now what?
We can't just sit here!
[KINTOKI] But we don't even
know where Douman went!
Then let's find out!
[SEIMEI]
Calm down!
We'll get him, but we
have to do this right.
[KAGUYA]
No.
[ALL gasp]
[KAGUYA]
No, please, don't do it.
Kaguya, what's wrong?
It's Rudra.
Douman will release it.
I release you... Rudra!
[DOUMAN] We will finally
join together as one,
and your power will
become my power!
We'll move on the capital.
The Light Palace.
And then, I'll snuff out all
the light in this entire world!
I will cover creation
in total darkness!
[CROWD chattering]
[DOUMAN] Heh. Go ahead!
Show them your true form!
[INARI A]
We have failed to stop it.
The moon's a giant monster! Ah!
It's happening again.
[YORINOBU gasps]
[RUDRA roars]
So that's it.
[SEIMEI]
Rudra!
[KINTOKI whimpers]
[growls]
[MICHINAGA] So this is
your end game, Brother.
Very well. But I will not let
you destroy the Light Palace.
It will remain mine.
We can still stop Rudra,
but we must act now!
[SEIMEI] You've saved
Raikou's life more than once.
And you've also saved mine.
You've done more
than enough, Kaguya.
Stopping this Horror is
a job for the three of us.
Let's go!
But Seimei.
How're we supposed
to fight that thing?
We'll find a way!
[SEIMEI]
Grandfather, protect us.
[DOUMAN laughing]
I'm sorry to have kept
you waiting, Rudra.
But now I will take your
strength and make it my own.
[HORRORS growling]
[roars]
[RUDRA roars]
It's going to kill us all!
[CROWD screaming]
I'll try to distract
that thing.
Don't bother fighting back,
get the people out!
Save as many women and
children as you can!
[MAGISTRATE S]
Yes, sir!
My Lord, we have a problem.
[YORINOBU]
Mm?
[CROWD shouting]
Is the Light Palace just
going to leave them all
out there to die?!
That's despicable!
We'll hold the line out here.
You just try to get
that gate open!
Right.
Leave it to me.
--[MAN 22C] Open the damn gate!
--[MAN 22D] We'll burn alive!
[WOMAN 22A]
At least take my baby!
Don't you dare threaten me!
Now get off of these steps!
If you don't open up, you're
no better than that monster!
I've no choice, my Lord.
We've got strict orders not
to allow commoners inside!
[YORINOBU] This is a matter
of life or death!
If you want to plead their case,
you'll have to do
it to Michinaga.
[YORINOBU]
Then move.
[SERVANT 22A] My Lord, wait,
you can't go in uninvited!
Please!
Please.
I beg my Lord, the great
and wise Michinaga...
Please. Hear my plea during
this time of crisis.
Let the people shelter here.
I will pledge you my life
defending the Capital,
in exchange for
granting me this--
[MICHINAGA]
This is the Capital.
[gasps]
All I consider to be the
Capital is this Palace.
And it is very well-protected.
No matter its size,
no Horror will ever break
through the magic barrier.
Outside these walls are nothing
but insects trying to crawl
toward that light.
I say, let the Horror
save me the trouble
of having to squash them myself.
Although. I will, of course,
allow you to stay here.
As long as you're behind
these walls, you will live.
[YORINOBU]
He's gone insane.
[CROWD screaming]
Let's go! Everyone, keep moving
to the Light Palace!
But the Suzaku Gate
is still closed tight!
You cannot lose
faith in Yorinobu!
He'll get that gate open,
I'm sure of it!
[gasps]
C'mon, don't make me
look like a fool!
[KANEHIRA]
Huh?
[RUDRA roars]
Douman!
He's become one with that thing?
What now, Raikou?
Well...
I'll cut his ties
to the darkness,
and push away the shadows!
[RUDRA roars]
[RAIKOU grunts]
Wow, Seimei.
Where'd you get that thing?
A little parting gift
I took from Rudra.
He didn't realize he left this
behind as he was pushed out.
And it's pretty fun
using it against him.
You have all the luck!
[BOTH gasp]
[RUDRA'S LEFT ARM roars]
[KINTOKI]
Ah!
[KINTOKI yelps, screams]
[RUDRA'S LEFT ARM roaring]
Kintoki!
[whimpering, screaming]
[RAIKOU yells]
[RAIKOU] Kintoki, you still
alive down there?
Yeah, never better.
[RUDRA roars]
[SEIMEI, RAIKOU grunt]
[SEIMEI]
I know what to do.
Rudra's too big for us to defeat
from down on the ground.
So use her!
[RAIKOU] Circle around, so I can
try to find it's blind side!
Here goes!
[RAIKOU]
I count 12 faces.
There's no way to
get the drop on it.
Raikou... this sure is fun.
[RAIKOU]
What was that?
Nothin'. Just thinkin' out loud.
[KINTOKI] It took a giant
monster for things
to finally feel normal again.
It's been so long since the
three of us fought together,
I love it.
[gasps]
[RAIKOU] We'll have to destroy
each face, one-by-one.
Dive!
Aye-aye!
[RAIKOU yells]
Nothing makes me happier
than that war cry!
[RAIKOU yelling]
[RUDRA roars]
One down, 11 to go!
Yorinobu, it's too
dangerous out there.
If you leave now,
you'll surely die!
Open this gate right now!
[MAGISTRATES gasping]
Let the people in!
The Light Palace will save
them from that Horror!
This is an order from the
merciful Minister of the Left.
Fujiwara no Michinaga.
Now move quickly,
there isn't much time!
I said open this gate!
Those traitors!
[MICHINAGA growling]
[MICHINAGA screams]
Fools. There is nothing
I'm incapable of doing.
And I will take back my palace.
[AIDE 22A]
Minister Michinaga! My Lord.
That filthy horde of commoners
has gotten as far as the
Pine Grove of Banquets!
It's Yorinobu.
Kill him... like
the rat that he is.
Yes!
[MICHINAGA]
Those dirty commoners
are doing what the Horrors
could never do...
Violating the sanctity of
my beautiful Light Palace!
And for this, they will pay.
[MICHINAGA]
People of the capital!
Thank you for
assembling in peace.
I assure you all that the
giant monster outside
cannot reach us here!
Because of that, I'm
allowing you all to stay
the night until the
threat has subsided.
Watch our victory unfold,
thanks to this great warrior!
My friend and ally,
the Golden Makai Knight!
He will kill this Horror
and free us from its
evil once and for all!
So do not be afraid.
Everything is under control.
Our culture and way of life--
this great city will be safe.
Until the end of time!
[CROWD cheering]
[YORINOBU]
I'm such a fool.
I never realized I
served such a lying,
opportunistic,
despicable man!
[gasps]
[MICHINAGA]
Heh.
[MAGISTRATE 22A]
The traitor!
[MAGISTRATE 22A groans]
Dammit!
[RUDRA roars]
We're never gonna
kill him this way.
We need to come up with
a new plan of attack!
[RUDRA'S RIGHT ARM roars]
[SEIMEI gasps]
Oh, no!
[SEIMEI groaning]
[KINTOKI]
Seimei!
Idiot!
You shouldn't have
bothered catching me!
Wait, whaddaya mean?
It's easier for him to kill us
if we're all huddled
in one place!
Our numbers are the only
advantage we've--
[KINTOKI]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[RUDRA roars]
[RAIKOU]
What are you doing?!
I'll buy you time by trapping
Rudra with my powers!
Ah!
[RAIKOU]
Kaguya!
[RUDRA roars]
[KAGUYA gasping]
[RAIKOU]
Kaguya! Are you okay?
That fall was nothing.
After all, I'm a Maudou Tool.
If ardent longing is not
the same as greediness--
[gasps]
C'mon, hurry up!
What's taking so long?
I can't watch anymore!
[ANCESTOR] Your name is Kaguya,
the one who seals Rudra.
The 12 lines carved into you,
represent the 12
parts of a spell
which will cut Rudra's
12 ties to darkness,
banishing him from Earth.
This darkness comes
from deep within man.
For this reason, I must give you
this spell to use against it.
Its words will prevent Rudra
from tapping into that power
and returning to this realm.
Now, my child,
now is the time to do
what you're born to do,
and seal Rudra within
the Crimson Moon.
[KAGUYA] Resistance is
not panicked struggle.
I know what they're for!
I remember the spell!
[RAIKOU]
What?
All of those mantra-like phrases
I've been mumbling, lately...
they are the spell
to seal it away!
There should be 12.
Twelve phrases, in total.
Which means I have
to remember two more.
[RUDRA roars]
[RAIKOU]
Yasusuke!
--[SEIMEI] The Silver Knight?
--[KINTOKI] Yeah, all right!
Sorry for making you wait.
Hello, friend.
Took you long enough.
[INARI A] Well, our Silver
Knight showed up after all.
[INARI B]
At the end of the day,
the Silver Knight is not one
to back down from a job.
[INARI C] All that's left
for him to do now
is tell Kaguya what he knows.
[INARI A] And with those
phrases on her tongue,
she will regain her
full powers at last.
Yasuske's done quite
well for someone
whose previous job was a thief.
Though I worry that this time
we may be cutting it
a little too close.
[RAIKOU] Rudra no longer
possesses Seimei.
[YASUSUKE] I know, I gathered
that. That's why I came here.
With Rudra in his true form,
I can get some real revenge
for my brother's death.
If the fate of the world
wasn't at stake,
I would take a moment
just to hug you.
Heh. I remember that dry wit.
You're definitely Seimei again.
Kaguya, I have this for you.
Haduaki requested I bring it
from the Watchdog Center.
[KAGUYA gasping]
[RUDRA roars]
I now remember all 12
parts of the spell.
Rudra!
[roaring]
With these words,
I know once more
who I am and what I must do!
I am a Madou Tool, and will
seal you away with my powers!
[YASUSUKE, RAIKOU]
Let's go!
--[SEIMEI] Yeah!
--[KINTOKI] Right!
[INARI A]
Connecting feelings.
The eyes gaze intently.
Far and deep toward
the distant tomorrow.