[RAIKOU]
Wait!
[YASUSUKE]
Move, Raikou! Or else!
[RAIKOU]
Yasusuke, listen!
Seimei is drowning in darkness,
but she can still be saved!
She just needs my help!
[YASUSUKE]
You're in denial!
This is for murdering
my brother!
[DARK SEIMEI gasps]
[YASUSUKE]
All right. You win.
I'll stop trying to kill her.
I make that vow as a
fellow Makai Knight.
But, in exchange, stopping
Seimei falls on you. Deal?
[RAIKOU grunts]
[DOUMAN]
Rudra's resurrection is near.
[INARI A]
The preparations are complete.
Inform Haruaki at once.
[KINTOKI]
You guys, look!
Uh!
Haruaki!
Raikou!
Now. We're ready!
[gasps]
Go fetch Kaguya, and
bring her to my house!
[DARK SEIMEI grunts]
[laughs]
[RAIKOU groans]
What's wrong, Golden Knight?
Finally lost the will to fight?
[RAIKOU grunting]
Did you really think you
could get away that easily?
[gasps]
Why is she here?
[DARK SEIMEI gasping]
[DARK SEIMEI groans]
Stop! Let me go!
What's going on here?
You're really trying to defeat
me with these parlor tricks?!
Oh, it was never my plan
to defeat you in this form.
What does that mean?! [grunting]
Quickly, Haruaki.
It won't hold for long.
[HARUAKI grunts]
You old fool.
What are you up to?!
Are you prepared for this?
Yes.
[RAIKOU] You want me to go
inside Seimei's heart?
[HARUAKI]
That's correct.
Since Rudra is bound
to Kiyome's spirit now,
that's how we attack it.
[BOTH gasp]
And you, who Kiyome trusts
more than anybody else,
are the only one who will
be able to enter her heart.
However, if you should fail,
then I'm afraid that you
too will never return.
In which case...
[YORINOBU gasping]
I'll do it.
But Raikou, wait!
Don't worry. I promise I'll
make it back, with Seimei.
All right, then I'm
going with you!
There's no need.
What, why not?!
[RAIKOU]
Listen.
I know I don't have
a ton of experience.
I only just learned to
don the armor on my own.
But still, despite all that,
I would like to bring some honor
to the Golden Knight lineage.
So please, just let me do this.
Gallantry is not arrogance.
Whatever you say, Raikou.
[HARUAKI]
Actually, there is something
that you can do, Kintoki.
Great!
In fact, we're going to
need the combined strength
of everyone here.
[DARK SEIMEI whimpers]
[groaning]
[HARUAKI coughing]
Oh, no!
[YORINOBU]
Are you all right?
[HARUAKI]
Kiyome.
[groans]
Seimei.
[gasps]
Uh...
[RAIKOU]
Seimei!
Hey! Can you hear me?
[SEIMEI gasping]
Seimei, it's me!
[SEIMEI]
Rai... kou.
[gasps] Raikou, is...?
It is you!
You came for me... [gasps]
[gasping]
[groaning]
Just hold still!
[SEIMEI gasping]
You all right?
[SEIMEI]
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry about it. Okay?
We all know you didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
Can you stand?
Uh... yeah.
[RAIKOU] Sorry it took
so long to save you.
Grandfather...
[RAIKOU]
Yeah. He's waiting for you.
[SEIMEI]
So then, he didn't tell Raikou.
Come on. Let's go.
[SEIMEI]
Thank you for coming to...
[RAIKOU]
Mm?
[RAIKOU grunts]
[SEIMEI gasps]
[DARK SEIMEI]
Golden Knight.
[BOTH gasp]
I won't give up my vessel.
Rudra!
It's fine.
I'll be the one to
save you this time.
As the Golden Knight.
Thanks, Raikou.
And also, hopefully, as
your Makai Knight, Seimei.
[DARK SEIMEI] Well now you're
just showing off, aren't you?
[RAIKOU grunts]
[screams]
[KINTOKI]
What's happening?
He's fighting off
the darkness....
[KINTOKI]
Hm?
...within her.
[DOUMAN]
Oh, you old fool.
Do you see?
She moves on her own
even when I'm not looking.
Although she's still incomplete.
He finally arrived.
All right. That's my cue.
Boy, have you already forgotten
how you were beaten
half to death?
[KINTOKI]
Yeah, things are different now!
[yells]
[KINTOKI grunts]
[KINTOKI yells]
You have learned
absolutely nothing!
[KINTOKI groans]
I promise you there's no
way I'll lose this time!
Oh, how sad.
Guess I'll have to break that
promise with your bones.
[RAIKOU grunting]
[DARK SEIMEI grunting]
[DARK SHIKI DOLL]
Shiki, shiki!
[RAIKOU grunts]
What?! But how?!
What's going on here?!
[SEIMEI] This may be
hard for you to grasp.
See, you're inside of me.
And here, my feelings are
in control of everything.
The darkness ate away at me
thanks to Douma Houshi's curse.
Until I felt alone in the world,
leaving my heart vulnerable.
Fragile.
Enough that a Horror like you
could enter and take over.
Fully infecting me. But now...
The light has returned
to me once again.
I can feel it inside me.
What are you
trying to tell me?
[SEIMEI] Here, I'll make
it simple for you.
You get the hell out of
my body right now!
[DARK SEIMEI groaning]
[DARK SEIMEI screaming]
[DARK SEIMEI]
I'll kill you, Garo!
[DARK SEIMEI screams]
[KINTOKI screams]
[DOUMAN growls]
It can't be!
[KINTOKI] See, I don't have
to actually beat you myself.
[DOUMAN]
Huh?
If I can just hold you off long
enough, well, y'know, we win.
[DOUMAN]
You pests!
You obnoxious little parasites!
No more games!
I swear, I'm going to kill you
all, right here, right now!
You did it, Raikou.
I'm proud of you.
[DOUMAN]
Hm?
Kintoki. You have done well.
Now it is my turn to help.
I won't let you die!
Uh?!
[DOUMAN]
There's no escaping me, rat!
I've grown tired of your tricks.
[gasps]
[DOUMAN growls]
[KINTOKI groans]
[DOUMAN] Now you just wait there
until it's your turn to die.
This is inevitable.
All that's left is to
create another path.
[coughs]
Oh, no, Haruaki!
[HARUAKI] I'm fine!
Don't let your guard down!
Hold on to Kiyome!
Well, I commend you for
making it this far, old man.
[HARUAKI]
Douman!
But I will kill you,
and eliminate the Golden Knight
along with the vessel's body.
[DOUMAN]
So that's how it is.
[HARUAKI groaning]
[DOUMAN] In that case, you're
coming with me, Abe no Haruaki!
[gasps]
What the...?
[yells]
[INARI A] My, my,
what a persistent fellow.
[KINTOKI gasping]
[KINTOKI]
Inari!
[INARI B] Hey, get your act
together, little bean!
[INARI C] Our superiors have
reprimanded us because of you.
Don't get in my way!
You took the words right out
of my mouth... you cretin.
It's all gone
according to plan.
Just as Haruaki said.
But if we lose now,
then everything until this point
will have been for naught.
[DOUMAN growls]
Oh, what a terrifying
face to behold.
[INARIS chanting]
[yells]
[exhales]
[DOUMAN grunts]
[DOUMAN screams]
Whoa. Amazing.
[INARI A] The little bean's
so easily impressed.
[KINTOKI gasps]
The only thing we did was
catch him off guard,
then swat him away.
That's it.
Once those two return,
then our task here will
have been completed.
What you do next is
entirely up to you.
[HARUAKI chanting]
[HARUAKI panting]
It's okay, I've got you.
How's Kiyome? Is she--?
She's safe.
Kaguya.
Yes.
Promise me, Golden Knight.
Anything.
Promise me that you'll
take care of Kiyome.
[RAIKOU] What do you mean?
What's wrong?
Hey, Haruaki!
Haruaki, wake up!
He... can't be.
[SEIMEI]
Taizan Fukun.
[RAIKOU grunts]
Seimei!
It's an onmyou spell
typically used
to call back the
souls of the dead.
It can be quite powerful.
However, though, you must
pay a price of equal value.
What kind of price?
It means that, in order for
him to bring me back here,
he had to become the
vessel in exchange.
[RAIKOU gasps]
[SEIMEI cries]
[crying continues]
[HARUAKI]
Kiyome.
[SEIMEI gasps]
Now's not the time for
you to be crying.
Grandfather.
Yes, yes.
After all, you've finally
been returned to me.
I'm so, so sorry.
There's no reason to be sorry.
I'm your grandfather.
That's what I'm there for.
I know that it was your spell.
You helped me keep the darkness
at bay and hold on to myself.
Well, at least as
much as I could.
That's why I was able to
last until Raikou came.
Twas the least I could do for
my beloved granddaughter.
If I hadn't done it,
well then, I never would've
been able to face
your mother and father
in the next life.
[SEIMEI cries]
Please, Kiyome, thank
the others for me.
[SEIMEI sobs]
I will.
[HARUAKI] Now, you know
what you have to do.
I can't.
[HARUAKI]
You must. Use the power
of the Golden Knight to
destroy what's inside me.
I can't!
My goodness.
You haven't changed a bit,
have you, child?
You're as stubborn as ever.
I... can't.
Kiyome, can you smile
one last time?
Please, won't you
do that for me?
[SEIMEI crying]
Lovely.
Hey, Grandfather!
[SEIMEI laughing]
I love you, Grandfather.
No!
If life is not just an illusion,
then death is not oblivion.
[SEIMEI crying]
[SEIMEI cries]
Now, Rudra's inside his body.
Raikou... please...
slay my grandfather.
Haruaki, why?
He gave his own life to
bring all this to an end.
I see. Then it will all be over.
[YORINOBU gasps]
[INARI A] A beast awakened
and a heart tested.
The final trial is upon us.
As the Crimson Moon
grows redder and redder.