[WOMAN A]
Excuse me, sir,
you're Watanabe no Tsuna, right?
[TSUNA]
Mm?
[WOMAN A] Minamoto no Mitsunaka
entered the priesthood
and now you follow him
under his new name
of Tada no Shinbochi, correct?
[TSUNA]
Spirit!
[growls]
And you're not an ordinary
spirit, are you?
Horror!
The Minamoto family,
they come from an ancient
bloodline of Makai Knights.
Unfortunately for you,
as their loyal servant,
I have learned a few things.
[WOMAN 8A]
Tada no Shinbochi.
He tossed his first wife and
son outside the capital
to ensure his rise to power
within the priesthood.
[TSUNA] Wha...? H-How
could you know that?
[WOMAN 8A]
I also know that Shinbochi
is now knocking on death's door.
Even if he successfully crosses
to the other world,
the darkness of his past
will return to ravage his soul!
Silence!
[roars]
[TSUNA grunting]
It's a retainer's job to cut
his master's ties to the past!
[MEN laughing]
[TSUNA] All it took was
one slash from my blade!
And she vanished!
Though not without leaving
me a little souvenir!
[MEN laugh]
[slurping]
[YORINOBU yawns]
Tsuna, what's going on?
[TSUNA] Perfect timing,
my lord yorinobu!
Come have a drink with us!
And behold this prize--
Uh... Where did that
thing's arm go?
[SERVANT B gasping]
[SERVANT A]
What are they?!
[YORINOBU'S MOM screams]
Mother!
[YORINOBU]
Are you all right?!
Oh, Yorinobu!
[YORINOBU gasps]
[TSUNA gasps]
[YORINOBU]
Did they hurt you?!
[SERVANT B] How many arms
did that thing have?!
Just two.
And I only cut off one
and brought that one back!
[yelps]
Ah! Get it off me!
Shinbochi!
[SHINBOCHI gasping]
Father!
It's gone.
These arms must be
some sort of spirit!
[SHINBOCHI groaning]
Forgive me, Yorimitsu.
Who's that?
You've said that name before.
Father, who's Yorimits--
[MALE SERVANT B grunts]
[TSUNA exhales]
[YORINOBU'S MOM grunts]
Tsuna. Mother?!
[RAIKOU'S MOM] You must
be strong, and endure.
Please Raikou.
Do not blame them.
The Light Palace or your father.
[RAIKOU] But we're gonna freeze
to death out here, Mother.
Why would father do this?
To his own family!
[RAIKOU'S MOM]
Oh, Raikou.
--[HORRORS growl]
--[RAIKOU gasps]
[RAIKOU yells]
[KINTOKI] I'm sorry, I couldn't
fight off the hunger anymore!
I used our savings
to buy a rice cake
and I ate it alone in shame!
But I got paid in potatoes for
helping the vegetable cart guy.
They're behind the shelf.
Take them! Take them all!
It's my penance!
All your sins involve food.
[exhales]
Did you have a dream
about a girl?
I heard your moaning
through the whole house!
Um. Good day!
Miss Seimei? Are you here?
[SEIMEI]
Oh, my!
I don't know where to start!
All these fried sweets you
brought look delicious!
But, such quality
is to be expected
from the young master
of the Genji Family.
Thank you for lunch! Ha!
I've seen this Shiki before
at the Light Palace.
It's Professor Haduaki's.
The Onmyouji, or perhaps
I'm mistaken on that.
Yeah, well.
Due to various circumstances
I won't go into,
it's my Shiki now.
So tasty!
Hey, don't eat them all!
But Yorinobu gave them
as a gift to me.
Isn't that right?
Uh... Heh...
This guy's so weak.
She gets flirty and he
melts into a puddle.
This is what happens
when a pretty palace boy
meets a girl who lives
life on the open road.
Yep.
Yorinobu will be coddled
from the crib to the grave.
I'm glad you agree.
[RAIKOU]
So one of his retainers
encountered a Horror
the other day,
and took her arm.
What's with all these
aristocrats attracting spirits?
Seimei, would you please
help my family?
Not only do you have a
reputation for beauty,
but for fighting
evil spirits as well.
On top of that, you are the
granddaughter of Abe no Haruaki.
No.
Seimei! How can you say that
after eating all the
treats he brought you?!
No, and that's final!
Raikou could get all
weird if we help him.
His family house, remember?
Right. I almost forgot!
Well, it's getting late.
No adventuring for us.
Let's table this talk for now.
[RAIKOU]
I'll help you.
[ALL]
Uh?!
Why're you acting weird?
There's a Horror to fight.
Well, no, hold on.
It might be a big slug
that looks like an arm.
Oh, that sounds so terrifying!
But it also sounds
like pest control,
and that's really not our job.
What are you two
even talking about?
If I want to help
him, I'm helping!
I wanted Seimei and the chance
to spend time with her.
Instead, I get him.
[RAIKOU]
I can hear you.
He's got bigger
problems than a spirit
if he thinks she's
so great. Look--
[YORINOBU]
So, about this--
Yorinobu, you are
quite obsessed.
There's nothing between
me and Seimei, all right?
We share a house,
but not a room or bed.
[YORINOBU]
It's not about her! I just...
I have a question about
your Golden Armor.
Yeah? What's that?
[YORINOBU] Forget it.
Let's go see my father.
[gasps]
[TSUNA]
Wait, did you say Raikou?
Are you sure that's
not a mistake?
[SERVANT A]
Yes.
He's a young man that
Yorinobu has asked to help
with the Horror.
I thought it was
impossible, too.
But we've seen Kintoki with him.
[SERVANT B] You know, we used to
call the young Lord Yorimitsu
Raikou as a nickname.
Yes, I'm aware, but there's
no way he's still alive.
Unless... he's a Horror?
That could explain
our master's illness.
Yorimitsu has returned
as an evil spirit,
and has cast a revenge
spell on Shinbochi.
That must be it!
[YORINOBU]
Tsuna, I'm back!
And I have someone
who can help.
That man there has served
my family for years.
Watanabe no Tsuna.
I see.
Finally, you come forward!
This is Raikou.
He has great experience
with evil spirits.
He'll solve our problem.
I assume he knows
much of Horrors.
Much indeed.
That face! It's him!
Yes, it has to be the
same Raikou we exiled.
[RAIKOU'S MOM] Don't banish
us from the capital!
The accusations are false!
Please tell him again that
I've not cursed anyone!
[RAIKOU groans]
Uh! Tsuna!
What was that for?!
[TSUNA]
Stand up!
If you resist,
I'll beat you harder!
[DOUMAN]
Oh.
I followed the Darkness I
felt and I ended up here.
And what an interesting show.
I must make sure that
no one interferes
with how things are unfolding.
[INARI A]
I see, so...
Raiko went to the House
of Shinbochi alone.
Seimei.
Why did you not tag-along with
him to keep an eye on things?
When he visits Shinbochi
we risk him remembering,
things from his past
that neither he, nor us,
want him to remember.
If Raikou were to somehow
overcome the seal
you've placed on him, he'd
lose control of his power.
And I'm afraid that we, well,
we wouldn't be able to--
We cannot turn a blind eye!
No, we cannot!
[KINTOKI]
They got a point, Seimei!
What in the world
were you thinking?
[SEIMEI]
I guess I just wanted to see.
That's all, really.
[KINTOKI]
Oh, yeah? See what?
[SEIMEI] I wanted to
see how Raikou reacts
when confronted with
the scars of his past.
Does he have the strength
to overcome them on his own?
I want to believe he does.
Deep in my heart. I can feel it.
[KINTOKI]
Yeah, but--
[INARI A]
No matter what you "feel,"
this is a risk we cannot take.
Because, if you sit this out,
we also risk letting
a Horror run free.
[SEIMEI groaning]
Fine! I'll help him!
Wow. Look how pretty they are!
Hurry, Seimei!
[KINTOKI yelps]
[SEIMEI gasps]
[BOTH yelp]
What the...?
Seems we got carried away
by an alchemist's spell.
And there's only one man
who can pull that off.
Well, if it isn't
our old friend.
Douman.
I won't let you meddle.
So, for now,
this will be your prison.
To be fair, my teacher doesn't
want me to meddle, either,
but things have gotten too
interesting for me not to.
Now, you two stay put
while I go see just what kind
of man this Raikou is.
[KINTOKI grunting]
[SEIMEI groaning]
[KINTOKI]
Seimei!
[DOUMAN chuckles]
[SEIMEI grunts]
Kintoki! Jump through it!
Stupid Raikou needs our help!
Right!
Dammit!
[RAIKOU grunts]
[TSUNA]
How are you still alive?!
We exiled both you and your
mother from the capital!
Going outside the walls
is a death sentence!
The bandits and spirits should
have made short work of you!
[YORINOBU'S MOM] Yorinobu,
you have to do something!
[YORINOBU]
Father. I need to know.
Please tell me about Yorimitsu!
The men of our bloodline
inherit the Golden Armor.
I thought that it would be mine.
You raised me my whole
life to believe that.
But however much I've asked
to see my birthright,
you've never once
shown it to me.
Is it... Is it possible ours
is the armor Raikou wears?
[TSUNA] Unfortunately,
our lord, Tada no Shinbochi,
did not have the strength
nor the talent
to don the Golden Armor himself,
regardless of his lineage.
So, he cultivated a new dream:
to raise a child with those
attributes he lacked.
A boy who could fulfill
a duty he could not.
Alas. This desire of his, too,
eventually unraveled
when Michinaga spoke up.
[SHINBOCHI] Nothing would
make me happier, my lord
than to take the Princess of
Nara's famous Fujiwara family,
to be my wife.
My sister does not object.
But one, small matter.
Yes, anything you ask.
The Golden Armor
is in your bloodline,
passed down through
the generations, correct?
[SHINBOCHI] Uh, My Lord,
how did you know?
[YASUMASA] Of course,
if you are to marry my sister,
the one to inherit it
will be her child.
[SHINBOCHI] Well, the armor
isn't really inherited.
It chooses its wearer
from amongst the family.
I already have a son,
named Yorimitsu.
So, I have no clue
if it will choose him,
or any of the future children
your sister bears for me.
The Golden Armor will
have no choice to make,
if there's but one son.
What?
[MICHINAGA] The son you have
with this beautiful princess.
Do I misunderstand
the armor's rules?
If he is your sole heir,
well, he will be chosen.
[SHINBOCHI]
Ah...
[TSUNA] On condition of
marrying the princess,
Shinbochi was to murder
his first son, Yorimitsu.
That's what Michinaga demanded.
Control over the Light Palace
will soon pass
to Lord Michinaga.
When that time comes,
he wants the Golden
Knight at his command.
[MICHINAGA] With the
Golden Knight on our side,
we would be able to defeat enemy
armies thousands of men-strong.
Perhaps even...
tens of thousands.
[SHINBOCHI]
No.
The armor is not something
that can be used against
the armies of living men!
[MICHINAGA]
Shinbochi.
[SHINBOCHI whimpers]
[TSUNA]
Shinbochi had been cowed.
He obeyed Michinaga's wishes.
[TSUNA]
The boy Yorimeets and his mother
were exiled to face
certain death.
And when the time was right,
Shinbochi ordered his retainer
to train his new son,
Yorinobu, to be worthy of
inheriting the Golden Armor.
[YORINOBU yells]
No. It can't be.
So Raikou is Yorimitsu,
and... my brother.
[RAIKOU groaning]
You hate us, for what we did
to you and your mother.
That's why you've returned
for revenge as a Horror!
Do not deny the truth!
You've got it all wrong.
I'm not a Horror.
And I don't hate my father.
Or the servants who helped him.
[BOTH gasp]
As a young boy,
I would struggle every
day with who I was,
and with what I should be.
I couldn't be like my father
who selfishly obeyed
Michinaga to gain status.
So...
for a long time, I was lost.
But then, I found myself.
How dare you double down
on your lies, boy!
[KINTOKI]
Stop right there!
[TSUNA]
Wait, are you Kintoki?
In the flesh!
Long time, Tsuna.
You look like an old man
compared to when I last saw you!
[TSUNA] And you
haven't changed at all!
No matter how many years pass
you still look
like a little boy.
Like your friend here,
the only explanation is that
you're an evil spirit!
You think he's a Horror?
You can say whatever
you want about me,
but I will not let you drag
Raikou's name through the mud!
Tsuna!
You want the truth?!
The only evil spirit is yours!
Uh!
[SERVANT B]
What?
[SERVANT A]
Look at his eyes!
[TSUNA]
No! That's Impossible!
[TSUNA screams]
I was right?
He took a Horror's
arm as a trophy.
But its evil has taken
possession of him.
You lie!
[groaning, roaring]
And now, Tsuna, that Horror's
feeding on a darkness
that's always been in you.
You can't be Yorimeets,
he's dead!
You're the monster, not me!
I helped exile the boy
and his mother!
I am the one who murdered them!
It makes sense now.
Deep down, ever since he exiled
you as a boy, he's felt regret.
Over the years, that guilt
only made his soul darker.
[TSUNA groaning]
[RAIKOU]
So when I returned,
his only way of
handling the guilt was
to convince himself
I was a monster.
But you're the one full
of darkness, Tsuna.
[TSUNA roars]
[SHINBOCHI]
Watch out! [groans]
My lord, no!
[TSUNA growling]
[RAIKOU grunting]
Raikou. You are...
I owe my life to the Armor.
It let me survive
the Horrors of exile.
And then,
I was saved by that silly woman.
Although, I think
she only did it
because she wanted a Makai
Knight who would obey her.
Years later, I finally went back
to the house I was born in.
I didn't have much of a plan.
I think I just wanted
to surprise my father
and everyone else who
now assumed I was dead.
And, maybe give them
a piece of my mind.
[YORINOBU laughing]
[YORINOBU'S MOM]
Great job!
[RAIKOU]
But then, I realized...
Revenge wasn't my fate.
It was to protect others,
like that smiling child.
That's why the
Golden Armor chose me.
To become a Makai Knight and
serve all of the innocent.
Yorinobu.
Seeing you as a boy
gave my life meaning.
The infectious laughter
of my little brother.
[YORINOBU gasps]
Brother!
[RAIKOU]
Uh!
Seimei!
[SEIMEI]
Oh, you look the same.
I heard your hatred
for your father
had made you a Horror already!
[RAIKOU] Really? And what would
you have done if that were true?
[SEIMEI] I'd crush you
with this chariot.
Yeah, I figured as much.
[SEIMEI grunts]
Zaruba!
[TSUNA roars]
[RAIKOU grunting]
The Golden Armor in action.
It's so beautiful.
[SEIMEI grunts]
[TSUNA growling]
[TSUNA roars]
[SEIMEI]
All right, here we go.
Get ready, Raikou!
[LION CHARIOT roars]
[SEIMEI]
Hit him while he's down!
[RAIKOU grunts]
[RAIKOU yells]
[TSUNA screams]
So, that is what this man
Raikou is capable of, eh?
[YORINOBU] Tradition demands
that as the eldest son,
you move back into
this household.
[RAIKOU]
Tradition or no tradition,
I'm Raiko now, a Makai Knight.
I'm no longer an aristocrat.
And I cannot go back
to that life.
Yorinobu, you are
the patriarch now.
This family is yours to protect.
And I'll protect everyone else,
as the Golden Knight.
Of course.
[KINTOKI]
So the whole time
you knew about Yorinobu,
Tsuna, everything?
[RAIKOU]
Yep.
[SEIMEI]
Well, great.
I spent all that time
worrying about nothing.
[RAIKOU]
Well let me ask you, Seimei,
would you return
to the Abe family?
No. I'd never go back there.
Exactly.
So true.
[INARI A] Light and shadow.
Black and white.
It is the contradiction
between the two
that makes them interesting.