[CARRIER]
Major Counselor.
Come in.
Pardon the intrusion.
The woman everyone refers
to as "The Tragic Princess,"
Suetsumuhana.
I've made it quite clear
that I wish to see her face
as soon as possible.
Tell me, where is her reply?
[CARRIER]
I've invited her several times,
but she refuses to come
because of turbulence
in the capital.
She says that now is not
the time for romance.
I do not understand.
[CARRIER]
Sir?
A letter carrier is
meant to carry letters.
Yet this woman here,
she brings me none
and speaks of things
I never asked her about.
Don't you find that
a little strange?
Yes. I think it's very strange.
[gasps]
[CARRIER]
Please forgive me!
[gasps]
[CARRIER screams]
Oh, you poor thing.
Your face has grown quite pale.
It's not a very good
look for you.
[TOORU]
Hm. Oh well.
What a terrible taste.
[SEIMEI] Look, who cares
what happened in the past.
Why don't you think
about the future?
Goodbye.
[RAIKOU]
I understand you even less.
[KINTOKI] Raikou. You really
should eat something.
Come on, Raikou!
What now? What do I do?
[grunts]
You snap out of it!
I get that you're upset right
now. It's only natural!
But you really can't afford to
be in a funk at the moment!
In case you've forgotten,
the Light Palace was attacked
and the capital's
descending into chaos!
If ever there were a time when
your powers were needed, Raikou,
it's now!
[RAIKOU]
You're right. Sorry, Kintoki.
That a fox spirit?
[INARI A]
You came.
Yes.
And the little one tagged along.
It's a great honor
for me to be called to
the Watchdog Center today!
I am so, so unbelievably
honored to be here!
All right, calm down.
[INARI A]
What's wrong?
What's got that funny little
bean so worked up and excited?
[RAIKOU] Don't mind him,
he's just nervous
being called here
for the first time.
[KINTOKI]
Also, I'm not a bean!
I'm Kintoki!
[INARI C]
A Kintoki bean.
Well, I would rather you
leave the "bean" part off.
Try not to tease the
guy too much, okay?
[INARI A]
So, Raikou.
it appears you can finally
don your armor on your own,
without any help.
[RAIKOU]
Yes, that's right.
And yet, somehow,
I still can't bring myself
to completely place
my trust in you.
Noted. I'll keep that in mind.
Oh my goodness.
You and Hakamadare.
How did I get stuck with
such difficult knights?
[RAIKOU]
Problems with Yasusuke?
[INARI A]
Ugh, that one.
The other day, when I
was talking to him...
[INARI A]
Are you even listening?
I heard enough to know
that you're pretty full
of yourself, old lady.
[INARI A] What did you say?
Yeah. I'm not taking
orders from you.
I do my own thing, ya got it?
[INARI A]
Such insolence.
[INARI B] I don't care for
that Hakamadare.
[INARI C] Gold is steadfast.
Silver is savage.
Uh, I see.
Now then, let's talk about
why we summoned you today.
Don't crowd! There's
plenty to go around!
Ow, hot!
Ha! Yorinobu burned
himself again!
[SUETSUMUHANA]
Sheesh.
This is why I can't leave you
in charge of anything, Yorinobu.
Hello, Suetsumuhana.
[MAN A]
Is she the one they say she is?
[WOMAN A] Look at her. Can't you
tell by the way she's dressed?
[MAN A]
I've heard rumors,
but I didn't think
they were true.
So did you burn yourself?
No, no. It's fine, really.
And here's some for you, ma'am.
Oh, thank you so much.
Pity to waste it on
an old crone like me.
Don't be ridiculous.
Now, please eat
before it gets cold.
Everyone's going over to
Yorinobu and avoiding me.
Hey there, kid,
what're you so afraid of?
Do I look like an
evil spirit to you?
[LITTLE GIRL B]
Mmm.
Then come here and get
some porridge, okay?
Just try not to
spill it on yourself.
You know, like
Yorinobu over here.
Yeah. Thanks!
[CHILDREN laughing]
All right, everyone,
get in a straight line now!
Okay, here you go.
Oh, great. Thank you, miss!
[YORINOBU]
Over the last few days,
since the Horrors
were wiped out,
the Light Palace has almost
completely recovered.
Still, the destruction
of the gate
caused many to lose their homes.
And as you can see,
the capital is in bad shape.
[RAIKOU]
Well,
will Kintou let you join us?
Look, Brother. I may not don
armor and fight like you can,
but rest assured,
I'll fight in my own way and
give it everything I've got.
Titles don't matter
to me at the moment.
And I've told my
commanders as much.
You've grown into
quite a man, haven't you?
I'm proud of you. You're
showing some real guts here.
Uh! You're embarrassing me!
If anything, it was you
who gave me the courage.
Well, you and...
the Lady Seimei.
[RAIKOU]
Uh.
So, um, what is
Seimei doing now?
[KINTOKI] We've been looking
for her, but so far, no luck.
Knowing her, I'm sure she's off
enjoying herself somewhere.
[SUETSUMUHANA]
Well, Yorinobu,
looks like we managed
to feed everyone.
Great, thank you.
Please, if you have a moment,
meet my brother, Raikou.
Oh, it's a pleasure
to meet you, Raikou.
Brother, this is
Miss Suetsumuhana.
She kindly responded
to my request for aid.
She has been a great help here.
It must've been tough
for an aristocratic woman,
making the voyage.
It's admirable.
I don't care about that stuff.
All the silly rules
and etiquette.
My family did put up
a bit of a fuss though
since they don't approve of me
leaving the house like this.
I'm sure that was hard for you.
No, not really.
But forget about me,
you've got it a whole lot
rougher than I do!
You think so?
Yes, well, perhaps.
Aw, you two are so
adorable together!
Right, don't they make
a cute pair, Raikou?
[SUETSUMUHANA laughing]
I think he's blushing!
Quit teasing Yorinobu!
Aw! Hey!
A strong woman, that one.
Gotta say, she's impressive.
Yes. Yes, she is.
[RAIKOU]
Who's that?
It's Tooru.
So that's him?
What, you know that guy?
Yes.
When I was young, I visited
his mansion on Rokujo Street.
He's considered the top
ladies' man among the Genji.
They call him "The Shining One."
[chuckles]
Wait, that name.
I hear people mention it all the
time in rumors of love affairs.
He overstepped boundaries
and the aristocracy
turned against him.
So he was forced to retire
in the country of Akashi.
Then what's he doing here now?
[YORINOBU]
The attack on the Light Palace
created a need for
court officials,
so he was asked to return.
[TOORU]
Let's go.
[YORINOBU] Somehow, he still
looks as young as ever.
He sends me letters
all the time.
What does he say?!
He wants to visit me
tomorrow evening.
Really? What is he up to?
[KINTOKI]
Whoa!
I wondered why they summoned us,
but I never expected this.
Such a spread just for
becoming a full-fledged knight!
The Watchdog Center's
really generous!
I doubt that they would give
us anything without wanting
something in return.
What're you saying?
[ZARUBA] Its possible danger
may be just around the corner.
You should be cautious.
[KINTOKI] They said they'd
give you a mansion,
complete with servants
and everything!
You should've taken
them up on their offer!
[RAIKOU] I'm more comfortable
here, just the two of us.
And I prefer the
peace and quiet.
[TOORU]
There's no need for words.
Your rapturous beauty says
more than your lips ever could.
Oh, indeed. I feel the same.
I am content just to gaze
upon your gorgeous face.
[TOORU]
I see.
Well, in that case, how would
you like to help sustain it?
Sustain?
Alas, I'm afraid this is
no longer going to be enough
to get the job done.
[YORINOBU]
Girls are disappearing?
[KINTOU] We've had several
aristocrats come in lately
to report missing girls
and I'm concerned.
When did this start?
Only a couple of
days ago, I believe.
[YORINOBU]
A couple days ago. And girls.
All right. I'm giving
this case to you.
I won't let you down.
[KINTOKI]
Hey, Raikou!
The Watchdog Center
sent a message!
Well, what is it now?
A Horror.
Then I'd better go
get dinner started!
You can't fight on
an empty stomach!
Yeah, I guess that would
be a problem, wouldn't it?
Have your senses dulled?
Ha.
[SUETSUMUHANA]
What?
You're saying Tooru
may be an evil spirit?
We're not completely sure yet.
But, after looking into it, we
can't dismiss the possibility.
And if it's true, you
could be his next target.
He's going after ladies
like you, Suetsumuhana.
[SUETSUMUHANA laughing]
Oh, come on, you've
gotta be kidding me.
I mean, you know what everybody
calls me behind my back,
don't you?
I'm the Tragic Princess!
What does that mean?
With my demeanor and body type,
and lack of musical talent,
I promise, no one
considers me a lady.
Once Tooru gets a look at me--
But that's utterly absurd!
[SUETSUMUHANA]
Uh...
[YORINOBU]
I don't know any woman
with a heart as
beautiful as yours!
Uh, Yorinobu.
Oh, boy! You've got some
serious game, there--
[laughing]
Calm down. Yorinobu's just
trying to be polite, kid!
Suetsumuhana,
I think you should take
everybody somewhere safe.
Tooru.
[TOORU]
A Makai Knight, huh?
[SUETSUMUHANA yelling]
Hey, evil spirit!
Brace yourself!
[SUETSUMUHANA]
I give up.
You shouldn't be here!
Why did you come?
[SUETSUMUHANA]
Please, let him go.
Oh, and who are you now?
You should know,
you've been writing me.
[TOORU]
What?
That's right, I'm Suetsumuhana.
Now go ahead, take me.
Really, you?
So hideous and unrefined.
You truly are the tragic
princess they say you are.
What?
[TOORU]
Just looking at you disgusts me.
Get out of my sight!
But wait. I thought she
was your next target.
Yorinobu,
I must say that you have
become quite beautiful.
Now, let's get out of here.
Huh? I don't get it!
What could he possibly
want with Yorinobu?
Well, maybe, uh...
You know, I'm thinking
it may take a while
for you to wrap your head
around this one, Raikou.
I'll explain it to you later.
But for now, we've
gotta just go after him!
Yeah, right.
What's going on here,
Tooru? Tell me!
[TOORU] I've brought you here
because you're beautiful.
And simply put,
I love beautiful things.
[YORINOBU]
But I'm a man!
[TOORU] Doesn't matter
if you're a man or a woman.
I find all beauty delicious.
[YORINOBU] How did someone as
lucky as you become a Horror?
[TOORU] Unfortunately,
I had no other choice.
[GIRL]
For a common girl like me,
you're a dream come true.
Beauty is not determined
by one's status or class.
[GIRL gasps]
[GIRL chuckles]
[GIRL]
You've got a gray hair.
Don't be upset.
It just shows that you're
working hard for the people.
[TOORU growls]
No, not me,
I refuse to believe it!
Impossible!
I can't be getting old!
No, no, no, this can't
be happening! Not to me!
Are you afraid of getting old?
Toru, what's wrong?
Do you want a body
that won't wither?
But how?
All you have to do is
accept me as a part of you,
and I promise to make it so.
[TOORU]
Yes!
Please! I deserve to be
beautiful for all eternity!
As you wish.
[TOORU screaming]
[GIRL screaming]
[YORINOBU] That's your idea
of having no choice?
You're insane!
[TOORU]
Sanity.
It's a small thing to sacrifice
to have beauty such as mine.
[YORINOBU] Is that all you see
when you look at people?
No, I see food.
[YORINOBU]
Bastard!
[YORINOBU yelling]
[TOORU]
You know, I wonder.
What does a man as beautiful
as you taste like? Yum.
[thud]
[yelling]
Kintoki, please help Yorinobu.
I'm on it!
[TOORU] This is why I hate
Makai Knights so much.
Right. Yorinobu?
What are you--?
[RAIKOU]
Snap out of it!
Damn!
Prepare to die, evil spirit!
Oh, it's you again, is it?
Yorinobu?
He's possessed right now.
Stay back!
Why am I being forced to look
at such ugliness in front of me?
Do you not find
her offensive too?
Yes, I find her very
offensive as well.
Stop, Yorinobu!
You're the one that told me
that I had a beautiful heart.
Remember!
[YORINOBU, TOORU]
Silly girl.
The word "beautiful" describes
my features, not yours.
True beauty is on the inside.
It's a person's heart
that makes them beautiful.
Suetsumu...
Come on,
don't let an ugly monster
like this guy control you!
[TOORU]
Me, ugly?
What, are you blind, girl?
I'm beautiful!
[yelling]
Now, Seimei!
Lingering feelings, eh, Raikou?
Oh, shut up!
[MASKS laughing]
[yells]
[RAIKOU]
The moon.
[yelling]
[RAIKOU]
I have to protect her!
[gasps]
[laughing]
[YORINOBU]
He won't hurt you.
I swear on my life,
I won't let him.
[SUETSUMUHANA]
Yorinobu!
[RAIKOU]
I'll protect you all!
[growls]
Go, Raikou!
[yelling]
[YORINOBU]
Brother. Kintoki.
Please, forgive me,
Suetsumuhana.
I'm so sorry.
I would never hurt you.
[SUETSUMUHANA] You're the first
man to ever stand up for me.
That was very brave of you.
I'm grateful for that, and
your kindness makes me happy.
I was right. You
truly are... beautiful.
[SUETSUMUHANA]
No! Yorinobu!
[KINTOKI]
It's okay.
He just passed out, that's all.
[RAIKOU] Seimei. It's true
that humans are weak.
That's why they continue
to spread darkness
and turn into Horrors.
You may not be able to forgive
them for their weakness,
but I'll still fight
to protect the people.
If we should meet
again, this time...
So it has begun.
[INARI B, INARI C]
It has begun.
[DOUMAN]
Beautiful.
It's as if the moon
were stained with blood.
[DOUMA]
This is the Crimson Moon.
[RAIKOU]
Zaruba.
I'm starting to think your
prediction may be right.
[ZARUBA]
I take no pleasure in that.
I swear, no matter what happens
next, I will not give up.
[INARI A]
It doesn't matter the era.
Some things never change.
Such is mankind.