[HORROR 24A roars]
[WOMAN 24A whimpers]
[HORROR 24A growling]
[MITSUNAKA groaning]
[MITSUNAKA whimpers]
[HORROR 24A roars]
[TOKIWAKA yells]
[TOKIWAKA grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[growls]
[INARI A]
You couldn't kill it?
Utterly useless!
I was told that you were one
of the best Makai Knights
supported by the council.
[INARI B]
What is your name, Knight?
My name is Tokiwaka.
Thought so. Tell us then.
Why not don your armor?
That fight might've had
a different outcome.
[gasps]
[INARI B]
What, you can't say?
[INARI C]
Oh, I see.
He seems to prefer wearing
armor around his heart.
[INARI A] Surely you are aware
that this Horror has managed
to defeat every Makai Knight
in the capital by now?
[TOKIWAKA]
Of course I am.
But, who was that other man?
[INARI B]
Minamoto no Mitsunaka.
He's a trainee who has
yet to receive his armor.
He's of no use until
his body has healed.
We will tend to
his injuries here.
If it's possible, I'd like to
speak with him when he wakes.
That should be fine.
We'll call for you once he's up.
[INARI C]
Right now,
you are the only chance we have
of defeating that Horror.
[INARI A]
Make sure you kill it this time.
Is that understood?
[TOKIWAKA] I thought I had
mentally prepared myself
to take on this last job.
[TOKIWAKA]
Hm?
[TAMAGUSHI]
[TAMAGUSHI gasps]
[TOKIWAKA]
She's a human.
I'm sorry if I scared you.
I was worried you were
an evil spirit.
Huh? Whoa! Wait!
[TAMAGUSHI]
Uh!
[TOKIWAKA grunts]
[TAMAGUSHI gasping]
Hey, calm down! Look at me!
I promise I'm not
an evil spirit!
You're lying!
You're trying to trick me!
If that was the case,
don't you think I would
have already killed you?
[TOKIWAKA]
She's... beautiful.
So, uh, I'm a traveler.
Name's Tokiwaka.
Nice to meet you,
my name's Tamagushi.
Well, sort of nice.
The whole axe swinging part
wasn't exactly pleasant.
Uh! Yeah, fair enough.
But I can keep apologizing
if you want me to.
[laughs]
Oh, wow, that smells delicious.
Thanks, cooking's a
specialty of mine.
My hands just seem
to take to it naturally.
Although it's a little bizzare,
I don't remember where
I learned to cook.
You don't remember? At all?
Uh. No! Just forget I said that.
It's impossible
to forget the thing
someone's asking you to forget.
[chuckles] Regardless.
Let's eat while it's warm.
Oh. It's great!
[TOKIWAKA] Glad you like it.
It's rabbit stew.
Uh!
I've seen that look before.
The upper class make a point
of not eating rabbit or deer,
but it's delicious.
Just like foul.
[whimpering]
It is.
[TOKIWAKA]
So, you mentioned earlier
that you snuck out
of your house.
Why take the risk when there's
an evil spirit roaming around?
[TAMAGUSHI] Because my husband
has grown tired of me.
[TOKIWAKA]
Husband? Oh, of course.
You... have a husband.
[TAMAGUSHI] I'm convinced that
he's begun seeing another woman.
He's been sneaking out at
night for some time now.
My suspicion finally
got the better of me.
But when I confronted
him about it,
he grew furious and
stormed out of the house.
And then I was so upset, I
locked myself in my bedroom.
But I felt like I
was suffocating.
Next thing I knew, I left.
How could any man be unhappy
with a woman like
you as his wife?
Uh! Huh?
[TOKIWAKA]
Uh... U-Uh! No--uh! Ho-Hold on!
I jus... I just meant...
Y'know...
I-If you were my wife,
and I-I... I was your husband,
then I would never--
[TAMAGUSHI] So you are an evil
spirit that tricks people?!
[TOKIWAKA] No, no, no!
That's not-- That's no it!
I'm... I'm just not
explaining myself well!
Oh, boy.
[TOKIWAKA] Her husband's
definitely a reason for concern.
He started sneaking out
a few nights ago.
Around the same time the
Horror Shutendoji appeared.
Here's hoping it's
just a coincidence.
[TOKIWAKA] I need you to please
find out as soon as possible.
Well, that shouldn't
be a problem.
You aren't the first person
to make that request today.
What?
[IZUMI]
I'm still waiting
for the client to return
for their answer though.
One of the capital's knights?
Or maybe Minamoto no Mitsunaka?
[IZUMI]
Oh!
Here it is.
All of Shutendoji's
victims were female.
And each one of the poor women
happened to be pregnant.
What?!
[IZUMI]
Another thing,
even though it's commonly
referred to as Shutendoji,
it originally called itself
the "abandoned child."
[TOKIWAKA]
Abandoned child?
All of the attacks
are mapped out here.
[TOKIWAKA]
They all occurred
in the northeast corner
of the capital.
And now I know.
[IZUMI]
Is that all you need?
You live up to your renown,
Izumi Shikibu.
Oh, please, just call me Izumi.
You're rather strapping, so I'll
only charge you half the price.
[TOKIWAKA gasping]
[yawns]
[TAMAGUSHI]
I always feel so sleepy lately.
[crash]
Uh?
[gasps]
You do realize it's a
nice sunny day outside.
And yet you're
locked up in here.
Well you don't have to
judge me for it, y'know.
Sorry.
Anyway, what made you decide
to drop by to see me?
Well, uh, you being
stuck alone in your room.
It made me kind of sad, so--
That was the best thing I
could come up with. Ha, ha.
[TAMAGUSHI giggle]
[TAMAGUSHI] I wonder if he's in
the same place tonight as well.
[TAMAGUSHI]
Was that Tokiwaka?
[WOMAN 24B gasping]
--[HORROR 24A roars]
--[WOMAN 24B whimpers]
[WOMAN 24B screams]
[TOKIWAKA]
Run fast!
[WOMAN 24B]
Right!
[TOKIWAKA]
Uh! I didn't hit him?!
[HORROR 24A roars]
[TOKIWAKA grunts]
[TOKIWAKA]
Don the armor now!
You can't hesitate!
[yells]
[groans]
[TOKIWAKA groans]
[TOKIWAKA]
The armor!
[yells]
[TOKIWAKA]
What? That's impossible!
[INARI B]
We're certain of it.
[INARI A]
A female has been abducted
by the Shutendoji
near Shijo street.
I know for a fact I cut
it down with my own hands!
[INARI B] Well, we're having
trouble believing that.
You failed to vanquish it.
Now complete your duty.
[gasping]
[TOKIWAKA] Dammit.
Could there be another one?
[ringing]
[TOKIWAKA]
The sound of those bells again.
[TAMAGUSHI]
Tokiwaka.
[TOKIWAKA]
Mm?
Tamagushi?
[TAMAGUSHI]
So you're a Makai Knight.
Yes, that's why
I'm in the capital.
I have come to defeat
the Horror, Shutendoji.
[TAMAGUSHI gasping]
[TOKIWAKA] I tried to hide it
from you but I guess you saw me.
So maybe, y'know,
try to forget what you saw.
We're doing this again?
You can't forget the
thing you've been--
Wait.
Hold on.
Do you think there's a chance
that your loss of memory--?
[TOKIWAKA gasps]
Maybe it has something
to do with this.
When we fight Horrors,
we don a mystic armor.
It's really the only
way to fight them.
The specific armor my teacher
bestowed upon me,
it's unsurpassed in
strength. Although...
It also carries a curse.
What type of curse?
Believe it or not.
I'm actually a 40 year old man.
Forty?!
When I don my Makai Armor,
it takes a chunk of
my time as payment.
But as a result, my time
has also been frozen.
[TAMAGUSHI]
So you continue to grow young,
and you never age either?
[TOKIWAKA] Would you believe a
lot of people envy me for it?
You live alone in your
own different time.
I think that's tragic.
Well, you're the first person
I've met who ever felt that way.
[TAMAGUSHI sighs]
Whenever I remove my armor,
I see a vision of
a golden butterfly.
I think it's like an echo--
a shimmer of my lost time.
[TAMAGUSHI] I suppose
it could be that, but...
What if you stop?
Just don't use it and
you can stay this way.
[TOKIWAKA] I've performed
my duty all these years
without the need for my armor.
But, this time is
different, and, well...
I'll be a child next
time I grow younger,
and then I'll no longer be
able to fight as a knight.
This doesn't have
to be your fight.
But I'm the only one
in the capital who can.
And I can't turn my back
on that. I can't show fear.
And I cannot hesitate.
[TAMAGUSHI] So that's what
it means to be a Makai Knight.
I'll never forget you!
[TOKIWAKA gasps]
I'll remember your eyes,
your voice.
Your warmth. Your kindness.
[TAMAGUSHI]
Everything about you!
[TAMAGUSHI cries]
[IZUMI] There was a
mortally injured monk
discovered yesterday afternoon
just along the edge
of the capital.
[TOKIWAKA]
Okay, what of him?
He used his final dying breath
to speak these words.
"There is an evil spirit
residing in Ooe Mountain."
Ooe Mountain. Interesting.
[IZUMI]
Right? So I did some research.
The crops of the village
by the mountain
were failing and the people
were all starving.
So they left the village,
deserting their children
to fend for themselves.
Deserted. The abandoned child.
It hates its parents for...
forsaking it!
That's the reason
why it targets women
carrying children in their womb.
[IZUMI]
Happiness is so fleeting.
[TOKIWAKA]
I heard what you yelled.
You said, "I have to be
the one to kill it."
I haven't been able to shake
those words ever since.
[MITSUNAKA]
My single drive in life
is to inherit the
armor of a knight.
The knights of the capital
have been falling,
one after the other.
I felt totally useless
and impotent
only being able to watch,
and I let myself be
consumed with anger.
A strong heart is
far more important
than physical strength.
One can't don the armor.
Not with a weak heart.
[TOKIWAKA] One can't don the
armor. Not with a weak heart.
I know I don't really have
the right to ask this of you,
but please, kill Shutendoji.
[TOKIWAKA]
You can leave it to me.
I left my house in
the middle of the night
without a word to my wife.
Aw, jeez, that's awful.
I'm so worried about her now.
[TAMAGUSHI panting]
I did it.
[door creaks]
[TAMAGUSHI]
Hm?
[TOKIWAKA]
Tamagushi?
Hello, Tokiwaka.
I've finally made up
my mind, thanks to you.
You have?
I know that I'll succeed.
Uh.
And rest easy. Your husband's
not what you assume.
He continues to
think only of you.
Mitsunaka loves you.
How do you know his name?
He'll be coming home in
no time at all and then,
well, then he can explain
everything to you.
Trust me, you don't need to
close your doors any longer.
Are you telling me
that you met with him?
He tries to carry too
much on his shoulders.
And he's got a bad habit
of blaming himself.
Please keep that in mind.
Oh, I already know.
I'd like you to take
this with you.
[TOKIWAKA]
What is it?
[TAMAGUSHI]
A protection charm.
I stitched it not only with
my hair, but my hope as well.
I pray that the golden
time of your life
will forever be by your side.
Thank you.
[HORROR 24A roars]
[TOKIWAKA]
Why the hell is it here?
It's only attacked pregnant
women so far--
[gasps]
Look out behind you!
[HORROR 24A roars]
You bastard.
I swear to you, you will
not harm her or her child!
[TOKIWAKA grunting]
Ah, c'mon, did you really think
it was gonna be that easy?
You're not escaping!
[HORROR 24A roars]
Running's not gonna
do you any good.
[HORROR 24A roaring]
What?
[HORRORS roaring]
So this is how you defeated
all the other knights.
[gasps]
[TOKIWAKA yells]
[HORROR 24A roars]
[TOKIWAKA groaning]
I have a reason
I have someone who
needs my protection.
And now I know that I have
people who'll remember me.
That's all I need!
[yells]
I'll cut out your darkness.
Right here and now!
[KINTOKI]
Good day.
I've arrived to begin my service
under Minamoto no Mitsunaka.
Oh. I was waiting for--
[gasps]
Nice to meet you.
Please call me Kintoki,
all right?
Uh. What's wrong?
Are you okay, my lady?
[TAMAGUSHI cries]
Please, I want you
to hold him.
Huh? Uh. Well, uh--
[RAIKO laughs]
[TAMAGUSHI]
You saved him.
This is the child you protected.
[TAMAGUSHI]
I'd like you to continue
to watch after him, okay?
Yes, ma'am!
[TAMAGUSHI]
His name is Yorimits.
We've all just taken to calling
him Raiko, though.
Little Raiko. I like it.
Don't worry, you can
count on me.
I'll protect him with my life,
no matter what.
From now on, I'll be your
attendant, Raikou--
[KINTOKI gasp, screams]
[KINTOKI]
That hurt, Raiko!