ANNOUNCER: Game to
Fuji, two games to one.
Fuji leads.
BOY: The brown bear.
Amazing.
[theme music]
-Here's another chance!
-He returned it again.
-Ryoma's good, but is
this the end for him?
-High lob.
-A smash.
-Impossible.
-What's wrong, Echizen?
-This is so unlike Ryoma.
-That boy.
So darn stubborn.
-I've never seen
Echizen like this.
I can't believe he
missed that smash.
-Another lob.
HORIO: It's no good.
The smash doesn't work.
He returned it!
-Was that chance,
or something else?
ANNOUNCER: Out.
-That was out?
Not Fuji.
Not this match.
-Fuji never misses
a counter shot.
-Not again.
-In case you didn't
know, you don't
have to hit any more lobs.
ANNOUNCER: Out.
HORIO: What the-- Out?
I can't believe Fuji missed.
-So, he was just checking
the timing earlier.
It's unbelievable what you do.
-You're amazing, Echizen.
-Thanks.
-Would you normally
aim for that spot?
-What do you mean?
-That kid can delay
his smash by hitting it
at the net to deflect it.
-Now I get it.
That must be why Fuji's sweet
spot went off ever so slightly.
-Can you really make
such a thing work?
-The little guy's
the one to do it.
-Eiji, were you really
able to see that?
-Yeah, well?
-That's amazing.
Echizen's coming back.
That's incredible.
-I can't believe it.
Now the match is up in the air.
-That brat showing off again
[beeping]
INUI (VOICEOVER): Hm.
It's been 10 minutes
since they ran.
Both of them are
the type of athletes
to start feeling tired
right around now.
-Hey, Coach.
-Hm?
-It's almost time now.
OK.
Momoshiro, get on Court
D. It's your turn.
-Huh?
Right.
Just what I've been waiting for.
I can't let Echizen be
the only one to look good.
So, who am I playing?
-I'll play you.
-OK.
In five minutes,
Kaidoh and Kawamura
will play each other on Court
E. And 15 minutes after that,
Oishi and Kikumaru will
commence play on Court C.
INUI (VOICEOVER): Each
person has different kinds
of exhaustion after totally
expending his energy.
The purpose of this
particular training session
is to see how strong
their concentration is
when they are physically
at their weakest.
-Wow.
This is amazing.
-It's Momo and the
captain, and a match
between the golden pair!
-That is a must-see match up!
-But I wanna stay and watch
Ryoma's match until the end!
-Oh, man, you're kidding.
I have to play the captain?
-Uh, Momoshiro?
-No luck.
No luck for me today.
-He looks ready to play.
-Yeah.
I'll say.
-Those two.
I wouldn't mind seeing
them play each other.
-In that case, let's
finish this up quickly.
-Will you lose to me?
-No way.
-Echizen's match is
really heating up now.
-Whoa, everywhere
you look, there
are great matches going on.
-But which one should
we be watching?
-Look over there.
Momo and the captain are about
to start playing their match.
ANNOUNCER: One set match,
Momoshiro to serve.
MOMOSHIRO (VOICEOVER): OK.
I won't hold back.
-OK.
Come on, Momoshiro.
I see.
You've gotten stronger
since the last time.
His powerful stroke will
be a formidable weapon
at the Kanto-- No,
even at the nationals.
-A drop shot?
-By Momo?
He's good, and he's
got the advantage.
-He returned it.
-Momo's powerful drop shot?
-Fantastic.
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER):
He has a fine attack.
KACHIRO: Momo's dunk
smash is awesome!
-Did you see that?
Amazing, he ended it.
-I can't believe he used a
drop shot against the captain.
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER):
He's no ordinary player.
He's Seigaku's
number one trickster.
-Right!
Here goes!
-It has been 15 minutes.
All right.
Oishi and Kikumaru start.
-All right, Oishi.
Let's get on with it.
But loser gets to
drink "penal-tea."
-That's really rough.
-Hey guys.
Look, the golden pair is getting
ready to play one another.
-Between Oishi's moon volley
shot and Kikumaru's acrobatics,
I wonder who the
stronger player could be.
KIKUMARU (VOICEOVER):
That Oishi.
He keeps on aiming
for the deep corners.
He wants to make me run
all over the baseline.
INUI (VOICEOVER): Eiji
you're quick to recover.
However, we have
to figure out how
to distribute your energy in the
matches for maximum efficiency,
especially against
someone like Oishi,
who thinks very strategically.
-Kikumaru and Oishi are amazing.
Even though they're
partners, they're
not holding back at all.
They're treating this
like a tournament match.
-You mean it's serious?
-You bet it is.
They may be partners,
but a match is a match.
It's serious business
when they're playing
-Eiji's great.
It doesn't matter if
I hit left or right.
Well, then, right
down the center!
-Kikumaru Beam!
-Wow, there it is!
Kikumaru's acrobatic form!
-Neither one of them is willing
to give an inch to the other.
-They know each other's style.
That's why this is
such a great match up.
KAIDOH: Take that!
-That voice!
It's Kaidoh versus Kawamura.
[? -burning! ?]
-It's power tennis at its best.
-Kawamura.
He's burning up.
-Sure is.
Amazing.
-That was out.
-Aw, his Boomerang Snake
Shot was wide left.
-Yeah, I guess
against Kawamura, he
feels like he's a
little overpowered.
INUI (VOICEOVER): Against
an opponent like Kawamura,
it's crucial to raise the odds
of the Boomerang Snake Shot.
[hiss]
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Hey, it's the captain.
So why is he-- the match
couldn't be over already?
Could it?
-No.
Not against Momo.
There's no way he
could have already--
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER): He played
him with all he's got, huh?
BOY: That's Tezuka.
Over in a jiffy.
-BOY: Tezuka-- you--
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER):
Momoshiro-- it
seems the sprain in his
right leg has healed.
However, if he
favors the other leg,
he won't be able to
display his top form.
-I see.
He's sure stronger
than he looks.
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER): When
he gets knocked down,
he always returns twice
as strong as before.
-Even though he won
today's match up,
who knows what will
happen in a month?
I'm looking forward to
the days that follow.
-Hey.
The sky suddenly
turned dark and cloudy.
-Looks like we're going
to get a heavy downpour.
-And here it comes now!
-Oh, dear.
Rain now, of all things.
-Oh, no.
Weather guy said--
-Aw, it's starting to rain.
-Never trust those--
-Anybody have an umbrella?
-This is bad.
I'm afraid we'll have
to call off practice.
-I guess so.
RYUZAKI: Practice is over.
Everyone inside.
BOY: All right, let's
get out of here.
-Seventh graders, get
the net and the balls.
Hurry.
-OK!
-This is terrible.
-Aw, too bad.
We'll have to play later.
-Huh?
Those two are still out
on the court playing.
-You've got to be kidding me.
-What are they thinking?
In a heavy rain like this?
-Got me.
Those two are crazy.
[shout]
-Echizen's-- amazing.
-Echizen.
-He intends to finish this.
-You won't run away, will you?
-We can still play.
It's just rain.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): He switched.
Right hand grip.
It's a kick serve.
-Hey, you two!
How long are you gonna be
playing out there, you fools?
-Huh?
-Now get this straight, you two.
This is practice.
If you're that eager to play.
You can do it any time.
You're on the same team.
The real match comes
tomorrow at the Metros.
Have you've forgotten that
rain is a tennis player's worst
enemy?
What if one of you gets hurt
in something as petty as this?
-Too bad, but this
match is mine.
-No fair.
Just because you're winning
4-3 doesn't mean anything.
It's not over yet.
-It's over and I don't
wanna hear any complaints.
-No matter what I
do, he catches up.
That kind of thrill
is rare, indeed.
-Say, Tezuka.
Did you feel this way
when you played Ryoma?
TEZUKA: So you knew?
-Yeah, sort of.
-Sweet skies.
Rain finally stopped.
Great.
-Huh?
-Since your match with
Fuji went unfinished,
you don't feel very
satisfied, do you?
-Heard about your match.
Seems your dunk smash was
returned easily by the captain.
-Shut up!
-If you think my
dunk smash is easy,
I'll show you right here now
how very mistaken you are.
-Wouldn't it be kind of a shock
if you lost twice in one day?
-Hey.
Don't talk with your mouth full.
-Still.
Seigaku is fun.
-How so?
-Because it seems like there
are two beasts on the same team.
-Don't you mean there
are three beasts?
-Huh?
-That's it for me.
MAN: Yuta Fuji.
Yuta Fuji.
Phone call for Yuta Fuji.
-Huh?
Yes?
This is Yuta Fuji.
-Huh?
Oh, it's you.
Shusuke.
So, what do you want?
SHUSUKE (ON PHONE): Ha ha.
I can call, can't I?
Just wondering how
you were doing.
-Just fine.
Everything's fine over
here at St. Rudolph's.
-That's great.
I played against Echizen today.
YUTA (ON PHONE): What?
You kidding?
So how did it go?
-You know, Yuta.
-Hm?
-The Seigaku team
is very strong.
-What?
You trying to say something?
Just spit it out!
-Give me the phone.
Now, Yuta.
-Mizuki?
-Ah.
Fuji of Seigaku.
Checking on the competition?
That just won't--
[click]
[beeping]
[laughing]
-Now then, Yuta.
Let's begin training.
-Huh?
But I'm done with all
my training for today.
MIZUKI: And you think
you're capable of beating
Shusuke Fuji now?
Come on.
I know you want to beat him.
We can work on your
skills together.
All night long.
YUTA: But Mizuki!
[wicked laughter]
[music playing]
[theme music]
TAICHI: Da da dada!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Yamabuki Junoir High
tennis manager Taichi Dan.
The semifinals of the
Metropolitan Tournament
have finally begun!
Fudomine is a
fearsome enemy, and we
mustn't let your guard down.
Please do your best, Akutsu.
Um, Akutsu?
What?
No way.
What happened?
Impossible!
Next on "The Prince
of Tennis," Trouble!
Akutsu, this is really bad.
Fudomine is--