-To the left!
[grunting]
-Trying to ace me, brat?
Don't make me laugh.
-Oh, no!
He's going to lose the point
on yet another passing shot!
[music playing]
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): Dad?
RYOMA (VOICEOVER):
I want to be strong!
[screaming]
-He changed directions
while he was in mid step.
-The kid's standing up.
And against Akutsu!
-Yes sir-ee.
SADAHARU: That seventh grader.
[spitting]
UMPIRE: 40-30.
-All right!
Echizen!
-Ryoma really
dominated that point!
-That is totally amazing!
-Ryoma let's win this, come on!
[swooning]
-Both of these players
sure have a lot of spirit.
-It sure is getting interesting.
-They still have a ways to go.
This is still child's play.
-But these kids
are really awesome,
SADAHARU: He never
fails to amaze me.
-First he made his
move over to the left.
SADAHARU: Then he shifted to
the right without taking a step.
Is that possible?
-So what do you think, Tezuka?
-It's because Echizen only uses
one foot on his split step.
-Right.
The normal split step would have
made him a step or two late.
Then he wouldn't have made
it to the ball on time.
-I guess only one
foot was supposed
to be used in the
original split step.
-Yeah, I think you're right.
KAORU: That guy made
Echizen dig deep.
-And he also brought out
his dormant abilities.
-Our seventh grader sure
showed us some amazing stuff.
TAKESHI: That's our boy.
AKUTSU: You think I'm
just a stepping stone?
Don't make me laugh.
Take this!
-Enough for a
return winner again!
-I told you you're
wasting your time.
-Oh no, he's got it!
AKUTSU: What the?
UMPIRE: Deuce.
-Yeah, he did it!
-Great, his shot
sailed by Akutsu.
[chuckling]
-Yay, Ryoma, yay!
Hey, Sakuno, I've never seen
you this excited before.
-Huh?
I don't know what you mean.
AKUTSU (VOICEOVER): He's
moving faster and cleaner now.
AKUTSU (VOICEOVER):
Don't get carried away.
AKUTSU (VOICEOVER): Look
the other way, brat.
[breathing hard]
UMPIRE: Advantage,
Echizen of Seigaku.
-Man, he returned it by using
his one legged split step.
[whistling]
-Echizen's good all right.
-Wow, that seventh grader's
completely changed the way
he moves in the
middle of a match.
-It's scary.
And he's still just
developing his game.
-Look Echizen's on fire.
-You're right, he's outstanding.
-Huh?
Wow, Kaido.
That's the first time I've ever
heard you say something nice.
[growling]
-Hey, just shut up.
-Come on, you brat!
-Huh?
-No way!
UMPIRE: Game!
Echizen of Seigaku leads
three games to one.
-There it is!
It's the Drive B!
-All right!
[shouting and cheering]
-Good, he caught up.
-Wow, this is really
starting to get interesting.
-Mmm-hmm.
-Well, Banji.
I'm grateful to you.
I truly appreciate that you had
Akutsu play this match today.
-I don't know what you mean.
-Thanks to him, looks
like samurai junior
became just plain samurai.
Ryoma Echizen became
a warrior today.
-Yes, Echizen sure is
a first class player.
To tell the truth,
I didn't expect
Ryoma to be so strong at
such a very young age.
It kind of took me by surprise.
But you know what?
Akutsu's tough, and he's not
about to let it end like this.
-Hmm?
-Look carefully, coach.
There's a reason
why he can't lose.
-A reason he can't lose?
-Yes.
KAORU: Game!
Echizen of Seigaku leads
three games to two.
-You're playing very well.
RYOMA: Thanks.
-But you still
have to be careful.
I know Banji very well, and I'm
sure he's planning something.
Thing is, I've seen plenty of
his dirty tricks before, Ryoma.
-He's brutal.
-Huh?
-It still makes me mad
when I think about it.
Ryoma?
Be sure to destroy him.
-Huh.
Guess you can't
let it go, can you?
NANJIRO: Ryoma's really
reaching his potential fast.
At this rate, it
might be possible.
-You just don't get it, do you?
-What?
-It all begins now.
NANJIRO: Banji will show us
his real talent as a coach.
From here on in my kid'll
have to prove whether or not
he's a strong player.
Wow, I'm really getting hungry.
-You mean, you're not
sticking around then?
NANJIRO: I don't think so.
This is all just child's play.
[sigh]
NANJIRO: Well, Ryoma?
What are you going to do?
[breathing hard]
-Hey there, Akutsu.
You better watch those
manners of yours.
AKUTSU: Who you
talking to, old man?
I'll bash in your
stupid old head.
-Well, well.
You still have some fight left.
AKUTSU: Stop bothering me.
I'm telling you, I'm not
going to play tennis.
-It's a gift.
Your shoulders are strong.
-Just lay off of me.
-No, I won't.
You've got to play, son.
You just don't see solid
forearms like this every day.
-Huh?
BANJI: Akutsu, this may just
be an old man's rambling,
so go ahead and ignore
me if you want to.
-Huh?
-That boy's game is
improving by leaps and bounds
as the match is
progressing along.
And it looks like
he's figured out
how to adjust to
your pace, Akutsu.
BANJI: I can tell you this.
There are lots of players on
the national tennis circuit who
will give you a
run for your money.
You'll find a dime a dozen.
-What exactly you try
to get at, old man?
-It's just, I think it's more
fun to be burning with passion
and it is to be bored to death.
Wouldn't you agree
with me, Akutsu?
AKUTSU: Why you!
Stop bossing me around.
BANJI: I didn't mean
to boss you around.
However, even though
you seem to hate it,
playing tennis isn't really
so bad after all, now is it?
I think it might do
you a world of good
to listen to an old
man's ramblings.
At least you could
kill some time.
So, what you think about
joining the tennis team?
-Akutsu, how about changing
up your pace a bit?
You don't have to be so
aggressive all the time.
-Who are you ordering around?
[chuckling]
AKUTSU (VOICEOVER):
Who do you think I am?
I'm Jin Akutsu.
Nobody stands a
chance against me.
I've crushed everyone
who's gotten in my way.
Up until now.
And from now on, too!
-Coach Ryuzaki?
If a person practices very
hard, there's really nothing
to be ashamed of he
happens to lose a match.
BANJI: But when someone mocks
the sport and hardly ever
practices, when that
person loses a match, well,
that is just humiliating.
And that is the reason
why he just can't lose.
ALL: Whoa!
BANJI: I know he can't
stand that kind of disgrace.
RYOMA: You have a ways to go.
AKUTSU: Give me a
break, you punk.
-Oh, no.
It appears Echizen's having
problems with his defense.
-Hey!
What's going on?
-Ryoma?
-I told you, brat.
I'll take you apart!
UMPIRE: Game!
Akutsu of Yamabuki leads
four games to three.
-Oh, no!
Now he's lost his lead!
Come on, Ryoma, go!
You can trash this
loser and make him pay!
[breathing hard]
-Looks like he
changed up his plays.
He's not solely relying
on his aggressive game
like he was before.
BANJI (VOICEOVER):
It's not easy for you
to take someone else's advice
-Let's see what you've got.
And show me how determined
you are to beat this rookie.
NANJIRO: Ka-pow.
[breathing hard]
[cheering]
NANJIRO: Get stronger, Ryoma.
-Man, Akutsu's really
turning up the heat.
I don't think there's
anyone who can stop him now.
-It looks like short stuff
might be able to stop him.
-Don't count on it.
-You know, anything is
still possible, man.
That's the true
beauty of tennis.
-It appears Echizen had
adapted to his fastballs,
but it's still tough for
him to change up the pace.
-It's amazing how could you can
just change his game so fast
like that.
-That coach certainly
has an incredible ability
to get through to his player.
-Nanjiro was right.
Banda directs a player
by little hints,
and he changes the
course of a game.
He's an outstanding coach.
Hmm.
AKUTSU (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe it.
The old man was right.
I'm varying the
tempo of my shots.
My drives are becoming
much more effective.
BANJI: What do you
think, Echizen?
Can you compete with Akutsu now?
RYOMA: Huh.
-Huh?
RYOMA: Ha!
-No way!
He hasn't given up yet!
-Come on, kid.
Try and stop this!
-I don't think either
of them will back off.
-Yeah you're right.
How will this end?
I'll have to see.
-It's going to go
right down to the wire.
I guess there's
nothing at all that
can stop now, at this point.
AKUTSU (VOICEOVER):
That's useless.
TAKASHI: Ryoma had
him figured out.
At least until Akutsu went
and modified his game plan.
And thanks to some really
good coaching, Akutsu's game
has reached a whole new level.
Normally the pressure will
cause a player to fall apart.
-Yeah, but it looks
like our Echizen
hasn't given in to
Akutsu mentally.
-That's right.
He's playing like real champ.
-Echizen knows instinctively
that the very worst thing
he can do at this
time is to tense up
on the tennis court like that.
KUNIMITSU: Tennis is
a unique kind of sport
that ultimately depends on both
technique and mental agility
as well.
RYOMA: Hey!
If you'd stuck to karate,
you wouldn't have a shrimp
like me beating you.
AKUTSU: There's no way!
-Akutsu's pride or
Echizen's courage?
Whichever one stronger
will give us the winner.
-The world champ, huh?
-Ha ha!
-Wow, he made it!
-Ryoma got to--
-The match point, wowee!
-Man, I'm getting all
weak in the knees, Sakuno!
SAORI: You know, perhaps
this is what tennis is really
all about.
It really doesn't matter
who wins the match.
In the end it's
important to know
that the ultimate
moment of truth
will arrive no matter
what we try to do.
-Did you say "the
ultimate moment of truth?"
-Yes, I did.
It's the magical moment
when two individuals let
their spirits come
together as one.
It's truly an incredible
thing to behold.
-Two spirits.
[music playing]
RYOMA: Hi, I'm Ryoma.
I see you're doing OK,
but I believe you still
owe me for Kachiro,
for Kawamura, oh yeah,
and for Arai, too.
Well, the game has
reached its climax,
so I'm going to finish
it already and win
the metropolitan matches.
Next, on the Prince of
Tennis, the decisive moment.
Oh, wait!
You owe me one for myself, too!