-Hey, who's that short kid?
-Wh-- what did you say?
Uh, I'm not really sure.
He has some serve,
that's for sure.
Hey, Akutsu, sorry, but
it looks like there's
trouble on the court.
I know we've been buds,
but can you leave now?
-Don't you dare order me around.
-Uh, I'm sorry.
-Looks like that kid
got to it before I did.
-Ahhh.
-I wanted to mess
with you guys too.
[theme music]
-Wow, it looks like we have
really great fish today.
-You're getting much better
about knowing the ingredients
for sushi.
-Well, I have a great teacher.
-Oh, really?
No doubt about it,
parents all over the world
hope their sons will take
over their father's profession
with great success.
-Well, it's still too early
to talk about that, Dad.
-Ever since you
were a little boy,
you kept changing your
mind over and over again
about what you
wanted to do and what
you wanted to be when
you were all grown up.
Why don't you try acting
according to your principles,
like I do.
-Well, as a matter of fact, I
have many things I want to do.
-Give me a break, will ya?
I know you were
crazy about karate
before getting
interested in tennis.
Whatever happened to that?
-Tennis is my number
one passion now.
-I see you've also been
developing the gift of gab.
-So you and Aria are
going to be ball boys?
-Yeah.
-You know, Aria
is short tempered,
so you'd better be
careful, Kachiro.
-He's right.
You better not
make him angry, OK?
-Hey, Kato, hurry up.
-OK.
-Hey, who are you?
What school are you from?
Hey, you better answer me.
-Um, Arai?
-If you don't have any business
around here then leave.
-Arai, you OK?
-Just what do you
think you're doing?
-You talking to me?
-Listen, don't you try
acting dumb with me.
Now get the heck out of here.
[punching sounds]
-Arai, are you all right?
-You're a member of
the tennis team, right?
-Uh-huh.
-There's a seventh grade
regular whose name is something
like Echigoya, isn't that right?
KACHIRO (VOICEOVER): A
seventh grader regular?
He must mean Ryoma.
-What a minute, you.
I'm not finished with you yet.
Not by a long--
-Arai!
Arai!
-Who do you think you're
ordering around here?
-I should go find a teacher
and tell them whats happening.
-Hey you.
Bring over Echigoya or else.
Echigoya.
He's not running away, is he?
Maybe I'll hit your
face with my next shot.
-Ryoma.
-Huh?
Echizen.
-What's going on
around here anyway?
-Be careful of that guy.
He's a total psycho.
-So I finally get to meet
the seventh grade regular.
-I don't think I've
ever met you before.
-Look out!
He's got a rock!
-I'm so psycho.
Man, its great.
-Ow.
Ouch.
-There, you've been
hurt pretty badly.
Someone did this to you,
and I want to know who.
And don't tell me you
fell down on your own.
-I fell down on my own.
-Won't you let me help?
-Someone from another
school attacked Echizen?
-Yeah, he's being treated in
the nurse's office now for cuts
and bruises.
Akutsu is obviously a very
violent type of person.
He kicked Arai repeatedly
and served rocks at Echizen.
He's from Yamabuki Junior High.
There's a possibility
we'll be playing them
in the finals of the
Metropolitan matches.
-It's Sengoku's team.
-We better report this to the
Junior High Physical Education
Association.
We'll need to ask Shusuke and
Miss Ruyzaki for the decision.
-Echizen, are you all right?
-Echizen.
What?
-It's nothing.
I just fell down.
-Hey, Echizen, if we file
a complaint against them.
-I fell down.
-No way, Oishi.
The look on his face says he's
going to settle this himself.
-Oh no.
Just, please, don't
make any trouble.
-Are you OK, Ryoma?
-Today's performance was
only an introduction.
-You.
-Don't rush things.
Advance to the finals of
the Metropolitan matches.
I'm a ninth grader
from Yamabuki.
Name's Akutsu.
-Seems like Inui's
training us harder
since he went to visit
Ginka Junior High.
-Ginka's training methods
must have motivated him.
-If Ginka's that strong,
I don't want to find out.
-Hey, you'll only get more
tired if you keep talking.
-OK.
-Is something wrong
with you Taka?
-Not a thing.
I'm fine.
-Well, tell me if
you don't feel well.
You know you shouldn't over
train before the Metropolitan
finals, OK?
-Yeah.
I'm all right.
-Ryoma, are you all right?
-I never felt better.
-OK, everyone, time
for a water break now.
[cheering]
-Thanks a lot, Inui.
I was thirsty.
-Recharge completed.
Ready to push on.
-You're welcome.
Here, this one is yours.
-What happened?
-Inui, what's going on?
-From now on, if your lap
time is more than one minute,
you drink this.
-What is it?
-I've named it penal tea.
This penal tea is very good
for the body and the mind.
-Get that horrible
stuff away from me.
-What do you think is
in that thick drink?
-I don't want to know.
-I'm accelerating.
I refuse to drink
that putrid slime.
-It's working perfectly.
-The more laps that go by now,
the more victims we'll have.
How about you, coach?
Care for a sip?
-No, thank you.
-I think its tasty.
-It doesn't look like
the others agree.
-It's spicy and I still have
a bad taste in my mouth.
-I don't feel so good.
-The regulars are still running.
-They must be on
their 30th lap by now.
-They're all in
really great shape.
-Sure are.
-They really are serious
about not drinking that.
-It's the last lap.
Let me take out a special one.
Last one to finish
gets to drink this.
ALL: Drink the whole thing?
-In that case, I can't lose.
What do you think you're doing?
-You can't run in front of me.
-What?
-It's not a good idea
to get between them
because they're so big.
-Hey.
Here.
-I will not drink penal tea.
Get out of my way.
-I'm not gonna let you pass.
-Hey, hey, look at me.
See ya.
I'm definitely not
drinking that stuff.
-Eiji, you're gonna
drink it all right.
-Taka.
-I'm running just behind Taka
to reduce the wind resistance
until the third corner.
-Everyone's working
so hard not to lose
but it actually tastes good.
You really should try it Tezuka.
-No thanks.
-Got a ways to go.
BOTH: Oh, Echizen, you little--
-Wow, everyone is even.
-Looking good.
Come on, Ryoma.
You can do it.
-Everyone is so fast.
-This works extremely well.
ALL: Here them come.
-It's about time for the finish
and the first runner to make it
to the last corner is--
ALL: Look, it's Ryoma.
-Whoa, it's all of them.
-You all finished
at the same time.
-That was close.
I'm exhausted.
-Inui, for heaven's
sake, you've got
to stop threatening us
with that horrible drink.
-There's not a
winner nor a loser.
I wouldn't want
this to go to waste.
So why doesn't
everyone share it?
ALL: Hey, you drink it all!
-All right, thanks guys.
-See you tomorrow.
-I'm exhausted.
-So Echizen, how's your injury?
-Hm?
-I'm so relieved your
injuries weren't too severe.
-Yeah.
-Hey, is anyone else hungry?
Why don't we all go and
get some hamburgers?
-Yeah, that's a great idea.
-Sorry, I can't
come with you guys.
-What?
You're not coming with us?
-I have something I
have to take care of.
-Well, that sure
is mighty unusual.
-Taka is usually more sociable.
-Hey, maybe he's trying
to watch his budget.
-Watching his budget?
BOTH: These burgers are going
to be on you, of course, right?
Thanks for the burgers, Eiji.
-Aw, man, you guys
are really ruthless.
-Is that Taka over their
walking by himself?
[giggle]
-Looks like he's
going to see someone.
-Hm.
-He must have a date.
-Ahhh.
-Hey, why are you following us?
-Don't ask me too
many questions now.
In any event, I have a feeling
I'll have some good data.
-What do you mean good data?
-Well, anyway, he was unclear
about what he was going to do
and who he was going to meet.
-Welcome.
-A girl?
Whoa.
He's reducing her to tears.
I can't believe Taka did that.
-What's wrong with the
world these days anyhow?
-He's quite a guy.
-What kind of notes
are you taking?
-His personal data.
-There more to him
than meets the eye.
-Yeah, that's for sure.
-Hello, thank you for waiting.
One super deluxe strawberry
chocolate sundae.
-Hey, kid, looks like
you ordered a yummy one.
-I'm gonna order
something as well.
-Yes, something to
eat would be nice.
-Here's our specials menu.
Please take a look, and
let we know what you like.
MOMO: Say no more,
I'll have one of these.
KIKUMARU: And I think
I'll have this one.
All of these go on
Taka's bill, right?
-Good idea.
And I think I'll
have another one.
-Hey, kid, what's
wrong with you?
RYOMA: Akutsu.
-What?
INUI: Yes, he's the one.
-So that's the crazy guy?
-But what's he doing
here with Taka?
-Hey, Akutsu, why
don't you look at me?
-Hey, Jin.
-I haven't seen you since we
took karate classes together.
Well, we're not here to
talk about the old days.
I was told you came
over to my school today.
-So, I just stopped by
to say hello to everyone.
-I'm asking you not to
bother my teammates again.
-It's stupid to talk
about such things.
-Don't make Yuki worry anymore.
YUKI: Jin, stop it.
-And don't even think
about ordering me around.
-Takashi, are you all right?
-But I'll let it
go, just this once.
For old time's sake.
-Jin, why'd you have
to go and do that?
-That's terrible.
Hey, Momo, you better not.
-Thank you for that
treat earlier today.
-Seigaku.
-I haven't introduced
myself yet.
I'm Ryoma Echizen, a
seventh grader at Seigaku.
Nice to meet you.
[theme music]
-Hi, I'm Katsuo Mizuno.
Everyday and in
every way, everyone
is training real
hard to get ready
for the Metropolitan Finals.
Ryoma and Fuji are
even going head to head
in a practice match.
And Ryoma is having a hard
time against Fuji's new move.
Next on the "Prince of
Tennis, The Brown Bear."
Don't they both look happy?