-I'm gonna get that
third singles spot.
-Wait a minute.
You got your eye on
that singles spot, too?
-I'm not much of
a doubles player.
Coach makes the decision
on that one, right?
-She never says until
the last minute,
right before we're ready
to go on the court.
RYOMA: Well then, should
we settle it ourselves?
MOMOSHIRO: Good idea.
Let's go.
[music playing]
-Later you guys.
-All right, then.
See you tomorrow.
Finally, the district
prelims start in two days.
To advance to the
metropolitan matches,
we have to take either first
or second place, right?
-First or second?
-Oh, don't worry, you dim bulbs.
You know our regulars are gonna
trash everybody else for sure.
Besides, our team is
the number one seed.
KACHIRO: That's right.
Three singles and
two doubles matches.
I wonder which
Ryoma will play in.
-Well, Echizen's not
the cooperative type.
I can't really see him
playing doubles at all.
I mean, the guy
is way too moody.
-Stop that!
Don't you dare say
anything mean about Ryoma!
-It's Tomoka.
-You scared me to death.
This is the boys'
locker room, you know.
-So what?
It's your own fault for
leaving the door wide open.
-Hey, Tomoka.
-So, where's Ryoma?
Huh?
-Oh, he's already gone.
-He left?
What about practice?
-You know we already played
for our team rankings.
That means no practice.
TOMOKA: What?
No way!
I can't believe they
cancelled practice.
I was gonna cheer
for Ryoma, too.
SAKUNO: There's always tomorrow
TOMOKA: Tomorrow's no good.
The district team matches
start the day after.
It'll be totally,
completely different.
-Why so different?
TOMOKA: "District prelims
start in two days.
Go for it, Ryoma!"
See?
-Yikes.
And tomorrow?
-It says, "fight, Ryoma.
It's your day."
What a bummer!
I worked so hard on these.
I stayed up past my
bedtime and everything.
-Cheer up, Tomoka.
I'll buy you a soda.
-That's OK.
It's no use.
And soda can't
possibly cheer me up.
-Hmm.
Let me think.
And after I said that, the
news spread like crazy.
Now a bunch of girls want
to join Ryoma's fan club.
As president of
the fan club, I'm
thrilled to welcome
anyone who wants to join.
And I'm going to sign up every
single girl in seventh grade.
So what do you think?
Pretty cool, huh?
-Huh?
Look, it's him-- Ryoma.
-I can't believe it.
Whoa!
MOMOSHIRO: Hey.
-Oh, hi, Momo.
-Hey, Echizen.
-Momoshiro's here too?
-So what exactly are
you doing in here?
-I'm getting a cheeseburger.
What do you think I'm doing?
-Eating junk food, are you?
-Aren't you guys on the
Seigaku tennis team?
-Yeah.
Yeah we are.
-Is it really true the
positions are set for the match?
It must be.
Are you guys regulars?
-Huh?
TOMOKA: What's
the deal with her?
She's not even in the fan club,
and she's acting all flirty!
-Tomoka, please just calm down.
-Since you're not denying
it, it must be right.
Hmm?
Seigaku's top singles would
be team captain Tezuka.
And your number two
singles would be Fuji.
-You sure know a lot.
AN: Well, the Seigaku
regulars are ultra-famous.
So tell me, which
one of you hotshots
is going to play
third singles, huh?
-Hmm.
Huh?
WAITRESS: Next, please.
-Huh?
I gotta go now.
Good luck, guys.
I'd like to order some
food to go, please.
-Can I help you?
Would you like something?
RYOMA AND MOMOSHIRO: Hmm.
A cheeseburger and a large cola.
Hmm?
-No, wait.
Make that a double cheeseburger.
-And some nuggets
and a shake, too.
-Add an order of
fries, and megasize it.
-Make it a large shake instead.
-Make that three
double cheeseburgers.
I'm starved after all
that tennis today.
-What?
-Double everything he ordered.
I practiced way
more than he did.
-OK.
-What is going on
with those two?
-Don't know.
-Hmm.
-Look at them eat.
This is gross.
I can't believe how
competitive they are.
-That's why they win.
[music playing]
SUMIRE: Hmm, who should
I put in third singles?
MAMOROU: Hi there, coach.
-Hi.
Glad you're here.
-I thought you might be hungry.
I brought this-- a nice snack.
-Thanks.
How thoughtful of you.
I'll make us some tea.
Come, sit down.
MAMOROU: Oh, uh, don't
worry about me, really.
SUMIRE: You're not with
your lady friend today?
-Oh, do you mean Saori Shiba?
SUMIRE: Yeah.
The two of you
make a nice couple.
-Oh, come on, coach.
Stop matchmaking.
Hmm, is that the lineup
for the district matches?
Looks like you're having
a hard time with it.
That doesn't seem
very much like you.
-I've got an awful lot of
great talent this year.
-Thank you.
So then, if you've decided
on the number one and number
two spots, that leaves
Kaoru or Momoshiro
for number three singles?
Right?
Hmm.
-I'm only beginning.
It's the first
match of the year.
But there's one
player in particular
I'm keeping an eye on.
MAMOROU: You mean Ryoma?
Why don't you let Tezuka or Fuji
sit out the first two or three
games of the year?
-It's not like I
haven't thought of that.
-I got it.
Why don't you talk
it over with Nanjiro?
He may have some
interesting ideas.
-I wouldn't ask that
good-for-nothing loser
for advice if my--
MAMOROU: Uh-oh.
Whoa.
Hmm, it's really late.
Uh, gotta run.
I'll be back.
Thanks for the tea.
Appreciate it.
Uh, bye coach.
-Oh, well.
Wasn't any help as usual.
[music playing]
I wonder if I should call.
I could use a little help.
[groaning]
MOMOSHIRO: I definitely
ate too much.
-That's because you
just wouldn't give up.
-Oh, knock it off.
I'm sick.
Listen, Echizen.
RYOMA: What is it?
-It's just like that girl
said before-- the first two
single spots are probably
going to go to Tezuka and Fuji.
Number one doubles is
locked up by Eiji and Oishi.
I don't know if you
know this, but they
were our ace team that went all
the way to nationals last year.
So when you think about,
that leaves Taka, Viper, you,
and of course me.
We need one for singles, two in
doubles, and one on the bench.
So that means--
RYOMA AND MOMOSHIRO: I'm gonna
get that third singles spot!
-Wait a minute.
You got your eye on
that singles spot, too?
-I'm not much of
a doubles player.
Coach makes the decision
on that one, right?
-She never says until
the last minute,
right before we're
ready go on the court.
RYOMA: I can't
wait till tomorrow.
MOMOSHIRO: Me either.
RYOMA: Well then, should
we settle it ourselves?
MOMOSHIRO: Good idea.
Let's do it.
You sure are quick
to pick a fight.
RYOMA: I just want to
get this over with.
MOMOSHIRO: OK, hotshot.
Let's go and see if we can find
a court with some lights on.
[music playing]
Hey, looks like we lucked
out and found a little street
tennis.
RYOMA: The lights look OK.
No complaints
whoever wins, right?
-You know, I'm glad to
hear you say that, pal.
[music playing]
-Uh, excuse me.
Do you know if there's
a court fee here?
-No, you don't have to pay.
-Hey guys.
-Huh?
-Look, it's that girl.
-Never seen you guys before.
Have you ever played?
MOMOSHIRO: A little.
-That's great.
Looks like we got a
couple of beginners.
-And still only one court.
You guys know our rules?
-No.
You know, I'm starting not
to like these guys very much.
IZUMI: I guess I'll
just have to tell you.
It's like a round robin--
a brutal round robin.
We play one game.
Whoever loses goes out.
-That sounds like fun.
I'm first.
OK, Echizen?
-I'll go first.
IZUMI: Oh.
And there's one more thing--
we only play doubles.
-Huh?
[music playing]
-We really doing this?
-We can't back down.
It'll look bad if we do.
UMPIRE: The Momoshiro/Echizen
team serves first.
Play ball.
[music playing]
-What was that call about?
-It was that old bat
driving me crazy.
And when I asked
her what she wanted,
she just kept right
on lecturing me.
-Don't be rude.
You owe her a lot.
She was your teacher, after all.
NANIJIRO: That was
a long time ago.
NANAKO: Oh, uncle.
[meowing]
[meowing and screaming]
Serves you right, uncle!
-Man, that hurt.
Oh, you know, when
she called, I think
the old bat had a question.
Ah, forget it.
-All right then.
You guys ready or what?
-Look, it's a kit
from middle school.
And one from grade school.
-Pretty gutsy.
-I really don't like 'em.
-Let's just take 'em apart, OK?
IZUMI: The challengers serve.
-Those guys are in high school.
They're pretty big, so
hang in there if you can.
-I have had it.
They're going down.
Let's put them out
of their misery.
-Gotcha.
-At least he looks like he's
got all the right moves.
[music playing]
-This should be a piece of cake.
Oh.
Oh, dude.
-Whoa, check that out.
-Oh, man, did you guys see that?
-I've never seen that before.
-That was unbelievable.
Man, that was awesome.
UMPIRE: 15-0.
30-0.
-Hey, that was a serve?
That's pretty impressive
for around here.
UMPIRE: Game to the
Momoshiro/Echizen team.
-He aced them four times.
-So, who wants to go next?
-We'll take you two on.
[music playing]
UMPIRE: Game to the
Momoshiro/Echizen team.
-This time the won it
on service returns.
-Scary.
-No kidding.
-What do you think?
-They're way better
than I thought.
But for doubles, they've
got a lot of problems.
[music playing]
-All right.
We're waiting.
So does anybody want to play?
FUKAWA: Yeah.
I think we're up to it.
UMPIRE: Cool.
They're the best players
we've got around here.
-It's those two guys.
-Here you go.
[music playing]
UMPIRE: The Fukawa/Izumi
team to serve.
Come on guys, get 'em.
-I'll bet you any amount of
money they've never even played
doubles before.
So just go ahead and hit the
ball right down the middle.
-OK.
[music playing]
FUKAWA (VOICEOVER):
Right down the middle.
UMPIRE: 15-0.
-I have gotten that
one if you'd let me.
-Well, no kidding, hotshot!
But it's the player
at the net who's
supposed to take the ball.
Got it?
[music playing]
UMPIRE: 30-0.
RYOMA: -Would you
watch me already?
-Don't you get it?
If you're up at the
net, just put it away.
-What a weird team.
They're so darn good,
but they're not in sync.
IZUMI: Fukawa!
-Got it.
-What?
That one's yours!
UMPIRE: 40-0.
Yeah.
-Oh, come on.
You've got to be able to pick
up the balls I can't get to.
-I've got a question.
Is that the sideline
for doubles?
MOMOSHIRO: Yeah, so what?
-I've never even
played doubles before.
-What?
No way!
Never?
-Do I really look like
a team player to you?
-I'd say this game's
all but over for them.
-Echizen, we can't let these
clowns get the better of us.
-Gotcha.
[music playing]
UMPIRE: Game and set to
the Fukawa/Izumi team.
All right!
-What?
We lost it?
We never even had a
chance to get into it.
-Momo, face it-- we did
kind of stink up the court.
AN (VOICEOVER): And
that is no exaggeration.
RYOMA: You have a lousy
sense of teamwork.
-That's great coming from you.
Singles would have
been different.
We could have wiped the court.
-Hey, you two.
Are you going home now?
-We lost, so we kind of have to.
-That's for sure.
You two couldn't keep
up with those guys.
I expected more from
Seigaku regulars.
I thought you'd do better.
MOMOSHIRO: She's totally right.
That was so bad.
Well, let's go, Echizen.
-Fukawa, Izumi!
You guys rock!
You trashed two great players!
-Yeah, it's no wonder you
starred on the Grokurin team.
-Gyokurin team?
Wait a minute.
Aren't they the first school we
play in the district matches?
-Playing them will
be a walk over,
especially if they play
like they did today.
-They're not bad,
not too bad at all.
But they're sure
not a doubles team.
IZUMI: No matter how many
times we played 'em, we'd win.
FUKAWA: You got that right.
MOMOSHIRO: Listen, Echizen.
I've been thinking.
You know what I said about
taking that number three
singles spot?
I changed my mind.
-You know, I was
thinking the same thing.
RYOMA AND MOMOSHIRO:
We'll own those guys.
[music playing]
-I never should
have called Nanjiro.
It'll all be good.
[music playing]
CASHIER: Hello.
That's 860 yen.
-Doubles for beginners, huh?
He's probably a novice.
How cute.
-He'll hear you!
-Oh, please come and
see us again soon.
[music playing]
-I'm Izumi from
Gyokurin Middle School.
-And I'm Fukawa,
also from Gyokurin.
IZUMI: Hey, Fukawa.
Those guys we played
doubles with the other night
were pathetic.
They're both really
good players,
but they just couldn't
get it together.
FUKAWA: Hey, look, Izumi.
Our opponents are
those same guys.
IZUMI: No kidding?
And they're from Seigaku?
Awesome.
Chalk one up for us.
MOMOSHIRO: Next on the Prince
of Tennis-- "The Perfect Match."
IZUMI: Are they
talking about us?
FUKAWA: You bet.