RYOMA (VOICEOVER): Man.
Oishi's tenacious.
TOMOKA: He got it!
HORIO: The return's too low.
It'll go in the net!
OISHI (VOICEOVER): Not with
Echizen's power, it won't.
[theme music]
-Yes, that's right.
Yeah, I got it.
Sure.
I'll see you soon.
Now then.
-Hm.
-Oh, so this is where
you were, Shiba, huh?
Hey, are these the photos
from when you went to Seigaku?
-I had to do something, right?
I can't just follow you around.
-Well, that's a good attitude.
Did you catch anything
interesting in these, Shiba?
Wow, look at this.
Hm.
Hey.
-Yes?
-Isn't this Kirihara?
So, he was at Seigaku?
-That's right.
Do you know him, Mr. Inoue?
-Of course I do.
Akaya Kirihara is
the eighth grade ace
at Rikkai, the school that
fields the top team from Kanto.
Just like Ryoma, he's
a junior high kid
who can do the split step.
SHIBA: Well, his tennis may be
good, but that not his manners.
He called me old!
Argh!
Can you believe it?
[mumbling]
-Gah!
I'll get back at him if
it's the last thing I do.
-Maybe he came to
scout the competition.
-Huh?
-That must mean they
consider Seigaku a threat.
It looks like the
Kanto tournament
is getting more and more
interesting, huh Shiba?
Come on.
Let's go cover the story.
-All right.
Here's what we do.
We go to Rikkai first, right?
-No.
To Seigaku.
-Huh?
Wait, I don't get it.
So, now tell me again.
Why are we going to Seigaku?
We know what all the regulars.
What's the deal?
-You don't understand
anything, do you?
-OK, what have you
been keeping from me?
Come on, cough it up.
INOUE: Don't worry,
you'll understand soon.
-Well, that's unusual.
-Even I wash my face sometimes.
-That's not it.
It's just that I've never
seen you wash your face prior
to a match before.
-Don't worry, Tezuka.
The weather is nice.
-Yeah.
-I'll just go on ahead.
-So, wanna go?
-Oh, that looks scary.
Oishi Sure looks like he's out
for blood this time around.
-Quit your jabbering.
It's distracting.
-That's part of the
strategy, Kaidoh.
The game begins in
the locker room.
I hear the pros do
it all the time.
-What am I supposed to do
against all those big shots?
-Take it easy.
It's only tennis.
-But then again, it
is tennis, right?
Taka, you forgot your racket.
-Still have a ways to go.
INOUE: Shiba, you
ready to rock and roll?
-I'm all set.
Hey, Mr. Inoue.
-Hm?
-I think this is going to
be a very exciting story.
INOUE: That's true.
You never know what's
gonna happen here.
That's why it's so interesting.
Now do you understand?
-Of course.
I'd like to think that I always
had a good eye for the story.
INOUE: You know,
you may be right.
SHIBA: Well, I'd count
on it, if I were you.
RYUZAKI: Listen up.
The Kanto tournament is the
toughest one we've faced yet.
Top notch players who we
haven't heard of may pop up,
so it's important that we
field the best team possible.
We're really gonna need our
strongest players out there,
so our top two
winners of each block
are probably the
smartest guys to field.
Don't get down.
-Right!
-Man, it's so tense around here.
-That's for sure.
Hey, what's going on now?
-It's Ryuzaki.
She's doing the
inter team ranking.
-Ooh, the ranking tournament.
-Oh yeah.
Seigaku's the only school that
has these monthly matches,
and I think they're the
biggest secret to our success.
-Except the seventh graders
aren't allowed to enter them.
-Of course you know, Ryoma's
the big exception to the rule,
as usual.
-Oh, I see.
Now it makes sense.
It's a ranking tournament.
-Hi, Ms. Shiba.
-If any of you think
you're a shoe in,
you are sorely mistaken.
This ranking
tournament alone will
determine who plays in
the Kanto tournament.
Got it?
-Yes.
-Let me put it to
you another way.
Right now, anyone
could make the team.
-All right.
We're ready to get started
with the ranking tournament.
Please go to your
assigned courts now.
TEAM: Yes!
KAIDOH: Whatever.
ANNOUNCER: Game
and match to Arai.
-Hey, I'm on fire!
Burning!
All right!
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Kawamura.
-Yes!
Way to go, Kawamura.
-A moon volley.
-You're looking
good today, buddy.
ANNOUNCER: Game
and match to Oishi.
Game and match to Nagayama.
-Man, the field is
quickly narrowing.
-Yeah.
The regulars are
sure cleaning up.
-But that Block A sure
looks mighty tough.
After all, Inui's still there.
So is Momo and Captain
Tezuka as well.
ANNOUNCER: Game and match to
Tezuka, six games to Love.
-Hm?
Here it comes,
Momo's dunk smash.
-Boom.
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Momoshiro.
BOY: Wow, again.
He didn't lose a single point.
-Uh, well, thank you
for the great game.
-Your approach to
the net isn't bad,
but try coming in
a little earlier.
-Uh, OK.
BOY: Aw, man.
If I lose today, I'm
out of the tournament.
BOY: I haven't even
won a game yet.
-Here!
-There it is!
Kaidoh's snake!
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Kaidoh.
[hiss]
-What a boring game that was.
That loser's in Block D.
ANNOUNCER: Match point, Echizen.
-Hey.
You still have a ways to go.
-It's a kick serve!
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Echizen.
Six games to Love.
-I guess you just weren't
lucky in the draw, that's all.
-Echizen, take it
easy on me, will you?
-Why should I?
-Well, it's just as we
expected it to turn out.
Looks like the regulars
are all going through.
-Well, that's no surprise.
They're all doing really well.
-No surprise?
-Huh?
ANNOUNCER: Game and match
to Inui, six games to Love.
-According to my calculations,
you were short 45 centimeters.
-We may have one more yet.
Seigaku's former number three.
Our data champ still
has some game in him.
-Wow.
Looks like Inui's
really fired up today.
I'm sure glad I'm
not in his block.
-Yeah.
I wanna go watch Block A.
-Don't sweat it.
His game looks really bad.
BOY: You see that?
Only two will remain
from each block.
BOY: It stinks that one of these
two guys has to lose his spot.
ANNOUNCER: Game and match to
Kikumaru, six games to Love.
-All right.
Hey, I'm the first
one to get a slot.
-No way.
Kikumaru is just
on a roll today.
-Hey, Arai, you're looking
at straight bagels.
-Aw, shut up.
When are we ever
going to be regulars?
I'm sick and tired of this.
-Eiji's lucky.
He's already won
his regular spot.
-Ha ha ha!
Don't you worry.
I'm a super regular.
Ha ha!
All right, all right.
So, you came fight?
Come on, come on!
Challenge me.
Let's go!
On fire!
-That means the regulars
will be Kikumaru, Kawamura,
Fuji, and five others.
-Tomorrow's match is
between Oishi and Ryoma.
-Neither one's lost a
match yet, but they're both
sure to get places.
-And that means three more.
But who's stronger?
-Is it Oishi or Ryoma?
We'll find out tomorrow.
OISHI: What a beauty.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER):
Man, Oishi's tenacious.
TOMOKA: He's got it!
HORIO: The return's too low!
It'll go in the net!
OISHI (VOICEOVER): Not with
Echizen's power, it won't.
I'm a ninth grader.
I've got seniority.
I can't lose to
some seventh grader.
BOY: I just knew
Oishi would get to it.
Amazing.
OISHI: Can you
reach it, Echizen?
ANNOUNCER: Out.
Game and match to Echizen,
six games to three.
-Wow, judging
instantly up in the air
whether the ball
might be in or not.
Ryoma Echizen is incredible.
-All right, Ryoma.
He made the cut.
-Good game, pal.
You're one tough opponent.
But guess what?
With one loss, I
made the team too.
-Ah.
This feels good.
Man, this heat's
making me tired.
-What's up with him?
He hasn't even done anything.
-Ryoma, I've been
meaning to tell you,
congratulations on your big win.
-You didn't lose
one single match.
Only three players left, huh?
-Echizen did some job on me.
What's wrong, Eiji?
-Hurry up, Momo's
match is gonna end
before you can say slam dunk.
-Hey, shut up, you pipsqueak.
-Sorry!
[hiss]
-Kaidoh always scares
the daylights out of me.
-Come on, you better
simmer down, Horio.
The match is just
about to begin.
HORIO: What?
You mean it hasn't started yet?
-It's all over.
You missed it.
-Huh?
-Momo didn't win.
Is that true?
Momo won against that junior
all-star player Sengoku,
but he only took two
games against Inui.
Plus he lost to Tezuka.
His score now stands at
three wins and two losses.
-Then that means Momo's
lost his regular slot.
-Horio stop!
[mumbling]
-Hey, do you think that
Momo's leg is hurting?
It might still be
cramping on him.
-No, that wasn't it.
He was actually in great shape.
-What went wrong?
-Well, I think Inui
just played a great game
and overwhelmed Momo.
These past two months, during
the preliminaries and also
the Metropolitan Tournament,
he hasn't been just gathering
data on our opponents.
No, not at all.
-Well now.
So, tell me, how
does it feel to have
been analyzed for
the last two months?
-So, he's been gathering
data on us too.
[hiss]
-Wow.
I never imagined
that the competition
was so fierce within the team.
-Well, these guys are aiming
for the top tier, right?
-Tezuka.
I've gathered my data.
This time, I'm going to win.
Without fail.
[theme music]
INUI: This is Sadaharu Inui.
The long-waited inter
team ranking tournament
is finally here.
I haven't forgotten the
feeling when I lost to Echizen,
or how I felt as I've lost
to you for the last three
years, Captain Tezuka.
My detailed data and
intensive training
were all just preparations
for this moment.
This time, I will win
against Captain Tezuka.