-Huh?
It's a snake shot!
-Looks like Saint Rudolph was
expecting a boomerang snake.
-Now's your chance, guys.
-A lob?
How many times did I
tell them not to hit one?
-Look how high Momoshiro gets.
-Momo's timing
couldn't be better.
-Yeah!
There!
ANNOUNCER: Game to Seigaku.
Five games to three.
[theme music]
-Yeah, let's go, Momoshiro!
-There's his snake shot!
-It's his boomerang snake!
ANNOUNCER: 15-Love.
[cheering]
-Not too bad, Kaidoh.
-You're in no place to say that.
Just stay out of the way, OK?
-Viper.
Don't get too cocky.
Big mistake.
-Huh?
Say that again.
-Hey!
-Leave me alone.
I don't wanna see your ugly
face around here again.
-You're the one who's
getting in my way.
-You better take
that back, you loser.
The way you do things
has always bugged me.
-What about you?
I don't know why I--
-At first they may
look a bit mismatched.
They're not.
I believe the sum of the parts
is even greater than the whole.
-It seems like
Seigaku's winning now.
I really don't like how
it's going, Captain Akazawa.
-Kaneda, come on,
think about it.
Yunagasawa and
Kisaru are golden.
They always come through
for us in a crunch.
And that is why those guys
have won all their games.
BOY (VOICEOVER): Darn.
That's some kinda
secret weapon he has.
[hissing]
-He can only do that if
the ball is near the line.
In other words, if I place
my shot near the center line,
he can't curve it
around the pole.
-That's it.
It looks like he's
playing in the middle
to cut off the boomerang snake.
BOY: This is bad, Kaidoh.
-Winning like that--
that's no fun.
-Come on!
-That's cool.
-Huh?
-You chump.
We wanted you to make that shot.
-He's not-- The lob's
got a slice rotation.
It hangs in the air and
moves with the wind.
It's too hard to hit
a dunk smash off that.
-No way you could smash that.
-Hm.
I Huh?
What the-- I can't believe
how high that guy jumps.
And his balance.
-Here it comes.
I'm gonna play it anyway.
-Straight down the line.
It's mine.
Huh?
The ball's kicking out!
-No way!
-Huh?
-Hmph.
-What did he do?
What just happened?
-Who knows?
It's bad.
-Looks like Momo just
cleaned his clock.
The ball took a weird
hop, sure enough.
-Hey.
Yanagisawa.
Yanagisawa!
-Is that player going to be OK?
-Yanagisawa!
-I see four refs.
Why do we need them?
-It's not good.
I'm afraid he's
done for the day.
-Yeah, I guess you're right.
-He can't play.
No way he can go on after
taking a hit like that.
BOY: You think he's
gonna be all right?
-That was some smash.
Did you see that?
Seigaku rocks.
-Hey, Yanagisawa, this
really isn't the best way
to concede a tennis match.
Hey, come on and
finish up, all right?
Hm?
This is no time to quit.
Hey, wait a second!
ANNOUNCER: St. Rudolph defaults.
Win to Seigaku.
[cheering]
-Boy oh boy.
Wasn't that a surprising ending?
-Those two guys, they never
do things the normal way.
-Strange things sure do happen.
-Huh?
Hey, wait.
Aw!
But I'm still itching to play.
Come on, man.
Oh, no no no.
-Jerk.
-Hey!
I haven't burned
off this energy yet.
Hey, come on!
Don't go!
Where you going?
Please, come on.
-Let go of me.
-Momoshiro's jumping dunk smash
sure was incredible, wasn't it?
-Yeah, it really smoked.
If things go like
this, Seigaku's
gonna win straight through.
-You have a point.
Seigaku's golden pair's up next.
There's absolutely no way that
Oishi and Kigumaru will lose.
-Oh, come on.
This stinks a lot.
An awful lot.
Man, that guy just ran away.
-No he didn't.
You hit him in the face
with a ball, you idiot.
-Shut up.
I didn't mean to hit him.
-Argh.
-So now, tell me straight.
-He's fine.
He's just exhausted.
Man, it's so frustrating.
They really had momentum.
If he just weren't hit.
-It was the wrong place
at the wrong time.
-No, you're wrong.
They kept improving their game.
We just didn't give
them enough credit.
They were really that good.
-Hm.
Hm?
Mizuki.
-Stop making excuses.
If you guys had listened,
you could have won.
That was disgraceful.
Captain.
We can never ever allow
that to happen again.
-Mizuki.
Don't worry.
I'll show them.
I'll give them a little
taste of my backhand.
We'll trash Seigaku's
golden pair.
-That sounds good.
ANNOUNCER: Seigaku
and St. Rudolph number
one doubles players, please
come to center court.
-Come on, let's go.
-Yeah, let's take
these guys apart.
-Right.
ANNOUNCER: This is
the second match
of the semifinals of
Block D. Number one
doubles to the court.
-Eiji, here we go.
-OK.
-I'm gonna have fun
with you, Eiji Kikumaru.
BOY: Did you hear?
Yuuta Fuji of St.
Rudolph is playing today.
BOY: No way.
Are you talking about
the lefty killer?
BOY: Yeah.
He was practicing for a
match with Seigaku's Tezuka,
but there was some
mistake and now he's
gonna be playing some
seventh grade regular.
BOY: really?
That'll have Seigaku
in a real pinch.
BOY: So the seventh
grader's a lefty too?
-Huh?
BOY: Actually he is.
BOY: Wow.
It's going from bad to worse.
-Oh well.
If I've gotta play a
south paw, at least
I should face
McEnroe in his prime.
-Oh, there he is!
-Ryoma!
-Hey, what are you doing here?
-Please, Horio, get me a drink.
-Not right now.
There's no time for that.
-Look, Oishi and
Kikumaru are in deep.
-Hm?
[whispering]
-Game to St. Rudolph.
That makes two games to Love.
St. Rudolph leads.
[gasping]
-They broke the golden
pair on their serve.
-Yikes.
-What's the big surprise?
It's all part of the plan.
-It looks like
those guys are only
returning balls to Kikumaru.
-Looks like they're trying
their hardest to break up
the golden pair so they're
only hitting the one player.
-What a pain.
They're forcing me
to hit shots I hate.
Well then, here.
-I get it.
He's purposely moving around the
ball to excuse his best shots.
I respect his talent, but
it won't work forever.
-Whoa, diving volley.
ANNOUNCER: Out.
15-Love.
-That was a close call.
-Hey, Eiji.
Don't worry.
I know that they're pounding
everything they've got at you.
Stay calm.
I promise I'll cover your back.
We'll do this together.
Eiji?
-Huh?
I'm good.
All right, let's take it back.
I can do it.
-Yeah.
-This isn't good.
Eiji's losing his concentration.
Usually, Eiji
focuses better when
they keep hitting
the ball at him.
What's up?
-I don't think it's possible
that our golden pair of Oishi
and Kikumaru can
just lose like that.
-Looks like they're
wearing Kikumaru down.
Hang in there, golden pair!
-I think Eiji's
losing his focus.
ANNOUNCER: 30-Love.
-There's too many
unforced errors.
-No.
-Ryoma.
Do you think Akazawa's pressure
could be too much for him?
-Yes, but that's not all.
-Inui.
-Akazawa is a great
singles player,
but he's not used to doubles.
Looks like they're
up to something.
There appears to be
another reason for this.
-Captain.
-OK.
RYOMA: You know, it looks
like there are at least five
or six balls.
-Hm?
What's that?
Did you see something?
-Whenever the bigger
St. Rudolph guy hits.
-That's it.
Whenever Akazawa
hits a backhand,
he has the strange habit of
using the top of the racket.
It's not the sweet spot at
the edge of the racket head.
So it hits harder
on the strings.
In the process, that ball picks
up an awful lot of movement.
The average person
simply cannot track it.
But Kikumaru has a
keen sense of movement.
His eyes track every
movement of the ball.
It is a gift as well as a curse.
-My eyes really hurt.
-I'll bet.
-No way.
You really see five balls?
I see only one.
-One, two.
I see eight.
ANNOUNCER: Net ball.
40-Love.
-In this humidity, they are
pounding so hard on Kikumaru
to force the shots
he hates to return.
Add in this blur shot, and
they're wearing him out,
mentally as well as physically.
So then what you've really
been trying to say is that--
-Kikumaru's been seen a
bunch of balls, right?
-His great eyesight's
killing him.
That just stinks.
-So that's it.
They have their
singles ace playing
doubles so he can
wear down Kikurmaru.
They weakened Kikumaru's sharp
eyes with Akazawa's blur shot.
St. Rudolph's manager
Mizuki came up
with a diabolical
anti-Kikumaru strategy.
-It's way too late
for you now, Inui.
Kikumaru is already
falling apart.
There's a limit to how long
someone can concentrate.
Kikumaru already reached his.
-Huh?
-Kikumaru may pull through.
He can concentrate.
-I hope they're called the
golden pair for a reason.
-Huh?
[excited chatter]
BOY: All right.
We're practicing doubles today.
Momoshiro Echizen
versus Oishi Kikumaru.
Hit the court.
-Sure.
BOY: Doubles?
Me?
BOY: Quit complaining.
BOY: Oh, man.
I don't like doubles.
BOY: What's the big deal?
Get on the court.
-Huh?
-What the-- What is this?
-Practice with the
rope, rookie, and it
will help out your doubles game.
-This is weird.
-No problem at all.
Got it.
-Echizen, don't pull so hard.
-Uh, OK.
-Huh?
-Kikumaru Beam!
-Whoa.
And that's why they call
them the golden pair.
-Their teamwork is so perfect.
-And look at that.
Their rope isn't tangled at all.
-Hm.
-You can see Oishi's style.
-Huh?
-He watches the
whole court closely
and controls the
opponent's pace.
Just like a chess
player who cautiously
waits for his opening.
-Of course, he'll
never tangle the rope.
-And I guess that's
why Kikumaru is
able to attack so
aggressively, right?
-Yeah.
-No wonder.
The golden pair.
They can't lose.
-Go for it!
Never mind the blur shot.
-Golden pair!
-That's sweet.
Kikumaru rocks.
-Kill the ball, Kikumaru!
-Awesome!
-Now's my chance.
-Kikamaru.
You're through!
-I don't think so.
-Huh?
It's Oishi!
-Oishi?
Too bad, Akazawa,
'cause this is doubles.
-Here it goes.
Oishi's best shot.
Absolutely control.
He'll aim his shot right
over his opponent, a top spin
volley.
-Huh?
-Oh no, the-- the moon
volley, heading near the line.
No way.
-That's not right.
Oishi didn't aim near the line.
-What?
-He aimed right at the line.
-Amazing.
They're even more golden now.
-I thought it was over for sure.
-Oishi is just smoking hot.
-Oishi.
-They're good.
It's no surprise to me that
they made it to the nationals.
Impressive.
-Yeah.
Only Oishi could do
a move like that.
-It's still early in the game.
[theme music]
KIKAMARU: Yahoo!
It's Kikamaru.
The St. Rudolph
match is a killer.
Why do they only focus on me?
This is bad.
But we've been working
on a new trick.
Right, Oishi?
Next on "The Prince of
Tennis," Mortal Blow,
Eiji's Famed Sleep Attack.
I'm not sleeping.
I'm not.