-Forget the slice serve, kid.
Give me what you've got.
[rock music playing]
-Here it is, our latest issue.
It should tell you all you need
to know about our magazine.
-You could've mailed it.
-Yes, but our magazine
spares no effort
in finding the best
student tennis players.
-Hmm.
So I guess you want to know
who's best around here,
is that it?
-Heh heh, you're on to me.
I'd appreciate any tips.
-My lips are sealed.
-I wrote that article.
Pretty good, huh?
-You should write
more objectively.
There's no place
for sentimentality
in the game of tennis.
-What's wrong with it?
I grew up watching all the
great players of the day.
They were my heroes.
I wanted to be just
like Nanjiro Echizen.
-Echizen, huh?
-He was a proud flower from the
Land of the Cherry Blossoms.
And they called him the Samurai.
[crowd gasps in amazement]
ANNOUNCER: Game, set, and
match to Mister Echizen.
-When he retired from the
game at such a young age,
I was crushed.
If only he'd played one
or two years longer,
he would've been the top player
in the world, the grand slam.
It would've been his for
the taking, I know it.
-Echizen.
I remember well.
GIRL: Hey, how's it going?
BOY: I'm OK.
GIRL: What's up?
BOY: Not much.
GIRL: Nice to see you.
BOY: Let's go.
GIRL: OK.
[bell dings]
-Hey, Echizen, wait up.
Yo, you're brand new
around here, aren't you?
Hey, are you going play
on the tennis team?
-Who's asking?
-My name's Horio.
Maybe you've heard
our school has
one of the best
teams in the country?
Me, I've already played for two
years at a really great tennis
camp.
They don't let just anyone
play here, you know.
But I'm a cinch
to make the team.
Huh?
Hey, Echizen, hang on!
-What's this?
The little mouse isn't
looking where he's going?
-Huh?
-If he's not careful, he's
liable to end up as cat food.
Huh?
Don't think I like
that glare of yours.
Oh, well.
I can tell you're
new around here,
so I'll let it pass this time.
Just watch where you're going.
-Who was that guy?
-I don't know.
Some goofball.
HORIO: Whoa, what a setup.
Look at those courts.
Seigaku's even
better than I figure.
Come on, Echizen.
Let's join up.
-You can forget about that.
Today new members
can't even register
because of the second
and third year matches.
But who knows?
Maybe you can try
again tomorrow.
-Most of the freshman
have already gone home.
So we thought, why
not stay awhile
and pick up balls on the ground?
-But that's no fun.
-Hey, over there.
You guys want to
join our tennis team?
-Yes, sir.
-You bet.
I'm a seventh grader,
Katsuo Mizuno.
-I'm Kachiro Kato.
-I'm Satoshi Horio.
I've played great tennis
for two whole years already.
I can even balance a racket
on the end of my nose.
-Hey, you.
What's your problem?
Haven't got a name?
Can't talk?
You deaf, or something?
-Leave him alone.
All right, now we're going
to play a really fun game.
-Really?
What kind of game?
-Heh.
I know the game.
Yeah, yeah.
You're all going to
love to play this game.
-The rules are very simple.
You serve from the other court.
If you can knock the can over in
ten shots, you win 10,000 yen.
-What?
-That's right.
It's kind of an initiation.
-It'll cost you 200 yen
to take the challenge.
Anyone game?
-For 10,000 yen?
I am.
[both together] We
want to try to too.
-We are ready to
accept the challenge.
-That's the spirit.
[chuckles]
-Hmm.
-Hey, Sakuno.
Why are you so interested
in tennis all of a sudden?
-Oh, but I've
always liked tennis.
I want to go early to turn
in my registration form.
-Hey, did you say
registration form?
You're going to the
tennis courts, right?
Thank goodness I found you.
I am so totally lost.
-Huh?
-Oh, I forgot, sorry.
I'm Saori Shiba.
I'm the junior editor for the
Pro Tennis Monthly magazine.
We're interested in the
boys team this year.
I hear they have some
really talented players.
I'm writing about
their new recruits,
but I can't even find
the tennis courts.
Can you?
-Hey, Shiba.
What are you doing over there?
-Oh, hi, Mister Inoue.
-All done with your interviews?
-Well, actually, I haven't
done any of them yet.
-None of them?
-Missed again.
Too bad, losers.
Next.
-Man oh man.
You guys are the
worst I've ever seen.
-But we've never played before.
What do you expect
from beginners?
-I don't think anyone
could hit that target.
It's too small and
much too far away.
-Well, then watch me.
I've had two years of tennis.
Hello, 10,000 yen.
Missed.
Must be a cross wind.
Well, this time for sure.
I'm losing.
-Yes you are.
And you've only got
one left to hit.
-It only takes one.
All I've got to do is hit
it just right, and then--
Oh, I'm a loser too.
-Time to settle.
-I must have stubbed my toe.
Well, I guess that
means we're out 200 yen.
[all sigh]
-Huh?
What's the matter
with all of you?
Can't you add?
Read and weep, my friends.
This game costs 500 yen per
serve, plus 200 for playing.
Pay up.
You owe us 5,200 apiece.
-5,200?
-Where are we supposed to
find that kind of money?
-You better find it
somewhere, or else.
-Hey, you over there.
Too scared to try it yourself?
-What a wimp.
He could never play on our team.
-Let's get this over with.
-Echizen, don't be a fool.
You're throwing good money away.
-There's no way a normal serve
will knock that can over.
It's too heavy.
-Huh?
-What are you talking about?
-Cheater.
There's rocks inside.
-Look at that.
He hit it square and
knocked the top right off.
-Hmm.
-Cheaters!
You ought to be
ashamed of yourselves.
Does your mother know you cheat?
-Shut up.
My mother has nothing
to do with this.
-Kid got lucky.
It can happen to anyone once.
-If I hit it 100 times, will
you give me a million yen?
-I can't believe
I just saw that.
-Little squirt.
-You think you're
such hot stuff?
Well, let me tell you something.
You're going to regret this.
-The only thing worse
than a loser who cheats
is a bad losers who cheats.
Why don't you grow up?
-Asking for trouble?
-Whoa, what a lucky shot.
Can you spell "lucky"?
-Hey, who is that guy?
-What are you two doing here?
Hope you're not
threatening them.
That would be very nice,
and I might get mad.
And that would be bad for you.
-Actually, Momo, I have to
go and do something, so--
-Me too.
-Later.
-Hey, we're not done, hot stuff.
-Oh my gosh!
-What's the matter?
-Am I dreaming?
Is that Ryoma?
-Are you kidding?
Come on, let's find out.
SAKUNO: Oh, it is him.
[Sakuno sighs dreamily]
-He's look right at me.
Sakuno, introduce us, quickly!
-Huh?
Oh.
This is Ryoma Echizen.
-Echizen?
Ryoma?
-Hey.
There's been quite a
lot of talk about you.
But you don't look like
anything special to me.
-Who are you?
-Name's Takeshi Momoshiro.
I wonder if what they
say about you is true.
I heard you know how
to do a kick serve.
-No way.
-What's a kick serve?
-Can we learn how to do it?
-Will it hurt?
-Want to find out?
-Let's.
Shouldn't take me too
long to take care of you.
-You call it.
-I call up.
-What was all that?
-Haven't got a clue.
-Story of your life.
You two don't know
anything, do you?
Guess I'll have to tell you.
They're deciding who's
going to serve first.
See this?
You spin it.
And when it lands, it's
upright or face down.
-Down.
It's my choice.
You can have the serve.
I'll wait for it in
the court over here.
-Hey, aren't you
going to serve first?
What's the point of winning
the spin if you don't serve?
I don't get it.
-I want to see that
kick serve right away.
-Oh, that is so cool.
Momoshiro, you rock.
-Call me Momo.
-Oh, I couldn't do
that, Momoshiro.
But can I be the chair judge?
-Sure, go ahead.
[Horio clears throat]
-Announcing today's match
between Momoshiro and Ryoma
will commence with me, Horio--
-That show-off Horio sure likes
the sound of his own big mouth.
-Mmhm.
Whatever, Horio.
Shut up and start
the match already!
-Um, OK.
This is a best of one set match.
Serve is Echizen.
Begin play.
HORIO: Fault.
-Yes.
It's all over now.
Ryoma wins, and he
made it look easy!
-Tomoka, a fault is a bad serve
that has to be taken over.
If Ryoma does it again,
Momoshiro will get the point.
-Oh, really?
That'd be terrible.
I couldn't stand to see that!
-Boy, that serve was
a really fast one.
-Yeah.
-Forget the slice serve, kid.
Give me what you got.
-Sorry.
-His eyes.
He's glaring at me again.
-Kick serve.
It's coming.
[all gasp in sequence]
-A kick serve.
I can't believe it.
-Hey, what's so special
about the kick serve, anyway?
-The usual serve slices left.
That's because the spin is
on the outside of the ball.
But with a kick
serve, the spin is
on the inside,
which red top spin,
making it harder to return.
-I get it.
So if you serve just right,
you could hit your opponent
in the head and knock him out.
-Yeah, but it's
practically impossible.
I can't believe a
middle school kid
knows how to serve like that.
It's fantastic.
-That's Ryoma.
He knows all the tennis tricks.
He's the coolest.
-First kick serve
I've ever seen.
Is that the best
that you can do?
I'm so worried.
-You look it.
You're sweating like a pig.
-Kid's getting on my nerves.
-15, love.
-No one makes a fool of me.
My only chance is to catch
the ball on the rise.
Got to charge to the net.
Back at you, hot stuff.
Heh.
Timing is everything when it
comes to hitting that serve.
But I'll get it.
-Poor guy.
He has no chance
against a kick serve.
Momo's doomed for sure.
It'll be a very
hard loss to take.
HORIO: 30, love.
Echizen leads.
-Feet, don't fail me now!
See that?
Lucky shot.
That's twice.
-If he keeps that
up, he might win.
-Lucky guy.
HORIO: 30, 15.
-Sorry, kid.
I've got the timing down now.
No way I'll lose
in a power match.
[all gasp]
-[all three] He nailed it!
[Momo gasps]
[thud]
-Hmm.
A drop volley.
Man, you've got a whole
bag of tricks, don't you?
-40, 15.
-Go!
Get him, Ryoma!
Show him why you're the best!
-Hmm.
[shutter clicks]
-Just like his father.
Those eyes, that
confident glare.
He's like the second
coming of Nanjiro Echizen.
[yawns]
-What's this?
No opponent?
I could have sworn I had
someone to play today.
Think I'll take a nap.
[birds chirping]
-If Ryoma wins this
point, he'll win the game.
-Shoot.
This is taking too long.
I got to finish him off.
-You've still got a ways to go.
-Oh, yeah.
That's right.
-Time out.
I quit.
You're way too good for me.
-Huh?
-What?
-Actually, I only wanted
to see a kick serve.
-Whatever you say.
-You were awesome.
I can't believe
he quit like that.
-Goofball.
Hey Echizen, where'd you learn
to do all those tennis tricks?
-At a temple.
-[all at once] Temple?
-Will you stop pulling my arm?
-We saw the whole match.
I think you're the
most incredible player
I've seen in my lifetime.
I'm Tomoka, I'm Sakuno's friend.
-Huh?
-Good to see you again, Ryoma.
Thanks for the other day.
-Have we met before?
I don't remember you.
[Sakuno gasps]
-I can't believe it.
He doesn't remember me at all.
-You don't look so happy.
-Hey, grandma.
-Quitting like you
did, it's not going
to make your life any
easier around here.
-So maybe that's what I need.
-So nonchalant.
If you hadn't already
sprained your right ankle,
you might have won.
-No, I could tell
he knew about it.
He knew.
-Whatever.
-The entire time, he was playing
with the wrong hand against me,
an upperclassman, like he
was giving me a handicap.
Heh, such arrogance.
Reminds me of me.
[Ryuzaki chuckles]
-Ryoma Echizen.
What an odd little boy.
-Not so odd, not so little.
Let's call him Samurai Junior.
SHIBA: Samurai Junior?
[gong sounds]
-Mm, very interesting.
I wonder where my idiot son is.
Maybe he found a girlfriend.
-Oh!
Now I remember.
[gong sounds]
[rock music playing]
-Yo, I'm Satoshi
Horio, and I've been
playing tennis for two years.
But man, that Echizen
is something else.
Even I, with my two
years experience,
think he's pretty amazing.
But how does he play so well
with an old, beat-up racket?
I can't figure it out, and I
have two years of experience.
Next on Prince of Tennis,
the Seigaku regulars
make their debut.
And these guys will have
you scratching your heads.
Don't forget to watch.
And look out for me, Horio, with
two years of tennis experience.