-Yikes!
He's moving to the net!
-Of course!
If he goes to the net--
-He might be able to catch up!
With the Ryoma Split Step!
[theme music]
-You're wasting your time, brat!
-Huh?
-No way!
-After our guy jumped, he--
-He hit it in the
opposite direction.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): He can't hit
cross court from that position.
ANNOUNCER: 40-Love.
-Echizen, hang in there.
JIN (VOICEOVER):
Hey, Kawamura, you
think this little
brat can beat me?
MEN: 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
1, 2, 3, 4--
-Look at them.
Our senior classmates
sure look awesome.
But the best one is Sumoto.
-Yeah.
He's the best among all the
junior high school guys.
-9, 10.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6--
-Huh.
Hey, who's that over there?
-Huh?
Oh, that's Akutsu.
-You know him?
-Well, he sort of
lives near where I do.
-What's all that noise?
-Oh, we're sorry.
It's just that we've got
a visitor in here today.
-Does he want to join?
Our teacher isn't here now.
If you want to
join, you're going
to have to come back
some other-- huh?
-I heard that there were some
tough guys at this place.
But you don't really
look that tough to me.
You, there.
How long have you
ben studying karate?
-What?
Hey, if yo uwant
to join this club,
you'd better not talk that way.
If you want to be
part of the group,
fine, but you'd
better straighten up,
starting right now.
-Don't order me around!
-Huh?
-If you're gonna act so
tough, well, then, you'd
better make sure you
can beat me first.
Otherwise--
-Who does this smart
alec think he is?
-Well, if your
brain won't listen,
then I'll have to teach
your body to listen.
-Hey, quit it, Sumoto.
If the teacher finds out
about that, you know--
-Just leave it to me.
-Man, this has really
turned into trouble.
This is impossible, Akutsu.
A beginning going
up against Sumoto?
Even the assistant
coach defers to him.
-Hey, if that's the best you
can do, you won't beat me.
Well, now, what's wrong?
Had enough of this yet?
By the look in your eye,
I'd say you wanted more.
Come on, then.
One more.
-Ah!
Argh!
Ow!
My arm!
-Come on, Sumoto.
You all right?
-Master Sumoto!
[laughter]
-I thought you were
supposed to be tough.
I expected more out of you.
-What did you say, punk?
-I'll teach you a lesson!
[shout]
[shouting]
-Heh.
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Yamabuki's Akutsu.
Two games to love.
-Oh, Ryoma!
-Don't worry.
It's Ryoma we're talking about.
-Did you see that?
He waits until Echizen moves,
then changes where he hits it.
-I don't see how
he's able to do that.
-But if Ryoma waits to move
until Akutsu hits the ball,
then it is too late.
-That's gotta be humiliating.
Echizen jumps one
way, but the ball
goes in the opposite
direction behind him.
BOY (VOICEOVER):
Akutsu, no matter
what you do, you
always act strong.
[groaning]
[coughing]
-The one kid-- kiddin' me.
-Hey!
Akutsu!
-Huh?
Who are you?
You want some?
-No, it's me.
From the sushi place.
-Oh, yeah.
You're Kawamura, right?
What do you want with me?
-Just tell me why you
do things like this.
Hey, Akutsu.
Huh?
It's Akutsu.
WOMAN: Jin, now please,
don't make anymore trouble.
JIN: Shut up!
I told you not to
order me around.
-Jin.
Jin!
-Huh?
-You got something to say to me?
-Not really.
I just thought that you
were really amazing.
You'd never studied
karate before,
yet you went up against
those advanced guys.
But you better watch
yourself around here.
If you go about doing stuff like
that, you might find that you--
-Don't you dare try
to order me around!
-I'm not trying to
order you around.
I'm worried about you.
That's all.
-Worried?
Who do you think
you're talking to?
A baby?
No matter who the opponent
is, I'll never lose.
I swear it.
Remember that.
Is that all you can do, brat?
Forget it.
Cause now I attack.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): To the right!
ANNOUNCER: 30-Love.
-Other way, you brat.
-Oh no, not again!
He keeps hitting it
to the opposite side!
-Inui, the stuff that beats
your data driven tennis.
-Should have been enough, but I
gather it just doesn't hold up.
There's no chance
it can stand up
to that guy's
physical abilities.
Echizen can
instinctively tell, even
at the very last second, which
direction his opponent will
hit the ball.
With his unique one
legged split step,
he always seems at
least a step and a half
quicker than the average player.
However, that's no
advantage against Akutsu.
ANNOUNCER: 40-Love!
-It's unbelievable, but Akutsu
can change the ball's direction
even after Echizen
has anticipated it.
What makes this possible is
his innate sense of balance,
the flexibility of his muscles,
the spring in his body,
and his natural gifts
as an ace tennis player.
-Yeah!
[cheering]
-I told you before, brat.
I'm not giving up
even one point to you.
-Inui, what would you say are
the chances Ryome will win?
-Impossible!
The guy's invincible!
-Akutsu's just too good.
-Come on, Ryoma.
You can do it.
-Oh, Ryoma!
-Is that all you can do?
You are such a
disappointment to me, brat.
-Ryoma?
What's he just
standing there for?
-Oh, Ryoma!
JIN (VOICEOVER): Idiot.
Don't tell me you're scared.
-Way to go!
It's a short lob.
Oh, that's an easy one to smash.
-Look!
Echizen's suddenly on the move.
-I get it.
Echizen's narrowing the area in
which Akutsu can hit the ball.
-Huh?
INUI: When they're
both at the baseline,
they can return the
ball anywhere they like.
A short lob will draw Akutsu
in, and by approaching the net,
Echizen can limit where Akutsu
can hit the strong shot.
JIN (VOICEOVER): I see
you'e been thinking.
However--
-Oh, no.
He's gonna lob it over Echizen's
head for another point.
-Running away?
-You've got guts, kid.
I'll give you that!
-Wah!
-Oh, man.
-Wow.
-He totally dropped him.
-That's gotta hurt.
-I hope he's OK.
JIN (VOICEOVER):
That's quite a trick.
First he provoked me,
then he set me up.
Hm.
-30-15.
-How'd he do that?
-Echizen?
-Hey, kid.
How long you going to
pretend to be asleep?
-Hey.
Didn't you say you wouldn't
let me win even one point?
I guess you lied, huh?
-Yippee!
Yeah, Ryoma!
-We shouldn't have
worried about him!
He always finds a way to win!
-I get it.
He deliberately provoked
him, and then moved up
to the net so he'd be a target.
Echizen made him hit
it right at his face,
but he had his racket
positioned in advance.
-Still got a ways to go.
JIN (VOICEOVER):
That brat is more
interested in competing
than winning or losing.
-That one seems to have
the ideal tennis ability.
Mm-hm.
Like father, like son.
-He won the point,
but that strategy
won't work twice against
someone like Akutsu.
-No kidding.
It doesn't change the fact
that he's still in trouble.
BOY (VOICEOVER): So, you nearly
kill yourself to win one point.
Oh, that's just like you.
-Well, isn't this great?
-Huh?
-He's moving up again!
What's he trying
to do this time?
-If he can hit the
ball early, a return
is his only chance to
attack Akutsu, instead
of waiting to be
attacked by him.
It should work.
-Echizen has figured
it out for himself.
-Huh?
-The [inaudible].
He just hit the
Super Rising Shot.
BOY: Yikes!
Not even Akutsu will be
able to reach that one!
-To the left!
-Trying to ace me, brat?
Don't make me laugh!
-Oh, no!
He's gonna lose the point
on yet another passing shot!
-Sorry, son of Nanjiro, but
there's no stopping Akutsu now.
-Echizen, show me your
own kind of tennis.
Ryoma Echizen's tennis.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): Dad?
-Take the next step, Echizen.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER):
I w be strong!
[shout]
-He actually changed
directions while in mid step.
MAN (VOICEOVER): When someone
meets an overwhelming opponent,
it's a chance to improve one's
skills and evolve as a player.
You're on your way.
Show us what you
can do, Echizen.
-40-30.
-If I'm not mistaken, he
just grew up a little.
[laughter]
-You see that?
Those two are laughing.
-What on earth could
they be thinking about?
-Hey, you're gonna make a
great stepping stone for me.
JIN (VOICEOVER):
I'm gonna crush you.
[theme music]
-Hello, everybody.
I'm Banda.
Call me Banji.
Coach Ryuzaki, Ryoma's
potential is on the rise.
His one-legged split
step is amazing.
However, you have yet to
see the end of Akutsu.
He's got a reason why
he can't possibly lose.
Next on "The Prince of
Tennis," I Can't Lose.
Akutsu, now is the
time to let them
see a glimpse of your pride.