-It's bad.
He's still bleeding.
His eye seems OK, but the
eye lid is split open.
-Wow, Ryoma.
That must hurt a lot, huh?
Hey, Taka, you don't need to go
to the hospital again, do you?
-You know, he shouldn't have
forced his shot like that.
-Heh.
Serves him right anyway.
-How is he, Oishi.
-It's not good.
There's no way
he's playing today.
I hate to forfeit the game,
but it's not happening.
-You think it's over?
-Shinji won't be at all
happy with this kind of win.
-That's for sure.
-Unbelievable.
Look at what happened
to your racket.
Echizen, I'm gonna
throw this in your bag.
-Hold it, Momo.
-Huh?
-While you're at it,
go ahead and get out
a new racket for me.
-Ryoma!
Oh, no!
[theme music]
-Whoa.
-You sure this is just
a district qualifier?
-Man, these guys
are really good.
-You know, the
two of them really
need to slow down their
pace a little bit.
-I don't think those
guys are the types that
worry about pacing so much.
-You're correct.
But still, I'm gathering some
good data here for later.
-It's cross court!
He can't get it!
ANNOUNCER: 15-All.
BOY: He forehanded
with his right.
No way!
-It's the two sword style.
-What's that?
Two sword style maybe?
BOY: Come on, let's go.
Hey, hurry up!
KATSUO: Ryoma's
going to the net!
-I've never seen Echizen rush
the net that aggressively.
-What the-- Who
does he think he is?
Now, that's a perfect lob.
-He'll never get it.
You can do it, Ryoma!
ANNOUNCER: 40-15.
-Wow, unbelievable!
-My gosh, he's totally amazing.
TOMOKA (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe
that Shinji is
getting pushed around.
And that kid hits with
his left hand now.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER): When Ryoma
plays tennis, he is so cool.
-Shinji.
When are you gonna get serious?
I know you let your
opponents feel confident
and then come back
from behind to win,
but if you don't start now,
this match is over for you.
I wonder, is Shinji
having a hard time?
-What an awesome overhead.
-Come on, Echizen!
It's time to turn up the heat!
-Game to Echizen.
Four games to one.
-That's not good.
-This is a complete blowout.
Ryoma's on fire.
-Exactly.
So we need to kick it up too.
-Who is that seventh grader?
He's running Shinji ragged.
Not good.
Oh Shinji.
You're not--
-There's something very
weird about his attack.
-Huh?
-Yeah, he's hitting top spin
shots and slices like one
after the other.
-You're right.
-This ball's mine.
[gasps]
-15-Love.
-What's wrong?
That was easy.
Even I could've
returned that ball.
-He was just unlucky.
-It's only one point.
Don't worry, you guys.
-That was lousy.
-It looks like the
little guy just
stopped playing for a second.
His opponent plays well.
Don't forget that.
RYOMA: What's with my arm?
-I will stop you.
Take my word.
-What just happened?
-Shinji stunned that
seventh grade player.
-Huh?
-It was a bit of
a gamble to try.
Top spins and slices.
By alternately unleashing
top spin and back spin,
the muscles contract,
which cause momentary spot
paralysis in the opponent's arm.
-How's that?
-It's only for a second,
until the feeling comes back,
and Shinji seized the moment.
-Where'd Shinji learn that?
ANNOUNCER: 30-Love.
-It's a bit risky, and
it can backfire big time.
It shows you how far
he's been pushed.
-He's doing it again.
-Huh?
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): Oh!
My-- my arm again.
-The kid is pivoting.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): That hurt!
-Don't do that.
He's turning his body
to force that shot.
INUI (VOICEOVER): Echizen.
No.
-It's hopeless.
When you're hit with
a spot paralysis,
you're gonna lose your grip.
-Huh?
-Oh no.
-Hey, watch out.
MOMOSHIRO: Taka, you're
going the wrong way.
Come on, let's go.
-Oh, yeah!
-Momoshiro.
Are you sure about this?
Coach might be upset
if she finds out
that you snuck out to get me.
-I'm sure she will.
But we should all be
there for the win!
-You know, you're crazy.
-Seigaku will win
the game, yeah!
huh?
[excited chatter]
MAN: Wow, would you
look at that game?
-Ryoma!
-Oh no.
Ryoma.
SHINJI: It's hopeless.
When you're hit with
a spot paralysis,
you're gonna lose your grip.
-Huh?
-Oh no.
-Hey, watch out.
[shocked whispering]
BOY: It's bleeding
-Ryoma!
Oh, Ryoma.
Are you all right?
-You can't come on to the court.
-Here.
-Keep it.
Get off the court now.
-But you really need
to get to a hospital.
-No way.
I'm fine.
-But you're bleeding
all over the court.
-Man.
My racket's busted.
-Oh.
Oh, forget about that.
You're hurt, Ryoma.
-Excuse me, miss,
but only players
are allowed on the court.
-You mean me?
Ryoma. we have to
get you out of here.
-Hey, hold on.
-You cannot play like this.
You're injured.
Hi grandma.
-You have to go now.
You're embarrassing the player.
My granddaughter
should know that.
What in the world were
you thinking, Sakuno?
-But granny, Ryoma is injured.
-Let's stop the bleeding.
Somebody bring the
first aid kit right now.
-Wow.
Do you think he's
going to be all right?
-He's bleeding a lot.
It doesn't look good for Ryoma.
-He's not gonna be
able to play like this.
-He was playing
well up until now.
-The poor guy's injured.
He shouldn't be allowed
to keep playing like that.
-This stinks.
He almost had it locked up.
You know, Echizen
would really hate it
if we had to forfeit
the entire match.
-So you're saying he
should just keep playing?
Why is that?
You'd be happy if he lost
his eyesight, wouldn't you?
-We're sorry!
-Oh my.
I can't believe I
yelled at you guys.
-I think she's gone
completely insane.
-She's just not
acting like herself.
-Yeah, she's acting like Tomoka.
GIRL: Hey, you guys.
-Huh?
What's up?
-That player.
Is he OK?
-Don't know yet.
-It's bad.
He's still bleeding.
His eye seems OK, but
the eyelid is split open.
-Wow, Ryoma, that
must hurt a lot, huh?
-Taka, you don't need to go
to the hospital again, do you?
-You know, he shouldn't have
forced his shot like that.
-Heh.
Serves him right anyway.
-How is he, Oishi?
It's not good.
There's no way
he's playing today.
I hate to forfeit the game,
but it's not happening.
-You think it's over?
-Shinji won't be an all
happy with this kind of win.
-That's for sure.
-Unbelievable.
Look what happened
to your racket.
Echizen, I'm gonna throw
this into your bag.
-Hold it, Momo.
-Huh?
-While you're at it,
go ahead and get out
a new racket for me.
-Ryoma, oh no!
-Oh, OK.
-You can't play.
You're injured!
-You really shouldn't
play, since you'd
be at a disadvantage.
ANNOUNCER: Echizen.
Don't tell me you
want to continue.
I can't permit it, especially
if you're bleeding.
I know you're disappointed,
but it's over, OK?
-Huh?
-I'll play.
-But Echizen, listen to me.
-But it stopped bleeding.
Ryoma, Come here now.
What do you mean it
stopped bleeding?
You can't keep playing,
you stubborn fool.
-But why not?
-But isn't it hurting you?
-No, it's not.
-Hm.
Oishi.
Bring the first
aid kit over here.
-Uh.
Yes, Coach.
COACH RYUZAKI: Ryoma.
This is gonna hurt.
RYOMA: Ah.
Coach Ryuzaki.
-Well, looks like we're done.
-Hey, it-- it stopped.
-He's patched up?
It was bleeding so
hard just a second ago.
-All right, kid.
This is a quick fix at best.
You've got 15 minutes
tops, you got it?
-Wow, it's Sumire magic.
-Fuji!
Do not call me that.
-If there's no blood,
then I can play, right?
-Well, I did say that,
but you are clearly
not in any condition to
keep on playing today.
-Hey Echizen, your racket.
-Thanks a lot, Momo.
I'm ready.
-Oishi.
-Captain?
-Huh?
-Listen to me.
Finish the match in 10
minutes, or you forfeit.
-Tezuka.
-You got that?
-That's enough time.
-Echizen, go for it.
But watch yourself out there.
-I think you'll need that.
-Hey, thanks Kaidoh.
[excited chatter]
BOY: How can he play like that?
This is unbelievable.
-Does he really think he can
play Shinji with that injury?
That's just crazy.
-That's insane.
And besides, his
opponent's so tricky.
He's in a really tough spot.
-There's no way he
can win like that.
-Even healthy he was in a pinch.
But right now?
-He's gonna lose!
FEMALE VOICE: Come on.
You can bring this
championship home.
SHINJI (VOICEOVER):
That's right.
Bring it on.
I haven't destroyed you yet.
Huh?
What's happening?
He's even quicker.
MAN (VOICEOVER): Wow.
[surprised chatter]
ANNOUNCER: 15-Love.
-Hey.
You guys worry too much.
It was just a scratch.
-Oh Ryoma.
-That's our boy.
He wouldn't even let
bloodshed stop him.
[cheering]
[theme music]
-Hoo ah!
I'm Takashi Kawamura!
Echizen, you don't need to
worry about that injury.
You can win, baby!
I us the heart!
Heart!
You gotta have it!
Stay tuned!
The next episode of "Prince
of Tennis," is Time Limit,
and I'm on fire!
Burning, baby!
Burning!