-I can't believe
it dropped so fast.
Get to it.
-He returned it!
-Kid's fast.
Here goes.
-Lay off of it!
Don't smash!
[theme music]
-Seigaku, fight, fight, fight!
Seigaku, fight, fight, fight!
-Come on!
And get those feet
off the ground.
-Why are we running today?
-They want us to train
harder for the metropolitans.
-This is way too hard.
-You're running today to build
up the strength of the team.
Whoever dropped out will be
getting my special penal-tea.
-No way!
[screaming]
-Today's penal-tea is a
brand new improved version.
Not another.
-I wanna try it.
Looks good.
-Not me.
No way I'll drink it.
I think Inui's
beginning to like making
us drink that
sewer water of his.
Huh?
Hey, Viper!
You can't do that!
-I still won't drink that junk.
-Stop there.
You're disqualified.
-Aw.
[screaming]
-The time for today
is 55 seconds.
Anyone who takes longer will
have a special penal-tea.
-Is he kidding?
-It sounds like fun.
-Pick up the pace, guys.
-No way I'm ever gonna
drink that stuff!
-If you're gonna sprint
you won't last long.
-That's true.
-I'll never drink that.
-Taka, what's up?
You're awfully nonchalant.
-Nonchalant?
Seem to me like he's
thinking about a girl.
-A girl?
-Just knock it off.
[giggling]
-It's stupid to talk
about such things.
-Don't make Yuki worry anymore.
WOMAN: Jin, stop it.
-And don't even think
about ordering me around.
-Takashi, are you all right?
-That's terrible.
[groaning]
-Hey, Momo, you better not.
-Huh?
-Thank you for that
treat earlier today.
-Seigaku.
-I haven't introduced
myself yet.
I'm Ryouma Echizen, a
seventh grader at Seigaku.
Nice to meet you.
-Jin Akutsu?
-Yeah.
That's the guy.
He quit coming to the dojo
when he entered middle school,
and I've only heard
bad things since.
I sure never thought that
he'd come back to play tennis.
-Come back?
What do you mean?
-He had the best
coach around back
when we were both in
elementary school.
He was really that good.
-Hm.
I'm probably just guessing,
but was the hot babe
sitting with him
your girlfriend?
-Girlfriend?
-So it's true then.
-You're so wrong.
-Come on.
This is no time to be shy, Taka.
-Hey.
I'm not shy.
She's just--
-Don't worry, Taka.
Everyone goes through phases.
-Phases?
What phases?
-You know, when you
fall for an older woman.
-Older woman.
-Shut up, will you?
-Quit it, would you?
It's our last lap.
Your pace is falling.
-In the end, only the
regulars are left.
Of course, this mug
awaits the last runner in.
A deluxe penal-tea super
special new version.
-Ugh.
That's right.
Come on, guys.
Wait for me!
-I can't lose, no way, no how!
-Not me either!
-Hey, Kawamura, your racket.
-Huh?
-I'm burning!
On fire!
Out of my way!
-Huh?
-Raa!
[chuckling]
[angry shouting]
-Hey, Fuji, got a question.
-Yeah.
What is it?
-I thought you liked
to drink that stuff.
-Inui's penal-tea?
Yeah.
I really think the
stuff tastes great.
-Then what the heck are
you running so hard for?
-Because it's fun
to watch all you
guys getting nervous over it.
-Man, I guess I better not
get on your bad side then.
-Hurry.
We're running out of time.
-On fire!
On fire!
-A little further.
-I'm not through yet!
-I won't give up now!
-Hm.
-Who you think won?
-What's their time?
-54 seconds.
Regrettably, they
all came in together.
-Just watching is
making me tired.
-Man.
They ran like crazy.
-Geez.
Do you think they're gonna
do that for every drill?
-Do you think Inui
is trying to kill us?
-I'm already dead.
-All right.
Stop the whining,
and get to work.
-Tezuka's right.
The St. Rudolph's
match was a joke.
You boys needed a
whole lot more stamina.
If we're gonna aim
for the nationals,
we have to toughen up.
When you're exhausted,
that's the best time
to test your true abilities.
-OK.
Time for practice matches.
I'll see all of you
guys out on the court.
-What?
Play right now?
Really?
After all that running?
-He's joking.
They can't play after
running so hard like that.
-It would be impossible.
-Fuji, Echizen, we'll start
off with the two of you.
-A match between
Fuji and Echizen?
-No way.
Practice matches
between the regulars?
-That's one amazing
match-up we get to watch.
-Who's stronger I wonder?
Fuji or Echizen?
-Now I play the big brother.
-Take it easy on me, kid.
-Hey, guys.
Do you think Ryouma
will be all right?
-Who'll win?
-Fuji.
-Echizen.
-Huh?
-Ugh.
-Let's see how far you can
get with Fuji, Echizen.
Show him your stuff, kid.
REFEREE: One set match.
Fuji to serve.
KACHIRO: The split step.
-Where the heck does Echizen
get all that stamina?
ECHIZEN (VOICEOVER): Fuji,
it's OK if I beat you, right?
-Hmph.
SATOSHI: Echizen's
rushing the net.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): Does he
plan to attack on his return?
I'll just move him side to side.
-Not bad, But I really
want to win this,
so I've got to attack.
-That guy, he's crushing
everything that Fuji hits.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): His
shots are might fast.
Not a single sign of retreat,
He keeps hitting the balls right
back, and what
makes it possible is
that-- his one-legged
splits step.
-Wow.
That ball was supposed
to finish up the point.
Come on!
-This is fun.
REFEREE: Game to Fuji.
One game to love.
REFEREE: Game to Echizen.
One game all.
-Cool.
This time Echizen
held his serve.
-What a tight game this is.
-Ryouma still has
a chance to win.
RYUZAKI: Hm.
It looks like they're still
feeling each other out.
-Which of them will
set the bait first?
That's the question.
-Whoa.
ECHIZEN (VOICEOVER): I'll
throw him off with a Drive B.
How about a triple counter?
-This is exciting.
What a rally!
Neither player's giving an inch.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): The
ball's speed, it changed.
ECHIZEN (VOICEOVER): Yes.
Here we go.
-Whoa.
Echizen threw down
the gauntlet first.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): I'll
just aim for his feet.
Huh?
-Wow.
Ryouma's sliding!
KACHIRO AND SATOSHI:
The Drive B!
ECHIZEN (VOICEOVER): I'll
aim for the left corner.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
Normally, a smash from that
angle would drive the ball out,
but Echizen's Drive B
just drops suddenly.
I can't believe it
dropped so fast.
Get to it.
-He returned it!
-The little guy's fast.
-Here goes.
-Lay off of it!
Don't smash!
-Huh?
-What a tight game.
SATOSHI: Hey, guys.
What just happened?
KACHIRO: I don't have a clue.
-Wha-- wha-- he returned
that smash with a volley.
-You're right.
That move even destroys
the effectiveness
of my dunk smashes.
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER): It's
called Counter Tennis.
It uses the power
your opponent produces
to generate more
power off your racket.
this is the second one of
Fuji's Triple Counters,
the Brown Bear,
REFEREE: 15- love.
-That was his Brown Bear.
-He returned Ryouma's
smash head on.
How'd he do it?
-For Fuji to use that trick
means he's taking no prisoners.
-What is that Brown Bear anyway?
-The old Brown Bear.
He uses his body's
centrifugal force
to absorb his opponent's
power, then watch out.
He sends it back behind his
opponent who, by this time,
has charged forward.
SATOSHI: Sweet.
All in the blink of an eye.
KATSUO: That's not something
a normal person can do.
-And that is why Fuji
is such a genius.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): Ryouma's Drive
B is tougher than I figured.
I can't find a good
way to counter it
I was only able to
return it because Echizen
was tired after
all that running?
-What's up?
Something wrong?
-Just thinking.
-I guess Echizen can't use
that huge smash of his anymore.
-Huh?
And why is that?
Come on.
Just stop to think about it.
Echizen hit a clean
winner, but Fuji
was able to knock it
back without a problem.
He is way too good to make
the same mistake twice.
-Oh, wow.
A smash.
-Huh?
-Wow.
He's gonna keep trying.
-Crazy Echizen.
REFEREE: 30-love.
-That's another Brown Bear.
-Whoa.
It's almost
impossible to believe.
Ryouma must be in shock.
-Hm.
So he was able to
kill all my smashes.
-You think Echizen's
spooked so easy?
-Nope.
I don't think so.
-Yeah.
Looks to me like Echizen's
ready to defeat Fuji.
-That's fine.
Just try and defeat me.
Better get ready.
SATOSHI: A floater.
Now's his chance.
TEZUKA: That's a
challenge from Fuji.
-Wow!
What a shot.
-It's a twist spin shot.
-Yeah.
It's the one he used
against Ibu of Fudomine.
-You used your head, Echizen.
-Huh?
-He returned it.
KACHIRO: The Brown Bear again.
SATOSHI: As long as
he has that trick,
smashes won't work
on him at all.
-Ryouma.
REFEREE: 40-love.
ECHIZEN (VOICEOVER):
Fuji's strong, but more
than that, he's good.
-Man.
I really have to keep
on my toes with you.
I can see how you beat Kaoru,
and Inui, and even Yuta.
I can't lower my guard
against you even for a second.
It would be the end of me
in the blink of an eye.
But it's still a little too
soon for you to beat me.
KACHIRO: Hey.
Here's another chance.
-Do you think Fuji hit
that lob on purpose.
SATOSHI: Wow.
Echizen went for it.
Cool.
REFEREE: Game to Fuji.
Two games to one.
Fuji leads.
-The Brown Bear.
It's amazing.
He took the claws
out of Echizen.
SATOSHI: Not another Smash!
-Every time it's
gonna be the same.
It's all in Fuji's technique.
REFEREE: Love-15.
KACHIRO: Ryouma won't
stop smashing it.
He's like a dog with a bone.
-They're both so stubborn.
-That's just like Echizen.
-I swear I'll beat him.
[theme music]
KACHIRO (VOICEOVER): Hi.
It's Kachiro.
Looks like Ryouma
and Fuji are having
lots of fun in their
match, but they
seem to be changing
into different people!
Hoo.
Scary.
Momo and captain Tezuka's
match is starting soon,
and there is so many
exciting things to watch.
Next on the Prince of
Tennis-- a Duel in the Rain.
Ryouma, it's raining!
Can you hear me?
Ryouma!