-Still got a ways to go.
You've still got a ways to go.
[creaking]
[meow]
-Hm?
-Hey, it's time to wake up.
We're going out.
[theme music]
-So, where are we headed anyway?
-It's like this.
A friend of mine's
granddaughter has just
started playing
tennis, so she called
to ask me if I'd be
interested in coaching her.
Eat some.
I have lots of stuff
to do, so I thought
you'd like to coach her.
How about that?
-You can't be serious.
-All right, here we are.
This is it.
Better get going.
Right there.
-But-- But, dad.
-Hey, thanks a lot.
You know, for coaching the kid.
-But I don't wanna.
-You can't say no,
because that little bean
cake was a gift from my
grateful friend, and you ate it.
-Huh?
-See you later!
Thanks again my helpful son.
-Hey, wait a minute.
Dad!
-I'm outta here!
-I can't believe it.
He tricked me again.
GIRL: Hey, Ryoma!
You really showed up!
Ryoma!
-I just decided that I'd
come along and be a hitting
partner for my friend Sakuno.
Are you going to
be our coach, then?
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): The
granddaughter of his friend?
My dad's crazy.
-I feel sick.
I overdid it.
Looks like I ate too
many of those bean cakes.
-You're both way too tense.
-Kay.
-Uh, Ryoma?
I'm sorry they
made you coach us.
-It's not a problem,
but you should
try to bend your
knees a little more.
-Got it!
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER):
All right, Sakuno.
Now's your chance
to impress him.
-There!
Oops.
-Just try to hit it.
-Yeah.
-Between the both of us,
we could only buy two.
Let's mark our balls so we
can find them easier later.
-Sounds good.
Hm.
What did you draw on yours?
-This.
-Wow.
That's so cool.
-I can draw one on
yours if you want.
-You're the best!
-I'm done.
That makes eight,
and nine, and ten!
Ryoma, look at me.
I hit the ball 11
times in a row.
-Nice, Tomo!
That's great.
-Ah!
Oh no, I missed the ball.
-Try holding your racket at
the very end of the grip.
-Oh.
Like this?
Wow.
That's much better.
-Mm-hm.
-Yes, Tomo.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER): Even though
this is only her second lesson,
Tomo can just keep hitting
that ball over and over.
She's got natural
ability, but I'll
practice hard and become
a good player too.
I'll just relax bend my knees,
and keep my eye on the ball.
Now I've done it.
I'll go get the ball!
-Sakuno!
Do you want me to come with you?
-No, I'll be fine!
That was embarrassing.
Even though I practice every
day, I'm not getting better.
Uh, oh, I found it.
I've almost got it.
Huh?
-What do you think
you're doing there, kid?
-It's just, I lost-- My ball
ended up over on your court.
-All right.
Come on over and get it.
-Excuse me, please.
-Go ahead.
Get your ball.
But don't dare
interrupt our practice.
-Oh, I won't.
-Aw, I'm so sorry.
I guess I goofed.
-I wonder where the heck Sakuno
went to find that lost ball?
Huh?
Sakuno?
-You better hurry
up, little girl.
-Yeah, you're wasting our
valuable court time, kid.
-Sorry.
-We're on the Ginka
team, and we're
playing in the semifinals
of the Metropolitan matches.
-Ryoma!
Ryoma, come quickly!
Something bad is happening!
Your time is up.
-Come on, you're
keeping us waiting.
-Uh.
Ryoma's face is on the ball.
I gotta find it.
-You better hurry up and
get lost, little girl.
You're holding up our practice.
-Wait a minute.
My ball has a
special mark on it.
I just need some more time.
-Get lost.
What part of that
don't you understand?
-Did you see that?
It came out of nowhere.
-Argh.
Huh?
-What just happened?
-Check that out.
-Who's that kid?
You think he's--
-He's the one who hit the ball?
-Unbelievable.
-I'm sorry.
Looks like my ball's
in your court.
-Wow, that kid.
He aimed that ball.
-Yeah, looks he aimed it right
through that hole in the fence
from all the way over there.
-That punk!
[cat screeching]
-Hey, just who do
you think you are,
stepping on our court like that?
-Sakuno.
Did you find your ball?
-No, I didn't.
With so many of them, I can't
tell which ball is mine.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): She'll
never find it in there.
-Hey, cowboy!
Are you listening to me?
I'm talking to you!
You took your best
shot, and you know what?
You're just lucky
you're alive, punk!
-Did that hurt?
Sorry.
Say, could you help
us find her ball?
-You better get out
of here before I
rearrange your smug face, kid.
-Come on, now.
Don't get so mad at the kid.
-Oh, yeah.
-There are more than
300 balls on this court.
You're holding up our practice.
You can't expect us to wait all
day for you to find one ball.
-That girl over
there with the braids
is the one who knocked
over our ball cart.
-No!
I didn't!
-Ryoma, he's hiding the
ball behind his back.
I can see it.
-Who's that girl?
Another little squirt?
-Scram, kid.
-Will not!
I know that you have our balls.
I saw them with my 20-20 vision.
I'm sure of it!
-I had a feeling about this.
-That girl's a liar.
-You guys are the liars.
You're being really,
really mean, you know that?
-So what if I am?
Huh?
-How about this?
10 balls each.
-Huh?
I'll play you all, and if I
lose, we'll give up searching.
But if I win, you've got to
give the girls back their balls.
-You're crazy.
-So, are you scared?
-We each play 10 balls?
There are 30 of us to beat.
That's insane!
-I like it.
[laughter]
-Hmph.
-Huh?
Hm.
Well, if you can beat us
all, their balls are yours.
And every other one
we've got out here, too.
-OK, everyone.
Come on over here.
Let's go, guys.
-So, who's going down first?
BOY: Hey, Akutsu?
I'm not sure about this.
I could get in a lot of
trouble for letting a student
from another school
in here, you know?
Huh?
Hey, what do you think
you're doing now?
Akutsu!
-So, where's my money?
-Huh?
What are you talking about?
-I want cash.
-Let's stop all this, man.
I don't have any money.
Huh?
-Hey.
What did you say?
Don't you-- don't you
dare order me around.
Don't you mess
with me, my friend.
-Our next opponent is Ginka.
We've never played them
before, but if they're
in the semifinals,
they're probably good.
-I heard that they
have a killer team.
-Suzuki, take the kid apart!
-Expect nothing less.
This should make him cry.
There!
-Fukushi and Tashiro
are singles players.
And Suzuki?
Well, I've heard
they're all tough.
-That was too good!
-Check it out.
Sure that short kid's not bad.
-You jerk.
Suzuki's just playing sloppy.
Get up, Suzuki.
-Who's next?
-My turn.
I'll destroy you.
-Tashiro, you better
watch out for him.
-Watch and learn, cupcake.
-Huh?
-Yes!
Ryoma rocks!
-Next?
-Aw man.
He just took out
our five best guys.
What are we gonna
do to stop him?
It's embarrassing.
-Who is he, and where'd
he come from anyway?
-Who cares?
We're just gonna
have to crush him.
-I heard Ginka's got another
regular named Domoto who's
supposed to be a
really strong player.
His big serve could certainly
give us some trouble.
-Then I have good news.
Inui's on his way to Ginka
to check out the competition.
-Hey, I'm here.
It's all over.
BOY: Come on, Domoto!
We're counting on you!
BOY: He's gotta
be getting tired.
BOY: Yeah, show him that
power serve of yours!
-All right.
Here goes.
BOY: Here it is!
Power serve!
DOMOTO (VOICEOVER):
Let him return this.
-Wow.
Hat a turn.
-Incredible.
-So, was that your warm up?
-Argh.
-Next?
-But we're supposed to be one of
the four best teams this year.
-How could this happen?
We were a slam dunk.
-All right.
Time for your next player
to step up to the plate.
Let's get going.
There's still 22 of you to play.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-Who's that short kid?
-What did you say?
Uh, I'm-- not really sure.
He has some serve.
That's for sure.
Hey, Akutsu?
I'm sorry, but it looks like
there's trouble on the court.
Uh, I know we've been buds,
but, well, can you leave now?
-Don't you dare order me around.
-Uh, I'm sorry.
Ah!
[crying out]
-Looks like that kid
got to it before I did.
I wanted to mess
with you guys, too.
WAITER: Here you go.
Enjoy.
-Those tea cakes were way
too sweet for my taste.
I'm sure this will be better.
-This is some nice place.
It's surrounded by woods, and
there's lots of fresh air here.
They've got ideal
playing conditions.
Ginka is among the best
four teams in the league.
We can't take them lightly.
I need data.
That is certain.
Their practices have
got to be really hard.
They look beat.
I guess we'll just have
to work harder then.
-Nice to meet you!
I'm Tomoka Osakata.
-I'm Nanjiro.
-I can't believe we really
won all of their balls.
-What's going on?
-Sh.
-Huh?
-Let him sleep.
He deserved the rest, and more.
[music playing]
[theme music]
INUI: Seigaku must train
harder than anyone.
Well, then, I'll pump them up
with my special conditioning
drink.
Next on "The Prince of Tennis."
Penal-tea.
Hey everybody, drink up.