ANNOUNCER: We are
approaching our last stop.
Please be sure to take
all of your belongings.
-Wake up, kid.
We're at the last stop.
Come on.
-The last stop?
What?
This isn't my school.
Where am I?
[theme music]
-Let's begin.
In English, the phrase I have
blank, is incredibly useful.
To have is a verb that
signifies possession.
I have, you have,
she has, they--
TEACHER (VOICEOVER): For crying
out loud, he's sleeping again.
Echizen, wake up.
Would you complete the
sentence on the board, please?
-Huh?
All right.
[yawn]
BOY (VOICEOVER): Echizen's
gonna make a fool of himself.
BOY: Whoa, how's
he gonna do that?
-Know what?
That's just-- That's
just not possible.
-I'm done.
That it?
-Yeah, that's it!
Nice job.
Well done.
Good answer, son.
-Your pronunciation's
not that bad, you know.
-Tell me he didn't
just say that.
-No way.
-I overslept, and now I'm
at some strange school.
What?
Today's practice match?
I can't make it.
It's already noon.
Do I have any idea where I am?
Not sure.
I could be anywhere.
Oh, I see it right here.
I figured out where I am, sir.
[beeping]
Sir?
Darn.
I'm not getting any reception.
Here's my big chance.
I'll go and check
out their team.
-One, two.
-You know where Echizen is?
-Oh, uh, he said he was
on the cleaning crew
today, so he'd be late.
Same deal for Horio.
-So then--
-That punk.
I bet he forgot
to do his homework
and so he had to stay late.
-Kikumaru, you sure
that's not you?
-What?
Hey, you're out
of your mind, pal.
-Cool.
So, this is Seigaku, huh?
Hey, not bad.
Come to think of
it, where's Tezuka?
Huh?
-That's fantastic, Fuji.
Great, looks terrific.
Just perfect.
-Who's that?
Is she another scout?
-Hold that pose.
BOY: She actually looks
kind of old for scouting.
-Hm?
-Did you just call me old?
Now listen.
You may only be in
junior high school,
but that doesn't give you
any right to insult a lady.
[phone ringing]
-Hello.
Oh really?
Ah!
I don't believe it.
Yeah, yeah!
I got it.
I'll be there soon!
An unexpected
emergency has come up
that I've gotta
go and deal with.
Next time, try to
be more polite.
-Uh.
-You're in big trouble, mister.
Oh, I gotta go.
-What a weird lady.
Now, I wonder where
I can find Tezuka.
Hm.
Hm?
-Hey there.
I don't think you go to
Seigaku, do you, pal?
What are you up to?
-Nothing.
What's it to you?
Uh, well, since I'm busted.
I'm the famous
eighth grade top gun
at Rikkai Junior High School.
The famous Akaya Kirihara.
-Rikkai Junior High School, huh?
They're the best team
in the Kanto region.
They won the Kanegawa Prefecture
Regional Preliminaries
in a total of one hour.
-That's pretty weird.
Why is Kanegawa's
best here at Seigaku?
-Well, I just thought
I'd spy a little.
-Spying?
GIRL: I can't believe
you lived in America.
-It's so awesome.
Was everyone just totally
different over there,
or were people
basically the same?
-No, the same.
-Hey, you know what?
I've been taking
English for two years.
-We weren't asking you, Horio.
Now then, what were you
just talking about, Ryoma?
So, did everybody
there have a pool?
-Hey, I used to take
swimming lessons, you know.
-Be quiet.
-Man.
This stinks.
Just 'cause Ryoma used
to live in America.
-Huh?
-Hey, throw me the ball.
Over here, man.
-Here!
Hey, pass it here.
-Excuse me.
I, uh--
-What was that, huh?
Come on, tell me.
-Hey, Kazu, what's the matter?
-I, uh-- Well-- this punk
clocked me with his broom
on purpose.
-Uh.
Uh.
-Really?
He's got guts, hitting
an upperclassman
on purpose like that.
-Hey loser, do you
really think saying
you're sorry is enough
after you hit me in the head
with a broom?
-Well, I-- I don't
know what to say.
I honestly didn't intend
to hit you like that.
I sweat I really didn't.
-Kazu, this kid just
said he didn't hit you.
-Yeah.
Certainly sounds like this kid
thinks he's innocent to me.
Who does he think he is?
-That's not it.
What do you want me to do?
I'll do anything you want.
Please don't hurt me.
-Anything, huh?
-Hm.
-Huh?
-I think I have something
you could do to pay me back.
I shoot, and if I happen to hit
anything other than the can,
we'll let you off
the hook this time.
-Hey man, let us try too.
-You bet.
Free lunch for the
guy who nails it.
Hmph.
So don't run away, kid.
Got it?
I can't hit a target
if it's not even there.
MAN: Hey, you over there!
-Huh?
-Glad to see you, sir.
Horio needs you.
-Huh?
What about Horio
-S-Spy?
-What's he thinking
coming here like that?
That jerk's clowning us.
-Arai?
-Hey, what's going on here?
-Wow, I found you.
You're Tezuka, right?
My teammates all
talk about a you.
You were the only person to
beat our team at the Kanto
Tournament last year.
-H--Hey.
How about this.
Could I have a match with you?
I'll go easy.
-There's no outsiders
allowed here.
-Hm.
Aw, come on, Tezuka.
Just play me a set.
Don't be a jerk.
If you keep frowning,
it'll stick.
Lighten up, man.
You're so serious.
-Hey.
Don't you dare be
rude to our captain.
Get out of here.
-Idiot.
-Why don't you mind
your own business?
-He returned my serve.
-Come on, Tezuka.
I'm not trying to
prove anything to you.
I'm just asking you to hit a
couple of balls with me, that's
all.
You're not gonna hurt
my feelings, are you?
I'll work you.
Kidding.
You don't have to play if
you don't really want to.
Hey.
You over there.
Here comes your ball.
-Yes.
Looking good.
-Hm?
-What's this?
-Hey, wait a m--
-Huh?
-Oh no.
This is not good.
[hissing]
-Somebody's dead.
-Kaidoh just snapped.
[shouting]
KAIDOH: Show me who did this.
Who's responsible?
[shouting]
-Hold it, I'm first.
KAIDOH: You keep out of this.
-Hey, you two, stop it!
-Everyone, 30 laps.
-Aw, come on.
Man!
No way!
-Ha!
Scorching.
That was nine shoots in a row.
All right.
You owe me lunch.
-That's not good.
Kazu's free throws are
getting better and better.
-Yeah.
-That's eight lunches.
Nobody can beat
me at free throws.
-Ah, finished.
-Huh?
-Echizen, let's get
changed and get out here!
Yes!
It's time for tennis.
Takako, Kumako!
How long are you gonna
take to finish up?
-Why are you bugging us?
-Talk about mood swings.
You were just crying
a little while ago.
-Shut up.
Hurry up and finish cleaning.
-Hey.
Looks like the kid's
still got his broom.
I bet you think you
got away with it.
Now we'll even the score, kid.
-No, not now.
Actually, I have to
go to tennis practice.
-You think I care?
-Yeah, you said you'd
do anything, didn't you?
-You stay right
here 'til I say so.
-Oh, please, sir.
Please don't kill me.
I'm so sorry.
-That's it.
-This is bad.
-What should we do?
-Hey.
-Huh?
-You guys made that
mess, so I think
you should clean it up now.
-Oh, Ehizen.
-What?
-Hey, who's this?
-You've got a broom.
Why don't you clean
it up yourself, huh?
Butt out, pal.
Who do you think you are?
It's quite Obvious
I guess nobody's
bothered to train these
seventh graders yet.
Disrespecting us like that.
Just go back to work and nobody
gets into anymore trouble.
You're history.
Hm?
-No sweat.
That's not so hard.
-Why you little--
-Whoa.
-So cool.
-Big deal.
Free throws are easy, right?
-What's with him?
-Hey, I got an idea.
Let's shoot 10 each.
I dare you.
-10 shots in a row?
-You're challenging
us at free throws?
-Is this guy crazy?
With a broom?
-OK.
You lose, then you'll
be eating asphalt along
with that other
seventh grade dirtbag.
-And if you lose, then you
and your little friends
get to clean up.
How's that?
-Hm.
-Where could he be?
Echizen's late.
Huh?
-All right, Kazu.
Nice shot.
-Yeah.
-It's your turn, wonderboy.
-Two points!
-I knew he was great at
tennis, but still, how did--
-He sunk it with a broom.
BOY: Nice shot.
BOY: All right.
-Hey.
-Hm?
-Do you think I
can move back some?
It's kind of hard
to shoot this close.
-Huh?
GIRLS: He made it.
-Awesome.
-Neither one's missed yet.
-Hey guys.
Something's going on.
This looks good.
-All right!
-Come on!
-Let's check it out.
-The eighth grade
basketball star's
going up against some seventh
grader at free throws.
-No way.
-Hey, would you look at this?
Everybody's come to
watch the shoot out.
-And they're even watching
from inside the classrooms.
-Man, you see that?
That little squirt
keeps on stepping back,
but his shots just keep
getting better and better.
-And that's putting a
lot of pressure on Kazu.
KAZU (VOICEOVER): Why
am I being so impatient?
Argh.
That's just not like me.
There's no way I
can miss this shot.
The star basketball player
can't lose at free throws.
Not to a brat like him.
-Oh, man!
-It's not possible!
-Yes, he missed it!
-If Echizen sinks this, he wins.
-Huh?
-I can't believe how far
back Echizen is going.
-So, you're gonna take it
from the baseline, huh, Ryoma?
-Need this, don't you?
-Hey, thanks.
You're a pal.
-I think he must be the seventh
grade tennis star everyone
talks about.
-Whoa.
-That's just awesome.
-He even made a swish.
He did it!
Echizen beat him!
-Wow!
That seventh grader won!
-Hey.
Hate to say this.
You have a ways to go.
-So, Rikkai's Kirihara was here.
-Yes, he was.
-They sure are a powerhouse.
If we continue to win, we'll
probably end up playing them.
We're gonna need to
strengthen the team,
don't you think, Tezuka?
-I agree with you.
But first, we've got to
begin our ranking matches,
to be prepared for
the Kanto tournament.
-You're right.
We'll have to start thinking
about the schedule and line
up too.
-Hm hm hm.
This is a huge campus.
I'm so lost.
I'm sorry.
Are you OK?
You sure?
Hey, do you play tennis?
I don't know.
OK.
Well, I have this Seigaku ball.
Hey kid, do you think you
could return this ball?
-Thanks.
-Hm.
Seigaku, huh?
ANNOUNCER: Next stop,
Rikkai Junior High.
Next stop, Rikkai Junior High.
-I can't believe it.
Looks like that kid
has overslept again.
Young man.
You're headed to the
end of the line again.
Young man.
Wake up.
[theme music]
RYUZAKI: Sumire Ryuzaki here.
Firstly, I wanna
congratulate you
all for doing such a great job
at the Metropolitan Tournament.
Exactly what I
expected of Seigaku.
However, the Kanto Tournament
is a whole new bag.
There's gonna be a lot
of top level players.
Therefore, those who
are not up to snuff
will be eliminated
from the regular team.
The ranking matches
will decide everything.
Next on "The Prince of
Tennis," A Seigaku Tradition.