-Morning everyone.
[theme music]
-Oh wow.
What a beautiful day.
-Let's see.
Today I think I'll use-- Hm.
I'm all out.
GIRL: Oh, I'm sorry about that.
I used it all.
-What?
You used up all my toothpaste?
-Hm.
[hiss]
-Whoa.
You've built up
some muscles there.
-During the district
matches, there
was this incredible
power player.
I can't lose to him.
-Good morning, Taka.
-Well, good morning, Oishi.
Looks like you're
up early today.
-Look who's talking.
Thank you for the other day.
-Oh, if it was nothing.
[humming]
[giggling]
-Quiet!
Eat your breakfast, will you?
GIRLS: OK!
[alarm beeping]
-Good morning.
Sleep well?
-Just fine.
-It's pretty weird.
You used to drag in the
morning, but not these days.
-Huh?
-Hey, mom!
-Your mom's left already.
She said that she had
a meeting or something.
-Huh?
-Next time, a Japanese
breakfast, Kay?
[meow]
-Oh.
You're up too, Kalpin?
[meowing]
-Kalpin sure loves that toy.
I bet it's because you're
the one that gave it to him.
-I doubt it.
-OK, Kalpin.
I'll get you some food.
-Hm.
NANAKO: Ryoma?
-Hm?
NANAKO: You're studying?
-Yeah, I have to get
ready for an English quiz
first period today.
I think it'll be
pretty easy, but I just
wanna make sure I
don't miss anything.
-Hm.
Your grade in English.
You don't want to fail.
Isn't that the truth?
-I never fail.
Huh?
I'm off.
-Knock them dead.
You'll do great.
[meow]
-Huh?
Huh?
Kalpin!
[meow]
-Don't follow me.
Go home.
I'll play with you later.
[sad meow]
-Hey!
You're gonna be late!
-Look who's talking, Momo.
Hey!
-Oh, I hate this!
An English quiz in first period?
-Huh?
-Hey, what's the matter?
Huh?
What's that you got there?
-Our cat's toy.
Kalpin's.
-What's the matter, Echizen?
-It's nothing.
I--
-Oh, I get it.
You're not so sure about a
little English quiz Ha ha!
Don't worry, me neither.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER):
Piece of cake.
-Huh?
What's the problem, Echizen?
Hm.
Looks like you're nearly
done with the quiz.
Here, go ahead.
Finish the last question.
-What?
The last question?
Huh.
What a shock.
I did really badly on the quiz.
Hm.
RYOMA: You still got
a ways to go, Horio.
-Yeah, you know, you don't
have to show off there, Mr.
Straight-A's.
Huh?
What?
-Hello.
-Hey, what are
you doing in here?
We have science class
in here next period.
-I wanted to check
something on my latest
experiment during recess.
Don't worry.
I received permission
from the teacher.
-S-So what is it?
Whoa, it changed colors.
I don't think that's so good.
-It's going to be
my best drink ever.
Would you like to try it?
BOY: Shall I compare
thee to a summer's day?
Thou art more lovely
and more temperate.
Rough winds do shake the
darling buds of May--
-Eiji.
-Huh?
-Himalayan cats aren't
usually strays, are they?
-Himalayan cats aren't strays?
What's up?
TEACHER: Kikumaru.
Please continue.
-Yes, uh--
-Page 87, line 8.
-Thanks, dude.
Let's see, where were we?
By chance or nature's
changing course
untrimmed, but thy eternal
summer shall not fade.
-Teacher.
-Yes?
Uh, wh-- what is it, Tezuka?
-The third formula is incorrect.
Please check it.
-Oh, huh?
[crunch]
-Huh?
Momoshiro.
-(MUMBLING) Yes sir!
-Again with the eating.
Well, if you don't get at
least a 90 on your test,
you will take it over.
-(MUMBLING) What?
You can't do that.
-Meow?
[meowing]
-Hey, lady!
I would like a melon bun, a
curry bun, and a fried noodle
bun.
-I got it.
Now go stand in line.
-Aw.
And add in a blueberry juice, K?
-All right, all right!
-She sure had some nerve.
She polished off every last
bit of my favorite tube
of toothpaste.
-Hey, there you are.
-What do you think that is?
[curious whispering]
-Hey, what you doing, Echizen?
-Nothing.
-It's lunch time.
Let's go eat.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): That
was Kalpin, wasn't it?
-Wow!
You're good, Sakuno.
-My grandma taught me all
her great baking secrets.
GIRL: What?
You mean scary Mrs. Ryuzaki?
She's not always scary.
She also loves to make cakes.
-Really?
-Can I have one?
-Sure.
-Oh!
Just a minute!
-Echizen, why are you
eating so quickly?
TOMOKA: Ryoma!
-Hm?
-Hey, Ryoma, we brought
something for you!
Oh, Ryoma, look!
Check it out!
HORIO: Oh, wow.
These look great.
Did you really make these?
-Um, it's not that difficult.
You bake 'em.
-Go, Ryoma, go!
We brought these to
fortify you for tomorrow!
-I'll have one.
-Not so fast!
-Why not?
-These are for Ryoma,
and nobody else.
-Don't be so mean.
I just want one.
-Hey, Echizen.
Wow!
Look what you've got!
-Hey, look.
It's Momoshiro.
-I want one, too.
-Go right ahead.
-Why does he get one?
I asked before, and you said no.
-It's OK.
He's allowed because he's
always helping Ryoma out.
-No way.
-Hey, what's wrong with you?
-Hey there, Momo.
-Hm?
-Give me that.
-What?
-You know, i really have no
idea what's gotten into that boy
lately.
-Yeah.
Echizen's been
acting mighty weird.
-What do yo mean?
Did something happen to him?
-Well, if anyone would know,
it would most certainly be me.
Besides, I've already
had two years of tennis.
-That has nothing to do with it.
[meow]
-Let's have lunch here.
Ah!
Whoa, what was that?
-I'm really sorry to do this
at recess, but let's vote.
All those in favor?
-Aye.
-No way.
Forget it.
[school bells]
[chatter]
-You're here early.
What's going on?
What's the matter?
-Nothing.
-Hm.
So, uh, Echizen, are you
worried about something?
-Sort of.
-Yep, I thought
there was something.
Horio also mentioned that
you're not your normal self.
-It's our cat.
-Your cat?
-I think he's at school.
-Did he follow you?
-No.
That can't be.
It's way too far.
-Now that you're bringing
it up, a girl in my class
said she saw a white
raccoon on the roof.
You don't think that maybe
that raccoon is your cat?
Oh, hey.
-Uh, I'll go and
look on the roof!
-Wait just a minute.
She saw him at lunch.
There's no way that your
cat's gonna still be up there.
-Well, maybe.
But he's somewhere.
-Here.
You can borrow my bike.
Why don't you take a good
look around on your way home,
and see if you can find him?
-Huh?
-Don't worry.
Cats are always roaming
around in weird places
you'd never expect.
-But Kalpin hardly
ever leaves home.
-Well, that's why you better
go out and look for him.
He could be home by now.
It's a sure thing.
You should take care
of your worries first.
Mm-hm.
Get going, Echizen.
-Momo, I promise I'll
repay you for this someday.
-No problem at all.
Come back as soon as you can.
-Is Echizen here?
-Well, apparently there's some
sort of family celebration,
so he had to go home for a few.
He said he'd be right back.
-I wish I'd known.
I was planning to
end practice early.
The metropolitans are tomorrow.
-Kalpin?
[meow]
[meowing]
-Hey.
Who left the door open?
Huh?
-Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk,tsk.
Hm?
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER):
What's it doing?
Oh, well.
[humming]
-Here, here, kitty.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Come on.
Come on, you.
[meow]
-Come on.
Come on.
[meow]
-Come on.
Come on.
Here.
Don't give up.
Come on.
Over here.
[laughter]
-Hm.
Kaidoh is usually
never this late.
-Hm.
He'll need to do
some extra laps.
-Oh.
Speak of the devil.
-Hello.
-Hey.
-He's in a good mood.
-What?
-You can tell?
Well done.
BOY: Good job, everybody.
BOY: Good practice.
-Yeah.
-Bye, see you later, Oishi.
-You're going home like that?
-I'd hate it if they ran out.
-Mm.
He's so impatient.
-Man, you're in great shape.
-Yeah, not too bad, I guess.
-Give this to Ryoma, will you?
And then I want to to--
-Well, looks to me like Ryoma
wasn't able to come back.
Huh?
What's going on?
-Momo, come and see!
In the clubhouse,
there's this big raccoon!
-A raccoon?
Huh?
-Hey, kitty.
Want a fish?
-Hm.
He doesn't seem real interested.
-Bye.
So long, guys.
[honking]
-Shusuke, want a ride home?
-Oh, hey, sis.
Well, I'll see you guys.
-'Til tomorrow.
-Yeah, these feel terrific.
I want them.
How much are they?
-Well, let's see.
For you, that will be
12,000 yen plus tax.
Let's see what I've got.
Oh no, I'm 80 yen short!
-Eiji?
-Oh, Oishi.
Oh, please can I borrow 80 yen?
Do you have 80 yen?
I'm 80 yen short.
Oh please, oh please.
-You need 80 yen?
-Did you find him, Ryoma?
-Not yet.
I'll check back at school.
-Ryoma!
-Hm?
-We'll find him.
I know he'll turn up eventually.
-Hey there.
Come on, Echizen.
Look here.
-Thanks.
-Here, this is from the coach.
-Thanks, captain.
-I'll just leave your bag here.
-You get some rest, all right?
-Hope the party was great.
-Huh?
The party?
What does he mean by that, huh?
Oh yeah.
-Huh?
-Hey wanna hit some balls?
I owe you one, after all.
-Hm.
So Echizen wants to pay
me back with a match.
I can't wait for the metros.
I'll tear up the courts.
-Oh?
I don't think so,
Momo, my friend.
It'll be me tearing
up the courts!
-Wow.
It's that brand new toothpaste.
-I'm sorry I used up yours.
-Thank you, sis!
-Shusuke.
So, do you want me to predict
the outcome of the Metro
matches?
-Sure.
But if I remember
correctly, your predictions
are always right on the mark.
It's kinda scary.
-Hey, Takashi.
Go to bed.
-OK.
-Tomorrow morning, don't worry.
You don't have to help me.
-What?
That would mess me up.
I gotta help.
-Echizen's shots sure had a
lot of power to them today.
-Night, Kalpin.
And soon, it will be the morning
of the Metropolitan Tournament.
[theme music]
-Hey, hey.
It's nice to see you again.
I'm Horio, with two years
of tennis experience.
The Metropolitan Tournament
is finally starting,
and those guys are nervous
just hearing the name Seigaku.
But Echizen sure is late.
He's tardy without a doubt.
But hey, no way.
You can't ask me to do that.
That's crazy.
Next on "The Prince of Tennis."
A new regular appears?
Oh yeah!
Looks like my time
has finally come.