[birds chirping]
-Ah.
Looks like it's 9:56.
Seigaku signs in a 10:00.
[sigh]
[scream]
[theme music]
[grunt]
-Yeah!
-All right!
-Woo-hoo!
-Way to go!
-What a shot!
-The line-up has been announced.
There'll be no
changes in the order.
Number one, Yoshinaga.
Two, Yamata.
And three, Kano.
-Ah, the Metros.
Everyone's revving to go.
I just wish we could record
this exciting atmosphere.
-Don't worry, Mr. Inoue.
Just leave it to me.
-Huh?
-Take a look at this.
It's a video camera.
Brand new.
I just bought it today.
-Oh.
Looks like you're
really going all out.
Aren't you, Shiba?
-It's got three CCDs.
It's a great camera.
I'll be able to record the faces
of Ryoma and everyone else.
-Listen, Shiba.
You do realize this is
a tennis tournament.
There's no point
in taking faces.
Ah.
Hi there.
-Huh?
-Oh.
Hello and good morning.
-So it's you again.
I'll out-cheer anybody.
Fight!
Ryoma go!
Lovely R-Y-O!
-Please stop.
You're embarrassing me.
-What are you talking about?
I couldn't be there
for district matches,
so I have to go all out today.
Fight!
Fight, fight, fight, fight!
-By the way, I don't see
the Seigaku team around
here anywhere.
-I imagine they're probably
signing in right about now.
Let's go.
-Ryoma!
R-Y-O go!
Huh?
Wait for me!
Hey!
-Tezuka and Fuji I
know about, but now you
say it's that seventh grader
Echizen I need to worry about.
Mizuki?
-That's right.
You're going to be sorry if
you don't take him seriously.
-Hey, look over there,
Mizuki, It's Yudai.
MIZUKI: Haha.
Hey, Yudai.
What's wrong with you?
What's with that face?
Looks like you're
trembling with excitement.
-I've come this far, and
now I must defeat him.
-Hmm.
We're in the process of
figuring out Seigaku's order
so that we can arrange for
you to face Shusuke Fuji.
-Ha.
Thanks.
-Haha.
Well, whatever happens, there's
no way those guys at Seigaku
will ever be able to beat
the St. Rudolph Academy team.
-He's late.
What could be keeping Ryoma?
-If all eight of us don't
sign in by 10 o'clock,
we'll be disqualified.
-But that would be terrible.
-We're in trouble.
What about Oishi?
Was he be able to get
in touch with Echizen?
-If he has, we haven't
heard from him.
I mean, out of all
the days, why did he
have to pick today to be late?
BOTH: Yeah.
I know.
-Hey, what's going on here?
-Huh?
-A strategy meeting?
If you don't hurry up and sign
in, you'll be disqualified.
-Oh, Mr. Inoue.
You see, Ryoma isn't here yet.
[gasps]
-Hmm.
-Isn't that just
like Ryoma, to be
late on the day
of a competition.
He's got nerves of steel.
[laughs]
-Tomoka, stop it.
This is no laughing matter.
-Hey!
It's me.
I got word from Echizen.
He said he was helping a
woman who was having a baby.
He's been at the
hospital all morning.
[gasps]
-Sounds like a line.
-He's lying.
No doubt about it.
-Well, if he's on
his way here, he
should make it in time, then.
I'll save the lecture for later.
Anyway, we can't wait for
him before we sign in.
[gasps]
-Huh?
Oh.
-Kaidoh, lend him your jersey.
-Ahh!
-Say, who's Osawa
Intermediate playing against?
-Ah.
Who was it now?
-Neither their team or
their supporters are here.
-Haha.
They probably got scared when
they heard our name called.
-Who got scared?
-Tachibana.
Sorry that we're late.
-Number 128, Seigaku.
Eight members to
sign in, please.
-Let me review this.
My first round, your team
will play all five matches.
And whoever wins three
matches is the winner.
-Yes, sir.
-The top five schools will
qualify for the Konto matches.
The top four will
win automatic entry.
The four schools that
lose in the quarter finals
will compete in a consolation
round for the fifth spot.
Do you understand?
-Yes, sir.
We do.
-All right, then.
Oh, I see you have a seventh
grader on your team, too.
-Yikes.
-Is anything wrong?
-You-- ha.
You've got a ways to go.
Haha.
-Haha.
How promising.
Well, good luck, then.
[laughs]
[collective sigh]
-You must be pretty
confident to be so late.
-Huh?
-Echizen of Seigaku.
-Don't think I know you.
-Hmm.
You're really something.
Seventh grade and
already a regular.
You're hitting with your left
today, aren't you, Echizen?
-You're in your uniform.
Going home already?
You've got a ways to go.
-Hmm.
How cocky.
But that stubbornness
will make it easier
for me to manipulate the
match when the time comes.
Ha.
-Oh no.
I wonder what's
really keeping Ryoma.
[laughing]
-Well, how this?
Do I look good?
So I've finally become a
regular on the Seigaku team.
I mean, of course,
with my abilities,
I'll be able to become
one for real pretty soon.
-There you go
again mouthing off.
You're lucky we
weren't found out.
-But I gotta admit,
I'm a little jealous
of the regular's team jersey.
-Yeah.
Well, it belongs to Kaidoh.
So it's a little big for me.
Huh?
-They got the regulars.
-Wowee.
They must be really very strong.
[laughs]
-Look at that guy over there.
[grunt]
-What an awful serve.
It's nothing compared to
my incomparable serve.
-Hey, kid.
ALL: Huh?
-People say you use
a mean kick serve.
-Well, ah, that's right.
-Well, I say you're
nothing but a liar.
And if there's one thing
I hate, it's liars.
-But wait.
I'm not lying.
-Ha.
Then how about we
play a game together?
-Uh.
-There's an open practice
court right over here.
Come on.
ALL: Ugh.
[gasps]
-Shiba, don't just
take Seigaku's pics.
You have to cover every school.
-OK.
OK.
-Oh.
Here comes last
year's winning school.
-Huh?
-It's Hyotei Academy.
Seigaku lost to them in
the finals last year.
-Hmph.
So they're the enemy.
Maybe I oughtta
beat them up first.
-Now now.
-Well, hello there.
-Hey, Atobe.
So how is everything?
-I don't think we'll be
losing no matter who we play.
Right, Kabaji?
-Yeah.
-That's some confidence,
but the Seigaku team
is much stronger than last year.
-Yes, but we'll nail them down.
Just wait and see
for yourselves.
-What's with him?
He's so full of himself.
-The confidence of
a champion, I guess.
[grunts and groans]
-Don't take it easy just
because it's the first round.
ALL: Yes, ma'am.
-It's Yamabuki.
-Hmm?
-They'll probably climb
the ranks as well.
-So, Banji, you came after all.
-Something wrong?
-No.
I just wish Ryoma'd
get here soon.
-This isn't good.
-All because Ryoma is so late.
-It's really Horio's fault
for getting so carried away.
-What should we do?
-What's the matter?
Hit a kick already, will ya?
-Uh.
This is the end for me.
[gasp]
-Oh!
Echizen!
ALL: Huh?
-Huh?
Seigaku regular Echizen,
hurry up and hit the ball!
-Hmm.
-(NERVOUSLY) Haha.
Yes, sir.
Right away.
-You're late.
Hurry on over here and
take my place, will you?
I got stuck having
to play this--
-Hang in there, Echizen.
-Hey, Echizen!
Wait!
Don't go, please!
-You're Echizen, aren't you?
[crying]
-Oh well.
I guess it can't be helped.
I think one week's worth
of juice should do it.
-Huh?
Make that three
days' worth, Echizen.
After all, this is all
your fault for being late.
-A month's worth
ought to be enough.
-Oh.
Oh.
SAKUNO: You can't
do that, Ryoma.
-Huh?
-After all, you were
the one who was so late.
So please help Horio now.
[gasps]
-Hmm.
Sure.
-Hey, dummy.
What are you stalling for?
BOTH: Hold your horses!
-Huh?
-And now a slight change.
Instead of Echizen, I, second
year tennis player Horio,
will now serve.
[scream]
[grunts]
-Oh, Echizen.
You're late.
What were you doing?
-I was just getting warmed up.
-I can't believe it.
That kid hit a kick
serve right in my eye.
Seigaku has a bunch of
those kids on their team.
Oh!
-What do you mean you were
just getting warmed up?
When we get back,
you're doing 40 laps.
-Easy on the head, Momo.
-Save the lecture for later.
Get ready for the matches.
-OK.
-Got for it Ryoma.
We're aiming for straight wins.
You can do it!
-I'm grateful he
saved my neck, but I
was wondering why he was
sliding around so much.
He dirtied my jersey on purpose.
What am I going to do?
I borrowed it from Kaidoh.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
-Yeah!
Ryoma!
You're wonderful, Ryoma!
Come on!
Go get 'em!
-Hmm.
If I'm not mistaken,
he's from St. Rudolph's.
ANNOUNCER: Game and match
to Echizen, Seigaku.
-Oh.
Has Ryoma's match ended already?
-It was a perfect game.
-Darn it.
And I just brought my new
video camera for the occasion.
-We're just in time.
You better do a
good job now, Shiba.
You never seen it
before, have you?
-Huh?
Never seen what?
-All right!
Now we get to see our
first formal match.
-Yeah.
That's right.
-I'm getting very excited.
-What's this all about?
-The last Seigaku player
and number one singles
is Kunimitsu Tezuka.
-Where are these guys from, man?
These guys look cool.
[crowd chatter]
ANNOUNCER: One set match.
Seigaku's Tezuka to serve.
-Shoot.
I'll take him on.
He may be a top
player nationally,
but he's just in
junior high like me.
Uh.
-That was amazing.
-His first serve was an ace.
-And what fantastic speed.
15-love.
-He's so good.
-That's why he's number
one singles at Seigaku.
-No way.
He accurately placed his serve
in this tiny service box.
-Yes.
Great serves!
-Wow.
What speed and control.
He's amazing.
-And it's pretty clear why.
It looks like he's
giving his flat serves
a bit of a slice spin.
Usually, if you can set a
ball in the right corner
after serving in the left,
it's impossible to get it.
-Wowee!
He hasn't allowed
his opponent a shot.
-So this is Captain
Tezuka's true ability.
-Not by a long shot.
BOTH: Huh?
-The captain's ability
is much more than this.
So far he's only just
getting warmed up out there.
-There aren't many
opponents Tezuka
would use his full energies on.
-OK.
I won't let my guard down.
-That's Seigaku, all right.
They've won every set 6-love.
-Seigaku?
Oh, man.
We play them next.
I guess what Kuki of Kakinoki
said about Tezuka being injured
wasn't true.
-Yeah.
The Seigaku team this
year has no weaknesses.
And if they do, I sure
wish someone would tell me.
Ah, man.
There's no way we can win.
-Hey, don't you have any
confidence at all, stupid?
-Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt you.
You're from Akiyama
3, aren't you?
Can you tell me
who's the captain?
-So who's Seigaku playing next?
-Akiyama 3.
-Oh.
Poor things.
Akiyama 3 doesn't stand
a chance against them.
[laugh]
-I wonder.
[gasp]
ANNOUNCER: 15-all.
[grunt]
[laugh]
-Fuji, Kawamura, you won 6-love.
But your match was
long, was it not?
-Yeah.
It wasn't all that easy.
-They kept poking at
my vulnerable spots.
-Hmm.
[grunt]
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Seigaku.
[laugh]
ANNOUNCER: Six games to one.
-We won.
We won!
-It's so hot.
I need something to drink.
-Good job!
We're 2 and 0.
-Just leave it to
the Golden Pair.
-But you two seem to be
having a lot of trouble.
I noticed several mistakes.
-They were doing
a lot of stuff I
don't like to see
on a tennis court.
-Yeah.
They sure were.
-Again, they picked
at our weak spots
trying to get us where
we're vulnerable.
-That team came up the ranks
back in the district matches.
I guess they must have
done a lot of research.
-Boy, it sure is hot today.
-OK, little guy.
It's your turn.
-All right.
ANNOUNCER: One set match.
Seigaku's Echizen to serve.
-Huh?
-Have you been
collecting any good data?
-Yes, I have, Inui.
-If I'm not mistaken,
you're going the new manager
at St. Rudolph.
Are you not?
-No, you're not mistaken, Inui.
You've been marking
me all this time.
Nothing seems to escape you.
-Hmm.
-Well, my name's Mizuki.
And I must say it's an honor
that you know about me already.
-Instead of spying,
don't you need
to go and watch your
own teammates play?
-Hmm.
They'll probably win without me.
Number two, double 6-love.
Number one, double 6-2.
Number three single, 6-2.
-Amazing.
You can pinpoint your
predictions on your data alone?
-Ha.
Hearing you say
that goes a long way
to building my self-confidence.
-Depending on how
you use it, your data
can have a very big
impact-- naturally.
-Naturally?
-There are times
when such information
can be used as a weapon.
-What are you talking about?
-Hurry.
-OK.
-You used Akiyama 3
as your attack dog.
Before the match,
you probably taught
them the Seigaku
players' weak points.
You did this so that they
would know what to look for.
Although we won the match,
we had a tougher time.
We were almost outwitted.
If it hadn't been for all the
data you collected and shared
about how our players
would overcome attacks
on their weak
points, we would have
had a much easier
time beating them.
Isn't that right, Mizuki?
-That's so unlike you, Inui.
Thanks to me, Akiyama was
able to play against Seigaku
on a much more even field.
Don't you think
they're satisfied?
[grunt]
ANNOUNCER: Six games to love.
Game and match to
Seigaku's Echizen.
[cheering]
-We'll use anything we
can in order to win.
I'm really looking
forward to playing you.
So long.
-What's wrong, Inui?
-Tezuka, we need to look out
for St. Rudolph's players.
-Hmm.
-What are you trying to say?
-They'll stop at nothing to win.
[evil laugh]
-Yo.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is Momo, everyone's idol.
By the way, the Metropolitans
are really revving up.
Aren't they?
Is it my turn soon?
And, uh, hey old lay,
what's with this order?
I'm playing doubles
again and-- oh no.
Not with this crazy guy.
Next on the "Prince of
Tennis," Momo and Viper.
I have no choice but to
do it, no choice at all.