-The Wave Surge?
-Graah!
Ai!
Gah!
-Ah-huh!
[theme music]
-Unh!
(THINKING) Come on.
We're going to win this.
Unh!
-(THINKING) Their
willpower is intimidating.
This match will
determine the outcome
of the entire tournament.
This ends now!
Unh!
-Huh?
-Oh!
-Ah!
-It didn't even bounce.
-What was that?
It just skidded along the ground
until it went right past them.
-That's one of the
best counter-shots
in Fuji's arsenal.
The Triple Counter.
-(ALL) The Triple Counter.
TACHIBANA: He
might be a problem,
this genius, Shusuke Fuji.
-Harh!
Unh!
Unh-ah!
-Looks like Seigaku's
back on track.
-Well, they're finally
playing their own game.
--[sighs] Wow, this
is getting good!
-I'm not letting you
get back into this.
Unrh, huh?
Can he read them all?
-Unrh!
-Oh!
[both gasp]
-That's it.
His Triple Counter!
-Awesome.
-Yeah!
Way to go, Fuji.
-Wow!
I guess he really is a genius.
Cool!
-Well, that was a tough one.
The Triple Counter.
Got to hand it to him.
-Yeah!
[both grunt]
-Atta boy!
-Aw!
-We've got 'em on
the run now, huh?
-(THINKING) Got 'em
on the run, do they?
Somehow, I think
this Fudomine team
isn't going down so easily.
-Pick up those balls.
Go on.
Quit being so lazy.
Hu-unh!
[crowd gasps]
MALE: That's not the spirit.
Get running, 20 times the field.
Move it!
-Play a match against
me if you're not afraid.
MALE: What'd you say?
Watch yourself, Tachibana.
-You've got nerve
talking like that.
-And if I win, you get to run
20 times around the field,
or at least until you drop.
-Ho.
-What?
-That's stupid.
Who'd want to do that?
Forget it.
I'm out of here.
-Anyone think they're
stronger than me?
Step up.
-(TOGETHER) Huh?
-Hey, Tachibana.
Last time, we cut
you a lot of slack,
but it seems like you just
don't want to learn, do you?
[all moaning in pain]
-So this is the new team, huh?
Well, from now
until next spring,
you're going to spend your
time picking up tennis balls,
and be happy about it.
--[sighs] You're a
failure as an adviser.
-Unh.
What the-- urgh.
-Unh!
-Ooh!
-Unh.
-[muffled moans]
-(TOGETHER) Oh!
Huh?
-Aww!
[cats meowing]
[loud purring]
-(ALL CHANTING) Nationals.
Nationals.
Nationals!
-(THINKING) Fudomine
Junior High.
These players are a tight team.
Appears their captain, Tachibana
certainly sees to that.
-Unh!
-Oh, yeah.
-Oh!
The Seigaku boys have really
come along, haven't they?
-Let's break those guys now!
This is our chance!
We do it here!
Ruah!
-Mm-hm.
(THINKING) Now this
next point is key.
If we can take this
game, it'll be our serve.
And then we will definitely
have a huge advantage.
-Sakurai, open up
the front court.
-Huh?
-(TOGETHER) Huh?
-(THINKING) Captain, I'm
going to use that shot.
-Ishida, so tell me.
Is your arm starting
to hurt again?
-Captain Tachibana.
-Nobody can return that
powerful shot of yours,
but it's too big a
strain on your arm.
You know that
better than anyone.
You know you won't be able
to play, so don't use it,
all right?
-[laughs] All right then.
You're the captain.
If you say so, then
I guess I won't.
-(THINKING) He going to do it.
-Ya-Yah!
-(THINKING) This next point
is crucial, all right.
-Hm.
Captain Tachibana,
Ishida's winning.
-Hah!
-Unh!
-Captain Tachibana.
-I guess he can't be stopped.
All right.
(THINKING) But just this once.
-Now you're talking!
Argh!
-Ahh!
Unh!
-(THINKING) Ishida,
don't waste this shot.
Bring the momentum
back to Fudomine.
-Argh!
-Go for it!
-The Wave Surge!
-[sighs]
-(ALL) What?
-The Wave Surge?
-Urah!
Ai!
Yah!
-(THINKING) Uh-uh.
I cannot let them take this one.
-(THINKING) Are you really
going to try and hit that back?
It's useless.
You can't return my
invincible flat shot
with those skinny arms of yours.
-Let it go, Fuji!
-You're not nearly
strong enough.
-[inhales] Mine!
Taka!
-Unh!
Urrgh, oof, oh,
unh, unh, oh, yeah!
Got it!
Unh!
-God, unbelievable!
-Believe it.
He returned it.
-Grr!
-Ishida!
-Unh.
Arghm!
-Look at his stance!
-Oh, not again!
-Can't be.
Not two in a row!
-Don't do it, Ishida.
You're going to
hurt your arm again!
So tell me, is you're
starting to hurt again.
-Captain Tachibana.
[growling]
-Nobody can return that
powerful flat shot of yours.
But it's too big a
strain on your arm.
You know that
better than anyone.
-[laughs] All right then.
You're the captain.
And I don't care!
Unh-dah!
Hawh!
[crowd expresses disbelief]
-Uh, hm?
-He overdid it.
I'll scold him later.
-Yeah, but did you see how
badly his strings broke?
-As a matter of fact, I did.
But something else
for broke too.
-This is fantastic.
I can't believe it.
Seigaku's winning the game.
-Yeah.
But still--
-What?
Huh?
-All right.
-Yeah!
-Go, Takashi!
One more game!
Finish them off with
your Burning Serve.
-Leave it to me, little monkey.
Hm?
What's the matter, Fuji-ko?
Ahh!
-(ALL) Huh?
-Hm.
-What happened?
-Taka, my friend.
You covered for me.
-Unh, uhm-mm-mm.
-What?
What's going on here?
-Sir?
-Yes?
-We have to default.
-What?
-What in the--?
-Huh?
-It can't be.
-Go and get some cooling spray?
-(ALL) Huh?
Yes, sir!
-What are you saying man!
I can still play.
You know how important
this first match is.
Quitters never win!
Unh!
Owh!
-Don't worry.
It'll be fine.
OK?
-Well, yeah.
I'm so sorry.
Ow-ow, ow-ow!
-Suck it up.
There's a chance
it could be broken.
-Ok, ow!
INUI: You need to
go to the hospital.
-(ALL) Eeh!
-Captain?
-Hm.
The air is getting colder.
Kamio, why don't you go warm up?
Shinji, go hit with him.
You should be limbering
up for your match as well.
-So what's up next?
Next up is the
Number One Doubles.
It looks like Oishi
and Kikumaru are
playing against
Uchimura and Mori.
-Then in that case.
-It can't be.
Come on.
Seigaku can't lose in a default.
It's wrong.
Just wrong!
-Huh?
Well, What's going
to happen now?
-Hm?
-Hm.
(THINKING) Our usually laid-back
friend has gotten serious.
Better watch out, hmph!
MATCH ANNOUNCER: This
is a one-set match.
Seigaku's Oishi to serve.
-(THINKING) We'll
flatten them in no time.
-(THINKING) OK.
We'll show 'em what
we're capable of.
-Huh, unh!
-(THINKING) I'll teach them.
-Unh.
Here, why, they call me
the Forward Net Killer.
-Eyah!
-(ALL) No!
-He's aiming straight
at Eiji's face.
Be careful!
-(BOTH) Oh!
-Unh!
That was totally easy.
-Oh!
-We did it!
We won the points!
[crowd murmurs admiringly]
MATCH ANNOUNCER: 15-Love
FEMALE: I wonder
how he did that?
FEMALE: He's so awesome.
UCHIMURA: What?
How could he?
How does he move like it?
-Just like that.
Got it?
-That rocks.
Yeah!
-Come on.
Piece of cake.
We can win!
-Unh!
Uh!
MATCH ANNOUNCER:
Game to Seigaku!
-Huh?
Ryoma?
Where are you off to?
-I'm thirsty.
I'm getting a drink of water.
-Well, don't be
gone for too long.
Matches are on.
RYOMA: OK.
-He always does
whatever he wants.
-Unh.
-Oh.
Huh?
It's that kid.
[sighs]
DOCTOR : You hurt yourself
by hitting a ball?
Mm.
The ball broke his
tennis strings?
It doesn't seem possible.
[laughs]
-Umph.
But it's true.
Really.
-Hm.
Uh.
MATCH ANNOUNCER:
Game to Seigaku.
-(THINKING) Wow.
Look at this!
This is some show.
They're hitting two balls
at such a short distance.
[thunder]
-Got it!
-Mine!
[thunder]
-Kaido.
You should probably get
some balls and warm up.
After all, your
match is up next.
-Mm. [sigh]
-And if you see
Echizen, bring him back.
-What?
No way!
-The little guy could
have gotten lost.
Upperclassmen need to help.
It's your job, right?
-Eegh.
Unh, aww.
-[laughs]
MALE: These two are Kamio
and Ibu of Fudomine.
-Hm?
(THINKING) Kamio?
That idiot!
-Oh!
-(THINKING) He-he-he.
Now we have a full cast.
-We managed to beat
Fuji in doubles,
but it really comes
down us in singles.
-Where is your confidence, huh?
-It's still here.
Don't you worry.
I'm bursting with confidence.
Even more than our captain.
-Huh.
-Hmm.
-[growling] Huh?
-Uh.
[grunting]
-What?
-Huh?
Hah.
-Oh?
-Huh?
-Uh?
-No way!
He went through that!
-Wow!
How did me manage that?
-He's a regular for Seigaku.
And only a seventh grader.
-(WITH DISDAIN) Oh.
-For real?
-You still have a ways to go.
Hey!
How'd you feel about
adding another ball?
-That punk!
Better stop mouthing
off kid, or else!
-Hey!
You got a problem with
our seventh grader?
-Hm?
-Oh-huh.
Uh-oh.
Enough's enough here.
-Huh?
It's An!
-Hey, aren't you guys supposed
to be out on the courts.
If you're doing anything
other than warming up,
I'll tell your captain.
-Yeah, OK.
Well, I can't wait for
our match, Mr. Seigaku.
Yeah.
-You guys may look cool, but
you're still pretty hot-headed.
But I still don't get
tired of watching you.
-Who's this?
-Don't know.
-Don't worry about me.
Worry about the match
you're about to play.
Kamio's the type of
player who's going
to give you a really hard time.
-Really?
Hmm?
AN: And Shinji Ibu, he's
got the same feel for tennis
as your genius, Shusuke Fuji.
-How do you know so much?
AN: [giggles] That's a secret.
Oh! [gasps] I can't
stand this rain!
See you later!
-Don't just stand there!
Get out of here!
-OK.
-Got it!
MALE: Not the rain!
No-ho, this is bad!
-No!
I'm getting soaked!
-Wait!
My umbrella should help.
-This rain may blow
over soon, but the game
could be affected by it.
-Uh!
-(THINKING) He slipped.
Now's my chance!
How do like this!
-Unh, unh!
-No way!
Not again.
-Hm.
Hmm.
AN (VOICEOVER): He's got
the same feel for tennis
as you genius, Shusuke Fuji.
[theme music]
OISHI (VOICEOVER): Hello.
I'm Shuichiro Oishi, assistant
captain of the Seigaku Tennis
Team.
That Fudomine team is amazing.
The Seigaku regulars were all
stunned by Ishida's Wave Surge
Shot.
Our Number Two Doubles
team was forced
to concede when Taka himself.
But Eiji and I will even things
out in our Number One Doubles
match.
In the next "Prince of
Tennis", "The Boomerang Snake".
But hey, Kaido, what in
the world is that move?