-OK, punk!
Try to return this, come on!
[rock music playing]
-Hey, did you hear?
Some 12-year-old kid's playing
in the boy's sixteens today.
Thank he'll win a match?
-No way.
They must make some mistake
when they registered him.
-No, I heard it's for real.
Can you believe it?
-Whatever.
The whole idea is
totally ridiculous.
-Jeez.
You're stupid.
You don't even know
what grip you're using.
If you guys really want more
top spin, use the Western grip.
Face the racket this way,
vertical, and hold the
handle like you're
shaking hands.
-I expect nothing
less than brilliance
from the number one player on
the Higa High School tennis
team.
-You got that right.
Rip it, and again!
And again!
-Hey.
You think you morons
can chill out?
-Hmm.
[racket clattering]
-Hey, can you believe it?
That kid's telling
me to shut up.
-Bingo.
You know, in order to
use a real Western grip,
you have to hold your racket
as if you're picking it up.
-What'd you say?
-The handshake grip
you were talking about
is called the Eastern grip.
Hey, don't worry about it.
Lots of people
make that mistake.
-Hey, come back here.
You scared?
Huh!
-Wow.
He made you look dumb.
-Hey, you guys, we got to go.
-Oh, me too!
Come on, grandma.
You invited me here.
And now you're
really, really, late.
[sakuno grumbles]
-Hey, do you where the
Kakinohizaka tennis courts are?
-Huh?
Oh, it's you!
Wow, what a coincidence.
I'm going to the tennis courts
too, to meet my grandma.
Are you in the tournament?
I don't know much about
tennis, but I love it.
-They're where?
-Oh.
I'm sorry.
Um, go out the south exit,
and then go straight ahead.
-Thanks a lot.
See you.
-Ryoma?
His name is Ryoma.
Grandma, you're late!
You're half an hour late!
What the heck took you
so long to get here?
-Yeah, I know I'm
running a little late.
But let's go.
[sakuno grumbles]
-That's the north exit.
-I know that.
To get to the tennis courts,
you walk out the north exit
and go straight ahead.
Come on, let's go.
We'll be late.
-Huh?
The north exit?
Oh, no.
I can't believe I gave
him the wrong directions!
[sakuno gasps]
-What are you so upset about?
Are you looking around
for someone you know?
-Grandma, if a player is late
for a match, what happens?
-It means he defaults.
-Default?
-Yep, that's it.
He's out.
-Uh oh, I think
I'm in trouble now.
-I wonder what that's all about.
Be sure to stay close, Sakuno!
-Huh?
Uh, excuse me.
-Did you make it to your match?
-I was late.
I defaulted.
-You bet.
It was your double fault.
[sakuno squeaks]
-I know.
You want to get a soda?
-Huh?
[mechanical whirring]
-Here.
-I'm sorry, I didn't
have any change.
I just wanted to say
thanks for helping me out
with those guys on the train.
Those bullies were really
giving me a hard time.
-What do you mean?
-Well, those guys
were so obnoxious.
If you hadn't said
anything, one of them
was going to hit
me with his racket.
At least, I thought so.
-You were on the train?
Where were you sitting?
-I was right across from you.
-It was nothing, really.
I just wanted those
clowns to shut up.
[Sakuno gasps]
-Too bad we're
bothering you, chump.
-It's that kid again, huh?
-All talk.
Looks like he's
already headed home.
Loser.
-I'm the top seed in
boy's sixteens, kid.
And don't you forget it.
So I dare you to tell me
to be quiet again, you
twerp, and I'll fix you.
What you looking at?
Huh?
This brat's got to play
a boatload of tennis
to get a tenth as good as I am.
I'll make you sorry, creep!
[sakuno shrieks]
-Come on, dude.
Let's go.
-Yeah.
-Hey.
Still remember that
grip I taught you?
-What?!
-Hey, if you do, I'd be
happy to teach you some more.
-Why you little--
SASABE'S FRIEND: Sasabe, you've
got a match to play later.
Are you sure you
want to do this?
-Destroying the kid will
be the perfect warm-up
to beating my next opponent.
SASABE'S FRIEND: Once you
put your mind to something,
there's no talking
you out of it.
Heh heh heh.
-Ryoma, I think you should
think twice about this.
-I may as well play.
It's dumb to go home
without warming up my serve.
Hold this, please.
-Best of one set
match, Sasabe to serve.
-We don't need any line judges.
We'll call it ourselves, OK?
-Fine with me.
-All right, kid.
Don't worry, I'll give
you a little handicap.
I'll serve you underhanded.
-He can't be serious.
-Huh?
-Love, 15.
-Oops, no problem.
I got a little careless.
-So this is where
you've run away to.
-Oh, grandma, you're here.
-This is going to
get interesting.
-Don't just stand there,
you've got to do something.
Grandma, these
high school bullies
are going to kill
my friend Ryoma.
He's just a little kid.
-Nonsense.
You just saw that service
return, didn't you?
This is going to be really good.
SASABE'S FRIEND: Hey, Sasabe.
I think you better give it up
and save face while you can.
-Shut up, you moron.
Anybody can return an
underhand serve, even you!
-Go ahead and keep it up.
People make excuses
like that when
you're about to get humiliated.
-OK, punk.
Try to return this.
Come on!
-There it is,
Sasabe's killer serve.
-Not good enough.
-Huh?
What the-- wah!
-You've got to be kidding me.
-He returned Sasabe's best
serve, that's unbelievable.
SASABE'S FRIEND: Wow,
that kid's quick!
Love, 30.
-I know what score is.
You don't have to keep calling
it out, you stupid jerk.
-Oh, don't underestimate him.
He's just warming up.
-Huh?
Grandma, you know that boy?
I just met him on the train.
-What, you mean I
didn't tell you?
That boy's the Prince of Tennis.
SAKUNO: Really?
The Prince of Tennis?
RYUZAKI: Ryoma
Echizen, 12 years old.
He breezed through the
United States Juniors
with incredible ease.
He won four times in a row.
The kid's the real deal.
SAKUNO: Four times in a row?
RYUZAKI: Yep.
He's the complete package.
SASABE'S FRIEND: Love, 40.
RYUZAKI: He's the sound
of my best student.
The family's been
away for a long time.
They only got back
a little while ago.
Ryoma is still an unknown here.
But when I heard he was going
to enter this tournament,
I told him if he
really had talent,
he should enter the
boys' fourteens.
But get this.
Ryoma said if he
was going to play,
he wanted to play in the
16-year-old division.
I couldn't believe
what I was hearing.
A real good competitor,
just like his dad.
-Game to Echizen.
-I totally don't believe this.
Sasabe dropped his service game.
-You're playing in
the finals, right?
Then let's get this over with.
-Just calm down.
How good could this
kid's serve be?
I bet he can't crack
100 miles per hour.
I'll break back in no time.
SASABE'S FRIEND:
Echizen to serve.
[sasabe grumbles]
SASABE'S FRIEND: 15, love.
-Man, that kid's really good.
-It's true.
He is good.
And he's got a tough serve.
But I've got a big edge.
And that's our
difference in height.
With my height and my wing
span, if I come to the net,
there's no place that
trick can hit it.
SASABE'S FRIEND: 15, all.
-Hey, what's the matter, kid?
What happened to all
that power of yours, huh?
SASABE'S FRIEND: 30, 40.
[sakuno whimpers]
-If I just come to the
net, it's all over.
SASABE'S FRIEND: Deuce.
-That's the way to
do it, all right.
If you can hit a top-spin lob
over your opponent's head,
there's just about nothing
he can do about it.
-Wow, Sasabe is--
-About to go down
to a seventh grader.
Can you believe it?
-This is bad.
I'm going to be a
total laughingstock.
-Oh, no.
Another lob.
I can't get it.
Go out, go out!
-Grandma, he did it again.
SASABE: Out.
-Huh?
-Too bad, kid.
It was just a little bit
long, just barely out.
-What?
He's crazy.
That ball was clearly in.
-Forget about it, we're not
allowed to say anything.
The boys just have to
work it out themselves.
-Huh?
Does that mean--
-It's all them.
It's the job of the
players to make fair line
calls themselves.
He can call it any
way he wants to.
SASABE'S FRIEND:
Advantage, Sasabe.
-Ripped that one.
He's starting to hit short.
SASABE'S FRIEND: Sasabe's
charging the net.
-Say your prayers, punk!
Yah!
-Idiot.
As long as I'm making
the calls, all your lobs
are going to be out.
Wha?
-What?
That was--
-Amazing.
He sliced the lob and
dropped it at the line.
-So, going to call
that ball out?
[sasabe growls]
SASABE'S FRIEND:
Game to Echizen.
[sasabe gasping]
-I can't reach it, shoot!
Why, you stupid brat!
Oops, sorry.
The racket just
slipped out my hand.
[dripping]
[sakuno gasps]
-Ryoma, are you all right?
-Don't step on court
during a match.
-But, but--
-You're having problems
with your grip?
You still have a ways to go.
[sasabe gasps]
-15, love.
-Not that.
Not the kicker.
-That's incredible.
His serve just jumped
up the other way.
-Ow!
-Did you see that?
That scrawny little kid just
totally smoked the ball.
-30, love.
[sasabe grunts]
RYOMA: 40, love.
This is it.
[sasabe whimpers]
-Stop!
-Bonehead.
SASABE'S FRIEND: Game
and set to Echizen.
-Sakuno, Ryoma won the game.
-He did it.
Ryoma actually won.
-No way.
I let that punk kid win.
Give me one more
set, and I'll win.
-Don't be a sore loser, man.
Just admit the kid beat
you, fair and square.
-That's OK.
I don't mind playing again.
-Give it up, already.
Don't you get it?
No matter how many
times you play him,
you're not going to
beat Ryoma Echizen.
-Why shouldn't I?
RYUZAKI: Because
he's left-handed.
-Huh?
-Oh, wow.
[sasabe whimpers]
-I quit, I quit!
RYUZAKI: Ryoma Echizen
has entered the stadium.
I can't wait to see
what this kid's got.
Ryoma's going to rock
the tennis world.
[rock music playing]
-Hi, I'm Takeshi Momoshiro,
a second-year player
with the Seigaku tennis team.
Call me Momo.
No one's listening, right?
-Nope.
-By the way, I hear
there's a hot new kid
on the court, Ryoma Echizen.
When he steps up, you've
got to be on your toes.
Next on Prince of
Tennis, "Samurai Junior."
You've got to watch.
You've just got to.