TAKASHI (VOICEOVER): We're the
ones who are going to win this.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): Man, their
willpower is intimidating.
This match will
determine the outcome
of the whole tournament.
This ends now.
[theme music]
-Hey, don't we play Mizuno
Fuji Junior High after lunch?
-That's right.
-Tezuka and Fuji.
So you checking out
the competition, huh?
Figured out anything
I should now?
By the way, Tezuka, I hear you
didn't play against Kyokurin.
Is there some problem you're
not telling anybody about?
-Let's go, Fuji.
-Hang on.
Let's see that arm.
Maybe there's an injury.
-Let go.
(VOICEOVER): He
didn't even flinch.
I'll get to the bottom of this
if it's the last thing I do.
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Fudomine.
-No.
It's impossible.
What a nightmare.
They were never this good.
-What?
Kakinoki lost?
No way.
They were candidates
for the metropolitans.
-But I'm telling
you it's true, Momo.
It's even there on
the match schedule.
-Now that you mention it, I
wonder where Ryoma is too.
-Ah.
But that's not what
I was thinking.
-Oh, it's OK.
I know.
-So who do we get to
play in the finals?
-Fudomine Junior High.
-They're not even seeded.
-Fudomine?.
If I'm not mistaken, they
weren't allowed in the matches
last year.
-Huh?
-Now it makes sense.
That's why they were
turned away last year.
You've been a big help to me.
It's a great
comfort to know I've
got at least one friend
at the newspaper.
Thanks again.
Goodbye.
INOUE (VOICEOVER):
Refused entry to matches.
Team captain, Kippei Tachibana,
at that time an eighth grader,
due to an incident of violence.
Hm.
Violence, huh?
-Hey there.
I just Fudomine play.
They have a completely
different team from last year.
With the exception
of Captain Tachibana,
their regular team is made
up of only eighth graders.
The key is their team
captain, Kippei Tachibana,
a ninth grader.
He's also acting as their coach.
And a completely
unknown eighth grader
was able to beat Kuki
from Kakinoki 6-2.
-I guess it's safe to
say it's not a given
that we'll win this tournament.
-Seigaku's got nothing to worry
about from these new kids.
I tell you, Seigaku's gonna win.
-Um, Horio?
-Come on, I'm on
a roll right now.
There's just no way on
earth Seigaku's going
to lose to those unseeded kids.
No way.
-Hey, Horio.
-What is it?
Can't you see I-- oh.
Fu-- Fudomine.
-You're Tezuka from
Seigaku, right?
-That's correct.
-I'm Tachibana, the
Fudomine captain.
Let's have a good match.
-Good luck.
-Oh, man.
What a surprise.
I thought we were really
in for it with those guys.
-They sure look tough.
-What's wrong with you, Horio?
-My knees went
and buckled on me.
-That guy in the back
keeps bouncing that ball
without even looking.
Those Fudomine guys are amazing.
-That [inaudible],
he's just trying
to stir up trouble again.
-I guess after playing
doubles and then sitting out,
the stress is beginning
to get to him.
[laughter]
TACHIBANA (VOICEOVER):
A seventh grader, huh?
-Come on, let's go.
-You still have a ways to go.
-This should be fun, huh Shinji?
-Yeah.
-OK, listen up.
The team you're meeting
in the finals is Fudomine.
They're not like any
team you've met so far.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Here's the lineup.
Number two doubles
is Fuji and Kawamura.
Number one doubles,
Oishi and Kikumaru.
Number three singles is Kaidoh.
Don't lose this one.
Number two singles is Ryoma.
Go wild, kid.
And number one singles
will be Tezuka.
-Ryoma is finally
debuting in singles.
-Hey, way to go, Ryoma.
-The finals will be between
Seigaku and Fudomine.
Seigaku's got this
one in the bag.
-Yeah, it's a number one seed
against an unseeded team.
ANNOUNCER: This is
a one set match.
Sakurai of Fudomine to serve.
-It's finally starting.
-Come on, you're a newsman.
Surely you can find that out.
-Oh, it's Mr. Inoue.
Wonder if he's going to
watch the finals matches.
-I won't take up too
much of your time.
I'd just like to ask you
a few questions concerning
your previous work as adviser
to the Fudomine tennis team,
specifically about
the day you quit.
Hello?
No comment, eh?
Thanks so very much.
Bye.
-Are you a reporter
for a tennis magazine?
-Well, yes, I am.
How could you tell?
-I heard you say
on your cell phone
that you were Mr. Inoue of the
monthly magazine "Tennis Pro."
-Yeah.
-Are you investigating
the Fudomine team?
-Huh?
Do you know anything about them?
-I know they're a
really strong team.
Fudomine's like this soda.
Doesn't look like much from
the outside, but on the inside,
there's this huge
power just waiting
to surprise those who
aren't expecting it.
They are truly an amazing team.
-Huh?
W-- w-- wait.
At Least tell me your name.
-An.
Uh, about that bottle.
I wouldn't open
it up right away.
-Huh?
-Look out.
Now I'm on fire.
-What a return.
-[inaudible].
ANNOUNCER: 30-15.
-Oh-- oh brother.
-They're unseeded.
How could they turn
out to be so good?
-They're experts
of heavy top spin.
-They're much stronger
than I expected.
-Fuji is playing in
number two doubles.
That's not quite what you
figured on, is it, captain?
-No.
I thought he'd go up against
Shinji in number two singles.
-Don't worry about it.
He looks like he's
having fun against them.
-You're probably right.
-Hm?
-Isn't that their team captain?
What's he think
he's doing leaving
in the middle of a match?
-It's quite a surprise.
-He must be pretty
confident if he
doesn't think he needs to
stay and watch the outcome.
-We took them too
lightly, didn't we?
ANNOUNCER: Service eighth.
40-15.
-Huh?
-Want some?
-No.
Thanks for offering.
-You're Kippei Tachibana
from Fudomine, right?
Your team is like
this bottle of soda.
A young lady said that
when she gave this to me.
I wonder what she meant.
It could be profound.
Don't you think so?
-What do you want?
-Please, there's no reason
to get your guard up.
It's OK.
I'm a reporter, but I don't
work for a scandal rag.
I do my reporting for
a tennis magazine.
There's something
I'd like to ask you.
It's for personal reasons.
Is that OK?
Uh, I'd like you to tell me
about the violent incident
last year.
-Got it.
-What a terrific rally.
-Those guys from Fudomine
are really persistent.
-I can't stand to watch if our
guys are going to lose to them.
-Fuji and Kawamura
are being pushed back.
-Fudomine keeps
returning every shot.
I really hate those
type of players.
-It's a battle of patience.
The team that can throw
the other side off balance
will be the team that wins.
-I promise you, I
won't ever write about.
-Then why ask me?
-To know the secret of
your team's strength.
Like I said, I report
for a tennis magazine.
I don't write about
anything but tennis.
It's not just my job,
it's my whole life.
The girl who gave me this
bottle also gave me a riddle.
Like this bottle, your team
hides amazing strength inside.
She said Fudomine was
different than they looked.
I've been wondering, could
last year's violent incident
have something to do with your
school's strength at tennis?
I can't help but
feeling that it does.
Am I wrong?
I know you punched
out your advisor.
That's what caused
you to be ejected
from the district matches.
That's about all I know
about the incident.
I don't care that you hit him.
I just want to know why.
-Mr. Inoue.
-Hm?
-If you promise me you
won't write about it,
I'll tell you what happened.
-Done.
-So you new kids want
to play matches, huh?
Now, when did I ever promise
you anything like that?
-You said if we played upper
class teammates and won,
we'd be on the regular team.
-And when did I say that?
You're still just
seventh graders.
You should be happy just
picking up tennis balls.
-Huh?
-Yeah?
And what do you want?
-Kippei Tachibana.
I've just transferred
to this school.
I'm in the eighth grade.
-Hey, are you all right?
-Don't got tattling
to the adviser.
You hear?
And don't rebel
against upperclassmen.
Respect the ranks.
TACHIBANA (VOICEOVER):
It was unforgivable.
With an advisor who wouldn't
do anything and bullying older
teammates with no
skills but big heads,
the poor seventh graders who
only wanted to play tennis
were treated horribly.
-Pick up those balls.
Go on.
Quit being so lazy.
That's not the spirit.
Get running.
20 times around the field.
Move it.
-You're the ones who
are going to be running.
-What did you say?
Watch yourself, Tachibana.
-You've got nerve
talking like that.
-Play a match against
me if you're not afraid.
And if I win, you get to run
20 times around the field,
or at least until you drop.
-That's stupid.
-Who'd want to do that?
-Forget it.
I'm out of here.
-Anyone think they're
stronger than me?
Step up.
-What's that you say?
All the seventh
graders are boycotting?
They're making a new team?
-Yeah, and the one behind
the whole thing is Tachibana.
-Hey, Tachibana.
Last time, we cut
you a lot of slack,
but it seems like you just
don't want to learn, do you?
-You guys don't lay a
hand on any of them, OK?
-You brats are such a pain.
So this is the new team, huh?
Well, from now
until next spring,
you're going to spend your
time picking up tennis balls
and be happy about it.
After all, they
started the fight.
Right, guys?
[laughter]
-Tachibana, hold on a sec.
-You're a failure as an advisor.
-What the--
-I can't believe it.
And you were the one who
said not to touch them.
-Aw, shut up.
After all, you guys weren't
shy about getting into it.
Now, look sharp.
We're applying to
create a new team.
-You think they'll say OK?
-We'll hang in
there until they do.
We're shooting for nationals.
-Nationals,
nationals, nationals.
-So that's the story.
That worthless advisor
and all the upperclassmen
left the tennis team soon after.
-I understand.
That incident is the root cause
of your strength as a team.
Thank you for telling
me all about it.
-You're wrong.
What happened was just an
opportunity, and we took it.
We don't care about
events of the past.
We're just not going to lose to
anybody, no matter who it is.
That's all there is to it.
-That was quite a smash.
-I wouldn't say that.
-Really?
-It's about time for Seigaku
to begin their counterattack.
Excuse me.
INOUE (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Fudomine.
-Hey, guys.
Their captain's just come back.
-His leaving was on purpose.
-Huh?
On purpose?
-Wait.
What do you mean?
-An excellent strategy.
During an important
match, the captain
makes a big show of
leaving the court,
causing a distraction which
puts more pressure on us
while reducing our
ability to focus.
TAKASHI (VOICEOVER): We're the
ones who are going to win this.
FUJI (VOICEOVER): Their
willpower is intimidating.
This match will
determine the outcome
of the entire tournament.
This ends now.
-It didn't even bounce.
-What was that?
It just skidded along the ground
until it went right past them.
-That's one of the
best counter shots
Fuji has in his arsenal,
the triple counter.
-The triple counter?
-He uses his opponent's
top spin on the ball
and adds even more spin
in the same direction
by means of a
heavy slice counter
shot that's almost
impossible to return.
He might be a problem,
this genius Shusuke Fuji.
-Mr. Inoue, where
have you been hiding?
-Is something the matter?
-This match up
Seigaku might not win.
[theme music]
FUJI (VOICEOVER): Hi.
I'm Shusuke Fuji.
Taka and I are playing Ishida
and Sakurai from Fudomine.
With my triple counter shot,
the match should be ours.
But Fudomine is coming back
with a devastating new weapon.
Are we in big trouble?
Hm.
We'd better watch
out for these guys.
Next up, "To Each
His Own Battle."
Taka, you amaze me.