-This can't be happening.
-There isn't a ball that you
can hit that I can't return,
young one.
-Ha!
Serves you right, kid.
You're not going up
against just anyone.
My dad was called the Golden
Retriever of Meguro
-Did he say golden?
-Retriever?
[theme music]
Your dad's
amazing, Kachiro.
And what a life.
Getting to work at a
great club like this.
-Aw, come on, guys.
It's nothing.
He's just the coach.
-Hey!
Wait up for us, guys.
Sorry we're late.
Did you wait long?
-Tomoka, What's that
you're carrying?
-The lunch I made.
-Lunch?
-You're not gonna eat all
that by yourself, are you?
-Are you kidding?
I brought enough for everyone.
There's a lot of
kids in my family,
so I'm used to doing this.
-So, Ryoma.
Practice as hard
as you can, then
eat lots and lots of this
food I lovingly made for you!
I worked really hard for a
whole week figuring out a menu,
and I know you're gonna like it.
It tastes good, ask my brothers.
-Who told them that we
were gonna come here?
-Don't know.
-I did.
It's more fun with
a big group, right?
-Ugh.
-Momo said he'd be
joining us later.
-What?
Momo's coming over here as well?
-And that's not all, either.
-Is there anyone
you didn't invite?
-Kachiro!
-Oh, hi, dad.
-I'm so glad you could all come.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
-So, you're Ryoma?
My son's told me all about you.
He says you're
really quite good.
-Well, uh--
-I want you all
to have fun today.
Follow me, and I'll
show you to the courts.
-I see.
How interesting.
-Uh, uncle.
-Huh?
Do you want something?
-You and those awful
magazines again.
Here.
Auntie wants you to get up
and take this right to Ryoma
without delay.
-Ah, get real.
Do I look like I'm
Ryoma's messenger boy?
-Auntie had
another message for you.
If you don't get this
lunch box to Ryoma by noon,
she's going to throw out
all of your girly magazines.
-What?
She wouldn't!
She couldn't do
something like that!
She really did throw
them out the last time.
I am so out of here!
-You kids can
use this court.
Yes!
It's great to be able to
play on such a cool court.
-But please don't interfere with
any of our other guests, OK?
Hey, Echizen.
Teach us that kick
serve, will you?
-No way.
-Hey, Ryoma!
Go for it!
-Excuse me, Coach Kato?
-Yes?
-I'm looking forward
to a good lesson today.
-Certainly, Mr. Sasabe.
Please wait for me
over by Court F.
-What do you mean?
Why can't we stay
here on Court A?
There's nothing wrong with it.
Why do we have to
walk all the way over
to Court F for the lesson?
We'll play right here.
That settles it.
Take that back to the locker.
See that you treat it with care.
Don't put it on the
floor or it'll get dirty.
-Who was that rude man?
He's one of our
regular customers.
He's very selfish
and unpleasant.
-We can move to
Court F if you want.
-No, I'll just give
him a piece of my mind.
-Hey, hurry it up, will you?
-What a meanie.
-Yeah, acts like
he's real tough.
-I don't think I
like him very much.
-Be right back.
-I was sure he was
gonna tell him off.
-I'm sorry.
Maybe it'd be better if
we all move to Court F.
-Don't worry about it.
-People are like that.
It's common.
-Hey, out of my way!
-That hurt!
Why don't you watch where
you're going, old man?
-Give me a break.
I'm in a hurry, kid.
So get out of my way, OK?
-Huh?
After banging into me?
No way.
-Get out of my way!
-Keep dreaming.
-Look here.
A young man like you shouldn't
be riding a bike anyway.
You should be training
your body and your mind.
-Listen, old man.
You're going to regret that.
You can't talk to me
like that and think
you're going to
get away with it.
Listen to what I'm saying!
-Shut up.
-Crazy old man.
-Move it.
Move it.
-I can watch Ryoma play all day.
-Echizen.
Oh.
Time for a break.
Oh man.
I can't take it.
I'm exhausted.
-You talk big, but
you sure lack stamina.
-You're right?
-You're so cool, Ryoma!
Hey, Sakuno, you're
always prompt,
but you were really late today.
How come?
-Huh?
There was no reason why.
I was just late.
-Hm.
Sounds fishy.
Oh, what's in the bag?
Let's take a look.
I wanna see it!
-Whoa.
Stop it.
Hey, don't look in there.
-I knew it.
Lunch for two.
I get it.
You were late because
you were making this.
Who's it for?
Ryoma?
-Oh, no.
It's, um--
-Come on.
You can tell me.
Horio?
Kachiro?
Katsuo?
-Hm?
-Hey, don't worry about it.
This means Ryoma's fan club's
gonna grow by one more person.
MR. SASABE: What?
You refuse to listen to me?
-Huh?
What was that?
-It was a voice.
It came from Court
A. Let's go see.
-That's enough.
We can't keep
doing this all day.
Enough of these warm ups.
We didn't come here just so
you could watch us exercise.
-But if you don't
warm up properly,
it could lead to pulled muscles,
or possibly even more serious
injuries.
-What?
He's gotta be kidding.
-Look here, we're grown men,
so don't lump us together
with those other weaklings.
-It's Mr. Sasabe and his gang.
-He thinks he owns the courts.
Someone should stop him.
-Coach Kato, I may not
look it, but I made it
to the Inter High championships.
Consider that when you
coach me, will you?
-Of course.
But I must warn you about
not warming up properly.
-Oh yeah?
You charge us such
high tuition fees,
but you're not gonna
teach us anything.
Forget the boring,
small stuff, coach.
We wanna learn how
to do dynamic things,
like putting top
spin on the ball.
Show us how the pros
do it, Coach Kato.
Show us the top spin.
-Uh--
-That old man didn't
come here to learn.
Listen to him.
He's just trying to cause
trouble for Coach Kato.
He's just a big old pest.
-You don't know how
to do it, do you?
I heard you didn't
turn pro because you
had some kind of injury,
but it was probably
because all you ever
could do was warm ups.
-That's a terrible thing to say.
-My son told me your son plays
on the Seigaku tennis team.
But knowing that
it's your son, he'll
probably spend three
years chasing balls.
It must be hard
having no talent.
I hear they're using a
seventh grader as a regular.
Seigaku sure has
fallen on hard times.
Ha.
-Wait a second, Ryoma.
-Mr. Sasabe, you can say
whatever you want about me,
but I won't allow you to
criticize my son or his school
in any way.
Do you understand that?
-Now, really, is that any way
to treat a paying customer?
I guess he can't take a joke.
-Hey, dad.
What's up?
What are you doing?
-Oh, well, we're
trying to learn tennis,
but this coach
refuses to teach us.
-Sounds like he's being
a real pain in the beck.
-Oh, I know him.
-Huh?
Are you sure?
-Wait a minute, Ryoma.
-Lose the coach, dad.
With your talent, you don't
need any lessons from anybody.
-Well, it's a sure
thing I'm a better
player than he'll ever be.
-Hey.
Have you learned how
to grip a racket?
How to grip it properly.
Do you know how?
-Huh?
-Someone you know?
-No, I've never seen
him before in my life.
-Hey you over there.
Do you wanna teach
me how to play?
-You want me to teach you
the fundamentals of the game?
-Dad, you better not
try and teach that kid.
-What are you saying?
That boy can't learn
anything from that coach,
so he's depending
on me to teach him.
All right, I'll teach
you how to play.
I'll show you the
beautiful techniques
that made me runner up
at the Inter High finals.
-I don't think this
is a good thing.
-Go easy on me.
-I wonder if uncle has
met up with Ryoma yet.
-Let me past, brat.
-Shut up, you lazy monk.
-Lazy monk?
I'm a worldly monk!
-Oh, yeah?
Well, you know what I think?
I think you're just
a plain old goofball.
Look at these abs.
Aren't they magnificent?
I'm practically
a regular Adonis.
-Why, you little twerp.
Look at this miraculous body!
WOMAN: Hello?
Excuse me?
-Hm?
-Please, let me through.
What are Momo and
Nanjiro doing here?
Hey, what's going on?
Oh, dear.
What's wrong?
I'm in a hurry.
Would you please
move out of the way?
-Look here, we're busy, woman.
So stay out of our way.
-What?
How dare you talk
to me that way.
It's downright harassment,
and highly insulting.
-This is between us men.
-So women we can
stay out of it!
-What?
How dare you.
That is discrimination
against women.
I demand that you take
that back right now!
-Shut up.
I don't care what you have
to say, so get lost.
-Forget this, let me through.
-No, let me through!
-Best of one set match.
Echizen's Service.
-Ryoma.
-Go, Ryoma!
Beat that terrible old guy!
-Hey. Better go easy on him
now, or he'll cry.
-Yeah, he' just just a kid.
Don't be afraid, kid.
Just give it all you got.
-You really believe
Ryoma can handle him?
-Just watch, Dad.
Ryoma can do amazing things.
-Right hand.
-There you go!
Those are good hit, kid.
Now see if you can do
it again even harder.
Don't hold back.
You've got to come
at me with all you got
if you want to play
this game as well as I do.
-I don't understand
why Ryoma didn't
use his kick serve on him.
-I think I know.
-Huh?
-He's using a very
intelligent strategy.
That's why he started off
using a regular serve.
No matter how good
a player he is,
he can't win without gathering
information about his opponent.
That's what he's doing
now, gathering information.
That Ryoma's really
something else.
-Of course, after all he
is a regular on Seigaku team.
-That's nothing for you
to be bragging about .
-He sent that ball
right in the corner!
-Don't take me lightly!
Not bad.
-This world's not that easy.
Love, 15, kid.
-All right! Way to go Dad.
Tomo, did you see that?
Oh, nevermind, he was
just lucky with that shot.
The old man is going to be
out of breath soon enough.
-Don't worry about
anything, kid.
I'll keep training ya.
Now, serve!
-Yes!
I bet he won't be able
to return that ball.
-There, Love-30.
-What's going on with him?
- They call him the retriever.
The retriever?
-Hahaha
Ok, kid... let's see if you
can get past this test.
-You know what a golden
retriever is, right?
A retriever's a type
of dog used by hunters.
-Hunting dog?
-Yes.
Someone who can
catch up to any ball
and return it back on to
the court like a hunting dog
is called a retriever.
The great champion
Bjourn Borg was known
as the world's greatest
retriever.
-This can't be happening.
Oh, boy.
-He was the second place winner
in the inter-high championship
so he's not just
boasting.
Haha. There isn't a ball that
you can hit,
that I can't return, young one.
Ha. Serves you right kid.
You're not going up against
just anyone.
My dad was called the golden
retriever of Meguro.
Did he say golden?
-Retriever?
He's golden alright.
That gold tooth's sort
of blinding me.
Save comments like that until
after you win a point. Kid!
Oh Yeah?
He really is a retriever!
He's keeping up with all
the balls that are hit.
-There's something
strange about Ryoma.
-What?
-Ryoma has the serve.
He could use his
kick serve to ace it.
But for some reason,
he's just not using it.
I don't understand why?
-He's going to the net.
He's planning to end it.
-Ha.
You took my little bait.
Here it goes!
-Huh?
-That's a passing shot.
-That's it.
Retriever stays close to his
baseline returning every ball.
Then, when his opponent
approaches the net,
he fools them with
a passing shot.
-It's not like Ryoma to
drop is service game.
-Game count, one game to Love.
The Golden Retriever of
Meguro, AKA Sasabe, leads.
-Can't believe I was
so worried about this.
Come on, dad.
You can smash him!
-Guess it's about time now.
-Look at that.
Ryoma's perspiring.
-What's the matter with him?
Why doesn't he win?
COACH (VOICEOVER): So
that's what he's doing.
I get it.
-Here it comes.
Foolish little boy.
I'll make you feel the power.
RYOMA: Love-15.
[cheering]
-What's with this kid?
-Ryoma wasn't just analyzing
his opponent's game.
He was actually warming up while
he was playing against him.
Look at how he's sweating.
His engine is running
at full speed.
He was warming up while grasping
the Retriever's style of play.
Amazing.
-So that's why he didn't
use the kick serve.
-Man.
I guess practicing
with us doesn't
count when it comes
to warming him up.
MR. RETRIEVER
(VOICEOVER): I was too
relaxed because I thought
he was just a kid.
-Hey, mister.
You've been hugging the
baseline all this time
like you were scared.
-What?
-You should come to
the net more often.
-Shut up.
-Hey Mr. Retriever.
Seems to me you stay
behind the baseline
because you can't
take the front.
Isn't that right?
-Huh?
-Oh, no.
He figured it out.
-Oh no.
-Still got a ways to go.
Game to Echizen.
-Ow!
-Hey dad.
Are you all right?
-I pulled a muscle.
-You pulled a muscle because
you didn't warm up properly.
Maybe that's why you didn't
win at the Inter High level.
Father and son should
learn the basics again.
-Father and son?
-A-OK?
-No wonder you're a
Seigaku regular, Ryoma.
Thank you.
-Seigaku regular?
-Don't tell me he's the
freshman who made the team?
-We're out of here.
[laughter]
-Come on, come on.
Would you hurry up and
move your bicycle?
-Shut up, old man.
You move.
-You're the one
who's in the way!
-If I don't get past this,
all my treasures will be lost!
-Your treasures?
-Mm.
Delicious.
Mm.
This is great Tomoka
KACHIRO: Wow, you're
a terrific cook.
GIRL: Savor the flavors, OK?
KATSUO: It really is good.
-He's eating it.
I'm so glad.
-Um, Ryoma?
Um, um-- Um, how does it taste?
-You still have a ways to go.
[screaming]
-His backhand isn't there yet.
Hey, what happened to my lunch?
-Oh boy.
-That Ryoma.
-Ah huh.
He's sure got
tennis on the brain.
KACHIRO: Sure does.
-Oh!
Stupid Ryoma!
[theme music]
SAKUNO: Hi, everyone.
I'm Sakuno Ryuzaki.
Ryoma and Momo are going
at it at a burger shop.
I wonder what that's all about?
On top of that, he's going to
play a match against students
from another school.
Oh dear.
Next on "The Prince of Tennis."
Ryoma Versus Momoshiro.
Will Ryoma be all right?