-All right.
Guess what's coming.
-Snake shot.
ALL: Kaidoh, no!
[laugh]
-Huh?
[theme music]
[grunt]
ANNOUNCER: 15-love.
BOTH: Huh?
-Ugh.
-Aw.
He missed it.
-Kaidoh, why didn't you
use your snake shot?
-Shut up.
What about your
dropped shot, Momo?
Your right foot should be out.
You still haven't really
fixed it, have you?
-He didn't use his
snake shot, sure enough.
-Those guys have us
scouted real good.
They seem to know all our
strengths and weaknesses.
-Hmm.
Well, that's all right by me.
-Looks like they were
waiting for Kaidoh
to use his snake shot.
-Looks like it.
This match might be a
little tough for them.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER): Scouted us?
Big deal.
[grunts]
[laugh]
-That's mine, sure enough.
[grunt]
[laugh]
-What's the matter with you?
Are you afraid to
show me your snake?
-Shut up.
[grunt]
-He's scared, sure enough.
-Oh, this is a bad.
Kaidoh's snake shot has
been totally shut down.
-Yeah.
It looks like they
have their hands full
just returning every ball.
-It looks like they're really
feeling the pressure right now.
This really is not
going well at all.
-Try this one.
[grunt]
-Kaidoh, follow the ball.
-Don't order me around.
[grunt]
-Atsushi!
-Leave it to me.
[evil laugh]
[grunt]
-You guys are
stubborn, sure enough.
[grunt]
ALL: Cord ball, yes.
And it's over the net!
-There.
You see how good they are?
They're quick enough
to rush to the net.
-Sakuno, what exactly
does cord ball mean?
-It's a ball that clips the net
and lands in the other court.
But because it's uncertain
where, it's hard to get.
However, those two
are quite used to it
in tournament matches.
-Man, how long is this
round gonna continue?
-Ugh, it's so hot out.
[laughs]
-Shoot.
If not for Kaidoh, we would've
won this stupid match already.
[gasps]
-That's what I was
getting ready to tell you.
[grunt]
[sigh]
-Is this is a match or a fight?
-It's already been
over 40 minutes.
-Yeah.
They gotta be on the
verge of exhaustion.
And then there's this heat.
-Change courts.
[sigh]
-And how are you boys
holding up so far?
-Well, I gotta
tell you, those two
are really quite competitive.
But I'm having fun.
-I'll bet.
Looks like you're
breathing hard enough.
-You looking for a fight?
-Now come on, you two.
It's hot enough out here already
without all this senseless
bickering.
-Hey, I'm the one being cool.
-Yeah.
I wonder about that.
-What'd you say?
-Stop it this instant.
You both seem to have
lots of energy left.
Now, how about applying
it to the match?
-Yeah.
Haha.
I guess you're right about that.
Come to think of it,
I'm not that tired.
-Hmm.
-Whatever.
But when it comes to
technique and team play,
they've got you beat hands down.
Now, what do you
intend to do about it?
-We have stamina.
-And we have spirit.
BOTH: So we will win.
All right.
[sigh]
-Hmm.
If you keep up your pace,
you're gonna win this match.
You memorized the data
on those two, right?
Statistics, probabilities?
-Sure enough.
-Sure did.
-It's hopeless.
They're getting on each
other's nerves so bad,
and they're not even
playing at all in sync.
At this rate they'll end
up dragging each other down
to defeat.
-What can we do?
-Yo.
Our genius of a manager told
is all about the two of you.
He even simulated your
data and analyzed it.
And his conclusion
was that we are
supposed to win this match 6-2.
Sure enough.
Sure enough, he's been
right on the money.
You've only won two games.
Mizuki's scenarios
can be frightening
no matter whom we play.
The match goes exactly
as he analyzed it.
We know what the result
will be without playing
any further, sure enough.
Haha.
BOTH: Shut your mouth.
You talk too much, sure enough.
-Huh?
ALL: Wow.
They're in perfect sync.
-Hey, Rudolph, listen closely
to me and learn something.
There's no such thing
as a scenario in tennis.
We'll prove it to you.
-OK.
Now let's go do this.
Concentrate.
-Shut up.
I know what to do.
Don't order me around.
-I'm not giving orders.
I'm just pumping myself up.
ANNOUNCER: Time!
-Huh?
-OK.
But do it fast.
-I understand.
-I wonder what he's
doing that for.
-Ah, who knows?
-Hey you.
I'm warning you.
Don't try to influence
the outcome of this game.
-Oh, excuse me.
Your game is so exciting that
the lines have become blurred.
You want to make things easier
for the judges, don't you?
[frustrated sigh]
-Well, gee.
Thanks.
-I don't like the
timing of this timeout.
-He did a good job of
cooling off Momo's energy.
-Yeah, but I strongly suspect
he has something else in mind
he hopes to accomplish as well.
-Hey look.
-He's coming this way.
-What's he doing?
ALL: Huh?
-It's just too bad it
has to be this way.
Isn't it, Inui?
The rules say the only one
who can coach the players
in a match is the bench
coach on the court.
-The bench coach can be
either a registered player
or one of the team's advisers.
What exactly are you
getting at, Mizuki?
-Oh.
Well, if you have
made it is a regular,
you could have been the one
up there now coaching them
to victory.
Haha.
-Well, if you had
made it as a regular,
you could have been the one up
there coaching them to victory.
-What do you mean coaching them?
How can that be?
I have nothing to tell them.
MALE SPEAKER: You
there, if you're done,
return to your place.
-Ha.
That's just sour grapes talking.
And you know it, Inui.
-Who is that guy?
He's hateful.
-He sure it.
-It appears as though this
is all part of the scenario
as well.
ANNOUNCER: Game
count 5 games to 2.
St. Rudolph leads.
Yanagisawa of St.
Rudolph to serve.
-Sure enough!
[cheering]
-You can do it, Rudolph!
Come on!
You can do it!
[cheering]
-Kaidoh!
-Don't order me around.
-They're so persistent.
They keep hitting
to our weak sides.
-You guys sure are
really very tenacious.
[grunts]
-But we really love
games like this.
[grunts]
-Ha.
Right, Atsushi?
-It's great fun.
[grunt]
-What's fun about this?
MIZUKI (VOICEOIVER): Shutting
down Momoshiro's overhead smash
is huge.
It's almost impossible to make
that shot at the middle school
level.
And if he's allowed to hit
it, he'll take advantage.
We must not give him any lobs.
The only ball our two agile
players cannot return is
Kaidoh's snake.
However, I've spoken
to the school coach.
And the countermeasure against
the snake is fail safe.
Haha.
-Ah!
Another rally?
Why can't they finish it?
-It's obvious.
Rudolph has studied
Momoshiro and Kaidoh well.
That's why they keep aiming for
their weak spots on the court.
-Everything is that
manager's fault.
-To prevent Momoshiro from
using his overhead smash,
their placing
their shots deftly.
-And leaves our guys
with their hands
full just returning shots.
-This is really bad.
-They have to create openings
so they can make their comeback.
Ryoma, where are you going?
-I'm going to go buy some juice.
-This is no time
for buying juice.
Can't you see, Echizen,
that our team is in a pinch?
-In a pinch?
What do you mean by that?
-St. Rudolph has our
team thoroughly scouted,
and their data is
practically perfect.
-Then that practically spells
the end for St. Rudolph.
Those two won't play
according to their data.
[groan]
-Huh?
What the-- ah!
ANNOUNCER: Deuce again.
-Am I seeing things, or did the
speed of that shot increase?
[gasps]
-Not wild enough, huh?
Just not wild enough.
-Looks like they're
ready to play.
-Hey, Kaidoh.
Don't tell me you're going to
use that shot on this tennis
court.
Are you?
-Shut up, you.
-Listen to me.
-Can't you see those
two react the minute
you take the stance
for the snake?
And by the looks of it,
they've practiced quite a bit.
Aren't you nervous that they
can return the snake shot?
-It's not just a matter
of hitting it, stupid.
-Oh, are they fighting again?
-Haven't you noticed, those two
haven't made any eye contact
during the entire
course of this match.
-What are you two mumbling
about, sure enough?
-Why don't you mind your
own business and shut up?
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER): I can
do whatever I want, huh?
-Hmm.
-Oh man.
It looks like
Kaidoh is going to--
-Kaidoh isn't even good
at receiving serves,
but yet he's the
one in position.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER):
Curse all of them.
-It's begun.
-Kaidoh is finally
ready to play at last.
Sorry, Mizuki, but our guys hate
to receive any kind of advice
during a match.
[hiss]
-Haha.
It's finally coming.
Time to show off what we've been
practicing for, sure enough.
[grunt]
-Don't hold back, Kaidoh.
Smash it if you can!
-Yeah!
Momoshiro's charging
straight for the net!
-The court is wide open.
-FANS: Get it, Kaidoh!
-It seems Momoshiro opened
up the left court on purpose
to lure the ball there.
-Go Kaidoh!
-He can do it.
He'll use the snake.
-Yes.
By all means, go for it.
[laughing]
-But wait.
That's not--
-He's not going to
use the snake shot.
[gasp]
[sigh]
[hiss]
-Oh.
That scared me.
Oh my.
Advantage to the receiver.
-ALL: All right!
Kaidoh's boomerang snake!
-Those guys are amazing.
-Whoa!
-That was amazing!
-What was that shot!
[spectators talking]
-Hey, that wasn't
in the data report.
That was no snake.
I have my doubt that that
was even an admissible
shot, sure enough.
-What is happening here?
-At this rate we can win!
We can win!
Yeah!
-All right.
They're gonna make a comeback!
BOTH: Go to it, Kaidoh and Momo!
BOTH: That's great!
That's great!
-We've still got a ways to go.
-Huh?
Hey, it looks like Ryoma's back.
-You haven't perfected
that shot, have you?
-Huh?
Ugh.
-If this were singles, that
ball would have been out.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER): Huh.
Huh.
If it stays within the
singles boundaries,
then it's 100% good.
-Now I understand
why it was decided
that Kaidoh ought to play in
a doubles match this time.
-Well, yes.
But there's another
thing to consider.
Some watch a play like
that and get pumped.
-I don't know about that.
Just because he sees
his rival's super shot,
there's no reason to think that.
Momo's not that naive.
-Don't even think
I'll ever lose to him.
-Momoshiro is that naive.
-I see what you mean.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
That round the pole
shot that Kaidoh used in the
district matches, that was just
an accidental shot
because his foot slipped.
It was a onetime shot.
-A boomerang snake, huh?
-Who gave it a ridiculous
name like that anyway?
-It doesn't matter.
In any case, that
boomerang snake
is just an extension
of his snake shot.
I'm sure of it.
-Mizuki drummed the strategy for
the snake shot into our heads.
I know we can counter
it, sure enough.
-All right.
I'm finally beginning to
see some passion out there
on the court.
[heavy breathing]
-A long match in
this kind of heat.
Both sides have little stamina
left in them right now.
But our boys mustn't
lose willpower.
-It's the boomerang snake.
-Sure enough.
[grunt]
-Huh?
-It's a snake shot.
-Looks like St. Rudolph--
-It's a lob.
---was expecting
a boomerang snake.
-Now's your chance, guys.
-A lob?
How many times did I
tell them not to hit one?
-Ahh!
-Look how high Momoshiro gets!
-Whoa!
-Momo's timing
couldn't be better.
-Ahh!
Yeah!
There!
[gasps]
-What the--
SPECTATOR: I've never
seen anything like it.
SPECTATOR: Seigaku is amazing.
ANNOUNCER: Game to Seigaku.
5 games to 3.
ALL: That's it!
Momo's overhead smash wins it!
-That wasn't just
an overhead smash.
He used the added momentum
of rushing forward
when he hit the overhead.
Because of that, he was able
to double the normal force
that his usual overhead
jump generates.
I've never seen a dunk smash as
awesomely powerful as that one.
ALL: Oh.
Momo is totally awesome!
-I can't believe it!
We were distracted by Kaidoh's
boomerang snake, sure enough.
I'm so mad.
We were asking for it.
Sure enough, we allowed
them to play their game.
-But his power.
-Huh?
-It increased.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
What happened?
Their skill level has gone up.
Their power at the
district matches
doesn't compare to
their power now.
Those two, they're getting
better as the matches progress.
[groan]
[hiss]
-It's just not wild enough.
Just not wild enough.
-Hello, I'm Assistant
Captain Shuichiro Oishi.
St. Rudolph's Akazawa and
Kaneda are formidable opponents.
They focus their
attack on Eiji, hoping
to wear him down
mentally and physically.
He's feeling the pressure.
But listen, Rudolphs,
this is doubles.
We'll show you why we're
called the Golden Pair.
Next on "Prince of
Tennis," the moon volley.
All right, Eiji.
Now, let's return that ball.