-Tezuka and Fuji.
So, you checking out
the competition, huh?
Figured out anything
I should know?
By the way, I hear you
didn't play against Gyokurin.
Is there some problem you're
not telling anybody about?
-Let's go, Fuji.
-Hang on!
Let me see that arm.
Maybe there's an injury?
-Let go.
[growling]
-He didn't even flinch!
I'll get to the bottom of this
if it's the last thing I do.
[theme music]
-This is going to
be very interesting.
-I didn't realize you two belong
to the illustrious Seigaku.
It comes as a shock to me.
-That's for sure.
We must be very lucky.
-Yeah.
What a big break for us.
If this were singles, no doubt
you'd have the advantage.
-Probably.
-Why, you--
-On the other hand, it
usually proves a lot more fun
to be able to beat your
opponents at their own game.
-Is that why--
---you've teamed up against us?
-I'm so very relieved.
This has worked out
just like we planned.
[grunt]
-Look, he fluffed the serve!
-I'll say he did!
-Now's your big chance!
Put it away!
-That was deliberate.
-Hmm.
Being great at singles
doesn't necessarily
make you a doubles player.
-It's not just the strongest
who win in doubles.
-Wow, a double poach!
-With both of them
at the net, there's
no place left for
them to hit the ball!
[grunt]
ANNOUNCER: 30 all.
-In doubles, working together
is the key to winning the game.
-Come on.
Let's do it.
-They've evened up the score.
Against Seigaku.
-Seems like they're trying
every trick in the book on us.
Even that fluff
serve had a purpose.
-Hmm.
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Giyokuren. operation
-This is almost too easy.
-Oh.
-Uh, Momo, I think
you took a ball that
should have been mine.
-No, the player in front
takes any ball he can.
-If you can't put it away,
you shouldn't try to hit it.
-What's that?
You've got a complaint?
-Grrr!
ANNOUNCER: Seigaku!
Warning!
-Oh, no.
They're arguing with each other.
-This isn't going well.
-Inui, is there any
chance that Ryoma and Momo
can turn the match around?
-Against a polished team
like Izumi and Fukawa,
only a coordinated
team can triumph.
So unfortunately, right
now, I'd say, not a chance.
ANNOUNCER: Game to Gyokurin.
Change sides.
-Oh, boys.
What was that about?
-But Coach, I'm not
used to playing doubles.
Can't you see those
guys have our number
and they're killing us?
-It's not our opponents
who are beating us.
Unfortunately, I think
we're beating ourselves.
-You really think so?
-You saw it.
They got you all confused, Momo.
-If you're trying to say it's
all my fault, I don't think so.
Look, punk, you're the one
who's hogging all the balls.
You're nothing but
a rookie ball hog.
-You were going for balls on
my side of the court, jerk.
-Not me.
You are so wrong.
-Stop it, you two.
Enough.
[laughter]
-A pair of hotheads.
-Yeah, so true.
COACH (VOICEOVER) Hmm.
You really think that
kind of trash talk
will affect my players?
Ha.
Huh?
-Grr.
-You're falling for it!
(VOICEOVER) Those two
just can't get it together
as a doubles team.
Too bad.
-Oh.
Kazuka, I think we
might have blown it.
-You're right.
-You can still do this.
Get tough, guys.
Come on.
You can do it.
[laughter]
(VOICEOVER) I've
just about had it.
Take this!
ANNOUNCER: Fault!
-Haha.
Sorry.
-It's OK.
Just shake it off.
-Oh, no.
What a mess.
-They're no good
playing together.
Not at all.
-They're self-destructing.
-Too bad.
[grunt]
(VOICEOVER) I got it.
-Now, that was cool.
-Cool for us.
ANNOUNCER: Love 15.
-Grrr.
[laughter]
-Oh, Ryoma.
-They're distracted now.
They're not concentrating
on the match.
-They've got to
pull it together.
-I guess this isn't our
dream team after all.
[giggle]
-Oh.
-Huh?
-Great minds think alike.
You were thinking the same
thing I was, weren't you?
-Looks that way, huh?
Well, I suppose we shouldn't
be fighting for balls, huh?
-I'll get everything on
this side of the line
and you get the rest.
That ought to work.
-Sounds like a plan.
-And don't even think about
coming on my side of the line.
-Not even if you begged me.
Ha!
-I can't believe they're
going to split the court!
-Now he's starting to
act like our Ryoma!
-Yeah!
-That's just crazy.
-What are they up to?
They act like they're
just goofing around.
-Ready, Echizen?
-Let's go.
[grunt]
-I'm not going to
play your game.
-Now I can defend my ground.
-Got it, got it.
-Mine.
-I think I just found a hole.
Right down the middle!
-That's just about how our
boys are supposed to look.
-You're so right.
[grunting]
ANNOUNCER: Game to Seigaku.
-Nice shot.
-Yeah!
-Oh, yeah!
-But what happened?
How come now they're
so much better?
-Huh?
-It's simple.
-Hmm?
-They both decided to
play singles again.
-Huh?
Singles?
-You see, if they're
both covering
the same half of the court,
they leave lots of court open.
Each one only needs to
cover one half the court.
So Momo and Echizen
split the court and each
played their singles game
on his half of the court.
That way, they're
free from worrying
about each other's
positions, and they
can concentrate on winning.
-Brilliant.
-It's probably not
the best way to play,
but I think Momo and Echizen
can definitely make it work.
(VOICEOVER) OK.
We just got a little
careless, that's all.
They're not going to
beat us just because they
drew a line across the court.
Huh?
OK.
We'll both rush the net.
[laughter]
-Look at that formation.
Double poach!
-Let's break these guys, now.
-When we're both at
net, no one can stop us.
Haha.
-My ball.
-This game is way too easy.
-Ah.
You're ball!
-Huh?
Echizen, you know
it's on your side.
-Don't worry, I'm all over it.
-You can't be serious.
They're going to try to play
singles against the two of us?
Hey!
Izumi!
-Yeah, leave it to me.
[grunting]
-And there's Momo's
overhead smash shot!
[gasps]
-Ah!
[loud grunts]
-Oh, yeah.
-It's good.
-It's not just good.
It's fantastic.
-I just knew those two
would snap out of it.
Their opponents must be worried.
There's no doubt the boys
could dominate from here on in.
-Yeah!
-That team sure is
running scared now!
-Yeah!
-Did you hear?
Gyokurin's actually holding
their own against Seigaku.
-I was sure that
this year's final
was going to be Kakinoke
against Seigaku,
but then again,
maybe I was wrong.
-You got that one right.
Haha.
It's going to be Kakinoke
versus Seigaku after all.
You can bet on it.
Ha.
-Who was that guy?
-Huh?
-You mean you don't know?
Kuki's some kind of legend.
He's the number one player
on the Kakinoke team.
-Double poach.
-That is no way to play
a doubles tennis match.
We can't let them do this.
-Let her rip.
(VOICEOVER) I can't believe it.
They're returning every ball,
no matter where we hit it.
-All right!
-Seigaku!
-Man, what is with these guys?
It's like they're completely
different players now.
Izumi, let it go.
It's heading out of
the court for sure.
-Yeah, all right.
-Guess again, buddy.
It's going in.
[gasps]
-Hey.
-Huh?
-I'm starting to like doubles.
How about you guys?
-You guys aren't even
playing a real doubles match.
-Come on, come on.
Let's do this.
-Let's do it, Momo.
(VOICEOVER) Man.
No matter which way I
hit, they get to it.
Which side to go to?
Which side?
I got it!
-Smack down the middle.
That's exactly
where I got to go!
-Hey, what are you doing?
Ah!
[gasping]
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Seigaku.
-And there's the match.
Our guys came through!
-That's great!
Ryoma did it!
[cheering]
-Hey, dude.
We totally won.
-Playing doubles at that.
-Those two actually
won the match.
-And they did it by only playing
doubles at the center line.
-You guys are really amazing.
-It's like I told you before.
We have a quick learning curve.
-Man, and you just don't
stop boasting, either.
-If you feel like
playing doubles again,
come on out to the park
and we'll play sometime.
-So, pal, you want to play?
-Sure.
Why not?
-Say.
I wonder where Shiba
ran away to this time.
[groaning]
-Who cares if you won?
How dare you play so badly?
Think how dumb you two
idiots made the school look.
-Look at that
Seigaku doubles team.
They won their match, and
now they're being punished.
[laughter]
-You know what?
I've had it with doubles.
-Yeah, me too.
[grunting]
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Seigaku.
Six games to love.
-Ha.
They're really
Seigaku's golden pair.
-We wouldn't want you
to get it into your head
that we play like those two.
-No sweat.
No sweat.
We'll give you the doubles.
But we'll win it in singles.
-Yeah.
Trash them in six games.
-Right.
-I don't want to play.
-Come on.
Do it for the team.
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Seigaku.
Six games to love.
-That's it.
I can still salvage one match.
-Hmm.
-Takashi.
Stay loose.
-Huh?
-All right.
That guy looks beatable.
-N-- nice to play you.
(VOICEOVER) So, I guess they're
not all tough guys at Seigaku.
Yeah.
This should be easy.
-Hey, Taka.
I think you need this.
Here!
Your racket.
-Oh, I'm sorry, Oishi.
[laughter]
(VOICEOVER) I can't believe it.
What a loser.
Forgetting his own racket.
Ha-- Huh?
-Come on, Taka!
All right!
I'm burning!
On fire!
-Eh--
-One, two, three!
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Seigaku.
Game and match to Seigaku.
Doubles, 2-0.
Singles, 3-0.
Seigaku wins all courts, 5 to 0.
Everyone bow.
-Thank you.
-Seigaku is so strong.
Pretty impressive.
They swept every game.
-What do you think's
their problem?
-They both got suspended.
Ryoma's out for the next game.
Moma's out the next.
-Hey.
No wonder they're sulking.
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Kakanoki.
-You know, you're a
really good player.
I was just a little
stronger today, that's all.
(VOICEOVER) There it is.
Kuki's famous line.
He practices tennis
long and hard
against local high school
teams, and it shows.
It's paid off for him.
Now he's in top form.
Hmm.
-Don't we play Mizuno Fuchi
Junior High after lunch?
-That's right.
-Tezuka and Fuji.
So, you checking out
the competition, huh?
Figure out anything
I should know?
By the way, I hear you
didn't play against Gyokurin.
Is there some problem you're
not telling anybody about?
-Let's go, Fuji.
-Hang on!
Let me see that arm.
Maybe there's an injury?
-Let go.
-Grr.
(VOICEOVER) He
didn't even flinch.
I'll get to the bottom of this
if it's the last thing I do.
-Wow, did you see that?
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Fudomine.
-Yeah!
-Impossible.
Man, what a nightmare.
They weren't this good.
-What a strange
day this has been.
The number two seed, Kakinoke,
was upset by complete unknowns.
Fudomine.
[theme music]
-Hello.
I'm Inowe.
I write for a monthly
pro tennis magazine.
Wow.
This year's district tournament
had quite a few surprises.
A mysterious dark horse team,
school, Fudomine Junior High,
came out of nowhere to
beat the number-two seed.
I wonder what's the
secret to their power.
Boy, my writer's curiosity
sure has been aroused.
Next on the Prince of Tennis.
The Triple Counter.
And don't forget to
check out Seigaku, too.