OISHI (VOICEOVER): Curses.
BOYS: A jumping smash.
-It's over, Oishi.
-Gotta hurry.
-Here we go.
GIRL IN CROWD: Kikumaru.
Kikumaru.
-Hey there.
-I can't believe he recovered.
It's too bad.
I thought that for
sure they'd have
to give up a game over this.
-I wasn't sure you'd be
able to help me in time.
All right, now, time
to finish this match.
[theme music]
-Gotcha.
Right here.
-How can that guy
still run so quickly?
-Wow, Seigaku's golden
pair is the coolest.
-Yeah, they're opossum
attack's a winner.
-They're sure putting
everything out there all right.
-Can't guess the
outcome at this point.
-Wow, they are good.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Kikumaru hardly moved at all
during the two games,
and Oishi covered for him
so that he could
get his second wind.
But it was their match point.
Pretty reckless.
-I'll put it away.
-Too bad, so sad.
See ya.
JUDGE: 40-30.
-That's just too good.
-Wow, Kikumaru's
totally awesome.
-Did you guys see how
he moved out there?
-It was so incredible.
-Go team.
Kikumaru's the best.
-Well, he certainly is
photogenic, that's for sure.
-Oishi pretty amazing too.
They fooled everybody.
Not least of all that
cocky doubles team from St.
Rudolph's.
I guess they proved they
really are the golden pair.
They must really
trust each other
to be able to play like that.
-We've got them on
the ropes, Eiji.
Now, it's time to
finish them off.
-Yeah, I'm with you, Oishi.
Ew, it's hot.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER): Humph.
KANEDA (VOICEOVER): It's
still our match point.
All we need is one
more ball and we win.
JUDGE: Fault.
Double fault.
Deuce.
-What incredible luck.
-Two more points
and it's evened out.
-Sorry, I don't know what's up.
-Don't freak out, pal, we
are still winning this thing.
-You're right.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER): What
are those guys doing?
They're so close to a win.
-Man, it's got to be
tough for their players.
-You bet.
-Psychologically speaking,
it's the hardest thing
in the world to lose
your lead like that.
You think you've got it won,
and then it slips away from you.
-Got it.
-There he goes again.
BOYS: Diving volley.
JUDGE: Advantage, receiver.
AKAZAWA (VOICEOVER): I can't
read their moves at all.
Their shot selection
is so weird.
It's hard to figure
out what to do.
KANEDA (VOICEOVER): What power.
Seigaku has unbelievable talent.
SUMIRE (VOIEOVER): I think
they're getting flustered.
They're messed up
by Seigaku's pace.
At this rate, it's
a war of wills.
KANEDA (VOICEOVER): Not good.
We're letting them set the pace.
-Move out of the way!
-Your ball.
-The blur shot.
AKAZAWA (VOICEOVER):
His eyes are closed.
-All right.
BOYS: All right,
Oishi's moon volley.
-Better back up 'cuz
it's coming right at ya.
-OK.
AKAZAWA (VOICEOVER): You can't
fool us with the same trick.
-It's a drop--
-Volley.
JUDGE: Game to Seigaku.
Six games, all.
-Yes.
-Nice trap there.
-Yep.
The noise his racket made
just before the volley?
I'm absolutely sure that it
didn't mean anything at all.
BOY 1: He really did it.
Good job, Oishi.
BOY 2: They finally caught up.
-Oishi is my hero.
-Well, Eiji, we are on our way.
-Oh yeah.
-This is good.
They're in a tiebreaker.
-This is so exciting.
-Man!
-They're working awfully
hard for this comeback.
JUDGE: 12 point tiebreaker.
Seigaku's Oishi to serve.
-You don't happen to know
about tiebreaks, do you?
-I wish.
-I'll be happy to explain
them to you, girls.
They consist of 12 points and
whoever gets to 7 points first,
wins it all.
But if the score
is 6-6, they keep
playing until one
team wins by two.
-They keep playing?
-Don't worry.
Those guys will take 7
points in no time flat.
-Oh yeah.
Our boys are burning
up the court.
-I sure hope so.
-Oishi is the first to
serve, so that's gonna mean--
-It's the Australian formation.
-In a tiebreak, the
first point is crucial.
JUDGE: 1-0, Seigaku.
St. Rudolph's Akazawa to serve.
-Huh?
Why is the serve changing?
-From here on in, so
that it won't be unfair,
each of the players
will be consecutively
serving up two balls each.
-Oh no, it's--
-Too
-What the--
-Beam!
JUDGE: 2-0 Seigaku.
-Yeah!
-Awesome.
They took two of them.
-There we go.
SPECTATOR 1: There's
no stopping them now.
SPECTATOR 2: Amazing.
They're just amazing.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
This can't be happening.
What kind of players are they?
SUMIRE (VOIEOVER):
What do you think?
Our boys have made your data
worthless, haven't they?
Tennis is fun because one
can't predict the moves.
Isn't that so?
AKAZAWA (VOICEOVER):
They're strong.
No wonder this pair went
all the way to he Nationals.
-St. Rudolph's is losing
right in front of our eyes.
JUDGE: 3-0 Seigaku.
-All right.
-That's the way to do it.
-Only four more to go.
-Hey, Kaneda.
-Yeah, Captain?
-Don't you ever give up.
What?
Are you trying to make me
play singles or something?
-I'm sorry, Captain.
-You know, we can
still win this.
-Huh?
-In point of fact, they should
have finished this up sooner,
before they even took
it to a tiebreaker.
-Here's your chance, Eiji.
-OK.
JUDGE: 3-1 to St. Rudolph.
-Sorry.
-Eiji, are you all right?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
-Oh, that's not good.
-St. Rudolph's on fire.
They got some of
their momentum back.
-You know what,
Inui, before, you
said something that we
totally don't understand.
-Yeah, you said they should
have finished the match
before the tiebreak,
but how come?
-You'll see soon enough.
-Mr. Inoue, what's happening?
-Hm.
JUDGE: Game and
match to St. Rudolph.
SUMIRE (VOIEOVER):
You played well.
[crowd cheering]
-Sorry, Coach.
-What are you sorry about?
You two boys put on
a mighty good show.
-Oishi.
-This is the worst.
-It is just a big shame that
Kikumaru wasn't strong enough.
No.
He barely had the
stamina to make
the tiebreaker, much less the
energy to play through it.
-Boy, he really ran out
of gas quickly, didn't he?
-Yeah, who'd have
guessed they could
win seven points straight.
-I just sort of wiped out.
-You had some tough luck.
-Hey, we're sorry, you guys.
The rest is all yours.
-Yeah, we got it.
-We won.
This amazing.
I thought we were through,
but we came back from behind.
-You're right.
AKAZAWA (VOICEOVER): Actually,
we were just plain lucky.
-Mizuki's scenario
was so amazing.
He was even able to guess
that we'd win the game 7 to 6.
-Mizuki.
-Those guys got--
-Pretty hard to
believe the golden pair
would just collapse like that.
-Man, those guys are tough.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
We're lucky to have won,
but the Australian formation
and Kikumaru's rebound, too many
unexpected things happened.
Even number two doubles.
Kaidoh's boomerang snake
and Momoshiro's dunk smash
that keeps getting stronger.
And then there was
that loss by default.
These were never in my scenario.
-Huh?
Are you serious?
-Yeah.
-But Mizuki's scenario
hasn't missed,
ever since the district matches.
If the scenario's not on track,
then it means we're slacking.
-It bounced up and-- whoa.
-Whatever, but I
can't lose to Seigaku.
Not to Seigaku.
That's for sure.
And I won't disappoint
Mizuki, either.
-Huh?
Shusuke Fuji?
Hey, that's your
big bro, isn't it?
[growls]
-Uh, Yuuta, I'm going on ahead.
Don't be too late.
-You're looking well.
How's it going?
So tell me, you finally
getting used to dorm life yet?
I was so sure you
would be playing
number one or two singles.
I was looking forward
to playing against you.
-Don't lie to me, loser.
I'll play you
anytime you want to.
Instead, I'll crush that seventh
grader, the one who beat Inui.
I'll use everything I've got.
That punk's going down.
Mizuki will beat
you into the ground,
and then St. Rudolph's will win.
-Don't know about me, but that
seventh grader's really tough,
Yuuta.
-We'll find out soon.
Good luck, pal.
-Hm, that's the ball Yuuta hit.
What a temper.
SHUSUKE (VOICEOVER):
Mizuki, huh?
-Ryoma?
Ryoma, uh, I came to
tell you doubles lost,
and Seigaku's in big trouble.
-Huh, I wonder where
Ryoma went off to?
-I saw him around here
just a minute ago.
-So high maintenance.
Of course, I know the scoop.
He's probably off taking
a nap somewhere right now.
-Third courts singles.
It's our most
important match of all.
Do you think Echizen is ready?
-Who can tell?
He probably went off to
meditate and prepare himself
for his coming match.
-Uh, Ryoma, I heard that there's
some really strong players
in the tournament today.
Seigaku seems to be having
a very difficult time.
If Fudomine and Yamabuki
advance to the semi-finals,
do you think you'll have
to play Fudomine again?
KUNIMITSU: There are
lots of strong players
in the Nationals.
-Stronger than you?
KUNIMITSU: Do you want
to find out for yourself?
-Echizen, become the
pillar of Seigaku's team.
-Know what?
I'll challenge them all.
-Number three
singles has started.
Come on, let's go.
ANNOUNCER: We will now begin
the number three singles
match between Seigaku
and St. Rudolph.
[theme music]
-This is Mizuki
from St. Rudolph.
The Seigaku tennis team is
playing beyond my scenario.
Ryoma Echizen, you're doing a
great job at provoking Yuuta,
but Yuuta is not called
lefty killer for nothing.
Next on the "Prince of
Tennis, Twist Spin Shot."
Enjoy watching Yuuta,
the lefty killer.