-He returned it.
-Not again.
Echizen fell right into
the viper's secret trap.
-Huh?
A what?
-Trap.
The viper uses the
snake shot as a trick.
What he's really up
to is-- is he's--
[theme music]
-Hm.
So that's the angle
he's gonna take.
You still have a ways to go.
-Huh?
He switched hands.
-Do you think that
Echizen will be
able to hit if he switches
his racket to his left hand?
It seems tough.
-Don't know, but we'll see.
-He's a natural lefty.
-Oh, hello, Coach Ryuzaki.
RYUZAKI: He's no
ordinary rookie.
OK, Ryoma.
Here's your chance.
-Come on, Ryoma.
-Oh, the snake shot?
-No, that was just a return.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER):
This kid hits well.
Lots of spin.
Low and deep.
Just inside the baseline.
But that doesn't matter to me!
-That was the snake shot.
Echizen can barely
get to the ball.
-Here it goes!
ANNOUNCER: Out.
-Echizen returned that shot.
-It didn't work.
-Awesome.
Oh, this is really,
really close.
Oh no.
-What a great guy.
-Stop.
He might hear you.
-Game to Kaidoh.
Game to Echizen.
-Hey.
The score's tied at 1-1!
Echizen's keeping up with
one of Seigaku's best.
Pretty impressive.
BOY: Man, it's hot today.
Just watching the
game makes you sweat.
Hey, so, uh, who do you
think's gonna win this?
-Finish!
-Look out!
Here comes the snake shot!
He got to it.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER):
His footwork's good.
He returned my best shot.
You may be really fast, but
that's why you're going down,
seventh grader.
-Ryoma's returning
every single ball.
He may have a chance after all.
-He's so good!
-Hey, keep on shooting him.
-Yeah.
-His footwork is
quite remarkable.
But still.
-He returned it.
-Not again.
Echizen fell right into
the viper's secret trap.
-Huh?
A what?
-Trap.
The viper uses the
snake shot as a trick.
What he's really up
to is-- is he's--
-Ryoma's really wearing out.
-I got it.
He has to chase after
those snake shots,
and it's totally
dehydrating him.
MOMOSHIRO: You got it.
Viper's style is
to keep tormenting
his exhausted opponent.
The more balls Ryoma returns,
the more exhausted he becomes.
BOY: Ryoma can't keep this up.
ANNOUNCER: 40-Love.
BOY: You sure know a lot
about his game, Momoshiro.
-Huh?
-You can say that again.
-I got it.
You must have lost to
the viper that way.
-What?
Shut up, you little seventh
graders, and watch the game.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER): So,
he's getting pretty close.
He's going down.
This cannot be.
He has to be totally drained.
His shot is so powerful.
Where is he getting this energy?
Weird.
His game is getting much better.
And even faster!
-Sweating just a little
bit, I see, Kaidoh.
ANNOUNCER: 40-30.
-What a great match.
-Aw.
-Hi there, uncle.
I'm home.
-Oh!
I wasn't expecting you so early.
You having fun in college?
-I'm having a great time.
I just now got back.
-Welcome home, Nanako darling.
-Hi.
It's great to see you, auntie.
-Dear.
Put that magazine away
right this minute.
NANAKO: Uncle!
I can't believe it!
You're reading trash!
NANJIRO: Uh, no!
Uh, no I'm not!
[meow]
ANNOUNCER: Game to Echizen.
What do you know?
Kaidoh's the one
who's out of gas.
Ah, he can't figure it out.
Echizen's playing him.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER): His
shots are still the same.
It's not possible.
I can't be slowing down.
ANNOUNCER: Game to Echizen.
-No way.
Echizen's running Kaidoh
all over the court.
-What's going on?
I thought Kaidoh was killing him
with those snake shots of his.
-I've never seen
Kaidoh look so tired.
-Huh?
Sakuno, why does
Kaidoh look so tired?
-I'm sure I wouldn't know.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER):
I hate that shot.
It always goes in!
I missed it!
-Looks like the viper
really got taken for a ride.
-What's going on?
Wasn't Echizen the
one who was tired?
INUI: Kaidoh used his
snake shot to make
Echizen run after the ball.
That was his strategy
to tire his opponent.
Echizen beat him at his game.
Ryoma keeps hitting the
ball low and deep just
inside the baseline,
right at his feet.
Kaidoh has to bend his knees
and keep this body low,
so every time Ryoma
hits that shot,
Kaidoh is using up double
the energy he normally would.
ANNOUNCER: 30-Love.
-By staying consistent,
Ryoma managed
to tie our his opponent instead.
[sigh]
-Ryoma is so totally cool.
Ryoma's, like, number one!
Ha ha!
He rocks!
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER): Looks like
I'm the one caught in the trap.
-It looks like both
players are exhausted,
but I think Echizen's got
the viper's strategy totally
figured out.
Kaidoh didn't realize
that he'd been caught,
so Ryoma had a huge mental edge.
I mean, I think that's where
the viper lost the game.
-He lost his head, that viper.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER):
OK, so I'm tired.
But he must be, too.
If I lose to a rookie,
I'll be a laughing stock.
ANNOUNCER: Game to Echizen.
Game to Kaidoh.
BOY: Kaidoh looks like he's
still got some fight in him.
KACHIRO: Now that Kaidoh
knows Ryoma's strategy,
I wonder if he can outlast him.
-Snake shot.
Top spin rules.
That's it.
That's the answer.
-Huh?
-Oh-- Oh no!
-Wow.
A snake shot.
-Snake shot?
-Snake shot.
-Why'd he do it?
He did a snake shot also.
-Ryoma is too awesome.
-This is so crazy.
-Mr. Inoue.
What was it that
Echizen said before?
-He said top spin rules.
-Top spin rules?
INOUE: He hits a huge
looping shot from low to high
to put major spin on the ball.
That's the most important part.
Many top pro players have
this shot in their arsenals.
Kaidoh's snake shot
is based on that,
but it takes a special
technique, so it's not easy.
But the rookie was able to do
it by only watching Kaidoh.
The kid is really good.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER): No joke.
That clown was able to hit my
snake shot just by watching me?
-It's not an easy
shot, Kaidoh, but I
happened to see an article on
that shot in a Tennis Magazine.
So I tried it.
After seeing you
hit the real thing,
I realized it's tough
without a long reach.
-Argh!
-He's got a
technique, all right.
But more than that,
Echizen obviously
has a lot of match experience
against high level opponents.
This match is over.
ANNOUNCER: Match point Echizen.
Echizen only needs
one point to win.
KAIDOH (VOICEOVER): No way.
I can't lose to the new kid.
Not me!
I'm Kaoru Kaidoh!
-Snake shot.
ANNOUNCER: Game, set, match.
Match goes to Echizen.
-The seventh grader won.
I can't believe it.
BOYS: Amazing.
Over Kaidoh.
I can't believe it.
-He won!
KACHIRO: Ryoma won!
HORIO: He won!
Yay!
Awesome!
Yes!
-He made it, Sakuno!
Yeah!
-Huh?
-What's he doing?
-He's just a sore loser.
-Shake hands?
Uh, good game.
-Nice try, Kaidoh.
-I'm not giving up
my place on the team.
Not to him.
-Nice job.
-You were great.
-Amazing.
-A seventh grader won.
-That was really cool, Ryoma.
-You're so cool.
-He's not even a
member of the team yet
and he beat one of the regulars.
Way to go.
-So the only players in Bracket
D who are still undefeated
are Echizen and you, Inui.
Am I right?
HORIO: I had faith.
I always believed Echizen
could beat Kaidoh.
KACHIRO: Horio, you're
always changing your story.
KATSUO: I was so
impressed with Ryoma.
I'm sure he'll be a starter.
How lucky.
HORIO: But who knows?
Kaidoh was an eighth grader,
but Ryoma's next opponent
is a ninth grade regular, Inui.
Even Echizen won't be able to--
-Ryoma is gonna win!
-Hey.
Don't get so angry.
RYOMA: Look.
It's not big deal.
Let's just finish cleaning up.
-Hey, Ryoma.
-You've been
practicing with a coach
since you were a baby, right?
Have you ever lost
in a tournament
when it really counts?
-I'm losing all the time.
-Huh?
-Aw, quit teasing us.
You wanna be a professional
player someday,
isn't that right?
-Not really.
-No way!
Don't say that.
-Ryoma, you're good enough
to make it as a professional!
-Not interested.
-What but why?
-Well, then why do you
bother even playing?
Hey Echizen!
-Hm?
MAN (VOICEOVER): Ryoma's winning
the match against Kaidoh.
Amazing.
Now I'm positive it's
gotta be his son.
-Huh?
-I think we have to go
and see the boy's father.
-See him?
Who?
See who?
-His father, Nanjiro Echizen.
[theme music]
-I'm Nanjiro Echizen.
call me Nanji.
A reporter named Inoue who
said he was a fan of mine
came to see me, but he only
asked about my son, Ryoma.
Heh.
How insulting.
OK.
Let's play some
tennis, and I promise
I'll answer all your questions.
If you beat me.
Next on "The Prince of Tennis."
Nanjiro Echizen.
Or how about this title?
The old man of tennis.
Huh?
Why not?