-Speed ace.
Yeah right!
-Ah!
Don't make me laugh.
Never underestimate Karukado.
Ah!
I will not lose!
Huh?
[theme music]
[grunt]
-Hey, it went around the net.
That doesn't count as
a legal shot, does it?
[hissing]
-Oh, wow.
That rocked.
-Sure did.
-Yeah, it curved just
like a boomerang.
-A boomerang snake!
-Wow, I want to play
games like them.
-Huh?
Huh.
Woah.
-Wow.
That was so cool, but
was it even legal?
-I'm absolutely sure it is.
The ball goes around the net
post and returns to the court.
No rules against it.
Even so, I've never seen it
used in a tournament before.
-Look there!
It was all a trick
that Kaido had
up his sleeve the whole time!
-All right, let's go Kaido!
-You know, if he's got
a great trick like that,
then he ought to use
the shot more often.
-Don't sweat.
It's still anybody's game.
ANNOUNCER: Game score.
40-30.
-Haha.
Hey.
That was a pretty
good trick, Viper.
[hissing]
-Now it's my chance
to turn up the heat.
[grunting]
-Huh?
Oh!
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Kamio of Fudomine.
One game to love.
[laughter]
-Huh.
Woah.
-The way he served so
quickly was well done.
-How did he do it?
-He did it by keeping
his ball toss low
and then hitting the ball
at an even quicker pace.
Kaido was taken by surprise.
-Huh.
Grr.
[hissing]
[grunting]
-That's it!
The boomerang snake shot!
ANNOUNCER: Love-15.
-Oh, darn.
He missed it.
-Too bad.
-Awww.
-Ah.
You cut it too close.
-That round-the-pole shot
was just a lucky move.
-Sure looks that way.
[grunt]
-I'll stop you
cold with my speed.
[grunt]
-I'm feeling the rhythm.
ANNOUNCER: Out.
Love-30.
-Hmm.
-It's no good.
-He can't control
his boomerang snake.
[grunting]
-Snake!
-Ah!
[panting]
ANNOUNCER: Out.
Love-40.
KAIDO (VOICEOVER): Man.
If I could just execute that
shot, I could beat this guy.
-Ahh!
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Kamio of Fudomine.
-It's not looking good.
Kaido's not himself.
-This is bad.
His snake shot isn't working.
And his boomerang shot
isn't any good either.
Oh, no!
[sigh]
-Ah.
-You're trying too hard.
What are you doing?
Swinging wildly like that.
This just isn't like you.
It's not your tennis.
You know, you're a
fool to pin your hopes
on such a low percentage shot.
Kaido.
Just what do you think you're
doing out there on that court?
KAIDO (VOICEOVER): She's right.
This-- This isn't
my kind of tennis.
-Akira is standing his ground.
That boomerang snake shot made
me nervous there for a while.
-Yeah.
Looks like Akira's
clearly able to handle it.
-He could walk off with
a love game after all.
-No.
-Huh?
-Kamio's rhythm is off.
He's playing much faster
than he usually does.
If he wastes his stamina, the
snake is bound to get him.
-Oh.
-Kind of makes me wonder.
Is Kaido all right?
-I wonder where Sakuno is?
-Oh, yeah.
You're right.
Where'd she go?
-I think to the girls' room.
-I'd better hurry The
match is starting.
Oh.
Looks like I'm totally lost.
Where were those courts?
Oh.
[grunt]
-Get off!
-Oh!
I'm so sorry.
I wasn't looking.
-What's that?
You step on my shoes and think
"I'm sorry" can fix that?
Huh?
KAMIO (VOICEOVER):
You're stubborn, Viper.
You have no chance of winning.
You must be getting tired.
Well, this is it.
[growling]
-Well, it looks like he's
found himself after all.
--I know.
But it still looks like
Kaido's in trouble.
-It looks like it's not
going to end simply.
When Kaido gets cornered,
he gets really dangerous.
[grunting]
-Sure is tight.
Kamio is quick, but
Kaido sure is tough.
-If he keeps going like that,
Kaido might just catch up.
ANNOUNCER: 40-30.
-Oh, it's match point.
That service break he lost
before has totally hurt him.
-If he drops the next
point, he's lost.
-Come on, Kaido.
You can do it.
Hang in there.
KAMIO (VOICEOVER): I've never
played anyone so tenacious.
You've done well, Viper.
But this is the end.
[grunt]
-No, look out, Kaido!
-Huh?
[grunt]
-Oh no.
It's a quick stroke!
[grunting]
-Ugh.
The net!
ANNOUNCER: Deuce.
[hissing]
-Come on!
-He stood his ground!
-Nice job, Kaido.
-Hey, Momoshiro.
-Hey, what's happening?
How's Tonka's arm?
-Ha.
He's still at the
hospital, but don't worry,
our boy is really tough.
-He's still at the hospital?
All right.
I'm out of here.
-Wait a second, Momoshiro.
How's the game so far?
-Oh.
You should check it out.
-You should really watch
where you're going, kid.
-Um, I'm sorry.
-I bet you think it's
no big deal that you
stepped on my brand new shoes.
They're a one-of-a-kind
pair, you know.
I kept them clean through all
my matches and you ruined them.
Don't you get it, kid?
-But what can I do?
-Just give me 30,000 yen.
-H-- how much?
-You heard me.
$30,000 yen.
-Shut up, jerk.
-Huh?
-You know, extortion
is such an ugly word.
She apologized.
Just leave her alone.
-And who are you supposed to be?
-Just a good citizen.
Let's go.
I think it's time
we got out of here.
-But-- he said--
-Hey, wait.
I'm not done.
[gasp]
-From now on, why don't you
mind your own business, OK?
ANNOUNCER: Advantage, server.
-This is it.
ANNOUNCER: Deuce again.
[hissing]
-Saved another one.
-What a game!
-Come on, Kaido.
Let's do it.
-This is your moment, Kaido.
You can do it.
-Hmm.
KAMIO (VOICEOVER) Hurry up.
And fold!
-Who's going to fold?
-Oh, no.
Another snake shot!
[grunting]
-Unbelievable!
He's so determined!
He's running so hard, but
he's still not out of breath.
-They've both been burning
up the same amount of energy,
but-- Kaido runs 10
kilometers in the morning.
10 kilometers after practice.
And 10 at night.
He does three sets of dashes
and that's just to start.
-What?
That's nuts.
He couldn't possibly
do that every day.
-Bingo.
That's three times
our regular routine.
-So you want stamina like
no one else in the league?
-Hmm.
-Then you should really
try this regimen.
-I will do double that.
-Kaido is incredible.
-Yeah.
ANNOUNCER: Net ball
makes it deuce again.
-Bad shot.
That sure doesn't
seem like Kaido.
KAMIO (VOICEOVER):
He's hanging tough.
Got to admire that spirit.
It's clear that the usual
offense won't work this time.
In that case--
-Take that.
---I'll step up the rhythm.
-Speed looks good, Kamio.
[grunting]
-Woah!
-Oh, no.
How could you hit your toughest
snake shot at a time like this?
[grunting]
-Hahaha.
Sorry about that, pal.
Guess it all comes down to luck.
Huh?
[grunt]
ANNOUNCER: Advantage, Kaido.
-I will not lose.
Who said it was over?
I don't care if
it's match point.
Watch out.
I will never, ever give up.
-Oh, man, he's stubborn.
-Slowly eating away
at an opponent.
Even if the player's ahead,
he can't help but feel
the pressure.
-Isn't it just like
him to fight like this.
[gasps]
[grunting]
-Ahhh!
ANNOUNCER: Game and match.
Kaido of Seigaku.
Seven games to five.
-All right.
We won the match!
[cheering]
-Oh, man.
I can't believe I
let the team down.
-He was a tough player.
-I did the best I could,
so I have no regrets.
But you know, the next two
matches will be much harder.
-Don't worry about it.
Just go ahead and
leave the rest to us.
Right, Shinji?
-Stay out of it.
-Oh!
-How dare you?
-Shut up and get lost, will you?
-What school are you from?
Do you always go around
beating up on girls like that?
-Do you always go around
looking for fights?
-Please, stop that.
Please stop.
-Bad idea beating up girls.
Really bad.
You idiot.
-Huh?
Oh!
-Oh!
-Yes!
That felt great.
Loser.
-Why, you--
-Momoshiro.
-That's me.
-This punk demanded money.
30,000 yen because she
stepped on his shoe.
-Well now, you'll just have
to throw them in the washer.
Just like everybody else does.
-And who are you?
-Momoshiro of Seigaku.
[growling]
-Shall I step on the other one?
-I'll get you for this!
-Come back, punk.
You didn't even
tell us your name.
-You saved us, Momoshiro.
-I can never thank you enough.
I'm just so sorry I
caused all this trouble.
-It's no big deal.
Oh, yeah.
You were the one looking
for Echizen that time.
-Oh, yeah.
That was me.
-I get it.
You guys are here
to cheer him on.
Awww, puppy love.
Well, you better hurry
up and get going,
or the match will
begin without you.
-Aren't you going?
-No.
Actually, I've got to
go to the hospital.
-Are you all right?
How badly are you
hurt, Momoshiro?
-No, no.
It isn't me.
It's Taka Kawamura.
Mura.
His opponent from Fudomine
hit this awesome ball
in the finals.
He managed to return the
ball, but he hurt his wrist
while doing it.
-You mean Kawamura who
returned Ashida's power drive?
Wow, what an amazing feat.
He must be good.
-You know a lot.
-Well, that's because I'm
a student at Fudomine.
-Oh.
That explains it.
You have a good
team, for a rival.
In fact, your captain,
Tachibane, is especially good.
He's definitely not your
average everyday player.
I really want to play that
tough guy in number one singles
and do my signature dunk
smash, just like this.
See?
-I'm not sure about
that, Momoshiro.
-Huh?
-Your dunk smash.
It's not junior-high level.
It's better than that, for sure.
I don't think anyone
can return that shot.
MOMOSHIRO (VOICEOVER)
She's well informed.
-But if you go up
against my brother,
he'll never even
give you a chance.
-Huh?
-What?
Brother?
You don't mean--
-Haha.
I'm tough-guy Tachibana's
little sister, An.
-Huh?
-Hey.
I understand now.
I finally broke down the way you
hit the boomerang snake shot.
It's really not too hard.
How about you and
I try it later?
-You sure you want to do that?
It's just going to
give you more enemies
during the ranking
matches, you know.
-Don't care.
I've already started
collecting more data.
Don't worry.
I'll still beat you.
-I will make you eat your words.
-Hey, look.
The match is starting.
-The first to win
three games wins.
If you take this game, Echizen,
you win the tournament.
Go for it!
-Come on, Ryoma.
You can do it.
-I can't wait to see Ryoma.
It's his big debut
as a singles player.
-Don't just stare at him.
Take some pictures.
-Oh, yeah.
Right.
-Shinji Ibu of Fudomine.
He's the one who didn't let that
seeded player Kuki get close,
right?
-Seigaku put a seventh
grader in that key number
two singles slot.
I don't get it.
-I feel kind of sorry for him.
Maybe it's a throwaway match.
ANNOUNCER: One set match.
Seigaku's Echizen to serve.
-He's using his right hand.
He's giving it all he's got.
-Hmm.
-Oh!
-Son of Nonjiro Echizen.
Knock their socks off.
[grunt]
[theme music]
-Are you all here?
I'm Sunida Reuzake.
That Ibo of Fudomine
is quite a player.
He's spoiling Ryoma's
specialty, the kick serve.
When I look at Ryoma,
I remember the old days
when Nanjuro was young.
Come on, Ryoma.
Go knock everyone's socks off.
Next on The Prince of
Tennis-- The Love Letter.
What in the world is that about?