ANNOUNCER: 30-Love.
-I can't believe it.
I couldn't even see
the path of the ball.
ANNOUNCER: 40-Love.
-All right, Yamabuki!
-He's got that smashed!
-We won!
-Sengoku!
Sengoku!
-Man, Sengoku got to
game point quickly.
-It goes to show how well
he can rattle his opponent.
-Well, this should be it.
Sengoku used his Tiger Cannon.
Momoshiro, it's over.
[theme music]
-All right, lackey
Sengoku, let's
see what a junior all-star
tough guy is made of.
-By the way, it's Lucky
Sengoku, not lackey Sengoku.
And for the record,
I don't really
think your dunk smash
is that impressive.
-All right.
-We will begin
number three singles.
It's a one set match, service
to Seigaku's Momoshiro.
-Hm.
-Hey, know what?
I'm going to make you sorry
you gave me the starting serve.
-You see that?
-Hey, it's Momoshiro's--
-Bullet serve!
-He's a big hitter.
SENGOKU (VOICEOVER): Hm.
That's a pretty solid shot.
-This is gonna be a tough one.
Go!
Momoshiro, yeah!
-What's with this guy?
-It seems he's as
good as Sengoku.
-It's much worse than that.
It feels like he's got Sengoku
playing on the defense.
-Uh-huh.
I see this is your style
of tennis, Momoshiro.
[shout]
-Why is Momo rushing
the net like that?
-Go!
SENGOKU (VOICEOVER):
Then I'll just
have to make a passing
shot to the left.
-Huh?
Hey, there!
Looks like you almost had
a winner there, buddy!
-This guy.
He's got some amazing speed.
-He jumped for it!
-Then that must mean--
-It's good!
Momo's dunk smash is awesome!
-Yeah!
-Amazing.
-Was that his dunk smash?
-It had to be.
-All right, he did it!
-Momo's been completely
dominant from the start.
-Yeah!
-Come and get me!
Take that!
-That Momo.
It actually looks
like he might be
able to take out a
junior all-star player.
When did he become such
a good player, anyway?
Well, Tezuka, I guess
yesterday's practice
wasn't a waste of
time after all.
-That's right.
Momoshiro's aggressive style
of play is his biggest weapon.
-Hey, Banji, better watch out.
Your boys will
have to work mighty
hard to shut down Momoshiro.
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Why is he so calm?
MOMOSHIRO (VOICEOVER): I
can't let my guard down.
The pressure's killing me.
I can feel him
breathing down my neck.
It's just like when Tezuka
neutralized all my attacks.
But Sengoku's as
cutthroat as I am.
This match will be mine.
-Huh?
-That shot's too high!
It's going out!
MOMOSHIRO (VOICEOVER):
That's a lob!
With a slice spin!
It's going to come down fast!
I knew I couldn't
let my guard down!
-Huh?
Huh?
Dunk smash?
-But that's Momo's shot.
-No way.
ANNOUNCER: 40-15.
BOY: He's pretty good.
He faked Momo out.
He pretended to
defend the lob, but he
was setting up for
that dunk smash.
-Wow.
I'm a lucky guy to get such
a clean shot off of you.
-You wouldn't think that a
top ranked player like Sengoku
would have to resort to such
cheap tricks, would you?
-Tennis is a sport where
the mental side of the game
can have a huge impact.
I wonder if Momoshiro will
be affected psychologically
after his opponent used his
signature shot against him?
-Excuse me.
I call a time out.
The strings on this practice
racket are too loose.
I'm going to change my stick.
Hm.
Much better.
And now it's time to use
my game racket, Omoshiro.
-It's not Omoshiro.
-But it sounds so much better.
[cheering]
-Come on!
Just do it, Momo!
ANNOUNCER: Game to Yamabuki.
One game to Love.
-A big break for me.
Just call me lucky.
ANNOUNCER: Change sides.
-That's impossible!
-But he led most of this game.
-It just went from 40-Love to
break point in no time at all.
-That fool.
He's really letting him
mess with this head.
-Hm.
Not so bad.
[humming]
-I knew it.
It's all been downhill for him
ever since that dunk smash.
-This is looking good for us.
-Sengoku's got
gamemanship down for sure.
-Sengoku!
Sengoku!
-Sengoku's looking really good.
-It certainly is
clear why he was
named a junior all-star player.
-Well, I guess it just proves
that he's a notch or two
above the other players.
-Huh?
-Yikes.
Nanzabiro's here.
-No.
My name is Nanjiro.
But I think you can call
me anything you want to.
-Hey!
Just who do you think you
are, talking to me like that?
-Hey, Nanjiro.
So what can you tell us about
Banda, the coach from Yamabuki?
Well, from what I heard, you
were a player at Seigaku.
Am I right?
Banda coached for a school
that wasn't well known.
A school whose team defeated
Seigaku in the metropolitan
matches.
But that's not all, is it?
It seems to me that both
you and Coach Ryuzaki
are awfully worried about
the way this guy coaches.
-Aw, it's not that bad.
Back then, we were the
number one seated team.
Our first opponents were
that old grandpa's boys,
Kuwanomi Junior High.
They were a team that
wasn't even on the radar.
However, that match
took unexpected turns.
It was not a good
day for Seigaku.
ANNOUNCER: Out!
Game and match to Kuwanomi.
-No!
ANNOUNCER: Game and
match to Kuwanomi.
-No way.
-Game and match to Seigaku.
Score of six games to Love.
NANJIRO: Of course, it was
a piece of cake for me.
But the rest of the
guys got flustered
by that geezer's smug grin.
It was bad.
Our team got killed
in that tournament.
To make a long
story short, Banda's
the king of gamesmanship.
It's amazing that we missed it.
Especially the old hag.
-So, now, you going to make
this interesting, Omoshiro?
Here I go, Omoshiro.
BOY: Look how high his toss is.
I can't believe he gets so high.
-No way!
He's going to hit
it from up there?
-Huh?
ANNOUNCER: 15-Love.
-How'd he serve like that?
-Yup.
I'm on a roll.
-It's like, his serve is
absolutely unreturnable.
-That is Sengoku's secret
weapon, the Tiger Cannon.
-Tiger Cannon?
-It is a shot that utilizes his
entire frame to the fullest,
allowing him to hammer the
ball from a high vantage point.
By doing that, he lands
the ball both close
to and in the center.
-30-Love.
-I can't believe it.
I couldn't even see
the path of the ball.
ANNOUNCER: 40-Love!
-All right, Yamabuki!
We won!
-Sengoku!
Sengoku!
-Man, Sengoku got to
game point quickly.
-It goes to show how well
he can rattle his opponent.
Well this should be it.
Sengoku used his Tiger Cannon.
Momoshiro, it's over.
-He's not too bad.
First he gets Momo off balance
by getting inside his head,
and then he messes him up with
that treacherous serve he uses.
Momo better watch out.
It looks like that guy's got
more tricks up his sleeve.
-It's amazing how he gets
his opponents all worked up,
and then gets them
to play his game.
So that's the Yamabuki
adviser Banda's tennis style.
-We're not done.
Let's not give up just yet.
Although that orange haired
boy of theirs is pretty good.
-Well, time of wrap this up.
BOY: He jumped!
BOY: The Tiger Cannon!
-Huh?
-Mm.
-40-15.
-Not too shabby, huh?
Our little trickster did good.
-How did he return that?
-He hit a winner off
Sengoku's Tiger Shot.
-No way!
It's gotta be a fluke for sure.
ANNOUNCER: 40-30.
-Wow, he completely
saw that one coming.
Man, this could mean trouble.
-You're absolutely right.
-Come on, Momo.
You can win this thing!
-Hey, Echizen.
Do me a favor and get
me my game racket.
-What?
You've got to be kidding me.
-Come on, I was just having fun.
-Why, you--
-Whoa!
-Wow.
-He's incredible.
-Yeah, this is really
becoming a slugfest.
-Seigaku's guy is awesome.
-Take this!
-Tie game, with Yamabuki,
Sengoku at three games each.
-It's all tied up again.
-Yeah.
Ever since they took that
break, they've pretty much
been keeping up with each
other the whole game.
-Even so, Momo's still
sweating buckets out there.
SENGOKU (VOICEOVER): This
guy is mentally tough.
I thought for sure he'd
crumble after I aced him
with that dunk smash.
-Huh?
-Uh-oh.
Our good friend here looks
like he might be hurt.
-Huh?
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
He's having cramps
in his left leg.
by compensating for
his injured right foot,
he's putting way too much
of a strain on his left leg.
Hm?
Although this could just be
momentary, due to fatigue,
Momo, the fact remains
that this still
puts you at a
serious disadvantage.
HORIO: Come on, Momo!
KATSUO: One more shot!
-Oh yeah.
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER): Still,
for Momo's leg to cramp up
like that, this has got to
be one tough match for him.
Sengoku didn't get this
far just by being lucky.
It appears he has the
skills to back it up.
Besides which, he seems to
have the motion tracking skills
that Momo lacks.
-Motion tracking skills?
-It's the ability to follow
moving objects, right, Inui?
-I've heard that Ryoma and
Kikumaru have good motion
tracking skills.
-They do, but Sengoku
can put them to shame.
-Huh?
SHUSHUKE: Momo may look
good on those returns,
but Sengoku's more
accurate and efficient.
It just goes to show you how
well he's able to see the ball
and read its path.
-I can barely even keep
my eyes on the ball
without it making me dizzy.
-Ah huh.
-You got it.
I'm sure that even
Momoshiro's hardest shots
look slow to that guy, huh?
-Wow.
-So then what should
he do now, huh?
-There's not much
he can really do.
-Five games to three.
Yamabuki leads.
-Hey, look.
Sengoku's one point away
from winning the game!
Akutsu?
-Yes, indeed, my friends.
It seems that Sengoku
can do it all.
-Ow.
This is not good.
Really hurts.
-Momo?
-Huh?
Trust me.
It'll be fine, Coach.
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER): Momo.
MOMOSHIRO (VOICEOVER): It's
as if he can see into my mind.
And yet I don't have a
clue what he's up to.
I went all want to put
this game away quickly,
but look what happened.
-He's a tough opponent.
-Ow.
-My, my.
-Hey, look at that.
-That guy's left leg's
beginning to cramp.
-Beginning?
-Are those cramps?
-Now they know.
SENGOKU (VOICEOVER):
Boy, am I lucky.
I really shouldn't revel in
other people's misfortunes,
though.
HORIO: No way!
A cramp in Momo's leg?
KACHIRO: Oh, no.
-It looks bad.
I doubt he can play a
decent match like that.
SENGOKU (VOICEOVER):
So he's been
playing on that leg all along?
-Whoa.
-A devastating return!
-I admire your
determination, Momoshiro.
-Momoshiro.
You are strong.
However, by compensating
for that right leg so much,
you prevent yourself from
using your full strength.
Your sprain healed over
a month ago, didn't it?
-I can't believe he's
still gonna play.
-Crazy.
-Yeah, the poor guy can
barely stand up now.
RYOMA (VOICEOVER): Come on.
Give it your all, Momo.
-All right, then.
Come and get me, Momoshiro.
-He jumped up off his right leg!
NANJIRO (VOICEOVER): Yes.
MOMOSHIRO (VOICEOVER):
You're right, Captain Tezuka.
SENGOKU (VOICEOVER): He's
gonna step into the ball.
No, he's not.
The ball's just
sitting on the strings.
MOMOSHIRO (VOICEOVER): I am--
-It can't be!
MOMOSHIRO (VOICEOVER):
I am tough!
[theme music]
-Hey, everyone.
Thanks for waiting.
It's me, Momo.
I'm not the most
serious guy around,
but Sengoku's no better.
I know I shouldn't
take him lightly.
No, I shouldn't.
This guy is really strong.
I don't know how
long my leg'll last,
but I'm gonna give
everything I've got.
Next on "The Prince
of Tennis," Jacknife.
Guess I just gotta score big.