(mellow orchestral music)
(birds chirping)
(calm orchestral music)
- [Akane] The weather's so nice, I almost feel like crying.
I'm gonna drown if keep staring at this big blue sky.
(groans)
- [Midori] Akane, you'll be late for school.
(scratching)
Did you hear me?
- [Akane] I've got a tummy ache so I'm staying home.
- Oh?
It doesn't seem like you have a fever.
It might be a cold.
Wanna see a doctor?
- No, I'll be fine if I rest.
- Mm, hope you feel better when you wake up.
(phone dings)
(gasps)
(sighs)
- Huh, hairpin?
- Didn't you get the text that Riya sent out last night?
All of us were going to wear our hairpins to school today.
- Yeah, Riya's mom made them for us by hand
so we thought it made sense to show them off
at the same time.
- So why did you not wear yours, huh?
Do you hate it?
- No, I'm telling you,
I stayed at my grandma's house last night
and left my phone at home so I missed the text.
- Akane, good morning!
- Hey, morning.
- Oh, good you're wearing it.
I'm so glad you actually remembered it.
- Yeah.
(bell chiming)
- Seeing all of us wear them like this
makes it feel like we're a hairpin squad.
- Yeah, team hairpin.
I like the sound of that.
- The way that the kamineko was portrayed by this writer-
- I really didn't know about the hairpins.
I wasn't lying, I swear.
So, can you try to convince the others
to believe I'm telling the truth?
Please, Akane?
(students laughing)
- [Girl] Are you still coming over later?
- [Girl] Yeah, of course.
(students chattering)
(lighthearted orchestral music)
BIRTHDAY WONDERLAND
(groans)
- Gorobeh, why would you sit on my face like that?
Why are you so nasty?
(Gorobeh yowling)
(Gorobeh purring)
(laughing)
I'm getting hungry.
(Gorobeh yowling) (Akane grunting)
Hi, Mom.
I.
- Go wait on the terrace.
I'll make something for you to eat.
(sighs)
(dog barking)
I feel guilty.
Being a cat must be chill.
I'm jealous.
(gasps)
- Here.
- It looks delicious.
Man, housewives have it pretty good too, don't they?
Still, Mom's cooking never ceases to amaze me.
- Do you feel any better?
- Yeah, I think my headache's just about gone.
- I thought it was a stomachache.
- Well, I also had a headache.
(giggling)
(humming)
- Would you mind running an errand for me?
(gulps)
- Huh?
- I need you to make a quick visit to Chii's shop.
- Huh, seriously?
I don't wanna.
Are you really gonna make me go see her?
Why mom?
- It's because,
because tomorrow's your birthday, isn't it?
I asked Chii if she could prepare a present for you.
And so, I want you to go get it.
- Wait, you mean I have to go out
and pick up my own birthday present?
That's totally weird.
I won't do it!
(dog barking)
- Ride carefully, okay?
(groans)
(lively music)
Have a safe trip, Akane!
"Restaurant"
"Chii's Curiosities"
- [Customer] No, I don't think you understand.
I'm telling you, I like this one more.
- But I honestly think this one suits you much better
than the mushroom.
- [Customer] Hmm.
- You should pick this one.
To give a little backstory,
I got it when I stayed at a hotel
in a town in Bolivia from an old man
who made beautiful sculptures of precious stones.
I instantly fell in love with it and asked to buy it.
But he said it wasn't finished yet.
However, I loved it so much that I kept insisting,
and he finally agreed to trade it for some chocolate.
Then when I returned to Japan,
I threw a light bulb in it and made it this little lamp.
I'm actually quite fond of it.
But if you promise to take good care of it,
I think we could work something out.
- [Akane] That witch is really trying to sell that thing.
- How much?
- Let's see. $10.
- Yah!
- [Akane] What a rip-off!
She said she got it for chocolate.
- How about you try it out first?
And if you decide that you like it,
then you can pay me for it later.
- I'm curious why you thought this would suit me.
(giggles)
- Because like I said, it's not finished.
No, way, it's Akane!
How have you been or more like where have you been?
I haven't seen you in so long!
- I just saw you last month.
You came over to the house
with some super stinky durian sweets
you picked up from Thailand.
- Oh, really, did I?
(laughs)
Ah, seems like you haven't filled out yet, have you?
(Akane grunts)
What's the matter?
(groans)
Wait a few years.
It just takes a little bit more time
for some girls to develop.
Oh, is that a bouquet from Midori?
Oh, thanks, Akane.
(giggles)
So, what brings you here?
- Huh?
- You came to pick up your birthday present?
I don't think I got an order like that.
- Are you going away again?
- I planned a trip to visit a flea market in Sorgue.
It's located in South France.
I've wanted to go there for a while.
It looks so beautiful, don't you think?
Are you thirsty at all?
- Mm-mm.
- Okay.
(enchanting music)
- Being around Chii is hard
but this place makes it worth it.
Hm?
Is this a piece of the Berlin Wall?
No, it couldn't be.
Huh?
(enchanting music)
(grunting)
Help me, Chii!
- Help you, with what?
- I'm stuck. I can't get out!
(knocking on wood) (Akane grunting)
- Did you just hear a knock too?
- Who cares?
Focus on getting me out!
(knocking on wood)
Huh? - Hm?
From the basement?
- [Akane] Wait, you have a basement?
- [Chii] It came with the place.
I use it for storage.
(creaking)
(exciting music)
(gasps)
- This place is just extremely difficult to navigate.
- Who are you?
Why are you in my basement?
Are you a thief?
I'll call the police!
- No, please.
Wait, please.
I assure you, I am not a thief.
Hm?
- Hm?
- Although I wonder if you're perhaps
a bit too old for the job.
- Yeah, I'm calling the cops.
- Listen carefully.
I came to this place to find the Goddess of the Green Wind.
- Huh?
- In other words, the girl who fits that hand print
on the table over there.
Oh!
(grunts) (energetic music)
(thuds)
What was that for?
How rude?
- Who are you calling rude?
- You are not who I seek!
(Chii grunts)
- [Chii] Hey!
- And you must be. (gasps)
Pipo, well done.
- Thank you, Master Hippocrates.
I'm glad to be of help. (giggles)
(gasps)
- Hm?
Hey, Chii, does that figurine normally talk?
- I guess I never checked.
- My body's stiff from staying still all morning.
Being able to move feels great!
(gasping)
- It flies too?
- I mean, maybe.
- Apologies for the delayed introduction.
I am Hippocrates and this little wee is my apprentice.
- Nice to meet you.
My name's Pipo.
- Now, it's saying nice to meet you.
- Well, it is the first we've met.
Mm-hm, so I guess that kinda makes sense.
- Huh?
- Pipo and I,
we come from a world beyond
that is connected to the basement of this establishment.
It is likely you've been completely unaware of this.
Well, what I should say is that I'm certain
you will not believe me.
- That's incredible!
- Huh?
- You're talking about a real alternate world?
We have books and films about worlds that are similar,
yet, totally different from ours
but you're telling me it's not just fiction?
Wait, then could our worlds
be part of a much larger multiverse?
And all of it's connected to my basement?
I've lived in this place ever since I was born
but I never knew this existed.
For how long, huh?
I need to know!
- I believe since ancient times.
(sighs)
- Now, I feel ripped off.
I can't believe something so cool was right under me.
Hey, what does it look like?
Give me all the details on your world.
- Can we maybe focus on getting my hand out of here?
- Oops, sorry, I forgot.
Since you look pretty important, you help her.
- Simply relax yourself.
- Huh?
- I'm terribly sorry but I must ask
that you come with us to our world immediately.
- Huh?
- Because you fit that hand print,
you were destined to be the Goddess of the Green Wind.
- Hold on a minute.
What is this guy even talking about?
- I honestly have no idea.
You know, you can't just ask a little girl you don't know
to follow you to a strange place.
So can I go instead?
- Huh?
- No, because you are not the goddess.
- Oh.
(Pipo grunts)
- Please, forgive us.
We know it's a sudden request.
However, our world is undergoing a major crisis right now
and when we need the goddess's help,
which means you're the only one who can save us.
- Oh, sorry.
- What are you talking about?
I don't have that power.
- Would you mind putting this on, please?
(mellow moving music)
(grunts)
- What is this heavy thing?
- How lovely, it suits you.
- Huh?
- That pendant is called the momentum anchor.
You see, it took me three days and three nights
to create this masterpiece using a secret element.
And I am rather proud of it.
- Isn't he just amazing?
He's known in our world as the greatest alchemist
that's ever lived!
You could ask anyone and they would know
who Master Hippocrates is.
- You're a real alchemist?
You're the first I've met.
- While wearing that necklace,
even if you feel a strong desire to turn around
and run from something,
it will help you continue on forward.
Yes, I think I did well in creating this piece.
- Get it off!
(exclaiming)
- Master Hippocrates is the only person
who can relieve you of that necklace.
Now, let's get going, shall we?
- No!
(grunts)
- Follow me, goddess.
(Akane whimpering)
- Hey, wait!
(groaning)
I'm coming with you guys too!
Wait for me!
(wind chime chiming)
(mysterious music)
(grunting)
- Master Hippocrates, the spider's road.
- This is taking longer than it needs to.
(gasping)
- There's no need to worry.
This is the spider who controls time
so it's not gonna hurt you.
(splashing)
- That's not our route.
Goddess, this way.
(grunting)
(tense music)
- Hey-
- Yes?
- I'm not a goddess, all right?
I'm an ordinary girl named Akane.
(tense music)
- You guys, okay?
Did anyone get hurt?
- No, Pipo.
I'm not okay at all!
Why we'd end up somewhere so high off the ground?
- We did not intend to land here.
- There are two entrances into this world.
The new one and the old one which we just used.
From the stories I've heard,
there were huge birds
that used to soar the skies around here.
Lots of them.
They're the ones who made this tower.
(birds chirping)
- Is that one of the birds you were talking about?
(squawking)
(exclaiming)
(roaring)
- Are those its eggs?
- It must be trying to protect them from harm!
- Calm down.
We wouldn't dream of cooking your beautiful eggs
to serve them sunny side up.
I promise you.
I mean they're too big for us to eat anyway.
(screeching)Whoa!
Whoa, whoa.
Think it understood?
- Come on!
- Stay still.
(groaning)
Now, descend quietly.
Are you all right, Akane?
- Mm.
(Pipo grunting)
(exhaust blowing)
- It's the armored mouse.
(ominous music)
(people gasping)
(clattering)
- Mother!
(whirring)
- No, my sweater!
- Seems you're up to no good again, Zan Gu!
- [Zan Gu] It's Hippocrates.
- [Doropo] And Pipo too.
These guys are real persistent, aren't they?
- What the hell is that?
(exhaust whistling)
(yelling)
(ominous music)
Akane, run!
- I can't move!
- Hey, make yourself useful!
(light mellow music)
(energetic music)
(chuckling)
- We really scared you, didn't we?
(somber music)
(clattering)
(bird squawking)
- The bird's eggs.
- No, wait!
- Master Hippocrates!
I brought you the sheep grass.
(leaf whistling)
(clattering)
(squawking)
(gasps)
(grunts)
(laughs)
- I got it!
Now, what is it?
(ground rumbling)
(distant sheep bleating)
(tense music)
- Ma, it's all the sheep from the village.
- How wonderful.
It seems they've come to help us.
(energetic music)
- They're huge!
- Do not move.
(energetic music)
(clanking)
- Draw back, now.
- Yeah, yeah, I got it.
- Those scoundrels are as troublesome as always.
- I kept your egg safe.
(squawks)
Oh, I see.
Be sure to take good care of it!
(chuckling)
- Hm, she did a pretty good job, didn't she?
- [Hippocrates] Hm.
- Master Hippocrates!
We thank you and your friends for saving us
from such a dangerous situation.
- There is a village nearby called Cockscomb.
This is the mayor and his mother.
(sheep bleating)
(Akane exclaiming)
- Ah, so comfy.
- [Akane] Mm-hm.
(sheep bleating)
- It's so beautiful.
What is this place?
- [Pipo] This is Cockscomb Field.
The village is just beyond it, down the path ahead of us.
(mellow music)
- I feel like I'm in a fairytale land right now.
- For generations, this village has kept sheep
they shear for their wool.
They dye it with the pigment from the flowers in this field
then knits scarves and sweaters with it.
- Wow, that's so interesting.
Ah, it's so cute!
(exclaims)
(chuckles)
Hello, ladies.
- Hello to you too.
- Good afternoon, miss.
- That's such a pretty color.
- Why, thank you.
- It seems so peaceful.
What exactly is this world in danger from anyway?
(imitating bleating)
- It's starting to completely lose its color.
- It is?
- [Pipo] The field isn't the same anymore.
The sheep fleece is getting course, the flowers are wilting.
- [Akane] Why is this happening?
- A lack of water.
- Wait, what?
- Every single thing in this world
has water to thank for granting it life.
- Life means that there is color.
If the water flows properly,
then beautiful colors can thrive but if it doesn't.
- Master Hippocrates.
- Welcome, great alchemist.
- It's really you.
- It's been so long since you returned.
- We're in desperate need of your help.
Master Hippocrates, the whole village agrees,
you're our only hope.
- Especially with Master Kamadoma not around right now.
- I am well aware.
And that is why I found the Goddess of the Green Wind
and brought her here to help us.
(chuckles) - Hm?
- This girl's the goddess?
- Really, the one from that legend?
- The goddess will save us all.
- [Akane] What? This can't be happening.
- [Pipo] About 600 years ago, something similar happened.
There was a drought that caused all the color to go away.
Everyone was in despair.
Just when they thought all was lost,
a girl suddenly appeared like the wind
and saved the village.
She became known as the Goddess of the Green Wind
amongst the people who live there.
It's a legend that's been passed down through the ages.
- No, no, no, no!
I'm just a normal girl,
I don't have the power to save this world.
Let's go home, Chii, I don't wanna be here anymore.
- I'd love it If I could take all these things
back to my shop.
- I'm going home, okay?
I miss my mom and dad!
I wanna see them!
(gasps)
- But we can't go home,
The tower stairs were destroyed
by that armored mouse thing, remember?
- Huh?
- Well, there's still the other exit
but it would take you two days to get there
by carriage at the earliest.
- Do you hear that, Akane?
So let's just stay here and take it easy
for the rest of the night.
(grunting) - Mm-hm.
- [Woman] It's ready.
- Hm.
We prepared a light dinner for you
as a thanks for your kindness.
Right this way, please.
(chuckles)
(calm music)
Please, eat.
Help yourselves to anything.
- What about your mom?
- She had something she needed to take care of.
You don't have to worry, just enjoy your meal.
- Well then, guess it's time to dig in.
- Mm, wait a second.
Is this chestnut soup?
Akane, you have to try it!
- So good.
- I know, isn't it?
- Mm-hm.
- [Chii] Mm!
- Before you ran into us, my mother and I
were on our way to the next town
where there's fair with that sweater.
But then we were attacked.
- You mean that sweater from earlier?
The one you said was stolen?
- Yes, my mother is the best knitter in the entire village.
But recently, it has started to strain her eyes.
After she'd finally finished working on that sweater,
she said it would be her last one.
- Those jerks, they took such a precious sweater?
How awful!
- Lately, sweaters produced from our village
aren't selling very well.
There was a rumor spread about how the color
and quality were bad.
We clearly didn't have poor products at our market
but it didn't matter.
And now, with everyone's livelihood at risk,
my dear sweet mother insisted on taking up knitting again.
(somber music)
With her skill, we thought it's best
to enter the contest at the Sakasatongari Market.
- Huh, good idea.
After all, people come from far and wide
in order to shop there.
If the sweater wins the contest,
then it could be well, it seems.
- Sakasatongari?
- This place here.
- I should mention, that will not be the last of Zan Gu.
- [Pipo] The stuff started happening
when that armored mouse first appeared.
- They're not dangerous, are they?
- Over the past six months now,
they've been popping up
causing all sorts of trouble and violence.
I can only assume they're some scoundrels from Nibi.
- Wait, what's Nibi?
- A town that's best to avoid.
It's not safe to go there.
(ominous music)
(machine whirring)
(clattering)
(exclaiming)
- Hey, you!
(vehicle chugging)
(Doropo grunts)
(Doropo scoffing)
(grunting)
(chuckling)
- Huh?
(shatters)(yells)
(Doropo chuckles)
Little brat!
(grunting)
- I did some nice work out there.
(vehicle chugging)
(ominous music)
(Doropo grunting)
(metal clanking)
(clanking)
(ominous music)
(chuckling)
- You are to keep working.
Is that clear?
(scoffs)
- I can't really make decent steel
with all this junk you keep bringing me.
(clattering)
(hissing)
- Mm, wouldn't wanna be in there.
- So will you be able to finish it in two days?
- Can't make steel with iron I don't have.
- I'll fix that.
I just need you to make it quickly.
(chuckles)
- You know, when you ask for something, you should say.
(grunting)
- You'll pay if you can't complete it.
(ominous music)
(chuckles)
- You'll be in a whole lot of trouble.
- I'll collect the iron for you.
Doropo, let's go.
- [Doropo] Yes, sir.
(light mellow music)
- This area here is Cockscomb
and north of that at the center of the world
is where the Timeless Rain Castle is located.
It's where the king of the Timeless Rain lives
and oversees the whole world.
The royal family has wisely managed the water for centuries
without having to resort to things like petty violence.
- Thanks to that, we've lived peacefully
and have enjoyed full lives.
They've been so very good to us over the years.
- Unfortunately, the most recent king and queen died
one after another about five years ago.
And their son, the prince, was left alone with no family.
Whether it's in public or in the castle,
he hasn't made a single appearance in the past year or so.
- Wait, that long?
Is there a reason?
- According to the rumors that have gone around,
he's really sick and has to stay in bed all day.
- The poor boy must've fallen ill from grief
over his parents' death.
(sighs)
- It is said his power has waned over the last few months.
And as a result, it is affecting the circulation of water.
- Can't you figure out a way to heal him?
I mean you are an alchemist, aren't you?
- But even if we had a way, we can't go to the castle
because of Kamadoma, the wizard.
In this world, wizards and alchemists protect specific areas
and they're not allowed to bother the other
and he kinda lives there, so.
- A turf war then?
You've got to be kidding me.
Well, if that's the case,
then why don't you just ask this Kamadoma guy
to do something about it?
- Chii, stop.
Huh?
- The thing is-
- He fell into a deep slumber when the crisis started
and has not awakened yet.
- What, so does that mean he's dead then?
- No, no, no, that's not it at all.
For three years, Mr. Kamadoma hadn't had a wink of sleep.
However, he suddenly fell asleep
and has been doing so for about a year now.
- Basically, he's hibernating.
- Uh-huh.
- So, like a bear does.
- Oh, yeah, you're right.
- Will you focus?
- Today was such a long day.
I'm feeling real tired.
Can I sleep now?
- You're too relaxed.
- I've not finished my story!
- Oh, right.
Try to hurry it up.
- The reason why I had to bring Akane here
was because I needed her to save the prince.
- Huh? Save the price?
Seriously?
- Ooh, how romantic.
- You be quiet!
- Akane.
This is the Goddess of the Green Wind
who appeared 600 years ago.
As it stands, neither Kamadoma nor I can heal the prince.
Only the goddess is capable of curing him.
(clattering) (ominous music)
(woman gasping)
(chuckles)
- That was a nice grab, Zan Gu.
- [Zan Gu] I require more.
(exclaiming)
- Move it! Get out of our way!
(yelling)
(man bouncing) (man grunting)
- Undo it.
(air blowing) (man groaning)
- Huh?
(boings)
Come on, come on.
(groaning)
- Stop using magic.
You're bad at it.
- Well, that's why I'm practicing.
I wanna get better.
I'm gonna be the best.
- You know, Akane, I really envy you.
I wish that I'd had the chance
to go on an adventure like this when I was your age.
- I just wanna go home already.
- So then you're not going to see the prince first?
- Of course, not.
- But if you don't, Akane, this world will-
- Someone, anyone!
Are you all right?
- [Chii] What's wrong?
- [Popo] My mother.
- Pardon me.
She's been making a sweater.
Pipo, the medicine.
- [Pipo] Right.
- Put her to bed.
- Yes, sir.
- No, please, wait.
I just want to finish this.
I can do it tonight If I keep working.
- You need to rest.
- My eyes are failing and my body is weak now
but I need to complete the sweater
so I can take it to the market.
- Mother, you have to be careful about pushing yourself.
What if your body gives out?
- You are the mayor of this village, son.
Think of its future first before you worry yourself
too much over mine.
- There, this'll help perk you up.
- Popo, the four of us will deliver her sweater for you.
- Please, don't trouble yourself.
It's my responsibility!
- Do not worry.
Just remain by your mother's side.
The Sakasatongari market is quite close
to the Timeless Rain Castle anyway,
so it is no trouble at all.
Akane, you agree?
- Huh, no not at all.
(chimes)
(grunts)
- Do you agree?
- Yeah.
(chuckles)
(rooster crowing)
(mellow music)
(gasps)
(tense music)
(sheep bleating)
You okay?
- Huh?
- What are you doing down there?
- Yoga!
That one was corpse pose.
You wanna come try it?
- Try being a corpse?
Uh-uh.
(grunts)
(chuckles)
(groans)
- This car will be a great help.
I thank you.
- I'm very glad to hear that, Master Hippocrates.
- Here's some food and water.
- How kind of you.
What's in these?
- Warmer clothes for you
since you'll be passing through
one of the more frigid regions.
- [Chii] Oh, neat.
- Please take care
of yourself. - Hey, Mr. Mayor,
is your mother still doing all right?
- She looks very tired but I assure you,
she is resting well now.
There is no need to worry.
I appreciate this.
Please deliver that sweater safely.
- Right.
Just holding it makes me feel so warm and cozy.
And even though it's wrapped right now,
it gives off a nice and gentle aura.
- Thank you so much for your kind words.
I'll let my mother know.
- Now, let's go.
We do not want to miss the contest.
- Well, I finished loading the car for you.
- Hurry and get in.
- Well, what are you waiting for?
Huh, Mr. Chauffeur?
- Huh?
(Chii scoffs)
- [Woman] Travel safely!
- [Chii] Bye!
- Good luck out there!
(sheep bleating)
- See you, fluffy boys.
I'll miss you.
(mellow music)
A nice little town.
- Yeah.
- The scenery is gradually changing.
(chuckles)
(laughing)
It got super cold all of a sudden.
This is so warm and cute.
Nice choice, mayor!
- [Pipo] Wow, it really suits both of you!
- [Both] How adorable!
(groaning)
(laughing)
(wind blowing)
- It's coming.
- What is that?
(tense music)
- Get out!
- I think we should stay put.
- I said out!
(Akane grunting)
That way!
Sit down and curl up!
(clattering)
Finally. (blows)
(Chii sighs)
- That was intense.
- [Pipo] Thank you so much, Chii.
- No problem at all.
- Thanks a lot, Mr. Hippocrates, for protecting us.
- Oh, yes.
(groaning)
(chuckling)
(Akane and Chii grunting)
(engine clattering)
(blows)
- Do sandstorms happen often?
- Here in the Land of the Red Wind,
they're definitely not unusual.
But to be honest, this is the first time
I've seen one that huge.
- It's also drier than normal.
The lack of water circulation
is to thank for that, of course.
(calm mellow music)
We must wait for sunrise.
There is nothing more we can accomplish today.
- You got it!
- Hey, wait.
Does that mean we have to camp in this place?
- Yeah, why?
- Huh?
But that means there's no shower.
Chii, I don't wanna stay here.
- But this is the best part of the adventure!
(chuckles)
(grunts)
(mellow moving music)
- Hey, what are you?
(clattering)
- [Chii] It works! (laughs)
- Nice job, Mr. Hippocrates!
- [Chii] Well, what do you know?
I guess alchemists are pretty useful after all.
- We've wasted enough time!
Hurry up!
- Okay!
Hey, are you ready?
- [Akane] Yup.
(dog snarling and barking)
(vehicle chugging)
(exhaust whistling)
- [Man] What's that?
What's he doing here?
(people exclaiming)
- [Man] Whoa, whoa, whoa, out of the way!
(exhaust whistling)
(people clamoring)
(calm mellow music)
- Seems like the dirty snow is only getting worse.
- We must hurry.
- Ah, it's so warm!
- Pardon me.
Do you mind if my companions and I stay the night?
- You wanna stay, it's gonna cost you.
- Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Hippocrates, the alchemist.
(scoffs)
- Beautiful, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- I thought you guys were a bunch of traveling clowns.
- Clowns?
- There's a huge water shortage.
It's making things pricey.
You can't use the bath or sink but drinking water's fine.
- Honey, stop!
You're talking to Hippocrates, the infamous alchemist!
- Oh, of course, how could I been so oblivious?
We'll arrange our best room
and prepare some hot water as well.
Anything for you, sir.
If you need anything, just ask.
- If you'd be so kind,
could you please prepare a warm meal for these two girls?
- Of course, I'll make a big stew for them!
(mellow music)
(chuckles)
- Mr. Hippocrates, aren't you eating?
- I'm off to find a nearby fuel station.
Make sure you rest after you finish eating.
We'll leave in the morning.
- See you soon, sir.
(gulping)
- You're drinking too much.
- Hey, no alcohol, no life.
- Excuse me?
(vehicle chugging)
Huh?
(ominous music)
- It's those guys!
(children crying)
- Give me something to eat.
- Who the hell are you guys?
- Don't you know the great Zan Gu?
You really gotta keep up with the times, old man.
(gasping)
(children crying)
- What kind of food would you like?
- Whatever human food you have.
- I'll bring something right away.
Thanks for your patience.
- Ah, yeah!
- Water too.
- Water?
But we barely have enough for ourselves,
let alone some to spare.
(crashing)
(groans)
(man gasping)
- Well, that was easy.
(grunting)
(tense music)
- What the hell?
(vehicle whirring)
- Sorry to be a bother.
- [Chii] Are you okay, sir?
- Yes, it's nothing serious.
By the way, you two.
(vehicle clattering)
- What are those scoundrels up to?
- Hm?
- You look exactly like him!
- My brother Voudan already told me the details.
This thing packs a punch.
- I better go smash that dumb well
into a million pieces, Zan Gu!
- Hm?
I'll need payment for my trouble.
- [Zan Gu] Yes, of course.
Use this to your liking.
- Hmm.
This will do just fine.
- [Zan Gu] Can you tell the quality of it
simply by looking?
- There's someone here.
- Zan Gu, what are you up to?
- [Zan Gu] None of your business, alchemist.
This does not concern you.
- When he said well,
he meant the timeless rain well
where the prince does the ceremony.
- The reason our world is suffering
is because of that good-for-nothing price.
Our royal savior is too sick to produce rain.
But we don't need his help if I blow up the well
and the water should start flowing again.
- Ridiculous!
(tense music)
I cannot allow that!
(tinkles)
(smoke blows)
Oh, dear, I let my guard down.
- I thought I said no magic.
- I did it 'cause he was about to do something!
He'll turn back to normal eventually.
(jolly music)
God, so annoying!
(chuckles)
- When you first stepped into the room,
I could already tell you are not people from this world.
- We're from one next to it.
Have you heard about it before?
What do you know?
- Not much.
You see, there have been stories passed down
about your world.
Over the years, it's been said there's a world out there
similar to ours referred to as a mirror world.
- Oh, wow, really?
- However, it ended up diverging at some point.
If I had to take a guess on why,
it's probably because your world changed
when the steam locomotive was invented.
- Are you saying you don't have trains in your world?
- No, we do have them.
It's just that nothing changed here
after they were introduced to us.
We still live our lives in a simple way as we always have.
- But why didn't society advance?
- I suppose the easy answer is we were happy
with things how they were.
(melancholic music)
I love life here and I wouldn't trade it for anything.
I'm content to watch our region's famous snowflakes
fall from the sky.
People would come from all over to see them
but they're almost nonexistent now.
From that alone, I'd say it's obvious something's amiss.
- Hey, Akane, has Hippocrates returned yet?
- Do not worry, I'll go out and find him.
- It's too late to go alone.
I'm coming with you.
- Hold on, I'll go too.
Goodbye, mister.
I really appreciated your story.
Thank you.
(chuckles)
- Well, it looks like he got
the fuel he mentioned, at least.
- Someone said Master Hippocrates brought back the coal
and then left soon after.
- Where the hell is he now then?
(light energetic music)
It feels a lot like spring out here.
I love the breeze.
- This area is called the Time of the Leaf Bud.
Master Hippocrates lives here
so we'll spot his house pretty soon.
I'm actually from this forest too!
- [Chii] Gee, I wonder which one is Hippocrates's house.
- [Pipo] Those big brown things you see
are the home, schools and workplaces of my people.
- [Akane] Wow, they look like the tree's fruit.
- What a perfect house for him.
It looks just as bossy as he does. (chuckles)
- If I could talk right now, I...
Huh?
How indecent of me fall into such brutish gestures.
- If that's his house, do you think maybe he's at home?
- No, I highly doubt it.
That window will be open if he was.
- He's way more irresponsible than I thought.
He dragged us out on this adventure
and now, he's suddenly MIA.
- I did not invite you!
Huh? (whimpering)
- Either way, we need to keep moving forward.
- Why are we in such a rush to get there?
- Tomorrow morning is when the drop mist ceremony
is set to happen.
- [Both] Drop mist ceremony?
- Yes, and we desperately need the goddess
to save the prince so that he's able to be there for it.
That's why you're here.
(melancholic music)
- [Chii] Seems like Zan Gu went through here.
- [Pipo] He was probably making a visit
to the Sakasatongari market.
(birds chirping)
All right, so the council is just over this mountain range.
(sighs)
- Still a long way to go.
- That's right.
And we need to get there before sunset, otherwise...
Huh?
(grunts)
Go on, shoo!
- Ugh, there've been too many flies around since yesterday.
Now, die!
(grunting)
(slow tense music)
(sighs)
I missed the stupid little thing.
- What a terrifying woman.
That was close.
- Oh, yeah!
I just remembered there's a shortcut to the left up ahead!
- Hey, that's where I smacked my shoe!
- Yes, thanks to me!
- Thanks, Chii, couldn't have done it without you.
- Imbecile!
- Careful, Chii!
We're real close to the edge.
- Can't help it.
(exclaiming)
(tense music)
- We'll never make it.
Let's go back.
- Oh, I don't like this.
We have no choice.
- Yes, we do!
Hey, wait!
At least let me out first!
(tense music)
(whimpering)
- Hey, so, is there a boy at school you like?
- What?
- Just trying to chat.
Well, is there?
- No, there isn't.
Too childish.
- Uh-huh, maybe in a few years,
you'll change your mind
and be madly in love with one of them.
- Yeah, fat chance.
- Oh, come on.
Now, your being childish.
Love is love and that's that.
- I just don't wanna end up getting dumped like you do.
(grunts)
- Huh?
- "When we met, he said he loved free-spirited girls.
But now, he say that I'm too free-spirited.
Men are the worst, aren't they, Midori?"
- Oh, that guy.
We'll that was just.
(cracks) (tense music)
(screaming)
(Chii and Akane panting)
I will find happiness, I swear it.
(lively music) (giggling)
It's nice driving on a bridge that doesn't swing.
- It sure is.
- [Pipo] Feel free to breeze through here.
- 'Kay!
- [Akane And Chii] Huh?
(tense music)
(shrieks)
- Oh!
(screaming)
(splashing)
(whimpers)
That was scary!
You mind warning us in advance next time, Pipo?
- Sorry, I didn't think you'd believe me.
- So, what are we supposed to do now?
- [Pipo] We gotta keep moving!
- What? And go where?
- With this, you can breathe and stay dry in the water
just like that.
- Wait a minute, really?
- Come on, follow me!
(Pipo grunting)
(sighs)
(inhales deeply)
- Huh?
- Whoa!
- It's dangerous, Chii.
- I'll go in first.
(groans)
(inhales deeply)
(calm mellow music)
(mellow music)
- [Hippocrates] I shall take a different route and catch up.
The water level has decreased quite a bit here.
(somber music)
- [Man] Do you know where the duke is?
- [Man] He mentioned he was going to see the prince.
(tense somber music)
- Lock it.
- Yes, sir.
- Is the prince still the same?
- Yes.
- It's strange that Ron hasn't been here either.
(gasps)
(sighs)
Honestly, what an irresponsible old wizard.
He's fast asleep while the prince is trapped
within that iron doll.
- [Man] On the day before the drop mist ceremony,
the prince was supposed to return to his original form.
- [Duke] That's what we were told but.
(melancholic music)
(lively fanfare music)
- Now, we're off to the ceremony.
- Where is it?
- Over by the water well in the market.
- Will the prince be there too?
Wouldn't that mean he's been cured?
- No idea.
I guess we'll find out when we see him.
- [Chii] Well we're still going
to Sakasatongari market anyway.
(buzzing)
- Huh? Hold on.
This fly.
- Yes, that's right.
Surely, my apprentice would know me.
(laughing)
This fly's got a funny little mustache on him! (laughing)
(sighs)
- Get rid of it.
It's gross.
- Oh yeah, of course.
Shoo!
(scoffs)
- [Hippocrates] Curse this!
(mellow music)
- [Chii] A cat?
- [Pipo] Master Kamadoma really likes cats
more than anyone I know.
People who come from outside the city
have to pass through this guard house.
- [Akane] Wait, why?
- [Chii] It's like immigration if I had to guess.
- Next!
(jolly music)
Stand right there, please.
(cats groaning)
(groaning)
What's inside this package here?
- Oh, it's a sweater
for the contest happening at the market.
(gasping)
- You're free to pass!
(giggling)
- Wait!
(blowing)
That one's not allowed to pass!
- Gorobeh?
- Is that your cat?
- We'll now start the trial process.
- Wait, a trial?
With Gorobeh?
- You, did I just hear you laugh?
- No, no, no, no, I would never do that.
Oh, that's right.
I have something for you.
Ta-da!
- [Cats] Huh?
- Here you go.
(cats gasping)
(chomping)
Nice, nice. (chuckling)
- [Akane] Definitely a witch.
- Idiots!
Don't let this human tame you!
(cats whimpering)
(munching)
(slurping)
(gasps)
A trial, this is a trial!
(giggling)
You, over there!
- Huh?
- [Chii] Hm?
- You're guilty!
- Wait, but why?
- Hold on a minute.
This girl is a. (yells)
- Guilty?
What in the world could she be accused of?
- She's committed the greatest crime known to our species.
Pulling an innocent cat's tail.
(gasps)
- You did, Akane?
- [Akane] Mm-hm.
- Now then, tail-puller,
you shall be punished for your despicable crime!
(gasps)
- Huh?
(cats grunting) (Chii laughing)
- So, no more tail-pulling?
- No more, I promise!
I'll never do it again!
(grunting)
(tail pops)
(cats grunts)
- Sigil of love!
(Chii giggling)
- You didn't have to laugh so much.
- I guess he won't be teasing Gorobeh anymore.
(fly buzzing)
(mellow calm music)
(Chii laughing)
Isn't this exciting?
Hey, can we take a quick look around?
- The sweater contest is more important right now.
- Come on, Akane, just for a little bit, please?
- What a child.
Where do I even take this anyway?
- Oh, it's over there!
- I'm going to the welcome cat's tent
two flights down, okay?
So stay nearby.
- Yes, ma'am.
(laughing)
- She's fast.
(people chattering)
(Chii laughing)
What's that?
- That's the timeless rain well.
The prince will prepare for the drop mist ceremony
in that blue and white tent there.
- [Akane] Here you go, sir.
This is a great sweater.
It's dyed a beautiful shade of red with Cockscomb flower
and it's really warm.
- Master Kamadoma is still asleep.
The prince remains in that doll.
We have to carry out the ceremony.
No matter the cost.
(gasps)
(creaking)(snoring)
- How in the hell are we supposed to get inside?
- Master Kamadoma!
(Kamadoma groaning)
- Take a look, it's a dried scallop.
It goes really great with a drink or two.
How about we swap?
These wet tissues are useful for everything.
This one here is super warm.
So, mind giving me a freebie?
- This place is enormous.
Where did she run off to?
- [Man] Word has that the prince is definitely here.
- When I first heard the rumor, he was ill,
I started feeling very uneasy.
- Don't worry.
Things will be fine as long as he carries out the ceremony.
- Oh, yes, you're right.
- So, has the ceremony ever been failed
by anyone in the past before?
- Yes, but thankfully, it succeeds more often than not.
- What happens if it fails?
- [Vendor] Hey, that twerp stole from me!
Catch it!
(energetic music)
Damn it!
- It's that guy!
- Please follow him, hurry!
(vendor grunts)
Akane, I think I actually might know him.
- Huh?
- We went to the same school together.
His name was Ron back then.
For some reason, he was always bothering me.
(mellow music)
After graduation?
Well, you see, my biggest goal right now
is to be an alchemist.
- If you're gonna be an alchemist,
then I'm gonna be better than you
as the greatest wizard in the whole world!
- [Pipo] Hm?
I heard a rumor that he became an apprentice
to Master Kamadoma.
So I wonder why he looks like that.
(light fast-paced music)
- There's a guard house up ahead.
We can catch up once they stop him.
Huh?
What the?
(mellow music)
- Cats know how to get a good nappin', don't they?
(light fast-paced music)
(tense music)
- If the armored mouse is here, then-
- [Pipo] Zan Gu must be here too.
- I managed to snatch some good stuff
from the market for us.
It's finally time.
- What are they gonna do?
- I'll read their lips.
Stay still.
- It'll go just as planned.
The armored mouse's new cannon is gonna destroy that well!
(cackles)
- It's gonna be a blast.
What do we do?
They're gonna destroy the timeless rain well.
- Is that bad?
- [Pipo] Yes, that will is essential
for this world's survival.
- Hey, aren't you gonna eat?
I understand how you must be feeling
but we can't change our minds now.
That well is the cause of all this trouble.
You said if it's gone,
we don't have to keep destroying things.
- One of the shining bugs died.
- Hm?
It's fine, we only need like one or two anyway.
(clangs)
What the heck, man?
Did I just make you angry?
Well, you can work it out on your own!
- [Kamadoma] What are you all doing?
- No one is allowed to enter!
(gasps)
Master Kamadoma.
We have been waiting for you.
The prince needs-
- Ah, excuse me.
I do have some good news for you all.
That is not the prince in that bed.
(men gasping)
Such amateur magic.
(puffs)
(men gasps)
The plating has now been removed.
(Chii grunts)
- Where did Akane run off to?
Well, I'm sure she'll come back if I wait here for her.
(sighs)
Man, what a great haul. (chuckles)
- It's impossible.
There's no way we can stop them on our own.
- They may have a cannon
but it will be useless without ammo.
I'll do my best to try and distract them.
You steal the shells while they're not looking.
- Huh?
- There he is!
Perhaps I, huh?
It seems I have a colleague.
It's quite odd for a fly to be that interested in a carrot.
Colleague?
I've almost turned into a proper fly.
Hm?
I should have known this would happen.
The momentum anchor has become an issue.
(somber music)
(engine chugging)
- Hey, what are you doing?
Wait, now?
But the plan was to blast the well
in front of everyone tomorrow!
Are you listening?
- You don't understand me at all, do you?
- You're right, I don't!
That's why I-
- You're just a poor excusable wizard.
All you were able to do is change me into a hideous monster.
- I'm sorry.
I tried my best!
You know that, don't you?
I wanted you to be happy!
I didn't want the prince to hate me!
- [Both] Huh?
(somber music)
- [Prince] Hey you, do something!
You're a wizard, aren't you?
- Yeah, but-
- [Prince] If you are able to make me talk in this form,
then you should be able to change me back!
So, do it!
(tinkles)
- Ah!
(tinkling)(grunting)
- I am not the prince!
I am Zan Gu now!
- I'm pretty sure that Master Kamadoma
will be waking up soon.
He's gonna be mad.
- Then we'll have to destroy Kamadoma too.
- What? That's not even possible!
- Stop, Zan Gu!
(grunting) (tense music)
It's important to you, right?
Please, don't destroy it.
- What do you know?
- If the water doesn't flow,
this entire world is gonna dry up soon.
- It's not your business!
Nobody asked you so shut up, will you?
- Ron, long time no see.
- What are you talking about?
I don't know anybody with that name.
- You don't need to pretend anymore.
If the timeless rain well is destroyed,
there'll be consequences.
(melancholic music)
The forest where we grew up and went to school
will eventually die.
And all our families and friends
will be in despair because of it.
- So what?
Don't talk to me like we're friends.
- But we are, aren't we, Ron?
(Hippocrates sobbing)
- Look at that, it seems the prince and Ron
are closer than we thought.
- Are you certain?
- I'll go get them immediately.
- No, the prince needs to decide
if he wants to come back or not.
However, I should still break the spell on them.
- Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Stop pretending like you know everything, you will twerp!
(zaps)
- Ron!
- Huh?
(energetic music)
- Mr. Hippocrates!
- Akane!
- Master Hippocrates!
(zaps)
(gasps)
(neighing)
- Over here!
It's safer.
Pipo, the carrot!
- Right!
Ron.
Ron!
(yelling)
To the exit!
(whimpering)
(neighing)
(yelling)
(slaps)
(neighing)
(energetic music)
(grunts)
Master Hippocrates!
- Please, turn around.
I want out.
- Just try and stop me.
If you're truly the Goddess of the Green Wind,
then stop me.
(somber music)
(grunting)
Those bugs are scared.
They're nothing, completely insignificant.
And you are the same.
(somber music)
- Stop it!
- We all die eventually.
- But even so!
- Better hold on.
Here comes the wall.
(crashing)
(whimpering)
(people exclaiming)
(crashing)
(ominous music)
Move.
- Do not do this, Zan Gu.
You're making a massive mistake!
(ominous music)
- [Captain] First platoon up the stairs.
Everyone else, hold!
- You were afraid, right?
You were scared of it, rhe ceremony.
It had been decided for you when you were born.
But still, you didn't wanna do it, huh?
- Three generations of men before me
succeeded at their drop mist ceremonies.
(melancholic music)
I knew that one day, it would be my turn to perform it.
But as I got older, my defiance suddenly began to grow.
After my parents died in succession,
I would sometimes sneak out of the castle
and head over Nibi.
One day, I ran into some delinquents
who robbed me of my belongings.
As the drop mist ceremony quickly approached,
my fear and anger only increased.
Kamadoma noticed, he became worried
as the ceremony coincided with his deep sleep
so he confined me inside of a small iron doll.
- If you destroy that well,
will your fear and anger go away?
(light mellow music)
How about I help with the ceremony?
I mean I'm supposed to be the goddess after all.
Totally makes sense, doesn't it?
I'll help you out.
You'll succeed for sure.
You see, I've been through tons of villages and towns
before coming to this world.
So I was surprised to see how amazing it was.
This place, it's so beautiful and filled with color.
We have more advanced technology where I'm from,
which makes things convenient but also inconvenient.
I love the bright colors of the flowers here.
And the stars in the night sky.
But my world neglects all that.
So I'm asking you to please protect this world.
Only you can do it.
I believe in you.
(enchanting moving music)
(gasps)
(mellow moving music)
You're back to being you again.
(all gasp)
- I've finally returned.
- The prince is back to normal!
(melancholic music)
- [Chii] Sorry for leaving you alone.
Were you scared?
- Mm-mm.
Mr. Hippocrates, I've done some thinking
and I think we should give the prince
the momentum anchor, however,
I know it was really difficult to make
but honestly, it's done a lot for me, like give me courage.
I know it's possible to make another one.
After all, you're the best alchemist in this entire world.
- Well, I can only make such a precious item
in my laboratory.
(groans)
- [Akane] I'm sorry, Chii.
- It's fine, get in.
What's that?
- This is a strong fuel made from valuable dragon's dung.
- Dragon's dung?
- Time to fly.
(energetic music)
(grunts)
(engine whirring)
(clanking)
- [Chii] Hm?
(giggles)
- My lab is upstairs.
- I lit the fireplace for you.
(window clacking)
(mysterious ambient music)
- Keep stirring.
Keep it slow.
Now, take in the light of the moon.
Then say a small prayer in your mind, deep within your mind.
- Right.
(light mellow music)
- Master Hippocrates.
- Be sure to keep it steady.
(energetic music)
- Hey, I forgot to ask.
Where were you after the snowy town?
(exhaust blazing)
- We have arrived.
- Master Kamadoma, it's time to change your clothes.
(Kamadoma groans)
- Will you be all right?
- [Guard] Stop!
Master Hippocrates.
- Pardon me.
- What is it?
- Wait!
Akane.
- Forgive me, I'm a little late.
This momentum anchor's for you.
May I?
- Of course.
(mysterious music) (gasps)
- I have a matching one.
If you feel like you wanna run,
this will help you move forward in any situation.
It's power helped me get to the castle.
Also that I could meet you, see?
- I'll trust it.
- The mantle of the goddess, give it to her.
- [Woman] Yes, sir.
(mellow orchestral music)
- I was wondering,
what happens if he fails the drop mist ceremony?
- Then he will lose his life.
- Huh?
- But by performing that drastic sacrifice,
he will ensure that our world
will be filled as water until the next generation.
The royal rain family has been tied to water
for many, many years.
And as the prince, I'm sure that boy is well aware of this.
(suspenseful music)
- You're scared?
- Mm-mm.
(tinkling)
(sighs)
(spectators murmuring)
- Something went wrong. - What's going on?
(gasps)
(wind blowing)
- Hm, what?
- The ceremony was a failure.
Now, I must dedicate my body to the well.
Huh?
Wait a second, but that's so cruel!
Hey, tell him to stop!
- Are you suggesting cruel things don't happen
for the greater benefit of many in your world?
- It's fine, Akane.
Thank you.
Farewell.
- Akane!
(both grunting)
(creaking)
(swooshing)
(gasps)
(tinkling)
- Well done, prince, good work.
I saw your admirable resolution as the rain king.
Congratulations.
Show your gratitude to that girl.
Reward her bravery.
- Yes!
(swooshing)
- [Woman] They're here!
They're alive!
- [Woman] What happened?
- She's still alive!
- I won't jump again, so don't worry.
- [Man] How's that possible?
- Wait, Akane, let me go.
The ceremony!
(woman vocalizing)
(uplifting foreign language music)
(Prince grunting)
(people cheering)
(panting)
(mellow foreign language music)
- If you look on that wall,
you'll see the hand print of the goddess from 600 years ago.
(Akane grunting)
- Aw, and I thought we fixed it.
- It's strange how the goddess always seems to trip there.
- I should return the momentum anchor.
- There's no need.
- Huh?
- You haven't had the anchor for quite some time.
I gave you an opportunity but in the end,
you moved forward of your own free will.
- So you're admitting to being a fake then?
- How rude!
What's more important than the item
is that it's user possessed as a strong mind.
- Hm, that just sounds like a bad excuse to me.
Well, you ready?
- Uh-huh.
- I have a favorite ask you.
(giggles)
Muah!
Thank you so much.
- No problem.
Muah!
- Master Hippocrates!
- Huh?
- Aren't you so jealous?
- Hardly!
(laughing)
Akane, for you.
This is a gift that was made for the guest
of the king of rain.
- It's beautiful, thank you.
- Pipo.
(sighs)
- We've been out here for three days.
Midori must be pretty worried about us.
- Yeah, you're right.
- You needn't worry about that.
Because one day in our world,
it's only about an hour in your world.
- Wait, is that true?
So then, next time we come here.
- Pipo and I will be gone.
This world, however, will likely not change much.
That much I know.
(mellow string music)
That music will guide you both home.
Now, go forward and move quickly.
Be sure to never look back.
- [Pipo] Take care!
I'll miss you!
- [Akane] We appreciate everything you've done for us.
Thank you!
(energetic string music)
- Oh, so that's where you've been.
- Hey, Chii, I'm going home.
- Yeah, sure, see you later.
And who might you be?
- I was here a few hours ago.
You recommended this lamp to me, remember?
When I used it at home, it worked like a charm.
So I'd really like to buy it now if that's okay.
Oh, you left those sitting around
and I figured they needed water.
You didn't come back right away
so I went and found that vase in your kitchen.
- You can have it.
Just look after my shop for a while as payment.
I'm taking a nap.
- Hey, wait.
- Play something that'll help me fall asleep.
(mellow music)
(mellow orchestral music)
- Mom, I'm home!
- [Midori] Welcome back.
- I love you, Mom.
Thank you for the amazing birthday present.
- Huh?
- By the way, Mom.
The world's huge, huh?
- Yes, it really is.
- On top of that, it's beautiful.
- Even more than you know.
(melancholic music)
- [Akane] It's been a long time
since I felt this close to my mom.
After all that's happened,
I can't help but feel like my world's expanded, maybe.
(lively foreign language music)
Mayu Matsuoka as Akane Uesugi
Anne as Chii Uesugi
Kumiko Aso as Midori Uesugi
Nao Toyama as Pipo
Keiji Fujiwara as Zan-Gu
Akiko Yajima as Dropo
Masachika Ichimura as Hippocrates
Original Story by Sachiko Kashiwaba, “Chika Shitsu Kara no Fushigi Na Tabi” (A
Strange Journey from the Basement), published by Kodansha Bluebird Paperbacks
Screenplay: Miho Maruo
Character / Visual Design: Kuvshinov Ilya
Art Director: Takashi Nakamura
Music: Harumi Fuuki
Subtitles: Andrew P. Kirkham
& Kazumi Kirkham
Director: Keiichi Hara
(Akane giggles)