[GROSSULAR] A coup
d'état in this day and age?
What an awfully
fascinating bit of gossip.
[MAUVE]
Yes, sir.
I presume this
is your rationale
for conducting surprise audits?
With all due respect,
that is our agency's purpose.
Indeed.
Leave no stone unturned.
Of course.
So it's only rumor?
[GROSSULAR] Your report will
be taken under advisement.
[GROSSULAR]
That said...
I assure you this
kingdom is at peace.
And ACCA is the
symbol of that peace.
[LOTTA] You'll be in the
Western Sector today?
Can you stop by Mugimaki
for some tomato bread?
See, this is why you
shouldn't get tanked.
[TEACHER 2A] Okay, kids,
eyes on the tour guide!
[GUIDE 2A]
Hey, Acca.
What can you tell me about ACCA?
Come on...
you learned all about it
in social studies, right?
[ACCA MASCOT]
Huh? Um, well...
Then let's begin
at the beginning.
It was established
ninety-nine years ago.
But an entire
century before that,
the kingdom we
live in was divided
into thirteen
separate countries.
These were united by
someone very important.
Can anyone tell me who?
[ACCA MASCOT]
His Majesty's great-grandpa!
Yes!
Things went smoothly at first,
but before long we
entered the turbulent era
of His Majesty's father...
...when the twelve districts
rose up in revolt against DMw
and attempted to
overthrow the government.
[GUIDE 2A]
Pretty awful, huh?
Fortunately, His Majesty's
father was a peaceful man.
Instead of meeting the
rebellion with force,
he held talks
with representatives
from every territory
and fashioned the
system we have now,
where districts are autonomous!
First the capitol was moved.
After that, a central
congress was created,
and finally, a special
independent civilian
organization was founded.
And that organization
was none other than ACCA.
Do you know where
the name comes from?
A species of bird
that went extinct
the year ACCA was established.
[ACCA MASCOT]
The acca bird!
That's right!
The noble acca bird,
universal symbol
of peace and harmony
that watches over us all!
Y'know, next year,
my kids'll be on that tour.
Wow, where does the time go?
[RAIL] Where are those
fire trucks headed?
North Sector.
Damn it.
[siren wailing]
[RAIL]
Just my luck.
If I'm gonna set the bastard up,
I need a fire in
our jurisdiction.
[JEAN]
Audit complete. We're good.
That didn't take very long.
They never do with
competent branches.
[siren wailing]
Another arson?
[GRUS]
No. Robbery, looks like.
Apparently, a
tobacco store got hit.
[JEAN]
Lotta tobacco theft lately.
Well, it's no surprise with
the taxes on those things.
Not everyone gets theirs
for free, Deputy Chief.
[phone rings]
[GRUS] Speaking of which,
did you find your lighter?
Nope.
Hold on a sec.
Scratch that.
[DISPATCH 2A] Suspect #1
is fleeing north on foot
through Block Eight.
We've lost the other one.
Where'd the rookie run off to?
[AGENT 2B]
I dunno.
[RAIL'S PARTNER]
Son of a--
Why the hell's he
keep disappearing?
[THIEF KID 2A whimpering]
[THIEF KID 2A]
Please, I--
[THIEF KID 2A whimpering]
[RAIL]
Stupid brat.
Tsk. Kids always make
a trial complicated.
[RAIL] Leave what you
took and get outta here.
Don't make me say it twice!
[THIEF KID 2A]
Yes, sir!
[yells]
[JEAN] What happened to not
smoking those on the street?
It's a filthy habit.
Agent Rail.
The arrests you've racked up
in the last three months
would've made you a
shoe-in for promotion.
Except on four occasions,
you've been caught
fencing confiscated goods.
You're evidently too comfortable
with the criminal element.
You wouldn't be cooking
up anything illegal
with my lighter, now would you?
Oh, look at that.
You've taken the ACCA
entrance exam; good for you.
[RAIL] Is Internal Affairs
on my case?
What?
No clue.
This is from a private source.
[RAIL]
Yeah, that's right.
Have your fun.
I'm just a workin' stiff.
Not like you'd understand
putting your blood,
sweat and tears into
something only to get squat!
Why should I work my
ass off if guys like you
with money and connections just
get everything handed to 'em?
It was drop a rank
or get fired.
Only way to save my job
was to join a branch
I couldn't care less about.
But why am I tellin' you?
[JEAN]
Don't be that way.
Those're pricey.
[RAIL]
Are you even listening?!
Your anger's misplaced, Rail.
I don't have money
or connections.
Don't gimme that.
You live in a palace.
Only because I'm the landlord.
Well at least I
feel better knowing
why you think you hate me.
You gonna get off my back
now that you know
I'm just a "workin' stiff," too?
I think we're done.
Agent?
Except...
I would like my lighter.
[JEAN]
Don't worry.
Internal Affairs doesn't
know you tried to frame me.
Still, might wanna be
more careful next time.
Think I owe you one?
[JEAN]
I'm with Inspection.
My job is monitoring HQ staff
at all the regional branches.
The messes branch staff
get themselves into...
...aren't my problem.
Let's see.
I know I need some tomato bread.
Usual.
I didn't realize you lived in
this neighborhood, Otus.
Hello.
Um... I don't, actually, uh...
I'm just here for my sister.
[MAUVE]
Ah. Where's your next audit?
[JEAN]
JumMku District.
[MAUVE] Yes, their bread
leaves quite the impression.
Oh, try the new fast food joint,
Basswood, if you can.
I hear it's all the rage.
So where's your
next audit gonna be?
Sorry, I heard that's
what you were doing.
Not anymore.
The Five Chief
Officers nixed it.
If I didn't know better, I'd
swear you just cracked a smile.
No, ma'am, I--
[MAUVE] Well, best of luck
out there, Deputy Chief.
[NINO]
How's Mushroomhead?
Saw her chatting you up?
[NINO]
Y'found it.
For something that
symbolizes peace,
you sure do battle
to keep track of it.
Oh, yeah, I meant to tell ya.
[NINO]
Hm?
I get the feeling I'm
being watched lately.
You think someone's inspecting
the Inspection Department?
No problem. I'll look into it.
[RAIL'S PARTNER]
Nice work, rook.
He'd have probably
set the condo on fire
if we hadn't caught him.
Well, yeah.
That is kinda how arson works.
This puts you in that
Otus guy's debt.
[RAIL chuckles]
Speak of the devil,
I think that's his
sister over there.
She's a knockout!
C'mon. Let's go.
[NINO]
Hey.
[LOTTA]
Nino!
Chocolate sundae.
[LOTTA] Jean's just never been
much of a drinker, y'know?
Next time you two
go out on the town,
make sure he takes it easy.
Yeah, course.
What'cha up to?
Breaking down property expenses.
Heh. Aren't you
marriage material.
More like a widow of business.
Oh.
My future husband's
gonna need to be handy.
Even if Jean quits ACCA, he
can't run the building alone.
He won't quit anytime soon.
[WAITRESS 2A]
Here you go.
That doesn't make sense.
He hates working for
the Inspection Department.
Why wouldn't he walk
away given the chance?
Besides, being a landlord's
much more stable.
And don't even get me started
on what they're paying him.
He talks about this
stuff with you, right?
Not a lot, actually.
[LOTTA]
Get him to open up.
I'll try.
How's work been going?
[NINO]
Keepin' me on my toes.
I'm following a hot lead, so
there's some legwork involved,
but those are the breaks.
That's the life of an
investigative journalist,
I suppose.
Is the money any good?
[chuckles]
Is that all you care about?
[LOTTA] The three of us should
do dinner sometime soon.
[NINO]
Home-cooked?
[LOTTA]
No.
[NINO]
I dunno.
Tell ya what; pick a time
when work's less crazy
for you two, an' I'll cook.
[NINO]
Now you're talkin'.
[LILIUM] More than likely,
the rumors of a coup d'état
will turn out to be just that.
[PASTIS] Perhaps, but
Director General Mauve
taking direct
action is worrisome.
[SPADE]
I concur.
It's not like her
to be fooled.
She's not a woman I'd advise
leading around by the nose.
[LILIUM]
You make a valid point.
Chief Officer Grossular,
were you unaware of these rumors
before the Director
General acted on them?
[LILIUM] I thought stirrings
of an imminent rebellion
were what changed
your mind with regards
to the Inspection Department.
[GROSSULAR]
They are.
You see, I have good reason
to believe the rumors are true.
Certain information
has come to light
that gives me cause for concern.
There is in fact a coup d'état
plot in the works, comrades.
And Deputy Chief Jean Otus
is directly involved.
[SPADE]
You're referring to the smoker?
[GROSSULAR]
Come, now.
Surely I can't be the only one
among us troubled by him.
Director General Mauve
has been ordered
to end her investigations.
This is a matter best handled
by the Five Chief Officers.
[LILIUM] You don't suspect
he's in contact with dissidents
in outlying districts.
His audit rounds would certainly
give him access to that element.
Then again, we have
to take into account
the fact that he's
requested a transfer
from Inspection
on multiple occasions.
[GROSSULAR]
Oh?
In point of fact there's no
actual record of the man
ever having submitted
such a request.
[JEAN] Don't feel like
I'm being watched anymore.
Thank you, Nino.
[GROSSULAR] We forestalled
Inspection's disbandment
and had him monitored.
But he's far more cunning
than anticipated.
The agents assigned to
his case must be exceptional.
There's a deep-cover
agent with Internal Affairs.
I believe he'd be an asset here.
Undercover operatives fall
under our jurisdiction.
Their true identities
are known only to us.
Neither Internal Affairs
nor any other department
has access to their records.
This includes
Deputy Chief Otus.
[knocking]
Come in, please.
[GROSSULAR]
This is Agent Crow.
Moving forward, he'll handle
surveillance in this case.
[DESK CLERK 2A]
Very good.
We have you in room 406.
What time would you like
your breakfast delivered, sir?
Don't bother.
I'll just come down.
We'd prefer to bring it up.
Fine. Eight, then?
[JEAN]
There's been some mistake.
I didn't book a suite.
[DESK CLERK 2A] We were
given orders to provide you
with that room.
[KORURI]
Oh! Uh...
Morning, Deputy Chief!
[JEAN]
Good morning.
[JEAN] Where's a good place
to eat once I'm done?
[KORURI]
Uh, about that, sir...
[BRANCH DIRECTOR 2A]
Otus.
Welcome to JumMku, my friend.
Thank you, sir.
And thank you very much
for the nice hotel room.
It's our pleasure.
If you have any problems,
just let me know.
[KORURI] Our main systems
have been on the blink
since this morning.
Always the way, huh?
We're doin' our best to bring
'em back online, though.
[JEAN]
That server belongs in a museum.
We should have something
figured out by tonight.
You guys wanna do
lunch at Basswood?
I hear it's good.
It'll be on me.
[GROUP]
Huh?!
[STAFF MEMBER 2A ] The produce
in this district is 2.5 times
larger than the
national average!
So most of what we
eat 'round these parts
is bigger than the human head.
But what sets Basswood
apart is the flavor!
Trust me, the food
will blow your mind!
Now I see.
You've all definitely put
on a few in the six months
you've been out here.
The kids in this
district are giants now.
The average height's
gone up again.
It's at darn near seven feet!
Really?
Would you like to
try the cake? Enjoy!
I feel oddly compelled.
Wow. You lost weight.
Uh, hey.
You working a story?
Sorta. Stopped by on
a local's recommendation.
Never thought I'd run
into you here, though.
Thanks, by the way.
That feeling that someone
was tailing me?
It's gone.
Oh, good, glad to hear.
Not that you had a
lot to worry about.
Just one of Mushroomhead's pals.
Ah. Makes sense.
He's probably moved on by now.
Thanks for havin' my back.
Hey, nothin' new, right?
Guess not.
You wanna meet up
for dinner tonight?
Sure. I'll call you.
Cool. See ya later.
[KORURI] Afraid I've got
some bad news, sir.
Looks like they're not gonna
be able to get the system
back up today.
[JEAN]
Huh. Right.
Well then, we'll go just
go somewhere else.
I'm really sorry.
Hey, guys.
Any luck?
[KORURI]
They're, uh...
Still on the fritz, sir.
Uh-huh. Big shock.
Yeah, I know.
Any backup systems?
Yeah.
But... we don't run 'em every
day unless there's a problem.
So we'll have to manually
enter any missing data
if you wanna create a log.
[KORURI gasps]
Let me help.
[OWL] Sorry to drag
you here after school.
I'm sure you're busy.
My staff requested sweets
from this cafe specifically,
but I couldn't find it
to save my life.
Well, if you want
cake with nuts,
I've heard this is the place.
I've been wanting to try
'em out for a while now.
Gah! So good.
DMwis famous for
this sort of thing.
His Majesty's said
to have a fondness
for these rustic baked goods.
Not quite sure where
I heard that though.
Yeah? I should go sometime.
You know, I've never
actually been there myself.
I feel terrible working
Jean as hard as I've had to.
All thirteen districts
in just six months.
I'd be more than happy
to lighten his load
and do a few myself, but...
Honestly, I'm not
a man for travel.
Prone to motion sickness.
You understand.
Always have been.
Oh, hey, don't feel bad.
My brother loves making
the audit rounds.
No worries.
Ugh, the hell are they
even talking about?
Why couldn't she
come here by herself?
God, she's gorgeous.
[KORURI]
Here ya go.
[JEAN]
Thanks.
No, no, no,
Deputy Chief, thank you.
Really, it would've taken us
forever to knock this out
on our own, trust me.
[JEAN]
Home stretch.
Almost there.
[KORURI]
Awesome!
[JEAN panting]
Sorry.
[NINO]
Hit a snag?
Yeah.
[NINO]
Cheers.
What about you?
Just about done.
That must be nice.
Hey, I could use a hand
if you wanna change jobs.
I'm kinda over travel right now.
Besides, we both know
you're a lone wolf.
Poor guy.
I bet I'm your only
friend in the whole world.
Not like work gives me a
whole lot of free time, y'know.
What little I have I spend
on my motorcycle and with you
gettin' three sheets
to the wind.
Yeah, well I guess some
things never change.
We've known each other what,
fifteen years now?
[NINO]
Yep.
It's odd.
You'd think I'd know
more about you.
Oh?
[JEAN] You've been that
way since high school--
always doin' your own thing.
Standin' out from the crowd.
[NINO]
What?
You tryin' to say I'm
standoffish or somethin'?
'Cause comin' from you,
that's hilarious.
[NINO] You an' I were
both a couple a' loners.
Probably why we
got along so well.
And you're damn right some
things never change, my friend.
Heh.
When you first joined ACCA,
I was positive you'd just become
another stuffed shirt, but nope.
Same ol' Jean.
Inspection's definitely got
its share of agents like that.
[NINO]
You hate it, don't you?
Be honest.
Meh. It's just not my thing.
Then why don't you
tell 'em to shove it?
There some special
reason you can't quit?
[JEAN]
Reason? Like what?
[NINO]
That's what I'm askin' you.
You complain about it
all the time, Jean.
But you're still
in that uniform. So?
[JEAN sighs]
Yeah, I know.
[NINO]
First time I've seen that brand.
What, these?
They're new to me, too.
Want some wine?
[NINO] You're not still buying
presents for someone, are you?
[JEAN]
We've had this talk.
[NINO]
Oh, yeah. Right.
[NINO] Subject Jean Otus
received cigarettes
at some point while
visiting the JumMku District.
Also, for the record, putting
a tail on me is ridiculous.
I've said it before
and I'll say it again:
No one knows the game like I do.
Is it that much to ask
that you have a little faith
in my skill set?
[NINO] Took you long enough
to make up your mind,
one way or the other.
Naturally.
You are a personal
friend of Jean Otus,
Agent Crow.
He saw your man
coming from a mile away.
Felt himself being watched
the moment he got out of bed.
I'd have never made a
rookie mistake like that.
Only a matter of time
before the other Chief Officers
realize the rumors
aren't just rumors.
[NINO]
I'll call back later.
He's completely oblivious to the
fact I'm keeping tabs on him.
Has been for the
past thirty years.
[ATRI squeals]
Oh my gosh,
you brought potato chips!
Where you headed off to next?
Suitsu.
In a couple of weeks.
Least you get a break
before you have to go.
[NINO]
Ah.
So this is where the little
rendezvous happens.
[door opens]
[MAUVE] We have to
stop meeting like this.
[JEAN]
Director General.
Would you like some?
[MAUVE] Oh.
From JumMku District, no less.
Bought too much;
didn't wanna waste it.
I can take it off your hands.
Thank you.
[MAUVE]
Otus.
Are you free this weekend?
Maybe for dinner?
[NINO]
Next time on ACCA:
Thirteen-Territory
Inspection Department:
"The Swirling Smoke
of Rumors in the Castle."
[NINO sighs] Jean wouldn't know
the truth if it slapped him
in the face.
But you know?
That's exactly how I like it.