I can't believe you
actually brought us goodies
on your day off, Deputy Chief!
[JEAN] Hey, y'know if
there's a dress code for Vert?
Over on Seventh Avenue?
[KNOT]
Let's see.
Oh, that fancy
restaurant from Koror
that opened one here.
I'd wear a tie.
Figured.
[PASTIS]
Seems farfetched.
You don't buy it, do you?
[SPADE]
It's not impossible.
[PINE]
What do you think?
Well, it's not as though
any of us can accuse Groschler
of being a team player.
Giving him sole authority
over Agent Crow
is a disaster waiting to happen.
[LOTTA] I don't know,
some colleague.
They're having dinner tonight.
I was really looking forward
to some quality time
with the three of us.
So, uh... did you
talk to him at all?
Hmm? Oh, no, I forgot.
[LOTTA]
Ugh. I swear.
It's like you and him
are the same person.
[NINO]
Yeah. My bad.
Just don't forget
next time, huh?
I wanna know why he won't quit.
[NINO]
Yes ma'am.
Don't get your hopes up
it'll do any good, though.
He's in for life.
Sorry for dragging you
out to such a stuffy place.
I was craving a
taste of my homeland.
[JEAN] So glad I held off
filing that transfer.
[NINO] What's the verdict
on that DMw cake?
All hype, or what?
[LOTTA]
No! It's delicious!
And they don't skimp on
the nuts, lemme tell ya.
[NINO]
Who'da thought.
DMwDistrict, wow.
Wish I could go sometime.
[doorbell rings]
Package for ya.
[LOTTA]
Coming!
Thank you very much.
Nino!
What's that?
Gimme a hand?
This thing must weigh a ton.
As you wish, Your Highness.
[NINO]
All the way from Fasu.
It's addressed to Jean,
so it's bound to be a gift
from someone at work.
Aw, score!
[LOTTA] I can make
potatoes au gratin!
You ever soak the
cheese up with a nice,
thick slick of bread?
It's the best!
Jean'll be thrilled!
What?
[NINO] Nothing.
Some things never change.
Just sayin' you still
get carried away.
[MAUVE]
Not a tee-totaller, I hope.
No, I just don't really,
you know.
Have all you like.
It's a private room;
no one'll see but me.
[JEAN]
I should be so lucky.
Never mind.
Better you have command
of your faculties.
Tonight's one I want
you to remember.
This isn't a social call so
much as a business meeting.
I believe it's customary
for prospective recruits
to be wined and dined, yes?
Of course if word got out
I was putting the moves
on some high profile official,
there'd be hell to pay.
But I can count on
you not to bat an eye,
even though for all
intents and purposes,
you're quite the chess piece.
Something wrong?
[JEAN]
No.
[MAUVE]
You are a lightweight!
Oh, that won't do at all.
Here, have my water too.
[JEAN]
I'll be fine, I promise.
Smooth one, Jean.
[MAUVE]
So, the coup rumors.
[JEAN]
Beg your pardon?
Someone hasn't had
his ear to the ground.
[JEAN]
Oh.
I mean, I've heard
stuff, I guess.
Just talk.
When there's talk of revolution,
I make a point of
paying attention.
In this particular instance
I've done some digging.
Afraid the rumor mill
has it right for once.
Chief Officer Groschler
doesn't agree.
My investigation was suspended.
Jean, I need your help.
You know the districts--
they're your beat.
If you hear anything more than
talk, I need to know about it.
Off the record.
A coup d'état? Really?
Sorry, but is something
like that even possible
in such a peaceful country?
Peaceful?
Ha! Now you're just
having fun with me.
[MAUVE]
You really don't know?
[SCHWAN]
Oh, please.
A coup d'etat?
That's ridiculous.
[MAGIE]
With respect, Highness,
if we ignore the rumors
until they become true,
the kingdom is finished.
So dramatic.
We'll be fine.
I promise you'll eat those
words once I'm crowned.
[PASTIS] We have to
attend Prince Schwan's
coming-of-age ceremony?
Evidently.
Seems a little last-minute.
"Attendance of the Five
Chief Officers is required,
plus the Director General,
the Deputy Director General,
and two officers
from Inspection."
[OWL] I hate to do
this to you, Jean.
Especially right before you
leave for Suitsu District.
Sorry.
I'd be happy to
join you, of course,
but me and planes...
motion sickness.
[OWL] Perhaps Knot would like
to fill in on my behalf?
[MOZ]
Huh?
[ATRI]
Aw...
If you're not busy.
[KNOT] Uh, well,
I do have the kids, sir.
[JEAN] Won't they be
on winter break, though?
Maybe you can get your
folks to look after them.
[KNOT]
I s'pose so, yeah.
It'll only be two days, right?
All right, fine.
I'm convinced.
DMwCastle.
Should give me a cool
story for the rugrats, huh?
His Majesty failed
to produce a son,
so there's no direct heir.
He sired only daughters,
as I'm sure you know,
the youngest of whom gave
birth to Prince Schwan.
According to the
laws of succession,
he is next in line
for the throne.
[JEAN] Prince Schwan is
coming of age soon, right?
[MAUVE] Yes, at which point
his status as heir-apparent
will be official.
The moment he assumes power,
this nation will be in trouble.
The kid's a complete idiot.
[JEAN]
You don't mince words.
I believe those
plotting the coup
include powerful figures
in outlying districts
who would rather die
before they'd see him
wear the crown.
Even ACCA branch
staff is suspect.
I'm aware this goes beyond
the scope of your position.
I'd consider it
a personal favor.
[JEAN] You're not kidding
around, are you?
[MAUVE]
Not at all.
The thought ever cross
your mind that I might say no?
I'm not one for defying
the orders of my superiors.
The will of the Five Chief
Officers is sacrosanct.
But when push comes to shove,
ACCA was founded by
and for the people.
It's our job to
protect the interest
of this nation's citizens.
We can't stand by while
a brutal shift in power
rips them apart.
We are not the "symbol of
peace and harmony," Jean.
We're the "defenders
of law and order"
without whom peace
wouldn't be possible.
You're among the few who
understands that, I can tell.
We're cut from the same cloth.
We both believe in order.
Now, will you help me?
[JEAN]
You make some good points.
I'm happy to help.
[JEAN] How do you say
no to a smile like that?
[NINO]
Go home, Jean. You're drunk.
[JEAN] Yeah, 'cause you
keep pouring, jackass.
[NINO chuckles]
So is this turning
into somethin'?
You gonna see her again?
[JEAN]
Yep.
Good thing you didn't give
'em your walkin' papers, huh?
Nice one.
Yep!
[NINO] I'll be in DMwp  same time as you love birds.
Covering the festivities.
You know how folks
love their royals.
See you at the ball, Romeo.
Ah. There we go.
Come on. They're about to
call our boarding group.
[LOTTA]
'Kay!
[MAGIE]
Your Highness.
I have advised the guests
to wear formal attire
for tomorrow's ceremony.
Good.
ACCA uniforms are
such an eyesore.
Historic moments want
a touch of glamour,
don't you think?
Can't have grandfather
announcing his retirement
to a bunch of proles
dressed for a funeral.
Picture it, Magie!
Me, my succession
claim formalized,
my adoring public captivated,
hanging on every word!
When asked to make a speech,
the first thing
I'll say will be,
"On this, my hour of ascension,
I declare ACCA to be defunct!"
Symbol of peace my left foot.
We're the people's inspiration,
not those glorified bureaucrats.
Don't you agree?
[MAGIE] You may be putting
the cart before the horse.
[SCHWAN]
Watch your tongue!
Why would Grandfather
invite so many people
if not to promote me?
Alas, the President
of the Privy Council
devised the guest list,
not His Majesty.
[SCHWAN]
Whatever!
It amounts to the same thing!
Now shut up, Magpie!
[SCHWAN]
When I am king,
and mark me, I shall be,
after dissolving ACCA I will
abolish the central congress!
The Privy Council then falls
to the crown's jurisdiction.
That's how it works, isn't it?
Eh? Well?
Speak, damn you!
Indeed.
You know you're only here
because you're pretty!
[MAGIE]
You flatter me, Your Highness.
If I may, you've neglected
an important point.
The Privy Council President.
You're an imbecile.
He will follow grandfather
into retirement.
The man dare not
tarnish his virtue.
He's paid it too
much lip service.
[POCHARD clears throat]
They've requested formal attire?
I assume that comes
from the Prince.
Who else would pull
a stunt like this?
He calls the tune, we dance.
Mind if I join you?
Please.
[MAUVE]
Thank you, sirs.
All the branch chiefs
have arrived.
I understand the
evening's program entails
our dining with them.
Should we include
Inspection staff?
I think not.
Yes, sir. Understood.
[PINE]
Strange.
Why is their department on
the guest list for tomorrow?
[MAUVE] They know the
districts intimately.
The royal family can't
afford to ignore them,
especially given the
stirrings as of late.
As of right now,
the crown has issued no
request for a formal meeting
with Inspection.
But that doesn't mean it
won't field an informal one
during tomorrow's celebration.
So the crown now stoops
to dignify hearsay. Huh.
Well, better safe than sorry.
If only we could all be
as impervious to gossip
as the Five Chiefs.
Imagine, all thirteen district
chiefs breaking bread
with central congress,
ACCA branch chiefs,
and of course yourselves.
That's a lot of political
heft in one place
for His Highness's
coming-of-age ceremony.
Makes one wonder, doesn't it?
Maybe something
special's in store.
[QUALM] That's the overview
of the day's events,
Your Majesty, from
ceremony to celebration.
[KING]
Mmm.
[QUALM] Does your august
self see any problem
with giving the
address tomorrow?
Tell me, Qualm, have you ever
known this dotty old man
to shrink from public speaking?
Never once, Your Majesty.
[KING] Will there be
sweets on the menu?
From the finest
confectioners in the kingdom.
[KING]
Any fruit?
[QUALM]
Freshly picked.
[STAFF MEMBER 3A]
Excuse me, Mr. President?
It's been given me to
understand Prince Schwan
intends to speak tomorrow.
What would you advise?
I fail to see any harm.
As he desires.
Things are going
exactly as planned.
Let the boy do what
he likes for now.
[MAUVE]
Jaw-dropping spread, isn't it?
Are you from around here?
[LOTTA]
Um, actually...
[NINO]
Actually, she's my assistant.
We're here for the story.
Ah, yes.
She's gorgeous!
You still runnin'
on fumes, sir?
[MAUVE]
The bread's to die for.
You're eating all that yourself?
We can go halfsies.
[GUARD 3A]
Hear ye, hear ye!
His Majesty the King!
[KING] Words cannot express
the joy at seeing one's
precocious little grandson
grow to be a fine,
stalwart young man.
That I may bear witness to
it in the company of all you
is a gift in my old age.
You honor this family and I
thank you for it sincerely.
[SCHWAN]
Is that all, Grandfather?
[KING]
Mm-hmm.
[SCHWAN]
But my ascen--!
[KING]
Hmm?
[MAGIE] His Majesty does not
appear to be abdicating.
[SCHWAN growls]
[CROWD gasps]
You wish to speak,
Your Highness?
Please, by all means.
[SCHWAN]
My heart is glad this day.
Indeed I did not expect
to be honored so.
That is to say, thank you.
I am grateful to those of you
who represent
our loyal subjects.
Without you we would fall.
This kingdom knows prosperity.
May it continue
to thrive forever.
[SPADE]
That was terrible.
So no announcement
of abdication after all.
Then what earthly
reason is there
for having so many of us here?
I'm just gonna have
a quick smoke.
Mind if I step outside?
[GUARD 3B]
Are you serious?
[SCHWAN]
I'll allow it.
[GUARD 3B]
But Your Highness...
Am I or am I not
the guest of honor today?
[SCHWAN]
Stepping out for a cigarette.
What a sense of humor.
Tobacco is scarce enough
in our nation these days.
The Privy Council President
doesn't care for smoking.
He frets over the habit's
ill effects on my grandfather.
Such a Samaritan.
But this man...
[MAGIE] She fits the criteria
for your taste in women,
Highness.
[SCHWAN]
Find out who she is.
Hey, that girl kinda
looks like Lotta.
[JEAN]
Hm?
What the hell?
[LOTTA] Nino brought me
as his assistant!
Isn't it great?
She said she
wanted to see DMw
so I thought, why not?
And what are you
doing to "assist" him?
Ah, you know,
carryin' bags and stuff.
Your hands are empty.
Don't be silly.
I'm wearing a nice dress.
Shall I capture this
moment for posterity?
[LOTTA]
Yeah! Come on!
[laughs]
[KNOT] I think I've died
and gone to dessert heaven!
[JEAN] His Majesty is known
to have a sweet tooth.
[JEAN]
Check out the strawberries.
[PARTY GOER 3A] I was of the
impression this gala was meant
for the prince.
[PARTY GOER 3A] How telling
that everything is to
His Majesty's taste.
They look so good!
[NINO]
Go for that one.
The king has a particular
fondness for them.
Wow.
[ATTENDANT 3A]
Madam.
Does the lady
enjoy sweet things?
[LOTTA]
Yes!
Then please, eat your fill.
Please tell me you got
photographic evidence of that.
Naturally.
[LOTTA giggles]
So did Groschler's line
turn out to be true after all?
[NINO]
Director General Mauve.
Would you care to comment on
today's proceedings, ma'am?
You're Jean Otus's friend,
if I'm not mistaken.
Right.
[MAUVE]
Huh. How very curious.
Sorry?
I endeavor to know
everything I can
about ACCA personnel.
[NINO] I'm fairly
certain I've been made
by Director General Mauve.
[GROSSULAR]
And what's Otus been up to?
[NINO]
Nothing noteworthy on him,
but have you noticed the
Privy Council President?
[GROSSULAR]
Hm?
Been watching Jean
like a hawk all night.
There are enough people
of power and influence
gathered under
one roof right now
to upset the pecking order.
If there were a
coup in the works,
all eyes would be
on the man responsible
for keeping it together,
and whaddya know?
They are.
Jean's the star of the show.
My gut tells me our
friend will be accepting
his third and fourth
cigarettes this evening.
[phone rings]
[NINO]
'Scuse me.
[phone rings]
[NINO]
Hey. Yeah, I know.
[JEAN]
I'm gonna step outside.
Going smoothly so far.
I think you're going
to be more than satisfied.
[LILIUM] Bold move daring
to smoke a cigarette in DMw
Bit brisk out here
for my tastes.
The night air in this district
just doesn't agree with me.
So, then why're you even here?
Well... Officially to pay my
respects to Prince Schwan.
Unofficially, to see
my two brothers.
Your brothers?
Older one's Furawau
District Chief
and our little brother's
an ACCA Branch Chief.
[JEAN]
Oh, wow.
That's impressive.
You didn't know?
[JEAN]
Sorry.
[LILIUM] I know when
I'm being lied to, Jean.
So I'll be straight with you:
I like you.
You're an honest man.
Why are you really out here?
You need a break from all
the eyes on you inside?
[JEAN]
Yeah.
[LILIUM] You seem bewildered
that so many people
are intrigued by you.
Why does anybody give a
damn about what I'm doing?
You're the intermediary for
rebels planning a coup d'état.
At least that seems
to be what they all think.
So, to the connected
and well-to-do,
you're a person
of great interest.
Rumor spreads like wildfire.
In select circles, you're
something of a celebrity.
[JEAN]
Well, that's annoying.
Clearly there's been a mistake.
Grossular ought to
vet his sources better,
though I wouldn't
put it past him
to have started
this intentionally.
In his version
of an ideal world,
ACCA holds absolute power.
The man is not to be trusted.
If there is a coup d'état,
he's the mastermind.
You're a puppet, my friend.
An effective one for being
none the wiser of your role.
[LILIUM]
Don't worry.
Grossular won't have
his way if I can help it.
ACCA may be rocked
to its foundations,
but law and order will prevail.
We're cut from the same cloth.
We both believe in order.
[LILIUM]
Help me, Jean.
Help me preserve the peace
and harmony of this nation.
Live up the emblem
on your uniform.
[NINO] Next time, on
ACCA: Thirteen-Territory
Inspection Department :
"Smoldering Embers
in an Isolated Nation."
Right, so the next audit is...
Oh, I see.
Totally different story
from the rest, huh?
How's he gonna handle that?