[MOND]
Magie, A moment.
[MOND] It's come to my attention
that His Highness Prince Schwan
has been seeking out
and speaking
with the first princess.
[MAGIE]
Yes, but only twice.
This would be the first
time he's taken an interest
in his aunt since childhood.
Very strange.
[MOND] What is he putting
in that woman's head?
Her personal guard
seems on edge,
given to highly
suspicious behavior.
I can't help but think
the prince is involved.
[MAGIE] I'm hard-pressed
to disagree with you, sir.
In any event,
I must make a full report
to Privy Council
President Qualm.
[SCHWAN]
Wait.
I assure you this is a
terrible misunderstanding.
Allow me to smooth things
over with my darling aunt.
Magie will report
to you how it plays out.
Better to give Qualm all
the relevant details, yes?
[SCHWAN'S AUNT] If there's any
truth in what the boy says,
the Otus siblings
are poised to become
a most unfortunate
obstacle to our goal.
My sweet, regal daughter.
Here I thought only
Schwan blocked our way.
This new threat must
be dealt with at once.
Go, make haste for Bon.
[MAGIE] Perhaps it has not
occurred to you, Your Highness,
that she will send assassins?
[SCHWAN] I did speculate
rather freely with her.
Being the dreadful person she
is, I wouldn't dare discount it.
Oh, dear.
When the snow abates,
I'll visit her again.
Though by then I might
be entirely too late.
My aunt does as she pleases.
If it happens, it happens.
Yes, it's me.
I have some very urgent
news concerning Miss Lotta.
[JEAN]
Hey, chief.
Thanks for taking Lotta
out while I was gone.
That was really nice.
[OWL] No, no, she was
the one who offered
to keep me company, actually.
I hate to bother you,
but mind if I ask a favor?
[OWL]
I suppose so.
[JEAN] It's just I have three
audits coming up, back to back.
I was thinking you could
drop in on her again
while I'm away?
Take her to tea maybe?
I'd be delighted to, Jean,
but are you sure
I'm the right person?
Trust me, sir, every
time she's gone out with you
she's had a ball, really.
If you want, you can ask
Knot and the others
to come along.
How can I say no?
Odds are they'll know the best
places to take her, anyway.
Appreciate it, sir.
This next round's
the longest one yet, huh?
[JEAN]
Yeah.
Heading all the way
out to Peshi District first
and then I fly into Yakkara.
And I finish up with Pranetta
on the way back home.
Well. Sounds a bit treacherous.
I'll be fine.
[ASSASSIN 9A] There's no denying
she stands out in a crowd.
Definitely royal blood
in those veins.
[ASSASSIN 9B] The brother's on
a business trip at the moment.
We'll have to take
care of him later.
[LOTTA gasps]
Look, whatever you want--
Shh.
Hey, wait,
you're that ACCA guy!
Your life's in danger, Miss.
Excuse me?
Just take my word for it, okay?
Don't panic, but
you're being followed.
There are some really
nasty people on your tail.
This friend of mine from
out-of-town warned me.
I owe him a ton of sandwich
bread for the heads-up.
Let's grab the
subway to ACCA HQ.
You'll be safe there.
Sorry, I don't really know
enough to fill in the details.
But whatever they're
cookin' up can't be done
out in the open.
It's gonna be fine.
I'm here to protect you.
How kind of you.
That's them.
We'll take the next stop
and blend in with the crowd.
[RAIL] This is Central
Marketplace Station.
I'd say we hop a bus
to the branch office,
but chances are they'll
have thought of that.
[LOTTA] Couldn't we
just head to my place
and get our bearings from there?
We could, sure.
Your building has a
top-of-the-line security system.
Trouble is, they already
know where you live.
[LOTTA gasps]
Oh, hey.
Shouldn't you be
in school right now?
[LOTTA gasps]
These are just like the
ones Jean brought home
from DMwfor me!
[CAFÉ OWNER 9A] Wouldn't be
much of a DMwstyle bakery
without 'em!
Have a seat. I'll make some tea.
[LOTTA] You said your friend
was from out-of-town?
Where's he live?
DMwDistrict.
How wild!
I've got a friend there who's
crazy about sandwich bread, too!
He said he was impressed with
how soft they make it here.
My mom was also like that.
Big connoisseur.
Apparently she was born
in another district.
Wow, wouldn't that be something
if she were from DMw too?
[CAFÉ OWNER 9A]
Yeah, well, you know,
they say lots of folks from
DMw Koro^ and Suitsu
have blue or blond hair.
Yeah my friend's hair
is blue, as a matter of fact.
I bet it looks real neat.
Hey, so this buddy
of yours out in DMw
I just realized my place is
around the corner from here.
Can we stop by real quick?
There's a back entrance.
I need to change clothes.
This uniform makes me stick out.
Hey, as long as you promise
not to play hooky again.
[RAIL]
Wow. I mean, wow!
[LOTTA] I'll just be a sec;
it won't take long.
[RAIL]
Sure. No prob.
[RAIL] She's the spitting
image of her mother.
Woman had to be from DMw
[RAIL]
Whaddya mean she's in danger?
[MAGIE] Assassins are headed
her way as I speak.
Whoa! Assasins?
[MAGIE] I'm sorry I can't
go into more detail.
But because of your
kindness in Bon,
I can give you
that much at least.
Please be careful.
[RAIL]
I don't get it.
What's the connection
between you two?
[MAGIE]
There isn't one to speak of.
Should you--
Should we be fortunate
enough to meet again,
I hope to have a
lively conversation
over sandwich bread.
[RAIL] Okay, I'm gonna
trust you on this.
[RAIL] I'll protect
Lotta no matter what!
Seriously, though,
why's her life being
threatened in the first place?
Jean's all the way
in Peshi District.
And Nino, who knows
what he's up to?
[PASSER] Lovely statue
of the Second Princess,
don't you think?
Popular legend has it
she keeps a watchful eye
over Peshi waters.
Anyway, the Branch Director
and District Chief are waiting.
You ready?
I brought something
to keep me occupied, sir.
Just swing back by
after you see them.
[HERRING] My predecessor's
decision is still an albatross
around all our necks.
To this day, Peshi is
haunted by the Royal Family's
terrible misfortune.
He didn't want the district's
reputation to suffer
more than it had.
Accepting responsibility
for the train accident
all those years ago
would've been the end of us.
Let me ask you.
What are your feelings on ACCA?
Should we be decommissioned?
[BOTH gasp]
[HERRING]
No. No, absolutely not.
Good to hear.
Anything else you
wanna talk about?
[JEAN]
Don't be shy.
[HERRING] Peshi District stands
with you unequivocally.
Please, sir, assume your
rightful place as king.
[RAIL]
You 'bout ready?
[LOTTA]
Yeah.
Wait. Now I'm ready.
We're not going on a picnic!
[alarm beeping]
What?!
[SECURITY ALARM]
Intruder alert. Intruder alert.
[RAIL]
We gotta go!
[LOTTA] Lemme call the
security desk downstairs!
It's too late, Lotta!
They're already here!
C'mon. We have to run!
This isn't happening!
Please don't break the window!
[RAIL] Not what we should
be worried about!
They've probably got people
waiting in the lobby.
Does the staff elevator
go to every floor?
[LOTTA]
Yeah.
It's safest if we head
to the basement--
we can take the stairs
back up from there.
[RAIL] The police have been
notified by now, I'm sure.
There's gotta be a
patrol car en route.
Lotsa traffic this
time of day, though.
Okay. Plan B.
There's a guy I know.
Kinda sketchy, but good
to have in your corner
when the chips are down.
[LOTTA]
Okay.
Damn it.
Who are these people anyway?
And what do they even want?
That's what's freaking me out.
I wish my brother was here.
No one's gonna lay a
finger on you, I promise.
[RESIDENTS chattering]
[RAIL]
Perfect.
There's a decent crowd.
This'll work.
Follow my lead and we'll
make a break for it.
[RAIL]
There's my guy. Awesome.
Look. The police are here, too.
[RAIL]
Jackpot, more protection.
Let me get their attention.
[RAIL]
Over here!
[POLICE OFFICER 9A]
Huh?
Hey, isn't there a
warrant out for that kid?
--Stop!
--[RAIL] Hey!
[police sirens]
[RAIL] Dammit, where
the hell are they going?
[RAIL]
Okay, on to Plan C.
We'd appreciate you
not causing a scene.
[ASSASSIN 9B]
Gridlock.
It's fine, no need to rush.
We've successfully
apprehended the target.
I don't understand.
What do you want with me?
[ASSASSIN 9A]
It's regarding your blood.
My what?
Come on, seriously?
Last I checked I don't have
an especially rare type.
We've been ordered
to eradicate a branch
of the DMwfamily tree.
Huh?!
Wait, so... what?!
[LOTTA] Are you trying to tell
me I'm one of the Royals?
[ASSASSIN 9A]
Exactly, Your Highness.
Let me be the first to
say what a shame it is
to liquidate one so innocent.
But our orders,
I'm afraid, are clear.
[ASSASSIN 9B gasps]
[OWL]
Ah, apologies.
I'm feeling rather faint.
If I could just rest here
for a little while.
Chief Owl?
Goodness gracious! Of all
the people to stumble upon!
Oh?
Cavorting with
folks from DMw I see.
[ASSASSIN 9B gasps]
If memory serves,
these black ties
indicate you work for
the First Princess.
Hmm.
Beg your pardon. I'm with ACCA
HQ's Inspection Department.
[ASSASSIN 9B gasps]
How strange...
Try as I might,
I just can't recall being
told to expect a visit
from royal emissaries today.
Excuse me while I confirm
this with the DMwBranch.
Hang on!
I'm sorry,
is there some reason
you don't want your
presence known?
Very well, release the Bon
residents in your custody
and I'm willing to call us even.
Is that an amenable compromise?
[LOTTA]
Thank you, Chief, really.
Now, now.
You saved our lives.
I'm so sorry, Lotta.
I guess I just wasn't
strong enough.
[LOTTA]
Oh, stop.
The whole thing would've
been a lot scarier
if I'd been by myself.
You did great!
So, someone care to
explain what's going on?
Uh...
I'm not sure I can.
None of it made sense to me.
[OWL] I'll look into it
on ACCA's side.
When Jean gets back
from his audits,
we'll sit down for
a nice, long chat.
[LOTTA]
Sure.
What were you doing
here anyway, Chief?
Actually, I was gonna drop by
and ask if you'd like
to join me for a bite.
Oh, and you're welcome
to come with.
I'm treating my staff to
something of a working lunch,
you see.
Come on, please?
The more the merrier, right?
[RAIL]
Sounds great. Thanks.
Let's just, uh, keep
what they said to ourselves.
[RAIL]
We're sharing a secret!
Best day ever!
[ÉBÈNE]
Very curious, ma'am.
Our sources place a group
of royal emissaries
in Bon District
earlier today.
They're said to have
been behaving strangely.
Forward that to the
Five Chief Officers.
So rumors of Otus's
esteemed pedigree
has at last oozed its
way down the grapevine
to the Royals themselves.
I'm surprised gossip
from the other districts
only took six months
to reach them.
Is there anything else?
Yes, an emergency
meeting tomorrow,
between the Five Chief
officers, ma'am.
Is that so?
[GROSSULAR] And if things
don't go as planned?
What then?
[PASSER]
'Scuse me, sir.
A gift basket from
the District Chief.
His secretary dropped it off.
You'll be in Yakkara
this time tomorrow?
[JEAN]
Yep.
Lucky you!
All the supervisors wanna
get assigned there.
Supposed to be lots of fun.
Yakkara folks are some of the
nicest around. Bums, but nice.
[FALCO]
This is it!
Yeah, ain't she a beaut?
So, there's two ways
to the branch office.
Which one ya fancy?
Why don't you pick?
[FALCO] Heads we go
right, tails we go left.
[FALCO]
Left it is.
Nice. No better way
to take in the sights.
Looks like you've gone native.
[FALCO] Bet your sweet
life on it, friend.
Place this one-of-a-kind?
What else can a man do?
That's what this country's all
about, when you get down to it.
Embracing diversity.
Today's the day, I take it?
You finally see fit to grace
your colleagues with the truth?
We're on the edge of our seats.
Indulge us, won't you?
Fine.
Allow me to enlighten you all
on the subject of Jean Otus.
To begin, as I'm sure you've
all been made aware
through various channels,
rumors abound
that he's the rightful
heir to the throne.
I myself first caught wind
of this shortly after
our initial decision
to terminate
the Inspection Department.
Investigating said rumor,
I discovered it to be true.
Now as you know, gentlemen,
each district has,
over the last several years,
been suspected of nursing
pro-coup sympathies.
In my humble opinion,
the times dictate
that ACCA give them
what they want.
Before a coup could
proceed, however,
it was necessary to clear
the way of any obstacles,
thus my call for Inspection
to be terminated.
You can imagine my
surprise upon learning
one of its deputy chiefs
was of royal blood.
Thinking he was better
used than discarded,
I agreed to let the Inspection
Department survive.
[PINE] Hold up, so your
assertion that Otus was acting
as an intermediary between
radical elements was--?
[GROSSULAR]
Yes.
A politically strategic
fabrication on my part,
one that fed on
speculation of his lineage.
People would believe
he was canvassing
for a path to the throne.
So...
Once Otus was
established as a radical,
I assigned Crow from Internal
Affairs to watch him,
and to gauge how
each district's leadership
would react to the rumor.
I urge you to think
carefully on this.
His Highness, Prince Schwan,
soon to inherit his
grandfather's crown,
will bring ruin.
He plans to abolish
ACCA entirely.
The only way to stop him
is to trigger a coup.
Otus is a good man.
He desires the preservation
of peace in our nation.
If allowed to become
the next king,
that peace will
likely be assured.
Of course, no longer being
on the DMwFamily register,
his ascension cannot be
accomplished by ordinary means.
Hence my linking him to
the pro-coup movement.
Both he and the coup
sympathizers needed a catalyst.
ACCA's future is at stake.
What say you all?
The people are not
in harm's way.
We will protect them
according to duty
by leading the charge ourselves.
[LILIUM]
Chief Officer Grossular.
Why choose subterfuge when
you might've laid this out
to us from the very beginning?
It seemed prudent to
assess how the districts felt
about it before vying
for all of your support.
To succeed, this first must
have the character of a mandate.
The citizens have to agree.
Thankfully, it appears
they are of one voice.
You wanted the truth;
there it is.
I assume you find my
argument wanting?
Not at all.
On the contrary,
I find myself in agreement
with your point of view.
You have my support.
[PASTIS]
You two see eye-to-eye?
My, will wonders never cease!
[LILIUM] Certain facets of
the plan need refinement.
But this country's
security depends on ACCA's
continued existence.
If a coup is the surest
path to safeguarding
the public interest, so be it.
Is there anyone
here who disagrees?
If I heard correctly that ACCA
will take the vanguard, no.
Long as we protect the citizens.
Besides, if you two
can agree on something,
who the hell am I to step in
and try to shake things up?
Hmm.
Provided Suitsu's natural
beauty remains unscathed,
I honestly couldn't care less.
Thoughts, Chief Officer Spade?
[SPADE] Standing by while that
delinquent halfwit of a prince
waves us out of a job?
No, thank you.
Agreed.
We have to preserve this
institution at all costs.
You cut the deck
nicely, Grossular.
I hope you know how
to call the game.
If there's an ace
up your sleeve,
now would be the
time to let us know.
The cards are what they are.
I merely dealt them.
[LILIUM]
See? What did I tell you?
That card motif
was a bit labored,
but otherwise we're fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
Let's drink to it.
A first-rate performance.
All went precisely
according to plan. Simple.
My reputation for opposing
you proved quite effective,
if I may so boast.
That endearing scowl has more
than fulfilled its purpose,
my friend.
Do remember, though,
we are to be of the
same mind from now on.
We must endeavor to keep
the game interesting, yes?
We can't have our colleagues
tiring of it too soon.
The next step is ensuring the
Director General stays quiet.
She may prove to be
the biggest challenge yet.
We will manage.
[GROSSULAR]
I wonder...
[GROSSULAR grunts]
Did I say "we?" I'm sorry.
I meant to say you will
manage it. Won't you?
[LILIUM]
Come now, Grossular.
Don't trouble that pretty
little head of yours.
Just do exactly as I tell you,
and everything will
work out for the best.
[NINO]
Next time on ACCA:
Thirteen Territory
Inspection Department ...
"Starfall in a City
Without a Sky."
No sky, huh? Whatever.
Even if it's pitch black,
I can always make out the
glow of a distant cigarette.