[FALCO] Heads up,
branch chief's making room
at the table for you tonight.
These folks do love
their games of chance.
[FALCO]
Get ready for a long night.
[JEAN]
Huh.
Poker, I assume?
Well, of course, but
before we cut the cards...
[BACCARAT]
Yakkara's finest.
A token of good faith.
This district is built on
the fortunes of crazy dreamers
after all.
We like to roll the dice.
Particularly when odds
favor the dark horse.
Seems like a pretty big risk.
Go big or go home,
right, "Majesty?"
[MAUVE]
You summoned me, sir?
What were your thoughts
as you stood here,
speaking as Director
General for the first time?
[MAUVE] Much the same
as yours, I'd imagine.
[GROSSULAR]
Really?
For me, as I looked out
on the neat little rows
of district staff,
The only thing in my
head was the siren song
of unification.
No two uniforms were alike--
every branch clung to its
own notion of selfhood.
[LILIUM]
So disjointed.
Autonomy is the ideal, granted,
but can we not
celebrate our differences
without overemphasizing them?
[LILIUM] What can be
unified ought to be,
don't you think?
I feel certain our values
align on that score,
Chief Officer Grossular?
ACCA stands as the
nation's clearest symbol
of law and order.
Unification strengthens it.
[LILIUM]
If only certain species of rumor
had the decency to die.
About the coup?
[LILIUM] His Highness Prince
Schwan is one heartbeat away
from the throne.
The primal instinct of
self-preservation stirs
in every district.
Revolution is imminent.
Rest assured,
I for one welcome it.
Not to preserve the
districts' sense of identity,
but rather to ensure
the health of this nation
as a whole.
Something only possible
if ACCA leads the charge.
Surely a difficult feat.
I note you offer no
argument to the contrary.
Very interesting.
Could it be that
we're of like mind?
What would you say we
venture a small ruse?
A ruse?
Well, if it bolsters ACCA's
role as protector,
I can only say yes.
[LILIUM]
Now this may seem simplistic,
but it should prove
quite effective.
Can't you see eye to eye?
Night and day, I swear.
Perpetually at odds.
Are we never to have
a unanimous decision?
[LILIUM]
Quashing seditious rhetoric
would be counterproductive.
Right now, the best course is to
focus our efforts on Inspection.
If Jean Otus is
in fact of royal blood,
he'll galvanize the districts.
Our coup will have
a standard bearer.
[LILIUM] Director General Mauve
is listening at keyholes.
She must be stopped.
[LILIUM]
Chin up.
You can do this.
I know you can.
There is no cause
for concern, my friend.
All will turn out for the best.
[MAUVE]
Forgive my insolence.
Are we here to talk
about the coup?
Whatever your decision in
that regard, Chief Officer,
I have no objection.
You're a decent man.
I know you'll work to protect
ACCA and the nation.
[MAUVE]
However...
I don't know that Otus has
been persuaded to join us yet.
He's a hard read.
[LILIUM] Thank you for
coming all this way.
ACCA will take the vanguard
in the upcoming coup d'état.
Oh?
[LILIUM] This country has
begun to move in the direction
of our family desires.
Let insurrection
be the proving ground.
Furawau will
consolidate its power.
[MOZ] Assorted cookies
from Hachikuma!
[ATRI]
That's cute.
I brought butter cake!
[ALL gasp, laugh]
Has anyone seen the chief?
Rain's probably holding him up.
Agent Rail.
Don'cha have a sweet tooth?
Oh, uh...
Here's the deal.
You seem like a nice guy,
so real talk for a sec.
If you wanna keep
working for ACCA,
there's no time like the
present for turning over
a new leaf.
No offense.
Yep, Internal Affairs
has had an eye on you
for a while.
Best clean up your act.
Of course, you know,
you didn't hear any
of this from us.
Hey, Lotta.
What do you think
of Bon's uniforms?
Cool, huh?
Yeah!
Especially the ones
worn by policemen, right?
It's got a slick design.
[ATRI] So, apropos of nothing,
is there a special someone?
No, not at the
moment I guess.
[KELI]
Did there used to be?
Details!
[LOTTA] Just a guy
I looked up to, sorta.
We weren't a thing.
He's a friend of my brother's.
[ATRI]
Ooh! Tell us more!
[RAIL] Maybe she means
that blue-haired dude.
[OWL] Yes, and somehow
I'm inclined to believe
that won't be the end of it.
All the more reason
for vigilance.
The royal family's
interest is unfortunate,
but don't let that affect
how you proceed.
[OWL]
Pranetta's next, is it?
[JEAN] Yeah, sorry, my bus
just reached the border.
So, hey, I hear you're
quite the social butterfly.
Yeah.
We were gonna barbeque
but then it decided to rain.
I hosted a dessert party
at our place instead.
[JEAN]
Nice.
It's dry as a bone out here.
Just be careful.
Always.
[LOCUSTELLA]
Deputy Chief?
Thanks for coming out.
[LOCUSTELLA] My uniform's
been altered to better fit
the locale.
The Branch Chief sent
me here with a message.
He apologizes, but there won't
be any big splashy welcome
for you the way they
do in other districts.
[LOCUSTELLA]
The District Chief agrees.
No disrespect to one
of royal blood, of course.
This is just how
Pranetta operates.
[LOCUSTELLA]
Hop on in.
There's water, but I recommend
you drink sparingly.
It's a precious resource.
[JEAN]
That's more like it.
It's a lot cooler than up top.
Let's drop off your
luggage before we start.
Plenty of time.
[JEAN]
This is it?
Sorry we can't provide
actual lodgings.
The night shift room
will have to do.
Should have everything you need.
[JEAN] Big convention
in town or something?
[LOCUSTELLA]
They're filming a TV show.
Cast and crew booked out
all the nearby hotels.
[JEAN]
Mmm.
I wonder...
Wouldn't think he'd
be able to follow me
all the way out here.
But he's gotta
be watching, right?
[knock, door opens]
Welcome, sir.
Glad to have you.
Oh, hi.
Right, so the reports
from yesterday
have all been compiled.
I'll input them shortly.
That'd be great, thanks.
Whaddya say we start the rounds?
Any thoughts on how
you'd like to do this?
Honestly, I don't know.
Maybe just do 'em in order?
Sounds good.
We'll go clockwise
from the north.
[JEAN]
Great.
[LOCUSTELLA]
You're already done?
Yup.
Not a whole lot of issues.
Things seem fairly
problem-free around here.
Yeah.
'Course, we have a
comparatively easy job.
Shouldn't take long for the
reports to be properly logged.
I'll head up
and send them on.
[JEAN]
Okay if I come with?
[bell chiming]
[JEAN]
Four o'clock.
Sure is handy having
those bells, huh?
Everyone'd lose track of
time down here otherwise.
Your circadian rhythms
go off the rail.
Takes a toll after a while.
Pranetta's a hardscrabble life.
TV's our only real pastime.
[JEAN]
C'mon.
Everyone romanticizes
this place.
Especially when
the excavation teams
hawk their wares.
People love that stuff.
If you ask me, they're
chasing after a dream.
[JEAN] Kinda sucks you can't
send reports from down here.
Seriously, why not
set up an antenna?
We would if the signal didn't
interrupt TV broadcasts.
Don't wanna poison the well,
if you catch my drift.
Folks would riot if we messed
with their only source
of entertainment.
Besides, a little exercise
never killed anyone,
right, sir?
When I was assigned to JumMku,
I must've put on fifty pounds.
Look at me now!
Maybe Agent Koruri
can be stationed here
after JumMku too.
Is that something you
can make happen?
I'll run it by
the Department Chief.
[HARRIER] The signal's not
bein' very cooperative today.
Think we should
find another spot?
Let's try moving further east.
There's a storm coming in.
[JEAN]
How can you see anything?
[LOCUSTELLA]
We can't.
Might as well eat dinner
while we wait it out,
I suppose, huh?
All we've got are
emergency rations.
Haven't had hardtack in ages.
[LOCUSTELLA] Sorry you
have to choke this down.
Wish we had somethin' better.
Hey, lighten up will ya?
It's like you're worried
about offending me or something.
Take it easy.
I'm still a person,
just like you.
[JEAN]
Man, this is tasty!
Can I open the pistachio?
If you like that
kind of stuff, hold on.
We've got actual snacks.
Popcorn from JumMku!
Cheese and caramel!
[JEAN] They say the two
hardest districts to live in
are Suitsu and this place.
But other than that,
they don't really have
much in common.
In Pranetta, people and
goods can move freely.
[LOCUSTELLA] In Suitsu,
there's a huge gap between
the haves and the have-nots.
The district itself is rich,
but you'd never know it
to look at the commoners.
Pranetta, on the other hand,
is as poor as dirt.
Sure, we have tons of acreage,
but nothing'll grow here.
There's only so much
food to go around.
It's tough.
You have to be a little
crazy to live here,
willing to give up
comfort for a shot
at your dreams.
Yeah, it's all about
the mining industry.
[LOCUSTELLA]
More or less.
It's why so much of our annual
budget is allocated to it.
What else've we got?
Not that we've made
any big discoveries.
The people just keep
doing what they do.
Could be there's
nothing worth digging up.
Still, nobody has a harsh word
for the way things are run.
Good luck finding
that in Suitsu.
Here, the only thing
we complain about
is not getting to see the sun.
When we catch a glimpse,
we treasure it.
Glad the storm let up
sooner than I thought.
[JEAN]
Hey.
What's going on over there?
Is that the TV show?
Nuh-uh.
Just a few locals.
This is the perfect time
to come up for air.
Heat's not so punishing at dusk.
[POLESTAR]
Hello there, Agent Otus.
Can't remember the
last time I saw ya.
Hey, Branch Chief,
been a while.
Join me for a stroll?
It's a lovely evening.
I'd be delighted.
[CROWD chattering]
[POLESTAR]
Well, sir.
Here they are, Inspection
team made it back safe.
--Here, Mister!
--Aren't you sweet?
Storm must've made things rough.
I'm sorry.
Eh.
It was impressive up close.
[JEAN]
Just like the people here.
Floors me how
cheerful they all are.
Did you happen to
bring your cigarettes?
[JEAN]
Of course.
Don't guess I could have one.
[JEAN]
Sure, absolutely.
Please.
A coup d'etat
won't much change
the day-to-day life of us folk.
Even if it comes off
without a hitch.
Unlike the other districts,
we've got nothing to protect.
That's why we sat the
revolution out a century ago.
Where's the incentive?
We're dreamers
of a different stripe.
Heaven forbid we wake up.
Imagine us stumbling onto
some vital new resource
in the rock.
You know as well as
I do there'd be war.
Particularly if, despite
ACCA's best intentions,
the country slides into chaos.
People need their
dreams to breathe.
Yet few things are
more suffocating
than the prospect
of one coming true.
Heh, be careful what
you wish for, they say.
Prince Schwan
wants to abolish ACCA
as soon as he takes the throne.
We'd rather stand with
one who understands
the necessity of
the organization.
Pranetta supports your
bid for the throne.
We don't have much,
but we're happy to share it.
What we take, we give back.
[LOCUSTELLA]
You know what?
I hope someday these
people can stand
under the midday sun
and look as cheerful
as they do now.
That's a freedom
everyone should have.
So what now?
Where do you go from here?
[JEAN]
Good question.
[OWL]
You must be exhausted.
Your next trip is soon, right?
[JEAN]
Two days.
Ugh. You poor devil.
They're running you ragged
to get the audits finished up
before the big
centennial ceremony.
Eh, I can handle it.
Word is the ceremony'll
be all-out.
[OWL]
Yup.
Isn't His Majesty
supposed to attend?
That reminds me.
Not to poke my nose
where it doesn't belong,
but you should have
a talk with Lotta.
Uh, not that you
don't talk, of course,
but tonight, when you get home.
Everything's okay, right?
[LOTTA]
You good with herbal tea?
[JEAN]
Yeah, thanks.
So what happened
while I was gone?
You can tell me.
Um...
[MAUVE] Can't imagine
he'll show up tonight.
I'm sure he'll
check in tomorrow.
[knock on door]
Director General.
[MAUVE]
Evening.
What a coincidence!
[chuckles] Forgive me.
I'm positively addicted
to their sandwich bread.
Oh! That looks new.
[STAFF 10A]
Have a sample.
[POCHARD] Mmm!
A loaf of this, please.
[phone ringing]
[MAUVE]
This is Mauve.
Understood. I'm on my way.
Is there some
sort of emergency?
[MAUVE]
Yes.
Command's in an uproar.
It'll be a long night.
[JEAN]
Damn.
You must've been scared.
Sorry I wasn't
here to help you.
What?
Oh, come on.
It's not your fault.
You had work to do.
Well I'm glad you're all right.
Remind me to thank Department
Chief Owl and Agent Rail.
Tell me something.
Was Mom really royalty?
[JEAN]
Apparently so.
I just found out myself.
From Nino.
Listen.
Nino actually works for
the DMwRoyal Family.
He's been watching over us.
Under orders of the
Privy Council President.
It figures.
I guess deep down I always
knew there was more to him
than meets the eye.
Remember that time?
We were kids and I was
dead-set on marrying him
when I grew up.
Wow, how long ago was that?
Anyway, I proposed to him
and he got all,
I dunno, weird, said
"it could never be,"
or whatever.
Even way back then I could
tell something was off.
He took himself
way too seriously.
So I'm not surprised.
Doesn't seem like a big deal.
I mean, nothing's
gonna change, right?
[JEAN]
S'pose we'll find out, huh?
Wanna grab some food?
Mmm. Let me get ready.
[NEWS REPORTER 10A] We interrupt
this broadcast to bring you
breaking news out of DMw
His Majesty King Falke
was forced to excuse himself
from an award ceremony
after what appeared
to be a brief collapse.
A spokesperson for the
Privy Council confirmed
just moments ago that His
Majesty has yet to recover
and will be absent from
scheduled public functions
until further notice.
[WOMAN 10A]
I know. I'm on my way.
[PASTIS] Let's not work
ourselves into a lather.
[LILIUM]
Yes.
The only real option is to wait.
However, there are
things that beg planning.
Mustn't be caught unaware.
You know, it's rather odd.
Grossular and I were
just discussing this.
[GROSSULAR]
He's right.
You've got a point.
His Majesty could be on the
verge of abdicating as we speak.
Ugh. That idiot prince
on the throne.
Tragic.
But would we not trigger
the coup before that?
Time's no longer on our
side where that's concerned.
The plan needs to be refined,
and we still have the centennial
ceremony to worry about.
Dignitaries from every
district will be in attendance.
Postponement's not an option.
All we can do now is pray
His Majesty pulls through.
The ceremony, yes.
There might be
an advantage there.
[door opens]
[POCHARD]
Oh! Chief Officer Grossular!
Pardon me.
I'd like a word with
Director General Mauve.
At your disposal, sir.
I would have gladly come to you.
[GROSSULAR]
I know.
Have you spoken
with Otus by chance?
No, sir.
But you expressly
ordered him to report
on a regular basis, yes?
Correct.
He hasn't yet shown up today.
[GROSSULAR]
I see.
[MAUVE]
Otus leaves for his final audit
the day after tomorrow--
Furawau District.
And if he continues
to neglect orders
from a superior officer,
what do you suppose
his reasoning might be?
[MAUVE] Well I certainly don't
think it slipped his mind.
Perhaps he's just overly busy.
As I've said, he's a
tough nut to crack.
[GROSSULAR] I anxiously
await your next report.
[MAUVE]
Sir.
[SCHWAN'S AUNT] Of all the
times for father to be
at death's door!
Schwan must be overjoyed.
If he weren't trouble enough,
now there's Schnee's
children in Bon.
I shan't let the brother's
absence be an excuse.
No mistakes this time.
Do your job and
eliminate them both.
We greatly appreciate
your being here.
Welcome to Furawau District.
[JEAN]
Next time on ACCA:
Thirteen Territory
Inspection Department...
"Furawau's Flowers
Smell of Malice."
Wait, why isn't Nino doing this?
[sighs] Didn't I say I was
useless without you?