[REPORTER 6A] Officials have
confirmed the accident occurred
at approximately 8:18 local time
on the Peshi-Rokkusu border.
The central council has
called an emergency session
and is about to
make a statement.
The victims are our
top priority right now.
Every available resource
is being put toward
rescuing survivors.
[REPORTER 6A]
As the search continues,
the scope of this
tragic disaster
is beginning to take shape.
According to the latest sources,
there are now sixty-three
confirmed casualties.
[GROSSULAR]
What do you want?
You wouldn't be here
without a reason, I'm sure.
I suppose not.
I take it your audit is done?
I still have the south sector,
but I leave tomorrow.
Something's on your mind.
Come, you have the look of
a man who's lost in thought.
Rokkusu's citizens
have good eyes.
I was thinkin' back.
An article I read in Koro¦
It was an interview with Mauve
when she was KoroÕs
Branch Director--
just after she'd been announced
as the new Director General.
The office had a wall dedicated
to her called "Mauve Avenue."
She was the first woman
from their district
to hold such a
prestigious title.
Anyway, the article
was hanging there.
She mentioned you
in it by name, actually.
I was just mulling that over.
Nothing major.
That's all?
I'm lying.
Look, I know you've got
someone watching me.
I wouldn't trust him
if I were you.
He's not exactly a
straightforward guy.
There might be a fib
or two in his reports.
If you're trying to tell me
something, I don't follow.
My folks are gone.
Have been for a while.
They died in the big train
wreck thirteen years ago.
The one on the border
between here and Peshi.
Both districts
responded to the tragedy
in their own way.
Peshi washed its
hands of any blame.
Rokkusu took full responsibility
and reached out to the victims.
A Branch Chief
counseled them to do so.
That's what allowed ACCA to
take over the National Rail--
enforce standards.
That Branch Chief was you, sir.
The railways are much
safer now because of you.
Lives have been saved.
"ACCA's purpose
is to build a better nation."
Those are your words.
Director General Mauve
cited them in the interview.
She respects you a great deal,
and I have to say
I'm in the same camp.
I don't really know
what's going on,
but I can tell you that much.
Whatever this "coup d'état"
business is about,
I'm clueless.
All I get is that I'm somehow
in the middle of things.
Some are saying you're
a coup sympathizer, too.
Not that I buy it.
It's just a rumor, and hey,
if they're wrong about me,
seems like odds are pretty
good they're wrong about you.
Anyway.
Sorry to shoulder in
on your time off.
So naïve.
[OWL]
Hey, Knot?
Correct me if I'm wrong, but I
thought Jean was due back today.
Yeah.
He's already been
by the office, chief.
Had to run, though.
He just stopped in to drop off
some goodies from Rokkusu.
[JEAN] Oh, thought you'd have
gone back home by now.
[MAUVE]
I've been awaiting your return.
So, then.
What have you got?
Any juicy tidbits to share?
Sorry to disappoint, but no.
Is that so?
It would seem you're a bit
less useful than expected.
[REPORTER 6A] We're coming
to you live from the press
conference where representatives
from both districts
are expected to speak.
Peshi maintains that this
was an isolated incident,
and is calling for
an investigation
into local operations,
whereas Rokkusu seems to
be using this as a platform
to discuss sweeping,
industry-wide reforms.
It's been one month since
the historic disaster
that claimed dozens of lives,
and talks between the
districts on whose border
it occurred have
come to a standstill.
A follow-up interview with
Rokkusu Branch Chief Grossular
has stirred up quite
a bit of controversy.
The victims' families
deserve peace of mind.
This is no time to quibble
over who's at fault.
The Rokkusu District Chief
and I are in full agreement
on this issue.
A statement will
be issued shortly.
This is a question
of standards.
It's time the national
rail be brought under
ACCA's jurisdiction.
We have a sworn duty.
We must protect the
livelihoods of all citizens.
In the end, ACCA
is for the people.
Just days after
announcing Rokkusu
will accept full responsibility
for the incident,
the District Chief is
embarking on a tour to speak
with the families
of those killed.
The Rokkusu District Chief
is being accompanied
on this trip by Branch
Chief Grossular.
[LOTTA]
This is ridiculous.
Rise and shine, boys.
You're burning daylight.
[NINO yawns]
I feel like an ex-boxer.
It's what you get for
passing out on the couch.
Jean passed out first.
I felt bad leavin'
him here alone.
Something happen
I should know about?
He got scolded by
a superior officer.
The department chief?
Think a little higher up.
[JEAN groans]
I'll get some water.
If I've told you once I've
told you a thousand times.
Before you put this on me,
I wasn't the one pouring.
I suggest you beef up
your reporting skills.
[MOZ] Deputy Chief, snacks
are on us, care for a slice?
No thanks.
Are you okay?
Yeah, sure.
You write up the
audit report already?
Owl started his vacation
today, just so you know.
Great.
[ATRI] You go on break
the day after tomorrow,
right, Deputy Chief?
Got anything big planned?
[JEAN]
Staying home.
So, what were you
thinking about doing
for New Year's Eve?
Well, we've got
a ton of options.
I'm fine with whatever,
long as there's champagne.
Obviously.
Let's see which one looks best.
[ATRI]
Heh.
Well, lookie what I found.
Huh?
What? No way! A party?
At the Deputy Chief's building?
[JEAN]
It's not my building.
And it's just a little
get-together in the atrium.
Lots of well-to-do
types live there.
We let 'em have their fun.
It'll mostly be department
store managers.
Can we go too, please?
Sure, I guess.
You and Lotta are
gonna be there, right?
Promise you won't
sleep through it.
[JEAN]
Well, Lotta will be there.
Oh, come on!
You're the building manager!
Yeah, but I don't do anything.
[MOZ] Ooh, Knot!
You should totally join us!
[KNOT]
Love to, but I have to pass.
Kids and all.
[MOZ]
Oh, I forgot. Sorry.
Eh, eventually
they'll be old enough
for me to have a life, right?
It's only a matter of time.
Why don't we just
have an after-party
here at our place?
When the little ones
get tuckered out,
they can crash in the bedroom
while we do our thing.
For that matter, the adults
can crash when they get tired.
There's plenty of room.
Take that outside, please.
We're a go.
Yay!
[MOZ, KELI, ATRI]
Cheers!
What the--?
Why is Mushroom Head here?
[LOTTA]
He with your department?
[JEAN]
No. Branch Office.
He sorta borrowed my lighter.
Huh. That's weird,
you're telling me he smokes?
Ehh.
Hey, speaking of cigarettes.
Ah! Good, he's gone.
Now's my chance!
Hello!
Oh, uh, hello there.
Happy New Year.
Yeah.
I heard you like DMw cake,
so I thought I'd bring you one.
Aww! How nice of you!
[LOTTA] Must be a thank you
for the lighter.
Aw! Talk about going
out of your way.
Jean's gonna love this!
What a sweetheart!
Oh, it's the chief!
About time, sir!
Happy New Year.
Sorry I'm late; traffic was bad.
Look--even Knot got to come
with his little ones.
[MOZ]
A kid's corner!
Whoever organized this party
thought of everything!
Yeah, it's nice he's able
to get out and unwind, huh?
[laughing]
[OWL]
Lotta.
Hey, Department Chief!
Happiest of New Years to you!
[LOTTA]
Happy New Year to you!
[RAIL gasps] That's the guy who
was having tea with her!
Well, they bake a cake
the people of DMw
ring in the holiday with.
Thought you'd like one.
[LOTTA] Ah!
Oh, this is too much!
Thank you!
[RAIL] He might be a bigger
problem than the brother.
[MAN 1A]
Jean!
Happy New Year!
[JEAN]
Back at'cha.
[MAN 1A] Feel free to
join us for a smoke.
[JEAN]
Don't mind if I do.
Oh, much obliged, by the way.
Fasu purchased fifty of
our donut vending machines.
[RESIDENT 6B] Things are
going well for us, too.
My company's now doing
business in JumMku.
Huh. That's great.
Yes, it is.
Can we still count
on you for this year?
O'course.
[LOTTA]
Look at this!
It's so cute!
Look at these people.
So high class.
But if it's not your building,
how come you live on
the top floor like a boss?
I'm guessing your
family's been doing this
for generations?
Just started with my folks.
Wait, are you serious?
Uh-huh.
No idea how we wound
up with this place.
So introduce us to
the landlord already.
I don't think he's here.
Not that I know
what he looks like.
[GROUP]
Huh?
Not a detail-oriented
kinda guy, are you?
I always thought you were
just a really private person,
but I'm starting to think you
don't have much of a life
to be private about.
[JEAN]
Hm.
[bell ringing]
[MAUVE] It's been a hundred
years since ACCA was founded.
Still...
It looks as though I'll
have to make the first move.
[MAUVE] As our
organization steps proudly
into the dawn of
its next century,
I expect you all to
redouble your commitment
to what we do.
Never forget:
when push comes to shove,
you stand with ACCA.
We protect the livelihoods
of all citizens.
[ATRI] That feel like
the same First of the Year
All-Hands Meeting
we always have?
[MOZ] You'd think it'd
be different for the big
anniversary.
[KELI] Well, I've heard
turnout's supposed to be huge
for the official centennial.
Right, still got that comin' up.
Don't be surprised
if the ceremony ends
with new assignments
for all of us in Inspection.
I mean, everyone'll be there.
I wonder if the
Deputy Chief will get
his transfer request.
I have a feeling we can
look forward to things staying
exactly how they are.
Yup.
If I've learned one thing,
it's to count on my team
from the KoroÃdays.
You're still fast as ever.
Luckily, ma'am,
the Powers That Be
permit you to rely on us
from time-to-time
in your capacity
as Director General.
And of course, no one
is particularly troubled
at the thought of our
putting an ear to the ground
in preparation
for the centennial.
Who would suspect we're
investigating rumors of a coup?
Truth be told,
I did hesitate to involve you.
Blowback could be severe.
If you'd been forced to act,
those in the know
would be made aware.
I've been ordered to
cease my own inquiries.
But, thankfully,
based on this report,
the danger does not
appear to be imminent.
His Majesty's health
was a concern.
I suppose he's well enough,
from what we've seen.
A coup would hinge on the
state of the royal family.
Meanwhile, the districts
are humming along,
business as usual.
That said, I'm not
completely satisfied.
Oh? Why is that, ma'am?
Upon returning home,
I had a chance to meet
with KoroÃBranch
Chief Grise and
District Chief Crème.
I casually mentioned the
potential coup in conversation.
The way they reacted
seemed rather odd.
Something is going on.
We'll look into it.
[MAUVE]
Please do.
And what of the
uprising in Suitsu
and subsequent cover-up?
I'm aware there's been a
great deal of whitewashing
in the past,
but not of this magnitude,
and not during my
tenure in this post.
Otus was conducting an audit
at the time of the uprising.
What an embarrassment
to Inspection.
The man's incompetent at best.
He was likely protecting
a subordinate.
Jean is quite loyal
to the department.
To a fault, perhaps.
Evidently, I can't say the
same for his loyalty to me.
One more thing.
I have no solid proof
as of yet, but...
on the subject of Grossular's
suspected involvement...
Let's hear it.
Yes, of course.
I will do as you say.
Look, I know you've
got somebody watching me.
I wouldn't trust him
if I were you.
How the devil did the man
know he was being tailed?
[sighs]
Look at that, Grossular's
actually slumming it
in the common room
with the rest of us.
Whad'ya know?
We're a hundred years old now.
If there's a time to be
unconventional, this is it.
[LILIUM]
Can I help you?
Why did you tell Otus
that we assigned someone
to spy on him?
I hoped it would goad
him into taking action.
And that didn't
strike you as careless?
[LILIUM]
My apologies.
[GROSSULAR] You've been
getting rather careless,
Chief Officer Lilium.
I would watch myself.
Duly noted.
Now if you don't mind, I'd like
you to share everything you have
on Jean Otus
with the rest of us.
How we proceed
must be determined
by formal discussion.
ACCA's future may
be on the line.
Very well. I agree.
All things considered,
I'd say I won that round.
[RAINY]
All right! Bring on the grub!
[STAFF 6B]
Coming!
[RAINY]
Go on, Mr. Otus!
Dig in! Have your fill!
[JEAN]
"Mr. Otus?" Please.
Didn't I have you call me
Jean last time I was here?
Oh! Yeah, right!
Sure nice of ya
to travel all this way.
Hey, sweetheart! More beer!
You're, uh, really getting
the red-carpet treatment, sir.
I can see that.
Ah, there we go! [laughs]
The locals sure are cheerful.
True, but they're laying it
on extra thick for you today.
I like the energy.
Well, they have the
highest life expectancy,
and the food here's delicious.
[RAINY]
Ah! District Chief!
Howdy!
Sorry I couldn't roll in sooner!
Okay, even he's here?
What is this?
Pleasure having
you here, Mr. Otus.
I'm Sereno, the District Chief.
Nice to meet'cha.
You know, son,
from far away you cut
a damn imposin' figure.
But to be honest, you're ten
times as impressive up close.
Like a classic action-hero!
What's impressive
is Hare District.
I mean, look at you guys!
Aw, go on.
We're just a pair of
crusty ol' wind bags.
Hey, he doesn't look it,
but the District Chief is
turning 91 years young
in a few months!
[JEAN]
That's incredible!
[RAINY] Next to this one,
I'm still wet behind the ears!
[laughs]
But there are people
here even older.
Heck, some were alive during the
big coup a hundred years ago!
[JEAN] And what about
the new possible coup?
[JEAN] If I don't dig up
something to give her,
I'm screwed.
[SERENO] I hate to make
you talk shop, but...
How's it comin' along?
[JEAN]
I'm sorry?
Oh, uh, well, y'know.
I was curious about the audits,
what with you makin'
all the rounds.
[JEAN]
Ah. This is my seventh.
So! How are things goin'
in other districts?
[SERENO] Forget it.
It's none of our business.
Strong fences make
good neighbors, eh?
[RAINY]
True enough!
You're the intermediary for the
rebels planning a coup d'état.
[JEAN]
I get it.
That's the role they think
I'm supposed to be playing.
I'll be damned.
These old-timers are
pumping me for info
on how the other districts
feel about a coup.
I should draw 'em out more.
If I play the part, I might
walk away with something useful.
Okay, how do I do this?
Here. Have at it...
if it's not too much.
[PARUS gasps]
No. Thank you, sir.
That's perfect.
[JEAN] Maybe I should
just get them drunk.
Why not? Works when Nino
wants me to run my mouth.
Some more?
Absolutely, but you first!
No, no. You first. I insist.
[SERENO] I like a man
who respects his elders!
[JEAN]
That was worth it, I s'pose.
Just bits and pieces,
but better than nothing.
[SERENO snoring]
[RAINY]
We should do this more often.
[JEAN] I know it's for
the Director General.
But it sucks doin' to them
what I hate having done to me.
[NINO]
Nice work.
Wanna drink?
Yeah, no.
[JEAN] I can't tell
if the info as any good,
but it's gotta be better
than showing up empty-handed.
[JEAN]
I don't think she's coming.
Oh, well.
[STAFF 6A]
Privy Council President, sir.
His Highness, Prince Schwan,
wishes to see you
when it's convenient.
[SCHWAN] The painting I had
specially commissioned
for my coming-of-age
is now complete.
I'd like to hang it.
In the Royal Family
Portrait Hall.
Very good, Your Highness.
I shall see that it gets done.
I wish to pick a
place for it myself.
Please grant me permission
to enter the Hall.
Grandfather considers
it something of a
"private sanctuary."
I dare not waltz in
without asking your leave.
Thank you, Qualm.
I shall take your stone-faced
silence as a yes.
Oh, and no need for staff.
I'll manage alone.
You may enter, Highness.
But I'm afraid only on condition
that we of the Privy Council
carry the portrait
in question for you.
I haven't set foot in
this room for ten years.
Where would you
like the painting?
That seems an ideal spot.
This is where grandfather sits
to collect his thoughts, yes?
Let us hang it here to keep
him in mind of the future.
And of me.
Well, Highness? Did you?
[SCHWAN]
It's in the perfect place.
I'm very happy to hear that.
And what of our
plans for the bakery?
Still on?
I don't recall that topic being
a point of discussion, Magie.
[MAGIE] Might I humbly
recommend His Highness
journey to Bon before he
dismisses the idea out of hand?
It's important to
broaden one's horizons.
[SCHWAN]
I see the appeal.
And as future king, it behooves
me to learn of the world.
Notwithstanding...
Our family is a slave
to its traditions.
We dislike our women and
children to wander from home.
I've never ventured
past the borders of DMw
All due to a now-thirty-three
year old tragedy.
Thank you.
And in other news,
today marks two years since
the last recorded accident
in the transportation industry.
[LOTTA]
Wow! That's good to hear!
[JEAN] The Transportation
Department is constantly
making improvements.
So's the Medical Department.
People's lives are
measurably improving
'cause of how things
are being run.
ACCA's popularity must
be through the roof.
[LOTTA]
Ta-da.
You made more toast?
[LOTTA] Problem?
What else you want me
to do with all the bread
you buy from Mugimaki?
You can choke down
one more slice.
[JEAN]
Popularity, huh?
[ANNOUNCER 6A] This is the final
boarding call for Flight BD022
with non-stop service to DMw
Any passengers still
in the travel lounge
are asked to make their way
to Gate 9 immediately.
[NINO]
Next time on ACCA:
Thirteen Territory
Inspection Department ...
"The Truth Emerges
in the Night Mists."
[NINO] Seriously?
He's already on his eighth?
Come on, man. Sheesh.
[laughs]
Stop and smell the
roses once in a while.