[YOUNGER BROTHER] We're honored
to have someone of royal blood
in our district.
This is as glorious a
day for the Lilium family
as ever was, eh, dear brother?
Indeed.
Um...
You do realize I'm just
here in my capacity
as ACCA Inspector, right?
[OLDER BROTHER chuckles]
Then I suppose you'd
better get to work,
hadn't you?
[JEAN]
My colleagues are waiting.
At least have some
tea before you go.
An herbal blend made
from our local flora.
[JEAN]
Speaking of which,
I can't get over all the
flowers you have here.
[OLDER BROTHER] They're the
district's pride and joy.
Furawau is
incomparably beautiful,
with delicate blooms as
far as the eye can see.
We find them essential--
a fair representation
of the people, in fact.
Elegant and cheerful.
[JEAN] Two words that
pretty much sum up
your District
Representative, huh?
Wouldn't surprise me
if you were related.
[OLDER BROTHER] He's only a
subordinate--but indispensable.
He seems more relaxed
here than in Bon.
Must be the easygoing
atmosphere I guess.
[OLDER BROTHER]
Almost certainly.
[JEAN] Is Chief Officer Lilium
a different sort of man
when he's home?
Hmm. Who could say
about that one, really?
He always takes
himself so seriously.
Rather makes him stand out.
Among the three of us, I mean.
So driven.
Embarked for the capital of
his own accord, you know.
He can be stiff, but
his love for this country
runs unquestionably deep.
[CANARII]
Welcome, sir.
[JEAN]
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Thank you, though.
Oh, my pleasure.
[JEAN] The residents look
upbeat, I'll give 'em that.
But I get the feeling
it's all for show.
The total opposite of Pranetta.
Something wrong?
[JEAN] Just struck me
how well you fit in here.
Huh?
[JEAN]
You're always smiling.
I suppose being
surrounded by flowers
has that effect on a guy.
Makes me feel,
I dunno, peaceful.
[JEAN] He's getting
reassigned to Yakkara soon.
I wonder if he'll adjust.
[ASSASSIN 11A]
This way!
[ASSASSIN 11B]
You know where the target is?
[ASSASSIN 11A]
The District Chief's estate.
He might stay the night;
he might go back to his hotel.
I don't know.
[ASSASSIN 11B] How the hell
are we supposed to lure him
to an isolated spot?
[ASSASSIN 11A] Eh.
We can't risk any witnesses.
There'll be an
opening at some point.
There has to be.
We'll wait.
No more mistakes.
Where was the audit
prior to this?
Pranetta District.
Ah, so right next door, then.
[JEAN] Drastic change of
scenery for being so close.
We have our share of desert.
Mostly on the outskirts,
where the borders meet.
Once you've gone that far,
there's no much of anything
worthwhile to mine.
Furuwau's native resources
tend to be concentrated beneath
the southwestern seabed,
you see.
But we feel for Pranetta.
Its citizens' lives
must be difficult.
Though, it's a shame more funds
weren't allocated to
improve their cities.
Might've made it a more
agreeable place to live.
[OLDER BROTHER] Can their
leaders be so arrogant?
No.
The citizens choose
to live how they do.
Fascinating.
Well it can't be said their
ambitions don't reflect
Furawau's own in
one important respect.
[JEAN]
Is that so?
[chuckles]
You see, over 90%
of the country's oil
is produced right here.
One might even say
we keep DMwrunning.
Our people take inestimable
pride in that fact.
What we produce,
the entire nation uses.
Furawau keeps all
of DMwin oil.
We are its backbone.
[ALTAIR] If we do happen to
find something one day,
we'd be glad to share it.
Of course we would.
But there's a difference between
sharing and having it taken
right out from under you.
Furawau's resources
flowed into DMw
before the current political
system was founded.
Now, they're compelled
to share what they have.
How could any self-respecting
district not resent that?
What do you think?
Shall we present it to him now?
Indeed.
Have you had enough to eat?
[JEAN]
Yeah.
Very well.
Let us change venues.
[JEAN]
So, about the coup d'état then.
Furawau's leading it?
Yes, we are.
I assume you'll take part?
Being the focal point,
as it were.
[ASSASSIN 11B]
Look. There's the car.
This is it.
Wait. Let him get out first.
Steady. We screw this up,
our lives are forfeit.
[ASSASSIN 11A]
We kill him and disappear.
No need for this
to be complicated.
[ASSASSIN 11A]
Son of a--!
[ASSASSIN 11B]
Take the shot!
To hell with the
collateral damage!
Kill the bastard.
[NINO]
Jean!
[gunshots]
[JEAN]
Nino!
[CANARII]
He's been shot!
Call an ambulance!
[STAFF] We can't do that without
the Branch Chief's approval!
[CANARII]
There isn't time!
The man's bleeding out!
[STAFF]
Uh... Right!
[CANARII crying]
I don't get it.
Why would someone want
you dead, Deputy Chief?
And why--why do we have
to keep this a secret?
It doesn't make sense!
No choice.
It isn't my call.
It's the District Chief's.
[CANARII crying]
He's awake if you would
like to go and see him.
[JEAN]
Devil's luck.
[JEAN] This and the thing with
Lotta weren't a coincidence.
They were working
for the royal family?
Yeah.
[JEAN] Apparently they
killed themselves.
Must be more than two.
I wonder if anyone got away.
[JEAN]
Could be.
This is my first time here.
For some reason the supervisor
never let me come to Furawau.
I don't know why.
Yeah, but see...
I still work for
the Five Chiefs.
So I'm on the job
here as Agent Crow.
Even followed my directive
not to harm anyone
connected to the Royal Family.
I think maybe a
commendation is in order.
You're chatty today.
Heh, Jean.
I can't tell whether you're
being dragged into all this
or if you're throwing yourself
in out of some sense of duty.
And it's not for me to say.
You just do your thing.
I'll do mine and watch over
you like I always have.
[JEAN]
Watch over me?
I think it's time
for that to stop.
It's not your place to
protect the Royal Family, Nino.
Seriously, that's not what
Lotta and I want from you.
[OLDER BROTHER]
Thank goodness!
You're all right!
I was honestly hoping
to avoid getting roped
into power politics.
But the people don't
want ACCA disbanded.
So...
[JEAN]
What we spoke about earlier?
I accept.
[OLDER BROTHER]
Given His Majesty's health,
time is of the essence.
Once you've returned to Bon,
we ask that you meet with
our brother right away.
[SCHWAN]
Why would I want to go to Bon?
I refuse.
[MAGIE] His Majesty's not
able to leave the castle.
You are to attend in his stead.
As his successor you
must think of appearances.
[SCHWAN sighs]
What am I attending?
[MAGIE] ACCA's Centennial
Ceremony of course.
No scheduled
meetings whatsoever,
and I shall leave directly
following the ceremony.
[MAGIE] Not before sampling
their authentic sandwich bread,
I hope.
[SCHWAN]
Oh, get over it!
[LILIUM] I understand Crow
proved something of a hero.
How is he?
[JEAN]
Better, I think.
Not good enough
to leave Furawau yet,
but for all I know he'll stay
even after he's healed up.
I see.
And yet he has other
responsibilities, does he not?
Forgive me. I'm prying.
Let us look forward,
both to your health
and your newfound resolve.
How many cigarettes did
you collect, by the way?
I spread word
among the districts
that support for our efforts
would be indicated
by offering a cigarette
to the heir.
Huh... Thirteen. Even DMw
[JEAN] Probably the
Branch Chief's decision.
I doubt the
Privy Council President
had anything to do with it.
We won't know until the day
of the Centennial celebration,
when we see the number of
guards at His Highness's side.
You're a clever man.
What's your take?
Do the people of this country
long to see Jean Otus
ascend to the throne?
I don't think it has to be me,
so long as it
isn't Prince Schwan.
[LILIUM]
But it does have to be you.
Only you can protect
ACCA, and by extension,
the people's best interests.
If the coup d'état
is successful,
if the rightful heir
assumes his role,
the citizens will breathe
easy knowing that life
will go on as it has.
To preserving the status quo.
You needn't worry, my friend.
After all, you're hardly
in this alone.
In the end,
it's all for the best.
[JEAN]
Yeah, so...
Sorry to keep asking you.
Hey, it's fine. No big deal.
I'm just surprised you
wanted me to look after her
in the first place.
Hey, while I'm in Furawau.
Wouldja keep an eye
on Lotta for me?
[RAIL]
Hm?!
I mean nothing really
happened last time.
I appreciate it.
So what are you gonna do?
You got royal blood
in your veins, right?
You're older than
that idiot prince.
Maybe you should
sit on the throne.
What if I do just that?
You'd be a lot better
than that moron.
[JEAN] Hmm.
Guess you have a point.
[RAIL]
Ah?
[REPORTER 11A] Lot of
important folks dropping in
on Bon this weekend.
ACCA's Centennial
celebration will be held
at the central
district branch plaza.
And it's gonna be big.
Representatives from
all thirteen districts...
[LOTTA] His Majesty's not well
enough to be there, right?
Prince Schwan's
coming in his place.
[LOTTA] So, uh, are civilians
allowed to attend or...?
[LOTTA]
What's wrong, Jean?
You seem preoccupied.
Nothing sleep won't fix.
[knock on door]
[GRUS]
Excuse me.
[door opens]
[chattering]
You're all here early.
[LOCUSTELLA]
Maybe your timing's a little off
because you're so close by.
No offense, of course.
[GRUS] I see we're still
waiting on a few colleagues--
Warbler, Parus, and, um, Eider.
[ATRI] Give 'em a break.
They have, like, a full day
of travel.
In Suitsu it takes
forever just to leave.
[GRUS]
Whoa. Your hair got long.
[PARUS]
Hello-hello!
[EIDER]
Hi, everybody!
[MOZ]
Parus! Eider!
[PASSER]
Eider, finally!
We've been waiting
for you to get here!
Excuse us.
What's going on?
[PASSER]
Fess up.
You've got a thing
for the Deputy Chief!
[EIDER] Uh...
Wait a sec, you think I--?
[KELI] Oh, c'mon, there's
no point trying to hide it!
[MOZ] You came all this way
to see him that one time.
[EIDER]
Well, yeah.
I mean, I did, but that was--
I didn't, that is to say--now...
Those ladies do
love their gossip.
I dunno, I think it's cute.
[GROUP]
What? You're dating Agent Grus?
[EIDER] He was a really
good listener, y'know?
One thing led to
another, then... yeah.
[PASSER] But Bon and
Fasu might as well
be different planets!
[chuckles] Hey, long distance
is the way to go, huh?
Uhh...
I'll have you know we're both
looking into getting reassigned
to be a bit closer.
[FALCO]
About that...
I hear the Deputy Chief's
post is up for grabs.
Warbler's a shoe-in
for the job if ya ask me.
Of course there might be a
little shake-up among the brass,
maybe some demotions.
Not to mention a coup d'état.
[FALCO]
Uhh...
[ATRI] We're not allowed
to talk about it.
[FALCO]
Hell, it's in the works.
[KELI] Doesn't mean we
should be running our mouths.
What did I just walk into?
What coup?
[FALCO]
Ah. Suitsu, right.
You'd be the last person
to know what's going on.
I take back what I said before.
Warbler's not a shoe-in.
[SANDPIPER]
Well this guy certainly is!
Sharpest tool in the shed!
Hey, Knot.
C'mon, what are
they talking about?
[WARBLER]
ACCA leading a coup?
[KNOT]
Yeah. Safest way to do it.
Don't worry, all the districts
are with us on this.
[WARBLER]
Hold on, back up.
What's the reason?
Well, to keep ACCA alive.
At least, so I hear.
Prince Schwan vowed to disband
us once he becomes king.
Can't have that.
Besides, nobody wants to
see the crown on his head.
We pull this off, ACCA survives
and the citizens are protected.
That's how it was
explained to me, anyway.
How did we jump from
ensuring ACCA's survival
to staging a coup?
That doesn't seem odd to you?
[door opens]
[OWL]
Warbler. If I may...
[WARBLER]
Certainly, Chief.
[OWL] It might strike you
as a touch extreme,
but the Five Chief Officers
and the Director General
have made their decision.
One way or another,
a coup will happen soon.
As such, the only way
to prevent the situation
from devolving into
utter chaos is for ACCA
to step up and take the helm.
[WARBLER]
One way or another?
That's ridiculous!
The districts have their
complaints, I'll grant you,
but there's no real
incentive for them to toss
the royal family out
on their ear like this.
So the Prince hates us.
He's the only one
talking disbandment.
He's a fool,
but he's not a dictator.
The Privy Council
will keep him in check.
Give the DMw
family some credit.
They wouldn't risk losing
the power they have.
Think about it, sir, there's
no benefit for them
in an autocratic system!
This coup isn't about
protecting ACCA and you know it.
Prince Schwan
intends to destroy us.
Can he?
Would the Privy Council
reign the boy in?
Is watching him tighten the
noose around his own neck
worth the risk to
this country's stability?
Surely not.
We can't afford to be so naïve.
If there's even a
chance we'll be disbanded.
With all due respect, sir,
you're biased.
This is crazy!
[MAUVE] You appear to have lost
your taste for sandwich bread.
[JEAN]
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Evidently, the cigarettes
I kept getting
indicated each district's
willingness to participate
in the coup.
How many total?
I was told thirteen.
Have you told anyone else?
I reported it to Chief
Officer Lilium, yes.
Before finally
bringing it to me.
Hmm...
What were you instructed to do?
I don't think instructed's
the right word.
I understand.
You're released from my order.
Thank you, ma'am.
[MAUVE]
Otus.
Are you all right?
Sure.
[JEAN]
Warbler?
So it's true, then.
The pro-coup faction is staking
everything on you being king.
[WARBLER] Has it really
come down to us pitting
His Majesty's grandchildren
against each other
so the kid everyone
loves to hate will lose
to ACCA's poster boy?
There's no block if the Privy
Council doesn't intervene.
No one objects,
the revolution is peaceful.
Jean just goes along.
You don't care about the throne.
Is it for ACCA?
What's in this for you?
Look, here's the deal.
I really want you
to take my post.
Thing is, there's
gotta be one final push.
[JEAN]
FYI...
The prince is a total
pain in the neck.
Your Highness.
You're sure it wouldn't
be prudent to speak
with your cousin?
[SCHWAN]
My what?
Cousin. The one in Bon.
My relatives live
in DMw you ass!
Unless, of course...
The brute managed to survive.
[MAGIE]
Still feigning ignorance?
Shut up! Ugh!
You're trying my patience!
I don't care if
he lives or dies!
Forgive my saying so, Highness,
but perhaps a future king
should pay more mind
to his subjects?
At least aspire to
win their affections.
I will thank you
not to loom above me
like a beggar!
Does your job entail
being a nuisance?
I'm not talking
about the two of you!
[MAGIE]
I won't belabor the point.
Ah, no matter.
Soon I'll be king.
It's only a matter of time.
A very special royal visit
in Bon this afternoon.
Standing in for his
grandfather, King Falke,
His Highness Prince Schwan--
[RAIL]
Wha--? Magie?
What the hell?
He's one of the Royal Guardsmen?
Bread guy! From the shop!
Is that the friend in DMwp   Agent Rail told me about?
[LILIUM]
Tonight is our final meeting
with the various
district representatives.
The coup will succeed.
Otus will be crowned
the next king.
Tomorrow ushers in the future
we've worked so hard for.
We've waited long,
the Lilium family.
[GROSSULAR]
The Lilium family, you said?
That's right.
You've waited too, of course.
We all have. Isn't that so?
[GROSSULAR]
Enough of this.
Stop speaking in riddles.
[LILIUM]
Once Otus sits on the throne,
control him, control the nation.
By the time anyone notices,
Furawau will have
fixed itself so firmly
in the corridors of
power that our rule
will be a simple fact of life.
But then, that strategy
is familiar to you.
People know in their
hearts that things
are moving in this direction.
Yet they're unable to resist.
That's the Lilium reputation.
No one dares cross us.
[MAUVE]
Excuse me, sir.
Are you not joining the meeting?
[GROSSULAR]
No.
Are you aware that
Otus is speaking
with Chief Officer
Lilium in private?
Yes, I am.
Very good.
[MAUVE]
Are you feeling well, sir?
[GROSSULAR]
Yes.
[NINO]
Next time on ACCA:
Thirteen Territory
Inspection Department ...
"Where the Bird Flies."
[NINO]
Everything will be fine.
Wherever you go.
Just let me keep an eye on you
for a little while longer.