[EGRET] I'm betting
you could use a break.
I'll go make us some tea.
Sounds good, thanks.
Can I smoke?
Keep it in here, please.
Don't let the residents
of DMwsee you indulge.
[JEAN] Going by the info
I picked up in Hare,
seems all the districts
know about the coup d'état.
They think I'm making the
rounds as a go-between--
running messages
for fellow dissidents.
So far, no one's
done anything--
they're just waiting
to see how this unfolds.
Makes me wonder
what's really going on.
Wherever I go,
it's the same story.
High-ranking officials
assume I'm part of it.
That's gotta be why
Grossular has eyes on me
around the clock, right?
Still, not everyone
agrees with him.
Grossular oughta
to vet his sources better,
though I wouldn't
put it past him
to have started
this intentionally.
If there is a coup d'état,
he's the mastermind.
[JEAN] Chief Officer Lilium,
for example--
He thinks I'm clean--
that I'm just being set up.
But he's stuck on the
idea this whole thing
is somehow
Grossular's brainchild.
He's got my back in
exchange for helping him
get to the bottom of this.
[LILIUM] ACCA may
be rocked to its core,
but law and order will prevail.
[JEAN] And then there's
Director General Mauve,
asking me to dig up dirt
while I'm on my audits.
Jean, I need your help.
[JEAN] But apparently,
she hasn't heard
I'm the supposed intermediary
for coup sympathizers.
[JEAN] I can't tell what
the other Chief Officers
really think, but for
all intents and purposes,
it looks like they're
onboard with Lilium.
Afraid the rumor mill
has it right for once.
[JEAN]
To top it all off,
Grossular went so far
as to hire my best friend
to keep tabs on me.
[JEAN]
If Nino has a stake in this,
damned if I know what it is.
Right now, everything
hinges on the Royal Family.
How much longer will
His Majesty King Falke
stay on the throne?
Wait...
What's the point of setting
me up as an intermediary
in the first place?
That's never made sense.
[QUALM] I trust security
will be airtight?
Oh, absolutely, sir.
[MOND]
You seem relaxed, Magie.
No doubt because tomorrow's
outing doesn't involve you.
I'm counting on you
to take special care
of His Highness while
the rest of us are gone.
[MAGIE]
Of course.
[MOND]
Whatever befalls Prince Schwan,
you are to remain at his side.
Worried the past
will repeat itself, sir?
[MAGIE] The incident
thirty-three years ago?
[MOND] We exist solely
for the protection
of the DMwRoyal Family.
Difficult to perform
at the best of times,
every so often that
duty is impossible.
The ship sank, Magie.
The king lost his most
prized possession
and we our beloved
brother-in-arms.
[MAGIE] The prince wishes
to see the world.
[MOND]
Oh?
[MAGIE] A strange desire,
I'll grant you,
but one likely driven by
his impending assumption
of the throne.
[MOND]
I see.
If that time comes,
still, you must remain
at his Highness's side
and protect him, Magie.
Wow, you're awfully bundled up.
[NINO] This DMwwind
cuts right through a man.
[JEAN]
Huh.
[NINO]
Buying Lotta a present?
[JEAN]
More like running an errand.
She wants these.
They're called snowballs.
Knot bought some
for his kids last time.
She's kind of obsessed.
Snowballs! Gimme!
[JEAN]
Only problem...
We got 'em at the morning
market while we were here.
I have no clue where
the actual store is.
[NINO]
Good news--it's up ahead.
Bad news--they're closed.
I can bring you
back tomorrow, though.
When's your audit done?
[JEAN]
His Majesty's having a day out,
so I have to put things on hold.
I'm free whenever.
Cool. Whaddya say
we make it three?
You'll wanna try
their signature cake.
Is it chocolate?
Apple, and outta this world.
Someone's expanding
his dessert palate.
You'll be a fan. Trust me.
When did you get
to be such a connoisseur?
Don't wear your uniform.
Makes you stand out.
[JEAN] But this is the
only outfit I packed.
[NINO]
'Course it is.
[JEAN] Wonder if there's
snow in the forecast.
[LOTTA laughs]
I'm in paradise!
They're gigantic and
there's so many!
[alarm clock rings]
This is torture.
I need them now.
Don't forget.
You promised me, Jean.
It's snowing!
So, uh, what was that you
said about standing out?
[NINO]
What, is it too much?
[JEAN]
Little bit.
[NINO] The owner and I
don't exactly get along.
[JEAN]
Lotta's gonna be over the moon.
[NINO]
What'cha getting for yourself?
[JEAN]
One of these snowballs, please.
[NINO]
His Majesty's favorite, I hear.
The Royal Family
adores this place.
The king really does have
a thing for sweets, huh?
[NINO] A slice each of the
white chocolate and the apple.
For here, please.
[CLERK 7A]
Pay no mind to them.
We're enjoying a
royal visit today.
--[JEAN] Huh?
--Oh. You didn't know?
Whenever His Majesty's
out and about,
he pays a visit to
a favorite patisserie.
We should probably go.
[OWNER 7A]
That won't be necessary.
You're welcome to stay.
The king requests that
we do business as usual
while he's here.
He enjoys hobnobbing with fellow
confectionery enthusiasts.
Sit anywhere but
the farthest table.
That one's reserved
for His Majesty.
Well, the owner
seems nice enough.
[NINO] He's just in a good mood
'cause he's got bragging rights.
[OWNER 7A] Remove your hat
and sunglasses, please.
That fellow there.
If memory serves, he's with
ACCA's Inspection Department.
You don't suppose he came here
because of His Majesty's
visit, do you, sir?
We only learned of it
ourselves this morning.
Surely a coincidence.
The inconceivable gall of
him showing his face here,
though, and who's
that man with him?
[MOND] Hmm, if there's
any cause for concern,
I'm certain Qualm will
signal us right away.
[JEAN]
This is amazing.
Mind if try a bite of yours?
Let no one say you don't
have nerves of steel.
[JEAN]
Huh?
[NINO] Most folks in this
situation couldn't even breathe,
and here you are
making chitchat.
[JEAN] What?
They told us to act normal.
It's not like I'm being
loud or anything.
Do you like the snowball?
[JEAN]
Yes, Your Majesty.
You've excellent taste,
my friend.
[JEAN]
Thank you, Majesty.
[QUALM] If it pleases my liege,
he's with Inspection.
Isn't that right?
[JEAN]
Yes.
Yet you appear to be
draped in local finery.
[JEAN]
Oh, uh...
I only brought my
uniform, you see.
These clothes are on loan
from my friend here.
Ah, yes, the photographer.
From the coming-of-age ceremony.
[NINO] Thank you for allowing
me to take pictures,
Your Majesty.
Some of the shots
I got were incredible.
[FALKE II]
Oh, no.
'Tis we should be thanking you.
I'm honored, Majesty.
[FALKE II] Would you fine young
gentlemen care to join us?
We cannot possibly eat
all of this ourselves.
[NINO]
The answer's yes.
You don't refuse a king.
[QUALM]
Here, please.
Would Your Majesty
be all right with me
taking photographs?
I promise not to publish them.
[FALKE II]
Mmm.
[JEAN] That was a
hell of a day, wasn't it?
[NINO]
Yes. Yes, it was.
It's not often I get thanked,
let alone by royalty.
Lotta and I thank you
all the damn time.
[NINO]
I meant in my line of work.
[JEAN] Rare to see him
so plastered.
[NINO] Like getting praise
from your boss.
[JEAN] I didn't even know
you had one of those.
[NINO chuckles]
Yeah.
Not a lot of praise outta him.
When I see the guy,
he just lays into me.
Like last time.
I shouldn't even be
talking to you like this.
Bastard'll never let me
hear the end of it.
[JEAN]
Sounds like a handful.
You like what you do
that much, pal?
[NINO]
It not about whether I like it.
Honestly, I'm not
even s'posed to.
But, then again...
I guess I kind of do.
It's why I get told off
all the time.
[NINO snoring]
[JEAN]
Did he just pass out?
Good choice, Schwan.
It's lovely.
Come, grandfather.
Which painting do you
like the best?
[FALKE II]
Why, all of them, naturally.
[CLERK 7B]
Our new mugwort walnut bread.
Would you like to
try a free sample?
Thank you.
[CLERK 7B] I'm afraid it looks
like the Director General
is a no-show today.
[door closes]
[JEAN]
Is she avoiding me?
[LOTTA]
Mmm, delicious!
How much flour did they use?
I love how the powdered
sugar and the white chocolate
make it look like
a real snowball!
Oh, did I tell you?
It actually snowed
the other day!
[JEAN]
Same thing in DMw
[LOTTA]
Yeah?
I'd give anything to be
there when it snows!
Must look like a fairy tale!
You're really into
that place, aren'cha?
Big time.
Mm-hmm. It's great!
You agree, right?
I mean, you go
to all the districts.
Which one is your fave?
[JEAN]
DMws pretty good, I guess.
But if I had to go with
a favorite, it'd be Bon.
[LOTTA]
I'm with you there.
Home sweet home.
I bet everyone likes
their own district best.
[LOTTA]
Where you head to next?
It's soon, right?
[JEAN]
Yeah.
I'll get Nino to take you out.
I thought he was
crazy busy, too.
[chuckles]
The Department Chief
and I have plans.
We're going to hit up the
café where they make
that marvelous
New Year's cake, so...
You don't have
to worry about me.
[JEAN]
All right. If you say so.
Where you off to?
[JEAN]
Koro¦
Bring back chocolate!
[JEAN]
Yeah, yeah.
[LOTTA]
Seriously, they're known for it!
[JEAN]
Are they now?
I can count on Nino
being there, then.
[NINO]
Several persons of note in Hare
seem to have taken a proactive
stance toward the coup.
[NINO] KoroÃdoesn't follow
the lead of other districts,
so we might see some
developments there.
I'll be on the lookout.
[phone beeping]
[NINO]
Thank you for waiting.
I wrapped up my report
to Chief Officer Grossular.
I'm heading out
to KoroÃtomorrow.
DMw
Pretty smooth,
all things considered.
Yes, I made sure to send
photographs in with my report.
I know. I'm fast.
I haven't had more than
a few hours' sleep
since we've been back.
Fatigue's starting to
get to me, but oh, well.
It's nothing a little
chocolate can't take care of.
Yeah.
KoroÃDistrict, that's right.
Understood. Talk soon.
It's been thirty years?
Man, I'm gettin' old.
[ÉBÈNE] Why would the
Director General entrust him
with such an important mission?
[CARMIN]
Excuse me!
[ÉBÈNE]
Keep your voice down.
[CARMIN]
I'm sorry. Take a look.
[ÉBÈNE] He's connected
to coup sympathizers!
I knew it!
[ÉBÈNE gasps]
Wait a sec.
[MAUVE]
I see. Jean Otus.
And he's presently
in Koro^ yes?
[JEAN]
Why were they staring at me?
Probably because they've heard
I'm mixed up in the coup,
specifically that
I'm a supporter.
I wonder if I'll have
a chance to explain myself
to the Director General
once they've talked to her.
[GRISE]
Welcome to KoroÃDistrict.
[JEAN]
Branch Chief Grise.
[GRISE]
You must be exhausted.
I recommend catching up on
your rest while you're here.
I, uh...
[GRISE] Other districts
wine and dine you, I'm sure.
Regrettably, that won't
be the case with us.
The District Chief and myself
are quite firm in that regard.
Men may prefer the
more roundabout approach.
We do not.
[JEAN] Didn't feel like
the right time to push
the coup d'état question.
[LARUS]
Deputy Chief.
I've made the travel
arrangements for your
sector audits tomorrow, sir.
[JEAN]
Great, thanks.
Efficient as always.
Enough to make a
guy feel kinda useless.
[LARUS] Can I help it if
women are slightly superior?
Not that we don't have our share
of competent men, of course.
I am curious about DMw
[JEAN]
Hm?
Does His Majesty appear
to be in good health?
[JEAN]
Far as I can tell, yeah.
I only worry for ACCA's future.
We all do.
[LARUS] Our fate is anyone's
guess when the next ruler
assumes the throne.
[SCHWAN'S AUNT]
Schwan, my dear.
To what do I owe this most
unexpected pleasure?
[SCHWAN] I hope we find you
in merry mood, Auntie darling.
What can I do for you?
[SCHWAN]
I wish to be told a story.
What sort of story?
[SCHWAN] An incident which
occurred when my mother
was too young to remember.
I thought if anyone's in
a position to lift the veil,
it must be be her older sister.
Tell me of your middle sister
and how she met her end.
It has been thirty-three years.
Give me the details.
So many shops here.
How'm I supposed to know
which ones are any good?
[JEAN] I'd pick Nino's
brain, but he's MIA.
Fascinating report I
was given this morning.
About you.
[JEAN]
Director General, I can explain.
It's all hearsay.
This stuff takes on a life.
You're royalty, Jean Otus.
First in the line of succession.
And as I suspected,
completely unaware.
Walk with me.
[MAUVE]
According to one source,
well, you're "the intermediary
for coup sympathizers."
That's what--
Another source boldly
asserts you belong
to the royal family.
My gut tells me
you're being used.
It's the only way to square
what I'm being told
with what I know.
While I'm not a woman who
overvalues her gut instinct,
when it comes to you,
I'm fairly certain it can't
be too wide of the mark.
So, am I right to conclude
you're just a patsy?
Yes, ma'am.
Thought so. Jean Otus is
clearly a man of integrity.
I could tell from the start.
I'm sorry, it was unfair
of me to write you off
the other night.
You really didn't deserve it.
I ought to have
known better.
What I asked you
to do was foolish.
You're too steeped in this mess.
Just so we're clear,
I really didn't have
anything to report.
Except that's not
entirely true, is it?
The uprising in Suitsu?
[MAUVE] You expressly withheld
important information
concerning Chief
Officer Grossular.
I know you've seen the
so-called "Mauve Avenue."
Which means you know
I hold Grossular
in high esteem.
So out of respect,
you attempted to shield
me from allegations
of his involvement.
Is that right?
When you put it like that,
it sounds so much worse.
But yes.
You dropping that in
my lap would've taken
more nerve than is advisable.
We needn't put my
feelings above the facts.
But I understand why you chose
not to report what you knew.
[JEAN] I wasn't just
trying to spare you.
There's more to it than that.
I don't think
Grossular's behind this.
I didn't want to spread
that rumor any further.
At the end of the day,
it just wasn't worth reporting.
[MAUVE]
You don't ask many questions.
About yourself, I mean.
Did you suspect
your true lineage?
I dunno.
Maybe I should look
into it, huh?
[MAUVE]
You're taking it well.
I wouldn't necessarily say that.
There is someone I can talk to.
[SCHWAN]
Leave the district?
Whatever for?
I thought Your Highness
wanted to broaden his horizons.
My horizons are
quite broad enough!
I've no desire to see
Bon for its own sake.
I merely wish to learn
about the girl.
[MAGIE] I didn't know you felt
so strongly for Miss Lotta.
Oh, would you shut up!
We need to ascertain whether
she'll stand in my way.
My aunt's tale brought
certain things to light
I daren't ignore.
I've become convinced
our Lotta is of royal blood.
[SCHWAN] Take the portrait of
the second princess at sixteen.
The resemblance Lotta
bears to it is so uncanny
one wonders if the
princess ever really died.
It's a mystery.
Of course, family or not,
she's still female.
The line of succession
remains unbroken.
[MAGIE] Your Highness realizes
she has an older brother?
You'll recall him as the
brute who stepped outside
to smoke during your ceremony.
[SCHWAN] Why have I
not heard this before?!
I couldn't say.
No fear, Your Highness,
if it pleases you,
I shall return to Bon.
Anything else about Lotta
we might have missed--
[SCHWAN] I don't give
a damn about the girl!
Look into her boorish lout
of an older brother!
[MAGIE]
Alas, I cannot.
What?!
[MAGIE] I am forbidden
from leaving your side,
Your Highness.
I've been ordered to stay.
Much like the princess's
guard who vanished
all those years ago, swallowed
by the unforgiving sea.
Yes, the guard.
And what was his name?
[MAGIE]
Abend.
One could scarcely find a
guard ignorant of that name.
He was said to have
beautiful white hair,
pure as the driven snow,
which caught the eye
of His Majesty's
equally beautiful
second daughter.
The man's loyalty
is spoken of still.
[NINO]
Jean knows the truth.
Mauve told him.
I didn't catch all the details
of their conversation, no.
But I know how he thinks.
He's bound to ask me.
Speaking of which,
here he is now.
Why don't I tell him everything?
Well, you could do it yourself,
except there's no time
to run it past Qualm first.
I've gotta go.
Right. Understood.
[JEAN]
Sorry.
Don't mean to interrupt you.
It's fine.
You get Lotta her present yet?
[JEAN]
No.
I was hoping to
pick your brain first.
Sure.
This uh... might take
a little while.
I've got time.
[NINO]
Next time on ACCA:
Thirteen Territory
Inspection Department ...
"The Princess Who
Spread Her Wings
and the Friend
Who Had a Duty."
[NINO] I hope you appreciate
how special tonight is.
I'm not one for
dwelling on the past.
This'll be the first
and only time.