[TV REPORTER 1A]
Rise and shine!
This is your morning report
with the Bon News Station.
Our top story:
His Majesty the King,
seen here addressing the
public from DMwCastle,
celebrates turning ninety-nine
years young today.
[LOTTA] Huh?
I had no idea he was that old.
[TV REPORTER 1A] ...including
several events in DMwitself.
Guess it goes to show ya
how peaceful this country is.
[LOTTA]
Better hurry, bro.
You'll be late if you
don't move it.
[JEAN]
Yeah, yeah.
That reminds me, Lotta.
I have a business trip today.
[LOTTA] Wha--? And you wait
till now to tell me this?
How am I supposed to
get your things ready?
[LOTTA]
Safe travels.
I expect you to bring
me a souvenir.
[JEAN]
Mm-hmm.
[LOTTA]
Oh! Your cigarette case.
[LOTTA] Can't leave home
without your signature prop.
[LOTTA]
"Jean the Cigarette Peddler."
Hey, Jean...
Can you bum me a smoke?
[MAN 1B]
Get a load of the smoker.
[MAN 1C] Wow, someone's
livin' the high life.
[phone ringing]
[MOZ]
All right, people.
Fresh from Hachi-kuma
on third avenue,
today's ten o'clock
snack is roll cake!
[KELI]
Yeah!
[ATRI] It's not quite
ten yet, but so what?
[KNOT]
Ah, morning, Chairman.
Care for some
delicious roll cake?
[OWL] I'll indulge once
it's ten o'clock.
Sorry, Deputy Chief,
I heard you'd be out
so I didn't get you any.
You look like something's wrong.
[JEAN] Our department's
'bout to be shut down.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[POCHARD] Not that you
need reminding, I'm sure,
but as you're aware,
the DMwKingdom
is a federation comprised of
thirteen autonomous districts.
Along with various
other agencies
vital to the civic health
of this kingdom,
ACCA was designed to function
independently of the state.
It shares this in common
with law enforcement,
medical, fire...
In fact a whole host of agencies
it is ACCA's job to oversee,
thus facilitating their
autonomy as constituents
of the federation.
I don't have to tell you that
we here at ACCA Headquarters
take our duty as administrative
watchdog quite seriously.
But might I ask you gentlemen
the ACCA Inspection
Department's mandate?
Well, sir, we monitor
and regulate the operations
of each branch, of course.
[POCHARD]
Precisely.
Your department was created
roughly a century ago
in a time of significant
political unrest.
Its primary function
was to keep a close eye
on the outlying districts.
Inspectors were stationed
at each ACCA branch
to supervise the flow
and distribution of data
at a granular level.
Senior officials
conducted random audits
to ensure the
process's integrity.
My point being... your
department's purpose arose
in response to
civic instability.
Therefore...
We're being canned.
Makes sense, I suppose.
Guess we all knew it'd
happen eventually, right?
What can you do?
We're obsolete.
It is unfortunate
we'll be split up, though.
[MOZ, ATRI crying]
[ATRI]
Say it isn't so!
Oh, and Jean.
You're still going out today.
[JEAN]
Huh?
Good luck. The next flight
leaves in 'bout half an hour.
[JEAN sighs]
[POCHARD] The Inspection
Department has been notified
of their termination.
[SPADE]
Thank you.
[door opens, closes]
ACCA will move forward
without Inspection.
And we're certain
this was a smart move?
[GROSSULAR] The budget
needs streamlining.
We're simply trimming
the excess fat.
That's all this is.
[LILIUM]
Interesting point of view.
The Inspection Department
has always ensured
things were above-board.
They kept us honest.
Is that your idea of excessive?
[GROSSULAR] They're only
necessary in uncertain times.
[PINE] A good inspector helps
smooth out regional operations
even when, for all
intents and purposes,
the country's doing well.
[GROSSULAR] And they've
done an admirable job.
But right now Headquarters
needs to demonstrate its trust
in the outlying districts.
[LILIUM]
Trust?
[PINE]
Well, what's done is done.
We can assess the backlash
later, if there is any.
[phone ringing]
[GROSSULAR]
Excuse me.
Anyone else find they
can breathe a lot easier
when that man leaves the room?
[JEAN] Land as far
as the eye can see.
This place is huge.
Bet you're thinking this
is the middle of nowhere.
Not many folks out n' about
now that the harvest is over.
Guess not.
[EIDER] We're mostly an
agricultural district, y'see.
Take a guess how much
of the nation's produce
comes out of Fasu...
Ninety percent!
Can you believe it?
[JEAN]
Impressive.
Pretty low crime
rate too, I'm told.
[EIDER]
Absolutely!
The residents are super nice.
Couldn't ask for an easier job.
D'you like it here?
You bet!
Good. Glad it's so cushy.
Too bad we're getting shut
down at the end of the month.
[EIDER]
What?!
[JEAN]
Watch the road, will ya?
[EIDER] What do you mean
we're getting shut down?
It was bound to
happen sooner or later.
Our department's a fossil.
Blame the peace and prosperity.
You had to know the other
shoe was gonna drop
at some point.
[EIDER]
Not so much, actually.
So what happens
to us afterwards?
Well, you're a supervisor.
I'm sure you'll
land on your feet.
[EIDER gasps]
The people I work with
are like family!
I can't just give 'em the axe!
Let's grab the check, huh?
And just so you know,
technically my job includes
evaluating subordinates.
[EIDER] Go over our stuff
with a fine-tooth comb.
You won't find anything
out of line.
[JEAN]
I'll give you this much.
You people are organized.
[EIDER]
On to the next stop.
Wait a sec...
There's a little bit of business
I need to take care of while
the branch director's on duty.
[BRANCH DIRECTOR 1A] Still
cartin' around those random
catalogs, Otus?
Well I'll be damned.
[JEAN] Feel free to hold
on to the ones you like.
Yeah. Donut vending
machines... you don't say?
That's a keeper.
[JEAN] Whatever helps pass
the time, am I right?
[EIDER]
So, uh... what was that about?
A company president
I know asked me to do it.
Well... station rounds
tomorrow, I suppose.
Ugh. It'll take forever.
This district is enormous.
What's the matter?
[keyboard clicking]
[JEAN]
HQ.
[MOZ]
Hey, Deputy Chief!
[ATRI] Don't forget
to bring us presents!
[JEAN]
Yeah, yeah.
Is Knot around?
[KNOT]
What can I do for ya?
[JEAN] I need to take a look
at the data logs for Fasu
and their inspector
shift records.
Yeah. Sure thing.
[JEAN]
Thank you.
Here, look at October third.
Um, 'kay.
[JEAN] The time stamp for your
west station's data transfer
is off by five minutes.
Weird it's only
the one day, yeah?
Yep, this data's
been tampered with.
You've got to be kidding me!
Uh, I mean, how so?
[JEAN] How far to the
west station from here?
By plane?
About an hour n' a half.
[JEAN]
Then we still have time.
[INSPECTOR 1A]
This is sort of unexpected.
Especially with His Majesty's
birthday festivities
in full swing.
This won't take long.
[JEAN] Are Constables
Maïs and Beets here?
I don't imagine so.
Municipal festivals
tend to be high tide
for black market deals.
[JEAN] On October third,
following an anonymous tip,
the constables conducted
a warehouse search
on the outskirts
of this district.
But there's no record
of the search; care to explain?
See, I'm inclined
to think they caught
some unlicensed tobacco
dealers in action,
and in exchange for
turning a blind eye,
agreed to take a cut
of all future trade.
The shift logs would have to be
changed to cover their tracks,
so naturally they'd
turn to the one person
with the clearance
to fudge the numbers.
What exactly are you suggesting?
Last I checked,
compiling all shift data
and forwarding the
records to HQ fall under
your job description.
Seems the moral dilemma
cost you about five minutes.
Whoa!
Wait a minute, Deputy Chief!
How can you be so damn sure?
A tiny discrepancy like that?
For the record, he might've
just been sick that day.
Is it confirmed in this case?
'Kay, you're, uh, not a man
who trusts subordinates.
The tip about the
warehouse was still in
the previous day's report.
Corroborating data.
[JEAN] In hindsight, it might've
been better to scrub that
from the shift logs, too.
No, wait! Please, sir!
I had no idea what
they were doing!
I'm innocent!
[JEAN]
Is that a fact?
Then tell me this, why do
you smell like cigarettes?
[EIDER]
You win.
Constables Beets and
Maïs confessed.
[JEAN]
Case closed, then.
'Course at the end of the day,
all we've done is smear
our own name.
I'm sorry, sir.
You were just trying
to do your job.
[JEAN] I try not to treat
subordinates like criminals,
but it comes with
the territory sometimes.
My job is doubting people,
plain and simple.
To be honest, I'll be
glad to leave it behind.
Plus all the travel
really takes a toll.
[EIDER] I can't help but wonder
where ACCA goes from here.
Without Inspection oversight,
you think the branches will
become more independent?
Or maybe, they'll just fall
in line with whatever HQ wants.
Probably the former, I'd think.
The districts prize their
individuality too much.
I'm not complaining, mind you.
That independent
streak's a blessing.
Heh, keeps this country
peaceful if you ask me.
Besides, ACCA is a
unified front in name only.
I mean, all thirteen districts
have their own uniform.
Your place has a
particular look and feel.
Same with all the others.
Everybody goes with
what works for 'em.
Best part about how things
are organized, I think.
If you don't want
to get absorbed,
you can always request
a position transfer.
No need to leave here.
[EIDER]
Thanks, but no thanks.
I want to go back to HQ; there's
so much I can learn from you!
[JEAN]
Huh?
What do you mean
we're not laid off?
Exactly that. We just received
the news this morning.
[JEAN] But we uncovered
potentially systemic corruption.
I thought they'd shut
us down immediately.
Hey, all's well
that ends well, right?
[EIDER groans]
[SPADE] Granted,
the Inspection Department
did create a bit of a stink.
But the district branch in
question was in fact corrupt.
Proof of why we need them.
They can smoke out
corruption before it escalates
into outright scandal.
As such, their
disbandment is repealed.
There's no
reasonable alternative.
[PINE]
None at all.
I'm surprised Grossular
conceded so quickly.
He was the most vocal
proponent of their termination.
Why would he change his mind?
Who in the world
could possibly guess
at what goes on
in that man's head?
He's a cipher.
Deputy Chief Otus.
I want him monitored.
[CROWD chattering]
[FIRE FIGHTER 1B]
Hurry! This way!
[CROWD chattering]
Sure have been
a lot of fires lately.
[RAIL]
Yeah, we get it. You're rich.
[RAIL] Maybe don't smoke those
in the street, though, huh?
[RAIL'S PARTNER]
Hey, rookie!
Get a move on!
[ATRI] Yesterday's logs
from Peshi District
are verified and being
forwarded to Data Management...
...now.
[KELI]
Snack time, everyone!
Today, we have a
five-pack of flan!
--[ATRI] Yay! Perfect!
--[MOZ] Gah! I love flan!
[MOZ]
Deputy Chief?
Aren't you off duty today?
[JEAN]
Forgot my lighter.
[KNOT]
What'cha got there?
Just a draft of the third
and fourth-quarter
audit schedule.
[KNOT]
Wow, that time already?
This stuff is good!
[KELI] Whoever thought of
the five-pack was a genius!
You should bring one
home for your family!
[KNOT] Nah, there'd be war
over who gets the extra.
[KELI]
Wait, what do you mean?
There's you, your wife,
and the three kiddos, right?
[KNOT] Yeah. My, uh,
wife ran off.
[GROUP]
Wha--?!
Chairman, don't you think
this schedule's a little much?
As it is, I have
to audit each branch
at least once every two years.
You can't really expect me to
hit up all thirteen districts
in six months.
[OWL] I'm afraid this comes
from the Five Chief Officers.
[JEAN]
Seriously?
Sorry, did I miss a meeting or
am I on their bad side now?
[OWL]
Who knows?
Probably the corruption
you uncovered.
They want us to batten
down the hatches
to make sure no other district
is up to anything shady.
Well, this is gonna be fun.
Hey, what're you staring at?
Jean the Cigarette
Peddler, genius.
Heh. You're obsessed.
[RAIL] Look at him, suckin'
those things down like air.
They say he's got a
fancy-schmancy apartment
downtown.
Prob'ly on the top floor.
Ugh. Loaded son of a bitch.
Oh, man.
What're you, like an
expert on this guy?
Rumors about people
you can't stand
are easy to come by, believe me.
Light bulb in the
entry way? Sure thing.
I'll have it switched out
for a fresh one, ASAP.
[MAN 1D] You're the best
building manager ever!
Oh, hey, Jean.
Something wrong?
I thought you were going
out for drinks with Nino.
Couldn't shake the feeling
I was being watched.
[LOTTA]
What does that mean?
I dunno, maybe
I'm just restless.
[LOTTA]
Take that outside, please.
Right. Sorry.
[JEAN] I shouldn't feel like
someone's watching me
all the way up here.
Unless it's God.
S'pose it might be him,
or an ACCA chopper.
[JEAN]
The Five Chief Officers.
[LOTTA] Maybe the brass
has it in for you.
Glad I'm not the only
one who thinks so.
Audit all thirteen
branches in six months?
Dang. Maybe you
should just quit.
We still have this place to run.
So, when do you have
to start making the rounds?
Today.
Seriously?
Oh... you don't need to
worry about packing catalogs.
No? Why not?
I'm starting with
the local branch.
[BAKER 1A]
Thank you. Have a nice day.
Gotta be the freshest
bread I've ever eaten.
Yeah. It's delicious.
[RAIL] Not somethin'
you see every day.
Elites from HQ shopping here?
I thought you ritzy types
only patronized
the kind of grocery stores
that sell beluga caviar.
This bakery is top of the line.
That's why you fellas
come here every day
for your donuts, isn't it?
Branch staffers get
really good at sniffing out
the cheapest places
to buy quality grub.
Honestly I'm shocked
a guy of your rank
even knows what street this is.
[JEAN] Not to burst your
bubble or anything, but, uh...
You do know branch personnel
make a lot more than us?
If only it wasn't true.
[JEAN]
Our entrance exam's harder,
but the pay leaves
a lot to be desired.
One of the seven
wonders of ACCA.
Someone you know?
Nah. Just some guy
who won't leave me alone.
Yeah?
Well I guess not
everybody gets to be born
with a silver spoon up his ass.
[GRUS]
An audit? Now?
Uh, I have to say,
I'm a little caught off guard.
Yep, wouldn't be much
of an audit otherwise.
Every time,
I feel myself age.
[OFFICERS laugh]
[INSPECTOR 1B gasps]
You there, grunt.
Tell the Branch Director
I've arrived.
Chop-chop.
Yes! Right away, ma'am!
You're here, too, Otus?
Interesting.
Nice job.
Sorry for the delay!
If you'll follow me, please.
"You're here, too?" Huh.
[GRUS] The Director General is
conducting a surprise audit
personally?
Has something happened?
[JEAN]
No idea.
I just finished up my rounds
at our west station.
En route to east station now.
I'll do the north one tomorrow.
[GRUS]
Pardon me for saying,
but you always light up in the
middle of the central plaza.
One would think the higher ups
might advise against it.
They haven't so far.
Oh, hey... hungry?
[PINE]
Otus. Hello!
Hello, sirs.
[RAIL]
Tsk.
[LILIUM]
Conducting an audit?
Oh, yes, sir.
[PINE]
Your department made the cut.
Barely.
Yeah, so I heard.
It seems Grossular had a
last-minute change of heart.
He was very much
pro-termination at first.
Luckily, he was willing to take
my opinion into account.
And there's nothing
this one and Grossular
won't butt heads about.
Yes, well, we
can hardly be said
to share the same views.
The man's a
hard nut to crack.
Let's just say he plays it
rather close to the vest.
Truth be told, he's a lot like
you in that respect, Otus.
Well, I would have to cast
my vote with him about us.
[JEAN] I just don't see
how our department
has a role to play anymore.
It's why I put in a transfer
request for something relevant.
No point sticking around
where I'm not needed.
Unless of course you
know something I don't.
No one has a crystal ball,
my friend.
But if for some reason things
stopped being as they are,
inspection would indeed
have a role to play.
[PINE]
Director General Mauve.
Apparently she was
doing an audit of her own.
[JEAN] You say that
like you're surprised.
Isn't she here on behalf
of the Five Chief Officers?
[LILIUM]
Hm...
Whatever errand she's on,
we can be sure there'll
be no loose ends.
[LILIUM]
Well, then. See ya.
Thanks for the cigarettes.
--[JEAN] Sure. Take care.
--[GRUS] Pleasure seeing you.
Okay, then.
[siren wailing]
[GRUS] So many fires lately.
Another arson?
Damn, it's four o'clock.
East will have to
wait till tomorrow.
I promised a friend
we'd have drinks.
[GRUS]
Oh, I see.
[RAIL]
How 'bout that?
These days it's strange to see
someone carrying something
that could actually
start a blaze.
Something botherin' ya?
Nah.
[GROSSULAR] A coup d'état
in this day and age?
What a fascinating
bit of gossip.
Where, pray tell,
did you hear it?
[NINO]
Next time on ACCA:
13-Territory
Inspection Department :
"The Partner in Crime's
Name is Nino."
[NINO]
Oh, I gotcha.
So it's finally my turn,
is that it?
You know, Jean, you're
essentially hopeless without me.