-Drive A
-Akutsu, no!
-Hitting a drive volley
from that short distance,
That's intense.
-You shouldn't underrate
tennis the way you do.
[theme music]
-You're wasting your time, brat.
Come get it.
Don't make me laugh.
That's useless.
-Tennis is a unique
kind of sport
that ultimately depends on both
technique and mental agility
as well.
-Hey, if you stuck
to karate, you
wouldn't have a shrimp
like me beating you.
-There's no way.
-Akutsu's pride or
Echizen's courage?
Whichever one is stronger
will give us the winner.
-So it's come down to this.
Finally, it's match
point Echizen.
-Amazing.
You did great forcing
Akutsu into this.
Go for it, Echizen.
One more point and
we'll be the champs.
-I didn't expect you
to play this well.
-I guess we're not
quite evenly matched.
-Shut up, brat.
-You can do it, Ryoma.
-Come on, Echizen.
You can beat him.
-Hey, Horio, can't you
just watch quietly?
-Why?
What for?
This is the most critical
moment of the match.
-That's exactly why .
This is the first
time I've watched
to great match like this.
I'm going to watch it
very closely because I
want to be sure to remember it.
-You're right, Kachiro.
We'll want to remember this one.
-I guess so.
Echizen, I'm begging you!
-Will you shut up.
NANJIRO (VOICEOVER):
High up in the sky,
the skylark is twittering,
beautiful heaven-- ah whatever.
-What of Akutsu?
-We'll know any moment.
-That's for sure, but how
will both players take it?
INOUE (VOICEOVER): Will
Akutsu's wild animal instinct
give him the advantage?
Or will the samurai
in training win?
Either way, from now
on, there's going
to be a fine line between
winning and losing.
It won't simply be a
matter of technique.
-Akutsu is very focused now.
If Echizen gets even
a little careless,
Akutsu will turn
this match around.
-Look, the super rising shot.
-OK, kid, let's
see what you got.
Bring it on.
AKUTSU (VOICEOVER): Yeah,
keep hitting the ball to me.
I don't feel it.
Brat.
-Looks good.
You can do it, Echizen.
-Question is, how
long will he be
able to hold that
level of concentration?
-What?
-Inui is right.
Echizen's concentration
won't last forever.
It's a very tense situation,
similar to a string stretched
extremely tight.
There's no string that
won't break at some point.
-Oh, and by the
way, don't forget
that you still owe me big time.
This is for Kawamura.
And this is for Arai.
Who you beat up.
I'm not finished with you yet.
You also threw stones at me.
-It's the [inaudible].
-I already know how
to return that shot.
-He returned it.
-And from pinpoint range.
-Come on, brat.
-Look out, Echizen.
-Echizen!
AKUTSU (VOICEOVER): What's this?
A drop volley?
JUDGE: Game and match.
Seigaku's Echizen.
-Echizen did it.
-Whoa.
-That guy's crazy.
-Watch out, Echizen.
TOMOKA: Ryoma!
-I won the match, but I
think you played fairly well,
for the most part anyway.
[laughing]
-He won.
He actually won.
That kid is great.
[cheering]
-Boy, that was an
amazing victory.
[interposing voices]
-Coach Ryuzaki,
you did very well.
-Well, it wasn't just me.
It's because everyone played
their best and refused to quit.
-We'll beat you next time.
In any event, this was
a humbling experience
for Yamabuki.
Well, I'll be going now.
-Oh, Mr. Banda?
-What is it?
-We must enjoy playing tennis.
I think today's matches
really showed that.
-You made it, Echizen.
-You're great, kid.
-My juice is just the
thing for exhaustion.
-Get that away from me.
-Oh, honey.
Huh?
-He's really something special.
-Yeah, I agree.
-But Fudomine isn't really
satisfied with the results,
right?
Connors against McEnroe.
Gilbert versus Lendl.
Navratilova and Graf.
Sampras and Agassi.
Davenport and Venus.
It's rivalries like these that
make tennis so interesting.
Here.
You gave me a soda
just the other day.
I've been feeling bad because
I didn't have anything
to give you in return.
Sorry, but this
isn't very cold now.
-Oh.
-Build up your power because
I'm sure looking forward
to seeing your next match.
-All right.
Thank you for those kind works.
-Hey, Akutsu, come on.
It was a close match.
Don't take it so hard.
-But, Akutsu, don't.
-I know you're
frustrated, Akutsu.
It was your first loss, and
that's always the toughest one.
But facing up to difficulty
means you have potential.
It's important you
understand this
applies on the court and life.
So playing tennis isn't so--
-It's boring.
-Huh?
-I'm not interested in
playing tennis, not anymore.
Playing that kid,
that was enough for me
to realize I'm through with it.
Out of my way.
-I guess he just
got too burned out.
-You were saying she
isn't your girlfriend?
-Is that true?
-Yeah.
I've tried to tell people a
million times, but no luck.
-Well, then, can you
tell us who she is?
-Uh, Yuki, is Akutsu's mom.
-What?
-But all this time, you've been
calling her by her first name,
like you two were close.
-Well, it's like this.
She gets mad if I
don't call her Yuki.
-And just how old is she anyway?
-I think she's about 33.
-She's quite young to
be Akutsu's mother.
-I get it now.
No wonder we misunderstood.
JUDGE: We will now announce
the results of the five schools
that will advance to
the Kanto Tournament.
Japan Junior High School
Tennis Tournament Metropolitan
matches.
In boys team competition, the
champion is Seishun Academy.
Congratulations.
Next is the runner up.
Yamabuki Junior High School.
Third place goes to
Ginka Junior High School.
Fourth place is Fudomine
Junior High School.
And the fifth place
team in Hyotei Academy,
which won the consolation match.
-Hm, that's no surprise.
Am I right, Kabaji?
-Yeah.
-Just look at him.
No wonder he's a
nationally ranked player.
Keigo Atobe is
incredibly strong.
He was even able to fight
off Mizuki with ease.
There's no doubt Hyotei
will be advancing
far into the regional
matches, and then there's
Jiro to deal with.
He beat Yuuta in only minutes.
We'll have to watch out for him.
-I'm sleepy.
-Hey, where's Tomoka?
-Oh, she went to watch
the awards ceremony.
-So what are you doing here?
Didn't you want to watch it?
-Not really.
I mean, I already saw Ryoma,
and I congratulated him
on his victory.
What's the matter, Sakuno?
-It's something I noticed
watching Ryoma's match.
I felt like Ryoma was off
in another world far away.
I told him how I
felt but I'm not
sure my words reached his ears.
JUDGE: And for this, the
end of the awards ceremony.
-Come on, how 'bout it?
Let's go, Sakuno.
-Huh?
-We can cheer him on again.
You know, I've seen a
lot of people like him.
They concentrate so hard,
they can't see or hear anyone.
But I still sense that they
do want us to be there,
and I have a feeling that our
support does make a difference
to them, even if
they can't show it.
-Support?
-Hm, every player must
stand out there alone
on the tennis court.
No one is there to help them.
But you know what?
Sometimes I can feel our
cheers making Ryoma stronger.
Giving him that extra something
that he needs, especially
when he's struggling in a match.
I absolutely believe it.
Just take today's match.
You saw what happened.
[cheering]
-Go for it, Echizen!
-Now, listen,
Sakuno, you can make
Ryoma stronger by
supporting him 100%.
You can do it.
-Thank you.
-Well, let's get going then.
Come on.
-OK.
-Ryoma won.
What do you think of that?
You think he still
has a ways to go?
-And just what's your
point, Mr. Inoue?
-Nothing.
-Come on now, you've
raised my curiosity.
-Watching today's matches I felt
there was a new wind blowing
in the world of tennis out
there, don't you think?
I thought we had entered an era
where it was no longer possible
for a Japanese tennis player
to reach the world class level
as you did, and as a
consequence of that,
there would be no more great
players like you to emerge.
-There are no national
borders in tennis.
You're either a strong
player or a weak one.
-Nanjiro, tell me, do you
think Ryoma will play well
at the world class
level when he's older?
-(SINGING) Not yet, not at all.
Not yet, not on your life.
-Akutsu, they say you're
quitting the tennis team.
Tell me why.
How could you?
You're big, tall,
strong and confident.
I only wish I could
be like you, but I
know that there's no
way that'll ever happen.
Why are you leaving?
Please don't resign.
-Taiichi, if your
goal is to be like me
you won't have much of a future.
There's no possibility
for you beyond that.
He's someone for you to
possibly model yourself after.
He looks like he's
waiting for ya.
Later.
-Akutsu!
I'm gonna get on the
tennis court as a player,
just you wait and see.
No, I will!
Echizen, aren-- I'm going
to become a player instead
of just being a manager.
And then someday, I'm going to
have a match with you and win.
-You still have a
long ways to go.
-Excuse me.
-It was only the Metropolitan,
so don't get conceited.
Hey, you over there.
-OK, Dad.
I'll make you cry.
-Here we go.
[theme music]
-Hey, here's Horio.
Now that we won the
Metropolitan matches,
it's about time we concentrate
on the academic side.
I'll find romance and do
my best in club activities.
But I tell you, Echizen really
loves to get into fights.
He'll get in real
big trouble if he
acts like he's got
a swelled head just
because he can speak English.
What?
There's an intruder
at the tennis club?
Next, on the "Prince of
Tennis, Freestyle Fighting."
Hey, calm down, everyone.
Calm down.