-That's it, good serve.
Return it.
Good shot.
Oh, this is great.
Hey, your backhand
is improving, man.
-Hey, grandma.
We meet at 2 o'clock
tomorrow, right?
I'm just making sure.
-Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm afraid I can't go
with you tomorrow at all.
-What?
-Well, I forgot.
There's some important work
I have to do on Sunday.
-But if you can't go,
who's going to introduce me
to the man who is going to
restring my racquet for me?
-Good question.
Huh.
Ryoma, can you
come here a minute?
Are you free tomorrow?
-Why?
-Sakuno's strings of are pretty
loose, and you know him right?
Old Man Haritatsu.
I was going to take
Sakuno over to his shop
to get her racquet restrung.
-And so?
-Well, I can't go.
So I was wondering if I
could ask you to take Sakuno.
-But, Grandma--
-I don't exactly get
along with that old man.
-Oh, come on.
Please take her?
-I, uh--
-You wouldn't want to turn
down a desperate young lady
in her time of
need, now would you?
-Oh-- I-- I'd really
appreciate it.
-Well, OK.
I guess.
-Great.
I'm counting on you.
Tomorrow at 2 o'clock at
the station ticket window.
[theme music]
-Oh.
Oh.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER): Sakuno
Riuzaki, you're officially now
in big trouble.
Oh, what am I going to do?
I can't decide that to wear.
Only 15 minutes left
until 2 o'clock.
Oh--
[phone ringing]
-Oh.
Uh, hello?
The Riuzakis.
-Hey, Sakuno.
It's me, Tamoka.
How are you?
Are you free today?
Can you come over and hang out?
I have to watch
over my brothers.
Huh?
Restringing?
Oh, your tennis racquet.
-Yes, and, uh-- that's not all.
-Uh-huh, and with Ryoma?
Huh?
What?
No way!
You have a date with Ryoma?
-It's not a date, Tamoka.
My grandmother is practically
forcing him to take me.
-Sakuno, you little sneak.
I want to go with
you and Ryoma, too!
Awww!
-I'm telling you.
It's not a date!
-I am starved.
Hey there, young fella.
Where you going?
Out on a date?
-Just going to
restring a racquet.
-Now, that's very unusual.
Why would you want to go all the
way down to Haritatsu's shop?
-I have to take Coach
Riuzaki's granddaughter.
-What's this about
a granddaughter?
I knew it was a date.
Haha.
So, my son has finally grown
into a man at last, huh?
Your daddy's happy to hear it.
-We're only going to have
her racquet restrung.
-OK, make sure you have fun
so you don't have any regrets.
So he's finally going
out on his first date.
Hold it.
Does he even know anything
about how to take a girl out?
I got to see this myself.
-Oh-- Oh, no.
I'm going to be late.
Oh-- Oh.
Oh.
-Haritatsu's place is this way.
-Oh, I'm sorry I'm so late.
You must have
waited a long time.
Oh.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER): Oh, dear.
I knew it.
He's angry.
I was 30 minutes late.
Oh--
-You're still green, Ryoma.
You'll never be a
man if you can't
learn to forgive a girl
for being a little late.
-Oh, what's the matter
with that priest?
-He seems weird.
-Thanks so much for a
great day today, Momo.
-Thanks to you, we learned a
lot about how to pick out shoes.
-Yeah, and you treat us
to a delicious lunch, too.
-Yeah, it's the least I can
do as your upperclassman.
-Huh?
-Hey, it's Echizen.
-You're right.
It's Ryoma.
And he's with Sakuno.
-Do you think it's a date?
-I don't know.
I guess so.
-Oh, man, there's no way.
Lucky guy.
I'm jealous.
-No joke?
So those two have a little
romantic thing going on,
do they?
Ahh, the wonderful joys
of youthful pursuits.
I know what we can do.
-Huh?
-Let's follow them, guys.
-Yeah, but Momoshiro, you
sure have lots of time.
-Oh.
-Come on, now.
At least take her hand
and hold it close.
-All right.
-Well, I didn't mean the
two of you, but all right.
Why don't you two go for it?
-Huh?
-Hmm.
-I wonder where they're going.
Maybe to a movie.
[laughter]
-Echizen doesn't know the
first thing about anything.
[humming]
[mumbling]
-What's the matter
with that guy?
Hey,
-I know that priest.
He's the one who
discriminates against women.
-Against women?
-Let's go.
-I've never been to this
part of town before.
There are lots of sporting
good shops around here.
I wonder if the man
who strings racquets
works in a place like this.
Does he?
R-- Ryoma?
-Over here.
-Oh.
Wait for me!
-That boy sure
doesn't talk much.
Huh.
Ramen noodles.
Now that I think
of it, I haven't
had a single,
solitary bite to eat.
-Hey, you.
-Who are you?
-I knew I'd seen you before.
You better tell us why you're
following those two around.
-Oh, I'm sorry, I
no speak Japanese.
-Cut the act.
No one is going to believe
a Buddhist priest pretending
to be a foreigner.
-Ah!
-Huh?
-Aww, he's gone.
-Suspicious.
-What's up with that guy?
-I know.
It must be Sakuno who
he's really stalking.
-Huh?
-That no-good scum.
Now hear this.
We have to protect
Echizen's date.
-Huh?
-You with me?
-Well, yes.
-This is it.
Old man Haritatsu's.
-This building?
This is it?
-What's wrong?
-Oh, well, nothing.
It's just not quite
as I imagined it.
-Why not?
-Well, it's kind of
hard to say, really.
I've never had my
racquet restrung before,
but I thought it would
be a nicer looking place.
-They went into that grubby
looking shop over that way.
-Where's the stalker?
-There's no sign of him.
-Hmm.
Weird, huh?
This seems a little
bizarre for a date.
-I wonder what they're doing.
[traffic noises]
-Anyone around here?
-Oh--
-I welcome you.
-Oh-- oh--
-Well, well.
If it isn't little Ryoma.
I haven't seen you in ages.
And how's Nonjiro getting along?
-I guess he's doing all right.
[laughter]
-I'm glad to hear it.
Please give him my fondest
regards when you get home.
Who's this young lady?
What a nice girl
you have with you.
It is a great pleasure
to meet you, miss.
I am Tatsugoru, a specialist
in restringing racquets.
People call me Haritatsu,
hari, as in needle.
-Oh, oh, um, yes, I'm
happy to meet you too.
My name is Riuzaki.
-Riuzaki?
Huh.
You must be related to Sumire.
-Yes.
I'm her granddaughter Sakuno.
-Well, this really
is a happy occasion.
Please, come on in
the back and sit down.
Ryoma's dad and Sumire
have favored me for years.
And even though I
haven't seen him in ages,
I still occasionally get
word about Ryoma's latest
accomplishments on
the tennis court.
-Oh.
[laughter]
-Young lady.
You think Ryoma's a
strong tennis player?
-He's amazing.
-Yes, but in my view, his
game is still child's play.
He needs to keep working
hard on it to get better.
And become more like Nonji.
-No, I'm not going
to be like him.
-Uh--
[laughter]
-I've heard that
until my ears hurt.
-Never mind all that.
-Uh-- Yes, I'd like you to
restring my racquet, please.
-And just what do we have here?
Hmm.
Young lady, I can
see that you try
to hit the ball as hard
as you possibly can.
But you have difficulty
hitting the sweet spot.
-Huh?
How can you possibly tell that?
-Not to worry.
I'll adjust the thickness
and tension of the strings
so your hand becomes
more sensitive to what
the ball does on your racquet.
-Oh, thank you.
ANNOUNCER: Well,
we've finally come
to the finals of the All
Japan Tennis Championships.
Today will be the
men's singles finals.
This is going to be a battle
between two of the greatest
rivals in the present-day
Japan tennis world.
We hope they'll soon gain
international recognition.
-Ryoma, you probably don't know
this, but Nonji at his peak
was one of the strongest
tennis pros ever.
Power, speed, great
reflexes-- and he
amazed the crowd with
his flawless play.
He retired so suddenly, but
after his debut as a pro,
he played 37 tournaments the
world over and won them all.
He truly shook the tennis world.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER): I
wonder who this Nonji is.
Could he be Ryoma's father?
-Shoot.
That won't even pay
for a bowl of noodles.
Man, am I starving.
Maybe old man
Haritatsu will give me
something I can
put in my stomach.
-Young lady, this is
going to take a while.
So why don't the
two of you go out
for a nice little walk
around the neighborhood?
-Let's go.
-Huh?
-Ryoma, did you want your
racquet restrung too?
-No, thank you.
-What?
But then why did you
bring it along with you?
-They finally came out.
-Where are they going now?
-All right.
Let's follow them.
-Man.
The district matches
were so exciting.
-I'll say.
Especially that
seventh-grade kid.
-Huh?
What's this you say?
Was he really that good?
-Yeah.
In the finals he got hurt
and one eye was swollen shut,
but he still won the
match in just 10 minutes.
-On top of that,
he defeated the guy
who beat Kuki from Kakenoki.
He was terrific.
-Wow.
So you're saying
it only took him
10 minutes to win the match?
And what was the name of
this remarkable seventh-grade
player?
-What was the name of that kid?
I can't remember.
-It was Echizen.
Ryoma Echizen.
-Yeah, yeah, that's it.
-Hmm.
-I wonder if he will catch
up to his legendary father.
-Hey, Ryoma.
Thanks for bringing me.
-No problem.
-Mmm.
That Haritatsu is a
very interesting man.
-Yeah?
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER) I can't
even get a conversation going.
-That idiot son of mine.
How could he?
Boring a pretty
young girl like that.
When's he going to learn
that playing tennis isn't
all there is to life?
-Gee, you know,
it really doesn't
look like they're on a date.
Echizen keeps walking farther
and farther ahead of her.
-Nah, that's just
the way Echizen is.
Always aloof.
But he sure doesn't
know the first thing
about how to treat
a pretty girl.
I'm going to go tell him
me has to be nicer to her.
-No, Momo.
You can't interfere.
-You got to just
leave him alone.
-I know that, but
that poor little girl
is suffering because of him.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER): Hmm.
OK.
I've got nothing to lose.
I'll act like Tamoka
and be more aggressive.
-Uh--
-Hey, Ryoma.
What kind of music do
you like listening to you
when you're all alone?
I really like--
-I don't listen to music.
What's so good about
listening to music?
-Huh?
Oh, well, I just
thought-- well, maybe
you might like to listen
to some kind of music
together sometime.
-Echizen!
He's making things
even worse for her.
-Hang in there, Ryoma.
-That idiot.
What does he think he's doing?
Why doesn't he hurry up and say
something to make her smile?
-Well, it seems like today--
-Huh?
-You sure are talking a lot.
Why is that?
-Oh!
[groan]
-Why did you have to say that?
[crying]
-I can't stand it anymore.
-No, wait, Momoshiro.
Don't!
-Echizen!
I've been watching you.
I saw everything!
-Momo?
What are you guys doing here?
-What difference does that make?
The question is,
what are you doing?
-Huh?
What am I--
-Never mind that now.
Just go after her and apologize.
-But why?
I didn't really say
anything to her.
-Just go apologize.
Even if the Gods forgive
you for making a girl cry,
I know I'll never be
able to forgive you
for reducing her to tears.
-Huh?
-Now run!
Get going!
While you still got time!
MOMO (VOICEOVER) Now that's
what the springtime of youth
is all about.
-Hey, kid.
You've got spirit and
passion just like me.
I like you.
Hahaha.
-Wait a minute.
Tell me who you are, old man.
-Can't you tell
we're two of a kind?
-Huh?
-Oh.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER) It's stupid.
Getting upset like this?
I'm always like this.
That's why Ryoma doesn't-- Huh?
-Want one?
-Yeah.
Thank you.
-Here.
It's finished.
-Thank you very much, sir.
-Young lady, in tennis
as well as in life,
don't lose your focus.
I, Haritatsu, see and hear
everything that goes on.
-Yes, sir.
-Please tell Sumire
I said hello.
-Yes.
Yes I will.
Thank you again.
-Let's go.
-Oh, Ryoma.
Got a minute?
Just playing a
beautiful game of tennis
all the time must be
getting boring for you.
It's time you gave up
playing kid's games.
-Oh.
-But I am a kid.
-Just like his father.
-Now it's your turn to
come with me on my errand.
-Errand?
What could that be?
-There now.
That's more like it.
-So now it's building
up to the end.
The kiss.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER)
What should I do?
I'm playing tennis
against Ryoma.
-Don't get flustered.
This isn't a match.
I'm just checking your form.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER): So that's
why he brought his racquet.
He wants to check out my form.
Ryoma.
An upperclassmen was praising
my form just the other day.
Don't you remember?
You cautioned me about
it, and now I'm better.
-Glad to hear it.
-Ah!
-Oh!
That's the form that
won you such praise?
-No.
Of course not.
I just slipped and fell.
Could you please
feed me another ball?
Ha.
Ryoma?
Thank you for taking
me to Haritatsu's shop
in Grandma's place.
-Hmm.
-Did she just say
"in Grandma's place"?
-What?
So it seems like this
wasn't a date after all.
-I should have known
it couldn't happen.
Too weird.
Echizen having a date?
Haha, that's ridiculous.
-What?
It's not a date?
How boring?
-Oh, what a waste of time.
I'm out of here.
Oh!
[groaning]
-Hey, Mister, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
-I'm so hungry I
can't even move.
-You're such a loser.
Come on, I'll buy you some food.
-Oh, yeah?
That'd be great, kid.
Thanks.
-What a weirdo.
What is this guy's problem?
-Well, well.
Look who's here.
And what are you doing
here on a Sunday?
-Coach Riuzaki.
-What is it, Tazuka?
-I want you to let me
play against Echizen.
[theme music]
-I'm Tazuka, the team captain.
Echizen, the most
important thing for you
now is to awaken
your true potential.
Right now, you're
just copy of your dad.
You've got to want
something badly,
otherwise you'll
never achieve it.
Let me see the kind of tennis
that only you can play.
Show me that you can take me on.
Next week.
Seigaku's Strongest Man.
Part 1.
Echizen.
You think you can beat me?