-Captain?
-Listen to me.
Finish the match in 10
minutes, or you forfeit.
You got that?
-That's enough time.
[theme music]
SHINJI (VOICEOVER):
That's right.
Bring it on.
I haven't destroyed you yet.
-Huh?
-Wow.
What a mtch.
-Echizen's doing really great!
-He hasn't slowed down at all.
-Not only has he
not slowed down,
but his shots are getting faster
as the match has progressed.
-Even with that eye injury.
Unbelievable.
-Hey.
By the way, what is
that technique of yours?
My arm feels a little
funny sometimes.
Like it's going numb.
Temporarily.
BOY (VOICEOVER): You've
got your pace back, Shinji.
-Looks like he's only
giving Echizen top
spins and slices to return.
-I guess the same thing was
happening before the injury
to his eye.
-I see.
That must have been the cause.
It's a spot.
I'm pretty sure of it.
-But what spot?
-By returning
consecutive balls that
spin at about the same speed
in opposite directions,
the muscles go numb,
but only for an instant.
Go numb?
But if that's true, then
he can't move his arm
when he needs to hit.
-Right.
Whenever Echizen is in a spot,
Ibu takes advantage of it.
-Game to Ibu of Fudoumine.
Game count four to three.
-Wow!
Can you even believe it?
-Fudoumine won!
-That's gotta hurt.
SHINJI (VOICEOVER):
I can feel it.
I can see it.
His muscles contracting.
-Oh, no!
He lost his service.
That's bad.
-He's already at a disadvantage
with his eye injury.
Now if he has to
deal with a spot--
-There is a 0% chance of him
being able to make a return.
His grip loosens for a moment as
well, so he can't hit the ball.
He has 7 minutes
and 40 seconds left.
-Shinji Ibu.
I'm very surprised Fudoumine
has such a talented player.
-Speaking of tennis
phenoms, he's
at the same level as Fuji, one
of our top regulars at Seigaku.
I can't believe he's remained
off the radar for so long.
-He's better than we expected.
By contrast, our little
guy is slowing down.
ANNOUNCER: 15-Love.
-Hey, watch out!
[groan]
-Looks like he's hurting
physically and mentally.
-Come on, now.
Do it, Echizen.
-Oh!
-Was that the spot again?
-There is no question about it.
ANNOUNCER: 30-Love.
BOY (VOICEOVER): Shinji.
You've completely
mastered the spot now.
-Less than five minutes to go.
-Go, Echizen!
-Yeah!
ANNOUNCER: 40-Love.
-He's allowing Fudoumine
to get back into the game.
It's sure going to
be a real showdown.
-Is he going to be
all right, Tezuka?
Forget about the 10 minutes.
Maybe it's time to pull
him out of there right now.
-Don't worry about it.
-Tezuka!
-Oh, dear.
Ryoma!
-That's nice.
Everybody feels sorry for you.
But that's just what you
wanted, now, isn't it?
-Hm.
You're just going to have to
play the match to the end.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-Sorry to interrupt
your muttering,
but can you please
hurry up and serve?
My guess is that I only
have about three minutes
or so left to beat you.
-Can you believe it?
That seventh grader is still
out there provoking him.
-He's a good
opponent for Shinji.
-You are so arrogant!
-Just top spins and slices?
I don't like that technique.
-Huh?
-But then again, I've
found two weak points.
-What?
Huh?
-Have you tried to hit
it against a person who
can hit with either hand?
-Whoa!
ANNOUNCER: 40-15.
-I see now.
That's the way he
intends to win.
-This is weak point number one!
-No way.
It's impossible to read
the direction of the ball
at the same time
you're switching hands
to get ready to hit it.
-He's doing a split
step with one leg.
I see.
If he can do that
kind of split step,
it's easy to switch
hands quickly.
What incredible reflexes.
-I don't care
which hand you use.
I'm going to make both
of your arms numb.
-Look!
I think the Fudoumine player
is only hitting slices now.
-You're right.
He's hitting both top spins and
slices to give Ryoma the spot.
-He wants to hit
top spins, but he's
finding it's not
so easy anymore.
-What?
-You hit top spins by skimming
the top part of the ball,
but it's almost impossible to
return a ball with top spin
when it comes at chest level.
In that case, he
can only hit slices.
-So that's it!
-It's hsi number two weak point.
-Hey, where's your
top spin, huh?
-He's shutting down Shinji's
spot shot, with that injury.
What a player.
-Seigaku's Ryoma Echizen.
-That's easy!
-Yeah, Echizen!
-It looks like he's
going to make it in time.
-No!
Ryoma's bleeding!
-Go, Ryoma!
-Echizen!
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Seigaku's Echizen.
-Great!
If Echizen wins the next
game, he'll win the match.
INUI: There's less
than two minutes left.
SHINJI (VOICEOVER): I'm
not gonna let you win.
I gotta let Captain
Tachibana take
care of the rest
of the tournament.
ANNOUNCER: 15-Love.
15-All.
-Shinji's not giving
up the match yet.
-Come on!
ANNOUNCER: 30-15.
40-15.
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER): Echizen
is losing his strength.
-How much longer?
BOY: Tezuka?
-Hey!
Echizen!
Time to nail down a glorious
victory for Seigaku!
SHINJI: I'm going to win it.
SHINJI (VOICEOVER): The ball
spun in the opposite direction.
ANNOUNCER: Game and match
to Echizen of Seigaku.
-Awesome.
He turned that overhead
shot into a kick serve.
-Wow!
Incredible, Ryoma.
-10 minutes.
Did I make it in time?
-Yeah.
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER): Echizen.
Great job.
[cheering]
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER):
That kid really did it.
ANNOUNCER: The champion
of the district
manages is Seishun
Academy, and the runner up
is Fudoumine Junior High.
We hope both of your
schools play well
in the Metropolitan Tournament.
Thank you.
-They made it, Mr. Inoue.
Ryoma's team won
the championship.
-Huh?
Hey, um, so, is your right
arm feeling any better?
-Oh, it's doing OK.
Don't worry about it.
It really wasn't
your fault at all.
-Here you go, Taka.
-Yeah!
Man, that was quite
a shock you gave me.
Ha!
-Wow.
What's wrong with this guy?
-I'll beat you next time.
-I'm looking forward to it.
-Hey, Mr. Viper.
-You shut up, rhythm dude.
-Hey, Echizen.
I'm sorry about your eye injury.
Are you all right?
You know what happened really
wasn't my fault, don't you?
Oh, I get it now.
You did it on
purpose, didn't you?
Right.
I'll bet you did.
Boy, you really are
something else, you know--
-Shinji.
-Oh, sorry.
-You still got a ways to go.
-Oh, Ryoma.
-Wow, you made it, Echizen!
-Congratulations, Ryoma.
-Is your eye feeling any better?
-It's OK.
-Bu-- But my grandma said for
you to come with us after you
change.
-Huh?
-I think Tachibana
really wanted to play
their team captain, Tezuka.
-I think so too.
But then again,
it's all my fault
he didn't get to play him.
-I didn't say that.
What's your problem?
-Yeah, but it was
still my fault.
-Hm.
Huh?
We won't lose again.
I can promise you that.
-See you at the
Metro tournament.
-Yeah.
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER): It
took them only six months
to bring the team this far.
I'm sure Fudoumine
will be a tough team.
INUI (VOICEOVER): I wonder why
Tachibana looks familiar to me.
I better do some
research on him.
RYOMA: It stopped
bleeding already.
-But you still need to
have it treated properly.
-Oh.
You say you got this eye
injury playing tennis?
-That's right.
-Are you sure was
caused by tennis?
-Yeah.
I already treated the boy
with the wrist injury.
What a rough match
you guys must've had.
-Are you all right?
-Yeah.
-Well, let's get out of
here and go somewhere else.
-Huh?
You mean we're going
somewhere else now?
-That's right.
No more moping.
Let's get ready and go.
What do you say?
Hm?
RYOMA: Reserved for the day.
Is this a sushi restaurant?
[chatter]
-Huh?
-Hey, where you going?
Come on in!
-There you are Echizen!
We're over here!
-Hi there Ryoma.
Big smile.
Say cheese for me.
-Cheese.
[excited chatter]
-Thank you for inviting all of
us to share our victory today.
-On behalf of our
magazine, we thank you too.
-Oh, it's my pleasure.
Feel free to eat
up all you wants.
-Mr. Inoue and Ms.
Shiba, would you
do me the favor of
keeping your eyes
on these kids for
a little while?
-Of course!
Their big sister
will watch them.
With all the tender
love and care
they've grown accustomed to.
-Shiba.
What are you saying?
-What's going on?
-What are you gonna have first?
-Well--
-This is my dad's restaurant.
I called and told him
about our championship,
so he closed the
restaurant for us.
Come on, this is our
victory celebration.
Look alive, be merry!
Eat all you want.
-OK.
-Congratulations on your
championship, Coach Ryuzaki.
-It's just the
district preliminaries.
It's only gonna get tougher.
-Oh, I'm sure you'll win
at the Metro tournament.
Especially with that
genius seventh grader
you have on your team.
He's very different
from my clumsy son.
-Hey, don't say that, dad.
You're embarrassing me.
-Well, here you
go, Coach Ryuzaki.
I really shouldn't.
I have to drive home.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
How about one for you, mister--
-Tezuka, the team captain.
-Oh.
I guess I'll keep my big
mouth shut from now on.
-This one's mine here.
Hey!
Kaidoh, no fair.
You know that spicy
eel is my favorite.
-Oh no.
I need more sushi!
RYOMA: Yeah, me too.
-Those guys.
A-ha!
Hey there, Fuji.
You're being sneaky.
You're taking all
the sushi rolls.
Hey, look over there.
-Hm?
Uh.
-Ow!
Wh-- wh-- what are you eating?
-A wasabi roll.
-Tea.
Tea.
I need tea!
[laughter]
-Time to leave.
We still have to
stop by the school.
[chatter]
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER): Oh, well.
Today's a special day.
BOY: Take a look at that.
MOMOSHIRO: Oh, man.
Look at this special
chirahi sushi bowl.
It looks great.
Thank you so much.
-Hey, Momo.
You've eaten too much already.
Try saving some for the
rest of us, would you?
-Give me a break.
It's first come, first
serve around here.
-Hey, you're sneaky.
Momo.
-Ryoma, how about
a picture together?
Take a good one now, Kachiro.
-OK.
-Hey, that's my eel.
Oh!
There's more eel right here.
RYOMA: I'm home.
-Yo, Ryoma.
Did you have fun
at the tournament?
-It wasn't bad.
I suffered a slight injury, but
it should get well on its own
soon enough.
-Huh?
Injury?
What's that you
have on your face?
Seigaku?
-You mean this eyepatch?
NANJIRO: Hurry up and get well?
-It's just a little souvenir
from the championship.
[laughter]
[theme music]
-I'm Kenzo.
-I'm Shusuke.
-We're the comicd spy duo!
-Listen, Shunsuke.
Let's learn about
Echizen's secret.
-Where are we gonna
follow him to?
-Echizen is a school
library assistant,
and he loves hamburgers.
-Well, you've sure done
a great job already, sir!
-Next on "The Prince of Tennis."
-Is the Tennis Court Burning Up?
-By the way, Seigaku
girls are super lovely.
-Oh, they sure are.