[music playing]
-So, it seems like the two of
you have been spying on us.
That means both of you
have quite a bit of nerve.
-Uh oh.
Kenzo, sir.
-Mm!
-Oh, hey, look.
It's Ryoma and Momoshiro.
-Hey.
-(THINKING) That's the pretty
girl I saw a little while ago.
[laughing]
-Uh, sir, what's
the matter with you?
-It's all right now.
If you say you really want
it, I'll give you a chance.
-Huh?
-All right, then.
Let's play a game.
[theme music]
-There's some new people coming.
-Which school are they from.
-Excuse me.
Are you members of
the tennis team?
-Yeah, we sure are.
-You know where the
tennis court is?
-You'll see it after
you turn that corner.
-Did practice already start?
-Yeah.
-We better hurry up.
-Thank you.
-Gosh.
How many people
has it been today?
-That makes quite a few over
the past couple of days.
-And they're still
coming over here.
-I'm very sorry.
But I can't meet your demands.
Every school wants a
practice match with us.
They all seem to
be focused on us.
Is it Tezuka they want to see?
Or maybe it's-- hmm.
-That sushi tasted great.
-Yeah.
I hope we can go
back there again.
-Hmm?
-You know what, Fuji, I really
can't stand that camera that's
always following us,
even during breaks.
I wonder how many schools
are here to watch us.
-Let's see.
-Whoa!
The camera!
-Ooh, there were quite a few.
-Yeah I bet Inui's busy
counting them all up for us.
-There were 49
people watching us.
Compared to the last
two years, that's
a 1.75% percent increase.
-Oh.
-That's Inui for you.
-Hey, break is over.
There's not much time left
before the district finals.
Keep practicing,
and stay focused.
-Yes.
-Uh oh.
The team's starting
to heat up now.
-Guys, where's Ryoma.
Have you seen him?
-You know he works
in the library.
So he'll be late.
-Oh yeah.
That's right.
KENZO: Shunsuke, keep
watching them very carefully.
SHUNSUKE: All right, Kenzo, sir.
KIYOSUME: Wow.
-Huh?
-There are many cuties on the
Seigaku girls' tennis team.
I wish I was a
student at Seigaku.
Hey, that girl is
totally my type.
-So, did you really buy this?
-Mhmm.
It's a tennis ball
attached to elastic.
The ball comes back
by itself, so I
can practice hitting my
shots without a partner
-Looks like they're having fun.
I envy them.
They seem so friendly
with each other.
If I didn't have to take
care of my little brothers,
I'd be able to
join the team, too.
-Hey, today is free play.
How'd you like to try your luck?
Give it a shot, Tomoka.
-Really?
Oh, it's coming back.
There.
-You're good.
-Whoa!
-Oh!
You OK?
-[giggling]
-Huh?
-Hey, this is pretty cool.
-Snake shot, wow.
He's called Rupaido.
He used that boomerang
snake shot in the finals,
against Futomine.
-Hey, look over there.
It's Oishii co-captain,
and Kawamuar,
famous for his burning serve.
-On fire.
-Ooh, great.
Well, no wonder
they're regulars.
-The schools playing
in the metropolitans
are finalized-- the always
present Hyoutei Academy;
Yamabuki Junior High, who's
player Senbuku has experience
at the nationals; and then the
Block Two runner up, Futomine
Junior High.
SHUNSUKE: Strange.
KENZO: What's wrong, Shunsuke?
-It's just that I don't
see the seventh grader who
played at the district matches.
It looks like the only ones
practicing on the tennis courts
right now are well known
members like Fuji, and Kikumaru.
KENZO: Let me see those.
-Whoa.
-He's probably goofing
off, because he's not
interested in practice.
-He's not as dedicated
as you are, sir.
KENZO: What?
SHUNSUKE: [gasp]
-Wow.
-Wonderful, Ryoma.
-Yeah, you're good.
-No wonder at Seigaku they
have a great seventh grader.
-[gasp]
-Oh!
-Hmm
-Hmm.
-Awesome.
-He just stands there.
-You're very close.
But if you put a little more
weight on your pivot foot,
your shot would be
even more powerful.
-Thanks for that tip.
-Huh?
Oh!
-[gasp]
Oh no.
-He must be out cold.
-Who is he?
GIRL: Yamabuki Junior
High, Kyosumi Sengoku.
-Well, what should we do,
take him to the infirmary?
-Oh well.
-Hey, wait, Ryoma.
SHUNSUKE: Sir, sir, that's him!
-Oh, she's so cute!
-Huh?
Hmm.
[cracking]
-Waah!
[thud]
[moaning]
-Huh?
-That's the seventh grader who
played in the preliminaries.
-Yowie!
That's the seventh grader who
played in the preliminaries.
-Ryoma Echizen.
-Stop repeating
everything after me.
Hey, look over there.
It looks like he
works in the library.
Now I get it.
SHUNSUKE: Yeah?
So what?
KENZO: You are such an idiot.
No, listen.
Usually, it's the silent person
in the class who helps out
in the library, also the
one who maintains his cool,
and doesn't like to
hang out with friends.
-Oh, now I see.
-Quick, write that down.
That kind of data will
be crucial to the match.
-Really?
-He may be Seigaku's
secret weapon.
So we really should
check him out thoroughly.
-All right.
-We big goal.
And we mustn't let
ourselves forget it,
not even for a single instant.
-Yes, I'll never
forget, Kenzo, sir.
-Remember what happened, and
how upset we we're at the time?
The other team members
treated us badly.
But this time we'll show them
how important we really are.
We made a vow about
this on the hill
during that magnificent sunset.
-You said treated us badly?
But they only cut us because
we goofed off so much
during the really
hard practices.
-Hey, stupid, I don't think that
was really a practice at all.
It was really bad.
I think it was a nightmare.
-But even so, you shouldn't have
got me involved in this affair.
-What did you say?
-Uh, nothing.
KENZO: Listen to me.
If we gather all kinds of
information about this team,
the one everybody thinks
will win at district finals,
our tennis team is
bound to want it.
But I won't give it
to them for free.
We'll show them how
important we really are.
-Hey, sorry for making you wait.
-No bother.
KENZO: That guy with Echizen
is Takeshi Momoshiro,
his doubles partner.
-We can get information
on both of them at once!
--[chuckling] We're
going to get them!
-I changed my grip size recently
from a number three to a four.
-Since you tend to hit so
hard, I think a number of four
suits you even better.
TAKESHI: Right?
RYOMA: How about tension?
TAKESHI: I increased it to 80.
RYOMA: Your elbow
will take more shock.
TAKESHI: I'll keep training
to tone my muscles.
-This conversation
is quite revealing.
-No, not really.
-[gasp] Are you sure?
-I'm not looking for
this kind of data.
I want information about their
humanity, what makes them tick.
In other words, the real truth.
SHUNSUKE: The real truth?
-For example, what
are they eating?
-Uh, double burgers with
a side of fries and Cola.
-That's got to be pretty
filling for the price,
and they never get tired of it.
Seems like they're
regulars here.
That could be very important.
-Huh?
Very important?
What kind of truth is that?
-Think about it carefully.
You see, every person has a
routine that they follow day
in and out, week after week.
Then something happens,
or something goes wrong,
and they'll have to
break that routine.
-Oh, I see.
-Now if they order
something different,
or if they went to a
different restaurant, that
would mean something
was going to happen.
And we have to know about it.
So pay close attention.
Always be aware.
-Oh, great, sir.
You are so insightful.
-[chuckling]
TAKESHI: Hey, let's go.
-Right.
-Hmm.
-[chuckling]
-These sneakers look great.
-Yeah.
But don't you think
they're a little expensive.
-I think they'll
give us a discount.
The Seigaku team
shops here regularly.
-This is Jupiter.
What's up, Space Orbiter?
-Jupiter?
Orbiter?
What are you suppo--
-They're code names, of course.
Can't you figure anything out?
-Why am I--
-Stop questioning
everything, and get to work.
-Whoa!
-I don't know about these.
Maybe if they had them in--
-Huh?
-Closer, come on.
Closer.
-[sigh] Hmm.
-Hey, these look cool.
-Which ones?
-These.
-They cost too much.
-But they're on sale now.
RYOMA: Hmm.
-Oh!
-Hey.
-Huh?
Huh?
-Oh no.
He spotted him.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
look over here.
Hey, hey, hey, over here.
Over here.
-Huh?
Mm.
-Uh oh.
-Huh?
-[clearing throat] Uh.
-Well, oh, um,
[nervous laughter] Excuse me.
-[whistling]
-Oh, sir.
-Idiot, use code.
Anyway, did you get what
they were talking about.
-Seigaku regulars are
good customers here.
And the shop is
having a discount sale
on shoes, shorts, and underwear.
-Uh, I don't want such
trivial information.
I'm definitely going
to need something
with more impact than that.
-More impact?
-Something that will
influence the next match.
Maybe if we could
find out about their--
RYOMA: Weak points, huh?
-Right.
Their weak points.
If we find out what
they are, our data
will become much more valuable.
Huh?
Wha?
I bought that ball I
showed you at this shop.
-Oh.
I want one, too.
-So, it seems like the two of
you have been spying on us.
That means both of you
have quite a bit a nerve.
-Uh oh.
Kenzo, sir?
-Mm.
-Oh, hey, look.
It's Ryoma and Momoshiro.
-Hey.
-(THINKING) That's the pretty
girl I saw a little while ago.
-Are these friends of yours?
-Actually, they're--
-[laughing]
-Uh, sir, what's
the matter with you?
-It all right now.
If you say you really want
it, I'll give you a chance.
-Huh?
-All right, then.
Let's play a game.
-Huh?
-I don't know.
They're kind of weird.
-You may be right.
Perhaps we shouldn't
get involved with them.
KENZO: Hey, you backing out?
-Hmm.
[music playing]
-Oh, Kenzo, how did
it turn out like this?
-Shut up.
We can't help it now.
-Even if there are pretty
girls here to watch our game,
there's a huge difference
between Seigaku's regulars
and us.
-Will you shut up?
We'll use the
chance to find some
of the weak points of
their doubles game.
Up or down?
-I'll take up.
-You sure this is going
to be OK, Kenzo, sir?
-Don't worry about it, OK.
If we get to serve first, we'll
have a chance to win this game.
Oh no.
We practically lost
the game already.
-Hey, we haven't even
begun the game yet.
So let's get started.
-Darn.
I guess we have to play now.
-Seems like it, sir.
[music playing]
-Huh?
GIRL: 15-love.
[giggling]
-Don't fail me now.
-Wow.
Great.
-I suppose.
-I don't have a chance.
-Come on, guys.
Get serious.
-Yes, I am.
Yah!
-Huh?
It's slow.
-That ball's mine!
Whoa!
-[gasp]
-[moaning]
-Are you all right, sir?
-Man, compared to that
terrible practice I endured,
this kind of thing, as bad
as it looks, it's a cinch!
Yeah!
-Oh, sir.
KENZO: Stop crying.
SHUNSUKE: OK, I will.
-I feel sorry for them.
-Mm.
-The battle has just begun.
-Huh?
-Wah!
[music playing]
-[panting]
-I can't believe it.
They haven't scored a single
point in the game yet.
-I know.
-What's the score?
-It's love-40.
-It's match point.
[music playing]
-Yah!
Wah!
Oh!
-What's that?
-Uh, sir?
-Huh?
-He made it!
-Wow!
That was awesome!
-Huh?
-You did it, Shunsuke!
-But it was-- I didn't--
-Yes.
We finally scored a point.
-Oh, s-sir.
-Shunsuke!
[weeping]
-[giggling]
-[grunting]
-Please, sir, watch out.
-You guys don't look like
you can play anymore.
And the match is almost decided.
-I, I'm still able to play.
-I think it would be
better if we stopped now.
-But--
TAKESHI: That was a great shot.
-Huh?
-You should be
proud to have made
a point like that against us.
I never expected to see such
a passing shot from you.
-Momo, it's sad you
couldn't manage that.
-And sometimes
you talk too much.
But I think you guys will
be good players some day.
-You really think that's true?
-Only if you
practice really hard.
-You're really,
heh, quite strict.
[laughing]
-Shunsuke, it feels good
after you play a match,
don't you think?
-I agree.
-Shunsuke, better give it to me.
SHUNSUKE: What?
[gasps]
-Huh?
-I'm done with this.
There will be no more gathering
information on the fly for us.
If we want to impress
our teammates,
we'll have to do it
on the tennis court.
-But sir.
-I enjoy playing
tennis a lot more
than simply watching
others play the game.
And as for you, we'll
practice some more.
And then we'll want
a return match-up.
-OK.
We'll be ready anytime.
-Later.
Thanks for playing
with us, and for taking
us lower level
players seriously.
Now we can brag that our
game with Seigaku's regulars
ended in a draw.
SHUNSUKE: OK.
-What a pair.
-Huh.
Eighth grade regular
Takeshi Momoshiro
has a one-sided love for a girl
who is also an eighth-grader.
Huh?
-[chuckling]
GIRL: What? who is it?
Let me see it.
GIRL: Hey, Tomo stop it.
TAKESHI: Come on.
Stop it.
Don't look.
Hey, don't look at it.
-[breathing deeply]
[music playing]
MALE SPEAKER: I'm Otube
of Hyoutei Academy.
Incidentally, did you
know we're the first seed
team in the district finals?
Hey, girly-girl.
You're so cute.
If I win my tennis match, you'll
go on a date with me, right?
Who's that guy
with the short hair
in that rhythm dude with him?
You're a pain in the neck.
You're really heating up.
Hey, it looks like a bunch
of weak players got together.
Next, on "The Prince of
Tennis: Kaoru's Troubles."
By the way, who's this Kaoru?