-[panting]
-All right, kid.
Let's continue.
What do you think?
Should I give you a handicap?
-No need to.
-Staying on your toes, eh?
Where'd you learn that?
-Why don't you mind
your own business?
-You're no fun.
Why don't you relax,
and ease up a little?
-Get on with it, and serve.
-Hah.
Act tough, and
you'll only be sorry.
[theme music]
-Game to Inui.
[gasps]
-[sigh]
SPECTATOR: I can't believe it.
Ryoma lost his serve.
-Well, you know it's not
so easy to make changes
in your style of play,
especially when you're
under that much pressure.
You try new stuff over and
over, but your opponent
is there waiting.
And any normal
player would probably
panic, and self-destruct
right about now.
-You know, you're
really pretty good.
It's apparent that
you've instinctively
calculated my reach and height.
And you always seem to
take aim just beyond it.
You may have more
talent than I do.
And you're definitely
stronger than you look.
However, as long as I know where
you're going to hit the ball
there's no shot I can't return,
no matter how good it is.
-Oh!
-There's no doubt that
one day, you'll become
a Seigaku regular,
but not today.
Because I'm going to win.
-You still have a ways to go.
-Hmm?
-Oh!
-I'm glad I enrolled
at Seigaku, because it
means I can beat all
kinds of tennis players.
-What does he mean he can beat--
-All kinds of tennis players?
-Ryoma's going to come back.
He's going to turn this
match right on its head.
-Huh?
Hmm.
-I just got the hang of
this footwork recently.
It's more complicated
than it looks.
You know, I wanted to keep
it a secret from everyone
around here, at least until
the national tournament.
-Oh!
Awesome!
-That's so cool.
Did you hear that Mr. Inoue?
Can you eve believe it?
-The national tournament?
He's not running
short on confidence.
-Mr. Inoue, I think
I've finally decided.
-Decided what?
-From now on, I'm going to
focus on Ryoma Echizen in depth.
-What, in depth?
[gasps]
-What I mean is, what ordinary
student would say something
like, I wanted to keep
it a secret from everyone
until the national tournament.
Yeah!
Go Ryoma!
You're so cute.
-Hey, cut that out.
-What's it to you what I do?
-If you're thinking of
doing a story on Ryoma,
you're going to have
to go through me.
I'm the president of
his Official Fan Club,
you got that?
-Huh, official fan club?
-Wanna join?
-I'm not interested in
joining his fan club.
I just want to let
tennis fans nationwide
know what makes Ryoma
so special and adorable.
-You just called him adorable!
How dare you do that?
I won't allow you to
do a story on him!
-Calm down, Tomo.
The game's about to begin.
Huh?
-(THINKING) The
national tournament?
You're kidding me.
Ah!
Now, which way will you hit?
The probability is--
-Isn't it a bother?
How about if I save
you all that trouble?
I'm doing it this
one to the right.
-[gasp]
-Uh!
-Not falling for that.
-Next one's left.
Uh!
-What?
Why is Echizen telling him
where he's going to hit it?
He's making it easy for
Sadaharu to return his shots.
-Next one's right.
Uh!
-I knew it.
This was bound to happen.
He's returning everything.
-Don't you see what's going on?
Ryoma is getting into position
at the same time as Sadaharu.
-Behind you.
-(THINKING) So Naive.
Too bad I figured you'd
attack on the same course.
-Next one's left.
-Ah!
CALLER: Out.
15-love.
-Oh man.
It was barely outside the line.
-Sadaharu couldn't have
gotten to it if he tried.
-You're right.
Ryoma's doing great.
He's moving so much
better than he was before.
-Hmm.
-Ah!
He's too cool for words.
-I think he's using
the split step.
-I overdid it a bit.
I've still got to work on it.
I've got to hand it to
you, though, Sadaharu.
You knew that was
going out, didn't you?
-Hmm.
(THINKING) Thanks a lot.
You knew it's not
that I didn't move.
I couldn't move.
His reaction speed, remarkable.
Tezuka used to be
the only one who
could compete against
my shots and data.
Interesting.
What data will you
show me this time?
I can't wait to find out.
-This time, right.
[music playing]
-Ah, here ya go.
-[grunting]
[dong]
-[panting] All right, kid.
Let's continue.
What do you think?
Should I give you handicap?
-No need to.
-Ha, staying on your toes, eh?
Where'd you learn that?
-Old man, why don't you
mind your own business?
-You're no fun.
Why don't you relax,
and ease up a little?
-Get on with it, and serve.
-Ha, act tough, and
you'll only be sorry.
-Uh!
-That's not too bad, my boy.
What a shame.
All that youthful energy wasted,
because the ball lands just
outside the line.
-Hey, old man.
I wish you'd be serious
once in a while.
-Yeah, yeah yeah.
Who do you think you're
talking to here, son?
You want to play
me seriously now?
Hah.
You still have a ways to go.
-You asked for it.
Old man, I'm going to
make you regret that.
Uh!
[music playing]
-What's with Ryoma's strokes?
He's starting to
play kind of weird?
-Mm, almost like he was jumping.
-It has a name.
It's called the split step.
-Split step?
-Mhmm.
-How can you play tennis without
knowing about the split step?
Just ask me about
it, and I'll tell you
everything you need
to know for sure.
SPECTATOR: Can you do it?
-Of course I can.
I've been playing
tennis for two years.
I can do anything.
The split step is one of
the fundamentals of tennis.
You jump up lightly,
just as your opponent
hits a volley, and
land on the ground
with the toes of both feet.
That makes your reaction
time to the ball
a half step faster as
you take your next step.
-Really?
Amazing.
-But how does that speed up
your reaction time to the ball?
-Well, you know, it's kind
of sort of like faster.
Fuji, you tell them.
-It produces a spring
in your muscles
that lets you accelerate as
you rush to hit the ball.
-A spring in your muscles?
What do you mean?
-If you're a half
step faster, you
can get to a ball that's one
meter farther away than you
normally could.
So Ryoma is actually
moving faster
than Sadaharu's predictions.
-Boy, you guys are so
knowledgeable about tennis.
-If only the same
could be said for you.
15-all.
[gasps]
-(THINKING) Split step.
-Next, I'll be hitting it to
the right, then attack the net.
-He's on the offensive now.
-Way to go, Ryoma!
-[sigh]
-He's so fast.
-The split step has sped up
his normal reaction time.
And he's not even
doing it right.
Ryoma's doing a variation on
the traditional split step.
Usually, you're supposed
to land on both feet.
But Ryoma lands on one foot.
He's already in position.
-Left.
-I had that one predicted.
-Oh no!
He can't reach it.
-Hmm.
Hmm?
-Next one's left, too.
-Wow.
Ryoma's amazing.
-Coming right.
-(THINKING) There's a 95%
probability that he'll go
right.
Yes.
As I predicted.
And now-- oh!
-Oh!
-15-30.
[sighs]
-Sadaharu is losing.
-I can't believe it.
-What's happening?
-Oh, unbelievable.
-He did it!
Ryoma won the point!
[interposing voices]
-Hmm?
-Oh, Ryoma.
-Ryoma's rhythm is
getting faster now.
He's playing to the beat
of his split step rhythm.
His step goes far
beyond the basics.
I've never seen
anything like it.
That kid's lots of fun.
-But hang on a second.
Landing on one foot
makes him quicker.
But unless he knows where his
opponent is going to hit it,
it's no use.
And if he comes down
on the wrong foot,
it's going to be a
disadvantage, right?
His feet would get
all crossed up.
And he'd fall flat on the court.
I can't figure out
how he does it.
There must be some
kind of trick.
Does Echizen have data that
predicts Sadaharu's shots?
-No way.
Only someone like Sadaharu
plays that kind of tennis.
-Then how is Ryoma doing it?
-Well, it looks like he's making
his decisions as he jumps.
You see, that makes him quicker
not just by half a step,
but by a step and a half.
-One and a half steps?
-That much?
That's a huge advantage.
-Uh huh.
-That's his secret.
His added quickness allows him
to reach unreachable shots.
-Yah!
Go get it, kid.
How's this?
-Huh?
-Woo-hoo-hoo.
Gotcha that time, kid.
You fell right into my trap.
-Give me a break.
You're so immature.
-Put you in your place,
didn't I? [laughing] Sorry.
I'll keep you company
until dinner time.
All right, kid.
Try this.
-I told you to get serious.
Uh!
Heading left.
-(THINKING) This kid's fast.
[grunting]
CALLER: Game to Echizen.
Game to Inui.
Game to Echizen.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-What a split step.
Unless you have
considerable natural talent,
that technique is
impossible to master.
And for a seventh grade
player to have done
it is almost unbelievable.
-Are you telling us that
Ryoma is a genuine prodigy?
-Of course he is.
If my Ryoma isn't a
genuine tennis prodigy,
then nobody around here is.
-Listen, you.
You've been calling
him your Ryoma.
Well it's not you Ryoma.
So why don't you just pipe down?
-Oh yeah?
What's wrong with
calling him that?
Ryoma is my prince.
-Are you kidding me?
(MIMICKING) Oh, Ryoma.
He's my darling prince.
-You only wish you
could call him that.
But you can't.
Because only fan
club members are
allowed to call Ryoma Prince.
REPORTER: What's the big deal?
[interposing voices]
-What's up with them?
-Why are they arguing?
-Just leave them alone.
-Sadaharu must think
that he's playing
against a totally
different person right now.
-Well, back to business.
I never thought I'd run into
another player whose shots I
could predict but not return.
It's not over.
If I calculate all
the probabilities,
taking into account the
current game pattern,
weather conditions, and
energy loss owing to fatigue,
I can still win.
-Hmm, Sadaharu's
one tough opponent.
-OK, here we go.
Huh?
(THINKING) He switched
to his right hand.
Is he really going to
serve right-handed?
[gasps]
-Oh, I get what he's doing.
-Hey Sadaharu.
Here's one more shot you
may be able to predict,
but you won't be able to return.
-(THINKING) Predict
but not return?
A right-handed serve.
He's trying to trick me.
But I won't be fooled.
Oh!
-He did it!
He used his kick serve!
-[gasp]
[sound of amazement]
-Yahoo!
Ryoma's going to win!
-Now that he's using
his kick serve.
--[panting] (THINKING)
Kick serve?
He has to use his
right hand to hit it.
But wait.
What if he could hit a shot
like that with his weak hand?
What if this kid is
really that good?
-I'm not as strong
using my right hand.
But I'm aiming for it to go
straight towards your glasses.
-Mm.
-Ah!
[music playing]
ICHI: Hiya, I'm Seigaku
ninth grader, Ichi Kikumaru.
With the regulars decided,
the Seigaku tennis team
begins full training for
the metro tournament.
Huh?
Sadaharu's going to coach us?
Give us a break.
What is that, a special drink?
Ugh, it's disgusting,
and tastes bad.
-Next on "Prince of
Tennis: The Hard Day."
Drink it up.