INUI (VOICEOVER): Kick serve.
He has to use his
right hand to hit it.
But wait.
What if he could hit a shot
like that with his weak hand?
What if this kid is
really that good?
I'm not as strong
using my right hand.
But I'm aiming for it to go
straight towards your glasses.
[theme music]
ANNOUNCER: 30-Love.
INUI (VOICEOVER): Shots
coming straight at your body
are the toughest
ones to get out.
To return a kick
serve, the best way
is to scoop back the
left leg for the swing,
then step into the shot
from the right foot
and hit a slice while
keeping sideways to the net.
Well, so much for theory.
-All right, yeah!
-Yay!
ANNOUNCER: 40-Love.
-If you're gonna
play based on stats,
then I'll just figure
out another way.
INUI (VOICEOVER): What a jerk.
Just a smart aleck rookie.
-He got it.
-You still have a ways to go.
ANNOUNCER: Game and set to
Echizen, six games to four.
-He won!
He's so cool!
Ryoma is amazing!
-Wow.
-I can't believe Ryoma won.
He's crushed two
regulars already.
Not bad.
-Really?
-Oh, hi, Momoshiro.
-I said to call me Momo.
Wow, Ryoma's pretty good
to take apart Sadaharu.
He's picked up his kick serve
since the last time we played.
-Sorry I got kinda mad,
but it was a great game.
-I gathered good data.
Just don't get it.
I should have won.
Must have used the wrong foot.
-I don't ever want to
play that guy again.
-How do you do it
every single time?
-Awesome!
I knew you were gonna to win
that one from the very start.
-Horio, you sure seem to
change your mind an awful lot.
KAIDOH: Sh.
You're bothering me.
Why don't you guys shut up?
-Yes sir.
-Let's go, Ryoma.
Four matches undefeated!
ANNOUNCER: Game to Echizen.
Game to Echizen.
Game and set to Echizen,
six games to Love.
-Wow, he did it!
-You guys know what that means?
Four matches won!
-Yeah, now he's a regular!
-Regular?
-It's too wonderful!
We'll have to congratulate
him later, right, Sakuno?
-Yes.
Yes, we will.
-Aw, man.
That guy has no mercy.
-Come on, he's right here!
Um, Ryoma.
It's cool that you're a--
-Hey, punk.
Move it.
-The last regular slot
is on the line here.
Each player has two wins.
-It's a tough call, but
probably Sadaharu will take it.
He's won every time
they played so far.
-The angle of his
snake shot has changed.
ANNOUNCER: Game and
set goes to Kaidoh.
Seven games to five.
-Tough luck, pal.
-It makes no sense.
My data appears to
have let me down.
-Did you see all the top
spin Kaidoh put on the ball?
It was the coolest-- Oh!
-Looks like we're going to
have a strong team after all.
-Yeah.
-Well, now the eight
regulars have been decided.
-Captain Kunimitsu
Tezuka, ninth grade.
Co-captain Shuiciro
Oichi, also ninth grade.
Shusuke Fuji, ninth grade.
Takashi Kawamura, ninth grade.
Eiji Kikumaru, ninth grade.
Takeshi Momoshiro, eighth grade.
Kaoru Kaidoh, the eighth grade.
And the only seventh grade
regular, Ryoma Echizen.
-I can't take it.
We're just not strong
enough to play the regulars.
-Ryoma.
Write your size on this.
-My size?
-Oh.
You know, that's
for your uniform.
-That's right.
It's gonna have youe name on
the back of it and everything.
KACHIRO: Oh, man.
That so rocks!
You have no idea how
cool this is, Ryoma.
You're the only seventh
grader with a team shirt.
-Oh man.
I wonder if I'll ever get one.
-Aw, no problem.
Once our senior
students graduate.
Whoa.
-Sakuno.
-Hey, what's up?
-Uh, I mean, Ryoma,
about the team.
-Hi!
Hey, Ryoma!
What's going on around here?
I hate to miss anything.
I can't stand it!
Congratulations on
making the team, Ryoma.
-Um.
-As president of your fan
club and your number one fan,
I'm so proud!
You too, huh girl?
-Well, yes.
Ryoma, I think that you--
-Oh, I know.
Why don't we go
somewhere to celebrate?
We'll have a big party,
'cause Ryoma's gonna
be a team regular.
So big!
-You're joking.
-Not at all.
We have to celebrate
special days like this.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, Ryoma!
Wait up for us!
-Ryoma!
-Echizen!
-Ryoma, I, um, wanted
to say to you--
[whine]
I just wanted you to
know how impressive I
think it is that
you made the-- Huh?
-Echizen?
-Well, yes.
I thought he might be hanging
around here during lunch,
'cause he's a
member of the team.
A regular now.
-I haven't seen him around.
He might be out on the courts.
-Oh.
Thank you so much.
-Echizen?
No, I haven't seen him.
-Any ideas?
-What a flirt.
Are you gonna confess
undying love for him.
-No!
Nothing like that.
-Ah, puppy love.
Oh to be young and in love.
-She's only one year
younger than you are.
-You know, you team
members work really hard.
Practicing on lunch
break and everything.
Nothing better to do.
We're just killing some time.
-For me, it's all
about beating this guy.
So let's play, Momo.
-All right.
-Wow.
The regulars are amazing.
I can't believe Ryoma made it.
Ah!
Oh, I'm-- I'm so sorry.
-Oh, Ryoma Echizen, where
could you have gone?
-Seigaku!
Fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight!
-Seventh graders,
I can't hear you.
-Sir!
-Our a regulars
sure do have spirit.
-Of course they do.
And the district prelims
are coming up soon.
-We'll win 'em.
What are you girls doing
here, watching again?
-We're not watching.
Oh, no.
We're cheering.
There he is! my dreamboat!
-Hey, you, over there!
-Wha--
-Pick up balls, and
stop your gabbing.
Here.
Here!
Come on, guys.
Pick up the paste.
-I can't believe your
grandma's so scary.
-Aw, she usually.
Just now.
-Team, time to line up.
-Now that, I don't
have to remind you all
that the metro tournament
is right around the corner.
The eighth regular members
we chose through our interest
squad tournament will
compete as a team
through the metro tournament.
Every school has raised its
level of play since last year.
We cannot take
anything for granted.
That's it.
-Everyone, back to practice
eighth and ninth graders court
see em.
-Regulars, practice serves.
-All righty, then!
Said!
-Just a minute, many guys.
For your regular
team members, I've
asked this young
man here to plan out
a very, very special practice
regiment for the team.
-Sadaharu?
-Hello.
To get through the long
match scheduled nationads,
We'll start with lower
body strength training.
These are ankle weights.
There are two half
pound lead bars in each.
They'll get your legs a
little bit better resistance.
-You know, that's
not much weight.
INUI: I also set out red,
blue, and yellow cones,
and made up lots of
these balls I colored
with red, blue,
and yellow lines.
-OK.
Sure, I got it.
-If you miss, you're gone.
Here we go, Eiji.
-It's red.
It's red!
-Whoa!
Look at the control he has!
-Blue!
-What an eye.
It's amazing how he tracks
the color just a second
after Sadaharu hits it.
-Yellow!
-Then he hits it back perfectly
to the same color cone.
No one's better than Eiji
at attracting moving object.
There is.
Look there.
He's better.
Red!
Huh?
Sakuno, they're not just
hitting them really hard.
Lookit!
They're smashing the balls, and
hitting the same color cones.
-I know!
Can that be possible?
-They're both doing pretty well.
-It shouldn't be well long now.
They're going to feel
those ankle weights.
-My legs feel like
they weigh a ton.
Now I get it OK.
OK, it's red.
-Sorry, that's blue.
-No way!
I know it's red.
Why'd you do that?
It was red.
I was right.
You tricked me, Sadaharu!
-When your stamina goes,
so does your judgment.
Kikumaru, you're out.
Oh, and I forgot to tell
you something If, you miss,
you get to drink my extra
special vegetable juice.
-What's up?
Why is it that strange
I don't you worry?
It's all edible.
Come on, drink it all, hotshot.
-What is this stuff?
Water!
-Ryoma!
-Huh?
-What you waiting for, guys?
You're next.
-I can't afford any mistakes.
It's red!
Blue!
Shuichiro is good.
That's one scope the kind
of quiet butcher can hit.
-[screaming]
-Here's your racket, pal.
-Gee, thanks.
-It's red!
-He's certainly a noisy player.
-Be he sure is a good.
His personality sure changes
when he gets on the court,
doesn't it?
-Yep.
-OK, red ball!
-Red!
-That's great.
He's so good.
-Momo can really power
one over the next.
-Blue!
-Steak shot!
Right in one.
Kaidoh did it.
-Red ball.
[groaning]
-Kaidoh couldn't even
take that awful cocktail.
-That juice looked
absolutely disgusting.
Bleh.
-Huh?
Shusuke messed up, too.
-Shusuke, you did
that on purpose!
I wanted to try this goop.
It's really not all
that gross, you know?
It's good.
-Liar.
It stinks.
-Man, it's hard to believe that.
He drink drank that stuff.
Will moved better
than I expected.
To the amount of who
you lost your grip.
When you hit the ball.
A little weight training will
strengthen those forearms.
-So Ichiro and Kaorou, you
guys are having trouble
getting your racket
around the ball.
All of you clowns need to work
on your quads and triceps.
-We don't even know
where they are.
-Momoshiro, pull back
your power a little,
and you'll increase
your accuracy.
-Right.
Kunumitzu, you didn't miss,
but you need flexibility,
and you're too serious.
And last, Ryoma.
Drink two of these a day.
-You can't make me grow, no
matter how much milk I drink.
-Drink it up.
-I wouldn't argue with him.
It really does work.
-He sure is living
proof of that.
-Let's get back to work, guys.
We'll add one lead
weight to your ankles.
-Hang on a second.
-Just add five.
-Huh?
-Isn't that what you're using?
-Seems maybe to me going
to get to five eventually.
What do you think?
-Even six would be
OK.
You are also slow.
Think 10.
-That's not fair.
I didn't sign on for this.
Quit messing with us.
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER):
Building stamina
will improve their games a
lot, but the biggest weapon
they have is--
-Kunimitsu, don't
overdo it right now.
I'm going you healthy
for the season.
Even my worry is that
we win every single one
of our tournaments.
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER):
Their desire to improve.
It's amazing how he got such
a competitive group together.
OK, back to practice.
Our goal is to be the
number one seated school!
-Seigaku!
Right!
-Well, this has
gotta be a mistake.
This shirt is a small.
-We've always supplied the
tennis uniforms for Seigaku,
but this one's a first.
Ah, come right in.
-It's just amazing.
Our regulars rock.
Don't you think so, Kachiro?
-Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Have you seen how well
Ryoma is keeping up
with the regular team?
-It sort of seems like he's
in a whole different world.
-Ryoma!
So, tell me, is that
your new uniform?
-Yeah, I just got it.
-Wow.
That's great.
It'll look wonderful.
Can I see it on?
-Yeah, I'll have it on tomorrow.
-Oh.
That's right.
I forgot about practice.
-Hm.
Just right.
-Ryoma, congratulations
on the team!
-Thanks.
[theme music]
-I'm Sasabe.
Been a while right?
Remember me, everybody?
I was the first one to play
that kid Ryoma in a match.
Got to admit it,
but this time it's
war between that
punk and my dad.
Hey, hey, Pops, you're taking
the spotlight away from me.
Next, on "The Prince of Tennis,"
Sounter Attack, Sasabe Again.
See what life in the
Sasabe family is like!