MAN: This match pits a
left against a lefty.
I wonder who will win?
The only seventh grader in
the tournament, or the younger
brother of that
tennis genius, Fuji?
BOY: Fuji's younger
brother, huh?
YUTA (VOICEOVER): Being
the younger brother
of the genius, all I ever
hear about my brother.
I'm me, Yuta Fuji.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-I hear you're Fuji's
younger brother.
I wonder which of you
is the better player?
I can't wait to find out.
[theme music]
-I wonder which of you
is the better player?
I can't wait to find out what.
-Echizen is trying
to psych him out!
-That's so totally like him.
-So that's Fuji's
younger brother.
-That's what I heard, too.
-Did you see that?
-Messing with Yuta
like that means--
the kid's a scary rookie.
-Sure enough.
[groan]
-The younger brother
against Echizen.
-They don't call him the
lefty killer for nothing.
-I hear that in a
practice match he
beat Saeki, the
player from Chiba.
-Wha-- really?
-Of the 16 matches he's played
against lefties to date,
he has won all of them.
-Huh?
-All 16 of them?
-Why is he so good
against left handers?
INUI: Well, I hear he's
played lots of practice
matches against left handers.
Most players are right
handed, and they're
used to how right
handers hit the ball.
So when they play against
an occasional lefty,
the spin on the
ball is opposite,
which makes them
very hard to play.
-That's right!
It's the opposite hand,
so the spin's opposite.
-And that's how he practiced.
-Does it really make
that much difference?
-It's harder when the spin
on the serve is opposite.
Of course, you do understand
that every service game is
to the advantage of
the server, don't you?
-Yes, I know that.
Especially if the player
has a strong serve.
-And at various points
during the game,
the serve area switch from
right to left, and back again.
-And--
-A right hander serving to
the right, or forehand court,
and a lefty serving
to the backhand court
are able to get enough
angle on their serves
to pull the receiver
way out of position.
It's also true that
more game points
are served from the backhand
court than the forehand.
-Really?
Then that means that a lefty
always has the advantage.
-Hm.
Right.
The only game points served
from the forehand court
is when the score is 40-15.
On the other hand, game
points from the backhand court
come at 40-Love,
40-30, and Advantage.
Three times in all.
-Oh.
-With game point being
the point to win the game
and keep the serve, it's
a very important point,
and the advantage to a
lefty is much stronger
than for a right-handed player.
The lefty's serve
is more effective.
-Oh, I get it.
-Huh?
-So that's it.
-What was that?
-I get it, I think.
-Could you go over
that again, please?
-Hm?
Oh, OK.
Listen up.
TOMOKA: Uh-huh.
-So it is the lefty killer.
Echizen has come up against
a real hard one this time.
If only we'd known,
we would have
had him practice against
Tezuka, another lefty.
-So our little guy
is at a disadvantage.
ANNOUNCER: This is
a one set match.
Fuji from St. Rudolph to serve.
15-Love.
-Now he'll serve from
the backhand court.
Watch this.
-Ryoma!
-It looks like
Ryoma's in trouble!
-It's like he's confused by
an opponent he's not used to.
-There's no way!
I don't care if he's right or
left handed, Ryoma's gotta win!
Come on, Ryoma!
-Tomoka, quiet!
-I should have known
from Fuji's brother.
-Yeah.
Looks like my little
brother has polished up
that on the rise
shot he's so good at.
-Fuji, how can you be making
jokes at a time like this?
-Huh?
Did he just do an
on the rise shot?
What is that?
-Um--
-It's a shot hit right after
the ball bounces on the court.
In other words, as the ball
bounces from the court,
and before it reaches its
highest point, it's hit back.
That means the ball comes back
a little quicker than usual.
What's more, you don't
wait until the ball has
lost its speed, but instead
add your own force to it.
That way, you don't give
your opponent a chance
to position himself
before the next shot,
and you can dominate the
match better that way.
That's an on the rise shot.
-Echizen!
ANNOUNCER: Game to
St. Rudolph's Fuji.
One game to Love.
-Oh, no!
It's early, and
Ryoma's fallen behind!
-Not good!
Just because he's a lefty, he's
causing all kinds of problems.
-Your feelings must be mixed.
-Why's that?
If Yuta's happy, then I'm happy.
-Looks like this is gonna be a
tough match for Echizen to win.
-It's a long way from that.
That guy just kept his serve.
That's all he did.
Now it really starts.
-Echizen is gonna use
his special serve!
-Wait.
You mean that he's gonna hit a
kick serve with his left hand?
He usually hits
it with his right?
-Exactly.
I get it!
He hits a kick serve
with his right hand
when he's playing a
right handed player.
But this time his
opponent is a lefty.
-Oh!
Ha!
-There it is!
-A kick serve!
All right!
-Hm.
What a serve.
No matter what kind
of weird ball it is,
it means nothing to Yuta.
ANNOUNCER: Love-15.
-I can't believe it.
-Wow.
What do you call that?
FUJI (VOICEOVER):
Well, Yuta, I didn't
know you've come this far.
to be sure of catching
a ball on the rise
lessens chances for
an irregular bounce.
But for you to return Echizen's
kick serve so easily--
I'd never have imagined it.
You're not the player
you used to be.
I'd even call that
a Super Rising Shot.
-Amazing.
-He handled Ryoma's
kick serve like it
was practically nothing.
-This is bad.
St. Rudolph is
distracting the game.
-Tomo.
-What?
-Even though he won
that point, he still
looks really fierce and angry.
I wonder why.
YUTA (VOICEOVER): That kid--
he was just testing me.
He wanted to see what
my shot was like.
That he would dare hit a kick
serve just to see my shot only
proves one thing.
He was just testing me.
He wanted to see what my
on the rise shot was like.
Just as Mizuki said, this is
a rookie to watch out for.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
That's right, Yuta.
Don't let him charge the net.
His strength lies in the power
of his serve and crafting
net play.
To say nothing of his amazing
one legged split step.
That one's a real pain.
But if you can handle those,
Yuta, then you won't lose.
Show him what your practice
against other lefties
counts for.
You show him, and then I'll
show the one you're really
after-- your brother, Shusuke,
by beating him soundly
from one end of the
court to the other.
MAN: He sure is
Fuji's kid brother.
-Huh?
So you mean he's really--
-Fuji's younger brother?
-That's right.
-Why didn't he
enroll in Seigaku?
-He was enrolled here
for a little while.
-Huh?
But he transferred out
after about six months.
-So then he was on the
tennis team, right?
-No.
-Huh?
-Why not?
-Probably because he didn't want
to be compared to the brother
everyone calls the genius.
-Ryoma's gonna try to
hit another kick serve.
-But it didn't work last time.
-Maybe he's just being stubborn.
-Because the timing to hit
a rising shot is quicker,
it feels like the
ball comes back to you
almost as soon as you hit it.
-And that means the kid doesn't
have time to get to the net,
sure enough.
-If he doesn't
get up to the net,
then like before, he'll have
to play from the baseline.
-Yeah.
This is bad, sure enough.
-Eiji, why are you
talking like that?
-Huh?
-Yeah.
I don't think I like
it, sure enough.
YUTA (VOICEOVER): No
matter how often you do it,
it won't matter.
my Rising Shot kills any
spin you put on the ball.
Huh?
What the--
-That was fast.
-I've never seen such speed.
ANNOUNCER: 15-All.
-Oh, come on, now.
Is that all you have?
I've played better lefties than
you without breaking a sweat.
TEZUKA (VOICEOVER): He's
faster than when he played me,
that's for sure.
And getting faster all the time.
YUTA (VOICEOVER):
Better lefties than me?
Don't kid me.
-He did it!
-He won another one!
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Seigaku's Echizen.
One game all.
-All right.
He caught up in the
blink of an eye.
-That's our Ryoma!
-Looks like he's lost the
uncertainties in his game
from the district matches.
-That seventh
grader from Seigaku.
What a comeback.
-Don't write off the eight
grader from St. Rudolph's
just yet.
-What?
The kid brother of that
Seigaku player Fuji?
-Seigaku player Fuji?
-The one they call genius?
His brother?
-Well, they do have
the same last name.
-What?
Don't tell me you didn't
know they were related.
-Related?
Really?
BOY: His kid brother, huh?
BOY: Oh, wow.
I've heard of this guy.
He must be really, really good.
-Yuta's not finished yet.
-Mm-hm.
-He hates to be a loser.
Always has.
MAN: Boy, that kid is amazing.
MAN: He's got the lefty
killer on the ropes.
YUTA (VOICEOVER): Right.
This is no time to
let my guard down.
There's something I have to do.
When I enrolled at
Seigaku last year,
all I ever heard was
talk about my brother.
I was sick of it.
So sick of all those voices.
So I didn't join the
tennis team there,
but instead started
taking lessons
at a tennis school
some distance away.
My goal was to become a
better player than anyone.
-One of the members of our
team couldn't make it today,
so would you care to join us?
-Yeah.
I'd be glad to.
-That's just great.
After all, I know he's
a pretty good player.
He's the kid brother of
Seigaku's genius Fuji--
-Coach.
MIZUKI: Is that so?
Well, more importantly, your on
the rise shot is really great.
I was impressed.
-Th-- Uh.
Uh, thank you.
BOY: I've heard of
Seigaku, sure enough.
-They're the toughest
school in the area.
-Did we play them in
the district matches?
Ha.
Oh well.
It doesn't matter.
-Huh?
-Oh, we forgot to
introduce ourselves to you.
The three of us will be playing
for the St. Rudolph tennis
team starting this autumn.
-This autumn?
What does that mean?
MIZUKI: They're recruiting
strong players from all over.
They're aiming to
win the nationals.
-You're really good.
I haven't lost this badly
since I played my brother.
Uh, I mean--
-No, I should say the same.
If you had perfected
that on the rise shot,
I would've been in trouble.
You've still a ways
to go yet, but you've
got lots of potential.
I can't believe you're buried
in a place like this, Yuta.
-Huh?
Uh, I wanna know more!
Yeah.
Please, tell me more
about St. Rudolph.
I want people to remember
my name for what I do.
That's what I've
been working on,
and this-- this is my answer.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER): Do it, Yuta.
SHUSUKE (VOICEOVER): What
kind of stance is that?
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Now you show them
the special shot
that I taught you.
Do it in front of everyone.
-Huh?
SHUSUKE (VOICEOVER):
What was that?
-Whoa, what kind
of shot was that?
-It was a shot with
an opposite spin.
-Wowie.
-Wow.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Did you see it?
That was Yuta's twist spin shot.
[theme music]
YUTA: I'm St. Rudolph
eighth grader Yuta Fuji.
I've been playing
tennis for years
just so I could beat my brother.
But now, the Seigaku
seventh grader
thinks he can beat
my twist spin shot?
Ha!
And he says he's played
stronger lefties than me?
Who's he kidding?
Brag all you want after
you've defeated me.
Next on "The Prince
of Tennis," Drive B.
Doesn't that sound good?
I accept your challenge.