-There's no way he's going
to beat a senior team player.
No way.
Not a chance that's
gonna happen.
[theme music]
-Echizen's been
awesome up until now,
and he's gone up against
some pretty good players.
But he will not be able to
compete at this level for long.
-Why not?
He was beating that quitter
Momoshiro the other day.
-That doesn't count, Momoshiro
had a sprained ankle.
If he hadn't been hurt,
he could've won easy.
All the top players are
better than Echizen.
He doesn't stand a chance
around the regulars,
no matter how hard he tries.
-But I'm rooting for
him, and so is Katsuo.
All the seventh graders look
up to Ryoma around here.
-Hey, here he comes now.
-Don't let the pressure
get to you, Ryoma!
-You can beat those guys!
We know you can!
-Hey, newbies.
-Yes?
-You're bothering me.
Get.
-Yes!
-We're out of here.
-Hey.
-What?
-I want to be left alone,
so get out of here.
-Sure.
I'll be going.
What a creepy guy.
[heavy breathing]
-That was scary.
That was Kaoru
Kaidoh, wasn't it?
-Yeah.
I think he's going
to play Echizen
in bracket D of the
upcoming ranking tournament.
-Bracket D?
Oh, bracket D. There's his same.
-What is a ranking
tournament, anyway?
-Are you trying to be the
school's new laughingstock?
I can't believe I have
to explain this to you.
Listen up.
Ranking tournaments
are held monthly
to select the top
players from among all
the eighth and ninth
grade students.
There are four brackets,
but only the top two players
from each bracket get
to play on the team.
Now, do you get it?
-Wow, Ryoma has his
work cut out for him.
-Yeah.
This really looks tough.
-And that's not all.
Winners get something
you'll never have.
One of those.
A Seigaku team jacket.
What could be cooler than that?
-I don't know about tennis
fashion, but you seem to.
-Don't forget, I already have
two years of tennis experience.
Maybe one day I'll be good
enough to make the team.
And then, mark my words,
I'll have a jacket of my own.
-You're about to trip.
-Oh!
Heh.
I meant to do that.
-Hey, you three over there.
Stop that fooling around,
and help us out here
by putting up the nets.
-Right.
-Oh, I wish I was better.
Like Ryoma.
Oh, I'll never be
as good as him.
Ah!
Ryoma!
-Bend your knees, keep
your elbows straight.
-Huh?
And other tips?
-Your shoulders are too
open, your hair is too long,
stand firmer.
-Oh.
Oh.
-Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh!
-Hurry!
Hurry!
The ranking tournament
is about to start!
-Hey, do you guys know
who Tezuka's playing?
-No idea, but I
heard they're gonna
let a seventh grader play!
-No way!
Really?
GIRL: He must be something.
GIRL: Who is he?
-My Ryoma.
My hero.
-Hey, what's the big idea?
-Calm down, Tomoka.
-What are you standing
around here for?
-Uh--
-We have to go cheer on Ryoma!
-Look.
It's him.
-Kinda short, isn't he?
-He don't look so tough.
-Echizen!
Your match is up.
-If you lose, I might
be traumatized for life.
-This is it.
Even the older
players are watching
to see what's going to happen.
[hiss]
-Huh?
-Move aside or be stomped.
-Uh, sure thing, Mr. Kaidoh.
We're moving now.
-What's Kaidoh doing here?
His match isn't scheduled
until much later.
-Yeah, but it looks like
he's already in battle mode.
[hiss]
-The other players
also look ready.
-Inui, you're in bracket
D too, aren't you?
How can you look
so calm right now?
This is only my game face.
-Today's ranking tournament is
going to be really exciting.
Let's go.
-Oh.
ANNOUNCER: Game, Echizen.
He leads three games to love.
-Keep it up, Ryoma!
That's the way to go!
-Chill out!
Echizen's got this one sewn up.
Huh?
Hey, where's Kachiro?
-He was just here a minute ago.
-Wow.
Oishi's really on fire.
Kikumaru's not
doing bad, either.
Seems like all the
regular team members
are winning in straight sets.
-Oh, Ryoma!
Ryoma!
-Ryoma!
Oh, you're so cool!
-Boy, those girls
sure are wild for him.
-Worried about our
little Echizen?
-No.
Not really.
ANNOUNCER: Game, set,
and match to Echizen.
Six games to love.
-Ryoma!
Ryoma!
-My goodness.
Sounds like she
needs medical help.
-Oh, hi, Miss Shiba.
-I see Ryoma's doing well.
He hasn't lost any games yet,
so it's been easy for him.
Tougher matches lie ahead.
-He doesn't look worried to me.
Look at him over there.
So calm, cool, and collected.
It's almost like he's at peace.
-Your game against Kaidoh is
the last match of the day,
and I for one hope you
beat him into the ground.
-There's no way he's going
to beat a senior team player.
No way.
Not a chance that's
going to happen.
-Huh?
What's wrong?
-I didn't mean to
make you anxious.
-No.
Just hungry.
-Huh?
-Now you've got my stomach
all tied up in knots.
Urgh.
-Ow!
-Hi.
Ryoma Echizen, bracket
D. Six games to love.
-Got it.
OK.
[chuckling]
-Fantastic.
Unbelievable.
Amazing.
Ryoma just keeps winning.
But before, you said
Ryoma couldn't beat anyone
on the team.
-I only meant the regulars.
Maybe if, you know, Ryoma
keeps playing this well,
he might win a game
against Kaidoh.
Hey, Kachiro, we've been
looking all over for you.
-I think you better
check your face, Kachiro.
-Aw, it's nothing.
A tennis ball hit
me right in my eye.
Anyway, check out
this tape I shot.
You gotta see it.
It's footage of Ryoma's
next opponent in action.
That's right.
It's Kaidoh.
-You shot Kaidoh
without him knowing?
-That's great!
We missed his match
'cause we were
busy watching Ryoma's easy win.
-So that's why you were gone.
We didn't know where
you went off to.
-Anyway, you've gotta see this.
He's something else.
RYOMA: Yeah.
He's strong and
fast on the court.
-Why, Ryoma, I've never heard
you talk like that before.
-Man, these top
pros are incredible.
-Not that, Ryoma.
This.
I risked my eye so I
could record it for you.
-Huh?
Hey, Echizen, where you going?
-Ryoma!
-Man, I hate it
when he's like that.
-We'll just have to watch
the tape without him.
Showtime.
-What's he doing?
What kind of shot is that?
-Inui?
-You can go to lunch now.
I'll take over.
-Great.
How's it going?
-I am winning.
No big surprise about that.
But that seventh grader
hasn't lost a game yet.
-But you'll know
how to beat him when
he goes up against you, right?
-It's possible.
-You and your
troublesome notebook.
I hate it.
-He's the one
who's going to have
trouble with his
next opponent.
-One of the regulars.
[hiss]
-Ah, Kaidoh.
You're looking cheerful
as ever, I see.
-You trying to pick
a fight with me?
-What's he doing?
-I've never seen anyone
play like that before.
-Kaidoh's playing style is very
unorthodox and totally unique.
I guess that's why everyone
calls him the viper.
-Viper?
Odd nickname.
-It sure is.
But then again,
he's a very odd guy.
-Yikes!
He's looking right at us!
-What an incredible serve.
There's no way Echizen's
gonna beat that guy.
It's impossible.
No way.
-I don't know.
-Huh?
-I think Ryoma can win
if he plays his best.
-You're crazy.
He's way too fast and
strong for Echizen.
-Ryoma's not an ordinary
player, you know.
I think he can beat him!
-Tomo always makes
me do everything.
She's so bossy.
Ryoma?
-Momo's overhead
smash is awesome.
-Match to Momoshiro,
six games to love.
-Mm, Momo's ankle sprain
appears to have fully healed.
-I didn't think
he'd be able to play
in this tournament
because of it.
-Nothing like an easy
victory to get back
in the swing of
things, huh guys?
See you later.
-What do you know This
time he didn't quit.
-Wow.
He only leaves just that
one mark on the wall.
RYOMA: Talking to me?
-Oh!
Sorry.
I-- I didn't mean
to interrupt you.
-You didn't interrupt me at all.
What do you want?
-Oh, um, well, your
match is soon and I-- I
wish you luck, Ryoma.
-Huh?
-Woe is me.
[meow]
-Ah, Karupin.
I have something for you.
See how you like this.
-Hey.
-What?
-Looks like your next match
is with Kaidoh, isn't it?
-I don't know.
Probably.
-That's a risky attitude.
You don't know who
you're dealing with.
You'd better be careful
with that viper.
-Viper?
-That's what they call him.
-Oh.
All right.
-That kid's crazier than I am.
[hiss]
-Kaidoh's hissing again.
-Echizen won't have
it so easy this time.
-This could be very
interesting if he's
able to handle
Kaidoh's trick shot.
It's going to be fun to watch.
-Hm.
ANNOUNCER: This as a
best of one set match.
Service, Echizen.
-Come on, you got him now.
-He got it!
-15-Love.
-Boy, that was lucky.
-One blink and you would've
missed it completely.
-If he keeps this up,
he'll win, I know it!
-You forget.
Kaidoh uses that trick
shot, and Echizen.
Doesn't know about it yet.
[hissing]
[meowing]
-Hey, hey.
Here it is.
Come and get it.
-Kaidoh wasn't
expecting that one.
[hissing laughter]
-Ryoma, you rule!
-He's gonna do his trick shot.
-Oh no.
-15 all.
-What was that?
It was weird.
-It was going one way and
then it went the other.
-It's early for trick shots.
-Can't be good.
-It just means he's really
serious about winning
the match.
-That shot.
It's the one we
saw in the video.
-You're right.
-That's Kaidoh's snake shot.
-You mean--
-That's what he calls it?
-So that's why he hisses.
-Yep.
And only someone
like Kaidoh can do it
because of his long reach.
When he sees the ball
approach, he shifts his weight
from his right leg
to his left, then
he swings as hard as he
can, putting a lot of spin
on the ball.
It's a very tricky shot,
but that's the viper.
Sneaky.
Always hissing.
He's a snake, totally.
He probably sleeps
all coiled up.
-Look at those mountain peaks.
Spectacular scenery indeed.
Don't lose to a snake, Karupin.
Ow!
You're supposed to grab
the snake, not my toe,
you dumb cat!
-Sakuno, I don't like
the looks of this.
Kaidoh's trick shot may
be too much for Ryoma.
-Maybe the challenge
is too great.
Playing against a regular was
bound to be tough for him.
-Hm.
[hissing]
So that's the angle
he uses for this shot.
Ha.
You still have a ways to go.
Time to kill a viper.
-Huh?
He's using his left--
-That means Kaidoh's
really in for it now.
-Shiba, this match
is just beginning.
[theme music]
KACHIRO: Hi, everyone.
Kato here.
Boy, this match up
is something else.
Ryoma and Kaidoh have me
on the edge of my seat,
and I'm not even sitting down!
Kaidoh uses an amazing
technique called the snake shot,
and he's giving Ryoma
all he can handle.
But it's not over yet.
There's plenty more
surprises to come,
and you wouldn't even believe
me if I told you what was gonna
happen, so I won't!
Next, on the "Prince
of Tennis," Snake Shot.
You have to watch it!