-Seigaku, Seigaku,
Seigaku, Seigaku, Seigaku!
Investigate,
Investigate, Investigate.
I've got to investigate.
Whoa, I-- I can't see!
I can't see!
Whoa.
Everything's gone black!
What happened?
[shouting]
-Hey.
Your bandana's
covering your eyes.
-Huh?
Oh yeah, you're right.
Thanks so much.
Oh, you must be from Seigaku!
-Very observant.
-All right!
Um, I mean, you must be
here to cheer him on too,
isn't that right?
-Him?
-Yeah, that seventh
grader, Echizenia.
He's an awesome
seventh grader like me.
I'd give anything to see
him play with my own eyes.
[theme music]
SAKUNO: I really didn't
our number two doubles team
of Fuji Kawamura would lose.
TOMOKA: But it's OK, Sakuno.
Don't fret.
Up next are Oishi and Kikumaru.
Seigaku's golden pair.
-I suppose you're right.
-It'll be a cinch.
An easy win.
-I wonder.
-Huh?
-Yamabuki Junior High's
number one doubles lineup
is the same as last year,
with Minami and Higashikata.
I hope Oishi does
not strain himself.
-No way!
You say that the seventh grader
is only 151 centimeters tall?
That makes him my height!
I thought he'd be
built more like Akutsu.
-Huh?
-Oh.
Never mind, I'm just babbling.
Anyway, you're a real
lifesaver, thanks so much.
-I didn't expect to hear that
a seventh grader, the Seigaku
regular, was such a shrimp.
-Don't tell me you're
on the tennis team.
-Um, well yeah.
But you see, I'm not a player.
I'm just the manager.
-Yeah?
-You see, I'm too
short to play, really.
-Ryoma!
-Hm?
-Are you goofing off again?
TAICHI (VOICEOVER): Ryoma?
-Well, come on.
Let's hurry.
Oishi's match is about to
start, and he needs our support.
-Yeah, I know, I'm coming.
I never knew tennis was
all about how tall you are.
-Mr. Inoue, don't you think
we should get going too?
Ah!
He's here.
Disgusting.
-Hm.
-I wonder what Mr.
Nanjiro's doing around here.
-I don't see him.
I don't see him.
I don't see that awful sight.
I'll go on ahead.
-Huh?
-Hey there, Oishi.
It's been awhile.
ANNOUNCER: One set match.
Minami of Yamabuki to serve.
-Now, Oishi.
Don't strain yourself
until after I'm done.
-Eiji.
All right.
Now we can play as usual.
-Let's go.
BANDA: Coach Ryuzaki.
-Huh?
What is it, Mr. Banda?
-We'll be taking
two of the doubles
matches again this year.
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER): That
old geezer, arrogant as ever.
But is it worth having
that problem child just
to strengthen
their singles game?
-Banji, isn't the game
of tennis supposed
to be about having fun?
-Oh, absolutely
correct, Coach Ryuzaki.
That's always been
my philosophy.
Oh, dear.
Things appear
unfortunate for Oishi.
Better remind him of
what happened last year.
ANNOUNCER: 15-Love.
[excited chatter]
-That was amazing.
-Yeah, what impeccable timing.
-They've certainly worked
to improve their game
since last year.
ANNOUNCER: 30-Love.
-Oh no.
It's early and they're
taking a beating.
-But doesn't it seem like
they're targeting Oishi?
-Yo.
Thanks for the drink.
-You came here to watch
Ryoma's game, yes?
-Nah, get real.
Why would I wanna do
something like that?
I got bored ringing the
bell, so I took a walk.
-Seems a bit convenient
that you came all the way
out here just for a walk.
-Let's see.
Wonder if there are any
pretty girls around here.
INOUE (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Something's up with him.
HORIO: I knew it!
They are focusing their
attack exclusively on Oishi.
-Game to Yamabuki.
One game to Love.
-Their attack
pattern is familiar.
It's the same tactic
they used in defeating
Oishi and his
teammate last year.
EIJI (VOICEOVER): Shoot.
What a nasty attack.
All right!
-No, don't move, Eiji!
OISHI (VOICEOVER):
Last year, I moved up,
thinking it would
help me partner
who was being singled out.
If we act impatiently now,
we'll lose the match for sure.
Their target isn't me.
They wanna draw out my partner
and break our formation.
The thing to do
now is-- The thing
to do now is counter their
attacks by staying composed.
BOYS: Moon volley!
ANNOUNCER: 15-Love.
-You didn't think you could
beat me with the same tactic
as last year, did you?
-Hm.
-He tore down last year's
walls all by himself.
-Oh, he's a level
headed one, and he's
maturing into a fine player.
-Nice one, Oishi.
-That's the magic
of Oishi for you.
-You just gotta love
that stoic vibe of his.
Of course!
-I see.
So this is the
Seigaku golden pair.
Looks like we can
have a little fun.
-Momoshiro.
Time for you to get warmed up.
-Got you.
Yeah.
I've got the adrenaline pumping.
-Hey you, don't
get carried away.
-What are you trying to say?
-Seriously.
Do your warm up properly.
-You don't have to
tell me anything.
[hiss]
-Huh?
-Da da dada!
Here's Ryoma's data!
-Don't you dare embarrass
yourself like this ever again.
-I'm very sorry.
JIN: Taichi.
-Y-- Yes sir?
-Mark my words.
I'm gonna nuke that little runt.
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Seigaku, one game all.
-Good work.
Let's keep it up, Eiji.
-Right Oishi.
-What's the matter, Banji?
You're not looking very well.
[groaning]
-Hey, Banji, are you OK?
Banji!
I swear, you're the same as
ever, you heartless geezer.
Unreal.
-He may have torn down last
year's walls by himself,
but every day, those
walls are getting
higher and higher, Ryuzaki.
BOY (VOICEOVER): I guess it's
time to go for the poach.
OK, Minami.
Our target is over there.
-He's sharp.
-A poach?
-Very nice.
-It seems as though
they controlled
the course of the
serve beforehand
and dictated its return
course for a poach.
-They're doing a
great job using sides.
-Furthermore, to return such
an accurate and powerful serve,
one cannot avoid playing
right into their hands.
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Yamabuki, two games to one.
Change courts.
[excited chatter]
-They pulled back
the winning tide
with their basic, surefire play.
They're plain, but
those solid basics
are definitely hard to beat.
That's why our
number one doubles
team is also known
as plain and simple.
BOY: Come on, plain and simple!
-Hey, don't you
ever call us that!
BANDA (VOICEOVER):
Plain and simple
are a tough team to beat with
their flawlessly perfected
basics.
OISHI (VOICEOVER): They're
doing great using signs.
They have certainly polished
their skills from last year.
Plain and simple indeed.
I can't find an
opening in their play.
At this rate--
-Oishi.
Daigoro the bear
snoozed off where?
-Daigoro the bear?
-Who'd he say snoozed off?
-What bear?
-Hey, Higashikata, concentrate.
Don't get all confused.
-Daigoro the bear snoozed off.
That's it.
That stuffed animal
at Eiji's house.
It's always slumped over.
-OK.
To the left.
BANDA: That's a good
strategy, sending
the ball on a cross court
shot, forcing the opponent
to run to volley, then cutting
off the return with a poach
by Kikumaru.
However, there's a
flaw with that plan.
Even from a stance
like that, Minami
can easily return it
with a straight shot.
-There!
-Yay!
-What an acrobatic shot.
-Yeah, go, Kikumaru!
ANNOUNCER: Love-15.
-Wh-- What kind of
trick play was that?
-It's OK to start attacking
them now, right Oishi?
-Yeah, you've waited
long enough, Eiji.
Time for action.
-Commencing attack.
-All right!
-Oh yeah!
HORIO: Kikumaru's on a rebound.
-There you go.
There.
-Huh?
-Victory.
RYUZAKI (VOICEOVER):
Sorry, Banji,
but it seems our students
have one upped yours.
With Kikumaru's
acrobatic play, you
can see the golden pair's
explosive abilities
for yourself.
ANNOUNCER: Game and match
Seigaku, seven games to five.
-Hm.
-They did it!
A comeback victory.
-Seigaku's golden pair
is totally awesome!
-Minami, Higashikata,
your game was flawless.
However, there was a
flaw in your hearts.
Knowing that you
beat Oishi last year,
you failed to take into
account his bond with Kikumaru.
This outcome is
the result of that.
Coach Ryuzaki, it seems I
underestimated you as well.
-Maybe next time.
-Yeah.
[rattling]
-Huh?
-Hey.
My thanks to you for such
a miserable, pathetic loss.
-Akutsu.
Now I can really torture
that seventh grader.
[wicked laughter]
[screaming]
-What's wrong?
All I did was ask if they
wanted to have tea with me.
They didn't have to go
off running and screaming
like that.
-Looking as disheveled
and unshaven as you do,
you can't blame them
for running away.
-Yo, Banji.
It's been a long time.
-It certainly has been.
I see your skill in flirting
has not improved very much.
Pity, Nanjiro Echizen.
-I'll say this.
You sure are as talkative
as ever, you old geezer.
-Are you here to
root for your son?
-Heh.
No, I haven't got
that much free time.
-Then it must be destiny,
competing against your son
at this late date in my career.
Or maybe I've just
lived too long.
-What are you saying?
-I can still remember the
game like it was yesterday.
It's a fond memory of mine.
One I'll never forget.
Now, years later, I look
forward to seeing your son play.
I'm sure I'll never
forget it either.
Goodbye.
MAN: Right.
Yamabuki Junior High's
advisor, Mikiya Banda.
Can you email me the file?
Yeah, as an attachment.
The data we analyzed
last month should still
be on the editor's PC.
Oh, and can you also look
up the win-lose statistics
for the schools
that Banda advised?
ANNOUNCER: We will begin
the Yamabuki versus Seigaku
number three singles match
in just a few moments.
-Yes.
The singles match that'll
decide the finals.
Oh, hey.
Now where did you run
off to, Mr. Inoue?
-I was gathering
important information
while you were fooling around.
-How rude of you!
I wasn't fooling around at all.
-I guess I'm not so
lucky these days.
I drew lots and got the
number three singles spot,
but my opponent is not Echizen.
Aw, how disappointing.
[clearing throat]
-Huh?
Excuse me for not being Echizen.
-Oh no, that's not what I meant.
I'm sorry.
I know, you're Momoshiro, right?
I heard you do a dunk smash.
That's pretty impressive.
-Spare me your
psychological tricks.
ANNOUNCER: Please
toss the racket
to decide who serves first.
-You call it.
-I'll take the serve.
-You shouldn't say that
until after you've called it.
-I'll get it.
I haven't missed a call yet.
-Hmph.
-Well, I guess I'll
be calling down.
-Well, you're pretty confident.
Yes!
It's up.
I got the serve!
Huh?
Hey!
-See?
I told you.
-Momo is so unlucky.
He would've had that serve if
it didn't get caught on the net.
-I can see know why they
call him by the nickname
Lucky Sengoku.
-Huh?
Lucky Sengoku?
-Know what?
I'll let you serve
first after all.
-What?
-Today's lucky
direction is northeast,
so I'll be on that side of the
court to receive your serve.
-Mm-hm.
Lucky Sengoku.
[phone ringing]
-Huh?
Hey.
Uh, it's me.
Ah huh.
-Man, it's hot.
I could really use a
nice, cold root beer.
-Oh, Mr. Inoue.
The match is just
about to start.
Don't you want-- Huh?
-Shiba.
It looks like we've got
ourselves a situation.
Long ago, Mikiya Banda
was a tennis team advisor
for a school that defeated
Seigaku in a team competition.
Back in those days, Seigaku
was the strongest middle school
team.
-Huh?
INOUE: Seigaku's ace player at
that time was Nanjiro Echizen.
[theme music]
SENGOKU: I'm Sengoku.
Kyosumi Sengoku, that is.
Finally, my turn is up.
Let's see.
Who's my victim this time?
Hey, it's Mr.
Spikey-Haired himself.
People call me Mr.
Brunette, but don't
get us all mixed up together.
I'm not that passionate
about my hair.
I get my wins with
my incredible luck.
Next on "The Prince of
Tennis," Lucky Sengoku.
You got quite a personality
yourself, Momoshiro.