JIN (VOICEOVER): I hate this.
It's stupid just
running after balls.
Tennis is lame.
-Drive A.
-Huh?
-Yes!
RYOMA: Oops.
I'm so sorry.
It's not good to take
tennis so lightly.
[theme music]
RYOMA: It's not good to
take tennis so lightly.
Well then, I guess
that should teach you
not to mess with Kachiro.
-Ryoma!
-Ha!
-Come on.
What you sitting there for?
Because I still owe you
one for Taka, don't I?
And while we're at
it, might as well
take care of Arai's
payback, too.
-While we're at it?
-You are brave.
But you won't get away
from me now, brat.
-Same goes for you.
-I've never seen
anything like this.
Akutsu's taking a
defensive stance.
-Akutsu's serious now.
-Ryoma switched his racket
over to his right hand.
-That means--
-A kick serve!
-That's unreal.
How'd he return like that?
-That kick serve is
not an easy one to hit.
-He just appeared at the net.
-He's fast.
In that position, he
can't hit cross court,
so he'll probably
go down the line.
-H hit cross court from there?
That kid must have
some reflexes.
-Boy, he moves incredibly
well-- for a punk.
-I'll say.
Looks like this match
could get rough.
-There's a surprise.
Even though his shots seem
irregular, he keeps attacking.
That's a strange strategy.
-Just don't think that I'm
gonna let you steal any more
points off of me, kid.
SAKUNO (VOICEOVER): This
guy just isn't normal.
I'm scared.
-Wow.
How does he manage
to hit like that?
-Look at that.
He returns those shots with
so much power and speed.
-Do you think he's really human?
-I'm not sure.
-He has no weak spot.
That's not good.
I guess there's always
somebody better, hm?
-His game is just different
from yours, Tezuka.
-I hope that's a
complement, Fuji.
BOY (VOICEOVER): That's
Akutsu's strength, Echizen.
-Is there something
wrong, Miss Shiba?
They're just moving too fast
to follow with this camera.
Maybe I should switch to video.
-That's it.
The punk kid has
finally found his prey.
-His prey?
What?
Wait a sec.
Are you talking about Ryoma?
-Is that the best
you can do, brat?
-Still, I wonder who will
end up being whose prey?
-This should be good.
-That's the way.
Go, Akutsu!
-Come on.
How can you root for that
creepy guy like that?
-He's not creepy!
Akutsu is great!
Someday soon, I'll
be just like him.
-Hm.
-Allow me to express my
gratitude, Coach Ryuzaki.
Akutsu-- Do you really
enjoy playing tennis?
JIN (VOICEOVER): I hate this.
It's stupid just
running after balls.
Tennis is lame.
-So.
What do you want to see me for?
I don't mind your age
if you want to fight.
-Hey, Akutsu.
We're asking you to quit
the tennis club, all right?
BOY: What do you
think of that new kid?
BOY: You mean that Akutsu?
Yeah, he's a total jerk.
-Hey, Akutsu.
Kids like you just mess
up the dignity of tennis.
-That's right!
-Yeah, what a
total punk you are.
You know, it's like, you can't
just go out and play, huh?
-Just shut up.
It's really not your business.
The dignity of tennis?
Give me a break.
Well, chump.
You want dignity, right?
Well, then win it on the court.
[shocked whispering]
-Hmph.
-Hey, kid.
I'll play you.
-Hey, Shiratama.
-Look, he's here.
He's the one.
-Shiratama.
Yeah, this is the kid
who's been causing trouble.
-Who is that?
-Who's that?
Dude, this guy's just
about a tennis legend.
-Yeah, don't you
know Shiratama's had
special training
since he was five?
And on top of it, he's been
a runner up three times
and finished in
the top four twice.
-I'm game.
Wanna play?
Your name's Akutsu, right?
I'll play.
But, if by chance you happen
to lose to me big shot,
well then, I want you
to get out of here
and leave our tennis
club alone forever.
That's what everyone
wants, you know.
-Sure.
Let's do it.
But, if you lose to
me, what do I get?
-Man.
This is just crazy.
He really thinks it's
going to beat our man.
-Heh.
Boy, he doesn't know
how wrong he is.
-Uh, let me think.
Well then--
AKUTSU: Don't pick a fight--
if you're not ready to lose.
Because if you go
down, I'll beat you up.
-Incredible.
-Shiratama sure is
taking a major beating
from that little monster.
-You've been playing since
you were five years old
and you still can't
win a whole tournament?
You just stink.
Come on.
No way!
-Is he OK?
-He did that on purpose!
-That's gotta hurt.
-What?
You're just a big
wuss, aren't you?
Get up and take it
like a real man.
You scared?
-Shiratama!
-Now, that wasn't fair.
-Bad sportsmanship.
JIN (VOICEOVER); I knew it.
They're chicken.
Tennis is lame.
-Akutsu, are you
playing tennis too?
I just started.
Isn't it fun?
ANNOUNCER: Game to
Yamabuki's Akutsu.
One game to Love.
Change courts.
-Oh, Ryoma!
-Ryoma!
-He's always on the attack.
-The word defense is
not in his vocabulary.
Being able to attack from
any position is his strength.
He's a very versatile player.
Even after starting his swing
he watches his opponent's
movements and can change
his shot's direction.
He's really got
extraordinary flexibility.
Amazing.
And a spring in his
step that you rarely
see in a power player.
His ability to react
instantly, his ability
to flex, his drive to destroy,
and his powers of judgment
could make him one of
the best in the world.
Except--
-Hm?
-He just doesn't
have the passion
or the enthusiasm for the game.
But now, with the emergence
of your young player,
Akutsu is now determined
to perfect himself.
That's why I sincerely
want to thank you
for that, Coach Ryuzaki.
BOY: No way!
You can't be as tall as I am.
151 centimeters?
-I never knew tennis was
all about how tall you are.
TAICHI (VOICEOVER): Ryoma
sure is an awesome player.
Hm.
But against Akutsu--
BOY: Hey, take it easy, Taichi.
See you.
I feel loose.
I mean, a little sore, too.
-Hey, what's going on?
Can you tell me who that
player is out there?
-Who?
Oh, Akutsu.
Yeah, old man Banji
brought him over.
Apparently, he's got
some amazing talent,
so the coach likes to
work with him whenever
he's got some time to spare.
-He hasn't missed
a single shot yet.
And he's-- he's--
he's so gigantic.
-Stop it.
Hey, make that kid
stop looking at me.
-Now don't worry.
You're hitting well.
He's obviously just
impressed by your talent.
Now try two balls.
-No way!
-Please.
-Come on now.
Isn't this fun?
-Not really.
Tennis is a pretty stupid sport.
-Hey, Akutsu, you dropped this!
-Don't need it.
-I know, I-- I could
wash it for you.
My name's Taichi, a-a-and I'm
the team manager and I do all
sorts of things for the team,
so it wouldn't be any problem
for me to--
-Throw it away.
-In that case, can I have it?
-Huh?
-You rock.
I've been watching you, and
you're gonna beat them all,
I'm sure.
Hmph!
I'm gonna play just like him.
-Right.
Now I'll be able to
catch everything.
-Akutsu, I know it's
been boring for you.
Until now.
-Yikes!
He's moving to the net.
Of course.
-If he goes to the net, he
might be able to catch up--
TOGETHER: With
Ryoma's Split Step!
-You're wasting your time, brat.
-Huh?
-No way!
-After our guy jumped, he--
-He hit it in the
opposite direction.
-Hey, this is getting
pretty interesting.
-Are you out of your mind?
Ryoma's getting ripped
apart out there.
-So, kid.
Is this how you get even?
Don't make me laugh, loser.
[theme music]
TAKASHI: I'm Takashi Kawamura.
I've known Jin Akutsu since
we were in elementary school.
He was good in both
karate and tennis,
but he quit because he was
constantly causing trouble.
He's playing tennis again,
but nothing's changed.
Am I destined to be
a helpless bystander?
Next on "The Prince of
Tennis," Samurai Spirit.
Ryoma, don't
provoke him anymore.
He's dangerous.