[whip cracking]
[BAZUKU] Where are your little
resistance friends hiding?
And what exciting new
plot are they cooking up?
Trust me, it's best
if you cooperate.
We want the Divine Emperor.
Really? Go on.
We're gonna shove your
head directly up his ass.
[laughs]
I'm glad you find all
of this so amusing.
[AMANDA yelps]
[AMANDA screams]
[AMANDA groaning]
Don't worry, I won't
kill you just yet.
Patch her up.
Sir!
[PRISON GUARD A]
On your feet!
[wheels squeaking]
[PRISONERS grunting]
[PRISONER D]
Please! Let me go home!
You shut your mouth!
[PRISONER D] I'm begging you,
please, I have a daughter!
Daughter?
[PRISONER D] Don't you
understand? She needs me!
Go on, get back to work!
[PRISONER D]
But I didn't do anything!
You have to send me home!
[screams]
You think this is a show?
All of you, get your
asses back to work!
Hey!
[gasps] Oh, no!
[PRISON GUARD A]
What, another one?
I'm tryin' to stop the guy!
[PRISON GUARD A]
No, wait!
[PRISONER D panting, crying]
Hey!
Uh! Don't!
[TAKUYA groans]
You just worry
about yourself.
The other prisoners don't
need your meddling.
[TAKUYA grunting]
You're never gonna
learn, are you?
[TAKUYA] Persistence is one
of my better qualities.
Sorry everything's
taking so long.
Me and the others, we're still
working on our escape plan.
Well, I'm not dead yet,
so, I guess I've got time.
"As long as you don't
die, there's hope.
And as long as there is hope,
there's possibility.
And as long as
there's possibility,
you must continue to live."
Y'know, I like that.
[TAKUYA] Someone very
important to me told me that.
Thank you. I'll remember it.
[PRISONER C] Hey, better eat
up. You'll need your strength.
[PRISONER B]
That man.
He said he had
a daughter, right?
Yeah, he did.
Such a shame.
I have a family on
the outside, too.
[PRISONER C]
We all do.
Right.
[KURTZ] So listen, the escape
plan has two separate parts.
For our first move, we'll create
some confusion in the quarry.
At that point, we'll take
advantage of the chaos
in order to rescue our leader.
When is this happening?
It will all happen on the day
they carry out the coffin.
[gasps] Bazuku, sir!
[BAZUKU]
It's ugly!
Look at that! Half-finished
piece of trash!
Start over! Now!
The ritual is upon us!
So you'd better make damn
sure that this is ready!
[TAKUYA] Explain to me
why we're doing it
on the day they
carry out the coffin.
I still don't get how
we could possibly leave.
Not with the tower there.
Don't worry.
They're shutting the tower down
that day, just to be safe.
I mean, the guards don't want
to die any more than we do.
[KURTZ]
So, we hit them when it's off.
[TAKUYA] Will both the Tower
of Garzel and the backup
really shut down?
Well, that's the hope,
but we can't be sure.
This is new territory for us.
We've actually never
seen them do this before.
So, if they leave the second one
up in order to prevent escapees.
[KURTZ] Then we'll need to
shut that one down, too.
[BAZUKU] It's the perfect
accessory for a beauty like you.
[AMANDA] Hmph. I won't
need to wear a disguise
in the imperial city anymore.
You know something?
If you weren't a sworn enemy
of the state, I'd want
to hire you, myself.
Heh. Funny, I'd rather die.
[BAZUKU]
I say we play a little game.
Called "how long can you
hold that tongue of yours?"
Actually... Here's the thing--
I once destroyed
the Tower of Garzel.
That's ridiculous.
Wait, how?
Hey! Take a sword and
stab it into the tower.
It'll act as a lightning rod,
using the tower's own
electricity to destroy it.
Are you serious? You're
pulling our legs now, right?
No, that's what happened.
I'm telling you the truth.
[DEO, KURTZ]
Uh...
[KURTZ] Well.... I don't
think this really changes
the plan itself.
Someone will still need to
destroy the backup, too.
I don't see a good way for us
to accomplish all of this
with only three people.
[footsteps]
[PRISONER C]
Hey.
We want to help out with
what you're planning.
We're willing to do anything
to get out of here.
For our families
on the outside!
[DEO, TAKUYA gasping]
[KURTZ]
Uh, wow.
[KURTZ laughs]
[DEO]
Well, Takuya?
If this plan ends up failing,
our fate's worse than torture.
If you're not okay
with that, then, go.
Even if this works,
some of you will die.
This is your last
chance to back out.
Okay, that means everyone
here right now is one of us.
[ALL]
Welcome to the resistance!
[BAZUKU] So, what's the latest
gossip on the prison ward?
Do you remember Takuya,
prisoner number 10-98?
It appears he's
friendly with Amanda.
I wonder if he might be
a part of the resistance.
[BAZUKU laughs]
That's not possible.
I know why he
was imprisoned.
He defiled the priestess
at the border,
the boundary at the
edge of the world.
He's not one of them.
There's another rat
in my prison. But...
[gasps]
[BAZUKU] He does seem to have
the right touch with the ladies.
That may come in handy.
I brought the prisoner!
All right. Now get inside.
Try to behave yourself.
[BAZUKU]
Welcome!
This seems like a
pretty fancy room
for the middle of the desert.
[laughs] Come along, I have
something to show you.
[gasps] This tapestry.
Well, what do you think?
An evocative piece
wouldn't you say?
[TAKUYA]
Yeah.
Looking at it kinda kills your
appetite for anything fun.
I like a young man
with an artistic soul.
Did you really bring me here
just to talk to me about art?
[BAZUKU] I'm actually
offering you a deal.
[TAKUYA]
Hm?
A little bird told me that
you're close to Amanda.
I want you to use your charms
to get her to talk to you.
What do I get if I do?
If you succeed, then I'll
let you see your daughter.
And her name is Yu-No?
If I'm not mistaken.
You'll let me decide how
it happens, though, right?
Well, yes, of course!
You can even make her
yours, if you like.
[TAKUYA]
Okay.
Can you lend me
that sword, then?
[BAZUKU]
Why, whatever for?
It belonged to
the knight, Ailia.
Amanda's sister, the only
relative that she had left.
Should come in handy.
Yes, that'll be fine.
You may have it.
[BAZUKU]
Very well!
The priestess's coffin
is finally complete!
[PRISONERS sighing, chattering]
[PRISONERS chattering]
[TAKUYA]
Can you help me?
I need to talk to Amanda.
Uh? Tonight? That'll be tough.
I really need it to be tonight.
Go check with Bazuku.
That's fine with me.
[PRISON GUARD H]
U-Uh.
[BAZUKU]
Let him do as he wishes.
But tonight the
priestess's coffin--
That was overdone.
Bring me another.
Sir.
[PRISON GUARD A]
Go!
[PRISON GUARDS]
Sir!
Okay. Here's the part
where it gets fun.
[TAKUYA]
Thanks.
Don't blame me for this.
[AMANDA whimpers]
[PRISONERS yelling]
[BAZUKU]
What is that?
[yelling]
[PRISONER B yells]
[PRISON GUARD A] You dog!
You're going to regret this!
You saved me!
Yep, looks like you owe me.
Stay together! We can't
go off course, now!
Stick to the plan!
Head for the Tower of Garzel!
[BAZUKU growling]
[PRISON GUARD A]
Warden Bazuku.
The prisoners, they're rioting!
Then activate the
towers, you idiot!
[PRISON GUARD A]
Sir, we can't.
You see, they're using some
of the guards as hostages!
We couldn't possibly
attack our own men!
[PRISON GUARD A gasps]
Do you think I care?
Get it done!
[PRISON GUARD A]
But, I...
Listen to me, you're all being
paid very competitively
for taking on the
risks of this job!
Therefore, if I ask you
to die, then you will!
[PRISON GUARD A]
Die?
Fine, then I shall
have to do it myself.
Here we go. You ready?
Ready.
[KURTZ]
Hey, Boss! Look, I got it!
[TAKUYA]
Bazuku's headed for the Tower!
Be careful!
Leave it to me!
This is the judgment of god!
[PRISONERS, GUARDS yelling]
No! Run away!
[PRISONERS, GUARDS whimper]
[PRISON GUARD C]
Look at the Tower!
Turn back, now!
Right!
[BAZUKU laughs]
It's time to accept your fate!
[AMANDA]
That's not good.
First thing, we have
to stop Bazuku!
[DEO] Damn it!
That backup tower is active!
Can you throw the sword?
[KURTZ] Maybe, but I'd
have to get closer!
[BOTH yelp]
[AMANDA panting]
[screams]
[gasps] Amanda!
[BAZUKU]
Stay where you are, don't move.
I would advise you to
put down that sword.
By the way, don't get any
funny ideas, all right?
I have this feeling
you're the kind of person
who wouldn't sleep well if
she died because of you.
[BAZUKU laughs]
Now let her go.
[BAZUKU]
Not quite yet.
[gasps]
First, I'll need you
to do me a favor
and kill all the prisoners.
[gasps]
[BAZUKU] I'll keep an eye
on her while you see to that.
What happened?
Why'd the lightning stop?
Here they come!
Go, guys, go!
We need to open
a path for Kurtz!
Do it, now!
[yelling]
[PRISONERS, GUARDS gasping]
Oh, wow.
Looks like Boss was
right, after all!
[PRISONERS cheer]
No! It can't be!
[BAZUKU]
You bastards!
Seems you have more than
your fair share of luck,
but your good fortune ends now.
I'll show you the price
for double-crossing me!
[TAKUYA, BAZUKU grunting]
[BAZUKU yelling]
[TAKUYA grunts]
[whimpers]
[gasping]
Damn you!
[screams]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[PRISON GUARDS screaming]
[BAZUKU grunts]
[TAKUYA] I think he might
be the lucky one.
[AMANDA]
The tower!
Ow.
Yep. That hurts.
Uh! Wait, can anybody hear me?
Please, help!
You can't just leave
here me to die!
Get in here and save me!
Is anybody there? Come save me!
[GUARDS gasping]
[TAKUYA] No good.
I think we have to jump!
[AMANDA] Impossible. Break so
much as a leg and you'll die
in the desert before you
reach the imperial city.
Would you rather we both
get fried here, then?
I don't plan to be killed by
lightning or die of thirst.
I choose death on my own terms.
As long as you're still
alive, there's hope.
And as long as there's hope,
there's possibility.
And as long as
there's possibility,
then we must continue to live.
Fine.
[BOTH scream]
[VOICE]
Takuya! Takuya!
[gasps]
Wha...? Who's that?
Takuya!
Wait. Is that Kunkun?
Get ready to jump!
--Let's go!
--Huh?!
Ha, ha! You saved us, Kunkun!
Woo!
[AMANDA] I can't believe you
really had a nogard for a pet.
Wow, Kunkun, you've really
grown up since we went away.
Ah! You haven't actually
changed, though, huh?
[laughing]
Uh. Is that the Imperial
City? It's huge.
[AMANDA]
But it's empty at its core.
[KUNKUN gasping]
Kunkun?
[TAKUYA, AMANDA scream]
[AMANDA groaning]
[TAKUYA]
Ow...
Kunkun?
Sorry. I pushed too hard.
No, it's okay.
Thank you for always
taking care of me.
[TAKUYA] I'm the one who
should be thanking you!
I love you and Yu-No so much.
Yeah. We'll play again someday.
All of us.
I want to be one
with you. I want to...
[TAKUYA gasping]
Will you please...
let me do that?
Kunkun.
Take this.
What for?
[AMANDA]
Nogards are food.
You understand?
[TAKUYA]
You-- You can't be serious!
She's not gonna survive long.
Do your duty as her owner.
[TAKUYA]
What are you even--
The imperial city
is a long way off.
Would you rather die here?
And let her death
be for nothing?
But, I...
[AMANDA]
It was her last wish.
Honor that.
It's okay.
[KUNKUN]
I love you, Papa.
[YU-NO] Episode 23:
"The Imperial City,
Where the Wind Blows."