[TAKUYA grunting]
[AMANDA] Let me go!
I'll end up taking you with me!
Don't say that!
I'm gonna save you!
Takuya.
I really am so glad that we met.
Thank you for being with me
on my last night here.
Amanda!
[MACHINE]
Nine hundred seconds
to complete synchronization.
Fifteen minutes to go.
I wonder how many
are going to die?
[growls]
[SOLDIER A]
Open the gate!
[SOLDIER B]
Evacuate the citizens!
[SOLDIER C]
We'll hold the line here!
[SOLDIER D]
Hurry!
[SOLDIER E]
Go! Go!
[grunts]
[grunts] Damn!
We don't even get time
to mourn our friend!
No! Amanda's still alive!
We'll have to do our
best to believe that.
Yeah.
We're gonna see this ritual
through and make Amanda proud!
Oh, Takuya.
I wonder if you'd be willing
to destroy that device for me?
You bastard.
No, don't!
He knows that if the barrier is
broken he'll be able to escape!
The barrier's what
matters, not me!
Not Ayumi.
[ABEL]
Luk...
Eihriuluk...
[grunting, gasps]
You always have been a
sleepyhead, haven't you?
Abel!
[grunting] How?
I followed the disruptive
event elements
and ended up here by chance.
So, guess what gets the credit?
Your favorite thing.
[ABEL, ERIKO]
It was "fate."
[ABEL]
Now, let's go.
You're the only one who can stop
him, but you won't be alone.
[MACHINE]
Eight hundred seconds
to complete synchronization.
Make your choice.
You're about to run out of time.
Don't do it! You can't!
Ayumi.
I'm sorry.
You're making the
right choice, okay?
Ryuzoji, if I let you go,
the event collision
will kill everybody!
Even if I save Ayumi,
the result will be the same!
[RYUZOJI] Come on now, it's
not the same thing at all.
Spending the last moments
of your lives together,
holding each other tightly,
feeling sure of that love
before you say goodbye.
That's very different from being
murdered right here and now.
Doesn't matter what you say, my
answer will still be the same.
That so? Too bad.
But fortunately, her advisor
seems to disagree with you.
Niarb!
[yelling]
I will not let the Empress die!
[screams]
No, Asche!
I'll destroy it! Ah!
[gasps]
[RYUZOJI] The Arima family has
caused me no end of trouble,
but this time,
you have my thanks.
This has been quite a pleasure.
[gasps]
Ayumi!
[MACHINE]
Seven hundred seconds until
the dimensional synchronization
system completes its process.
[RYUZOJI] The ritual will come
to an end soon, and it'll do so
in a way that I think you'll
find particularly thrilling.
[growls]
[RYUZOJI]
I no longer need this body.
[CRIMINAL A growls]
No...
So, is this...?
Ryuzoji. The real one!
[roars]
They're losing.
Priestess, you must concentrate.
We have to accelerate
the synchronization.
I know, but if Mother
is destroyed,
then we're all going to die.
Many have sacrificed so that
this ritual might be completed.
Everyone must fulfill their
roles if we are to succeed.
Their roles...
[GRANTIA] Priestess, you must
fulfill your role, as well.
[yelling]
[yells]
[DEO, KURTZ grunt, yelp]
[TAKUYA]
Kurtz! Deo!
Oh, shit.
[ERIKO] Class A Dimensional
Criminal! This is the end!
Oh. I see you're still alive.
But do you really think
you can stop me?
[ABEL]
You won't escape!
[RYUZOJI]
Abel! Damn you!
[CRIMINAL A growls]
[TAKUYA]
Nice of you to join!
Cutting it a little close,
aren't you?
I was on a hot date.
[CRIMINAL A grunting]
[ERIKO gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Don't worry. I got you.
Thank you.
Eihriuluk! Do it, now!
No, you have to
get out of the way!
Shoot while I've got him!
[BOTH gasp]
You have to hurry
or he'll escape again!
No! I can't!
Eriko. I was so happy
when we were together.
I may not have been able
to reach the event root
like we'd hoped...
But in exchange,
I learned about
eternal love with you.
Eihriuluk!
Abel!
[groaning]
[ABEL laughs]
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi. I'm sorry.
I was able to save you before!
Why couldn't I now?
You know why.
This was my fate, and there
was no way to change that.
I won't let my life be ruled
by such ridiculous crap!
Don't say that. It's true.
This was the only reason
that I was born at all.
Nobody was born to just die,
so I don't believe
that for a second!
Heh. You've grown up so strong.
[AYUMI]
You're so much like Kodai.
This only happened to you
because you fell for my dad.
I'm so sorry.
Takuya, when I first arrived
here in Dela Granto,
I learned real loneliness.
[AYUMI]
I was able to stop Ryuzoji
from taking over this world.
And then, before I knew
what was happening.
I became the Divine Emperor.
The days were lonely.
And the nights...
They were even worse.
But somehow, I just knew
you'd come to me one day.
I think that was the only
thing that kept me going.
Sorry. I was late, huh?
You're so warm.
It feels nice.
Ayumi.
[AYUMI]
Would you... hold me tighter?
[gasps]
I've never really
liked being cold.
[MACHINE] Warning: 200
seconds until the dimensional
synchronization system
completes its process.
Two hundred seconds until
the limit horizon is breached.
Not good. The limit
horizon breach
and synchronization are
happening at the same time.
Wait, what does that mean?
If they occur simultaneously,
that means that just when
you and I synchronize,
Dela Granto and Earth
will reach a point
when they can no longer
avoid each other.
That means...
[TAKUYA] Even if the ritual
succeeds as planned...
[ERIKO]
It's basically a 50/50 chance.
If only we had even
an extra second.
[ERIKO]
Yeah, that's all we need.
It would change everything.
At this point, even a
femtosecond would be enough
for us to avoid the
destruction of the world.
[gasps]
[ERIKO]
Not now...
Eriko, what the hell's
happening to you?
[ERIKO] The Dimensional
Bureau must have decided
that my mission
here is finished.
Now that my job is done,
I'm being forced back
to my own dimension.
Arima.
No matter what, don't lose hope.
Of course I won't.
[ERIKO]
I'm really glad I met you.
And I really hope
that we'll meet again
in another parallel world.
Priestess, farewell to you.
It is time now.
Right.
[TAKUYA]
Yu-No, are you okay?
Yeah. I'm just fine.
Remember, long ago,
when you and me
and Mom all slept in
the same bed together?
We'll do it again,
just wait and see.
[YU-NO]
Yes.
[gasps]
Okay, here I go.
[TAKUYA]
Wait for me!
Even if you're sent out beyond
the dimensional horizon,
I'll always come for you,
always, do you hear me, Yu-No?
[YU-NO]
Papa.
Papa!
Grantia, look. At this
rate, they'll all...
[PEOPLE chattering]
Hey, what's that?
[MAN B]
What the...?
[PEOPLE chattering]
[GRANTIA] Unfortunately, the
fate of dimensional collision
cannot be avoided.
[YU-NO]
If only we could make it happen
in a time and place
where nobody lived.
The energy is of a
different magnitude
than any other cycle before.
Using the maximum event shock,
it's not completely
impossible, but...
But what?
[GRANTIA] If that's done,
the body of the priestess
will exceed the speed
of the event elements.
Okay, what happens then?
The event order of the priestess
begins to run backwards.
The way tachyons that
exceed the speed of light
go backwards in time.
What happens then is
impossible to know.
I'll do what has to be done.
[GRANTIA]
Very well.
This is an event spiral,
repeating on an infinite loop.
As we speak,
another Dela Granto
is wandering the dimensional
rifts, repeating its approach
and withdrawal from this
earth time and again.
Please, tell me this.
Will we ever be able to break
the chains of fate that hold us?
I'm really sorry.
I... I think it's over.
Don't say that!
I finally found true friends.
You told me I'm not alone
and wanted to live with me.
[TAKUYA]
I'll get you some psychite!
[inhales]
I promise you!
I'll have to go get it
from another dimension!
Wait for me!
You just keep holding on!
[gasps]
[KANNA]
Mother...
[TAKUYA]
I'm back.
[KANNA gasps]
[gasps]
This is...
[KANNA]
What? Is something wrong?
Now I see. So, that's
how it ended up, huh?
[laughs]
[TAKUYA] It connected.
It finally all connected!
That means the route I followed
was actually the right one!
Wasn't it, Amanda?
You seem different now.
I swear I just said
goodbye a moment ago,
but it's almost like you've
become a different person.
I know, it's a lot.
I can't believe how
much has happened.
[TAKUYA] As promised,
here's the psychite.
In its crystallized form,
so it'll never break.
I don't know how
to thank you!
My entire life has been
one continuous struggle
simply not to die.
And then you came along and
showed me how to really live.
Yuki and Mio helped, too.
You're right.
They're good friends.
And you know, now that
you have what you need,
things will only keep
getting better for you.
So please. Be happy.
Wait, hold on.
Are you going somewhere, Arima?
Someone's waiting for me.
They've been waiting for
thousands of years, now.
I have to go and see her.
[gasps]
Bye, Kanna.
Thank you so much
for everything.
[grunts]
[MIO] So, listen. I've decided
to go study abroad, after all.
[gasps]
I want to get away
from Sakaimachi
for a while, you know?
It's okay, I get it.
Look. I'm, uh... I'm...
Uh?
It's, uh...
Don't forget about me!
[MIO]
Uhh...
Listen, I know how much you
like the boss and everything,
and I get it! But I'm...
I'm not ready to give up yet!
[laughs]
[MIO] I like that about you,
Yuki! I always have!
[MIO laughs]
[YUKI gasps, laughs]
[TAKUYA grunting]
[gasping]
[groaning]
Here we go, it's this way.
[TAKUYA panting]
Yu-No!
Are you okay?
Papa. I missed you so much.
[TAKUYA]
I missed you, too.
I was able to touch the
depths of Grantia's mind,
but I couldn't change
fate, no matter what.
So Dela Granto fell right
here, 8,000 years ago.
I see. That means... it's
still below Mount Sankaku?
[YU-NO] It's thanks to this
that I was able to come here.
[TAKUYA]
Yu-No?
I have to leave you now, and
merge with the fabric of time.
This is goodbye.
[gasps]
So thank you, Papa.
No. You won't be alone anymore!
[YU-NO gasps]
[TAKUYA] Last time,
you had to go on your own.
Not this time.
I can't do it again.
I won't let you travel to
the end of the world alone!
There's nothing there, though.
You will be there.
And Sayless, too.
[YU-NO]
Papa!
Takuya.
I've seen everything
you've been able to do.
And so has your mother.
To be perfectly honest,
I'm more than a little
bit jealous of you.
And do you know why?
You and Yu-No will travel
the rift between events.
You'll see it all.
As if looking through a window
into the truth of history.
You're the envy
of all historians.
Also, as an observer
of the Tree of Vrinda,
I shall continue with my search.
[clock ticks]
[KODAI]
Now, it's time.
I'm glad we got to
have one last talk.
I don't know if
we'll meet again,
but I'll be here
dreaming till then.
It's pitch black in here.
Yeah, it sure is.
Just the two of us, huh?
Guess so.
This may be hell for all I know.
I don't think that's true.
We're an instant, but
also, we're an eternity.
And now we're traveling
up the stream of events.
Hey, Papa.
Look at that.
[TAKUYA]
It's sprouting.
[YU-NO]
It's so cute.
[TAKUYA]
It's still just a baby.
Yet it remembers everything
about this world.
Hey! What would you think
about giving it a name?
We should!
[YU-NO] Actually, I kinda
already thought of one.
Do you know what that name is?
Yes. I think I do know.
Good, the name of
this child is...