[TAKUYA grunting]
[KANNA]
Hey, what'd you make?
[TAKUYA] A mermaid!
And now she's finished!
[gasping]
[KANNA]
Aw, it washed away, huh?
I'll make another one!
Great! How about
we do it together?!
[TAKUYA]
Yeah!
[KANNA laughs]
[beeping]
[TAKUYA groans]
Uh... Just ten more minutes.
[AYUMI] Takuya!
Hey, are you awake up there?
[grunting]
[AYUMI]
Your friends are here!
They look ready for
some fun in the sun!
[YUKI, MIO laugh]
Would you like to come in?
Oh, thanks, but we're
okay to wait here.
[YUKI, AYUMI]
Uh?
Sorry, guys, I'll be ready
in just a few minutes!
Come on, Boss, a day
of adventure awaits!
Hurry! We're gonna miss
the train if you don't.
[YUKI]
Want me to help you pack?
[MIO laughs]
That's so weird.
They're bein' loud again today.
[AYUMI]
Did you remember sunblock?
Oh, and you sure
don't want to forget
this insect spray, either!
Right, yeah. Thank you.
Oh, I forgot!
Where do we keep
the fever reducer?
It's always in the second
drawer of the cupboard.
Why, do you have a fever?
Nah, just like to be prepared.
[AYUMI]
Speaking of "just in case,"
you should bring a few
candles with you, too.
Sure, also. I was thinking
a harness and a whip
might come in handy. Those would
be in your room, right?
No! Of course I don't
have a whip!
I'm out!
[AYUMI]
Oh, wait, one more thing! There.
This was Kodai's.
It suits you.
[TAKUYA]
Okay. See ya.
[AYUMI]
You all have a good time!
--[YUKI, MIO] Thanks!
--[TAKUYA] We will!
So, it's three of them, huh?
[YUKI]
I can't freakin' wait!
[YUKI, MIO laughing]
[creaking]
Wasn't that Hojo?
[doorbell rings]
[KANNA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[YUKI]
Whoa! Hatano, you look so cute!
[TAKUYA] Yeah, it's weird seeing
you out of your uniform.
Well, I guess we'd better go!
If we don't, we'll be
late for our train.
[YUKI] Hey, Shimazu!
You should try one of these!
It's addicting but
it's totally worth it.
You can have some, too,
if you want! Don't be shy!
[TAKUYA]
Is all this crap we brought
really necessary, though?
[YUKI] Yes! It's stuff you need
on a summer trip to the beach!
That's fair, but couldn't
we have at least
blown up the swim ring
after we got there?
Pretty sure you can buy
watermelons there, too.
No, if they only
have pre-cut ones,
we wouldn't be able to
do watermelon splitting!
Would that really be
such a bad thing?
Yes, it would actually
be a terrible thing
because Shimazu said
she's never done it!
Uh. Really? That's just
what you do in the summer!
Yeah, well, my dad
said I wasn't allowed.
Right, I get it.
A fancy girl like you can't be
exposed to anything so barbaric.
It's her first classic
summertime experience!
And I'm gonna be beside her
every step of the way!
It's your first time,
too, isn't it?
Would you like someone
to stick beside you
every step of the way, too?
No, I've actually split
watermelon before, so, I'm good.
Oh, Is that right?
I have to admit, I have a
pretty hard time imagining you
swinging a stick around
violently like that.
I think I'm better
at it than most.
[YUKI] Cool, so, what
time is our transfer?
We'll have to wait a while.
[YUKI] Oh. In that case,
who wants a snack?
[MIO]
Uh? Already?
[TAKUYA] I can't believe
he followed us here!
Wait, explain who's
following who?
That dude's constantly
trailing Kanna.
Sounds like he's one of
those creepy stalker guys.
[YUKI] I mean, should one of us
call the cops or something?
Or at least tell
the station chief?
No, wait. I've got an idea.
[HOJO whistles] That's a nice
package you've got there.
[TAKUYA]
I'm a grower, not a shower.
Aren't you interested in
knowing where Kodai Arima is?
Why, do you know?
[HOJO] Not me. Kanna's the
one with all the answers.
Know what I'd do?
If I were you, I'd steal her
pendant, and then I'd say,
"if you ever want
to see this again,
you'd better tell me
where Kodai Arima is."
[TAKUYA] That's a terrible
idea, man, ciao.
Hey! Hold on!
Damn, can't stop!
Come on! Seriously?
[HOJO grunts]
Okay, where did you go, huh?
[gasping]
[HOJO]
A watermelon?
Bye-bye!
[HOJO]
You brats tricked me!
That train runs nonstop
to the end of the line.
Don't ever come back, dude.
My watermelon.
Bye, little friend,
it was fun while it lasted.
Don't let it get
you down, buddy.
We'll buy you one
when we get there.
And Kanna, you can use
this since yours is gone.
[gasps]
I appreciate it. Thank you.
[MIO grunts]
--[TAKUYA] Wow!
--[YUKI] Whoa! This is huge!
Just so everyone's clear here.
There's not a shotgun-wielding
mayor inside, is there?
That's weird.
You wanna tell me how it is that
you know my dad has a gun?
It's just a hunch, you know?
I can totally imagine him
as that kind of dad.
Threatening any guy who
comes near his daughter.
Well, don't worry.
Dad's pretty busy with
the city council today.
So! Welcome, everyone!
[TAKUYA, YUKI]
Thank you!
[KANNA]
Thank you for having us.
I think I'll head upstairs
to get changed now.
You boys go ahead
and find a place
to change into your
swimsuits, okay?
[YUKI]
Roger that!
Well, you heard the lady,
let's get changed!
Yeah.
[YUKI gasps, yelps]
Don't look!
Are you really
screaming right now?
[KANNA] Don't worry about me.
I'm not easily phased.
So, you're planning to stay
down here while we change?
[KANNA]
I'll go upstairs.
That seems like
the wisest option.
I don't wanna be
mean or anything
but Hatano's a weird girl.
Fair.
[TAKUYA]
Hojo's out there somewhere.
Maybe, just in case...
[TAKUYA]
Whoa! A private beach!
[YUKI]
This is amazing!
[MIO]
Calm down, you guys.
You act like you've never
seen a beach before.
[TAKUYA]
Oh-ho!
She wears a bikini really well.
He's right! You do!
[KANNA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[TAKUYA, YUKI]
Uhh...
What were you expecting
her to wear?
[clears throat] Never mind.
Come on, let's get
this party started!
[TAKUYA, YUKI]
Yeah!
What are you making
over there, Arima?
Heh, heh. Hot mermaid!
And now, she's finished!
Ahh! No! Why?
I'm sorry your mermaid
got washed away.
Tell me something, Kanna.
You have an older sister?
No. I've always been on my own.
On your own?
What about your family?
I'm alone. I don't
have a family,
but I used to live with my mom.
Oh. I understand.
[YUKI]
Hey, Boss!
I told you! It's no good!
They don't sell whole
watermelons here!
Weird for watermelon season!
Well, they sell it all cut up.
And now Shimazu won't
get to experience
her first watermelon-splitting!
Thanks, but it's fine.
Don't worry about it.
[gasps]
[YUKI laughs]
[TAKUYA]
Pardon me, Madame.
Uh?
Would you care for
any assistance?
No, thank you. I don't
think I can trust you
to slather me without
taking peeks.
I'll slather you
however you like.
Would you stop it with
the creepy hand thing?
Right. Fair.
Seriously, though.
I'm still kind of amazed.
I can't believe your dad
let us have the villa.
Well, if he finds out about it,
that gun will make
an appearance.
He doesn't know?
Please, don't tell me that.
I said that I was staying
with my girlfriends.
Uh! I mean, you didn't
have to lie just for me.
[gasps] I didn't do it for
your sake, you narcissist!
Oh, that's right!
I need to take some photos
so I have proof. Hey, Hatano!
That's weird.
Where the heck is she?
What's goin' on, are you
guys not getting in?
It's so perfect out there!
We don't know where Kanna is.
Huh?
[TAKUYA]
Kanna!
[YUKI] Hatano? I wonder
where she could be...
We should split up
and look. Hey!
Are you in here?
Hatano, you here?
[TAKUYA]
Kanna! Where did you--
I'm sorry, is there
something wrong?
--[MIO] What?
--A watermelon.
Where did you get that?
[KANNA] Turns out there's a
watermelon field just down
the road and the farmer
said I could have one.
[gasps] Thank you, Hatano!
[TAKUYA] Okay! I think
it's time to get started!
Let's make Shimazu's
first time good!
Right, here I go!
Uh? Wait, is it normal
to start this far away?
[TAKUYA]
Don't forget the blindfold!
What? Are you serious? No way!
And now you get to spin around!
[MIO gasping]
Go get 'em Shimazu!
But how? I don't know
which way to go!
You wanna go a little
more to the left!
[TAKUYA] You need to go right,
you're too far to the left!
--Not that left!
--No, seriously, the right!
Am I on the right track
yet or am I really off?
[TAKUYA]
Veer right! Trust me!
[YUKI]
Keep going just like that, okay?
You've got this! Just keep
truckin'! Don't give up!
You're doing so great, Shimazu!
Ahh!
[YUKI]
Ohh...
Huh? Uh? Why was I even
listening to you guys?
The watermelon
is way over there!
[TAKUYA]
Sorry! I mean,
that's kinda how it
goes your first time!
Yeah? Well, then, I think you
should be up next, Arima!
I used to be on the
kendo team, you know.
So just don't go blaming me
if the melon gets pulverized.
Well, in that case, we
should let you go last!
Hatano! Would you
like to go next?
Sure. I'm ready.
First, I'll put on
the blindfold.
Spin.
Here I go.
Right! You wanna go a little
more to the right, Kanna!
[BOTH shouting]
[YUKI]
U-Uh...
--[YUKI] Huh?
--[TAKUYA] Uh?
[ALL gasping]
That was really delicious.
Yeah. So, uh...
I just wanted to say...
Thank you for the melon.
[YUKI, TAKUYA laughing]
[KANNA]
It was nothing.
[TAKUYA]
Wait up, Yuki!
[YUKI]
No way, you gotta catch me!
[MIO] Hey, wouldn't you like to
go feel the water for yourself?
[KANNA]
But I...
You could just stay in the
shallow part if you can't swim.
[KANNA] It's just that...
I didn't bring a suit.
That's no problem!
I have an old one I always
keep here. You can use that!
[TAKUYA]
...you can't catch me, big baby!
Crap! Did she disappear again?
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH gasping]
--[YUKI] Whoa!
--[TAKUYA chuckles]
Is something wrong guys?
[BOYS]
You look great! Really!
You could lose your pendant
if you wear it in the water,
so you may want to consider
leaving it here.
Sure.
It's cold.
You don't have to
go in, you know.
I want to.
It feels really good.
[MIO laughs]
[YUKI, TAKUYA, MIO laugh]
[YUKI laughing]
[YUKI] Look, I brought fireworks
so we can do them after dinner!
[TAKUYA] Cool, but first
things first: let's eat!
[gasps]
Uh. Hey, is something wrong?
Where's my pendant?
I know I left it right there,
and without it I...
[YUKI]
What the...?!
Check it out, all the meat
for the barbecue is gone!
Down to the last hot dog!
This is super weird.
[clattering]
[ALL gasp]
What just made that sound?
I have no idea.
Think the mayor's after us
with a shotgun after all?
No, are you kidding me?
If that was my dad, you and
Yuki would be dead by now.
That's good to know.
[ALL gasp]
What the hell happened here?
The device is gone. I wonder
if this could be Hojo.
--[clattering]
--[ALL gasp]
[TAKUYA]
What's down there?
It's the basement.
Yuki, come with me.
[YUKI]
Sure!
[TAKUYA]
Mio, look after Kanna.
Got it.
Look, don't worry about a thing,
okay? We're all here for you!
[TAKUYA]
Uh...
Seriously?
A dog did all of this?
[BOTH scream]
[TAKUYA]
We can't let him get away!
[MIO, KANNA scream]
[TAKUYA]
Are you two okay?
We're fine,
but whose dog is that?
He's wild. Just stay back.
[ALL gasp]
[TAKUYA]
Watch out!
[YUKI grumbles] I was looking
forward to that barbecue.
It's a bummer that we lost
all our fireworks, too.
So, do we have
nothing for dinner?
[MIO] I think I've got some
instant ramen in there.
All our perfect summer
beach plans...
[TAKUYA grunts]
Nah, I don't think I will.
[MIO]
What're you talking about?
Uh. We only get one shot
at youth. Know what I mean?
What?
This summer will
never come again.
It'll only happen once,
and that's why it's special.
[door creaks]
Uh? You got some sun, huh?
Yeah, and the water stung a
little bit. Not bad, though.
You should put some
after-sun lotion on it.
Have a seat. I'll help you out.
[MIO]
That was a pretty full day,
but it was fun, don't you think?
Mm? Did you not have fun?
It's just that this was
my first time doing this.
Hanging out with
friends, I mean.
Yeah, I think it was fun.
How about we all come back here
and do this again next summer?
[YUKI, TAKUYA grunting]
Yuki, stop! Stop pushing!
You're gonna make us fall!
[YUKI, TAKUYA scream]
[thud]
What?!
--[TAKUYA] Ruff, ruff...
--[YUKI barks]
Oh no. Is that
another wild dog?
[BOTH barking, howling]
[MIO] Hey, Hatano. What do you
think of Arima? Do you like him?
[KANNA] I've noticed
that when he's around
my heart beats faster.
[MIO]
Wow. It's funny you say that,
because mine does
the same thing.
[KANNA]
I guess, we're the same, then.
[MIO]
We are.
[BOTH snoring]
Oh, there it is.
I thought I lost my yummy hot
dog earlier but it looks like
I just found it.
Time for dinner!
[crunch]
[TAKUYA screams]
[YUKI] Well, you two. Shimazu
and I are going this way.
See you around, Arima!
Goodbye, Kanna.
[KANNA]
Bye, see you soon.
[TAKUYA]
Later!
That really surprised me.
It was a lot of fun. Thanks
again for inviting me along.
Aw, stop, it was my pleasure!
So, anyway, you want
me to walk you home?
No. Thanks,
I'll be fine on my own.
Bye, then.
[TAKUYA]
See ya.
Uh?
[TAKUYA]
Kanna!
[YU-NO] Episode 16:
"Inside Unmoving Time."