[TAKUYA gasping]
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi?
Sorry, I'm coming in now!
Kick my ass if I'm wrong!
You hear me?!
[gasping]
[TAKUYA]
No... No...!
This can't be happening.
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi!
[TAKUYA screams]
I have to fix this somehow.
[TAKUYA]
I'll find a way.
Dad...
For the first time in my life,
I'm grateful for you.
[ERIKO] 'Kay. I'm passing
out the quiz now--
Let's do this!
[ERIKO]
Hey!
--You okay, boss?
--What's the deal?
You were bragging just a
second ago, weren't you?
[ERIKO] Why did you come
to class in the first place
if you were only
gonna run away?!
[TAKUYA] There has to be
some way to save her.
Something I can do
different this time.
Anything!
[TOYOTOMI chuckles]
This isn't right.
C'mon, Chief. Don't worry.
I can make your little
problem go away, easy,
and I don't ask
for much in return.
[AYUMI]
No! Stop it!
I'm sorry, but I
don't wanna do this!
Listen, I'm trying to help out,
so you don't have to lose
your job at Geotech.
You wouldn't want to give up
your research, now would you?
[gasping]
[TOYOTOMI]
Your reputation would be ruined.
Then you'd be out on
the street, in no time.
I'm afraid your son's future
would go right down the drain.
Forgive me, Kodai.
[door opens]
[BOTH gasp]
Don't do this!
[TOYOTOMI]
Great...
Takuya?
You are gonna pay, right now!
Children these days.
Awfully needy, aren't you?
Give Mom some privac-- Oh!
Ow!
Oh, no. Takuya. Stop it!
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi, you don't need to listen
to a word this asshole says.
[TOYOTOMI]
What the hell are--
[TAKUYA]
Come here!
[TOYOTOMI]
Uh! Let go, you little brat!
[AYUMI]
Please, just let him go!
I'll take care of this
mess on my own!
And don't blame yourself.
None of this is your fault!
Hey! You think you can
get away with this?
[TOYOTOMI groaning]
Let me go!
[door clicks]
How in the world
did it come to this?
[TOYOTOMI groans]
Don't you ever come back here!
Leave Ayumi the hell alone!
[TOYOTOMI] This is a crime,
I'll have you know! Assault!
No. It's felony assault!
I'm going to the cops
and then you are going
to jail for a long time!
[TAKUYA]
Whatever.
Say goodbye to your freedom!
In the end, ow,
the good guys always win!
[sighs] That should
do it, right?
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi.
[TAKUYA gasping]
[TAKUYA]
Why?
I fixed it. Didn't I?
You weren't supposed to die!
[TAKUYA]
I'll do it again.
This reality is bullshit!
It's not over yet!
[ERIKO] 'Kay. I'm passing
out the quiz now--
[TAKUYA]
Okay, let's go!
[ERIKO]
Hey!
Bye, I guess?
What's the deal?
You were bragging just a
second ago, weren't you?
I wanted to yell at him, but he
looked like he'd seen a ghost.
I wonder if it's an emergency?
[YUKI] You mean like...
a poop emergency?
C'mon. Don't worry.
I can make your little
problem go away, easy,
and I won't ask much.
[door opens]
[AYUMI gasps]
Takuya!
[TOYOTOMI]
Jeez, kid. Next time knock.
--Takuya, hold on!
--Uh, hey?
Stop! That hurts!
We were having an important
conversation, here!
Was it about your
purple panties?
Now cover that thing you're
stinking up the room.
We're outta here.
You're gonna regret this!
That's enough!
Would you please let me go?
I said that's enough!
It's complicated, Takuya.
But I do have my reasons.
[TAKUYA]
You've got this wrong.
Listen to me.
Toyotomi set this thing
up from the start!
He hired those Yakuza
guys to attack you.
He stole those top-secret files.
He's trying to blackmail you!
[gasps] You're making
all of this up.
[TAKUYA]
I'm serious!
Where's the proof?
Do you have any?
Well, I...
I know you don't like Toyotomi--
you've made that clear.
But you don't understand.
He'd never do those
horrible things.
In his own way, he was
trying to help me.
I still believe in him.
That bastard was about to rape
you, and you defend him?!
Why would you do that?!
You gotta pull it together!
I'm here to help you!
Stop this!
I don't have the strength
to keep fighting like this.
[AYUMI]
Just leave me.
[gasps]
I give up.
I'm tired.
I can't do it.
[gasping]
[tires screeching]
[crash]
[BYSTANDER 5A screams]
[DRIVER 5A]
What just happened?
[BYSTANDER 5A]
Call an ambulance! Hurry!
[DRIVER 5A]
It's too late.
--[BYSTANDERS murmuring]
--[sirens blaring]
No... Ayumi.
[TAKUYA]
No matter what it takes--
I'll save you!
[ERIKO] 'Kay. I'm passing
out the quiz now.
Uh. What's wrong?
You're not leaving now, are you?
[ERIKO gasps]
Hey! Arima!
[door slides]
What's gotten into that kid?
A bathroom emergency?
Oh, I've been there.
No wonder he looked mad.
[TAKUYA]
Beating up Toyotomi didn't work.
Taking Ayumi away didn't work.
What else can I do?
Well I'll be damned,
look who it is.
Haven't seen you in a while.
[PUNK 5B]
You didn't forget us, did you?
[PUNK 5A]
You all by yourself?
Where's your little pal Yuki?
Listen, man. I don't have
time for this right now.
Aw come on, we're holding
a party just for you!
[groans]
Oh, the fun we used to have.
And now it's finally
time to pay you back.
You heard me!
I don't have time for this!
[PUNK 5B groans]
[TAKUYA grunts]
--[TAKUYA groans]
--[PUNKS laughing]
[TAKUYA whimpers]
[TAKUYA]
Hey, Ayumi?
[gasping]
[screams]
You think I'm gonna give up?
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi!
[grunting]
[TAKUYA gasping]
[BYSTANDERS chattering]
--[BYSTANDERS chattering]
--[alarm blares]
[TAKUYA]
What can I do?
You don't really wanna
die that badly, do you?
Please, there has
to be something...
[TAKUYA]
"The Reflector Device
does not have
unlimited influence.
Some worlds have a high
phenomenological density.
Alterations to them
have a limit radius.
Where some events are
impossible to stop.
This barrier is referred
to as an 'Event
Schwarzschild Radius'.
And the unavoidable situation
is referred to as 'fate'."
[TAKUYA] You're saying
she's meant to die?
Well, screw that.
I'm not letting "fate"
decide a damned thing.
You think I'll
give up that easy?
[KAORI]
Well! Look who it is!
Did you get stood up by a girl?
I was just joking. You don't
have to look so serious.
I've been waiting for you.
All right.
I'll cut to the chase.
[gasps] An ID card.
[TAKUYA grunts]
Hey, not that I'm complaining,
but it seems a bit convenient
that you're offering
me that card.
It's simple enough.
I know you've been snooping
around Geotech,
but if you really want
to get the whole story,
you're going to
need one of these.
Oh, I get it now.
After my message, you wanted to
know what Toyotomi was up to.
You're quick on the uptake.
[KAORI laughs] It's a deal.
In exchange for that ID card,
I'll tell you anything
you want to know.
Give me one little
second. [laughs]
I've got the goods
in here somewhere,
I just need to find them.
Here.
Whoa. These photos...
Uh-huh! Those will come
in pretty handy I bet.
Thank you. They're perfect.
I like it a lot better
when you're smiling.
Almost reminds me of your dad.
[TAKUYA] If that's supposed to
flatter me, it's not working.
[KAORI] And you look even more
like him when you're angry!
I'm leaving.
Oh. Actually.
What is it? If you wanna
have some fun, just say so.
What, are you crazy?
[KAORI] Wow. You get an
offer from a hottie like me
and turn it down?
Uhh. Where's the hottie?
Seriously, all I see
is some thirsty cougar.
[KAORI]
So that's how it's gonna be.
[TAKUYA]
U-Uh!
[KAORI]
You know,
I've always wanted to
take a boy's virginity.
Now might be my chance.
Hate to tell ya, but you're
a little late for that.
Well, that's no fun. Never mind.
[TAKUYA]
Oh, before I forget.
You wanna tell me what big scoop
this ID card's gonna get you?
[KAORI] Later. So you have
something to look forward to.
[ERIKO] 'Kay. I'm passing
out the quiz now.
Okay. Last time.
Uh. Boss?
Hold on! I thought you said
you were going to ace this test!
You're not angry?
No, it's all right. Now.
It's time for your quiz!
Don't be shy! What's the matter?
[AYUMI]
No!
[door opens]
[TOYOTOMI growls]
[TOYOTOMI] Jeez, kid.
Awfully needy, aren't you?
Can't you give your poor mother
a little privacy for once? Huh?
Forget him.
You don't have to listen
to a word he says,
Ayumi. He's a liar.
Those Yakuza guys who
attacked you were hired by him.
[BOTH gasp]
You've got some
imagination, don't you?
Listen, you can't throw around
these wild accusations.
You need proof.
All right, then. Does this work?
[TOYOTOMI]
Uh! It can't be. No way.
Where did you get these?
What's going on?
Is that what it looks like?
But why would you do this?
Give it up, Toyotomi.
You're done.
'Fraid there's no talking
your way out of this one.
[laughs]
What the hell are
you laughing at?
I'm young, I'm attractive,
and I'm going places.
I gave some washed-up old widow
a chance to get with this.
If she can't appreciate me,
it's her loss!
Son of a--
Adios!
[TAKUYA] I'm not done with
you yet! Get back here!
[door slams]
[panting]
[TAKUYA]
Hey!
Awful persistent, aren't you?
I'm not gonna be your new daddy,
so give it up already!
Keep runnin' your mouth.
Let's see how well that line
works for you in prison!
[TOYOTOMI]
You gonna make me say it again?
The good guys always
win in the end!
Hello!
[TAKUYA]
What did you do?
I hit him on the head
with a pot, obviously,
but I wonder if it'll be okay.
Will what be okay? Y'mean the
pot? 'Cause he's out cold.
[KAORI]
Why would I care about him?
[TAKUYA]
Fair enough.
[KAORI] I've been wanting
to hit that slimy bastard
for a long time now.
It felt good. Huh.
I kinda wanna do it again.
[TOYOTOMI groans]
[KAORI]
I see.
Ayumi's situation makes
this a bit tricky.
I wouldn't recommend going
to the police just yet.
What d'you mean?
The media's about to report
that Ayumi sold data to
a rival company, which will turn
this whole thing into a circus.
But that's just a rumor.
It's not even true!
People love a good
scandal, though.
They're always hungry
for stories like that.
So we just let this bastard go,
like he didn't do
anything wrong?
[KAORI]
Of course not.
But we'll do it my way.
It may be a more delicate
approach, but if you trust me,
I think you'll be satisfied.
All right.
Now you hurry back to your mom.
She could use some support.
[gasps] I shouldn't
have left her.
Thanks for all your help!
[KAORI]
Any time.
--[door opens]
--[TAKUYA] I'm back!
Ayumi!
[gasping]
[water splashes]
Please no...
[AYUMI]
I'm sorry Kodai. I tried.
But I can't do this anymore.
I'm too tired.
Ayumi!
Please, leave me alone.
[TAKUYA] I'm not going anywhere
until you hand me that razor!
Come on,
we'll work through this!
[AYUMI]
Stay back!
I'm done. Okay?
I don't have it in me
to keep doing this.
Can we please just talk?
I'm here for you!
Don't stop me.
I've made up my mind.
Oh, Kodai.
It's been so long, but I'm
coming to see you now.
--[TAKUYA] Stop it!
--[splash]
[AYUMI]
Get off!
[TAKUYA]
No way!
Let me go! It's my life!
[TAKUYA] I'm not giving up
after all of this!
Do what your mother
tells you to do, Takuya!
[TAKUYA] You really think
that's gonna work?
Ayumi, please.
Just calm down and we can
work this out together.
You're just a teenager!
I'm not going to listen
to some lecture from you!
Did you...
Did you just slap me?!
You were acting like a brat
throwing a temper tantrum.
Stop being such a smartass!
You don't know what
I'm going through!
Yeah, But I know your
bra size--is that enough?
[AYUMI]
You idiot! Stupid, stupid idiot.
I'm in so much pain.
I'm so lonely without him!
I know how you feel.
[AYUMI]
No! You don't!
Well. Maybe you could
talk me through it.
I'm falling apart!
Why are you so calm?!
[TAKUYA]
"Don't be a fool, Ayumi.
Why, you know better than this!"
[AYUMI gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Ha, ha! Come on.
It sounded a little
like him, right?
Heh! Hardly. You
may be father and son,
but you two couldn't
be more different.
And here I thought I nailed it.
Guess I'll have to be
charming all on my own.
Well? Feel better?
Yeah. Thank you for this.
I will never let
you down again.
I'll prove your innocence.
[gasps]
Life'll go back to normal, and
you can continue your research.
What have you been up to?
How much do you
really know, Takuya?
Don't you worry about that.
Even if it means going to
another time, another world.
I'll do whatever it
takes to save you.
But I need you to believe in me.
Don't ever do something
like this again.
Can you promise me that?
All right, you have my word.
[YU-NO] Episode 6:
"Beyond a Pale Light."