[GUARD F]
Find out if she's a virgin!
[gasps]
[GUARD G]
Do not resist us!
[GUARD F]
Hold her down!
[GUARD G] Priestess or not,
the rules are absolute!
[TAKUYA]
Sayless!
Takuya!
[GUARDS gasp]
[GUARD H]
She's speaking, too?!
Takuya, run!
Get out of here!
This is unbelievable.
So, she offered them both?
She gave that man
her body and her soul?
[yells]
[gasps]
[GUARD F groans]
There you are, you bastard!
[TAKUYA gasps, groans]
[chirps]
Papa.
[KUNKUN chirping]
[TAKUYA groaning]
[GUARD G]
Hey, you swine!
Do you have any idea who you
just drew your sword against?
I honestly don't give a shit.
You monsters just broke into
my house and attacked my wife!
What do you bandits
want from us anyway?
Wait, who's the bandit?!
You murdered Ailia, the knight,
and then you stole this house!
No, that's not what I did!
[GUARD H]
Uh-huh.
Then you dared to imply that
the royal guards were bandits.
That's a very bold
insult for a peasant.
[TAKUYA]
Wait, what?
We're taking the priestess
with us now.
Done by the order of
the Divine Emperor.
[TAKUYA] I couldn't care
less whose order it is!
Got it?! You're not taking
Sayless away from here!
[SAYLESS]
Takuya!
Go, now! You have to
get out of here!
Please, don't struggle.
Sayless!
[groans]
Damn it, no! You...
Learn your place!
Don't hurt him!
[TAKUYA grunting]
[GUARD A] Uh! Priestess!
What are you doing?
[gasps]
Please, don't do this!
Uh!
[GUARDS gasp]
Takuya.
I won't forget.
Not ever.
[gasps] Stop this, now! Please!
You don't wanna do this!
Sayless!
Takuya...
I love you.
[KUNKUN grunting]
Kunkun, stop doing that!
Come on, what is it?
I'm trying to get home
as fast as I can!
[KUNKUN chirping]
[YU-NO]
Jeez!
What is it?
Mama?
I need you to trust me.
You and I will become one.
[YU-NO]
Become one?
I love you, Yu-No.
[TAKUYA gasping]
Sayless. Please, no,
this can't be happening.
You can't go! Come back!
[TAKUYA screaming]
I swear. I'm gonna kill you!
I'll kill every last one of you!
I think it's time
I deal with the man.
[GUARD H] Leave him.
For now, we need to focus
on getting Keyales's body
back to the imperial capital.
[GUARD 20A] Hey, look
what I just found inside!
[GUARD H gasps]
Is that...?
[GUARD G]
Impossible!
[GUARD 20A] The sacred
treasure of the capital!
[gasps] Leave that alone!
It's not--
[groans]
[thud]
So, he stole the sacred
treasure, too?
How dare he.
[GUARD H]
Let's go!
[YU-NO]
Papa! Papa!
Come on, you have to wake up!
[grunting]
[TAKUYA]
Yu-no...
Papa!
[KUNKUN chirps]
[TAKUYA] I just...
I couldn't protect her.
I couldn't keep Mama safe
no matter what I tried to do!
[TAKUYA]
I'm sorry, Yu-No.
[KUNKUN whines]
[YU-NO]
Papa.
Mama didn't really go anywhere.
She lives here.
She's right inside my heart.
It's real.
She's here.
She is?
Mama came to me, and
the two of us became one.
Oh! She wanted me
to tell you something.
"From now on, the three of us
will always be together."
Isn't that great?
[YU-NO laughs]
[SAYLESS laughs]
[TAKUYA gasping]
[gasps]
Of course. It's great.
Sayless. I love you.
[ADVISOR]
So, Keyales had already
lost the right to
be a priestess,
to the same man who stole
the sacred treasure?
[GUARD H]
Yes, sir.
[ADVISOR]
Suicide, though? Very dramatic.
However, it may be a fitting
end to a fallen priestess.
[GUARD H]
Without a priestess,
we will be unable to
hold the ritual, sir.
Indeed. It's certain
the world shall perish
if things stay as
they are right now.
[EMPEROR]
Mother has spoken.
She tells me that Keyales
gave birth to a daughter.
Go and find her immediately!
[GUARDS]
Yes, sir!
[EMPEROR] What of the man
who was with her?
[GUARD H] He's probably
died in the desert by now.
[EMPEROR]
Have you discovered who he is?
No, sir, we know nothing yet.
But the priestess did address
him as "Takuya."
[EMPEROR]
Takuya...?
[chirps]
Sorry, buddy.
I'm afraid we won't be able
to carry enough food for you.
Goodbye, Kunkun.
Goodbye!
[chirping]
Don't follow me!
The desert is very
dangerous, okay?
That's why I can't
take you with me!
[KUNKUN whines]
Kunkun, go!
I hate you!
[TAKUYA]
Sorry.
Thanks so much for
being her friend.
We'll miss you... Kunkun.
Goodbye.
[TAKUYA] Man, this may have
been a terrible decision,
but I have to get to the
imperial city, no matter what.
I need to get the
Reflector Device back,
and I have to get the
psychite for Kanna.
Uh? Papa, look at that!
There's a town over there!
You see it?
C'mon, let's go!
[TAKUYA] Yu-no,
there's no point in going.
What do you mean?
What you're seeing is a mirage.
An illusion caused by
the bending of the light.
It's not real.
Oh, it's not?
[YU-NO yawns]
I'm sleepy, Papa.
[TAKUYA] You can sleep as
long as you don't fall off.
[YU-NO] Okay. We're not
there yet, are we?
[TAKUYA] We'll have a
daddy-daughter date on the way.
[YU-NO]
Sure. What's a "date," though?
[WOMAN grunts]
[TAKUYA]
Here.
Hold on, isn't that your water?
[chuckles] It's okay. I don't
want any more today, that's all.
[YU-NO] Hey, Papa. We'll be
there soon, won't we?
At the capital?
[TAKUYA]
Yeah, we're almost there.
[TAKUYA] We keep having this
conversation over and over.
But I can't tell the truth.
I won't take away her one hope.
I know these exchanges are
meaningless, but I can't stop.
[TAKUYA]
Mm? Uh!
What is this?
[YU-NO]
There's lots of them, huh?
[TAKUYA] It almost looks like a
dumping ground for old coffins.
[TAKUYA]
There's nothing inside.
[coughs]
Papa. Am I seeing
another mirage?
[TAKUYA grunting]
[TAKUYA gasping]
[CAMEL groaning]
Oh, Papa, he's saying
he's very tired.
I'm sure.
You need to eat.
Thanks for all that
you did for us.
[TAKUYA] We're completely
out of food and water.
So, all we can do now is pray.
Pray that we're not out of luck.
[TAKUYA] Yu-No! Come on,
sweetie, you have to wake up!
Papa, we're almost
there, aren't we?
[TAKUYA grunting]
Water! Please!
Just a little bit of water!
I need water for Yu-No!
[TAKUYA groaning]
[TAKUYA] Damn it.
Just another stupid mirage!
Unless... Hold on.
The sun's not even up yet!
[TAKUYA grunting]
[TAKUYA panting]
It's real, an oasis!
[TAKUYA]
Yu-No! You're gonna be okay.
[WOMAN humming]
[gasps]
[gasping]
Hm?
[TAKUYA]
A-Ah!
Really? Wait, is there another
hot naked girl over there?
What, another one? Where?
[laughs nervously]
It's nice to meet you.
[screams]
So, you're planning on having
your way with me, now,
isn't that right?
You're a pervert and
a beast and a brute!
You're going to use to me
to satiate your manly lusts.
That's not true!
You're gonna make
me your sex slave!
Stop! What are you
even talking about?
So? What's stopping you?
Have your wicked way with me!
I'm ready for you, don't worry.
[SALA humming]
What the hell is
this girl's problem?
Papa?
[SALA] Wait, you came to beat
up the Divine Emperor?
Yeah, that's right.
And that was important
enough for you
to drag a kid across the desert?
That guy deserves a punch in
the mouth for what he did to me.
Problem?
[SALA]
Not really, nothing like that.
It's just...
[laughing]
I think you might be going
up against the wrong guy!
I mean why do you want
to punch the Emperor?
I'll leave that to
your imagination.
So, what about you, uh. Sorry?
I'm Sala.
[TAKUYA]
What are you doing out here?
[SALA] Well, the truth is,
the imperial city
is really dangerous these days,
thanks to the rebels. So,
I finally gave up and ran.
[TAKUYA] By "rebels," you mean
some kind of resistance?
[SALA]
Yep. People who want
to defeat the Divine
Emperor, just like you.
[SALA gasps]
When you get there,
you should try to find
them and talk to them!
[TAKUYA]
I'm not trying to make friends.
That's not...
You really do just want
to punch the guy.
Yeah, basically.
[laughing] I'll say this.
You are an interesting one.
Uh!
[laughs]
[YU-NO laughing]
[YU-NO]
Papa! Watch this!
Woo!
[YU-NO laughing]
[YU-NO]
It feels so good!
Wow, look at you! You seem
to be feeling better!
I am! And I'm sure it's because
I got to spend so much
time talking with you!
[SALA]
Hm?!
This is something
really new for me!
So fun! I mean,
it was my first time
getting to talk
with another girl!
Oh? Wait, what about
your mother, though?
[YU-NO] Mama didn't talk, she
was kinda different like that.
Oh, yeah? You mean she
was really quiet?
[YU-NO]
Mm-mm. That's not it.
Mama was... Uh.
Sure, I understand.
So, what you're saying is,
I'm not supposed to talk to
strangers about you, right?
Yes. I got it.
Hey, what's up? Who are
you talking to over here?
Mama's here.
She's always inside me.
[gasps]
Oh, I can't say that, either?
I guess we've got it
kinda tough, don't we?
Hey, how long are you
gonna keep following us?
Didn't you just
flee the capital?
Well, I'm worried, though.
I mean, how can I just abandon
someone who says
they're going to punch
the freakin' Emperor?
[TAKUYA]
Uh! Man, did we need this!
[SALA] Ha! There it is! It's
really about to come down, hard.
I say we go wait it out
inside that temple!
How does this thing open?
Leave it to me. Tad-ah!
[SALA humming]
[SALA] Push here, and here,
and now we're done!
I can see why you ran
away from the capital.
You're extremely talented.
I'm just very good with
my hands, that's all!
Hey, Papa?
Yeah? What is it?
It's my heart. It feels like
it's pounding so hard.
Your heart does?
[SALA]
Hey fellas!
[gasps]
I brought someone very special
here to meet you guys!
Sala! How could you?!
Look, don't blame me, okay?
I mean, come on,
you know you've got that huge
bounty on your head, right?
[GUARD B] He's the one who
defiled Keyales the priestess.
[GUARD C] Wait then,
is that girl her successor?
No!
Let me go! Help me, Papa!
Yu-No! Yu-No!
Where the hell am I?
[PRISONER A]
Welcome to the quarry.
Although in our case,
it's more accurate to
call it "the prison."
[TAKUYA]
The prison?
What the--?
[TAKUYA]
Isn't that...?
[YU-NO] Episode 21:. "The
Quarry Where Demons Rule."