They're going to be okay.
They have to be.
--Uh.
--[YUKI gasping]
There's no way Mother
Nature made this, right?
It's like a machine.
[YUKI] But everything in here
is carved out of the mountain.
What's going on?
[yelps]
[TAKUYA]
What is this place?
[YUKI] Who do you think
built this place?
I mean, we're in the middle
of the mountain, right?
I know I talked about how
nobody'd really checked out
Mount Sankaku yet, but this is
beyond what I even imagined.
[gasps] The underground
base of Gelgey the Fiend!
It's exactly like this!
Who's Gelgey?
Gelgey the Fiend is very
dark and very powerful.
The treacherous leader
of an evil organization!
He forces the innocent
to engage in hard labor
to accomplish his
terrible, nasty deeds.
Is this one of those things
where I need to punch you
to wake you up?
[laughs] It was a joke.
[sighs] Well, that may be.
You might not be all
that far off, though.
Look at that. My guess is
this place must've been
some combination of
a prison and a mine.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Well, maybe it's because
they're from a long time ago?
No, and you won't find it
in our history books.
[TAKUYA]
Huh?
Looks like we can
go through there.
[footsteps]
[BOTH gasp]
[YUKI]
Huh. Looks like a dead-end.
[thud]
Hey, what's that? A rock?
It's a crown. At least,
I think that's what it is.
Wait, it's goes in there, right?
Oh, crap, what's happening?
[TAKUYA]
Who knows?
[YUKI]
Huh?!
Wow, a hidden passage.
What kind of high-tech maze
is this place, anyway?!
[groaning]
[TAKUYA]
I'm gonna go on ahead.
And I want you to
follow from behind.
Ahh! It's another body!
You're such a spaz.
Uh, sorry about that.
[TAKUYA] Maybe he was one
of the workers here.
[TAKUYA] Hey, those look like
the letters on Futago Rock.
Boss, over there.
[TAKUYA]
Hm... Oh! That's Mio's!
Shimazu...
That notebook she always
keeps with her is missing.
Was she here, though?
Staring at this same thing?
So is she lost down here?
Without food or water?
She must be so scared!
[TAKUYA] Yeah, this isn't good.
We need to hurry.
Shimazu! Where are you?!
Uh. Wait, where're you going?
[YUKI] I'm coming! I'll be
right there! Just hold on!
Hey! Wait up!
[YUKI yells]
[TAKUYA gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Yuki! Yuki!
Shit...
[rope stretching]
[TAKUYA grunting]
Yuki! Where are you? Answer me!
[YUKI groaning]
Boss...
Yuki!
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Oh, no...
[footsteps]
[TAKUYA]
Hang on, buddy! I'll help you.
[YUKI]
No, forget me. Find Shimazu.
Don't be an idiot!
What're you trying to say?
Please, listen to me, Boss!
[gasping]
This is all my own fault.
Because it's my fault
that Shimazu--
[coughs]
[TAKUYA]
Don't talk! Try to stay calm!
I'll get Mitsuki, okay?
[YUKI]
Please. You have to go save her.
No. Oh, please, no.
Wake the hell up, Yuki!
Come on! Wake up!
Do you hear me?! Come on!
No way. This can't be real.
Yuki! Wake up!
Say something ridiculous!
[TAKUYA cries]
[TAKUYA] Any world where Yuki
dies has to be a terrible lie!
Listen, here's the thing.
What's up, Boss?
[TAKUYA] It's just... I actually
think you should stay here.
[BOTH gasp]
Wait, why are you saying that?
You just said we
could go together!
I stopped to think about it.
I'm worried you're too emotional
to be clearheaded in there.
Honestly, I think
you'll get in the way.
You don't get it!
This is all my fault!
I need to be the one
who saves her!
[TAKUYA]
You'll just make it worse, okay?
[gasps]
[TAKUYA] I don't have the
time to look after someone
who can't take
care of themselves.
Mitsuki, let's go.
[MITSUKI]
Yeah. Okay.
Heh. That was textbook "you."
What are you talking about?
That was some pretty
tough love with Yuki.
You're a good friend.
Look, the kid's really clumsy.
That's why he gets
himself kill--
[clears throat]
What?
Nothing, forget it. Anyway,
I think it's right around here.
There we go.
You knew it was here, how?
I dunno. I guess I play
a lot of video games.
Now, shall we?
[MITSUKI]
Look! Is that her bag?
[TAKUYA]
I think so.
--[rumbling]
--Uh?
What could that be?
[TAKUYA]
This isn't what happened
in the universe
where I just was!
[MITSUKI gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Mitsuki!
[MITSUKI screams]
[TAKUYA groans]
[TAKUYA]
Man, that was rough.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, I can't believe it,
but I am.
Unfortunately, I think
I lost my flashlight.
Yeah, me too.
Dammit. Where'd it go?
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps] What the hell
do you think you're doing?
[TAKUYA]
Ah. Sorry.
[growls]
Hey, it's dark.
I couldn't see anything.
Can we keep focused
on the task at hand?
Sheesh, yeah, of course we can.
Wait. Look, I think
there's something here.
Hey! Stop!
Don't try to touch me just
because I can't see you!
Sorry! It wasn't deliberate!
Wow, your body's just as
sensitive as ever, isn't it?
[MITSUKI growls]
[TAKUYA]
Here we go! Check it out!
Ahh! Mitsuki!
What happened to you?
You're as old and
dried out as a mummy!
Shut your mouth,
you little jerk.
Sorry.
You think it's someone
who got lost?
Hard to say.
[TAKUYA] It seems a lot
newer than the other bodies,
doesn't it?
[MITSUKI] This belonged
to Dr. Yurika Imagawa!
[TAKUYA]
Uh. Dr. Imagawa?
Wait, didn't she
work with my dad?
[MITSUKI] Yeah. I remember
hearing that she'd gone missing.
Guess she was here.
What's it say in her notebook?
"It's overwhelming.
The fear and anticipation
threaten to crush me."
Even as I write these words,
my hands are shaking
as if I were a child."
[IMAGAWA]
Mount Sankaku.
It's possible that the key to
history's greatest mysteries
lie right here, where I stand.
After all, these ruins have
been here for millennia.
I still regret the fact
that I couldn't bring
a whole team with me.
[IMAGAWA] These ruins are
starkly different from those
of any other culture
throughout history.
I truly think this phenomenon
might have been...
[MITSUKI] "...caused by an event
collision between two dimensions
that crossed each
other's boundaries."
What is an event collision?
[IMAGAWA]
"Dr. Arima's theory was that
event collisions occurred
approximately every 400 years."
[IMAGAWA]
For example,
Takanoamahara exists in a
different dimension than ours,
but there was an event
collision with Japan,
resulting in the importation
of a new culture.
I was able to
thoroughly investigate
the electromagnetic and
gravitational fields
of Sakai-machi, and I
concluded that, indeed,
an event collision had
taken place in the past.
What must occur to cause
an event collision?
I was so obsessed and eager
to solve the mystery,
that I foolishly allowed myself
to get to the point where I
could no longer go on.
However, my heart remains
joyous and full of curiosity.
This feeling. Yes, it reminds
me of that moment.
That fateful day, when Dr. Arima
handed it over to me.
I still remember as if
it were yesterday.
The moment I first held that
strange, foreign object.
[MITSUKI] "The wondrous thing
I couldn't let go of...
Which I later decided to call
the Reflector Device."
Uh. Oh great.
[MITSUKI]
The Reflector Device.
You have it, don't you, Takuya?
Uh. What're you talking about?
[laughs] Yep!
Hand it over, right now.
That's Ryuzoji's gun!
So? Give it here, chop chop.
[TAKUYA grunts]
Takuya. Be a good boy.
I can't.
My dad entrusted
the device to me.
Sure.
Well, then, you
leave me no choice.
[TAKUYA gasps]
[gunshot]
Next time, I'll be
aiming for your head.
Now, give me the Reflector
Device immediately.
[groans]
Run, Takuya.
What's happening?
Is it the Niarb?
[MITSUKI]
Takuya, I have to shoot you.
But... I... I don't want to.
I don't want to but I must!
Listen to me! Ryuzoji's
controlling you right now!
You need to get
ahold of yourself!
If he wants it,
I'll get it for him.
That's my job. I'm afraid
your time's up. Bye!
[TAKUYA grunting]
You're not getting
away from me.
[TAKUYA panting]
Yes!
[TAKUYA]
What's that?
A coffin?
[MITSUKI]
Takuya!
Where're you hiding, sweetie?
Son of a bitch!
Playing hide-and-seek?
Well, well. Don't worry, I won't
keep you waiting for very long.
[TAKUYA screams]
[gasps]
That light! What is it?
[MITSUKI grunts]
[footsteps]
[MIO]
Hey, wake up!
I don't, uh...
[MIO]
Takuya!
Please, just five more minutes?
I'm really wiped out. Okay?
Good grief, would you
please just wake up?
[TAKUYA grunts]
Hey, don't, that hurt!
[gasping]
[MIO screams]
[smack]
[TAKUYA]
Ow! Was that necessary?
You're impossible!
I'm really glad you're
safe, though, Mio.
'Course, I had a feeling
a history nut like you
would be harder
to kill than that.
Wow, quite a compliment.
Forget about that--
did you get hurt?
[MIO]
Heh. I'm good.
Although my butt's a
little cold right now.
Nice! Anything I can do
to warm it up for ya?
[MIO]
No thanks, you pervert.
I thought I was a
goner at one point.
But somehow I knew
that, eventually,
you'd make your
way down here, too.
Sorry that it kinda
took me a while.
[TAKUYA] Anyway, wow.
This place is weird.
A glowing, underground lake?
From here, it looks like
the glow is coming
from the rocks that
are under the water.
Rocks that glow...?
It's the psychite.
What'd you say?
Nothing. Let's get out of here.
Surely we can manage that.
[MIO] I'm not even sure
where I should begin.
Generally speaking,
I start with mild flirtation.
I was always convinced that
the Takanoamahara people
just had to be related to
Mount Sankaku in some way.
But you can't deny the fact is,
these ruins are a lot
older than that.
That's right.
So, I want to do a
real investigation.
Solve the mysteries.
All of them.
I don't just mean Japan's,
but the mysteries
of all of humanity.
[TAKUYA]
You know,
Dr. Imagawa's notes said
the same thing you just did.
You read them, right?
[MIO]
Yes. I found them in the cave.
To me, her theory about
event collisions was
especially shocking.
The part where she said
that one dimension
might collide with another...
I know. Do you believe it
could be a valid theory?
I have to admit, it is
pretty hard to believe.
However, if it is the truth,
it would explain why there's
an entire civilization here
that's not found in our history.
[rumbling]
[gasps]
There's that sound again.
[TAKUYA gasps]
Watch out!
[gasps]
Mio!
[TAKUYA]
Grab on.
Come on, guys. Get back safe.
[TAKUYA]
Doin' okay?
[MIO]
Uh? Don't stare! Look away!
Maybe I should go
look for the exit.
Seems like a solid idea.
[MIO] Uh! Hold on!
Don't just leave me here.
But...
Trust me, okay?
You won't find an exit.
I've obviously already
looked for it everywhere.
Please, just...
Don't leave me here alone.
[MIO]
The papers this morning.
[TAKUYA]
Hm?
On the bulletin board.
You weren't responsible
for that, right?
Sorry. Yes, I did it.
[MIO laughs]
What's funny?
I guess somehow I knew
you'd take the blame.
It was Yuki, wasn't it?
[TAKUYA] Uh! No way! Wh-Why,
did he tell you that he did it?
[MIO]
Mm-mm.
No, I could just read him.
When we talked about it.
He's, uh...
He's a really bad liar.
Before I came down here,
I actually hit the kid.
I'm not saying it's a
reason to forgive him.
But try not to blame
him too much.
[laughs] Guess that's
a lot to ask.
It's not.
I mean, I was hurt
when I saw them,
but everything those
papers said was true.
People would've found out.
If not from the papers,
then some other way.
Besides, I believe my father
deserves to be punished
for the things he's done.
[coughs]
Hey, you okay?
Tell me something.
Do you think we'll die here?
Uh. No, of course I don't.
Yuki's waiting for us up there.
I think he'll go
to the police. Uh?
[MIO]
Arima.
Will you... kiss me?
[MIO]
Please, I...
I want something else
to remember when I die!
One time?
[gasps]
This isn't your last memory,
because we're both
getting out of here alive.
Do you hear me? Alive.
[TAKUYA]
Should I head back now? Crap.
I don't remember the path
I took to get here,
and I don't know if
I'll see Mio again.
I'll rest up for a little bit,
then I'll get outta here.
[KEIKO]
Takuya.
Takuya. Don't worry.
[TAKUYA gasps]
[KEIKO]
I'm here.
I'm right here beside you now.
[TAKUYA]
Mother?
[YU-NO] Episode eleven:
"That Kiss, Once More."