[STUDENTS chattering]
[MALE STUDENT A] So the rumor
was true? That's nuts!
[chattering continues]
[ERIKO] We can assume
there's some reason
she needs to stay
near Mount Sankaku,
and that it's most
likely related
to whatever reason she had
to keep transferring schools.
[gasps]
That's why I asked you to
make sure that she was okay.
You've picked up on it,
haven't you?
The fact that her secret
is deeply connected
with your parents.
There's no way
you don't feel it.
[gasps]
[ERIKO]
Kanna went home, you know.
I think you get what you
have to do now, right?
Yeah.
Did you see what
was on the board?
That's crazy.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I heard she's gonna
be transferring soon.
[MALE STUDENT C]
So she's expelled?
That can't be...
Is it me or is this
getting outta control?
Uh? Where's Arima?
That's a good question.
I can't imagine where
he'd need to go right now.
[doorbell rings]
[TAKUYA]
Kanna! Are you in there?
Kanna?
[rattling]
Well, what do you want?
You were the one I saw on
the beach when I was a kid.
I know it was you.
[TAKUYA] You haven't aged
a bit in 50 years.
That's why you keep
transferring schools
around Sakaimachi.
So no one will suspect your age.
Tell me I'm wrong.
[KANNA]
So, is that it?
[gasps]
Is that all you want to ask?
That clears it up for you?
I do want to know more
about you than your past.
A whole lot more.
I want to know everything
there is to know.
When I'm with you, it's like...
It's hard to explain,
but it's like I'm with family.
Kinda weird, right?
With family? Really?
Just tell me what you can.
Don't say anything
you don't want to.
All I'm hoping for... is to
know you, and how you feel.
[KANNA]
Once, there was a young girl.
A girl without a father.
She lived alone with her mother,
whom she loved more
than anything.
[KANNA] Her mother was
more like a sister to her.
She was her best friend.
But the trouble was,
the two of them couldn't stay
in one place for very long.
They simply didn't age
the way normal people did.
So, as the years passed by,
both of their appearances
remained the same.
[KANNA] Eventually,
her mother passed away.
The girl cried and cried,
and she cried some more.
She knew she couldn't bear
to go to an orphanage,
so she decided to live
on her own from then on.
She soon learned how hard
it was to survive alone,
but she also made a discovery.
Somewhere along the way,
she'd become a woman,
and she craved human connection.
But soon it was clear:
that was easier done with
bodies than with minds.
So she sought it out.
That connection she thought
would numb the pain.
She felt pathetic and
worthless all the time.
Poor fool. She couldn't
forgive herself.
So many times, she thought
about leaving all this behind
to be with her mother.
But right before she died,
her mother had said
something to her.
"As long as you don't
die, there is hope.
And as long as there is hope,
there is possibility.
As long as there is possibility,
you must promise to
continue to live."
So she did as she was told.
She did her best to survive,
even though all she
wanted to do was go.
One fateful day, she met a man.
A friendly man,
who laughed and smiled at her.
And the quiet, elegant
woman by his side.
The two were like
husband and wife.
And their home was full
of kindness and warmth.
They told her they'd
take her in.
And they gave her love and
affection, like true parents.
Heh. So the old bastard
did one thing right.
[KANNA] But neither
of them are here now.
Because of that, the girl
was left on her own again.
There was really nothing
left for her to do now,
except maybe sit around feeling
sorry for her pathetic self.
[TAKUYA]
No! That's not true!
What about me and
Yuki and Mio, huh?
We're your friends
and we're right here!
You are never alone!
Look, you don't
have to say that.
I know how you must
look down on me now.
What? That's ridiculous!
[KANNA]
Okay, then.
[TAKUYA gasps]
[KANNA] Can you look at me
like this without judgement?
Can you hold me in your arms?
[phone rings]
[KANNA, TAKUYA gasp]
[ringing continues]
[KANNA]
Yes?
[HOJO] I made it so you couldn't
go to school anymore.
Now I'm thinkin' maybe
I'll kill Kodai Arima's son,
how 'bout that?
Get yourself to Meiunji
Park at 9 PM
and I'll meet you
next to the fountain.
Just remember,
you can't escape me.
[TAKUYA]
Was that Hojo?
Leave me alone, please.
I'm not doing that!
I need you to leave.
I can't stay here
with you, okay?
[YUKI] Yo, Boss, you left
this behind earlier!
Oh, sorry. See ya.
Hey, you just got to see
Kanna, didn't you?
So? Is it all true?
Is she really leaving school?
She seems pretty
set on it, yeah.
She also said she's moving.
Man, right when we finally
got to know her.
Wait, she told you all of
this and then you just left?
She said she couldn't
stay with me.
She actually said those words.
There's nothin'
left for me to do.
[exhales]
[MIO] That's not like
you at all, Arima.
[TAKUYA gasps]
I've never known you
to give up so easily.
Don't say that, you don't
even know what's going on!
It's complicated.
True. I don't know a thing.
That's totally fair.
But I didn't think you'd ever
walk away from a friend
when they needed you most.
When we were all at the beach,
I don't think I'll ever be
able to forget that day.
I didn't know Kanna was even
capable of smiling like that.
I don't know what's
going on with her,
but I do know one thing.
She didn't need you to
leave her alone today.
She was just protecting herself.
Sometimes, when people
really care about you,
they push you away deliberately.
I hear ya Mio. Thanks.
Shimazu...
[MIO]
I'm so sorry Yuki.
Just give me a few
minutes alone, okay?
[door opens]
[footsteps]
Kanna!
[gasps]
[footsteps]
[TAKUYA panting]
[ERIKO]
I'm sorry she's leaving, too.
But there's nothing we can do.
It's her decision.
I know that, but...
It's just that...
Hatano is a real friend.
We haven't known
each other very long,
but she already
means a lot to me.
I don't know what's going on
with her, but I want to help.
I know she'd do the same for me,
and I'm also worried
about that weird guy.
Wait, what weird guy?
You didn't know?
Hatano has an actual stalker.
[TAKUYA panting]
[TAKUYA]
Where is she?
[HOJO]
Cut the crap, little girl!
[gasps]
[HOJO]
Now. Where is Kodai Arima?
Tell me! Tell me!
[TAKUYA]
Stop it!
Old man, get your
hands off her, now!
Arima! Don't!
Stay away!
I'm all right! Please!
Get out of here, okay?
[HOJO]
Shut up!
[KANNA groans]
Bastard!
[HOJO groaning]
My head!
[groans]
[screams]
Whoa, him, too?
[HOJO laughing]
This is perfect.
I can carve you up right
here in front of her, now,
won't that be fun?
[KANNA]
Please! Stop this!
I'll do it.
I'll tell you what you want.
[HOJO gasping]
Regarding Kodai Arima.
No, don't do it, Kanna, please!
He's... He's no longer
in this world.
[TAKUYA, HOJO gasp]
He left and went to
a different place.
It's a separate
dimension from this one.
[KODAI] By now, you've heard
of Dela Granto, haven't you?
[KANNA] It's where my mother's
from, isn't that right?
Dela Granto exists in an
entirely different universe.
However, once every 400 years,
when it approaches Sakai-machi,
there's always a
small group of people
who cross over
into this dimension.
So, wait, are you saying
my mother and Keiko...
Yes.
Keiko is...
No.
I should call her
by her true name.
Keitia... is gone.
"I must go on a journey
for the next me."
That's what she said
before she left.
I remember it perfectly.
What is that?
[KODAI]
She left this here for me.
She must've brought it
from Dela Granto.
It's not anything that
could've originated
from this world, that's certain.
[KODAI]
History does not repeat itself,
because history
only flows one way.
But the flow of time
is different.
Keitia was the one who
made me certain of this.
That's why I've decided...
I'm going to see her.
I'm going as a historian.
And I'm going as a man.
[TAKUYA]
So, what you're saying is
the real reason my dad left
was 'cause he wanted
to follow my mom?
That's right.
[HOJO laughing]
Seriously? Give me a break!
Ugh! Do you really expect
me to believe that?
Stop it, it's the truth!
What did you want to hear?
I thought you would
at least come up
with a better lie than that!
You'd better start telling
the truth, girl,
or you're gonna regret it!
Get your hands off her,
you perv!
[HOJO groans]
Did he hurt you? You okay?
[KANNA]
Arima, why?
I don't understand.
I'll never be able to fully
understand your pain, Kanna.
But you're alive.
You've survived and you're here.
[KANNA]
Yes, I'm alive, nothing more.
I have no dignity as a person.
What point is there
in going on living, now?
Look, your perspective is messed
up because you've been hurt.
No, but the things I did...
[TAKUYA] You survived,
and you're not alone!
Don't give up, we're right here!
I promise, we aren't
going anywhere!
I don't think you realize
how much Mio and Yuki
care about you.
And you're dear to me.
I mean, just in case there
was any question about that.
I want you to live with me.
[gasps]
[HOJO groans]
[KANNA gasps]
You stay back!
[yells]
[TAKUYA grunts]
Arima don't do this!
Yeah, this looks dangerous.
[HOJO laughs]
[HOJO yelling]
Arima, look out!
[HOJO grunts]
[yelling]
[HOJO groans]
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
[HOJO groaning]
[groans]
[TAKUYA]
Eriko? What the...?
Hey, sorry I got here so late.
But what are you doing here?
And what're you wearing?
[ERIKO]
Grow up.
Actually, I've been keeping
tabs on this one for a while.
Though I'm a lot more
interested in his employer.
What do you mean, his employer?
That bastard, Ryuzoji?
[ERIKO] He was most likely
being controlled by the Niarb.
Shimazu had just come
to me about Hatano.
She was incredibly concerned,
so I decided to check it out.
Wait a minute.
Mio talked to you?
[ERIKO] I'll deal with this
one if that's all right.
I've got questions.
[TAKUYA]
Eriko...
[ERIKO]
Take care of Hatano, okay?
[thud]
Uh! Kanna!
Please, try to find my pendant.
Yeah, of course!
[TAKUYA]
Got it!
Here.
[gasping]
What's...
What's happening?
The light!
No.
A--
Arima.
Kanna, no!
You have to wake up, okay?
You have to!
[TAKUYA]
It's because of this thing.
So, then, if I go back
before it broke...
[HOJO groaning]
I can't.
Going back won't change a thing.
It'll just keep happening.
[footsteps]
This is really bad--
her fever is worse.
Hey, Kanna,
what is that pendant?
It's quite literally
the flame of my life.
The center is made of psychite.
What Geotech wanted?
The psychite?
You're talking about the stuff
under Sakaimachi, right?
They said they hadn't succeeded
in crystallizing it yet.
Remember, this is a
different dimension.
The only place where the
stone naturally exists
is in Dela Granto.
I didn't know it was only there.
It's true.
It can't be crystallized here,
doesn't work in this world.
[TAKUYA gasping]
I'm really sorry.
I...
I think it's over.
Don't say that!
I finally found true friends.
You told me I'm not alone
and wanted to live with me.
[TAKUYA]
I'll get you some psychite!
[KANNA exhales]
I promise you!
I'll have to go get it
from another dimension!
Wait for me!
You just keep holding on!
[KANNA]
I guess it's finally time.
Kodai gave me one last message
to pass along to you.
So I'll tell you now.
[TAKUYA panting]
[KANNA]
To go to Dela Granto
you'll need eight
jewels in total.
The last jewel is in his study,
and it shouldn't be
too hard to find.
It's inside the
grandfather clock.
[KANNA] Once you've
collected all of the jewels,
go to the caves under
Mount Sankaku.
[KANNA]
The burial chamber, in the back.
[TAKUYA panting]
Here we go, Kanna.
It's time for this to end.
You're gonna be okay!
[TAKUYA grunting]
[KODAI] You who bear
the seal of the king.
When light and shadow,
heavenly being and devil
combine together,
the name of the king will
suddenly appear above thy head.
Speak it!
Speak the name of the king!
The name is...
[inaudible]
[YU-NO] Episode 18:
"Twilight in Dela Granto."