[yelling]
No, wait!
[TAKUYA]
Yu-No. What's happened to you?
I'll kill anyone who
defies the Emperor!
[gasps]
What're you doing?
[TAKUYA]
Get down!
[YU-NO yelps]
[GUARD A] We won't tell
you assholes anything.
Might as well give it up!
[ASCHE]
Is that so?
Well, maybe I'll just start
carving you up, piece by piece,
until you change your mind.
Your ears, your eyelids,
then your lips.
[whimpering]
[KURTZ]
I'm glad you're safe Boss!
[DEO]
That was crazy.
I wasn't expecting her
to be there, were you?
[TAKUYA] The girl in
the mask was my daughter.
Huh...?
Hold on, you have a daughter
who wants to kill you?
Is it possible it's just
a rebellious phase?
[TAKUYA]
I don't know why or how,
but Yu-No's completely
forgotten about me.
Still...
You know what I think?
I believe that her memory
loss is only temporary.
So if it comes back...
I'm sorry.
Do you even realize
how many of our men
the masked woman
has already killed?
I'm sorry, but I'm asking
you to leave her to me.
[TAKUYA] What's this,
an underground tunnel?
Yeah, it's kinda creepy.
[TAKUYA] The event element
measurement device.
[DEO]
The longer we take,
the more likely we
are to be discovered.
Yeah, you're right!
Let's get going!
[TAKUYA]
What is this place?
[KURTZ]
Careful, that looks dangerous!
Who is that?
Another prisoner?
Hey, you okay?
It's been a long time, Takuya.
[gasping]
[TAKUYA]
Ryuzoji!
Wait, do you know this guy?
Quick then,
let's get him free.
No, don't.
I thought you knew him?
Tell me, why did you
let them catch you?
You don't even have a body.
You could escape this!
Heh. Well, the story is
the Divine Emperor
outsmarted me.
I never would've expected
her to work with Mother
and prepare a divine
device to seal me.
C'mon, let's go.
You're looking for the
priestess, isn't that right?
What was your darling
daughter's name again?
Ah, yes. Yu-No.
I think that was it.
[TAKUYA]
Where is she? Tell me!
What happens when you find out?
What are you planning
to do then?
Don't tell me you're
actually thinking of saving
the daughter who attempted
to take your life!
[growls]
Who is this?
That's a really good question.
[ASCHE grunting]
It's no good.
This goes way beyond
my lock-picking skills.
[AMANDA]
Well, then.
Something important
must be in there.
[SALA]
Oh? Is that you, Amanda?
[AMANDA]
Sala!
[ASCHE]
Well isn't this convenient.
Been a long time!
[TAKUYA]
Tell me! Where is Yu-No?
I can only tell you one thing.
In order to allow the god
entrance into her body,
it's necessary for a
priestess to offer up
one of her body's functions.
Your mother. Keitia.
She offered sight as her
sacrifice and became blind.
So my mom was a priestess?
[RYUZOJI]
Your wife, Sayless,
decided to choose words
as her sacrifice.
So, of course,
she could never speak.
And as for your daughter, Yu-No,
she chose to offer her heart,
which meant that she
lost all her memories.
That's why...
[RYUZOJI] But there's still
a way to get her heart back
if that's what you want.
[gasps]
If you help me now, break
this barrier and set me free,
I'll tell you anything
you'd like to know.
[TAKUYA]
You know I can't do that!
I was under the impression you
wanted to save your daughter.
Your beloved Yu-No.
[ERIKO]
Ryuzoji!
Nice of you to drop in.
How nice, this is like
a little reunion.
I've finally found you.
Where did the hot
lady come from?
Takuya, is this another person
you knew from before?
You could say that.
So, I'm guessing this must be
a pretty enormous weight
off your shoulders, huh?
Yes. Thanks for all your help.
You two are so naive it's
almost embarrassing.
You have no clue
what he really wants.
[DEO]
Just ignore him.
Doesn't this seem strange
to you, though?
He defiled the last priestess,
and now his daughter
is the new priestess.
[gasps]
That's just the beginning.
Isn't it also a little curious
that he knows me?
And that he also knows
that strange woman
who appeared out of nowhere.
Wow, did you get tired of
the skin-tight mini-skirt?
Not that this doesn't work.
[ERIKO]
What do you mean?
This happens to be the
official uniform for my job,
thank you very much.
[DEO yells]
Stop!
[DEO grunts]
Niarb! Ryuzoji!
[grunts]
[TAKUYA]
The barrier!
[laughs] Looks like it's
now time for me to go.
[TAKUYA]
Wait! Ryuzoji!
He's going to try to get
back to the imperial city.
All he ever wants to do
is create more chaos.
But don't worry.
I'll catch him before that.
[ASCHE]
You sure about this, Sala?
You're a maid here
in the city now, right?
[SALA]
Don't worry, it's fine.
Honestly, if you're here, I
figure that must mean the castle
is pretty much done for, anyway.
[ASCHE whistles]
[SALA] I've already had my
share of fun with the guards.
[AMANDA]
You what?
Sorry. You didn't
need to know that.
Bye-bye, now! See ya around!
[SALA humming]
[sighs] She's just
the same as ever.
[sighs] Now my head's throbbing
like nobody's business.
Yeah, I feel like I've got
the worst hangover of my life.
[TAKUYA] And of course, the
room where they're keeping
the priestess is super
heavily guarded.
How the heck are we
gonna get through?
Hey, Boss, leave it to us!
Yeah, we kinda need to pay
you back for our screw-up.
[KURTZ]
Intruders!
[DEO]
Intruders inside the castle!
[GUARD B]
What?
[KURTZ] Quick! We must
protect the Divine Emperor!
--[GUARD B] Ugh, C'mon!
--[GUARD C] Damn it!
Very nice job, you guys.
[gasps]
Who are you?
It's me. Yu-No.
It's your father.
Stop it!
Liar!
[TAKUYA gasping]
[YU-NO] I don't want to
see that stupid cloth!
Please, Sayless!
[screams]
Sayless. I know you're
inside there, aren't you?
You have to tell her, too!
Uh! Stop talking!
Help, Sayless!
Tell her that we're family!
[YU-NO gasps]
No!
[coughing]
Yu-No! Remember!
Come back to me!
[yelling]
[TAKUYA grunts]
[gasps]
Yu-No, you are my
precious daughter.
The one I love most.
Your mom and I are here for you.
[gasps]
Momma.
Yu-No, you remember now?
Papa?
That's right!
I'm your Papa, sweetheart!
Papa!
It's really you!
I missed you so much!
Yeah. Me, too!
I was afraid that we'd lost you!
[DEO]
Hey, Amanda!
[KURTZ]
We're back!
This room is enormous.
The hell is this even
supposed to be?
[footsteps]
[AI] Hello! Welcome to
the hall of memories!
[ASCHE growls]
[ALL gasp]
[AI giggles]
[TAKUYA]
I want you to stay here, okay?
But why?
If the priestess disappears,
there'll be a big uproar.
[YU-NO]
I see. What'll you do?
I have to go.
There's still something I
still need to take care of.
I'll come back when it's over.
[yelling]
[EMPEROR]
I've been waiting.
[TAKUYA gasping]
[EMPEROR]
And here you are.
Hello, Takuya.
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi?
[AYUMI] Takuya. About what
happened to Sayless...
I am so sorry.
[TAKUYA]
What for?
[AYUMI] I took the life
of the person you loved.
Yeah, but I need you to know I
realize that wasn't your fault.
[AYUMI] Anything my men did
is my responsibility.
[TAKUYA]
You haven't changed.
Huh?
You think so?
This is for you.
The Reflector Device!
[AYUMI] I kept it safe because
I knew you'd come for it,
and here you are.
Thank you.
But I still can't believe this.
That you're the Divine Emperor.
That's quite a long story.
[AYUMI] That day, when I
was struck by lightning
on Mount Sankaku, I somehow
ended up in Dela Granto.
I was saved by Ryuzoji,
who, by that point,
was no longer even human.
Under his supervision,
I officially took control
of Grand Mother.
Over the long years,
the people of Dela Granto
had unfortunately
lost the ability
to control the Unified Computer.
I tried to find every
piece of information
I could from Mother.
That's how I eventually learned
that Ryuzoji was planning
to rule over this country
using Mother's power.
Grand Mother seemed to
become more and more afraid
of Ryuzoji, so she chose me
as the one to defeat him.
With her help,
I was able to create a device
that could seal creatures
with no bodies, like Ryuzoji,
and we locked him
below the city.
That's when I chose to become
the Divine Emperor myself.
The lucky thing was,
Mother's will was respected
like some kind of god.
So the transition
didn't take long at all.
It's been so long since
we've had any guests!
How exciting!
Does anyone wanna tell me what
a little kid's doin' down here?
Hey, kiddo.
Maybe we should get you
someplace a little safer.
--[DEO yelps]
--What is she?
[AI] I wish you didn't look
quite so angry, Amanda.
[gasps] How do you know my name?
And Kurtz, and Deo,
and Asche, too, and Bobby!
Come on! Everybody, let's smile!
[giggles]
Oh, great, she knows
about us, too?
This is not some ordinary kid.
I'm not! I'm Ai, the A.I.
and I tell everybody old
stories about Dela Granto!
Hey! I bet you wanna hear
one of my stories now!
Don't you?
[AYUMI]
When I became Divine Emperor,
I learned the relationship
between Earth and Dela Granto.
It was thousands,
maybe millions, no...
Tens of millions of years
ago, on the planet Earth,
there lived a
civilization that was
incredibly advanced,
scientifically.
[GROUP gasps]
The people who are living
now have a term for them.
They are known as
the Earth Precursors.
But then, one day, their
civilization suddenly became
exposed to a tremendous
danger. The scientists...
[AI] ...all predicted that
big meteors would fall
all over the planet and
that everyone would die!
And those meteors...
...had a name of their own.
"The Tears of God."
So, you're saying the race
that ruled the earth was
destroyed by meteors.
Sounds like the dinosaurs.
[AYUMI] Their scientific
abilities had reached the point
where even the will of god
had no effect on them.
And in the face of
their destruction...
...they developed the most
incredible technology
that there ever was!
Check it out!
[ALL gasp]
[AI] Isn't it amazing?
They'd move this huge island
to a whole different dimension
where it would be safe!
And so, that was the birth of
Dela Granto, as we know it.
[TAKUYA chuckles] So the whole
neighborhood up and moved, huh?
Basically! Yes, they did.
And the leader of that move
was the prominent
female scientist, Grantia.
[TAKUYA]
A scientist? Not a politician?
[AYUMI] Yes. Massive amounts
of new technology
was necessary to allow humans
to live in another dimension.
For example, they needed
artificial plants...
...to provide an oxygen supply.
And a heavy fusion reactor,
the artificial sun, Melgio.
You know all those
pretty well, right?
But the environment in
this other dimension
was too different. So, sadly,
everybody started to die.
Humans dropped down to 10%
of their former population,
poor things!
So they tried something else.
They modified the living
beings themselves
to give them the power to adapt
to the new environment.
[TAKUYA]
They altered living beings?
[AYUMI]
Correct.
Didn't you ever notice anything
particularly strange
about the various
creatures in this world?
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Of course.
That's why Yu-No grew up
as fast as she did, right?
[AYUMI] That was another
result of her adaptation
to the environment.
Her time as an adult
was increased so she'd
be more productive.
Wow, fascinating.
[AYUMI] But, and this
is terrible to say...
A lot of the
modification attempts
ended up being failures.
[AMANDA]
No! Then these monsters...
She's saying they used to
be human, just like us!
[AI]
But at the same time,
they became unable to survive
on the floating continent
without a certain
essential energy ore.
And the name of that ore was...
[BOTH]
...it was psychite.
The same thing that I had
been researching at Geotech.
[TAKUYA] It was also the
stone that Kanna needed.
The one I came to Dela Granto
for in the first place.
But then, just when they'd
solved that problem,
they realized that
their calculations
for Dela Granto's
orbit were off!
[GRANTIA] According to the
orbital calculations I've done,
our dimensional floating
continent and Earth
have continually
approached and separated
from each other over time.
And all of this occurred
over a 400-year cycle.
Are you serious?
Then my dad's 400
Year Cycle Theory...
[AYUMI]
As it turns out, he was right.
Also, only the leader of the
scientists Grantia was able
to control the enormous,
floating continent. But...
I'm aware, there is
no way to escape
from the end of
my natural lifespan.
So, I have developed technology
that will allow my mind
to live on as data
and therefore control the
continent even after my death.
Unfortunately, it has
one undeniable flaw.
It requires a specific catalyst.
Someone with whom
I can synchronize.
The catalyst needed
is a human female.
You mean the priestess?
[AYUMI] Yes. Grantia's scan
program would select her.
She would be required to lose
one of her body's functions
in order to make it
easier to synchronize.
So, my mom served
as the catalyst,
and then Sayless,
and now it's Yu-No's turn.
Takuya. The Earth
and Dela Granto
are about to be at their
point of maximum approach.
[AI] If Earth and Dela
Granto get too close,
then it's Ka-boom! Big trouble.
[ALL grunt]
So we're gonna die?
What can we do?
You just need to do the ritual.
The priestess needs to
synchronize with Grantia
and avoid the collision!
If that happens...
...then both worlds
will be saved.
However, nothing good
ever comes without a price.
I'm so sorry, Takuya, this is
very difficult to tell you,
but even if the ritual succeeds,
the priestess, Yu-No,
will most likely be annihilated.
[gasps]
Thank you, that concludes
my presentation.
So what did you think?
Pretty interesting stuff, huh?
So, that means the ritual
we all thought was a lie...
The priestess, and the Divine
Emperor's involvement...
It's real. This proves
that all of it was true.
We came here with
one major goal,
which was to stop
that ritual. But now...
[AI] If that happens, I think
you'll have a big problem.
[DEO]
Amanda.
[crash]
[GROUP gasps]
[AMANDA gasps]
[grunts]
[YU-NO] Episode 25:
"The Promised Ritual."