[TAKUYA]
Dad?
[KODAI] Oh. You came
to save Kanna, did you?
Pretty impressive, for you.
The truth of the matter is,
without psychite,
Kanna won't survive.
Keiko was exactly the same.
[TAKUYA]
Where is mom now?
Don't worry.
Keiko is here with me.
In a world that's known, in the
realm of philosophy, as "Idea."
[TAKUYA]
I'm coming after you, Dad.
Just stay there and wait for me.
[KODAI]
Yes, it's time, I think.
Although time as we know it
doesn't actually mean
anything at all.
Which is a lesson you're
about to learn very well.
[TAKUYA]
So, this is Dela Granto?
Huh...
Wonder if those are edible?
[TAKUYA grunting]
If my dad wanted me
to play survivalist,
the least he could've done was
give me a little heads-up
or something!
[MACHINE A]
Check.
Activating hall.
[MACHINE A]
Check.
Forced teleport.
[TAKUYA]
It's been years since I've spent
so much time in the woods.
[TAKUYA whistles]
[rustling]
Shoot, if I use this, I won't
be able to get back to Kanna.
[yells]
[screams]
[sighs]
[TAKUYA panting]
What the hell is this place?
[SAYLESS screams]
[SAYLESS]
Help me!
[TAKUYA]
Who's there?
[SAYLESS]
No!
Stay away!
[BAT MONSTER grunting]
[TAKUYA]
U-Uh!
What the hell is that?
Oh, no.
U-Uh!
[grunting]
[TAKUYA]
Hey, you!
[yelling]
[BAT MONSTER grunting]
[sighs] Good thing it was
weaker than it looked, huh?
You okay?
Mind if I ask your name?
Where did you come from?
[gasps]
Wait a minute,
can you not speak?
That's odd.
Could've sworn I heard a girl's
voice calling out before.
[SAYLESS sighs]
Ha, ha! Not sure what to do,
but you know,
you're pretty much my only hope
in this world, so, here we go!
My name's Takuya.
Ta-ku-ya.
And I promise I'm not scary.
See? Look!
[SAYLESS laughs]
Ha, ha! Good, a laugh!
[gasps]
Why don't you tell me
if your name starts with
any of these letters, okay?
A... That's I, U, E, O?
How 'bout...
Ka, Ki, Ku, Ke, Ko?
Welp, looks like this
is gonna take a while.
[TAKUYA] All right, what we know
is, your name is Sayless.
And you don't know
where you're from,
or anything about Sakaimachi
or psychite. Right?
So now there are two lost
people instead of one, I guess.
[laughs]
A desert?
[TAKUYA]
Mm! What is it?
That way?
[TAKUYA]
A house?
Maybe there's someone there!
Let's go see.
[TAKUYA]
Hello? Is anyone home?
Excuse me, is anybody here?
[TAKUYA]
Uh.
Hey, Sayless.
Would you say this room
is pretty typical?
Wow, interesting.
So, I guess this
world's civilization
isn't all that
primitive, after all.
[SAYLESS]
Watch out!
Drop your weapon.
Who are you? And don't lie.
Honestly, I wish I knew
who I was in this world.
Let me know if you
figure it out.
Are you from the city?
You're asking if I
came from there?
Is it Sakaimachi?
[AILIA]
Hm...
Take off your clothes.
Aren't you even gonna
buy me dinner first?
Disarm, immediately.
[TAKUYA]
Heh. Ah, very perceptive.
You noticed my Magnum, huh?
Magnum? You're toying
with me! Do it, now.
[AILIA groans]
Holy crap! Are you okay?
[gasps]
Oh. Hey.
What the--?
What did you do to me?!
[TAKUYA]
Hardly anything, really.
I mean, you peed yourself,
so I took care of that,
but nothing else.
Uh! Sorry, I wasn't serious!
Sayless handled
everything, not me!
[footsteps]
[AILIA] I'm sorry for pointing
my sword at you like that.
My name is Ailia,
and I'm a knight.
I guard our border at the
request of the Divine Emperor.
[TAKUYA]
The border?
[AILIA] Yes, the boundary
that separates Dela Granto
from the rest of the world.
I'm tasked with defeating
the monsters
that tend to show up here.
Wow. Sounds like being
a border guard is intense.
Yes, it certainly can be.
[coughing]
[AILIA]
Takuya, why did you come here?
[TAKUYA] Well, my only goal
is to find psychite.
Have you heard of it?
Sorry, I'm afraid I haven't.
What is it for?
Is it a jewel to give
to that girl?
No, nothing like that.
The stone's going
to another person.
[BAT MONSTER squawks]
--[TAKUYA] Uh!
--[AILIA grunts]
[BAT MONSTER screeches]
[AILIA] The monsters
have grown in number
and gotten more violent
with each passing day.
Mother nature. She shows
her wrath every 400 years.
Four hundred years again, huh?
That number comes up a lot.
[AILIA]
The wrath of Mother Nature
shows the people of
Dela Granto no mercy.
Great rains. Floods.
Earthquakes.
Lands turned to desert.
[TAKUYA] Natural disasters
can't be helped, though.
[AILIA]
There is a way.
In five years, a ritual will
be done to purify this world,
and at that point,
a god shall manifest.
A god?
[AILIA] In order for a priestess
to become the vessel of the god
she must sacrifice
her physical abilities
in exchange for divine power.
For instance, some lose
the ability to walk.
Others, their voice.
[gasps] Wait a minute.
Do you mean Sayless?
Yes, I had that thought,
as well.
But the thing is, if she
really is a priestess,
how'd she get here from
the Imperial City?
Guess she must've
crossed the desert.
[AILIA] Crossing the
Rafaelo Desert under
Melgio's hateful
gaze is impossible.
Completely impossible.
Honey, I'm home!
Wow, looks like you
really know how to cook!
Wonderful! Shall we eat, then?
I am so ready for this!
[ADVISOR]
The Priestess is gone?
[GUARD A] We've confirmed
she was on the dais
as of this morning.
[ADVISOR] Divine Emperor, what
would you like for us to do?
[EMPEROR] The royal guards must
form a team to track her down.
I shall consult
the will of Mother.
[ADVISOR, GUARD A]
Yes, sir!
[yelling]
[AILIA]
This "kendo" of yours
isn't meant for real
combat, is it?
Look, I've never held
a real sword before!
[AILIA] Never let your guard
down in Dela Granto.
All the knights on the
border except me have died.
It is deceptively dangerous.
[TAKUYA] What lies out there,
beyond the desert?
[AILIA] The Imperial City,
and on the way, the quarries.
What the heck are the quarries?
I don't have details.
But I know that's where
they mine the holy stones.
And are these holy stones
different from psychite?
I don't know. I'm sorry.
[TAKUYA] No, I get it. You can't
cross the desert, right?
[AILIA]
Yes.
[grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[growls]
What the...?
I'll handle this.
[HARPY A growls]
[gasps]
[HARPY B growls]
[AILIA gasps]
[growling]
[TAKUYA grunting]
[screams]
[TAKUYA yells]
[HARPY B growling]
[TAKUYA panting]
You're not hurt or
anything, are you?
No, and just after I told you
not to let your guard down, too.
[TAKUYA] What happened?
That's not like you.
I don't know. I had this
memory of my little sister.
Your sister?
[AILIA] Amanda. She's the
only family I have left.
She was different from me
in every way imaginable.
She ran away from home.
I have no idea what
she could be doing now.
[coughing]
Ailia! I knew it, you're sick!
Yes, but fighting
against it won't help.
This disease that
eats away at me...
It's my fate.
We'll go to the forest later.
Okay.
Is there something on my face?
No way, you're just
as pretty as always.
I'll be back later.
Hey, what's up?
So, you're going over there
to pick some flowers?
It's dangerous.
--Let me go with you.
--[splashing]
I got one! Wow! It's a fighter!
Holy crap, it's a big one!
Are you seeing this?
[TAKUYA grunting]
Sayless, wait, wait, no!
Hold up!
[TAKUYA] Who's the greatest
fisherman ever?
It's me, obviously!
[APE MONSTER roars]
[TAKUYA]
Sayless! Behind you!
[roars]
You get away from her!
[APE MONSTER roars]
Sayless, run to Takuya, now.
[AILIA yelling]
[roars]
[AILIA gasps]
Ailia!
Are you okay?
[panting]
You saw this, didn't you?
You already knew.
You knew that this was
the day I would die.
[AILIA coughs, groans]
Ailia!
I knew all along that
you were the priestess.
Why did you abandon the ritual
and choose to come here instead?
You have to... go back
and save this nation...
...from Mother Nature.
It's something only you can do.
Therefore, it's what
you must do.
[AILIA]
The wish of all the people.
So, you have your own
personal task.
[TAKUYA]
And I have one, too.
I'm going to one of the
quarries in the desert.
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
I need to find the psychite.
Sorry, Sayless,
it's what I have to do,
and you have to complete
your task as well.
[TAKUYA]
Look, I have to go alone.
You wouldn't do well
in the desert.
Fine.
[TAKUYA exhales]
That's strange,
did Sayless give up?
Well, I'm glad.
That's for the best.
Oh, man, that's bad.
[growls] This sucks!
[TAKUYA panting]
[gulping]
[sighs]
Anyone here?
Hey, Sayless?
[TAKUYA] Don't tell me
you're still out there.
[SAYLESS] Mother...
Is what you told me a lie?
Is it?
[SAYLESS]
I won't stop believing it.
Hey, Sayless!
Sayless!
Can you hear me?!
[SAYLESS]
Takuya.
[gasps]
Tell me where you are!
[SAYLESS]
I'm here. Find me.
The light of life,
the light of Melgio,
envelops me.
Melgio?
[TAKUYA]
Should I go towards the sun?
[SAYLESS]
I can feel it.
[TAKUYA]
Sayless!
[SAYLESS] I feel his breath.
I hear his voice.
[TAKUYA]
...I'm coming!
I'm here, okay?
Here, drink this.
[gasping]
I heard your voice
calling to me.
It's what led me to you.
Now, I understand.
[SAYLESS]
Takuya.
My meeting you.
It was destined.
It's fate.
Oh, yeah?
[YU-NO] Episode 19: "The Bond
between Parent and Child."