[TAKUYA]
So weird.
It felt like Ayumi and Ryuzoji
were telling the truth.
So, was it all a dream?
The girl? And that gun?
No. I know it had to be real.
Okay.
[TAKUYA]
Yup, back where it was.
One more time!
Whoa. It seems like what
I carry stays with me.
[KODAI]
Takuya.
Tell me, what is history?
Did you really call me
in here to ask me that?
[KODAI]
Answer the question.
History is the sum
of everything
the human race has
done up till now.
[KODAI] Heh. A surprisingly
old-fashioned view.
It's been said that
history is the memory
of how things have
changed throughout time.
But the reality is,
history is the memory of
the process of change.
What does that mean?
"History" has quite
a broad application.
It can refer to the
changes to time itself.
Not that I expect your
flea-sized brain
to comprehend
something like that.
You trying to pick
a fight with me?
[KODAI] For instance,
let's say I wondered
what would happen if I hadn't
eaten this piece of cake,
so I went several minutes
back in time to find out.
Call it a thought experiment.
What do you think
would happen then?
Anyone would have
the same answer.
They'd say that you'd just
create a new history,
where you didn't eat the cake.
Well, then everyone
would be wrong.
Lemme ask you a question.
In this scenario, what
happened to the initial impetus
that led me to go back in time?
I mean... You went back
in time because you ate
the cake, isn't that right?
So, if you never ate it
in the first place... Huh.
[KODAI] Right. The initial
reason I made the choice
to go back wouldn't
simply disappear.
So, if I eat the cake,
then choose to go
back into the past,
then, a world where I don't
eat the cake is born.
And all three of these truths
are carved into history.
[TAKUYA] "The Reflector Device
is an object that allows one
to move to another,
parallel world."
"Don't be mistaken, though,
it's a different beast
than a 'time machine'."
Uh.
Ouch. Oh, not again.
Is it a side effect from
using this thing too much?
Uh-- Ah!
Hey, Kanna! Were you
watching all of that?
[KANNA]
Depends what you mean by "that."
[laughs] Well, I assume that's
a "no," which is just fine.
See ya later.
Summer break starts tomorrow.
I want you to work as hard
at having fun as you do
at your studies.
You all better go and have
the time of your lives.
[bell tolls]
[YUKI] Hey, why're we making
a diorama of Sakaimachi?
Doesn't seem very historical.
We're doing it
because Doctor Arima
always believed
that the city itself
actually hid a significant
historical mystery.
Then there's Mount Sankaku.
What do you think about it?
[YUKI] Hm... Well, it's kind of
a weird mountain to begin with.
That's true.
It's hard to believe that
erosion from sea winds
could make a shape like that.
And the geology...
Hey.
Uh. Arima, what're
you doing here?
Do you wanna join
the club after all?
No I just had a question.
I came in here yesterday,
didn't I?
Uh, yeah.
I remember it perfectly
because you came in
right as we were talking
about Doctor Arima.
Oh, that's right!
You asked if you could borrow
his dad's research notes.
[TAKUYA]
I see.
Somethin' wrong there, Boss?
Nope. I just wanted to check.
Lemme borrow your phone.
Wait a second!
Asking would've been nice!
[TAKUYA]
Yeah, sorry. It's urgent.
Hello?
Hey, Takuya, you okay?
[TAKUYA]
You were talking with Ryuzoji
this morning at school, right?
What happened with my
dad's research notes?
Well, I promised that
I would send them
to him as soon as I could.
[TAKUYA] Hmm. So that
hasn't changed, then.
Nothing! Never mind.
[AYUMI] Actually, I'm glad
you reminded me.
If you don't mind,
I'd like your help with that.
Help with what?
[AYUMI] Kodai's notes have a
lot of random personal things
mixed in. So, it would be
super helpful if you could
sort through them before
the delivery people come.
A-Ah. You want me
to go through his notes?
The whole room?
I'm afraid so.
Hey, Chief.
[AYUMI] Uh. One sec. Sorry,
things are crazy here.
I understand. I'll do it.
[exhales]
[YUKI] Aw, Boss, you're
such a good stepson.
You're gonna have to
help me with this.
[YUKI]
What?! Why me?!
[MIO]
I'll do it! I'd love to.
[TAKUYA, YUKI]
Uh.
I know everything about
Doctor Arima's research.
Nobody's better suited than
me to go through his things
and say what's part of
his work and what's not.
Whaddaya think?
Will you let me help?
Sure, that's fine, I guess.
'Cept it means we'll need
to hang out all alone.
[YUKI gasps] Great! I'll
be joining you, then!
You saw that special on
the paranormal, right?
They covered our city!
It was so cool!
Yeah, of course!
Did you hear them explain
the whole curse thing?
About how the police kept
getting strange reports
that people were being attacked
by a headless monster.
[MIO] And then, there was
all the craziness when they
actually found a torso
with no head or limbs.
And those missing parts
still have yet to be found.
The most likely theory is
that it's a mountain cat.
I've heard other theories.
My favorite one is zombies.
For real! Last night, people
were saying it was aliens!
So ridiculous.
Those lightning strikes,
and then the curse.
There sure is a lot of
weird stuff going on.
You never change, do you, Mio?
You're all about history
and the paranormal!
I'm interested in both from a
purely scientific perspective.
Solving this is our
duty as members
of the Historical Research Club!
Right!
[TAKUYA sighs]
[clock ticks]
[gasps]
Hey, everything okay, Boss?
Uh? Yeah, totally, I'm good.
Hey, if you happen
to find any porn
while you're digging
around, I call dibs.
Though, I'd be shocked if Dad
and I had the same taste.
[MIO]
Wow, another one.
Hey, Arima? Would
it be okay with you
if I made some copies before
we sent this off to Ryuzoji?
Yeah, sure. I don't care.
How about these? Want 'em?
[TAKUYA] Yep, put fragile
stuff over there.
Got it.
[TAKUYA]
Hm?
Knew it. He never did
stop researching.
He kept studying the
400 Year Cycle Theory.
[YUKI]
Four hundred year cycle?
What is that?
It's a fascinating concept.
Basically, it's a famous theory
Doctor Arima proposed.
Although, it's less a theory
and more the fantasy
of a delusional lunatic.
This theory has remained
completely original, even today.
Yeah, so "original," in fact,
that his academic
society disowned him.
[sighs] Why do I try
to talk to you?
If only Dr. Arima were here,
maybe he could break through
that thick skull of yours
and drive in some sense.
Hey, I feel the same way.
I'm still pretty sure I owe
him a big punch in the jaw.
The way he up and died on me.
[gasps] I'm sorry.
That was insensitive.
Listen don't even
sweat it, okay?
I know when you get really
excited about something
you kinda lose track of
what's going on around you.
Uh.
[YUKI]
Cool, so...
Anyone gonna explain
the 400-year thing?
Oh. My dad's theory was
that Japan undergoes
a revolution of sorts
every 400 years.
Around the year 1600,
the Edo Shogunate
was established.
Before that in 1200,
they established
the Kamakura Shogunate.
In the year 800, they moved
the capital to Kyoto.
And it was about 400 when the
Yamato court unified Japan
under its control.
[MIO] It's important to remember
that in each case,
the revolution was brought
by outsiders to Japan.
That part isn't written
in the official histories.
[TAKUYA]
My dad's theory was that
even the ancient
nations of Japan
and our unique culture were
originally brought here
by people outside
of the country.
Of course, he got lots of
complaints from the right.
The details are all
written here, in Legacy .
That book looks
very intimidating.
You're a part of the
Historical Research Club now,
so I really hope
that you'll read it!
'Course! Your wish is
my command, Shimazu!
That thing's out of print,
you know. He won't find it.
I have some.
For reading, for collecting,
and for lending them out
to those who are in need.
I see.
[YUKI] Man! Can't believe
we're finally done.
Yep, and we never
found any porn.
Hey, look, it's still light out.
Let's go to Mount Sankaku!
Huh? You've got way too
much energy, Shimazu.
What could we even
do there this late?
We could do that thing I told
you about before, obviously.
When was this? Like, back when
you used to pee the bed?
Uh. I never did that!
Uh. You sure? Not even
when you were little?
Of course. Yes,
I did back then.
Dang it! How'd you
get me to confess?!
Uh. It's time to investigate
Mount Sankaku, right?
Well, let's go!
C'mon, we can do this!
All right, there she is!
Mount Sankaku!
This is pretty dang exciting!
[MIO]
Yeah, it is.
Why? Don't you think so, too?
Of course I do.
[door creaks]
We're screwed if the foreman
sees us. Let's hurry.
Hold on, isn't that...?
[TAKUYA]
Hey.
This place is dangerous.
You really should
stay away from here.
[TAKUYA]
If it's so dangerous,
shouldn't you be
avoiding it, too?
Fine, goodbye, then.
Hold on a sec, Hatano.
What exactly are you doing here?
[KANNA]
I'm enjoying the fresh air.
We could all see
you doing something.
The question is what
that something was.
[KANNA] I didn't feel well,
so I was sitting down.
That's all.
Hatano, are you
hiding something?
How do I even answer that?
Tell me what you want me
to say and I'll say it.
Look, that's not how it is.
[MIO]
Did you leave these?
They're always here when I come.
I wondered who
was bringing them.
You can answer that question
with a yes or no, can't you?
[TAKUYA]
Mio, wait.
Well, goodbye, then.
Where're you going?!
Hey, knock it off.
I don't have time for this crap.
Are you attracted to her?
[MIO] Look, Hatano
isn't a good choice.
What are you talking about?
It's just that there are
some rumors going around
about her right now, that's all.
Like, what do you mean?
[YUKI] Futago Rock really does
have a weird shape, doesn't it?
Scientists did radiometric
dating on it once,
and they discovered that
it's somewhere around
8,000 years old.
Pretty incredible, huh?
Whoa, 8,000?
[TAKUYA] That writing's
older than the four
ancient civilizations?
[MIO] Radiometric dating has
never been perfect, though.
Something as simple as a meteor
falling can change the results.
[YUKI]
Huh.
Anyway, all we're sure of
is that we know nothing
about Mount Sankaku.
Hang on, you guys, calm down!
Another man got
injured two days ago!
You expect us to keep working
in these conditions?
Look, I'm only doing what the
company tells me to do, okay?
You're the one who told us to
move those rocks, you jackass!
No! [groans]
Those were Chief
Arima's orders!
[WORKER 2A]
We're wasting our time.
[WORKER 2B] Let's go
talk to Geotech directly.
[WORKERS]
Yeah.
I try to play nice and
they act like assholes.
[TAKUYA]
Hey.
Uh?
Sounds like you've been
feeding them a line of crap.
[TOYOTOMI]
Oh, it's you!
Sorry, not sure what you mean.
Care to elaborate?
You just lied about
Ayumi being the one
to order them to
move those rocks.
[TOYOTOMI] Hmph. If I
hadn't said something,
those thugs would've
bashed my head in.
You're a piece of work.
Who is that?
Right, this is Ass-Hat.
He works with Ayumi.
"Toyotomi."
He films sad clown porn.
I run a construction site!
Bet you told them to do it
without getting her "okay."
Oh, yeah, you got any proof?
[TAKUYA]
Not yet.
But I'm pretty sure
that's how it went down.
Let's say it was true. Even if
I did, it's still really her
responsibility because
she's my boss, right?
So the buck slides past me
and lands right with her.
You piece of shit.
[TOYOTOMI]
What did you say?
Don't worry about it.
[TOYOTOMI]
You meddling kids better not
have been up there on
Mount Sankaku, you got it?
That place is
strictly off-limits.
That's not true.
Mount Sankaku is a public space.
They've already finished
their investigation
of the lightning strikes.
[TOYOTOMI]
I'm sorry, miss.
But it's under Geotech's
authority now.
It's dangerous.
We're tearing down Futago Rock
when we expand
the construction site.
[gasps] But you can't do that!
Those are historic landmarks
and should be declared
an Important Cultural Property
by the government!
Well, if you don't like it,
you're free to sue
just like anyone else.
Mayor Shimazu's already
given his permission,
and the legal application
paperwork is almost complete.
Will you at least explain
why you're tearing it down?
Company secret, I'm afraid.
Which means I can't tell you.
[MIO] So you've given
no proper reason,
and all you need is
the support of the mayor?
That isn't right, and it
shouldn't be allowed to happen!
Ugh. Who the heck
are you, anyway?
I am Mio Shimazu.
I'm the mayor's daughter.
You're the mayor's daughter?!
Uh-- Hey, listen.
I'm just doing what the company
tells me to, you know?
Anyway, it's really only
a matter of time
before the City
Council approves.
Democracy is all
about the process.
You need to get approval
before, not after.
[TOYOTOMI]
I don't know what to tell you.
I am personally going to talk
to my father about this.
Oh! Woulddya look at the time,
I've gotta be somewhere!
Bye!
Remember, in the end,
the good guys always win!
Uh?
[TOYOTOMI]
Ooh!
[TAKUYA]
What's his deal?
[MIO]
I'll ask my dad about it.
But since time is
of the essence,
we should continue
our investigation.
[YUKI]
Right.
Yuki, think you could
walk Mio home?
Leave it to me!
The cheap hotels are
that way, by the way.
Uh!
[door clicks]
[TAKUYA]
I'm home.
[AYUMI] Takuya. Unfortunately,
I'll be home late again tonight.
Please go ahead
and eat without me.
Mother, you know how much
I love you, right?
[ACTRESS 2A]
Don't say that.
I know I'm not your real mom,
but you and I can't--
[ACTOR 2A]
So what? I don't care!
[ACTRESS 2A]
But what about your father?
I could never betray him.
[TAKUYA]
Excuse me?
What could I possibly help
you with at this hour?
[TAKUYA]
My name is Takuya Arima.
I want to get in touch
with my stepmom, Ayumi.
Well, then, I'm afraid
you've missed her.
She left not too long ago.
[TAKUYA]
Where'd she go?
I can't tell anybody that,
not even her stepson.
[TAKUYA]
Please, I'm begging!
Besides, I know you're the type
who takes this job seriously.
Not the type who
watches TV at work.
[ACTOR 2A]
Mother!
[clears throat] She was
on her way to a meeting.
A scientific equipment
leasing corporation
in the warehouse
district at the port.
[AYUMI screams]
Uh. Ayumi?
Who are you and
what do you want?
[MAN 2A] Just like we
said on the phone.
We're repairmen with
the leasing company.
You really think
I'd believe that?!
Didn't anyone ever tell you not
to judge a book by its cover?
Look, lady, let's just
get to it. Hand it over.
Hand what over?
[MAN 2B] Don't play dumb.
We want that research data.
[AYUMI] I don't get it.
Why are you doing this?
[MAN 2A]
Just hand it over, honey.
[MAN 2B] Unless you're
interested in getting hurt.
[TAKUYA]
Okay!
[door creaks]
[TAKUYA]
Hey!
[MEN]
Huh?
[AYUMI]
What're you doing here?
I came to make sure
you were okay.
Was this guy a part of
the script, or what?
I don't think he's
part of the show.
I've notified the police.
[MAN 2B]
Ha. You're bluffing.
In five minutes,
you'll find out.
In five minutes, you won't
have one unbroken bone
left in your body.
[AYUMI]
Stop this! Please!
[gasps]
[AYUMI]
I'll give you the data, okay?
Here it is! But please,
just don't hurt him.
[TAKUYA] Ayumi, no! You don't
need to give that to them!
Takuya, listen to me.
Don't do anything crazy.
Please!
I say you put this kid
out of your head
and move on with
your life, lady.
We're so much more fun
to hang out with.
You haven't had
a man in a while.
I can tell by the
look on your face.
[AYUMI gasps]
[AYUMI screams]
Get your hands off her,
you bastard!
[yells]
You're pathetic.
[AYUMI]
Takuya! Are you all right?!
Don't mess with professional
brawlers, kid.
[MAN 2A]
You still wanna do this, huh?
Yeah. It's time for Round Two.
How'm I gonna pull
this off unarmed?
[door opens, crash]
--[TAKUYA] Hey!
--[MEN] Huh?
What're you doing here?
Ayumi, listen. You need
to get out of here.
Was this guy a part
of the script, or what?
I don't think he's
part of the show.
[yells]
[AYUMI]
Takuya! Are you all right?!
[groaning]
Don't mess with professional
brawlers, kid.
[MAN 2A]
You still wanna do this, huh?
That's right. I always have
been the stubborn type.
[AYUMI]
What're you doing here?
Was this guy a part of
the script, or what?
[MAN 2B] I don't think
he's part of the show.
[TAKUYA yelling]
[TAKUYA groans]
--No! Takuya!
--[MAN 2A] Easy...
Takuya! Are you all right?
[TAKUYA grunting]
Once more.
[TOYOTOMI]
Hold it right there!
[MEN]
Huh?
[TOYOTOMI chuckles]
[YU-NO] Episode 3:
"Tears That Can't Be Stopped"