[KANNA]
Bye, then.
[TAKUYA]
See ya.
[thud]
Uh?
[TAKUYA]
Kanna!
I'm sorry to cause you
all this trouble.
Don't worry about it.
So, that fever reducer.
Oh. Yeah, it's what my mother
always used to use.
Wow. It really works,
doesn't it?
Uh?
Yesterday was so much fun.
I think I got overexcited.
Well, then, how 'bout
you get some rest?
'Kay. Goodnight, Arima.
Sleep tight.
Man, that sneaky bastard.
It looks like he was giving
her money every month
right up until he disappeared.
The real question is,
where'd he get the cash?
[gasps]
[TAKUYA gasps]
Is that Kanna?
I didn't know she could
smile like that.
That her sister?
Uh.
Wait, this is weird.
Why are there three
rocks in this picture?
That's impossible.
[door slides]
[TAKUYA]
Hey.
[MIO]
What're you doing here?
There's no class
today, you know.
Yeah, I actually
came to see you.
Huh?
I've heard that stuff before.
You say that to all
the girls, don't you?
I'm interested in Mount Sankaku.
Doing some research.
Naturally, I decided
to come to you first.
Oh. Now, that makes more sense.
Here, this'll have
everything you want to know.
Okay, this book looks
older than both of us.
Do you remember,
what Kanna said before
about the diorama we're making?
When I heard that, I decided
it was time to look into
the history of
Sakaimachi's geology.
'Course you did. I'd expect
nothing less from a history nut.
Look, don't call me a nut,
okay? I really hate that.
--Well, how 'bout--
--[MIO] Shut up.
But I haven't said
anything yet.
Right and that's fine
because I already know
what you were gonna say.
Give it a guess, then,
if you're so sure.
[MIO]
Hm? Well, let me think.
Oh, Mio.
"You are a shining goddess
descending upon the world
of historical study!
I have to confess,
I believe you might be
even more beautiful
than the stunning Aphrodite,
Goddess of Love!"
That about right?
You've completely
lost your mind.
[MIO laughs]
[YUKI]
Yes! They came out perfectly.
[HOJO humming]
It's that Hojo guy.
"In the chaos during and
immediately after the war
there was a short-lived plan
to destroy Mount Sankaku."
[MIO]
Yes.
The plan was scrapped but
one rock was destroyed.
That's why it's
called Futago Rock,
which actually
means "Twin Rock."
[TAKUYA] Looks like this
photo was taken in 1945.
This is definitely it!
So, hey. Do you think
anybody's out there
who's lived more than
50 years without aging?
You really might wanna cut
back on all the sci-fi novels.
Yeah, normally, I would
agree with that.
--[door slides]
--[YUKI] I'm back!
Masakatsu Yuki, reporting in
with all those pictures, sir!
Uh! By the way,
I saw that weird stalker guy
on the way over here.
You talking about Hojo?
He's in the back alleys
of Central Street.
That means he must be up
to something naughty again!
What do you mean by "naughty"?
Oh, man. I don't know.
Ugh.
Oh, good, you made it.
Look, Hojo. I've decided.
I want this to be our last time.
You what?
[paper rustling]
[MIO]
Hm?
[MIO] Hey, what do you
think about this?
What is it?
The geology of Sakaimachi?
[YUKI]
Huh... How weird.
Doesn't it almost look like a
bomb went off or something?
Yeah, it does. I wonder...
Is it possible Sakaimachi
could've been made
when two different
things collided?
Collided?
Interesting.
Doctor Arima's research
actually said something similar.
In his 400 Year Cycle Theory,
he proposes that once
every 400 years,
different dimensions
approach each other.
So, yeah, maybe
it was a collision
instead of a gentle approach.
Dr. Imagawa mentioned
the exact same thing.
Called it an "event collision,"
where two different
dimensions collided.
An event collision, huh?
That would also explain
Mount Sankaku's unique geology.
How did that work?
I mean, just
practically speaking?
Did one dimension fall
right outta the sky?
[MIO, TAKUYA]
Hm...
Yeah, I don't know.
[door slides]
[TAKUYA, MIO, YUKI]
Mm?
Arima. I need a minute.
[HOJO] Uh. The last time?
Whaddya mean by that?
I mean I won't see you anymore.
Oh? What, are you
swearing an oath
of chastity to Takuya Arima,
your new best friend?
Arima has nothing
to do with this.
Heh. You're always
so expressionless,
but it's easy to tell
what you're thinking.
And how do you think
your friend would feel
if he knew all the things
you've done in your life?
Kinda makes you wonder if
he'd stick around, doesn't it?
[KANNA grunts]
All right. This will be
our last time, then.
But in exchange,
you're going to tell me
the truth about where
Doctor Kodai Arima is.
I know you were his lover,
so there's really no use
in trying to deny it now.
[KANNA gasps]
You're gonna tell me
the truth right now.
Or, I promise you,
I'll make it so you can
never go to school again.
But... That means...
[KANNA]
It'll be like it was before.
I'll just keep repeating
the same thing, as always.
Hang on, what's that
s'posed to mean?
[POLICE A]
Hey, you there!
Uh. What?
[gasps]
Would you care to tell
me what this is about?
Uh. Well, yeah,
it's simple, really.
You see... My daughter's
determined to act
like a rebellious teenager.
Your daughter?
[KANNA]
Mm-hm.
Wow, you two look
nothing alike.
I know! Weird, right?
Come on now, honey.
Let's go home.
[ERIKO] Oh, man. So, you saw
Hatano collapse again.
Yeah, but at least the
fever reducer seemed to work.
By the way, where exactly is
Shimazu's vacation house?
Next town over.
You can't swim here
because of the Geotech
construction project.
[ERIKO] Outside Sakaimachi,
huh? I knew it.
[TAKUYA]
Hm?
I'm just grateful
that she's still safe.
Sounds like I was right
to put her in your hands.
Hey, yeah, what's that
about? I mean, why me?
[ERIKO]
Hm.
Teacher's intuition? Uh?
[TAKUYA]
Intuition?
The truth is, I have a
pretty high opinion of you.
Well, that's nice to know.
Wait a minute.
Did you figure out my talent
for discovering the location
of your nipples
simply by staring?
Ow...
No, I mean the way you try
to get close to anybody,
regardless of common
decency or etiquette.
It's very uniquely you.
Then let me ask you something
totally not my business.
Doesn't Kanna have
anyone to look after her?
[ERIKO] Apparently,
they've been overseas.
We haven't been able
to get ahold of them.
[ERIKO] There's a lot about
Kanna that I don't understand.
Her school transfer
record, for instance.
[TAKUYA]
Huh?
It's interesting.
She keeps hopping around
from one school to another,
and not just here,
but the next town over,
and the town next to that.
It's been pretty
endless for her.
That might be kinda rare,
but it's not weird.
What's weird is the number
of times it's happened.
How many times?
Well, I can't find
all of the records
but based on what I have,
she's transferred schools
well over 20 times.
Uh.
[HOJO] Hey. Lookit who
it is. How ya doin'?
I was in a pretty good
mood until I saw you.
Heh! I haven't introduced
myself yet, have I?
Here's my card--
why don't you take it?
Dude, stop breathing on me.
Hey, now, don't say that.
I mean, let's be honest,
you don't even know me.
So that doesn't seem
exactly fair, does it?
Go on, take the card, kid.
[TAKUYA]
"Space Detective McDumbass."
Don't be a prick,
that's not what it says!
So?
What does some guy from a
detective agency want with me?
Believe it or not, I was
hoping to get your help.
Help with what?
As far as I can tell,
there's one person
who knows where your father is,
and that person is Kanna Hatano.
Uh?
My father.
Is he still alive somewhere?
Yes, he is.
You probably don't know this,
but Doctor Arima was
paying Kanna's bills
for almost an entire year.
The truth is, she was
your dad's lover.
Heh. Oh, good, if you
knew that already,
then we can get
right to the point.
How 'bout you and I make a deal?
Yeah, I don't really
see that happening.
Not ever.
Aw, I guess you really
don't like me, then.
There's no guesswork
involved, man.
I'm just not that into you.
--[gate creaks]
--Uh?
Don't you want to know
where you dad is?!
Hey!
[POLICE A]
You, there! Sir!
What's all the fuss about?
Seriously? You again?
Uhh... I was just havin' a
little argument with my son?
[doorbell rings]
[AYUMI]
Coming!
Uh?
Sorry to disturb you.
I'm a classmate of Arima's.
My name is Hatano.
He lent me his hat,
so I wanted to return it.
Oh, did he really? [laughs]
Takuya!
Your friend Hatano is here and
she brought something for you!
Would you like to come in?
No thank you,
I need to get going.
Oh, hey Kanna, what's up?
I brought your hat back.
Ah. Why does it seem
like your classmates
are all cute girls, huh, Takuya?
[TAKUYA]
Huh?
[AYUMI] Is she the one
you're really after?
Ah. Stop being weird!
Ayumi, I'll be back later,
okay? Let's go. C'mon.
[AYUMI] Hatano, you come
see us any time, all right?
[birds chirping]
[TAKUYA]
The birds are chirping.
The water shines in the sun.
If this isn't the epitome of
peace, I don't know what is.
I can understand how
it seems that way.
Ah, you don't agree?
Birds are on alert.
They never know when a
predator might attack them.
And the fountain?
That's nothing more
than a monument to our
destruction of nature.
It's a very fragile balance,
and we exist on top of it.
Any perceived peace
is an illusion.
Ah. Good point.
It's not just a "point."
It's the truth.
Okay, whatever you say.
[CHILDREN laughing]
[TAKUYA]
Kanna.
I have a weird question.
[KANNA]
Yes?
Do you remember how I told
you that I knew someone
with that pendant back
when I was a kid?
The thing is...
She looked like you and was
the same age that you are now.
Uh... So, I know this
might sound crazy, but...
Was it you?
Did I know you way back then?
[DOG whimpers]
[gasps]
[panting]
If there's no collar, doesn't
that mean he's prob'ly lost?
Lotta that goin' around.
[growls]
[gasps, laughs]
Well, it looks like dogs must
prefer cute girls, huh?
Animals just don't judge people
based on appearance, that's all.
If I could only see
the world like they do,
I bet I could be happy.
No anger, and no worries,
or heartbreak, or loneliness.
[TAKUYA] I don't know, I think
anger and sorrow are part of
what makes life
worth living, though.
Here's the thing, that's
something people only say
if they haven't experienced
true anger or sorrow.
[TAKUYA]
Uh?
I'm sick of it.
Being hated, and being betrayed.
[DOG barks]
You know Arima, I've never
met anyone like you before.
Well, thanks, I guess.
But now, all I want is
to know more about you.
I want to learn
everything I can.
There's no point in that.
Telling you things about me.
Why do you say that?
Isn't it normal to want to know
more about your friends?
You mean me?
Am I... your friend now?
Yeah. Mio and Yuki
feel the same way.
We're friends, for sure.
You can be very cruel sometimes,
can't you, Arima?
Uh?
[KANNA]
Goodbye.
[HOJO]
Fancy meetin' you here
What do you want now,
Mister Creeper?
Don't call me that, it's rude.
You should learn
some manners, boy.
And it's time someone
taught you some respect.
Just leave us alone.
Get outta here.
Who the hell is paying
you to do this, anyway?
Sorry, can't tell you that.
So, about that deal from before.
What?
Look, we both want to know where
Doctor Arima is, don't we?
Why pretend that we can't
help each other out?
C'mon I'm not askin'
you for very much.
What I need you to do is take
this and leave it somewhere
in Kanna's room. That's it!
You want me to bug her room?
It sounds so sinister
when you put it that way.
I prefer the term
"listening device."
[HOJO gasping]
That was expensive!
Oh, wow, sorry about that.
If I were you, I'd send the
bill straight to your boss.
Listen, if you don't
help me with this,
something terrible
will happen! Shit!
Huh?
[POLICE A]
Oh, come on.
Find a new parenting style.
This one isn't workin' for ya.
[laughs] I'll be sure
to work on that.
[RYUZOJI]
You've gone past your deadline.
What's the problem?
[HOJO] Well, so far, Kanna
Hatano is refusing to talk,
and Doctor Arima's son is being
very uncooperative, as well.
Really? I find that
very interesting
considering my other agent
has made excellent headway
in the same amount of time.
[HOJO]
Uh?
[HOJO grunts]
I just need is a
little more time,
and then I can get you all the
information you could want.
Yes, If I can keep
Kanna isolated,
to the point where there's
no one she can rely on...
[RYUZOJI sighs]
[HOJO]
Uh?
Look deep into my eyes, Hojo.
[HOJO]
What?
[HOJO gasping]
[MALE STUDENT A]
So the rumors were true?
That's nuts.
She looks totally normal.
I guess you can never
tell with some people.
What's this all about? No!
[TAKUYA gasping]
[ERIKO]
I see.
So that's the reason you've
transferred so many times.
Are you planning to do
the same thing now?
Eventually, you're going to run
out of places to go, you know.
I've never belonged anywhere.
Never had a place to go
that meant anything.
[KANNA]
Is it the same for you, Takeda?
[TAKUYA]
What the hell is this?
What do you think you're doing?
You can't just tear it down!
That's all there is to do
with trash like this!
You guys should be ashamed!
I'm taking it!
[MALE STUDENT B]
No, wait! You can't!
You'd be violating their
freedom of expression!
[TAKUYA, YUKI]
Freedom of expression?
[ALL]
Uh?
That belongs to honest people
who take responsibility
for the things they say!
I've got your back, Boss!
Uh. Yeah.
[YUKI]
I have no idea who did this.
But it's a really
terrible thing to do!
It's true. Remember those
weird rumors about Hatano?
[MIO] Would you stop talking
trash, you guys?
How would you feel if you
showed up at school and saw
that someone did this
to you? Just imagine it!
[STUDENTS murmuring]
That was really great, Mio!
I guess it's lucky this
happened during break
and not in the middle
of the school year,
but who do you think
would do this?
[TAKUYA grunts]
[TAKUYA]
What? Kanna's transferring?
[ERIKO] That's right. She had
all the paperwork ready to go.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[ERIKO] I know I told you
she'd done this before,
but when I looked into
all those transfers,
I found something out.
Uh?
There's a clear pattern.
She's only been transferring
to certain schools
around Sakaimachi.
[TAKUYA]
Huh?
Essentially, she's stayed
within a pretty tight circle.
Always on Sakaimachi's doorstep.
She never strayed
from that pattern.
Why was she doing it, though?
I don't understand it.
[ERIKO] We can assume
there's some reason
she needs to stay
near Mt. Sankaku,
and that it's most likely
related to whatever reason
she had to keep
transferring schools.
That's why I asked you to
make sure that she was okay.
You've picked up on it,
haven't you?
The fact that her secret
is deeply connected
with your parents. There's
no way you don't feel it.
[gasps]
[ERIKO]
Kanna went home, you know.
I think you get what you
have to do now, right?
Yeah.
[YU-NO] Episode 17:
"A Pale, Ephemeral Vow."