[TAKUYA]
I mean it!
Just tell me when you're
gonna come back, already!
[KODAI]
I don't know.
And what about Ayumi?
You're just gonna
leave her alone?
Unlike you, Ayumi understands
the importance of my work.
I'm sure that's what
she tells you.
Come on, can't you show her half
the kindness she deserves?
[KODAI chuckles]
Falling for her?
[grunts] What is your problem?!
I'm worried about her,
that's all!
[KODAI] Then you'd
better look after her.
Who knows what she's
going through right now.
[gasps]
Ayumi?
[water running]
[AYUMI]
Takuya? Is that you out there?
[TAKUYA]
Yeah.
No matter what happens,
even if my dad treats you wrong,
I promise I'll always
be here for you.
[AYUMI]
Thank you, but...
I'm just so tired of everything.
Living only brings more pain.
I can't do it.
[TAKUYA gasping]
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi!
[TAKUYA gasping]
Anyone home?
I knocked this time, okay?
I'm coming in!
[water running]
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Oh, please no.
Ayumi?
[gasps] Ayumi!
[gasps]
Takuya, what on Earth
is going on with you?
[TAKUYA]
Uh! I'm sorry!
It's not what it
looks like, I swear!
[sighs] What is wrong with me?
It was just a dream, you idiot.
[phone rings]
Hello. It's Takuya.
[TOYOTOMI] Oh the little
slacker, perfect.
If you want porn actors, you're
barking up the wrong tree.
That joke wasn't funny
the first time, either.
Save the banter for later.
I need to talk to
the chief right now,
not her freeloading house guest.
Just put her on for me.
[TAKUYA] Sorry jackass,
but she's busy right now.
Changing your diaper?
You idiot.
[TOYOTOMI]
This is important.
Tell her it's an emergency,
all right?
[door clicks]
What's wrong?
Who are you arguing with?
[TAKUYA]
Uh. Oh, it's uh...
Captain Douchebag from work.
Toyotomi, y'mean?
I can pick it up in my room.
Tell him to wait a sec.
[TAKUYA]
Sure. Got it.
[TOYOTOMI] What did you
call me you little jerk?!
So how has school been
treating you lately, Mio?
It's just summer classes,
but I'm busy with my club.
Well, that's good.
It's nice to pour your
heart into something.
It is.
I have a bit of a
proposal for you.
Proposal?
How does a foreign exchange
program sound to you?
I'd be leaving, you mean?
[MAYOR] Things around here are
about to get a little messy,
I'm afraid. I don't want to
see you get pulled into it.
Yeah, but...
[MAYOR]
I'm going to be frank with you.
The paperwork is already done.
You'll be starting next week
at a school in America.
That's not right! You can't
decide that on your own!
Besides, I need
to stay in Japan!
Sakaimachi is the subject
of my historical research!
That may be so, but I
think you can benefit
from an international
perspective.
Looking from the outside
might teach you something
new about your home.
Mio, it's already settled.
Let's not fight.
[TAKUYA]
Wow, looks great.
You're staring.
I don't have food on my
face or something, do I?
No.
Oh, no, my eyes aren't still red
after last night are they? Jeez.
You feel better now?
Heh, 100%.
All right, if you say so.
[AYUMI] You still have
summer classes, don't you?
Worry about your grades.
I can take care of myself.
Well, see you later.
[AYUMI]
Have a nice day.
[TOYOTOMI]
Check and mate.
I'm just being paranoid.
That dream messed me up.
Hey, Mio!
[MIO]
Morning.
Something wrong?
You sound upset.
Oh, I get it. It's that
time of the month.
You should find a new joke.
Uh. Well, we're stuck going
to class on our summer break.
Can't blame you
for being grumpy.
I'm the same way.
You say that, but in my case,
I'm attending class voluntarily.
I didn't fail my exams,
like you did.
Mean, but true.
Stop skipping classes
and stop showing up late
while you're at it. You need
to take this seriously.
[TAKUYA]
Uh.
Got it?
[TAKUYA]
Hey!
[TAKUYA] Where the hell
did that come from?
[KAORI] What are you planning
to do with that thing anyway?
I can't imagine you'd just
sell it to make some cash.
Is it academic curiosity,
or something more?
Better not to ask
so many questions.
For the both of us, that is.
I've heard that enough
times already. That's fine.
But I'm not happy
about his involvement.
I don't want him interfering
with my work, all right?
[RYUZOJI] I always have
a contingency plan.
Call it my personal
policy, if you like.
[TAKUYA grunts]
Goodbye. We'll speak again.
Oh, hey. Perfect timing, kiddo.
Can we have a little chat?
[TAKUYA] What does a
journalist need from me?
It's nothing too unsavory.
I just wanted to know what your
mom researches at her job.
Does she tell you?
And why do you care about
something like that?
The scandal!
I'm trying to get to the bottom
of what's going on at Geotech.
[TAKUYA]
Oh yeah, I saw your show.
[KAORI] Really? Well,
thank you for tuning in!
[TAKUYA]
As short as your skirt was,
I'm surprised I never
saw your panties.
[KAORI]
I'm a pro.
I cross my legs at just
the right angle.
[TAKUYA] I figured you
just weren't wearing any.
[KAORI]
Oh, I'll try that next time.
Anyway, I want to figure out
if Geotech is working with
the mayor behind the scenes.
I know you go to school
with the mayor's daughter.
Isn't she a friend of yours?
Yeah.
[KAORI] Has she said anything
to you about this?
Anything at all,
no matter how small?
Sorry, but I don't know a thing.
Besides, even if I did know,
I'd never sell out a friend.
'Specially to you.
Come on. I'm not asking
you to sell someone out.
I'm trying to help people, here.
How kind of you.
[KAORI]
I mean it.
Your friend is innocent--I
wouldn't dream of hurting her.
Mayor Shimazu's the bad guy.
If things are about to get ugly,
you need to make sure
she doesn't end up on the wrong
side of this whole mess.
Trading info can only help her.
We all deserve
to know the truth.
Don't give me that look.
I mean it.
If something comes up,
contact me as soon as you can.
And since we're friends,
you can call me Kaori.
It was nuts! He fell
flat on his face!
This is a surprise.
You actually showed up today.
You can consider it a favor
to a friend, I suppose.
You got something on
your mind, Shimazu?
If you need someone to talk to,
or a shoulder to cry on,
I'm always here for you!
I'm a master of all matters
of the heart, y'know!
[MIO]
Heh. Thank you.
If I can confide in anyone,
you're at the top of the list.
Sounds good! Hey, let's do
your fortune really quick!
Let's see here,
you're a Taurus right?
Looks like your lucky item
today is... watermelon!
That seems rather useless.
[YUKI] Also... It says to be
careful around mountains.
Mount Sankaku, maybe?
[TAKUYA]
Toyotomi? That's not good.
Wonder what he was
calling about today.
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--Actually. I gotta go.
[YUKI]
You okay, Boss?
[MIO]
Hey!
[ERIKO] Hold it! I have
to say, you've got guts
trying to skip class the second
your teacher shows up.
Summer is beckoning--
I must heed the call!
Oh, how I long to be free!
The fleeting days of my youth
can't be confined
within this prison!
Well if you truly want to be
free, then free your mind.
Fill it with knowledge.
How 'bout this? Let's have
today's class on the beach.
And bring watermelon!
Of course! Then we'll
put on blindfolds--
and play "find the melon!"
I sense some already-- Ah!
'Kay. Fine.
We're having a pop quiz.
Anyone who gets a perfect grade
is exempt from class for
the rest of the summer.
All right!
But you better keep your
promise after I ace this thing!
Unbelievable.
Did you forget you're nearly
at the bottom of the class?
Ha, ha! Don't count me out!
[TAKUYA] I've got this
on my side, after all.
Might take a few tries,
but I'll get it!
'Kay. I'm passing
out the quiz now.
Each grade has their own test so
make sure you get the right one.
[PA chiming]
[PA VOICE] Takuya Arima,
you have a phone call.
Please come to
the office immediately.
You heard 'em. Too bad!
[ERIKO growls]
Just go.
[TAKUYA]
This is Takuya.
[MOCHIZUKI]
My name is Mochizuki.
I'm with Geotechnics'
legal department.
Uh. Okay.
[MOCHIZUKI]
I'll get straight to the point.
Do you happen to know where
Chief Arima is right now?
I'm not sure, but she said she'd
be working from home today.
[MOCHIZUKI]
We tried earlier,
but she's not answering and
she's not returning our calls.
Why? Is something
going on with her?
[MOCHIZUKI] I'm not at liberty
to share the details.
So, uh, what now?
[MOCHIZUKI]
Well, I can tell you one thing
to put this in perspective.
The situation could possibly
develop into a criminal matter.
If you find your mother,
please tell her to come
to the office immediately.
[TAKUYA]
All right. I'll do that.
[MOCHIZUKI]
Good. Thank you.
[dial tone]
[phone ringing]
[TOYOTOMI]
Ayumi. Stop, let's relax.
You don't need to talk
to anyone but me.
[AYUMI whimpers]
[TOYOTOMI]
And that means no distractions.
[TAKUYA panting]
[TAKUYA] What the hell is
going on here, Ayumi?
Then you'd better
look after her.
Who knows what she's
going through right now.
[TAKUYA panting]
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi!
[TOYOTOMI chuckling]
[BOTH gasp]
Takuya?
Toyotomi?
Why did you--
Why did you come home?
Go away!
Go away! Please!
Uh-- No, listen. I was just...
[TOYOTOMI] Hmph. If the lady
wants privacy, give it to her.
Hey, shut up! I don't know
what's going on here,
but you keep your hands off her!
[TOYOTOMI grunting]
[AYUMI gasps]
[gasping]
Uh! Please not in the face!
You spineless bastard.
[TOYOTOMI screaming]
[thud]
What did--
Stop it. Don't do this.
You can't!
But this asshole was about to--
That's enough. I'll be fine.
Please, Takuya.
Don't cause me any more trouble.
"Trouble"?
No, I... I was just trying to...
[TOYOTOMI]
Heh. Thank you for the save.
But damn, that boy
has some anger issues!
You wanna go again?!
[AYUMI]
Stop it!
Are you okay?
Did he hurt you?
Tell me if there's anything
I can do to help.
[laughing] I went through this
all the time when I was young.
A little roughhousing isn't
going to bother me one bit!
Heh!
[BOTH laughing]
[TAKUYA growls]
All right, fine.
Do what you want!
Sorry for interrupting you!
[TAKUYA] Damn. It's like
I'm the bad guy here!
All I wanted to do
was protect her.
She doesn't have
anyone else anymore.
[KAORI]
Well! Look who it is!
[TAKUYA]
Uh.
Must be fate that
brought us together!
You must be stalking me
is what I'm thinking.
That's some confidence!
Are you sure you're not the one
stalking a pretty lady like me?
Uh. By the way...
You wrote this.
Did you know something was going
on between him and Ayumi?
Let's just say I had a hunch.
It's not what you think.
I've got a room at the City
Hotel right down the street,
if you want to talk.
I have a few details that I'm
sure you'd like to hear.
They're about Ayumi.
Whatever it is,
I'm done with this!
Even if the police start
getting involved?
Uh!
[KAORI]
I can't say any more here.
Come to my hotel room.
[elevator dings]
[gasps]
Something wrong?
[TAKUYA]
No.
I didn't invite you here
to gobble you up.
You don't need to look
quite so nervous.
Hey, been waitin' for you.
C'mon!
I need you to promise
me one thing first.
Don't show up at
my school anymore.
Ah, so you spotted
me today, huh?
All right, fine.
Now, get in here already!
[elevator dings]
[KAORI sighs]
Want something to drink?
A beer?
I'm not here to have fun.
Just tell me what's
going on with Ayumi.
[KAORI]
Could you relax a little? Jeez!
[TAKUYA] Just so we're clear,
I'll listen to you,
but I won't do anything
that might endanger Ayumi.
You really love
your mom, don't you?
Of course, we're family.
Well, good.
Because this plan of mine
will definitely help her.
Yeah, we'll see.
I have some juicy information
I'm still sitting on.
Something nobody else
has reported on yet.
[TAKUYA] Stop wasting my
time and just tell me!
[KAORI] Some secret data was
stolen from Geotech yesterday.
Whatever the content was, it
was highly important because
Chief Arima is going to be
fired for letting it slip.
Well, that was the story at
first, but now they're saying
she might have sold the
data to another company.
She'd never!
Their legal department
probably gave you a call
already, I'd assume.
[KAORI laughs]
Don't worry.
I said this would
help her, remember?
I know she didn't do it.
She's been set up.
Why would they do that?
[KAORI]
Anyway. Here's the offer.
I'm going to prove her
innocence and reveal the truth
to the world, but to do that,
I have to break
into Geotech first.
That is the part
where I need your help.
I don't get it.
What am I s'posed to do?
[KAORI]
All I need is one of these.
An ID card.
I want you to take this fake
card I had made, swap it out
with your mom's, and bring
the real ID card back to me.
[TAKUYA]
This is completely insane.
[KAORI]
It's also completely urgent.
Right now, this information
is a Geotech secret,
but it's only a matter of time
before the news gets out.
Once the police get involved,
your mom will be
arrested, I'm sure.
Then the story
will be all over TV.
And that includes my program,
if I can't prove the truth.
All right,
but one question first.
[KAORI] As long as it's
not about my age or weight,
fire away.
Sneaking into Geotech
would be dangerous.
Why are you willing to
take a risk like that?
On your show last night,
you were happy to blame Ayumi.
Yesterday was yesterday,
today is today.
All I'm looking for
is the biggest scoop,
and this is it for sure.
But wait,
do you know who set her
up in the first place?
Be patient.
Once I sneak into their office,
I'll figure it out no problem.
Wait...
That must be it.
From the start...
...this was all
Toyotomi's fault.
In that case, I should go.
Thank you, Kaori!
Uh. Hey! Where are you going?!
I thought that we had a deal!
[TAKUYA]
I'll think about it!
I should have trusted my gut!
She was only acting that way
because he was blackmailing her!
I have to set this straight!
I'm sorry Ayumi. I let you down.
[TAKUYA]
Uh.
Ayumi!
[TAKUYA gasping]
[water running]
[TAKUYA]
Ayumi...?
Sorry, I'm coming in now!
Kick my ass if I'm wrong!
You hear me?
[gasping]
[TAKUYA]
No... No!
[TAKUYA screams]
[YU-NO] Episode 5:
"Spiral of Tragedy."