[KODAI] Takuya, your history,
like everyone else's,
is carved into
the Tree of Vrinda.
[KODAI]
Creating history
means traveling through
infinite possibilities.
[KODAI] This might come
as a surprise to you,
but not a single thing you've
done is without meaning.
Events that are bound
by the laws of causality
flow like a river,
smoothly and organically,
in direct accordance with
their event elements.
Nothing, not even time itself,
can break this particular law.
At least, that's what I thought,
until I finally learned
of their existence.
Our time is almost up. Takuya,
we will see each other again.
[KODAI] It's been decided
by the weight of events,
the momentum of
the event elements.
If you prefer a more
literary phrasing,
it is, quite simply, our fate.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[TAKUYA]
Hey, Kanna!
I'd like to get to
know you a little better.
I'm not really sure what to say.
This is kind of sudden.
Oh, that's right. I forgot we've
barely spoken in this world.
Something wrong?
[TAKUYA]
Nope! Nothing at all.
I just think it's time we
got to know each other.
Check it out. Arima's hitting
on the ice princess.
She does have a weird
sexiness about her, right?
[STUDENT 14A]
Yeah, I admit, I get it.
[bell rings]
[TAKUYA]
Hey, wait up!
What're your plans today?
I need to speak to Takeda
about something.
What about after that?
Nothing, really, I guess.
So, uh... Got any hobbies?
[KANNA]
No, none.
[TAKUYA]
Favorite band?
[KANNA]
I don't listen to music.
[TAKUYA] Well, surely you
have a favorite food?
[KANNA]
Nope.
[TAKUYA] Okay, help me out,
here. What're you into?
[KANNA]
Green. I like plants a lot.
I thought the ocean
was more your thing.
You know, because of
the way you watch it.
Not a fan of the sea.
It just happens to be
my responsibility.
Responsibility?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
[door opens, closes]
[TAKUYA] Looks like Eriko's
been skipping school again.
Uh. You okay? What's wrong?
[KANNA groaning]
Whoa, you're burning up!
[TAKUYA] She's sweating like
crazy. I gotta do something.
Damn it! Where is that total
slacker of a teacher?
I'll do it. I'll wipe
you down, Kanna.
And I won't look! So help me,
I refuse to look!
I'm doing this out
of medical necessity.
It's a tough job but
somebody's gotta do it.
That feels like fresh pudding.
[KANNA grunts]
Oh! Ah-- Uh, sorry!
Closing my eyes was
a stupid idea.
[unzipping]
Uhh...
[clothes rustling]
[KANNA exhales]
Better? You were sweating
really badly.
[KANNA]
Sometimes, I get these fevers.
But lately, it feels
like it's been
happening even more than usual.
Uh. No don't get up yet.
Could we talk a little bit?
Yeah, I guess so.
This'll sound weird, but I've
seen your necklace before.
I just wish I could
remember where.
Maybe it's what they refer
to as "déjà vu" in psychology.
I could've seen it somewhere
with my dad at some point.
Back when I was a kid,
he used to drag me all
over the place with him.
Your father, he passed away
not long ago, right?
That must be hard.
[TAKUYA] Tch. He was a lunatic
who called himself a historian.
So, it is what it is.
Yeah, I understand.
[door opens]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps] Well, what
do we have here?
Glad you're together,
it saves me time.
Do you mind explaining
where the hell you were?
I had to do something really
disturbing to treat her fever
and it's all your fault!
What did you say?
[KANNA] What did you want
to talk to us about?
Well, here's the thing...
So, um, do you happen to know
anything about Hatano?
What is she like?
[YUKI] The girl who just
transferred here, right?
Unfortunately, I don't know
much about the upper classmen.
Oh, that's right.
[YUKI] Actually, another student
from Hatano's old school
is in the kendo club with me!
I can definitely ask him
about her if you want!
That'd be great.
[knocking]
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Hey, you guys.
Wait. Why're you here?
You've finally decided
to join our club! Hooray!
[TAKUYA]
Yep, somethin' like that.
And I, uh...
I brought someone else.
[MIO]
Hatano?
[TAKUYA]
Can we both join?
Why exactly did you
bring her here with you?
I didn't realize that you two
were even really friends.
[TAKUYA] Eriko asked me to
look after her for a while.
She's been a little bit
sick and needs help.
A teacher asked you
to take care of a girl?
Of all the people in the world,
why would she leave it up
to a walking libido?
I don't know how you
dare say that about
a stand-up guy like myself.
[laughs]
Look, whatever. Yes,
of course you can join.
As a matter of fact,
you can help us
make this diorama
if you want... to...
It's incredibly well-made.
I know, right?!
Except, the terrain
right here is a little off.
[YUKI, MIO]
Huh?!
[MIO] But it's just
like the photo, see?
Tell me this. How old would
you say that photo is?
I'd guess, maybe
about ten years old?
Exactly, it looks
a lot different now.
Huh?!
[KANNA] Sakaimachi's geology was
formed in the Cretaceous period
as part of the Nakaminato area.
But Mount Sankaku is made
of dried limestone,
so it's actually
more like a desert.
It changes. It shifts
with earthquakes
and things like that.
[gasps]
She knows a lot.
Amazing.
Hey! Y'know what else?
Fifteen years ago, there was
another part of Futago Rock.
Do you think we should go
check it out right now?
[TAKUYA] Sure, there's no use
sticking around here, anyway.
[YUKI]
Cool, let's all go!
[inaudible]
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
Uh. Wait, Kanna!
[MIO]
Hey, where are you going?
C'mon, guys, you need
to calm down.
[WORKER 11A] Another worker
was hurt in a lightning strike!
[WORKER 2B] You expect us to
keep working on a job site
where there are no guarantees
for our safety?
You're in danger!
[TOYOTOMI]
Uh. Listen, you can't--
You have to call off
the hauling operation.
Are you one of the protestors?
No, I'm not.
Lemme guess, you gonna tell us
we angered the gods
or somethin'?
Another lightning
strike is coming.
What?
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Lightning strikes are
a natural phenomenon.
[KANNA] I'm saying this out
of concern for your safe--
Look, if you've got a problem,
take it to a judge.
They'll decide,
that's how things tend
to work in this country.
And who're you?
Go screw yourself.
[TOYOTOMI]
Oh, you're the slacker stepson
who's been causing problems
for my boss, aren't you?
Yeah, I know you, too.
How's the porn industry
been treating you?
I'm the man Geotech put
in charge of this site.
Then make them stop!
Let go of me!
This suit cost me a fortune!
[KANNA gasps]
[MIO]
Are you okay?
[TAKUYA]
Dude, you're an asshole.
Oh, give me a break, I was only
shaking her off me, that's all.
I paid 800 dollars for this suit
and she was wrinkling the micro
suede. It's dry clean only.
--[YUKI] You're a jerk.
--[rumbling]
[WORKER 11A]
You hear that, Toyotomi?
I think the girl was right;
I really don't like
the look of those clouds.
[WORKER 2B] Welp, it looks
like we'd better call it a day.
[TOYOTOMI]
W-Wait! Y-You can't!
[WORKER 11A] I'm sick of this
lousy job. Let's go grab a beer.
Thanks a lot! Hope you're
happy with what you've done!
Just get the hell
outta here. Now.
There we go.
Those clouds are totally gone.
Like they were never even there.
[MIO]
You're right.
Yuki? Will you take Mio home?
I'm on it! What about you?
I'm gonna walk home with Kanna.
Huh? You're taking her?
[TAKUYA]
Yeah, why?
[MIO grumbles]
Hatano, look,
if he tries anything weird,
you can just hit him.
Okay, got it, thanks.
I would never!
--[TAKUYA] See ya.
--[YUKI] Okay!
[MIO]
See you later.
[KANNA]
Yes, goodbye.
[YUKI] Hey, we should get those
photos developed right away!
[MIO]
Good idea!
So, where do you live?
This way.
It's pretty late. Is it okay?
I don't know what you mean.
Won't your parents be mad?
No, I actually live alone.
Oh, wow, are you serious?
Thank you for helping me
out today. Goodnight.
[HOJO]
Hey! Kanna!
[TAKUYA]
Uh.
I finally found you!
[KANNA]
Good evening, Hojo.
Who's this guy?
I've been a lil' bummed 'cause
you haven't called me up lately!
Let's have fun! Come on.
[KANNA] I'm sorry. I'm not
feeling all that well today.
[HOJO]
Aww, don't be like that now!
[TAKUYA clears throat]
Uh, who in the hell are you?
[TAKUYA]
Just some guy.
[HOJO]
Come on, let's go.
[TAKUYA]
Hey! Get your hands off her!
[KANNA] Arima, thanks, but it's
okay. I can handle this myself.
[HOJO] Listen, kid,
who do you think you are?
Shut up, crazy drunk dude.
[HOJO] Shut your mouth!
You don't know my life!
--I happen to be Kanna's--
--[KANNA] He's not a stranger.
Hojo is someone I know.
Arima happens to be one
of my new classmates.
Ah. Well, I'm glad to hear it.
I thought maybe you'd gone and
made another special friend.
What does that mean?
[HOJO]
None of your beeswax, kiddo!
You got no business
gettin' yourself involved
in other people's
private lives, you twerp.
[TAKUYA]
What was that?
Stop this now! Both of you!
[KANNA]
Let's go. Come on.
[HOJO] Kanna, you can
call me any time, okay?
I'll be waiting.
[KANNA]
Keep walking!
[HOJO chuckles]
[KANNA]
Come in.
[TAKUYA]
Oh, um... I dunno.
I think it's probably
best if I head on home.
[KANNA]
I see. All right.
[gasping]
I'll be okay.
This happens all the time.
You don't look close
to "okay" to me.
[panting]
[TAKUYA] This is just like what
happened in the nurse's office.
Where do you keep
your medicines?
I don't actually have any.
[TAKUYA]
Huh?
[KANNA]
I'm going to rest for a bit.
[TAKUYA]
Mm.
[TAKUYA] It's the exact
opposite of Ayumi's room.
Uh?
[TAKUYA]
Alcohol? No way.
Hey, how ya feelin'?
[KANNA grunts]
I'm feeling a lot better.
I'm glad to hear it.
Guess I should probably
take a shower.
I need to get rid
of all this sweat.
Oh...
[gasps]
You're such a bastard.
[TAKUYA]
Why is he still here?
[thud]
Uh. Oh, no.
[door slides]
[TAKUYA]
Kanna! You okay?
[shower knob squeaks]
[TAKUYA gasping]
[KANNA]
What, is something wrong?
[TAKUYA] No, I just heard
a loud noise and thought
you might have collapsed again.
But... you're safe... Cool.
[KANNA]
I need shampoo.
Uh?
I ran out and I need
to wash my hair.
There's a new bottle under the
sink. Can you bring it to me?
You got it. Be right back!
[sighs] Does she just not get
embarrassed by anything at all?
Uh. Here we go.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[TAKUYA] Here it is!
I'll leave it right here!
[KANNA]
Thanks, I appreciate it.
[sighs] What am I doing here?
Wait, what is this? Uh?!
She was getting money from Dad?
[door opens]
I'm sorry but I wasn't trying
to poke through your things.
I promise.
But these deposits continued
right up until my
dad disappeared.
And you seem to know an
awful lot 'bout my dad,
and Ryuzoji, and the
correction of chaos.
You almost know too much.
Well, I guess,
it seems as though
I need to tell you everything.
But not right now, okay?
I have my own reasons for that.
Kodai gave me
instructions to tell you
when the right time came.
I'll do it then.
My dad did?
So, tell me. Are you planning
to spend the night?
Uh! Spend the night?
[KANNA]
Yes.
That's a weird offer.
You mean it?
[KANNA]
Only if you want to.
It's late and I'd like to
go to bed. What do you say?
[TAKUYA]
I should just head home.
[door creaks]
Did you have a good time?
No, not the way you mean.
Were you waiting for
me out here or what?
Tell me kid, what's the deal
between you and Kanna?
I could ask you
the same question.
What the hell's a middle
aged drunk doing here?
You just like hanging around
young girls or what?
Ha! Whatever. I only have
one thing to say to you.
Stay away from Kanna.
You can talk to her
in class, nowhere else.
[TAKUYA]
Why's that?
[HOJO] Trust me, there are
some things in this world
it's better not to know.
Oh, wait, if you're leavin',
I guess it's my turn now!
[TAKUYA]
Wait just a minute!
I only came out here
to get some air!
[TAKUYA grunts]
[growls]
You're back.
[TAKUYA]
I think I'll stay after all.
Hey, you asleep?
Not yet.
There's one thing
I'd really like to ask.
Okay.
My father... Is he still
alive somewhere?
Yes, he is.
Thanks, Kanna. That's all
I needed to know, for now.
Goodnight, Arima.
[TAKUYA] Are you kidding?
I don't need a new mother!
What, are you in love
with her or something?
She's eight years
older than you.
Hypocrite! You're planning
on marrying your student
who's 20 years younger than you!
[KODAI]
In the face of real love,
something as petty
as age difference
doesn't even factor in.
I think it might be time
to discuss your mother.
I'll tell you everything.
Your mother, Keiko,
passed away years ago.
That is a fact,
carved into history.
However, despite what
most people believe,
not every fact is true.
[TAKUYA]
What the hell's that mean?
Listen to me.
History is not just a record
of changes from the past.
[TAKUYA]
What are you talking about?
[KODAI]
Your mother. She's...
Hold on! I can't hear you!
[whispers] Keiko is...
Dad, what?!
[inaudible]
[gasps]
[chopping]
[KANNA]
Oh, good morning.
Yeah. Morning.
Surprised you didn't try
anything last night.
Whoa, not sure I heard right!
Would you mind repeating that?
What's the deal, do you
not find me attractive?
No, that's not the problem.
When I'm with you,
I feel kinda weird.
What do you mean?
[TAKUYA] Like I've known you for
a long time. Like you're family.
I mean, would it upset you if
you reminded me of a, a mom?
No. It's fine.
If Dad was doing weird
things to you, I'm sorry.
No, he wasn't that
type of person.
Please have faith
in your father.
[YUKI]
I'm so bored.
Yeah, I guess there's
really not much to do
till the photos are developed.
I say we do something
summer-ish.
I need you to define
"summer-ish."
[TAKUYA]
Hitting on girls in swimsuits.
Is that literally
all you think about?
Yup!
[YUKI] But doesn't
the construction mean
the beach is shut down?
[TAKUYA sighs]
Hey, guys?
My dad actually has a private
beach next to a resort.
It sits just outside
of Sakaimachi.
Huh?!
Right, you're family's loaded!
If I were to ask him,
I think he would probably
let us use it for a day.
Are you serious?!
[BOTH]
Yeah!
Hey, you're not gonna tell us to
stay away from the ocean, right?
Since we won't be
near the mountain?
That's right.
All right, then it's settled!
Don't worry. I'll take
care of the tickets!
[KANNA]
Um. I can't really...
What is it, do you not swim?
I can, but I...
[TAKUYA]
Don't have a swimsuit?
No, I do.
Then you should come with us.
It's just... I've been
kind of sick lately.
The thing is, if that's
the case and you're not okay,
we'll feel better
if you're with us.
We won't be able to help
if you collapse alone.
That's true.
I guess you're right.
All right! We're going
to the beach!
Well, so much for hitting
on hot girls in swimsuits.
What exactly were you
planning to do, anyway?
[TAKUYA]
I guess we might as well enjoy
this rich girl's beach
while we can, huh?
[YU-NO] Episode 15: "A summer
that won't come back."