[AYUMI]
I'm so sorry.
Takuya, this is very
difficult to tell you,
but even if the ritual
succeeds, the priestess,
Yu-No, will most likely
be annihilated.
Uh!
Thank you, that concludes
my presentation.
So, what did you think?
Pretty interesting stuff, huh?
So, that means the ritual
we all thought was a lie...
The priestess and the Divine
Emperor's involvement...
It's real. This proves
that all of it was true.
We came here with
one major goal,
which was to stop that
ritual, but now...
[AI] If that happens, I think
you'll have a big problem.
[DEO]
Amanda.
[AMANDA gasps]
--[thud]
--[ALL gasp]
[gasping]
[ERIKO]
Ryuzoji.
You're not getting away!
[AYUMI]
I'm sorry.
Details are hard to predict, but
we know some things for sure.
She'll be sent beyond
the dimensional horizon,
but there's a chance
she'll be able to survive
in another world.
Although, the chance
is one in ten billion.
So small.
Takuya, if the ritual doesn't
happen, then both worlds
will be destroyed,
do you understand that?
It's all up to her!
Only Yu-No can do it!
What do I do, though?
How do I tell her this?
[AYUMI] You'll find a way.
I believe in you both.
[ADVISOR]
The time has come
to finally put an end
to the resistance.
[ALL grunting]
[ADVISOR]
Aim!
--[AYUMI] Stop!
--Fire!
Uh! Divine Emperor!
[ADVISOR] Why would you put
a stop to this execution?
These rebels infiltrated
the hall of memories!
[AYUMI] And that is why
they must survive.
[ADVISOR gasps]
[AYUMI] You learned the truth
when you were there, didn't you?
In the hall of memories.
[REBELS gasp]
If you did, please, help us.
Your world needs you now.
[gasping]
[REBEL C]
The Divine Emperor isn't evil?
[REBEL D] You're saying it
was all some misunderstanding.
[REBEL A]
It's too late for that, now!
[REBEL B]
Leader?
I'm so sorry.
I've been wrong this whole time.
So, things have changed.
The Divine Emperor now
says she needs our assistance
in order to save this world.
I want to help her.
Our goal has always been to
fight for the Imperial City.
I realize this might be too
much to ask, but if you can
trust me again, and I hope
you will, I need your help.
Look, sure, it's a shock
to learn the truth,
but that's nobody's
fault, you know?
Here's the deal, guys, we don't
have time to debate this!
[REBEL D]
We know that, okay?
We're still the resistance,
and our job is to protect
the people here.
Yeah. Besides,
saving the world might
actually be kinda fun, right?
Not like we have
much choice, anyway.
[REBEL C]
We're behind you, Amanda!
[BOBBY] We'll do all we can
to make that ritual happen!
Well, sounds like it's settled.
We're in.
You guys... Thank you!
Papa?
Hey, there.
[YU-NO]
Papa!
I've missed you so much!
Aw, jeez. You haven't
changed a bit, have you?
[YU-NO]
What did you wanna talk about?
Something wrong?
Well, it's...
It's about that ritual.
So, um. As it ends up, the
priestess has an important job.
And, uh, it's, uh...
You see, it's actually
something only you can do.
But, the thing is,
afterwards, you'll, um...
You might not...
Yeah, I know. You're saying
that I might disappear.
What? You already knew?
[YU-NO] Mm-hm. But if
I don't do anything,
you and everyone else
will die, right?
Well, yeah. Unfortunately,
that's the case.
Then this is obviously
something I have to do.
In fact, it seems I was
literally born to do this.
[gasps] Yu-No.
I'm sorry.
You're the one taking
all the risk, here,
and I'm the one
crying like a baby.
[YU-NO laughs]
But I'm not scared, Papa.
Even if it's bad, you'll come
and save me, won't you?
Of course. Uh! Oh, right.
[YU-NO]
Hm?
Take this with you.
How pretty!
It's your good luck charm.
So, if anything happens,
I can come and find you.
Papa. I love you
Love you, too, so much.
[ADVISOR] You went so far as to
ask the resistance for help.
I don't understand.
Why do we need
such tight security?
[AYUMI] Because we'll be
fighting Ryuzoji. Trust me,
normal security measures
aren't going to be enough.
[ADVISOR]
Forgive me, Divine Emperor,
but he just escaped from prison,
do you truly believe he'll
come back here willingly?
I do. I'm certain of it.
Get ready.
Stop there!
[ERIKO]
You won't get away!
[AMANDA]
Can't sleep, huh?
[TAKUYA]
Uh?
Not tonight. Finally gave up.
I gotta say, the view up here
is pretty incredible, though.
[AMANDA]
Yeah. It's kinda hard to believe
that it's all about to
disappear, isn't it?
[TAKUYA] Only if we don't
do something to stop it.
[AMANDA] True. You're right.
I won't let that happen.
The resistance is gonna
do all we can to help.
We have to make
the ritual a success.
[TAKUYA] You're just like her.
Your sister.
When this is over,
I would like to bring some
flowers to her grave.
Yeah. I'm sure she'd like that.
[AMANDA]
I guess it didn't end up
being my last night, after all.
[TAKUYA] No. There won't be
any more "last nights."
You're very committed to your
job, Dimensional Inspector.
Yep, I'm stubborn that way.
I'll follow you anywhere
to bring you down.
[chuckles] I guess I'll
never be safe, huh?
Answer me. Why you annihilated
three event trees?
Talk! Why did you
stop the splitting?
Look, an A-Class dimensional
criminal like me?
We're used to dedicated
agents like you.
We know how to deal
with your kind.
Are you kidding?
That's the reason you wiped
out those timelines?
You let those
innocent people die!
All life is self-serving.
It just so happens
I'm no exception.
Tell me, what's different
about what I do
from the way humans breed
cattle to eat their fill?
Pure evil, that's
the main difference.
I can't let you run
free another second!
[RYUZOJI]
Oops. It's dangerous to show
you too much of my
true form, I'm afraid.
[ERIKO] Oh, please do.
Then I can end this!
[RYUZOJI laughs] I'm not ready
to die quite yet, Eriko.
What you and Abel were
researching together,
the search for the
root of all events,
I happen to be very
interested in that.
No. You can't...
What're you--?
[yelps]
[gasping]
Now then.
[MAN A]
Wow, it's time.
[WOMAN A] I can't believe
it's almost over.
[MAN B]
Our patience and suffering
are finally gonna pay off!
[KURTZ whimpers] 'Kay, now
I'm starting to get nervous.
Oh, yeah? Look at me,
the same as ever!
Huh! That's pretty amazing.
[ASCHE]
Heh! Don't be ridiculous,
you're scared to death.
You think so? Gimme proof!
Go ahead, do it!
It's just obvious.
Really? Well, it's obvious
you're drunk off your ass!
Would you shut up?
I'm celebrating!
[KURTZ] Guys! We're all
friends here, okay?
Look at them.
Some things never change.
That's oddly comforting
right now.
So, this Ryuzoji guy. Do you
think he's really coming?
Yeah, probably.
But I won't let him
stop this. I can't.
[CITIZENS murmuring]
[AYUMI] My people,
we shall now perform the ritual.
The bizarre weather events,
the famines they
caused over time,
and the attacks by
the strange monsters.
We've survived it,
and it's finally time
for all of that to
come to an end.
You have persevered
through this trying time
and endured every
challenge it brought you.
And now the moment has come.
The ritual to bring peace
to Dela Granto begins!
[CITIZENS cheering]
[inaudible]
[gasps]
So, is that...?
It's Mother.
[AYUMI]
Oh, great Grantia! Come to us!
Let your mind enter
into our Priestess!
[gasps] You must be Grantia?
[GRANTIA] Indeed. I will now
disable the bodily functions
of the priestess. This might
hurt you a little bit.
[YU-NO]
All right.
[GRANTIA]
Come this way, then.
[MACHINE] Initiating dimensional
synchronization system.
Eighteen hundred seconds
until complete synchronization.
Sounds like it's going
to take some time.
Yu-No, you can do it.
[BOTH gasp]
The event elements are in flux.
Look!
What is that thing?
[MAN D]
A bird?
[MAN E]
No way.
This is nuts.
I don't like the look of this.
[CITIZENS screaming]
Yu-no!
Wait! What was that sound?
So he's appeared, then.
[MALE GUARD A]
Don't panic!
Everyone stay calm!
[RYUZOJI]
Well, that's a disappointment.
Looks like I didn't even
manage to scratch it.
[gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
Ryuzoji!
So, he really showed up.
That was one hell
of an entrance.
[AYUMI]
Tell me, why?
Why would you stop the ritual?
Why are you eager for the
destruction of both worlds?
Well, perhaps it's because
my life is an eternal one.
So, to me, destruction
is inevitable.
No matter how much
people struggle,
the conclusion that awaits them
at the end of eternity
is unchangeable.
It's simple. I'm just
making that conclusion
come a little bit sooner
for them, that's all.
With dimensional collision,
which is the ultimate
catastrophe.
Truly a pitiful creature.
Living forever has ruined you.
How do you not know?
Life is beautiful
because it's fleeting.
I'll help you.
Someone needs to teach
you that lesson!
[ADVISOR]
Activate the device, now!
You see? We knew you'd
be coming to stop us!
This barrier is strong.
Unbreakable.
You won't be able to leave here.
So, even without a body,
the event collision
will destroy you.
[chuckles]
I always was convinced that
you were a clever girl.
And look, now you've even
managed to take me as a hostage!
Whatever it takes,
the ritual will proceed.
I won't let you touch Yu-No!
[YU-NO] Please, Grantia, can you
tell me what's going on outside?
[GRANTIA] Priestess,
you must focus your mind.
You must try to let
everything else go.
[MACHINE]
Fifteen hundred seconds
until complete synchronization.
[AYUMI] Nothing will come
of further conflict.
If you're willing to be wise
and let the ritual happen,
I promise fair treatment.
[laughs] You are
very convincing.
But you can't hide the fear
in your heart from me.
There are 25 minutes left.
If you really think they'll
all pass without incident,
then you aren't as
smart as I thought.
Also, as the ritual proceeds,
you'll find that the
events of Dela Granto
will become more
and more unstable.
[rumbling]
[MAN F]
What about the ritual?
Go! Let's move!
[MALE GUARD B]
Women and children first!
Ah! Really wanted
the rest of that!
Do you think Ryuzoji
is doing this?
Forget that and focus!
'Cause if you don't--
[BOTH gasp]
What's happening?
Everything's shaking.
Tell me, is everyone in danger?
[GRANTIA] You must focus solely
on the ritual's completion,
not the people. Concentrate.
But they'll die...
[GRANTIA]
Priestess,
you'd really sacrifice
billions of lives
just to prevent the deaths
of a few hundred people?
You're the only one who
can save both worlds.
You know this, right?
Yes.
[CITIZENS chattering]
[grunts, gasps]
[AYUMI] You're trapped.
What do you think
you can accomplish from
within this barrier?
If I'm unable to touch
the priestess herself,
then I'll just have to
find some other method.
Oh, really? Like what?
Behold, my dear.
It's almost time.
[AYUMI grunts]
[AYUMI]
A dimensional rift?
Indeed it is.
Only a few can exist
inside that subspace,
but I have harnessed this one.
Now, bear witness
to their arrival.
[CITIZENS scream]
What are those things?
[KURTZ yelps]
Bodiless creatures!
Amanda! Be careful!
Yeah, I know!
[RYUZOJI]
Come on, now.
Have you ever seen anything
quite this magnificent?
But how? To do something
on this scale...
[RYUZOJI]
I'll give you this:
it's obvious you prepared
for my intervention.
It's just a shame that you
didn't prepare any better.
That horde has lost its home,
so it's up to me to guide it!
Now, go! Go forth,
you lost and wandering souls!
Destroy everything
and bring chaos to all!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[gasping]
Damn it! There're too many!
Take that! Get outta here!
[grunts] Amanda!
What's the plan?
[AMANDA gasping]
We have to fight, but I can't
believe how many there are!
[TAKUYA] Damn it!
We're way too outnumbered!
[MACHINE]
Twelve hundred seconds
to complete synchronization.
How is there still
that much time?
Wandering souls, listen
to my voice, and obey!
[gasps] It looks like they're
after the barrier device!
Oh, no! We have to protect it!
--Right!
--We're on it, Boss!
[grunting]
The disruption is greater
than anticipated.
Its energy is much stronger
than it was 400 years ago.
At this rate, the dimensional
walls will collapse.
[CITIZENS scream]
[GUARDS screaming]
[GUARD B]
What the...?
Holes are opening in space!
[TAKUYA]
Be careful Amanda!
Takuya!
[gasping]
[TAKUYA grunts]
[TAKUYA grunting]
[AMANDA] Let me go!
I'll end up taking you with me!
Don't say that!
I'm gonna save you!
Takuya, it's okay. Just let go.
[gasps] No, don't give up!
I guess... I won't
get to visit her.
My sister is gonna be pissed.
[TAKUYA grunts]
No! Stop this!
Takuya. I really am
so glad that we met.
Thank you for being with
me on my last night here.
Amanda.
Amanda!
[TAKUYA gasping]
Is she gone?
We lost Amanda?
So, she disappeared beyond
the dimensional horizon.
Or something else
might have happened.
She may have been sent to
a different world, like us.
[MACHINE] Nine hundred seconds
to complete synchronization.
Fifteen minutes to go.
I wonder... How many
are going to die?
[gasping]
[YU-NO]
Episode 26:
"A Girl Who Chants Love at
the Bound of This World."