[clock ticking]
[KODAI] It's impossible
to resist causality.
This is the correction of chaos.
It seems that you weren't meant
to be in that world after all,
so a correction must be made.
You will be sent back
to where it all began.
[TAKUYA]
Wait, what are you saying?
It's fairly simple, really.
You'll experience the same
events over again.
Only this time everything
is going to play out
slightly different than before.
Takuya, remember this:
Causality rules over
everything in this world.
To discover its vast and deep
secrets is to explore history.
[TAKUYA]
What does that mean, though?
Hey! Dad!
Answer me! Answer me!
[clock ticking]
[TAKUYA grunting]
Mount Sankaku?
So I'm re-starting from here?
[TAKUYA groaning]
[TAKUYA] It's gonna suck if
I have to keep doing this.
[phone ringing]
Uh?
Hello?
[YUKI] This is your
friendly wake-up call!
From the one who's here in your
hour of need, hero on call,
Masakatsu Yuki!
[TAKUYA] Dude, where do
you get all this energy?
Did somebody wake up on the
wrong side of the bed today?
Cheer up! Summer break
starts tomorrow, Boss!
That's right, it does
start tomorrow.
[YUKI]
Could you not sleep?
You did get a good nap
in class yesterday.
[TAKUYA] Actually. I saw
a pretty terrible monster,
if you want to know the truth.
Whoa, you think it might
be the one from the curse?
Sometimes, and I know
how this sounds,
but I get this feeling that
maybe the old legends
and folk tales are
real, you know?
How are you this excited?
[YUKI] Like, there might be
an entrance that takes you
to some alternate
universe that only opens
once every few hundred years!
Wait a minute. Where are
you getting this from?
It's fascinating stuff, right?
It was in a book I read by
Doctor Kodai Somethin'-or-Other.
--Uh. Boss? Uh, hello?
--[dial tone]
It's fairly simple, really.
You'll experience the
same events over again.
Only this time everything
is going to play out
slightly different than before.
[bell rings]
So it would seem.
Oh, stop it, you're so silly.
[RYUZOJI, AYUMI laughing]
[AYUMI]
Oh, Takuya!
[door closes]
[TAKUYA] Hey. Didn't you two
see each other just last night?
We were supposed to,
but I had something to do
and couldn't make it.
Heh. And I was reduced to
waiting around at home.
Lately, I've been keeping
to the indoors at night.
Scared of the curse,
guess you could say.
[AYUMI]
Oh, come on, you are not!
[AYUMI laughs]
Laugh all you want, but I have
no plans to be the third victim!
[TAKUYA grunts]
[gasps]
[KANNA]
The teacher's not here.
[gasping]
Wait, why's this here?
Excuse me.
[MIO] So, you've finally
revealed your true nature!
What're you talking about?
[MIO] Here I thought
you were just a pervert,
but you're a mega-pervert!
I'm gonna stop you there.
Believe me, I'm the most
straight-laced, buttoned-down
dude you'll ever meet.
Are you being serious right now?
You're literally touching
someone's panties!
Where the heck is
Ms. Eriko, anyway?
Don't ask me.
[MIO] I mean, her clothes
are right there. Why?
How should I know?
Maybe the lucky thing finally
shed her cocoon and flew off.
[MIO]
She's not a freaking butterfly!
And could you please
stop being gross
and put the panties down
while you talk to me?
Fine! Bye!
[MIO]
Where do you think you're going?
[MITSUKI]
Takuya.
Uh.
I need to talk to you.
How has Ryuzoji seemed to you?
Notice any changes lately?
What type of changes?
For example, this is small, but
he used to criticize smoking,
and now he's started
smoking cigars.
[TAKUYA] People pick up
bad habits all the time.
What's the big deal?
It's not just that.
His mother actually came
to me about this first.
[TAKUYA]
"Please, marry my lonely son?"
Stop, don't joke.
[TAKUYA]
Ha, ha. Sorry.
She could see it. And then
I started to notice it, too.
Subtle changes in his character.
There's no denying
that he's different.
You know what?
There's been something bugging
me about Ryuzoji, too.
Have you noticed him talking
to anyone strange lately?
[MITSUKI]
Yes. I have.
[TAKUYA] There's this one
self-proclaimed journalist
named Kaori Asakura
to be careful of.
There's another one besides her.
He's actually hired
a detective now.
[grunts, gasps]
[groaning]
[TAKUYA]
What's wrong?
[MITSUKI sighs]
[TAKUYA]
You okay?
Yeah. It's just a migraine.
[TAKUYA] I talked to
Ryuzoji this morning,
and something felt off.
Wow, you too?
One thing, in particular,
when he talked about the curse.
Laugh all you want, but I have
no plans to be the third victim.
He said the third?
Yep, and as far as I know,
the news has only
reported one victim.
Strange, what are we
supposed to make of that?
Hard to say, but it didn't
feel like he misspoke.
I'm taking my dad's
research materials
to Ryuzoji's house today.
I'll use the opportunity
to check on him.
I appreciate that.
There was no one
I could really talk to
about this. So, thank you.
Please. Let me know if
you find anything.
[TAKUYA, YUKI sputtering]
[YUKI] I can do this,
I can do this, I can do it,
almost done, ha, ha, ha!
[TAKUYA, YUKI]
We're done!
[ERIKO] Once you turn
those in, you can go.
[BOTH]
All right!
[BOTH laughing]
[YUKI]
Huh? You really have to go
to Ryuzoji's house
right now, Boss?
'Fraid so, I'm takin'
him my dad's stuff.
[YUKI] Well, You're
a lot braver than I am.
That mansion of his
totally creeps me out.
You coward.
I want to go, too!
I mean, it's only fair
since he promised me
before that I would
get to see his tapestry.
[TAKUYA] Look, I'm just
going to take some stuff,
and this one's all
I need to carry it.
Wait, did you say
I'm going with you?
[MIO] It would be awkward
for me to visit him on my own.
So, this is a good
chance for me to go!
Well, I don't mind you coming if
you feel that strongly about it.
[TAKUYA, MIO, YUKI gasp]
You wanna come, too?
I need to head home now.
[TAKUYA] Aren't you at all
curious about Ryuzoji's house?
Everyone's talking about
it 'cause of the curse.
He smells different.
Different from everyone else.
[BOTH]
Uh?
Ryuzoji is not the same.
[TAKUYA, MIO]
Uh...
Hatano can be kind of
tough to talk to, huh?
She's pretty intense,
it's true. So hot.
She seems to be avoiding
people deliberately.
But yeah, she's hot!
[BOYS]
Like, really, really hot.
Wow, what a shock that the boys
are into the mysterious beauty.
[doorbell buzzes]
I stand by it.
This place is terrifying.
[door creaks]
Well, hello, young people,
is there something I
can do for you today?
I brought the documents
that I was asked to bring.
I'm Arima.
Pardon?
[TAKUYA] Um. I called here
a little bit earlier.
Oh, dear, I'm so embarrassed.
When you get old, you forget so
much, everything's a surprise.
Do come in, won't you?
[UME] Goodness, it's a little
bit chilly today, isn't it?
Come on, stop walking so weird!
I'm trying but there could
be a wildcat or something,
you don't know!
Or even better,
there might be an alien.
[gasping] Boss, look over there!
[TAKUYA]
What is your problem?
It's just a rotten,
old storehouse. Shut up!
The mansion was originally
built 400 years ago,
and then the entire place was
completely remodeled.
It looks like it's in
pretty bad shape, though.
It's strange, isn't it?
Almost as if the storehouse
had traveled back in time.
[UME] Now then, let me guess,
you've come here to see my son?
[TAKUYA]
Uh. Yes, that's right, we have.
Except, that man
isn't my son anymore.
He's changed.
A mother sees these things.
[TAKUYA]
Hm?
I wonder. Have you children
heard this old saying.
I've pondered it lately,
"the swallows and sparrows
know not the thoughts
of geese and swans."
[ALL]
Uh...
[laughs] You should see
the look on all your faces!
[door slides]
Mother? What are you
talking about out here?
Oh! Uh, forgive me, dear.
You have to know I didn't
mean any harm by it!
Oh, please, forgive me!
[UME screams]
Well, welcome to the center
of the curse, kids.
I apologize if Mother
frightened you at all.
She has Alzheimer's
and doesn't seem to recognize
her own son anymore.
I didn't realize.
You're not very much
different in age than Ayumi,
isn't that right?
So, that's not something
you'll have to worry about.
Right. I guess.
[YUKI]
This place is so huge!
Or maybe it just looks that way
because there's no furniture.
I've gotten rid of everything
that isn't directly involved
with my research.
I don't even have a bed.
Where do you sleep
if not in a bed?
[RYUZOJI]
On the floor, of course.
[YUKI] That sounds
pretty uncomfortable.
I can't sleep in a soft bed.
I feel like I'm floating.
It's far too hard to relax.
[RYUZOJI]
This is the tapestry.
[MIO]
Whoa...
[TAKUYA]
Wow.
[YUKI]
It's enormous!
Is this piece from
400 years ago, too?
Probably. It's been here
for many, many years.
But it might have
come from overseas
and been brought over
here 400 years ago.
So, maybe it's even older.
[laughs] Chip off
the old block, huh?
You're exactly like
your father, you know.
Kodai made the same observation.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[YUKI] Whoa, it looks like
the people are on fire.
[MIO] You can almost
feel their suffering.
[TAKUYA]
Is it symbolic of something?
Maybe there's some
kind of hidden meaning.
[YUKI]
Oh, yeah! Cool!
[MIO] That structure kind of
reminds me of a church.
[TAKUYA] Yeah, it definitely
feels religious.
[YUKI] So, in that case,
do you think this bright light
is God punishing mankind or
something crazy like that?
[MIO]
Huh, maybe.
What sin would they have
committed, do you think?
Thank you for those
very interesting opinions.
I will take them
into consideration.
I'd love to sketch it.
Would you mind if I take some
time to do that while I'm here?
[RYUZOJI] Of course not!
You seem to like it quite a lot.
Yes. It's wonderful!
Actually, to be honest,
I didn't care for the tapestry
much when I first saw it.
I can see why. Looking at it
kinda kills your appetite
for anything fun at all.
However, once Kodai
demonstrated an interest in it,
I came to see the
tapestry in a new light.
Because of him?
Well, yes, you
have to understand,
I was well aware of the
strength of Kodai's intuition.
I think I'd like to talk with
Takuya in private, if I could.
Is that all right?
Of course! I'll stay here
and finish my sketch.
And I'm gonna hang out with her.
Excellent, we'll go
to my room, then.
This might come as a surprise,
but I've always wanted
to talk with you like this.
[TAKUYA]
Yeah, me too.
You remind me so
very much of him.
Of the Kodai Arima
I remember so well.
[TAKUYA]
I have a question.
Go right ahead.
Well, I've wanted to ask...
What was he
researching with you?
[RYUZOJI]
Mm. That is quite a question.
I'll have to go back a pretty
long way to explain that.
Kodai and I were classmates.
We were in college together.
Even then, we shared
a common goal.
We both wanted to discover
the hidden elements of history,
the things that would never
be put in any textbook.
Years later, Kodai was banished
from respectable
academic society.
[RYUZOJI] But I remained
extremely impressed
by his Four Hundred
Year Cycle theory.
[RYUZOJI]
So, naturally, I invited him
to come conduct his
research at my university.
Kodai focused on
Sakaimachi as a place
to research both the Four
Hundred Year Cycle Theory
and the Takanoamahara people.
[RYUZOJI] And then he met a
physicist, Yurika Imagawa,
who was investigating
the fact that the magnetic
and gravitational
fields of Sakaimachi
were different than
in other places.
We were engaged in nearly
constant heated debate.
Professor Imagawa was focused
on pursuing a unified theory,
based on quantum mechanics.
I ended up choosing
humans themselves
to be my research subjects.
Do you know what
your father picked?
Kodai dared to
choose immortality.
That was his research theme.
Immortality?
[RYUZOJI]
Do you find that surprising?
Well, I mean, I knew
he was a little nuts
but I didn't think
he was that crazy.
[RYUZOJI] Tell me this--
when you really consider it,
what do you think the dawn
of the universe was like?
Or the dawn of this world,
if you prefer.
[TAKUYA]
Wait, what's this about?
[RYUZOJI]
I'm interested in your opinion.
For instance,
one prominent scientist
claims that the universe
has always existed.
[TAKUYA] That doesn't
seem realistic to me.
"Eternity" isn't real.
[RYUZOJI] Of course, one other
popular theory is the big bang.
[TAKUYA] Right. The one
that says a small,
high-density nucleus exploded
and became the universe.
[RYUZOJI] What are your
thoughts on that theory?
[TAKUYA]
Well. I mean,
it's at least better
than "eternity," right?
[RYUZOJI]
Okay, then, tell me this.
Before the big bang,
what existed around
the "small nucleus"
you speak of?
I... Yeah, I have no idea.
That's our job as researchers.
We theorize about things.
We study inexplicable events
and prove our theories.
But back to the subject at hand.
When we were working together,
Professor Imagawa's research
notes spoke of a woman.
According to the professor,
she lived in reclusion not
far from Ken-no-Misaki.
She was blind, and she
had the most perfect,
shining gold hair complimented
by beautiful, pale skin.
Her name was Keitia.
which was later
changed to Keiko.
And this young woman
was your mother.
[TAKUYA gasping]
[YUKI] The boss said
it was supposed
to be symbolic or something.
[MIO] If you look closely
and listen carefully,
you might be able to discover
a message from
those in the past.
[RYUZOJI]
Through his research,
Kodai ended up growing
very close to Keiko.
They fell in love and soon
after, you were born.
So strange. I barely have any
memory of my mother at all.
[RYUZOJI] It was easy
to forget she was blind.
Her lack of sight didn't
seem to hinder her.
She helped Kodai
with his research
and took care of you
when you were sick.
[TAKUYA]
Sick?
[RYUZOJI]
That's right.
You seemed to get fevers all the
time when you were very young.
I suppose that I could
send you after Kodai.
It's one option, anyway.
[MIO]
Hey, this is an entrance, right?
[YUKI] Yeah, now that you
mention it, it seems obvious.
For some reason, it reminds
me of something else.
[YUKI]
Of what?
[MIO]
Mm...
Somehow, we've managed
to go off-topic.
[TAKUYA gasps]
[RYUZOJI]
Takuya Arima.
Do you think I could
ask you a question?
I'll answer if it's
something I can tell you.
Be honest.
Did Kodai give you anything
at all before he disappeared?
[TAKUYA]
Mm! I have no idea.
As you're aware, he pretty
much up and died on me.
[RYUZOJI] Then did he leave
you anything? Anything at all?
Maybe something you
discovered later?
What are we talking about?
Uh.
[TAKUYA gasps]
[RYUZOJI] For example,
perhaps something similar
to a time machine?
[TAKUYA gasping]
[RYUZOJI]
Well?
No, he didn't.
[TAKUYA]
This is weird. I'm dizzy!
See, my theory,
is that Kodai found the truth
hidden here in Sakaimachi.
That's what I believe,
at any rate.
What's wrong?
I can see you sweating.
No, I'm... I don't know.
[TAKUYA] What is this?
What is he doing to me?
I know you must have a
device in your possession
which Kodai left
specifically for you.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[RYUZOJI] So, I want you
to give me what you have.
[TAKUYA grunting]
Now! Give it to me!
[TAKUYA groaning]
He was actually able
to resist the Niarb?
Is this because of the factor?
[knocking]
[MIO]
Sir?
[YUKI]
Hey, Boss?
[MIO]
You all right?
This was fun, but it's
time to call it a night.
[TAKUYA gasps]
[MIO]
Thank you for having us.
My pleasure, come back any time.
I would like to say it again.
I couldn't be more sorry
about Kodai, Takuya.
He could still be alive.
You know how persistent
the old man always was.
Not here, though. I bet
he's somewhere far away.
[RYUZOJI chuckles]
Those are the same eyes.
Sometimes Kodai would look at me
with exactly the same
expression on his face.
[YUKI]
Man, looking at that tapestry
for so long kinda made
my blood run cold.
[MIO]
Yeah, me too.
What were you and
Ryuzoji discussing
for all that time
together, boss?
Nothing much, just immortality.
[MIO, YUKI]
Huh?
[MIO] Really? It's not
like he's that old.
[YUKI]
Right?
Did you consider the words
I spoke to you before?
I hope you've at least given
them a bit of thought.
Uh...
Do you mean the thing you said
about the swallows
and the sparrows?
So, you haven't yet. I guess
I should've known that. [laughs]
Very well. Let me ask you
another question.
[ALL]
Huh...
Have you not noticed the thing
that exists within this mansion?
My ears can hear it
even if yours cannot.
Listen, it's the
breath of 400 years.
[YU-NO] Episode 8: The Swallows
and the Sparrows Know Not."