[APE MONSTER A roars]
[sighs]
[TAKUYA] There sure are a
lot more of these, lately.
Hey, I'm home from work!
Uh. I'm startin' to
sound like my dad.
Sorry, but this was all
I could manage to find.
Food is getting
harder to come by.
Think it'll last us
a few days?
[SAYLESS]
Mm.
[TAKUYA]
How's she doing? Asleep?
[SAYLESS]
Mm.
Heh, heh. Let's do our best
not to wake her up, then!
[TAKUYA]
Dad.
I followed the
clues you left me.
I made it to Dela Granto.
[TAKUYA] There are no clocks
or calendars in this world,
but I think it's
been about a year.
[baby cries]
[gasps]
[TAKUYA] Right, right, I get it.
I know what you're thinkin'.
It's about the baby, right?
[wails]
[TAKUYA] This big stork
dropped it outta nowhere!
Okay, yeah, that's a lie.
[TAKUYA]
It's just what you thought.
Sayless and I have a daughter.
Come on, a man and
a woman, all alone.
Of course it's gonna happen.
Her name is Yu-No.
Sayless chose it for her.
The weird thing is,
I've heard that name before.
Yu... Yu-No.
[cooing]
[TAKUYA] Is there some kind
of crazy connection?
[TAKUYA] Sayless and I exist
humbly and peacefully,
living together off the land.
It works well.
We have a good life.
[door creaks]
[TAKUYA laughs]
[TAKUYA] I can't imagine a world
without Sayless and Yu-No, now.
[TAKUYA] So, to protect
the family I'd grown to love,
I took up the job
that Ailia used to do.
[TAKUYA] They just keep
coming, don't they?
What the heck are
these things, anyway?
[yells]
[TAKUYA] Heh, heh. Whatcha get
for messin' with the Kendo club.
[MONSTER A]
Divine Emperor.
[TAKUYA]
Mm?
Whoa, it talks?
That was weird.
[cries]
I never realized before
how much babies cry.
Here you go.
Ha, ha! She's so cute!
Ow, ow, ow! Hey, no biting.
[cries]
[TAKUYA gasps, chuckles]
[TAKUYA]
Sorry.
Looks like she's enjoying it.
Hey, now, Yu-No. Stop hoggin'
the boobs, I like 'em, too!
Sorry. It's seriously like
I've become my dad.
[TAKUYA]
I've thought about it.
Several times, I've
thought of going back.
Of course, I haven't
forgotten my promise
to bring the psychite
back for Kanna.
Before she died, Ailia told
me that the holy stones
were mined at the
quarries in the desert.
I think... those holy stones
might be psychite.
I've attempted to cross
the desert several times
in order to find out
if that's true.
But the more I try,
the more I realize
escaping from this harsh land
is basically impossible.
[gasps]
Tell me something.
You came from the
Imperial City, right?
How did you make it
across the desert?
Without even a map or food?
[SAYLESS]
Mother's guidance brought me
to the end of the world.
In order for me to summon
the goddess Grantia.
I don't pretend to understand,
but when a priestess hears
the will of her goddess,
it must be amazing.
Sorry. I really shouldn't
have asked.
It doesn't matter to me
what your reasons were.
[gasps]
[TAKUYA] I'll always be here.
I'll keep you safe.
[GUARD A]
Go! Go after them!
[GUARD C]
You're not goin' anywhere!
[GUARD D]
Get back here!
[GUARD A]
Don't just stand there!
[GUARD B]
She's getting away!
[GUARD D]
Move, move!
Watch that side!
Keep her surrounded!
Surrender, right now!
[GUARDS gasp]
[MALE B]
Wait, damn you!
[MALE A]
Fire your arrows!
[MALE B]
She's getting away!
[GUARDS grunting]
[MALE C]
You can't run forever!
[MALE A]
Don't lose her!
[MALE D]
What do we do?
[MALE B]
Great, now we've lost her!
[footsteps]
[YU-NO]
Papa, there you are!
[TAKUYA yelps]
[YU-NO]
Hey, are you taking a bath?
Can I get in there with you?
Daddy needs a little privacy
while he takes a bath, sweetie.
[TAKUYA]
Yu-No seemed to grow up so fast.
A little too fast,
if I'm being honest.
Uh! Whoa, did you see that?
She's standing on her own!
[TAKUYA] It was impossible to
believe how quickly she grew.
At just three months old,
she was running,
and then...
Uh? Good morning, Yu-No!
Mama! Papa!
I love you both!
I love you both so very much!
Whoa. She's talking already!
Sayless, did you hear that?
I love you, Mom!
[TAKUYA] Yu-No started
talking just six months
after she was born.
[TAKUYA] One year later, she
seemed about four years old,
and four years later,
she was about 16.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[TAKUYA]
Now I'm afraid she's gonna be
older than me
before too long.
[YU-NO]
Papa, can I ask you a question?
Why is it you won't
take a bath with me?
[TAKUYA]
Uh...
Do you not love me anymore?
Are you kidding me?
Of course that's not true,
what gave you that idea?
Good, then give me a big hug!
After all, you give Mom big
hugs all the time, right?
I've seen you together!
Uh! Well, I mean, we do
a bit more than hug.
Hug!
Ah. Hug. Hug!
I'm glad you and Mom
are here for me.
I'm a very lucky girl.
[gasps] Hey, Yu-No.
[YU-NO]
Hm?
[TAKUYA]
How would you like a friend?
What is a friend?
Can you eat it?
[TAKUYA]
Nope, you can't eat friends.
Let's see, they're
kind of like... Uhm...
Comrades, I guess!
Comrades?
Yeah! The ones you
hang out with.
The ones who get you through.
They're always there,
through thick and thin.
And you laugh and cry together.
[YU-NO]
Papa?
Uh. Sorry, what was
I talkin' about?
[YU-NO] We were talking
about eating friends.
No, we weren't.
You can't eat them,
friends are kind of like--
--[TAKUYA] Uh?
--[YU-NO] Huh?
Wait here for me, okay?
It's dangerous, so stay put.
[whimpering]
Great.
Begone, you!
Stay away from me!
There. I knew it.
They really can talk!
[yelling]
[TAKUYA grunts]
Papa, no!
[TAKUYA]
Don't come any closer!
[yelps]
[yells]
Papa!
No matter what,
I won't let her hurt you!
[hisses, groans]
That's right--
stay right where you are!
Stop, please!
[KUNKUN chirps]
[TAKUYA gasps]
[whimpering]
What?
[gasps]
So, what's that lizard thing?
This is my child.
Never mind what it looks like.
It means more to me than
anything in the world.
Where did the two
of you come from?
[MONSTER GIRL A]
We just managed to flee
from the Imperial City.
Meaning, you crossed
over the desert?
[grunts] I apologize for
my violence before, but...
If you're a parent,
you should understand!
[chirps]
Sorry, love. I couldn't
protect you this time.
I was looking forward
to watching you grow up.
So be strong, my love.
[chirping]
The baby's so sad.
Did its mommy die?
Yeah.
[YU-NO laughs]
You're cute, aren't you?
Aww, look at you,
sweet little thing!
Careful, Yu-No, that
thing might bite you.
[YU-NO]
Nah, I'll be fine!
Hey, Papa?
[TAKUYA]
Hm?
Uh... I know that look.
I'm pretty sure I know
what's coming, but...
Can we-- Can we please
take it home with us?
That's what I thought.
It's okay, right?
I'm positive Mom will say yes!
Well, how do you
plan to feed it?
Uh! Right, I guess I don't
have any milk to give.
Hey, maybe Mom can, though!
No way! Those boobs are mine!
What about yours?
Actually, they have been
feeling a little full lately.
But that's impossible!
Can we keep it?
I promise I'll work real hard!
Right, Kunkun?
Kun!
Kunkun? What is that?
[YU-NO] That's its name! It
makes that sound when it cries.
Okay, fair enough!
At least it's better than
"Spot" or something--
[groans]
[YU-NO]
Kunkun, let's go!
[KUNKUN]
Kunkun!
[YU-NO]
Hey, let's race to the house!
--[YU-NO laughs]
--[KUNKUN chirps]
[TAKUYA]
Well, whatcha gonna do?
Uh?
[gasps]
Humans? Hey!
Hey! Can you hear me?
Come back!
I don't get it.
What was that about?
Please. It's been forever since
I've seen any other people!
So I guess you can't
sleep, either?
What is it?
[SAYLESS gasping]
Look, everything's fine.
I told you I'd protect you.
[door clicks]
[BOTH gasp]
Papa. Momma.
What do you need, sweetie?
Can't you sleep?
[YU-NO] It's just that I...
I want to be with you.
We're always with you,
sweetheart.
That's forever. I promise you.
Can I?
What do you think?
You heard her, come on.
[YU-NO]
Yay!
[YU-NO laughs]
It's been so long since
we've slept together!
That's true.
[YU-NO] Hey, what's wrong, Papa?
You look disappointed.
Nope. I'm fine.
Oh, I know! You wanna be
alone with Mom, am I right?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
where'd you get that?
Because you like to hang
out and eat together!
Uh... Well, that's true.
Hey, Momma!
Do you love Papa a lot?
[SAYLESS]
Mm.
I do, too!
I think I might even love
him as much as you do!
Isn't that cool?
[ADVISOR] You saw a strange
human at the border?
[MALE E]
Indeed.
We happened to find him
while pursuing livestock.
He seemed to be living there.
That's strange since
only the knight Ailia
should be at the border now.
What would you like
to do, your Highness?
[EMPEROR] There's still
the matter of the Priestess.
Investigate immediately.
[MALE E]
As you wish.
Just look at it!
Isn't it so cute?
[TAKUYA yawns]
Yeah. I can't deny it,
it's pretty darn cute.
Hey, now!
Hey, Momma!
How many wild strawberries
do you think I should bring?
[gasps]
I see.
[YU-NO]
Okay.
I'm gonna go play
with Kunkun, now!
'Kay? Come after me
once you get our lunches!
[door creaks]
[YU-NO]
Come on, let's go, Kunkun!
--[KUNKUN] Kun!
--[YU-NO laughs]
Who knew those two would
be best of friends?
I'll go bring us
a bunch back!
So look forward to it, 'kay?
[TAKUYA] Slow down! You keep
that up, you'll get too tired!
[YU-NO]
I'll be fine!
[TAKUYA] Oh! Nice job!
You found a good-lookin' bunch!
[YU-NO]
They look so yummy!
[KUNKUN]
Kun-Kun!
[TAKUYA] Should we try a few?
We won't tell your mom.
--[YU-NO] Yeah!
--[KUNKUN] Kun!
[roars]
Not again...
Yu-No, I need you
to go and hide.
Uh-huh.
I'll kill you dead.
[gasps] So, yeah,
they can definitely talk.
Hey! Why do you guys come here?
You shut up!
'Kay. Guess we're
not talking, then.
[yells]
[APE MONSTER B groaning]
Imperial city.
Another one?
He came from Imperial city, too?
Whatcha doin'? Are you
still hungry, Kunkun?
[chirps]
[TAKUYA]
If I ask those people,
maybe I can cross
the desert, too.
But what about my life here?
What about Sayless and Yu-No?
Hey, what's wrong? Eat too much?
No.
Huh? Did something happen?
Papa, listen. I have
something to say.
[TAKUYA]
You know I'll hear anything
you have to tell me, princess.
It's just that... my heart
feels like it's fluttering.
Did you fall in love with
a prince or something?
That's not it.
Then what is it?
Never mind, it's not important.
Forget it.
Little guy really does
eat a lot, doesn't he?
At this rate, we're gonna
be out here all night.
[TAKUYA]
Uh...
That's...
They came back here to see us!
Come on, let's go!
Not yet. Look at him,
he's still really hungry.
[TAKUYA]
All right, I'll go alone, then.
Be careful on your way back!
'Kay.
[TAKUYA panting]
[GUARD F]
Find out if she's a virgin!
[GUARD G]
Do not resist us!
[GUARD F]
Hold her down!
[GUARD G] Priestess or not,
the rules are absolute!
[TAKUYA]
Sayless!
[GUARD G]
So, it was a man!
Takuya!
[GUARDS gasping]
[MALE H]
She's speaking, too!
Takuya, run! Get out of here!
[YU-NO] Episode 20:
"Into the Rafaelo Desert."