[STUDENTS murmur]
[MIO]
How could you?
[TAKUYA]
Hm?
I never thought you were
capable of something like this.
[TAKUYA]
U-Uh!
Move it!
[STUDENTS gasping]
Hey, what's your problem?
Yeah cut that out, Arima!
You can't let people post
whatever dumb gossip they want.
I dunno, isn't that
freedom of expression?
If that's the case, then what
are they so afraid of?
No one gets freedom
from responsibility.
If you got somethin'
to say to someone,
then you should say
it to their face!
I refute that claim.
Take Watergate, for instance.
The truth never
would've gotten out
if someone didn't leak
info anonymously-- Uh!
So the pen is mightier
than the sword?
Wanna put that to
the test right now?
I think I'll pass
this time, thank you.
Okay, show's over, get to
class! Shoo! Shoo! Go on!
[STUDENTS chattering]
Since when does
he care so much?
He must have a crush
on Shimazu, huh?
[FEMALE STUDENT D]
Yeah.
Damn it. Who did this crap?
[MALE REPORTER A]
Mayor Shimazu,
what do you have to say about
the recent allegations?
[KAORI] There are rumors that
you've been involved
with Geotech's construction
permits and land buyouts.
Is there any truth to that?
I have no comment at this time.
Please Send any
inquiries to my lawyer.
I'm surprised she has
the guts to even come here.
She probably thinks her dad
can bribe his way out of this.
This'll all blow over soon.
Don't let it get to you.
I expressed concerns about
Father's business deals, myself.
But the only person I spoke
to about that was Arima.
So you're saying you think he's
the one who posted those papers?
[MIO]
Yes, probably
[clattering]
Uh.
[YUKI]
From now on, come to me instead!
Huh?
If you have a problem,
then I can help!
Um, thank you.
[door slides]
[BOTH gasp]
Mio. Can we talk?
[MIO]
All right.
I didn't put those papers up.
And I didn't tell
anyone what you said.
[MIO]
I don't really care.
[gasps]
After all, it's not as if
I have a right to complain.
Everything written
there is true.
I shouldn't be stubborn.
I simply can't go to
this school anymore.
Mio...
So, this is goodbye.
Uh. Wait. Hold on!
Did something happen?
You wanna talk?
[TAKUYA]
Mitsuki.
[MITSUKI]
Mm. If she's acting like that,
sounds like she still
thinks you did it.
[TAKUYA]
Maybe.
[MITSUKI] Hm... Does that
mean I have a chance?
[TAKUYA]
C'mon, I'm being serious here.
Okay, okay fine.
[TAKUYA] Did you see
anyone fishy last night?
Or catch anyone checking
out the bulletin board?
[MITSUKI]
Nope. No one.
[TAKUYA]
Oh, well.
[MITSUKI]
It's strange, though.
Never mind how they
got the info--
Why would they post
something like that
on a high school bulletin
board of all places?
What were they trying
to accomplish?
D'you think they were
trying to get at Mio?
[MITSUKI] Well, she's pretty,
she gets good grades,
and she's the teacher's pet.
So you mean anyone
could be jealous.
[MITSUKI] Maybe, but surely you
can narrow the list down.
Okay, let's think.
They'd have to have
something against Mio.
They'd have to be connected
to the high school somehow.
And maybe they would benefit
from Mio going away?
[MITSUKI]
Are you talking about me?
Because it sounds like it.
That's fair. I mean,
we both love you.
Last night, when I saw
you there at school,
you looked so happy together.
What if I was jealous?
Even if you were, you wouldn't
do something so cowardly.
I know you, so I'm
confident in that.
[MITSUKI] Love makes you
do strange things.
Just ignore me. I'm sorry for
running my mouth like that.
I know we don't have that kind
of relationship anymore.
Well, I'd better
getting going now.
Can't keep Ryuzoji waiting.
[TAKUYA] Thanks. You were
a big help, as always.
You come to me anytime.
I'll see you
'Kay.
[REPORTERS chattering]
[REPORTER B]
Where is he?
Mister Shimazu is working.
He hasn't returned.
Then when's he coming back?
[REPORTER D] How do
you know he won't skip town?
[MAID A]
He's a very busy man.
It's not unusual for
him to return late.
[MIO grunting]
[YUKI grunts]
Yuki.
You feeling any better?
[KANNA]
Much better. Thank you.
Hey, Eriko? Kanna's here?
Another one of those
weird fevers?
Yeah. I still don't know
what's causing them,
so I'm not much use.
Take care, 'kay?
Once again thank you.
[door slides]
[ERIKO]
By the way,
did you see those papers
posted on the bulletin board?
Uh-huh. For a second,
then I tore them down.
And I'll tear 'em down
again if I have to.
I see.
There were rumors that you
were the one who put them up.
You don't strike me as
the gossiping type, though.
I wouldn't wish that sort
of thing on anyone, okay?
Especially not Mio.
Of course.
I'm sorry you got wrapped up
in all this gossip as well.
You're a good kid.
I'm lucky to have a teacher
who understands me.
But what if Mio actually
got involved in something bad?
You wouldn't just stand by and
watch, right? You would stop it?
That's the least
I could do for her.
I figured. Sounds like
something you'd say.
I am worried that this stuff
with her dad is just
gonna get worse.
And if that happens, she really
won't be able to come to school.
Frankly, we're already
past that point.
Wha...?
Following a report from
the local prosecutor,
Mayor Shimazu has announced
his resignation.
The city council has stated
their intent to withdraw
their support from the Geotech
Construction project.
Additionally,
the lightning stri--
I got a call about
this a second ago.
Mio's transferring to
a school in America.
[gasps]
[phone rings]
[TAKUYA]
Hello?
[AYUMI]
Uh. Takuya?
[TAKUYA]
Hey, Ayumi.
We ran into some complications
here at work.
I don't think I'll make
it home till later.
Why don't you order out
for dinner tonight, okay?
[TAKUYA]
Yeah, no problem.
Don't stress yourself
out too much.
Things sound like they're
gettin' pretty crazy.
[AYUMI]
Don't worry.
The executives are the
ones under fire, not me.
There's nothing I can
do about it, either way.
I'll just have to wait
and see how it plays out.
I didn't catch it all,
but it sounds like the news
was talking about the
lightning strike stuff, too?
Also under control.
I spent a lot of time talking
to the affected families.
It's slow-moving, but we're
headed in the right direction.
That's great.
[AYUMI] Anyway, instead
of worrying about me,
maybe you should
look out for Mio?
Uh. Okay, but how do
you know about Mio?
Remember? You brought
her to the house one time.
She was really cute,
so she stuck out in my mind.
I thought you two
might be going out,
but I didn't want
to say anything.
[TAKUYA]
Uh... No, we're just friends.
[AYUMI]
Really...?
[TAKUYA]
Yes, really.
Then, as her friend,
try to do what you can to
help her out, all right?
[TAKUYA]
No problem.
[AYUMI]
See you later.
[TAKUYA]
Yeah.
[TAKUYA] It's probably better
if I go see her in person.
[TAKUYA]
Well, so much for that.
Not even my charming
personality will get me in.
Hey there! So we meet again!
It's cause you stick
your nose everywhere.
Now, be honest with me.
Did you know the
mayor was corrupt
before the news even broke?
Maybe.
[KAORI]
Heh, heh, heh.
I had a feeling
that was the case.
[TAKUYA]
Hm?
[KAORI]
Over here.
What is it?
This scandal is turning
into a disaster.
And it's not going to be pretty
for your classmate, either.
If you had come to me first,
I would've made sure the
story was handled better.
[YUKI]
Boss!
[panting]
Is something wrong?
[YUKI]
It's Shimazu. We need to talk!
She ran away from home?
[YUKI] Yeah. I heard
from one of their maids.
[YUKI] I'm a friend of Mio's.
Is she home?
No, she... Uh. Keep this is a
secret, but maybe you can help.
I'm useless, but I thought
maybe you'd know what to do.
It hasn't been that long--
I doubt she's gone far.
Let's split up and search!
[YUKI]
Boss...
I'll head over to the school,
then look along the coast.
'Kay. I'll check around
downtown, I guess.
Good! We'll meet in front
of the school in two hours.
[YUKI]
Got it!
Not at school, huh?
[MITSUKI]
Takuya?
Is something wrong?
[MITSUKI]
I see. That's not good.
[TAKUYA] No kidding.
Anyway, I need to get going.
[MITSUKI]
Wait. Let me help you find her.
Just tell me where
to go and I'll do it.
Listen she was my student
when I was a substitute.
I need to do whatever
I can to help her, 'kay?
I mean, sure!
'Kay, then. Why don't you search
the area around Meiunji park?
Will do.
[TAKUYA]
We're supposed to meet
in front of the school
in about an hour.
[MITSUKI]
You got it.
[TAKUYA]
Thank you!
[groaning]
[inaudible]
[TAKUYA]
Hey! Mio!
[KANNA]
Arima.
[TAKUYA] Kanna.
Have you seen Mio anywhere?
[KANNA]
Unfortunately, yes.
I tried to warn her,
but as usual,
she wasn't willing to listen.
She went to a dangerous place.
[TAKUYA]
Ah, don't tell me...
[KANNA]
Be careful.
[gasps] Yeah, sure! Thank you!
[YUKI]
Huh? Ms. Ichijo?
I heard the story from Arima.
I'm here to help.
[YUKI]
I see.
So I take it you
haven't found Shimazu?
[YUKI]
'Fraid not.
[TAKUYA]
Hey!
Uh. What's up?
[TAKUYA]
I know where Mio went.
Well, let's hear it, then.
[panting]
She's Inside Mt. Sankaku.
Why would she go in there
at a time like this?
She's leaving soon.
She probably thought this was
her last chance to explore.
It's just like I thought.
There was a cave down here
and nobody even knew?
Mio's the one who found it.
[YUKI] Does that mean
she went in there alone?
[TAKUYA]
We better hurry.
You're right, time is a factor.
It hasn't been made public yet,
but they'll be resuming
construction at the work
site tomorrow morning.
After all those accidents?
The point is, the police
could get involved.
That's bad for everyone.
Then we'll just have to settle
this mess before morning.
You've explored old ruins
before, correct?
Sure, a long time ago.
'Kay, then. You and I
can search inside.
Yuki will hold down the fort.
Wait a second! Take me!
I can't just wait out here!
Sure you can. Someone has to,
in case this all goes south.
That's not what I mean!
What I'm trying to say is...
...this is all my fault!
I'm the only reason
we're out here!
So, please! Will you just
let me help you fix this?!
I see. Well, that's
one mystery solved.
Those papers on
the bulletin board
at school this morning...
were mine!
[gasps]
[YUKI] I was walking in front
the nurse's office last night.
And, just by coincidence, I
heard you and Shimazu talking.
Then, I just... I lost it.
I don't know.
My head was messed up.
I'm sorry.
[YUKI cries]
You're not crazy. You just let
jealousy get the better of you.
[gasps]
[TAKUYA]
I can't believe this.
[YUKI gasps, groans]
[TAKUYA]
You're better than that.
[YUKI]
I know, it was stupid.
I thought Shimazu was over you
and maybe she would
love me instead.
So when all of that
came crashing down,
I didn't know what to do.
[coughs] Heh, but that's
a crappy excuse, I know.
I'm sorry. That's all I can say.
[YUKI cries]
[TAKUYA]
The inside of Mt. Sankaku
has never been
investigated before.
So we don't know what could
be waiting for us in there.
In fact, we don't even know
if Mio is safe or not.
But listen. All that matters
is that we bring Mio back.
And we will! Then, as soon as
we do, you'll apologize to her.
You got that?
Got it.
Sorry, Mitsuki. Looks like
I'm gonna have to ask you
to stay out here.
You better not screw this up.
[gasps]
Give it your best.
You still trust me?
I'm just giving you a chance
to clean up your own mess.
Thanks, Takuya. I mean, Boss!
Would you stop calling
me that already?
Listen, you two.
If run into anything dangerous,
then get out immediately.
Like we said before, tomorrow
morning is our deadline.
If you're not back then,
I'm calling the cops.
Understood.
You ready?
Yeah.
I didn't expect the air
in here to be so damp.
[YUKI gasps]
It's an underground stream,
not sea water.
You're really good
at this stuff, Boss!
Guess that's no surprise,
since your dad was an explorer!
[TAKUYA]
Historian, actually.
[rumbling]
[gasps]
Something moved.
It's quiet now.
You think Shimazu might
be in trouble down here?
No point in discussing it.
Let's hurry.
What's that?
Looks like a cage.
[TAKUYA]
Get back.
O-Okay.
Just don't do anything stupid.
Have some faith, will ya?
[gasps] I think I did
something stupid!
[TAKUYA]
That didn't take long!
[BOTH gasping]
There's no way Mother
Nature made this, right?
It's like a machine.
[YUKI] But everything in here
is carved out of the mountain.
What's going on?
[YUKI yelps]
[TAKUYA]
What is this place?
[YU-NO] Episode 10:
"Feelings Overlapping."