[TAKUYA]
Mitsuki...
Well, as soon as she wakes up
we can ask her what happened.
Don't we need to take her
to a hospital or something?
[ERIKO]
Nah, I've cleaned her up.
Her life's in no danger.
[TAKUYA] Mm? Wait a minute.
Where're you going?
[ERIKO]
The storehouse.
Gotta get rid of the body.
Hey, uh, about Ryuzoji.
Why're you investigating him?
Don't worry about that;
I'll tell you later.
You'll need to learn the truth
at some point, anyway.
Please take care of Ichijo.
Be careful, though,
the Niarb is still in effect.
I got it. Thanks.
Why does this one feel different
from the other parallel worlds?
[MITSUKI groaning]
[TAKUYA]
You awake?
Huh?
Well, it's about time,
Sleeping Beauty.
I was about to see
if a kiss might work.
You know, like a prince
from a fairy tale.
[MITSUKI]
Where am I?
Bed, with me.
In my head, anyway.
In reality,
it's the nurse's office.
But what happened to me?
You got into a bad accident
in Ryuzoji's car.
Accident? No, this is dangerous!
[groaning]
You hit your head,
you should take it easy.
I bet there are painkillers
in the First Aid box.
[TAKUYA] Great, lots of
bandages, very helpful.
[TAKUYA]
Uh. The power's out?
Crap...
[rustling]
[MITSUKI yells]
[TAKUYA groans]
[laughing]
You're gonna die. Get ready!
[gasps]
Well done, Ichijo.
Thank you, I'm so glad
you're pleased.
No! Ryuzoji!
[RYUZOJI] It's useless.
Don't bother resisting.
At least I don't have
to use mind control
to get someone to agree with me.
[RYUZOJI] Hm... You know you and
your friend should be far more
careful when meddling in affairs
that are quite beyond you.
[TAKUYA]
Eriko?
[RYUZOJI]
Don't be alarmed.
She and I are actually
old acquaintances.
I mistakenly thought I was safe
after Abel's death, but then,
I didn't expect her to come
after me the way she did.
Who's Abel?
I should've kept my mouth shut.
Go ahead, show it to him.
Yes sir, as you wish.
[TAKUYA]
Wait. Is that...?
[RYUZOJI]
Yes, it is.
It seems clear that you
know what this jewel is.
Which means... Kodai must have
given you the Reflector Device,
just as I thought in
the very beginning.
I've wanted it for
myself for so long.
[TAKUYA growls]
[RYUZOJI]
It's wasted on you.
You, who still know nothing
of its actual power.
Don't you think that at
the very least, it should be
in the possession of someone
who knows its true worth?
So, tell me. Where is
the Reflector Device?
Heh. Actually, it's a whole
lot closer than you think!
[BOTH gasp]
You're gonna die. Get ready!
[TAKUYA grunts]
[TAKUYA]
Stop it!
[MITSUKI grunts]
Mitsuki, you gotta
wake up! Please try!
[MITSUKI gasping]
Takuya.
You're so good to me.
Are you back? That you?
[MITSUKI chuckles]
[MITSUKI grunting]
Quit it! Seriously!
[MITSUKI laughs]
Takuya. Time to say goodbye!
[MITSUKI yells]
[MITSUKI groans]
Hey, didn't know
you could fight.
I heard some noise, so I figured
I should come and check on you.
Didn't I tell you to be careful?
Yeah, and I did what you said!
Why else do you think I'm
here from a parallel world?
Interesting. Well, it looks
like this route might've
been the right one, then.
Listen, can't you just tell
me what's been going on?
What is it that Ryuzoji's
been planning?
Why did he do this to Mitsuki?
Let's head to his mansion.
I'll tell you more there.
[TAKUYA]
Hold on.
Is it cool to move the body
before the cops come?
Look, I get it,
but there's no time.
[TAKUYA]
Uh.
[ERIKO]
Here we go.
Okay, so what's up
with this wall?
I can tell the coloration
is different.
You're right. So, knock it down.
Uh. Why me?
Just do it. We're in a hurry.
First it's trespassing,
then I move a corpse...
Might as well finish the day
with some property damage.
[TAKUYA grunting]
[TAKUYA gasps]
[TAKUYA]
What the hell?
[ERIKO] Look closely.
Do you notice anything?
[TAKUYA] I can't really figure
out what I'm looking at.
No torso! That's just
limbs and a head.
[TAKUYA]
No way.
[ERIKO]
That's right. The monster seen
during the uproar
about the curse.
This is Abel's body, with
Ryuzoji's soul stuffed inside.
[ERIKO] As for Ryuzoji's body,
it's been taken over
by something else.
Uh? Are you kidding?
That's really possible?
Yes, it is, I'm afraid.
For a Class A Dimensional
Criminal, anyway.
They're beings of pure thought
who travel between
different dimensions.
[TAKUYA gasping]
[ERIKO] Well, I'm sure it's
asking a bit much for you
to believe me immediately.
But at that time, I still
hadn't become aware of the fact
that he was actually
something else.
You haven't failed me yet.
I believe you.
I've been investigating
Ryuzoji for some time.
I'm hoping that
we can arrest him.
Arrest him? Okay, c'mon,
just who exactly are you?
[ERIKO]
A long time ago--
Well, actually, it was the
future, from your point of view.
There was a man named Abel.
He was a scientist.
And he and his assistant spent
their days doing research.
The two of them studied
the science of events.
They researched
the tree of Vrinda.
[ERIKO]
It's basically a diagram.
It shows all the potential
events that can result
from one single cause.
Endless possibilities branching
out from one source.
The nodes on the diagram
split like the roots of a tree,
stretching out according
to a set of rules.
This sequence of events
becomes a new reality
in and of itself, creating
new sequences in turn.
That's where the parallel
worlds come from.
Abel was curious and
performed an experiment.
He went searching for the root
of all the events that
have ever taken place.
Are you sure? It seems too
dangerous to go to the root.
There's nothing to worry about.
It's only my mind that
will be traveling backwards.
I don't know.
Come on, relax.
I'll be fine as long
as you're with me.
That's 2 to the 50th event
splits. Looking good so far.
Now, he's reached
the sixth layer.
[ABEL] So much light. Infinite
events are passing me by.
He's reached the fourth layer.
Incredible.
Tell me what you see.
Ha!
The truths of the universe!
They're here.
[alarm blares]
[ERIKO] What's this? Abel,
stop! It isn't what you think!
[laughs]
[CRIMINAL 13A screams]
[gasps]
[ERIKO]
No. Look at these readings!
A Class A dimensional criminal?
[CRIMINAL 13A yells]
[ABEL groans]
What is this thing?
And why is it going after Abel?
Two to the 96th
event splits passed.
Approaching the first layer.
Abel, you have to run!
Or else you won't make it back!
[ABEL groans]
[CRIMINAL 13A growls, yells]
[ERIKO]
Abel! Are you okay?
What happened to the criminal?
I'm just fine. Don't worry.
Continue the experiment.
I'm so glad!
Wait, you're not...
Is something wrong?
[ERIKO] No. You're not...
You're not Abel!
[ERIKO yelps]
You're right, but I've
inherited every one
of this man's memories.
My, my, you're not
easily fooled, are you?
I guess that's because
you loved each other.
Abel...
This is a good body. I like
it very much. I'm taking it.
[ERIKO] As easily as that,
the dimensional criminal
commandeered Abel's body,
then it fled here
to the parallel universe
you and I are in right now.
At that point, he switched
from Abel's body to Ryuzoji's.
Abel's soul is out there,
stripped of its body,
wandering event space
with no way back.
[TAKUYA] I hate that tapestry.
It always creeps me out.
Here it is.
[TAKUYA gasps]
Just through here.
Hey, the device!
Look, it's going nuts!
Of course. It's resonating
with what's up ahead of us.
[TAKUYA]
What is this?
[ERIKO] Something that
allows one to move between
parallel worlds.
It basically serves
the same purpose as
your Reflector Device.
[TAKUYA]
It's wrecked.
[ERIKO]
It was probably destroyed
entering this dimension.
That's why he approached you,
pretending to be Ryuzoji.
I'll admit, that's an
entertaining theory.
Of course, there is
the inconvenient issue
of it being a total fantasy.
Ryuzoji.
The bones in the storehouse wall
and the rumors about the curse.
Not to mention, this dimensional
transportation device.
All these fragments fit together
and lead us to one conclusion.
Ryuzoji!
You're officially under arrest!
Heh. You wanted me so badly you
became a dimensional inspector?
Look out!
[TAKUYA]
Uh.
[RYUZOJI]
Hmph.
[TAKUYA yelps]
[TAKUYA]
How did he not just die now?
To a being pure of thought,
the body is just the vessel.
However...
There are limits to what
a vessel can take!
[RYUZOJI grunts]
Get ready, this is it!
[gasps]
No! Eriko!
It appears we now
have the advantage.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[RYUZOJI] Ichijo. I want
you to tie them both up.
Right.
[groans]
[RYUZOJI]
Is something wrong?
I'm fine. Sorry.
I'll do it now.
[TAKUYA grunting]
Such a fool.
[MITSUKI groans]
[TAKUYA]
Mitsuki!
This body is about done for.
No, wait!
[RYUZOJI grunts]
I'm sorry.
You were trying to help.
It's okay now.
Everything's okay.
No, it's not okay!
You're dying because of me!
Can I tell you something?
Throughout all of this,
I was always thinking of you.
[TAKUYA]
Hello? Hello?
You there? U-Uh.
You know I've always loved you.
I think you knew that.
The jewel.
Take it with you.
I know you're going to
need it on your travels.
Takuya, keep following
your path, okay?
And don't be afraid.
[gasps] Please, no.
No, you can't go!
Stay with me, okay?
Do you hear me?
Come on! Please don't go!
[ERIKO]
It's useless.
Going to another parallel
world won't bring her back.
Nothing will. This conclusion
was already ordained.
The hell does that mean?
It means that it doesn't matter
whether she was shot or not.
The outcome would be the same.
The flux in the event
potential is just too high.
U-Uh...
Haven't you traded
goodbyes with her before?
You have, haven't you?
[gasps]
[ERIKO] You would be better off
forgetting about Mitsuki,
you hear me?
She's already doomed.
She'll be lost.
[ERIKO] It's one of those events
that can't be avoided.
The kind people
refer to as "fate."
So, my saying goodbye
to Mitsuki is fate?
[ERIKO]
Yes, and it won't change
no matter what parallel
world you're in.
That can't be right.
I don't believe it
and I won't accept it!
[gasps] Not again!
It's the forced
revision of causality.
The correction of chaos.
[TAKUYA grunts]
[ERIKO]
Just in case,
I think I should erase your
memories of me and Ryuzoji.
If he thinks you might
know who he really is,
then he's gonna go after you
even in the next world.
You ready?
[TAKUYA]
Yeah.
[ERIKO]
Time for you to hop universes.
What will you do
when you get there?
What I have to.
No matter what fate
awaits me up ahead.
You'd better believe I'll
keep following my path.
[KODAI]
Takuya.
[clock ticks]
[TAKUYA]
This again.
Remember the simple truth that
causality guides everything.
[TAKUYA] Sorry, I'm not
interested in your lectures
right now. I'm sick of this.
Even if it is my fate, saying
goodbye to the people I love...
There's one who will show you
which path you should take.
That person's name
is Kanna Hatano.
[TAKUYA]
Kanna? Really?
And as soon as you're able
to gather the eight jewels
together, a new path is
going to be opened to you.
[TAKUYA]
A new path?
[KODAI]
Takuya. I'll be waiting for you.
[TAKUYA grunting]
Here again, huh?
Oh, right.
[groaning]
[TAKUYA] I'm getting sick
of these headaches.
[TAKUYA]
Hey, Kanna!
[KANNA]
Mm.
I'd like to get to know
you a little better.
A lot better, actually.
[YU-NO] Episode 14:
"The Transfer Student's Friend."