[WITCH 8A]
Don't you think it's strange
how most people don't
seem to recognize
that the extent of a
leader's abilities
places limitations
on the capabilities
of the group being led?
But you get what I'm
talking about, right?
Yeah. Loud and clear.
"Frustrating" doesn't
even begin to describe
what it's like to talk to people
who never understand you.
It's ludicrous, isn't it?
Well, I have no desire to play
with those people anymore!
You can't touch tar without
your hands getting dirty.
So, I'm at a loss.
Maybe everyone else has their
own issues to deal with.
Stop it!
Apparently, I'm not
getting through to you
like I thought I was.
Or are you one of them?
Hey, give it a rest
for a second!
[WITCH 8A]
"Give it a rest"?
I see.
I thought you were an ally.
But you chose to be my foe!
Uh.
[gasps]
What about you, huh?!
You did the same thing!
[HARUTO grunts]
It's fine.
I still want to help her.
♪♪♪
[MAN 8A muffled]
Watch it! Get outta the way!
[BOYS]
You can't play with us, Haruto!
[FEMALE STUDENT 8A]
Jeez, you're such a pain.
[MALE STUDENT 8A]
You're bugging us!
[FEMALE STUDENT 8A]
You're a total drag.
It's time to pay your dues!
[SUONO'S PARENTS] I thought you
were a little smarter than that.
[HARUTO gasping]
[splash]
[muffled] I'm glad to
see you're awake!
Are you feeling all right?
[muffled] Huh?
[muffled] Do you
feel better now?
[muffled] What'd you say?
[KANZAKI]
Two witches have appeared now.
That's nice and
glamorous, isn't it?
[HARUTO]
Yeah, I guess so.
But, one of them has
a strong personality
and is super aggressive.
You like strong young
women, don't you?
[HARUTO laughs]
[HARUTO]
What the--?
The stronger one may be closer
to the end of her rope
than you might think.
Why don't you offer
her a sympathetic ear
to bounce ideas off of?
And? The other one?
[HARUTO] Ah. I wasn't able to
talk to her for some reason.
[KANZAKI]
Hm?
It was bizarre.
I couldn't hear her.
But, there was something
else strange.
You couldn't hear what
she said to you?
Or any other sounds,
for that matter?
Nope. And now that
I think about it,
I don't think she could
hear my voice, either.
Then, you'll both need
to devise a new method
of communicating
with each other.
Anything coming to mind?
[inaudible]
[muffled] Are you
feeling all right?
[MARI] He can't communicate with
someone inside a dream?
What's with that?
I have no idea. That's why
I was running it by you.
[MARI]
Mm-hm. Well, a dream
is a sort of world of thoughts,
wouldn't you agree?
They could be on such
different wavelengths
that they simply have no
common point of reference.
If they're able to meet one
another in the dream world,
I'd say their wavelengths
are close enough
to fine-tune the difference.
[KANZAKI]
Hm?
[gasps]
[phone vibrates]
That lady at the end of the bar.
[MARI]
Huh?
"Deaf Vocal"? What's that?
Excuse me. What is this
"Deaf Vocal" thing?
[MAN 8B]
Hm?
♪♪♪
[CROWD cheers]
Deaf Vocal is a band,
and they specialize in songs
for deaf audiences?
♪♪♪
She sings in sign language?
One could say the energy
of her thoughts
was conveyed through
her motions.
Her thoughts... in motion?
[KANZAKI] Her hearing
impairment could be due
to a number of factors.
Genetics, or perhaps the result
of an injury or illness.
Still, she works her
hardest, every day.
[inaudible]
[sirens blare]
[rumbling, muffled chattering]
[RESCUE WORKERS muffled shouts]
[MAN 8C muffled]
Hello?
I've been stuck in the rubble
for an entire week!
And nobody even realizes it!
[gasps]
Tell me. Are you deaf?
Yes, I am, but only
back in the real world.
[HARUTO]
But while you're in this world?
It's not a problem.
[HARUTO]
So, you can hear?
I wouldn't call it "hearing,"
but I can clearly understand
the things you're saying,
without having to
watch your mouth.
Having to watch... my mouth?
[WITCH 8A]
Mm. While I'm in this world,
it's easy to say exactly
what I think.
I can clearly convey
whatever thoughts I please,
and can listen to others
without impairment!
It means that everything
I want can come true!
Besides, you take the form
you want in this world.
You what?
You don't want to wake up from
this dream any more than I do.
Somewhere, deep down inside,
that's what you're feeling.
Uh! No way.
You're wrong about that.
I'm going to wake up
soon enough
and return to doing
the things I want
when I get back to
the real world.
And what do you want to do?
Well, I'm not sure.
Is it the kind of thing that
you're only able to do
when you're in the other world?
Then that's a different matter,
for when you're actually there.
You just need to focus on
doing whatever you can
when you're here.
What I can do while I'm here?
You've already started
spontaneously.
You're sitting here,
listening to all of my griping,
taking my abuse while I work
out all of these feelings.
Well, I'm here because I knew
that you needed my help.
It was almost like I could
sense that your heart
was ready to shout out.
That's just the thing.
You were the only one I've met
who could hear my heart.
Huh? Just what are you saying?
You mean that nobody else other
than me could hear you
whenever you tried
to speak to them?
[WITCH 8A] Yes. Isn't that
right, Mister Cat?
Oh, you mean him?
Hey! You couldn't hear
what she was just saying?
Who would choose to
listen to a stranger
empty out all of their
emotional baggage?
People subconsciously choose
to only hear the frequencies
that suit their wants and needs.
And that's why, or at least
that's my best guess,
for why others can't
hear what I say.
I think I'm starting
to understand.
You've experienced it for
yourself in this world,
haven't you?
In what world? It wasn't here.
It was here.
[gasps]
You couldn't hear her.
You couldn't tune into
her sound, could you?
I called out to you
with my other voice.
A voice from another you?
You mean her?
You can have everything
you could ever want
here in the dream world. So why?
I already told you,
we each assume
whatever forms we wish
here in the dream world.
That's what this is about?
None of that seems right to me.
I wanna hear everything
you've got,
and continue to do my best to
help others when they need me!
Yes. Talking with you has
already helped me plenty.
And probably not just me,
but others, I'd imagine.
However, I think I know
who you're really helping.
That would be yourself,
wouldn't it?
Do what? Help myself?
Right. I think
it's pretty clear.
You came trying to help me,
because you're really
helping yourself, aren't you?
You didn't come here
because you needed help...
...but rather, you gave it.
[HARUTO] So, I'm helping you
because I want to help myself?
That's strange. I've never
even thought of that.
[HARUTO] But I have no control
over the things that happen.
There isn't any way
to help myself.
And that's why you
help others, isn't it?
--Huh?
Up to and including
this moment,
a number of people have
needed your help,
and have approached you for it.
It all makes sense, really.
You naturally attract them.
I do?
[WITCH 8A]
Where others refused to listen,
you took what they said
and accepted it.
[WITCH 8B] However, you refuse
to accept the positive aspects.
Which means you can't hear
the things that would
give you courage, or maybe
even cheer you up.
Wait, are you implying
that I can't hear when
others cheer me on?
Come on now,
that can't be right!
I've heard them thank me.
And yet somehow, you're thinking
"poor little me," don't you?
Self-deprecation?
Because I won't accept
unearned praise?
You were surprised when you
learned that I was in a band,
even though I was deaf,
weren't you?
Well, to be honest...
Still, I want to get
out there and sing!
I want to be an actress, too.
And to walk the runway!
If you heard that
for the first time,
would you still laugh it off
and give me the old
"that dream isn't possible
for you" nonsense?
[WITCH 8A]
You couldn't do that, could you?
You've seen for yourself.
You know that this dream
isn't impossible for me.
It's not as if everyone
has to follow the same path
in life as each other.
But if you can
understand an inkling
of the ideas I've been
sharing, then I'll be glad.
I'd also be glad if the
anime and movies I love
had closed captions.
[WITCH 8A]
Mm-hm.
You'd be glad?
[WITCH 8A]
Mm!
[WITCH 8B]
Mm-hm!
By learning about the uniqueness
of another person...
By changing your point of view
just the slightest bit,
your feelings toward that person
allow for a closer connection.
Getting to know one another,
listening intently,
without judgment, for their
inner voice to speak.
All it takes is opening up
the doorway to your heart
just a little bit wider,
and you change.
[water rushing]
[wind rustling]
[birds chirping]
[horn blares]
[CROWD chattering]
[WITCH 8A]
I'm glad.
[HARUTO]
Hm?
[WITCH 8A] I'm glad. Thankful I
got the chance to meet you!
[WITCH 8A laughs]
[gasping]
I'll see you around!
Huh?!
[HARUTO gasping]
She certainly was a preachy
little thing, wasn't she?
Whether you took the things she
said as overly preachy or not,
surely would depend on how
wide you open the doorway
to your heart. Makes sense,
now doesn't it?
[KANZAKI]
According to the research
of American psychologist
Doctor Albert Mehrabian,
the input we receive from
communication with others
is 55% based on
facial expressions.
Whereas vocal pitch,
volume, and tempo affect 38%.
While the actual meaning of
the words that are spoken
accounts for a mere
7% of the total.
Huh. The words mean that little?
It's not just the words we use.
We need to acknowledge the
importance of various forms
of communication
that connect us all.
[MARI] Like how they say a
person's innermost feelings
are directly reproduced
in the range
of an analog record
that people can't hear.
I've been wanting to ask.
What are you doing?
And why'd you bring
a guitar in here?
I went to a live music venue
for the first time in a while,
and it gave me the urge to play.
Geez, turn the sound off
while you're tuning!
But I can't tune it unless
I make it make some noise!
It's not until a person's
heart produces the sound
of their actions that they can
start tuning themselves.
But still, you have to cut out
the sounds that interfere.
[LILY]
Would you like to know
what your favorite idol
is really like?
I bet you would!
[EGOS]
Tell me, baaa!
[LILY]
Next time's dream is:
"Idols Don't Go to
the Bathroom!"