♪♪♪
Hi, everyone!
You having fun?
[ALL]
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Of course! My world is a
realm of absolute amusement!
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER]
Great news, everybody!
Some new friends have
come to play with us!
Hey! Who the hell are you?
Where are we?!
What's happening?!
Let's play!
[MACHO 1A] What're you
plannin' to do to us, lady?
Hush, my sweet.
Ah! No! Please don't
turn me into food!
Don't worry.
I won't eat you.
Look around.
Absolute cuteness is everywhere!
And you will become
something to match the rest!
Otherwise, you and I couldn't
be friends, little guy.
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER] Behold.
I am the Witch of Thunder.
Relax. You're going to have
so much fun here with us!
Now, let's all move on
to the next game!
[MONSTERS growl]
[MONSTERS scream]
[laughs] All done!
Who's the strongest
in the world?
[ALL]
The Witch of Thunder is!
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER]
Thanks, everyone!
You're the best, too!
The fun's just getting started!
Onto the next game! [laughs]
[gasps] Can't believe I fell
asleep fully dressed.
[footsteps]
Nope. Still dreaming,
so it would seem.
If it's still a dream,
then let me sleep.
[gasps]
[gasping]
Hello!
Huh?!
Wanna play... together?
You and me?
Well, that depends. Play what?
Oh. Whatever I want, whenever
I feel like it! Heh!
I have no idea what
that's supposed to mean.
It's okay if you don't know
what's going on, silly.
I know exactly
what I want to do!
All right, fine then.
Where do I need to go?
This way.
[groans]
[LILY]
No!
[HARUTO grunts]
What attacked me? What was that?
A witch.
A witch?
Come. Now.
I've been waiting.
Just for you.
[HARUTO]
Huh?
If you don't help,
I'll surely disappear.
Please, Brother.
"Brother"?
[gasping]
[roars]
[HARUTO yelps]
[grunts]
Man! That dream was weird.
[HARUTO]
A red door?
Hey you!
You called me "Brother."
What gives?
Hello again!
We were interrupted.
Hey, the door's gone! [gasps]
[HARUTO whimpering]
[BOTH scream]
[HARUTO panting]
Say, odd wardrobe choice
for a place like this.
What would a cat know?
[BOTH gasp]
My, this is an
unpleasant situation.
It's a dream, right?
Things'll be just fine.
No. You came in through
the red door, didn't you?
Yeah, with the eye.
The land of dreams is strange.
When you die here,
you could die in real life.
What?
[KANZAKI]
Yes, for example,
you wouldn't want to get
flattened by them.
But it's a dream!
Anything can happen,
because it's a dream!
So what.
This your first time
in the dream world?
It would be for most people!
[BOTH]
Mm?
Hurry, Brother! This way!
It's you!
Uh. Hey, who the hell
are you talking to?
[gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
What?
Who would dare defile
my dream world?
[BOTH groan]
Hey. What are you?
That door just now.
How'd you make it show up?
It wasn't me. It was that kid!
What kid? Where?
The one who opened the door.
She saved us.
Okay. I have no idea
what you're talking about.
You didn't see her?
How am I supposed to see
something that isn't there?
But she was there!
A girl with long, white hair.
Oh? White hair?
[gasping]
Yes, I see.
[KANZAKI]
This is interesting.
Very, very interesting.
It's quite the phenomenon,
in fact!
Oh, yeah. Coming from
the anthropomorphic cat.
Okay, other than the white hair,
what distinguishing
characteristics did she have?
How was she dressed?
Her gown was all white, just
like her hair, but her eyes...
I don't remember!
We just met!
Ah, yes, understood.
I think I might know who she is,
from your description.
If so, this is a huge discovery!
A miracle. An epiphany!
That girl in white you met
must be Lily, I'm certain of it!
Lily?
In my time researching
the dream world,
the girl in white has always
been a titillating side note,
as she resurfaces
again and again
in literature and art
across the various
dreamscapes I've experienced.
Word has it that some
researchers were able
to establish direct contact
with the girl known as Lily,
just as you have.
"Word has it," huh?
If you say so.
It's an unexpected delight
to have crossed paths
with you, my friend!
I'm certain it will
give momentum
to my dream world research!
Hm... Hey, what's your name?
Oh, yeah.
Haruto Tsukishiro.
Haruto Tsukishiro!
I'm Katsumi Kanzaki.
I'm the leading
contemporary authority
on dream world research.
And you're a cat.
The feline form before you
is merely my avatar
in the dream world.
You're in the presence
of an incredible genius,
I'll have you know.
[HARUTO]
If you say so.
And what's this "dream world"?
Wow. I guess you really
don't know anything.
About what?
This place! That's why
you've got your own face on.
The hell are you talking about?
What's wrong with my face?
This is the dream world.
A dimension chock
full of witches.
A witch.
Yeah? Witches, huh?
Stop!
Don't touch it.
You'll be accessed
by the witch of this realm,
if you're not careful.
What?
[KANZAKI] I research the evil
influences witches have
on the dream world, and their
effect on the real world.
And I fight day and night
to undo the damage
they're causing in
the waking world.
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER]
Find it.
Find whatever's been
defiling my dream.
[laughs]
Where are you going?
I want to get out of
here, and quickly.
[KANZAKI]
Wait a minute, Haruto.
You won't be able
to get anywhere
without a little help from me.
Oh?
You came into the witch's
world through a red door,
but the only way to leave this
world is through a blue one.
So, where is it?
Tracking down the blue
door of this realm
is a whole other adventure,
my friend!
What'd I expect from a cat?
Haruto Tsukishiro!
You don't have to call me
by my full name.
Let's join forces to
solve the mysteries
of the dream world together!
You're the only person I've
ever met that could see Lily.
Something tells me she's the key
to finding an explanation
for the dream world.
Which is why I require your full
cooperation for my research!
Uh-huh.
And what do I get out
of this partnership?
[KANZAKI]
Huh?
I just wanna leave this
crazy place. Nothing else.
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER]
I found you.
[BOTH gasp]
[screaming]
[KANZAKI]
Run!
We've gotta find that blue door!
[KANZAKI] It'll be game over
if the witch catches us!
Then that's it. I'll go to her.
Uh! Wait, what're you saying?!
Ow, ow, ow.
This is where I met
Lily for the first time.
Oh, so that's your plan.
Yo! So you wanted to play?
I sure hope you know
what you're doing.
Aw. I tried to get you to
play with me earlier,
but instead,
you let go of my hand.
But I changed my mind,
and I also brought a friend.
Hello.
Neither of you is very cute.
Let's fix that.
[BOTH grunt]
Huh! It went straight
to my hips!
Okay. I didn't expect this.
[STUFFED ANIMALS laughing]
See? You're much cuter now!
We'll have so much fun together.
From now on, you'll be my pets!
Have you seen Lily yet?
Nuh-uh. Keep quiet
about that for now.
Okay.
You're bossier than I expected.
What are you two sweetie-pies
whispering about?
[KANZAKI]
Just the standard dessert
teddy bear gossip, madam.
What's this "madam" nonsense?
Oh, she might kill us
if we offend her.
But this is all just a dream.
Plus, last time,
Lily came to my rescue.
This is your big plan?
Why you got caught by
the witch on purpose?
Bingo.
[KANZAKI] You shouldn't be
so reckless, you know.
[HARUTO] It'll be fine.
We're just playing some games.
Are you talking about me?!
[BOTH gasp]
You guys were talking about
me just now. I know it!
No, you misunderstand.
I know you were
talking about me.
Just like the others.
Everyone talks about me.
They all just assume I'm a
boring-as-vanilla-
little-good-girl.
But I'm not as good
as they think I am!
Some people just make
wild assumptions.
You certainly don't
seem good to me.
Hey! Don't make her mad!
Come on, this is weird.
I mean, why are we discussing
if she's a good girl or not?
Who cares!
Yes, but what is "good"?
The very concept is
steeped in relativity.
Much akin to the supposed
interest of single women
in eligible bachelors
at dating mixers.
You mean cats have
dating mixers?
Catnip &amp; cocktails?
I only look like a cat
in the dream world!
You're boring.
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER gasps]
You're totally boring.
That wasn't fun.
What?!
[HARUTO grunting]
We're finished.
You're no fun.
Time to die!
I won't let anything keep
me from having fun!
[KANZAKI screams]
Brutal! [gasps]
Here you go. I'm done.
Share!
Whatever shall I do with a
back-talking little bear?
Take a nibble?
Oh! Not scared?
Maybe a little,
but it's just a dream.
Fine.
Then I'll do this to you.
[groaning]
[gasping]
[STUFFED ANIMALS laughing]
[HARUTO]
It's a dream! That's all!
This is just a dream!
[HARUTO gasps]
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER]
It's play time!
Just kill her.
What?!
[LILY]
Look.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[YOUNG MAN 1A]
You know.
I think I'm startin'
to fall for you.
Huh?
Wanna go out some time?
Just you and me?
Sure.
Huh? What, seriously?
Yes. I'd like to
do that, please.
Come on! What a bore!
I lost, you guys.
Come on out!
[YUKO gasping]
[GIRL 1A]
Really, Yuko?
I can't believe you got
all serious about this.
I thought you'd be more frigid,
and say something like,
"I'm not interested.
I'm sorry." You know?
Who would've guessed you
were so desperate for a man?
This whole thing was
just a game, Yuko.
This is lame!
How much did I lose, you guys?
What a crock!
You should've turned me down!
You're totally boring!
[YUKO whimpers]
Oh, look, she's crying.
[LILY]
She was a straight-A student,
and helped her parents with
chores around the house.
She tried to keep up the image
of being a serious,
distant girl.
She bound herself
to this perception.
But the more she tried
to be the person
others expected her to be,
the more she felt like
she was suffocating.
She went to sleep.
[HARUTO]
She went to sleep?
[LILY] All of the witches in the
dream world have been stricken
with Sleeping Beauty
Syndrome in the real world.
This is why the witch
must be defeated.
So she'll awaken from her sleep.
I don't understand!
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER laughs]
[HARUTO groans]
Game set and match.
Ah, I feel better.
Who's the mightiest witch in
the whole world, my darlings?
[ALL]
The Witch of Thunder is!
Is this really what
you wanted to do?
What did you say?!
Your game. It's boring.
This is my world,
so I can do whatever I want
in it, you understand?!
As long as I'm having fun,
then everything's fine!
It's boring, and cold.
I don't know why you
wanna stay here.
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER]
How dare you?
[HARUTO] This is a pathetic
"dream world," if you ask me.
The whole thing seems
kinda thrown together.
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER]
Dreams are random!
There are still tons
of things I like here.
It doesn't matter!
But, you're still all alone.
[gasps] That's what I like!
And I'm not causing problems
for anyone, am I?
You don't know how tiring
it is to be the girl
everyone expects me to be.
I'm not allowed to fail!
It's too much pressure.
I really want to be spoiled.
To have my way, but I can't!
That's why I felt like there was
no choice but to bind myself.
At least I have some
control in this world.
I can do what I want
when I like!
[HARUTO] Is that everything
you've got to say?
[gasps]
Yeah? Then it's my turn now!
You're wasting your
life in here.
All this talk about
binding yourself
trying to make people
feel sorry for you!
You've got it all wrong.
That isn't the way BDSM
is supposed to work!
You don't know
anything about me!
Now shut your stupid mouth!
When you say it like that,
I believe you.
No one expects you
to be perfect.
It's okay to be
more laidback.
Believe me, it's a
lot less stressful
when you can just shrug it off.
It's easier that way. I know.
Laidback, huh?
I could never allow
myself to do that!
Don't be so hasty
to write it off.
Give it a try, and you'll
start feeling better.
[gasping]
First off,
we'll just skip school!
Does that sound good?
After that, we can go
do something fun.
Really?
Really.
I give you my word.
Now, open your eyes.
Oh, man. I didn't say anything
about making all of your
clothes disappear!
[gasps]
I'm very sorry.
It didn't hurt, did it?
It was a dream.
It didn't hurt at all.
I wish we'd met long ago.
[HARUTO]
You mind if I ask your name?
[YUKO]
Yuko Sakurabe.
[gasps]
Man. I had a dream I got eaten.
You did get eaten.
That's why.
So then, you did this?
I hope I wake up soon.
I've got things to do.
Yes, well. I'm thinking
more and more,
you're someone to
keep an eye on.
I guess. Lily showed up.
She did?!
It's the blue door!
Once you wake up, be sure
to swing by my laboratory!
There are still a great number
of matters for us to discuss!
Huh? Professor?
Well then. Back to sleep.
[LILY]
Follow your dream.
But will you follow it
all the way to the end?
Even if that end's
considered a taboo?
[EGOS]
Taboo, baa!
[LILY] The next dream is:
"Time Stopped at Age Twelve."