[knocking]
[MIREI'S MANAGER]
Saegusa!
Can you hear me?!
[MIREI'S FATHER]
Come out right now, Mirei!
[MIREI'S MOTHER]
Stop this nonsense, young lady!
[MIREI'S COACH]
Come on, answer us!
[MIREI]
You let me down.
It was all on the line,
and you failed.
You failed.
Saegusa!
Would you just stop for a second
and reconsider all this?!
Please, Mirei. You have
to open the door!
Stay away! I can't take anymore!
I'm done skating!
From now on,
I'm living my life
the way I want to!
[MIREI'S MANAGER] Please, don't
do anything you'll regret!
[MIREI'S COACH]
I'm breaking it down!
[ALL gasp]
--[MIREI'S COACH grunting]
--[banging]
Here we go.
Farewell to the old me.
[gasping]
Something tells me your
dream involves a witch.
Yeah, no duh.
I was able to figure
that one out on my own.
Where's this ire coming from?
I just don't like
seeing people in pain.
Ms. Saegusa. Mirei, right?
I'm sure I've heard of her.
It's so weird.
Who smashes their own
leg with a hatchet?
Something must've
driven her to it.
A cute girl like that...
Did you fall in love?
It's not like that!
Okay, we already know
this witch's name.
I'll go do some research.
Once I've accessed the database,
we should have plenty of
information to work with.
But listen up.
I'll try to phrase
this very plainly.
She's still a witch. Your love
isn't going anywhere.
I told you, it isn't like that!
[KANZAKI]
Mm? For me, too?
If you don't want any,
that's fine.
[KANZAKI]
Mm...
[KANZAKI] Mirei Saegusa.
Eighteen. Figure Skater.
At the age of three, her
grandfather took her
to a local ice rink,
introducing her to skating.
She picks up spins and jumps
by watching other skaters,
and is scouted out by a coach
from a skating
school in no time.
She then becomes a household
name by coming in first
in the All-Japan Championship
at the tender age of 14.
From this point on,
she's a domestic superstar.
With her rich expressiveness
and technical prowess,
she takes the skating
world by storm.
Couple that with her
endearing good looks,
and you have a national idol.
As the obvious favorite
for the upcoming Olympics,
her fame swells
like never before.
In her last appearance at
the world championships,
she messed up a triple
jump and fell,
which put her in second place.
Shortly after, for unknown
reasons, she came down
with Sleeping Beauty Syndrome
and fell into a coma.
So, what do we do now?
[MIREI'S MANAGER]
Saegusa! Can you hear me?!
[MIREI'S MOTHER] Stop this
nonsense, young lady!
Stay away! I can't take anymore!
I'm done skating!
From now on,
I'm living my life
the way I want to!
Here we go.
Farewell to the old me.
[HARUTO grunts]
[LILY]
You like her?
[gasps] Ah! What the hell?!
When'd you get here?!
Mirei's pretty.
Wouldn't you say?
[HARUTO]
Huh?
[LILY] Now, you're
wondering how I know.
[grunts]
[LILY] I can tell. I know
everything about you, Brother.
[HARUTO] Seriously, why do
you keep calling me that?
[LILY] I think this one must
be crying out for help.
Huh?
She's sending out a
message, telepathically.
[HARUTO]
Huh...?
[LILY]
Gotcha! I was kidding!
I just wanted to see
what you would do.
You pain!
I'll teach you to mess with
"Brother Dearest"!
There, it is! I've got
you saying "Brother" now!
[HARUTO] Just because I
was making fun of you!
[LILY laughs]
But you still said it!
[knocking]
[door opens]
[KANZAKI]
Pardon me.
[KANZAKI] Yurina. Please
don't end up like this.
You have to wake up!
[HARUTO]
She was really that famous?
So, why have I never
heard of her before?
I don't really watch figure
skating. Did you know?
[KANZAKI]
Yes. I knew.
[HARUTO] But still,
why would a big star like her
smash her own leg?
[KANZAKI]
In her last competition
before she fell asleep,
she messed up.
The loss must have driven her
to the depths of despair.
[HARUTO] I couldn't imagine
doing something so extreme.
I'd miss being fussed
over too much.
[KANZAKI] There are worlds
that the common man
will never understand.
[HARUTO]
I'll take your word for it.
[KANZAKI]
Say, what if we skipped dealing
with this witch altogether?
[HARUTO]
Hm? Just what're you saying?
[KANZAKI] It's just...
this one is rather different.
[HARUTO] Don't you care
about your sister?
I care. Of course.
[HARUTO]
Then that's that.
I wanna help this girl out,
any way I can.
Huh?
[HARUTO]
Besides, she's already here.
[KANZAKI grunting]
If you aren't up for it
this time, Professor,
then I can do it alone.
Hold on. When did you
suddenly get so eager?
[HARUTO] She came to me
to share her dream.
I think it has to be
some kind of sign.
If I can do something to
help her, I'd like to.
Besides...
I couldn't ignore a cute
girl's telepathic message
and still live with myself!
[KANZAKI sighs]
Well, I have no right
to try to stop him.
It's his choice.
[bell tolls]
What's this? It looks
like an average college.
[GIRL panting]
[GIRL]
Oh. I'm so sorry!
No, no. It's my fault.
Well, okay.
What the hell do I do from here?
[GUY 5A]
Figure skating?
Do we even have that
at this college?
[LADY 5A] Mirei Saegusa?
Sorry, don't know her.
[GUY 5B] If there were
a girl that cute here,
trust me, I'd know.
[GUY 5C]
For a small finder's fee,
I'll track her down for ya.
[phone chimes]
[HARUTO] So, uh.
I can't seem to find her.
[KANZAKI] Come on, try using
your head for once.
[PA chimes]
[ANNOUNCER 5A]
Mirei Saegusa.
Someone from your family
is waiting for you.
Please report to the General
Affairs windows at once.
[MIREI] Excuse me.
My name is Mirei Saegusa.
I was just paged?
You said a family
member was here?
What?! No way! It was you?
[gasps]
Wow, I'm glad I thought to
have you paged, because you
have a completely different
image going on this time.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but have we met before?
No, you and I have
never met in person,
but your look has
totally changed
since you were a
celebrity, you know?
[gasps]
[HARUTO]
Huh?
Hey! Hold on! Wait a second!
I'm never going back!
Just who are you, anyway?!
What do you want?!
And why do you insist on
barging into my life?!
[HARUTO] You're the one
who called me here.
You came to me because
you needed help.
I don't know what you're saying.
I just want to enjoy my
new, ordinary life!
Why would I want any help?
Now let go.
[HARUTO]
Are you really happy here?
That's my business, and it
has nothing to do with you!
[HARUTO]
It's just a regular college.
[gasps]
I guess you don't understand.
How could you?
No. No one can understand.
Look, my mind's already made up.
I'm living a different
life from now on.
[MIREI] As far back as
I can really remember,
I've been out on the ice.
Five AM, every day, running 10K.
After school, skating at
the rink until closing time,
then gym work and stretching
until bedtime.
There was never any
time for field days.
No culture festivals.
I really missed going on field
trips with the other students.
I ate countless meals
in a moving vehicle,
and on my days off,
I spent 20 hours in the rink.
Have you ever been so
exhausted from training
that you fell asleep
right on the ice?
[inaudible]
[MIREI]
Must be nice...
[MIREI'S COACH grunting]
[gasps]
[MIREI'S COACH grunts]
[MIREI'S MOTHER gasps]
But you started skating
'cause you liked it.
I still do. Even now.
Yeah?
I never thought the practices
were too strenuous.
But then, it wasn't about
a gold medal for me,
or about being a star.
That didn't matter.
I just... I just wanted
to have a normal life.
A normal life? Like what?
[MIREI]
When I was younger,
I was happy just to hit
the ice and skate.
I wasn't anxious about anything.
As long as I was out on the ice,
I could be myself.
Then, some publicists decided
I needed more exposure.
Before I knew it,
I'd become an idol.
I hated it.
It wasn't what I wanted
my life to be.
And I realized I had
lost sight of myself.
Look, I totally understand
what you're saying,
but you're not missing much!
And I'll be the first to tell
you, a comfortable, normal life
is nothing to write home about.
If I had talents
like yours, I'd--
[MIREI]
I've had it!
All I want is to enjoy my youth
like everybody else gets to!
I want the experiences
other girls my age
were able to have
that I missed out on!
And I don't think wanting
that is asking too much!
[gasping]
[MIREI] Joining clubs, study
groups, playing with friends.
Falling in love.
Being able to just enjoy
the moment, that's all.
Like the other kids got to.
That's the only thing
I've ever wanted.
[MIREI cries]
[HARUTO]
You're right. I'm sorry.
You totally have the right to
choose your own path in life.
With that in mind, I've
come up with a great idea.
I can show you what average
campus life looks like!
You'd do that?
Of course, no problem!
Besides, I'm a college
student, too!
Well?
[LILY]
18if.
[HARUTO] So? How do you like
regular academic life?
[MIREI]
I've had so much fun!
Going with you was the
right decision after all!
[HARUTO]
You think?
If you're having that much fun,
then the tour was
definitely worth it.
[phone vibrates]
[gasps]
[HARUTO]
Was that a text from Yuki?
'Atta girl! You're cute
together, for real.
I hope everything goes well.
Thank you very much.
[COLLEGE STUDENTS chattering]
[COLLEGE STUDENTS laughing]
[YUKI]
Saegusa! Hey.
Oh, Yuki!
Listen, are you gonna
be free this Saturday?
Uh! I-- Yes! I don't
have any plans.
Perfect!
Because I happen to have two
tickets to a movie premiere.
Care to join me?
Like... Like just me and you?
What's wrong? Is that a no?
Oh! No! That's not what I meant!
Then it's settled!
This Saturday, 'kay?
I'll be in touch.
'Kay...
[MIREI]
What do I do, Haruto?
I have no idea what I'm
supposed to wear for a date!
[HARUTO] Anything you wear
is going to be fine!
Besides, you've performed
at major venues, right?
[MIREI] Come on,
just give me a little insight
into the male mind that
I can put to use!
[HARUTO]
Ah, well.
I don't know how much
I can help you there.
[MIREI] What if you tagged
along for our date?!
[HARUTO]
Don't be ridiculous!
Sorry I'm late!
[gasps] Um.
No... No problem.
[YUKI]
Waiting long?
Oh, no, not at all.
[YUKI] Wow, I almost
didn't recognize you.
Nothing. You ready?
Uh, sure!
I'll just keep an eye on them,
and see how things pan out.
[inaudible]
[seagulls squawking]
[MIREI laughs]
I had no idea
there was such a beautiful
place this close!
[MIREI laughs]
You mean you never
came here as a kid?
Like on a school trip?
[MIREI]
Mm-mm.
[gasps]
Yuki. I had fun today.
I wanted to thank you for
inviting me out with you.
I've never experienced
anything like what we did.
It almost feels like
I'm still in a dream.
[YUKI]
Don't mention it.
All we did was see a movie
and get some tea.
Yeah, but I just...
Yuki, I had a wonderful
time with you.
[YUKI]
It doesn't have to end here.
Do you still have some time?
[MIREI]
Huh?
[YUKI]
'Cause, there's one more place
I'd really like to take you.
Okay. Sure.
I'm glad. I like you.
I want to get to
know you even better.
[gasps] Likewise.
Why here?
[ice skates scraping]
[YUKI grunts] What's wrong?
Haven't skated before?
No, I wouldn't say that.
Then let's go. Take my hand.
[gasps] 'Kay.
[gasps]
[MIREI] It's strange. I can't
believe how "right" this feels!
[MIREI laughs]
This sensation!
[MIREI gasps]
Oh, uh. Sorry.
That was amazing.
You looked so self-assured
and beautiful.
Yuki...
[gasps]
[CROWD cheering]
Where did he go?
Come back to us, Mirei!
You owe it to yourself to try!
[gasps]
Now, skate your heart out!
Go, Saegusa!
[gasps]
[CROWD cheering]
[YUKI]
Come on. Skate, Mirei.
After all, this is exactly
where you belong.
[MIREI]
No, stop.
Please don't!
No!
[HARUTO]
Like I tried to tell you,
a "normal" life
isn't always easy.
[MIREI] But why?
This is my dream, isn't it?
How could something
like this have happened?
I don't know.
It was all going really well
there for a little while.
But in the end,
it might just be your destiny to
be out there in the spotlight.
Right. Fate.
[HARUTO] It's the one place
you can really be yourself.
You see?
[MIREI]
Yes.
In the long run, this is the
only path I have, isn't it?
[YUKI]
That's right, Mirei.
Gliding gracefully
across the ice
is where you shine
your brightest.
Keep on skating.
You were meant to be a star.
You were born to it.
That's destiny.
[HARUTO gasping]
I guess I'll be going then.
Maybe I'll even get
to see you skate
sometime in the real world.
I'll look forward to doing so.
[inaudible]
[HARUTO]
It's gonna be all right.
Knowing you, you're strong
enough to bounce back.
[gasps] Mirei?
Miss Saegusa, can
you understand me?
[gasps] Doctor! Doctor!
[KANZAKI] What do you think?
Did she seem happy?
Yeah. Sure.
It looked like she'd
gotten over it.
[KANZAKI]
I see.
[HARUTO]
Also, I could sense something
when I was looking at her.
Something... inescapable.
And, I've been carrying
it around with me
this whole time without
ever realizing it...
[KANZAKI]
And, what would that be?
No idea.
[KANZAKI]
Hm? Again?
[HARUTO]
You don't have to eat it.
Why not? Let's dig in.
[HARUTO]
Know what I'm in the mood for?
Skating.
[LILY] You'd beat up bad guys
if you were a superhero,
wouldn't you? I would.
[EGOS]
Evil beware!
[LILY]
In the next dream:
"Curses Return Upon
the Casters."