[CROWD mutters]
♪
[LILY hums]
Wait. You know this song?
[LILY gasps]
You said that Eve was
being protected by a witch.
Have you ever met her, or...?
[LILY] Mm-hm And she
wasn't the first, either.
The protector must meet certain
criteria. There are rules.
Like what?
Being virginal is the
most important.
So, why the lily?
[LILY] Because white lilies
represent virtue.
They're also known as
Madonna lilies. Lovely.
Lilies? If you say so.
I wonder what kind of witch
this next one's gonna be?
[gasps]
Are you surprised?
I'm surprised.
Good to see you, Professor.
[KANZAKI]
You got everyone together?
When they awoke, they started
looking for others like them,
and put together a contact list.
They developed the ability
to sense the former witch
in one another.
[YUKO] We all share
the same wish, though.
We'd all like to
get to meet Haruto.
[MISAKI]
We hadn't made much progress,
each of us searching
for Haruto separately.
So we've pooled our efforts to
track him down here in the
real world.
You, too?
The scope of the Valanga royal
intelligence network is
at your service!
Have you discovered anything
of note that might lead us
to Haruto here
in the real world?
[KANZAKI]
No.
While we were witches, we
were able to sense something
in Haruto that made him quite
different from the others.
"Different" how?
[MISAKI]
It has to do with time.
It's hard to explain,
but the time that envelops
Haruto is different.
Unlike yours. Or anyone's.
[KANZAKI]
Hm?
Don't look at me.
I don't get it.
Right now, the rest of the
witches are out searching
the town for clues. Based on
what we felt in the dream world.
[KANZAKI] So you're all
using your feelings
as sort of a compass
to help track him down?
[YUKO]
Yes.
[KANZAKI] Seems like an
imprecise methodology.
[MISAKI gasps] People who've
been in the dream world
have a different
aura about them.
Like how they say celebrities
project an aura.
Sometimes you can just
tell by looking at them.
So, what does it look like?
It's simple, there's a
bit of a glow around them.
First I've heard.
Perhaps it's a side effect of
Sleeping Beauty Syndrome?
Looks like another red door.
[LILY] On the other side.
A witch's world.
What's that sign?
I don't know.
Think it has something
to do with Eve?
Maybe it's connected,
but I have no idea.
This sounds like
a job... for him.
Really? But, you guys
were fighting.
So we can never speak
to each other again?
We disagreed, I'm not
going to be petty.
[phone rings]
[KANZAKI gasps]
Haruto!
[WITCHES gasp]
Got it. I'm on my way.
[YUKO] Has something
happened to Haruto?
[KANZAKI]
I have to go.
[YUKO]
Huh?
You can communicate with
the dream world through that.
If you discover anything
new about Haruto,
let me know.
I'm counting on you.
[EHYEH] Great Goddess Eve.
I feel your presence!
My soul is set ablaze with
the magnanimity of your power!
Soon, you will wake!
May your awakening be swift!
For the sake of all
your lost children!
How is the search going
for the girls out in the field?
There have been no major
developments, as it stands.
Then again, the only leads
we have to work from
are our feelings.
[MARI] Haruto sounds
like a helluva guy.
I'd like to meet him someday.
That same wish is the hope
that drives us forward
in our search.
To speak face to face.
Not just a dream, but real.
To truly meet Haruto!
[KANZAKI]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm sorry. I was a jerk earlier.
--[KANZAKI chuckles]
--♪
What is it?
That melody? Yes, that voice.
You mean you've
heard it before?
My sister.
--Huh?
--Really?
Yes. Is she calling from
the other side of this door?
It sounds like your
sister's voice?
Well, what do you think, Lily?
Wait, Lily's here?
[KANZAKI]
Hm.
She's right there!
I've been standing
here the whole time.
[KANZAKI] That's the crest of
the Thorn Cross Association.
They worship Eve as a goddess.
Eve again?
You already know about Eve?
I know her better than anyone.
The Professor mentioned
an emblem, earlier.
This is what he
was referring to.
What is it?
I've seen it.
Those Thorn Crossers.
They're preaching all over the
world about Eve awakening.
I'm worried about his sister.
Would one of you
girls accompany me?
You want to go to the
Professor's laboratory?
Yes.
If his sister experiences any
changes while he isn't around,
we'll be on hand to
keep him up to date.
Sure, I'll come.
You girls keep an eye
on the place for me!
[KANZAKI] If what Lily
has told us is true.
[LILY]
It is the truth!
What the Thorn Cross Association
says is the opposite.
[HARUTO] We'll find
out once we meet Eve.
Meet her? And then what?
She isn't like
the other witches.
Everyone dies if she
wakes up, right?
We kill her.
[KANZAKI gasps]
I was afraid it would
come to that.
But how?
Only Brother has the
power to destroy Eve.
And if he fails,
then we all die.
\Will you?
[HARUTO sighs]
I'd like to meet her first.
[HARUTO grunts] What's with
the intimidation tactics?
We won't get very far unarmed.
We need some weapons!
And where do you
suggest we find them?
We'll come up with something.
It's a dream!
We aren't coming
up with anything!
[gasps] It's a sign of things
stirring in the dream world
where the goddess slumbers!
[YURINA] Yield, intruders.
On your knees.
I will permit you to
gaze upon my visage.
[HARUTO] She must be
the witch of this world.
I can't detect the
witch's thoughts.
There's only the cannons.
But they were created
by a different entity.
That isn't the issue.
That's my sister.
[YURINA] I am the Witch of
White Lilies. I protect Eve.
My virtue guards her
door from invaders.
What're you talking about?
Yurina! It's me, your brother!
I'm here for you!
[ALL shout]
[YURINA chuckles]
Something tells me the
witch didn't recognize you
as her brother.
I see. Eve is trying
to get rid of me.
Do what?
[LILY] This witch is
being controlled by Eve.
That's why I couldn't
delve into her thoughts.
We didn't step into a dream
world controlled by the witch.
This is Eve's world!
[AIRI pants, grunts]
What didja stop for?
A hospital?
Since the incident, I've come
here a number of times.
[AIRI gasps] Why now?
What do you need?
It's been a while. I'm paying
my respects to the doctor.
Huh? Come on! We're getting
sidetracked here!
[MANA]
Doctor.
Ah! It's you. And this
is your friend?
I'm Airi Kojima.
It's nice to meet you.
Huh?
Girl, your doctor looks
like a hot pop star!
I'm happy for you. Good to
see you with a friend.
You are friends, right?
Yeah, you know it!
We're thick as thieves, doc!
We were just in the area,
so Mana here decided we should
drop in and say hello!
[MANA gasps]
[AIRI gasps]
Was that?
[MANA]
Mm-hm.
Ah yes, that patient. He's been
comatose for a long time.
The poor young man
hasn't been awake
since before he
was brought to us.
Did you feel it?
Yeah. Just what it
felt like in my dream.
[AKITO]
Hm?
[LILY shouts]
[HARUTO]
Hang in there, Lily!
I'm okay. Just give me a second.
I'm getting sick of this witch!
It isn't right to shoot
at children like this!
All the same,
she's still my sister.
That's his name.
Yeah.
We've found him.
Hold on.
There's a chance it could be
someone with the same name.
But we felt it! That hint
of the dream world.
We'll make sure.
But how?
[KANZAKI] Yurina! I thought
I understood what you wanted.
But was I wrong?
Was becoming an idol
something you never intended?
[HARUTO]
Hm? An idol?
Indeed.
Yurina passed an audition
that her friend had signed her
up for, and quickly
became an idol sensation.
She had so many people
cheering for her.
She wore herself out trying
to meet all their expectations.
And I know you weren't trying
to run from your problems
by developing Sleeping
Beauty Syndrome.
You kept working hard
out of a sense of duty,
but the same sense of duty that
drove you brought you to a stop.
Wake up, Yurina!
Enough, already!
Sleeping Beauty
Syndrome is like death.
But you are still alive!
And as long as you are, you can
still choose a different path!
[HARUTO]
Professor!
That's a good question.
We just have to
ask them flat out.
I suppose so.
--[phone beeps]
--[YUKO gasps]
What's wrong?
Kayo who?
Kayo? The Witch of First Love.
Witch of First Love?
But she passed away,
didn't she?
She can't come to us,
but perhaps she left part
of her soul in this world
to look after Haruto?
Awesome! You just got
a text from a ghost!
I'll try to text her back.
[MISAKI]
That's so cool!
[AIRI]
You're kidding. A dead person?
Oh. Hi.
[AIRI gasps]
[MANA]
We can see her.
We sure can.
[KAYO chuckles]
Enough! Stop this!
[phone rings]
[KANZAKI grunts]
What's up? I'm a little
busy right now.
We've finally tracked down
Haruto in the real world.
Huh? What was that?
I said, we know where
Haruto is now!
[YUKO gasps]
What's that noise? It's so loud!
[YUKO]
Huh?
♪
I'm sorry, Yuko, but I
can't chat at the moment.
This world has
started to collapse.
It what?
We'll all die. The witch too.
That voice, it's hers!
You know who it is?
It's Yurina! The idol
idols want to be!
Can you save her?
I can try!
[NENE] You're a witch.
All you have to do is dream.
Now hurry up and go to sleep!
♪
Who are you?
Misaki?
[MISAKI] Haruto. It's an eye for
an eye, and an idol for an idol.
I don't really follow,
but at this point,
I feel we've exhausted
our other options.
[MISAKI sighs]
Yurina. You're an inspiration!
Out of my way!
There's only so much
Misaki is going to be able to do
by herself!
Eve seeks purity above all else.
Which means, if we
taint that purity,
eve will withdraw, and have no
further need for this witch.
Easier said than done.
Be gone, you pest!
[MISAKI]
Yurina, you have to wake up!
I will not be distracted
from my mission!
The goddess is sleeping.
Be gone!
[MISAKI grunts]
You told me that I'll have
to kill Eve, didn't you?
That's right.
[HARUTO]
I thought of how to do it.
[LILY gasps]
I was thinking I might take
an approach like this.
[LILY gasps]
[YURINA]
Lily? Get lost!
[BOTH grunt]
You did it! Great job!
[HARUTO] Eve is watching
me through you, right?
Then look at me.
--Let me go! Right now!
--Not happening.
[KANZAKI]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
[screams]
I've spoiled the purity
of your white lily.
[YURINA gasps]
[HARUTO]
Hi there.
Haruto! What were you thinking?
Oh, no! What'd you do?
I liked it.
Eve is no longer with her.
Worse ways to lose, right?
[KANZAKI]
Don't go spiking the ball!
How dare you try to play
my sister like that!
And right in front of me?
You're going to answer for what
you did to her back there!
Ow! Ow! Whaddaya mean, answer?
Come on, Brother,
that's enough!
You mean?
What? Even as a cat,
she could tell?
Yurina! You're back
to your old self!
Well, that should do it!
Should do what?
Speaking as an idol,
this little photo could cause
a life-shattering scandal.
No way! How'd you even get
that in the first place?
This is a dream.
Anything can happen.
Don't even think about trying
to sell those to the tabloids!
[MISAKI chuckles]
[KANZAKI shouts]
The Professor's definitely an
older brother, that's for sure.
Yurina. Let's sing together!
[YURINA]
Huh?
We have to destroy that.
[YURINA] Whoa. Wait a second.
What's going on?
[MISAKI] An evil goddess is
lurking on the other side
of that fort.
That's right. So sing!
And you are who?
A fan of yours.
Fan?
Now what?
[roaring]
[KANZAKI]
Yurina. A song?
[LILY]
Or else we'll die.
So if I start to sing,
everyone will be saved?
That's right. Including you.
♪
You've grown
stronger too, Misaki.
[MISAKI grunts]
Awesome.
♪
Seems like you enjoyed yourself.
Well, this is a dream.
Is that the final door?
Wait. It's the same door
that you use, isn't it?
[LILY gasps]
Now, would you take
Yurina out of here?
Sure.
And make sure not to let Eve
get into your head again.
Catch you later! Be safe!
"Catch you later"?
Haruto just kissed you!
Or does that not concern you?
Hey, take it easy, will ya?
You're giving off
an old-fogey vibe.
Fogey? That's not fair!
[YURINA grunts]
Welcome back to the world.
[YURINA]
Who are you?
Someone else who was saved by
the young man you just met.
He's the reason you're awake.
Get ready. I'm going to send an
image of Haruto to everyone.
[EKG beeps]
That's him?
Is that really Haruto?
[NENE] All those tubes.
What happened to him?
[CROWD chatters]
You saw?
Yes.
What does it mean?
How long has he been asleep?
So on the other
side of that door,
the goddess Eve is sleeping.
No. She's awake now.
What?
Eve's awake? Damn.
[LILY]
Mm.
[EHYEH gasps]
The miracle! The glory!
The goddess whom we worship,
has finally awakened!
The time of our
salvation is at hand!
[CROWD mutters, gasps]
It's the beginning of the end.
I suppose it's time
to meet this goddess.
♪
[LILY]
The dream comes to an end.
[EGOS]
It ends, baa.
[LILY] Next time's dream is:
"Eve's Sigh."