[SHARK LADIES]
♪ The first bite exposes ♪
♪ the true heart of a predator ♪
♪ And whenever my gaze
meets up with yours ♪
♪ I'll sink my teeth
in even deeper! ♪
♪ S-H-A-R-K!
We're the Shark Ladies! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four--
just one more bite! ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[MISAKI]
But, just so you know.
Sometimes, it's different.
It's hard putting
yourself out there
when you could get hurt.
I've no time for casual love.
The "easy" girl,
I won't be her.
I know our love could
stand the test of time.
I just wish you knew the way
that I felt about you.
Because I just want
to be with you!
[AUDIENCE MEMBER 9A]
Yeah!
[AUDIENCE MEMBER 9B]
I wish you knew
how I felt about you, too!
[music pays]
[sighs]
[ERIKO]
Where the hell is our manager?
How much longer are we going
to have to wait around?
We weren't together at all
during our performance today.
[TAMAKI] ------- your way
to the top, huh?
How dare you! I--!
Well done, Shark Ladies!
Terrific work today!
It was another powerful
performance.
You should all be proud!
Misaki has a meeting
with the staff
from the next movie
she'll be starring in,
so I need to take her to
Ginza directly from here.
Big shocker.
Miss "Center Stage" here
gets treated differently
than the rest of us.
[RINA] Are you dating one of
the producers or something?
I bet that's all it takes for
you to get so much work.
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't a tad jealous.
Don't be ridiculous, ladies.
Everything you've read in
the tabloids about Misaki was
founded on baseless rumors.
They're all lies!
[ERIKO]
See ya!
[DIRECTOR 9A]
Apparently, reception for the
first film was
pretty lackluster.
But with a talent like
yours behind it, Misaki,
the movie is bound
to be a guaranteed hit.
We're talking exceptional
domestic and international take.
And if being in front of the
camera is an issue, don't worry.
Mister Inubosaki here will
be your acting coach.
If you have any questions about
your character, look to him.
She'll do fine!
Everyone is looking forward
to the fresh perspective your
acting will bring to the film.
[MISAKI] Oh. That's very
kind of you to say.
[PRODUCER 9A] So, Misaki.
You drink wine, don't you?
This is some of the finest
stuff, straight from Burgundy...
[MISAKI] This isn't right.
What am I doing here?
I worked as hard as I could.
Underwent tough training.
Auditioning.
I didn't work so hard
to become an idol
to do something like this.
[EMPLOYEE 9A]
Sir, please wait. Stop!
[gasps]
[STALKER 9A] I told you to
get outta my way, moron!
[PRODUCER 9A]
What's going on here?
You ------- harlot!
How dare you trample all
over my emotions like that?!
[gasps]
[MISAKI screams]
--[MISAKI groans]
--[crash]
[stabbing]
[RINA groans]
Where am I?
[PRESIDENT 9A]
Ah! No way!
What's going on?
It vanished!
Where has my "Little Me" gone?!
Ha, ha! Dwell not on what we've
lost, but what we've gained!
Ew, now I'm even
more confused.
[INUBOSAKI]
What happened to us?
I've become a tiny girl!
[PRESIDENT 9A]
That voice!
Is that really you in there,
Inubosaki bro?
[WITCH 9A]
Shut your damn mouth!
What the--?
Uh!
[WITCH 9A] Welcome to
Nightmare Idol School.
Hold on. Is that you, Misaki?
No, darling. I am the
Witch of Youthful Beauty!
And starting today, I'll put you
all through a hellish training
regimen of my own design.
Only then will you see what
it takes to be a true idol!
Quit messin' around!
Ah!
[ALL]
Whoa!
Wish my wiener were here.
He would've loved that!
Nightmare Idol School has a
strict "no boys allowed" policy.
That's why I had you film
gentlemen turned into females,
so that you too could undergo
my personal training.
Now, what do you say?
Hang on, Misaki.
I'm a little fuzzy on
the core concept.
[WITCH 9A]
Wrong!
The correct answer is,
"Yes, my Lady"!
[yelping]
[grunts] You think you're better
than me, but you're not.
Oh? Which one of you sows
thinks you can step up to me?
[MUTSUMI] Right over here,
-----her-way- to-the-top Misaki.
You've got real nerve.
Do you honestly believe that
I'd be clueless about what
you've been doing?
Wait. What are you insinuating?
That one night after another,
you happily cater to the deviant
tastes of an older producer.
Doing the sorts of things that
would make a lady blush.
What are you doing?
Stop that. It's weird!
Nobody asked for your
opinion, you little pervert!
You're just a fly,
flitting around
and landing on fresh poop.
Though that's really an insult
to flies, you're
the poop itself!
And now, you'll become the
piece of shit you always were!
[STUDENTS scream]
[laughs] Now each and every
one of you knows what happens to
those dumb enough to cross me.
Do we have an understanding?
What's your answer, swine?
[STUDENTS]
Yes, my Lady.
I can't hear you!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, my Lady!
[laughing]
[WITCH 9A]
Un, deux, trois !
[MANAGER 9A] Teacher!
I can't lift my leg anymore!
I'm exhausted!
You simply aren't
trying hard enough.
Perhaps you can tell me the name
of the Incan civilization's
first emperor?
Uh, ah...
Manco!
The name of the first Incan
emperor is Manco Capac!
It's no use, my Lady!
I don't know what your crotch
is trying to tell me!
Because you're weak!
Now, what is your crotch
trying to tell you?
[MANAGER 9A screaming]
[laughs] Across the sea, in the
land of Russia, there's a place
whose name describes your
current situation perfectly!
Do you know where
I'm talking about?
[MANAGER 9A screaming]
It's burning! Hot!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Um, my Lady?
May I be excused?
I really need to go
to the bathroom.
[WITCH 9A]
Bathroom?
Everybody knows that first-rate
idols never even touch a toilet.
But please, Mistress.
I can't hold it.
Hey, if you wanted to have
a burning ---- too,
all you had to do was say so.
[RINA gasping]
[WITCH 9A laughing]
Wow, perfect timing.
You should be thankful
for your own indecency!
[NANA]
... deux, trois !
Again! Un, deux, trois !
[WITCH 9A] Hm...
What's your name, new girl?
My Lady! My name is Nana!
[WITCH 9A]
Huh. It looks like someone
actually wants to
put the work in.
Very well, back to
what you were doing.
Thank you very much, my Lady!
Again! Un, deux, trois !
Un, deux, trois !
Un, deux ...
[panting] I'm dyin'.
[ALL groan]
[WITCH 9A]
Hmph. The girls from Shark Lady
have more stamina than
the rest of the group.
But you have to smile, got it?
You think you can show those
ugly mugs to the fans,
and they'll be okay with it?
[WITCH 9A laughs] Was
yesterday's spirit just a lie?
I can keep this up
all day, my Lady!
I like that look in your eyes.
Very well then!
Here we go!
Running music, start playing!
[ALL panting]
[SHARK LADIES]
♪ Shark. Shark. Shake it now ♪
♪ This here is
Shark Lady style... ♪
First, we'll increase
your stamina!
That means, you run!
What are you five
simpletons waiting for,
an engraved invitation?
You're some of the
sorriest sad-bodies
I've seen in my entire life!
Move!
[WITCH 9A]
You must keep your body limber!
You'll need that flexibility
when you're asked to hold
different poses!
[INUBOSAKI grunting]
[WITCH 9A]
Bend more, damn you!
[grunting]
My crotch! My crotch! My crotch!
♪♪♪
[SHARK GIRLS]
♪ Your attention, please: ♪
♪ a flash flood of love
warning is in full effect ♪
♪ Begins with
"pleased to meet you" ♪
♪ ends with someone's
heart a total wreck ♪
♪ I've got the sneaking
suspicion ♪
♪ I was doomed to lose
from the very start ♪
♪ This dreamy feeling's
coming faster, ♪
♪ just like the beating
of my heart! ♪
♪ So far, no one seems
to notice me ♪
♪ I know that my aim
will be true ♪
♪ I'll lock on to
your signal before ♪
♪ anyone gets their
sights set on you! ♪
♪ Shark Ladies are
bloodthirsty carnivores ♪
♪ With nothing to fear
in this world ♪
♪ Let's circle our prey
before we ♪
♪ smash right through
the status quo! ♪
♪ S-H-A-R-K!
We're the Shark Ladies! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four--
just one more bite! ♪
♪ I guess I'm scared
of being hurt, ♪
♪ I want a love that will last ♪
♪ I'm so afraid of losing you, ♪
♪ I've just gotta find a way to
have you all to myself ♪
♪ All to myself! ♪
♪ And fast! ♪
[WITCH 9A] What kind of
idol do you want to be, Nana?
I want to be just like Misaki
from the group Shark Lady!
[gasps] Heh. But as things
stand right now,
Misaki's a fallen idol.
She's being attacked
on TV and in the tabloids,
and is getting flamed
by the trolls on the net.
The other members of her team
don't even trust her anymore.
But, they're wrong.
Misaki isn't the type of person
who would do those things!
[gasps]
She'll be a top idol
for eternity!
A shooting star loved
by millions of people
across the nation!
She doesn't fall in love, or
have to go to the bathroom!
Misaki's a perfect idol!
[WITCH 9A]
A perfect idol?
I'm not sure anyone is
worthy of that title.
Wait, where are you
going, my Lady?
[WITCH 9A]
Years ago, the Daimai Orions,
a professional baseball team,
hired a foreign player they
had to call Frank Marnie.
Do you know what his
real name was?
[NANA]
No. I can't say I do.
[WITCH 9A]
I see.
Look it up later,
when you have time.
Then you'll understand
the truth about idols.
[SHARK GIRLS]
♪ It doesn't matter much ♪
♪ if it's my first
and final love ♪
♪ All that I want is for you
to be my First Bite! ♪
♪ We are here to provide
you with a thrill ♪
♪ We're coming for you
herbivore men, are you ready? ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪
♪ Better make way for
the Shark Ladies ♪
♪ We'll always find
your true heart with ♪
♪ our very First Bite! ♪
♪ We're hunters and
we'll never let you leave ♪
♪ We'll gobble you up ♪
♪ until you forget
how to breathe ♪
♪ Here we go! Shark Lady! ♪
♪ S-H-A-R-K,
we are Shark Lady! ♪
♪ Making love whenever
we please! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ just one more bite, yeah! ♪
♪ Here we go, Shark Lady! ♪
♪ S-H-A-R-K,
we are Shark Lady! ♪
♪ Making love whenever
we please! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four--
just one more bite, yeah! ♪
♪ S-H-A-R-K!
We are Shark Lady! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four--
just one more bite! ♪
♪ S-H-A-R-K!
We are Shark Lady! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four--
just one more bite! ♪
Did I whip the lot of you into
the world's best pop group?
[ALL]
Yes! Yes, my Lady!
So, what do you wanna
do for dinner tonight?
I had the strongest urge
for curry this morning!
[PRESIDENT 9A]
What about you, Rina?
[RINA]
I had that yesterday.
[LILY] You look like you're
having some fun.
But that isn't the reason you
came here. Is it, Brother?
[MANAGER 9A]
Eriko, wait up!
Your disguise may have
fooled the rest of them,
but you can't trick me with it.
Silly brother.
Lily!
What's gone wrong?
You've let the witch
take the lead.
Or did you decide to just
watch the situation
for the time being.
Just watch the situation?
Nothing like that.
Everything's been going
great for me around here,
I couldn't be happier!
Huh?
I've always been a
fan of Shark Lady.
No, a huge fan of
Misaki herself!
Now Misaki is right there
in front of me,
and we get to talk to
each other every day!
Who cares if she's a witch,
or if she abuses me?
This is still the greatest
reward I could ever hope for!
Ah! Something new inside me
is awakening from the time
I've gotten to spend with her!
Sweetest Misaki.
[LILY]
I'm speechless.
I never would have guessed that
you were such a total pervert.
Since that's how you are,
I think you deserve this.
[gasps]
[HARUTO]
What are you doing?!
[LILY laughs] Now you're going
to beg to tone things down!
[HARUTO]
No, no, no, no! This is bad!
Everyone else is at ease,
and I'm standing at attention!
[alarm blares]
[door opens]
My Lady! We've caught
a man on school grounds!
You what?
You caught a man?!
[HARUTO screams]
Damn!
Stop! Please, stop this!
[screaming] Damn it!
Let me go!
[HARUTO screaming]
[WITCH 9A]
You disappoint me.
I had high hopes for your
future at our academy.
Then, you disrespected
me with your betrayal.
Uh...
Let's start with you
telling me your real name.
[HARUTO]
Haruto... Tsukishiro.
[WITCH 9A] Yes. Now I see
your true form, Haruto.
Your true form.
[TAMAKI]
What'll we do, ma'am?
You said that no men are allowed
in the Nightmare Idol School!
Yes, that was the rule.
This man must be punished.
[PRESIDENT 9A laughs]
Just the words I've been
waiting for, my Lady!
You're asking me to
punish a man while
in the body of a
sweet little girl?
I couldn't think of
a hotter scenario!
I should be able to
snag some nice footage!
My style of play
is pretty severe,
but the punishment
must fit the crime!
Bury the carrot deep.
Then watch it grow.
[HARUTO whimpers]
And don't forget about
this little bad boy.
[screams]
[PRESIDENT 9A]
Aw, yeah.
It'll probably hurt to have
something like that used on you,
huh? Isn't that right,
Haruto's "little Haruto"?
[HARUTO screaming]
Now, it's our turn
to play with you.
Do you like it when
girls caress you?
Like this...?
[HARUTO groaning]
What'll happen if I run my
fingers down your chest?
[HARUTO screaming]
[ERIKO]
Oh, my!
"Little Haruto" looks like he's
straining to break free!
Please don't!
Just stop, already!
Um. I think that's enough.
Uh. What'd you say?
You heard me,
that's quite enough!
Really? Oh, I think I get it!
You want to deliver
the finishing blow yourself,
don't you?
[gasps]
Yes, my Lady.
You're our teacher, after all.
We need to watch and learn
from your techniques.
I can't.
Huh?
I don't want to do it!
I don't want to do anything
at all to this man's...
This man's what, my Lady?
You know what!
Like the name of the
ninth head of state
for the Nguyen
dynasty of Vietnam!
You've all heard of him, right?
[HARUTO]
Are you okay?
[WITCH 9A]
Haruto?
But how did you escape
from the dungeon?
As long as you, the witch,
aren't around to interfere,
I have a couple of
tricks up my sleeve.
[HARUTO grunts]
[yells]
[ALL screaming]
Go get 'em!
[ALL groan]
[HARUTO grunting]
[TAMAKI screams]
I can't work myself
free from this goo!
No more.
I am spent.
You seriously did all of that?
This is the dream
world, my Lady.
Anything goes in here.
[WITCH 9A laughs]
I feel like such a fool.
[HARUTO]
What do you mean?
[WITCH 9A]
I mean what I said.
I came to this world,
and every single thing
started going my way.
So, I thought I'd get a little
payback on all of those people
who'd hurt me in the past.
But it seems that in the end,
I was the one who ended up
losing, and so I ran away.
I became a loser,
even in my dream.
But the you that exists
back in the real world
isn't a loser any
way you slice it.
You've been the textbook
definition of a perfect idol!
[WITCH 9A]
That's enough!
Nothing I've done has ever
made me the perfect idol!
[NOVELIST 9A]
C'mon, Misaki.
It's no big deal.
It is for me. I don't
think you understand.
I didn't come here for this.
Ha, ha! Thanks for
the scoop, guys!
We call this bad publicity.
An idol being sold to the
public as "the pure one"
can't have a scandal!
I have no idea what I'm going
to say to our sponsors now.
[MANAGER 9A] ...as far
as my agency is concerned,
we are more than prepared--
[STATION PRODUCER 9A]
What's the point in
the manager apologizing to me?
It'll be much more
effective if, you know...
What are you saying, sir?
You still haven't clued in yet?
A fine young talent,
like Misaki here.
She's got a lot of loving fans.
Even on the business side.
[WITCH 9A]
I'm not a perfect idol.
I use a toilet,
like everyone else,
and I want to find a boy
to fall in love with.
But I kept holding
myself back for
the sake of our adoring fans,
and for the other
girls in the group.
I've masqueraded as an idol
for so long, it's all I know.
But now it's all too much!
I think that you've got your
facts mixed up there somewhere.
[WITCH 9A]
Huh?
You told me you've been
holding yourself back
for the sake of everybody
else, but that just isn't true.
Wasn't it really for the
sake of your own dream?
[gasps]
People can become strong,
because they have a dream.
Because you felt so strongly
that you wanted to become
something great, like an idol.
You were able to dedicate
your whole heart to it!
It's those eyes again.
[HARUTO]
My eyes?
More precisely, those
were the same eyes
I saw when you were Nana.
Those eyes of yours.
They woke up
something inside me
that had been dormant
for a long time.
One day, I want to
perform for everyone,
and make the entire
world happy with my
singing and dancing!
But, just so you know,
sometimes, it's all
so different for me.
It's just that I'm terrified
of getting hurt.
But so be it. I'll just
try to do my best!
Misaki.
Thanks for your help, Nana.
Or Haruto, I guess.
I'm really glad that I met you.
[HARUTO laughs]
If I'm the witch of
this world, I wonder...
What does that make you?
Maybe you could be
my prince, huh?
[HARUTO chuckles]
Maybe.
Now then, the spell is about
to be broken, my Lady.
Take care now.
I don't know very much
about men, but just a sec.
I'd feel terrible if
your "little Haruto"
caught a cold because of me.
[SHARK GIRLS]
♪ Bloodthirsty carnivores ♪
♪ With nothing to
fear in this world ♪
♪ Let's circle our
prey before we ♪
♪ smash right through
the status quo! ♪
♪ S-H-A-R-K!
We're the Shark Ladies! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four--
just one more bite! ♪
♪ I guess I'm scared
of being hurt, ♪
♪ I want a love that will last ♪
♪ I'm so afraid
of losing you, ♪
♪ I've just gotta find a way
to have you all to myself ♪
♪ All to myself! ♪
♪ And fast! ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[panting]
I have an announcement
that I'd like to make today.
This was my final performance
with Shark Lady.
From this point forward,
I'll no longer be an idol.
[AUDIENCE MEMBER 9A]
What?!
[AUDIENCE MEMBER 9B]
So, the rumors were true?
[AUDIENCE MEMBER 9C]
You betrayed us!
I have learned about
the power of love!
From now on, as a solo
singer--as a woman--
I'll chase my dream,
with everything I've got!
[muffled chattering]
[sighs]
Show them.
Make them see what
chasing your dream
with all your might looks like.
[HARUTO]
Okay, Misaki?
Let's go on an adventure
inside of someone else's dream.
I'm certain it will
be... pleasant.
[EGOS]
Pleasant, baa!
[LILY] Next time's dream is:
"Dream Dimension Alpha."