[EHYEH] Everything in this
world has spawned forth from
the dreams of the goddess Eve.
And we that live
in it, are merely visions
the dreams source
has given life.
Then, what does that make us?
Where are our true selves?
I say unto you: those with
the Sleeping Beauty Syndrome
are on the true path.
Why waste your time grieving?
Those maidens are fortunate.
The dream world has awakened
them to their true selves.
They have received
Eve's blessing!
Verily, unfettered by the
shackles of this world,
they have blazed a
trail to true freedom!
With the liberty to
behave like witches,
they have redefined beauty!
Eh? Is someone here actually
taking that loud fool seriously?
[KANZAKI gasps]
♪
Great news! I found a clue!
[HARUTO]
Huh?
It might help get Yurina
out of the dream world.
More importantly, why am I the
only one who can't wake up?
[KANZAKI]
Huh?
All the witches have
woken up, haven't they?
I'm checking on that.
But from what I can tell,
all of the girls suffering from
Sleeping Beauty Syndrome have
returned to the real world.
Well, with one exception,
it saddens me to say.
An exception?
One of the girls passed away.
The Witch of First Love.
Kayo Sugisaki.
Yeah, I remember.
Still, when do I get out?
That's why I tried to tell
you about the Yurina clue.
It might be the key to solving
the mystery about you.
And, not just you,
but Lily as well!
I don't care about
any of this stuff!
This could all be tied to you!
What do you mean you don't care?
I suspect that everything
is interconnected!
[HARUTO] I suspect that all you
really care about is yourself!
As long as you can
save your sister,
you don't give a damn about
what happens to me, right?
[KANZAKI]
How dare you.
You should apologize
for what you just said.
[HARUTO]
Not happening.
I want some answers,
and I want them now!
[KANZAKI sighs] At the very
least, I'm more mature than you.
[HARUTO]
Yeah? So what?
I have come to the conclusion
that this back and forth
is unproductive, therefore,
there is no further reason
to continue our discourse.
Are you heading out to
look for your sister?
You said something about a
clue earlier, didn't you?
What's wrong?
[KANZAKI] I don't feel
like talking anymore.
Hold on!
[HARUTO gasps]
I want this dream to end!
I represent the
Thorn Cross Association.
I'm Ehyeh. Nice to meet you.
Professor Kanzaki. Your research
in the dream world is easily
the finest work done
in the field to date.
It's an honor to meet
you in the flesh.
[HARUTO]
Hm?
Hey, Brother!
Oh, it's you.
So you and the professor
got into a fight, huh?
How do you know about that?
Because it's all a dream!
I'm ready for this dream to end.
Would you like to know
why you're the only one
who still hasn't woken up yet?
What? Do you know why
I'm still dreaming?
I can tell you exactly why
you're still in slumber.
It's because I'm the
one keeping you asleep!
[HARUTO gasps]
Oh? You really surprise me,
Professor Kanzaki.
You aren't familiar with Eve?
No, I'm afraid not.
Actually, my younger sister
has Sleeping Beauty Syndrome,
and I was wondering whether
her case and the others were
related by a common source.
That's wonderful! Rejoice,
for your sister receives
the blessings of Eve
in the dream world,
like a flower
blooms in the sun!
[KANZAKI grunts]
'Kay, so, what exactly is
it that you want from me?
Something important
that only you can do.
Because, I've come to believe
that you and you alone have
what it takes to prevent
Eve from ever reawakening.
Eve, who? What're
you talking about?
Eve is Eve. You know,
as in "Adam and Eve".
[LILY]
If Eve awakens...
...then everyone will die.
Her promise will provide
salvation for all of humanity.
[KANZAKI grunts]
[EHYEH] This is what we in the
Thorn Cross Association
firmly believe, and so we
worship the goddess Eve,
who sleeps in the center
of the dream world.
A mighty being responsible
for not only the beginning
of this world, but also
the birth of mankind.
[KANZAKI] Back out on
the street, you said that
the entire world is no
more than a dream that
Eve is having, right? I still
don't understand that aspect.
[EHYEH] You're already familiar
with the story of Adam and Eve,
I presume. They were the
first man and first woman,
blessed by God with
the Garden of Eden.
However, they were tricked by
the devil into consuming fruit
from the Tree of Knowledge,
which angered God,
and he threw
them out of Eden.
[KANZAKI]
Yes, I've heard that much.
[EHYEH] After lamenting
her actions for years,
Eve was so tormented by what
she'd done that she closed
off her heart from
the rest of the world,
and fell into a deep slumber.
In her sleep, she would
give birth to dreams.
In turn forming this
world in which we live.
If we take a look
through history, it becomes
clear that our reality is far
from the paradise of Eden.
People suffer from one
illness or calamity to another,
the gap between rich
and poor grows wider,
and war is waged
with no end in sight.
Man continues to
grow more depraved.
All because we ate from
the Tree of Knowledge.
God was furious at
man's transgression.
Now we receive his punishment.
That is the core of Eve's dream,
and it is what we call reality.
The here and now.
Then, if this is all a dream,
what does that make us?
Our forms are naught
but temporary illusions.
True reality lives
inside dreams.
[KANZAKI] You mean,
that's my truest aspect?
We must all endeavor to
awaken to our dream selves.
For only then will
we find salvation.
The key to such self-discovery
lies in the witches who built
kingdoms in the dream world.
The witches?
Eve found respite in slumber,
and her dreams helped to shape
this world of suffering.
But what about the
maidens with what we call
"Sleeping Beauty Syndrome?"
Yea, they construced a dream
world of only witches.
In that world of theirs,
everything they
desired became real.
Such a wonderful place.
It is the true Garden of Eden!
[EHYEH] And at the moment that
Eve reawakens, mankind will
finally be set free from this
world of suffering she's made.
No more war or poverty.
No. Nothing short of
an eternal paradise.
[KANZAKI] So then, what you're
saying is the witches should
never be woken up?
Because they've developed
into their true selves,
and set an example
for the rest of us?
Precisely. And yet, someone
dares keep them from their
true selves. Returning them
to this world of pain.
[gasps]
[EHYEH]
Someone evil to their core.
All of the witches
you've saved thus far
have been vital to my plan.
They're the linchpins whose
existence grant us access to
Eve's door, which we'll
need to open.
The witches?
They're all connected?
[LILY]
Yes. Remember?
Game set and match.
Ah, I feel better.
Who's the mightiest witch in
the whole world, my darlings?
[STUFFED ANIMALS]
The Witch of Thunder is!
[HARUTO] This is a pathetic
"dream world", if you ask me.
The whole thing seems
kind of thrown together.
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER] You don't
know how tiring it is to be the
girl everyone expects me
to be. I'm not allowed to fail!
It's too much pressure.
I really want to be spoiled.
To have my way, but I can't!
That's why I felt like there was
no choice but to bind myself.
At least I have some
control in this world.
I can do what I
want when I like!
I've dreamed about
this for a long time.
[HARUTO] The dream of yours,
it's over once you've killed
all three of them. It will end.
What will you do then?
\What I do after doesn't matter.
If they don't die, I can't live.
[KAYO] Why is it
always me? It isn't fair!
[WITCH OF GLUTTONY] When I eat,
I put on weight really fast.
[HARUTO] Is putting
on weight a bad thing?
[WITCH OF GLUTTONY]
Mm-hm.
The last time I ate and
gained weight, I ended up
getting dumped by my boyfriend.
[MIREI] Joining clubs, study
groups, playing with friends.
Falling in love.
Being able to just enjoy
the moment. That's all.
Like the other kids got to.
That's the only thing
I've ever wanted.
Involved? They're all guilty!
Those spineless fools knew
what was happening,
and pretended not
to see anything!
They deserve it!
[NENE]
Did you forget that?
[YOSHITSUNE]
Pot. H-He died because of me.
I will never forget that!
There's no way I ever could!
[SUONO] It's not as if everyone
has to follow the same path
in life as each other.
But if you can understand
an inkling of the ideas
I've been sharing,
then I'll be so glad.
By learning about the
uniqueness of another person.
By changing your point of
view just the slightest bit,
your feelings towards
that person allow
for a closer connection.
Getting to know one another,
listening intently,
without judgment, for their
inner voice to emerge and speak.
[gasps]
She'll be a top idol
for eternity! A shooting star
loved by millions of
people across the nation!
She doesn't fall in love,
or have to go to the bathroom!
Misaki's a perfect idol!
[MISAKI]
A perfect idol?
I'm not sure anyone is
worthy of that title.
Cheer up, Jane. It'll be okay.
You don't have to worry.
[JANE] This is the part where
I draw you in close, Haruto.
Listen to me, Jane.
This dream must end, okay?
Please! I know you can do it!
We'll go, together! Come on.
Summon your courage, and rise!
What does a make-believe world
like this have for you?
Open your eyes,
and start walking, Jane.
Don't give up, Jane.
I know you can do it, Jane!
Jane! Jane! Jane! Jane! Jane!
Jane! Argh! I'm done!
Well, I never really thought
of them as witches.
They just seemed to have
their own issues to deal with.
[LILY] There are many
witches in the world,
but not even I knew which of
them had become key figures
in our struggle against Eve.
But the witches were the ones
who contacted you each time,
not the other way around.
That's how we discovered
who the linchpins were.
But why did they search me out?
Because you are you.
That doesn't explain anything.
[LILY] When the ten
linchpins have been removed,
the door to Eve opens.
Brother, come with
me to her door.
[HARUTO] What'll we
do when we get there?
I want you to stop
Eve from waking up.
Stop her how?
[LILY]
By killing her.
Kill her? But why? Why don't
you just do it yourself?
I mean, you're the one who
wants her dead, not me.
Because. I can't do it.
Why not?
You saw it right?
The world coming to an end.
All of mankind will be killed.
You still haven't
answered my question!
[EHYEH] Professor. You know
who the evil one is, correct?
[KANZAKI]
Inside dreams, I do.
I'd like to ask you to
help us stop him.
He puts in jeopardy
all we strive for.
Ten witches have already
awoken because of the evil one.
Now. Open your eyes.
[THE WITCH OF THUNDER gasps]
I wish we'd met long ago.
I have a new dream.
What that means,
I'll have to learn.
Thanks for your help.
[KAYO] Thank you, Haruto.
You made me feel joyful.
I've never been happier!
I love you. I hope
you'll remember that.
Keep me in your heart.
[HARUTO]
Aah!
[WITCH OF GLUTTONY]
Oh!
Yes! It's good! And so fun!
Right... Fate.
[HARUTO] It's the one place you
can really be yourself. You see?
[MIREI]
Yes.
In the long run, this is the
only path I have, isn't it?
[YUKI] That's right, Mirei.
Gliding gracefully across
the ice is where you
shine your brightest.
Keep on skating. You were
meant to be a star.
You were born to it.
[LILY]
That's destiny.
[inaudible]
[HARUTO chuckles]
[HARUTO]
It's gonna be all right.
Knowing you, you're strong
enough to bounce back.
Then, that means...
I must still be alive!
[HARUTO]
Mm-hm.
Oh, good. That means I
can get out of here!
That's all up to you,
from this point.
Are you prepared to face
the harshness of reality?
That's a choice you'll
have to make for yourself.
I am ready.
Thanks, Haruto... and farewell.
[SUONO] I'm glad! Thankful I
got the chance to meet you!
[HARUTO]
Hm!
[SUONO]
I'll see you around!
[HARUTO]
Huh?
Now then, the spell is about
to be broken, my lady.
Take care, now.
[JANE] He was willing
to give me a chance.
Yeah? Does that mean I can
see you again on the outside?
[JANE] What? Would you be
interested in being my friend?
[KANZAKI]
Of course.
Tin man.
The interference of the evil one
has angered our goddess, Eve.
Why did he awaken the maidens?
What right did he have to
tamper with their emotions?
Now Eve is trying to wake up,
stirred by her displeasure.
Then, Eve is waking
up out of anger?
Will she try to save mankind
after she lets off some steam?
We pray for her to wake,
not out of anger, but instead,
out of pure love
for her children.
"Love" is another
ambiguous word,
when held in the
context you're using.
If it is love that
reawakens our goddess,
she'd forgive the world
for what was learned
from the Tree of Knowledge.
That's the only way humanity can
hope to escape the punishment
God set aside for us.
[KANZAKI] All right.
So, if Eve is woken out of love,
and comes to save us,
her children,
then what kind of
world will await us?
[EHYEH] The whole world would
become Sleeping Beautys.
I don't think I
fully understand,
but it sounds depressing.
Don't believe a thing they say.
[KANZAKI gasps]
[KANZAKI]
Who are you?
[AKITO] Someone who despises
the Thorn Cross Association.
That's all that counts.
Do you know something
I should know?
Do I look like I do?
If not, then why did you
bother talking to me?
Take it easy, I'm just
trying to warn you.
You don't want to fall for the
line of bull those fools are
trying to sell.
You're being very evasive.
What is it that you're hiding?
Not a thing. I just said I
hated those guys, didn't I?
Anyway, I'd steer clear of them
from now on, if I were you.
You want to enjoy
a long life, right?
[KANZAKI gasps]
That kid's a weirdo.
[phone rings]
[YUKO] Yes? Oh, Professor!
It's been a long time.
[KANZAKI]
It's been a while.
There's something I
wanted to ask you.
[YUKO] Something to
ask me? What is it?
[KANZAKI] It's about Haruto.
And not just you.
I was hoping to speak with
all the other witches as well.
[YUKO]
About Haruto?
Then there's a lot that we
would like to share with you,
now that you mention it.
[KANZAKI]
Huh? Did you say "We"?
[YUKO]
Yes, all of the former witches.
[HARUTO]
If I open this,
then I'll be at the door
that leads me to Eve, right?
[LILY]
Yes.
[HARUTO] Well okay.
I guess I have no choice.
[EVE chuckels]
♪
[LILY] The witch's singing
voice rings out.
Turn your ears towards her,
and listen to her feelings!
[EGOS]
Listen up, baa!
[LILY] Next time's dream is:
"The Witch Wars."