Murder. Murder. Murder.
Murder. Murder. Murder. Murder.
Murder....
Oh, I'm sorry.
Murder!
[gasping]
Run! He's got a knife!
[MAN 6A]
Murder. Murder.
[whimpers] No!
[MAN 6A]
Murder!
[gasping]
[FEMALE PASSERBY 6A gasping]
Rin, pyo, to, sha, kai,
jin, retsu, zai, zen.
Kyu, kyu, nyo, ritsu, ryo.
Evil begone!
[MAN 6A screams]
[phone vibrates]
[NATSUKI] The cursed words keep
coming up again and again.
I wonder if the old saying
"curses return upon the casters"
is really true?
Cough up the toll.
Yeah, pay the
inconvenience fee!
And if you don't
feel like paying,
I can share this with
the whole school.
[MEI]
Hurry up and take it.
[MIKU] If you're too slow,
they're gonna catch you.
Come on.
Heh!
[MIKU laughs]
[KASUMI laughs]
[MOMOKA, MIKU gasp]
[KASUMI]
Aw! Sorry, my hand slipped.
Wow, that is so mean!
Natsuki's gonna cry!
[NATSUKI]
Are you enjoying yourselves?
Is this how you have fun?
What're you waiting for?
Don't you want your
wallet? Pick it up!
[KASUMI]
Go on!
[MEI]
Pick it up!
[GIRLS]
Pick it up! Pick it up!
Pick it up!
[KASUMI laughs]
Ew, that is nasty!
I know, I'll mop up
everything that got dirty!
[KASUMI]
Good idea.
[MIKU]
It's not cleaning her up at all!
[KASUMI] Because she was
already trash to begin with.
[GIRLS chuckle]
[NATSUKI] I wish break time
would hurry up and end already.
[bell tolls]
[NATSUKI]
It's hard to hide
when it's scrawled all
over my textbook.
[NATSUKI]
I'm home.
[exhales]
Kyu, kyu, nyo, ritsu, ryo!
Evil begone!
[NATSUKI laughs]
That last episode of On-Bara,
you were so cool!
[phone vibrates]
That's enough for today.
I'm too tired.
[NATSUKI]
Where am I?
Did I die?
Is this the afterlife?
Huh?!
No way. It's Haruyoshi's!
The cosplay's perfect!
[NATSUKI] Wow, it's just like
the show! What is this?
Some kind of On-Bara theme park?
[NATSUKI]
These!
These are the wishes
that the client wrote
back in episode three!
That's the tree that was hit
by lightning in episode eight!
Here it is! That's the angle!
[squelching]
Oh, yeah!
Rin, pyo, to, sha, kai,
jin, retsu, zai, zen!
Kyu, kyu, nyo, ritsu, ryo!
Evil begone!
Oh, wow! It's the real thing!
The afterlife is awesome!
Wait! What?!
How precious!
Here comes a monster!
Rin, pyo, to, sha, kai,
jin, retsu, zai, zen!
Kyu, kyu, nyo, ritsu, ryo!
Evil begone!
Yeah!
Kyu, kyu, nyo, ritsu, ryo!
Evil begone!
[NATSUKI]
[panting] No one else's here.
It's just monsters.
Is this all there is now?
Tomorrow, and the next day?
For a year?
For the next 10 years?
Even though I decided
a long time ago
that I would never let bullies
like you make me cry.
I just... Why is
everything like this?
[gasps]
[NATSUKI cries]
[NATSUKI]
Why me?
I curse you.
I won't forgive you.
I'll never forgive you!
Nightmares én masse ?
At Musashi-Tama Middle School,
more and more students are
losing sleep over similar,
unexpectedly dark nightmares.
Hm...
[NATSUKI]
Momo.
Momo. Momo.
Why is a waste of flesh
like you still breathing?
[gasps]
Hey, Sakurai.
Were you dozing off?
[MOMOKA]
It was just a bad dream.
Huh?
[gasps]
[MOMOKA]
Excuse me! I'm not feeling well.
May I go to the nurse's office?
Yes. Fine.
Would you mind escorting her,
Class Representative?
[gasps]
After you.
[gasping] No!
[panting]
[NATSUKI]
I won't forgive you.
[MOMOKA]
No!
[NATSUKI]
I won't forgive you.
I'll never forgive you!
[gasping]
Hey! Look out!
Are you hurt?
Please... Please help me.
[gasping]
Feeling better?
Yes. And thank you.
You wouldn't happen
to be a student
from Musashi-Tama Middle School?
Well then,
I was hoping you could give me
a little insight on something.
Huh?
Can you tell me anything
about the spate of group
nightmares at your school?
[gasps]
[KANZAKI] So, basically, after
this Natsuki Kamikawa girl
attempted to commit suicide,
everybody in the group
that bullied her started
experiencing similar, recurring
nightmares, is that it?
But it doesn't stop with us.
The other students
who didn't bully her,
even our homeroom teacher,
they're all having
bad dreams, too.
[KANZAKI] And all these people's
nightmares are the same?
They vary a little,
depending on the person,
but everybody remembered
being chased by Natsuki,
or someone who looked like her.
I see, and what's
this Natsuki up to?
Would you say she seems
different than before?
Who knows?
She hasn't been back
to school since then.
Some people say she passed away,
and now she's haunting us.
--[phone vibrates]
--[gasps]
[gasps]
[MOMOKA]
Miku!
Miku...
[cries]
Please, forgive us! Natsuki...
I want you to try
diving into the dream
of a local middle
school girl named Natsuki.
There's been a rash of
nightmares at the school,
recently. Starting with the
group of girls who bullied her.
If they're bullies,
it sounds like they're getting
what they deserve.
They aren't alone.
The nightmares have
begun spreading
like some kind of epidemic.
Which means there's a
chance the entire school
could be stricken with
Sleeping Beauty Syndrome.
You're positive this was the
way we were supposed to go?
Probably.
Probably-- Ah!
[HARUTO whimpers]
[KANZAKI]
That was a close one.
Watch out!
Hm? [screams]
Ah... Thanks for the save!
Maybe it's just me,
but we don't seem to be very
welcome around this place.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[HARUTO]
Ah! Run!
Hurry up!
I am hurrying!
[KANZAKI]
We should be safe here.
Man, that was close!
This is the place...
[NATSUKI] May calamity and ruin
fall upon Kasumi Fukumoto.
May calamity and ruin
fall upon Mei Asakura.
fall upon Momoka Sakurai.
Excuse me.
Could we have a word with you?
[NATSUKI]
Who're you?
A friend.
My name's Haruto Tsukishiro.
And I'm Katsumi Kanzaki.
[NATSUKI]
You won't trick me.
You're really ghosts!
We are not ghosts!
[gasps]
We were hoping to ask
you to stop the curses.
At the rate you're going,
you're gonna spread curses
to the point that everyone
in town gets brought down.
"Gets brought down"?
So, that means my
curses are working.
[KANZAKI]
They are--
Then I'll curse them again!
Curse them to their graves!
All the damn bullies
around the world.
The ones who push things way too
far, and who prey on the "weak,"
even though those poor souls
have done nothing wrong.
This world is far better
off without them.
With all the bigotry
and scapegoating,
humanity has set
itself on a course
of continual conflict
and suffering.
Tell me what worth people
who perpetuate that have!
You don't understand,
it's affecting your classmates
that weren't even involved
in the bullying!
Involved? They're all guilty!
Those spineless fools
knew what was happening,
and pretended not
to see anything.
They deserve it!
She's got a point there.
Doing nothing only makes you
complicit in the bullying.
But still, who are you to decide
what other people are worth?
That's the mentality of a bully.
[NATSUKI]
Hm?
[HARUTO]
Think of yourself,
you have value that no one
can take away from you.
You don't know anything
about me, all right?
So you'd better watch
what you're saying!
You work hard, and when
you make a mistake,
it's difficult to let it go.
[gasps]
[HARUTO]
Must've been tough.
You stood out because you were
smart, as well as focused.
Every day, you always
gave everything 100%.
If you ask me,
I think that proves your worth.
You should be proud.
Oh. Really?
Not to mention there
are several people
terribly worried
about you, Natsuki.
People like your mother,
who sobbed and said she was
sorry for not noticing how much
you were suffering.
I spoke with Momoka as well,
who apologized profusely.
No way.
Thank you both.
Too bad. We're all out of time.
Goodbye.
[gasping] What the hell?
The invasion fleet
from Alpha Centauri
has finally come to Earth.
Humanity is finished
if nothing is done!
Well, then.
We'll have to resist the
invaders with our giant robot!
Your robot? Don't you mean
your space battleship?
Are you ready?
[gasps] Sure!
[KANZAKI]
Put them on the main monitor!
[HARUTO]
That fleet is huge!
Scramble fighter wing!
[NATSUKI, HARUTO]
Roger!
[KANZAKI] Pretty weak on
the cosplay front, Kanzaki.
Unit One, engage!
Unit Two, engage!
[HARUTO]
Huh?
Have fun out there, you two!
[gasps] Where'd she come from?
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
Emergency launch.
To avoid danger, please
remain in your classrooms.
Repeat: Emergency Launch.
To avoid danger, please remain
in your classrooms.
Haruto, blasting off!
Go!
Natsuki, moving out!
Time to link up!
Roger!
[laughs] This kicks ass!
Go, Giant Robot Natsuking!
What now?
Pretty cool name,
don't ya think?
Yeah, not too bad, I guess.
Go! Natsuking!
We'll start off by kicking
things into gear!
You've got it!
Here goes.
[BOTH]
Natsuking kick!
[yelling]
[HARUTO, NATSUKI]
Natsuking kick!
[panting]
There are too many.
Ready up, finishing move time!
I can't wait!
Here we go!
[BOTH]
Activate! Eye-Beam Laser Cannon!
You've got a nice smile.
What? Where'd that come from?
Who knew? You're quite
the otaku, aren't you?
You seemed to be having a pretty
good time yourself, old man.
Uh! What was that?
The cat's the old one!
You know, it's been way too
long since I had any fun.
I wish I could have met someone
like you earlier, before I died.
Before you died? [gasps]
This place isn't the afterlife.
You've got Sleeping Beauty
Syndrome, Natsuki.
Huh? "Sleeping Beauty
Syndrome"? What's that?
[HARUTO] It's the illness
that keeps people asleep.
Then, that means...
I must still be alive!
[HARUTO]
Mm-hm.
Oh, good. That means
I can get out of here!
That's all up to you,
from this point.
Are you prepared to face
the harshness of reality?
That's a choice you'll have
to make for yourself.
I am ready.
Thanks, Haruto.
And farewell.
[MIKU groans]
What do I do, Mei?
I can't go to school
like this, can I?
Uh! Don't ask me!
We're all getting flak
for picking on her!
Just leave me alone!
[phone vibrates]
[LILY] Imagine you were
a country's monarch.
Think. What would you want
to protect, and why?
[EGOS]
Think it over, baa!
[LILY] Next time's dream is:
"And Now There Are None..."