[gasps]
Whoa, more cats.
[SAKU gasps]
G'mornin'!
Uh. Yeah. Morning, Hinata.
[SAKU]
I'm sorry.
[HINATA]
Hm? About what?
My place is so out of the way,
but you still pick me up.
Isn't it a pain to
get up that early?
Nah, don't worry about it.
Honestly? I'm up at
the crack of dawn anyway.
Well, thanks then.
[HINATA] Soo, have you decided
on which club you're gonna join?
Uh, no. I mean, not yet?
Then you should
come check ours out!
Who knows, you might like it!
Remind me which club
are you're in again?
It's the Singing Club!
[SAKU]
Oh, that's right.
Think about it.
You know that you're an
awesome singer, right?
Just drop by after
school today and see!
It's okay. I'm not that
interested in clubs, honestly.
Really? Well, if you're sure.
Yeah, I'm sure.
[HINATA]
Just sayin'.
Joining a club can be a
great way to make friends
after you're done with classes.
[SAKU]
I have to work.
[HINATA]
Oh, okay.
[MIKE]
Hinata.
Oh, hey there, Mike!
Good to see ya, man!
Check it.
Check what?
Is that the rare Mendako
March merch? No way!
[MIKE chuckles]
You're so lucky!
They're hard to get!
[MIKE chuckles]
That being said...
What the hell?
How'd you get two of 'em?
I'm lucky, too.
Hey. Good Morning, Saku.
Uh, thank you so
much for yesterday.
Why are you thanking me?
You cooked.
Still.
[HINATA] Wait, what? You guys
know each other already?
Yeah. He kinda did
me a flavor favor.
[HINATA]
Hey, Chiguma!
Oh, hey, g'morning.
Didya just get back
from aikido practice?
Yeah.
Um, good morning, Chiguma.
Hey, dude. Wondering
'bout the outfit?
I'm in both the Aikido Club
and the Archaeology Club, too.
[SAKU]
I didn't know that.
[HINATA]
Huh? Wait! This again?
Have they already
met before, too?
[SAKU] Oh! Thanks for
having me the other day.
Sure! You're welcome
to hang with us anytime.
'Kay.
[SAKU]
If you're curious,
I went along on one of
their outings this weekend.
[HINATA]
I get it.
So you were checking out
the Archaeology Club then?
[SAKU] Well, uh,
it kinda just happened.
[HINATA]
In that case, it's only fair
if you come by my club, too!
We go do fun weekend
events just like they do!
[SAKU chuckles]
[USUKI gasps]
[gasps]
[MITSUKI] Is everything
all right, Mr. Usuki?
Mitsuki. I have a
hypothetical for you.
If you go through a door,
and then it vanishes
when you look back,
is it possible that
you never went through
said door to begin with?
Uh...
Archaeology is the
study of history,
which we deduce by
examining its ruins.
But then, what if we
never discover them?
Can we say they ever
actually existed at all?
Well, Mitsuki? What's your
opinion on all of thi--
And if you don't listen,
was I actually speaking to you?
Or did I say nothing at all?
[SAKU]
Morning.
Hey!
Hi, Saku!
Hey, Kai. Um, thanks
again for yesterday.
[KAI chuckles]
[SAKU]
Huh? Uhh...
[KAI] Our culinary cook-off
of curry was truly inspiring!
[SAKU]
Thanks?
[KAI]
Let's do it again! Sound good?
[SAKU]
Again?
[SOSUKE] You should go ahead
and join the Singing Club.
[SAKU]
Why?
[SOSUKE]
I told you already.
They want to use my songs
in the upcoming competition.
If you're the one singing them,
then I'll feel a
whole lot better
about giving them permission.
[SAKU]
Huh.
I'll be honest with you.
I like your voice better
than the VOCALOID version.
Hinata wants to do
this VOCALOID song.
But the issue is no
one has this range.
It'd be a bit of a stretch,
even with all of us.
If that's the case,
what about that one friend you
mentioned earlier--is he in?
Well, I'm not super sure if
he's gonna bite, actually.
Oh? Is he thinking of
joining another club?
[HINATA] No, he says that
he's too busy with work.
Too bad. Sorta sounds
like he's a lost cause.
Who knows? He did
just go on an outing
with the Archaeology Club,
so it's kinda hard to say.
[MITSUKI]
It certainly is.
Whatever! Just be assertive
and see if he shows up.
I already told him
to come check us out,
but he didn't seem into it.
Well, if he does stop by,
we'll just casually let him
know that our club's the best,
and then he'll stay.
This is precisely why
you're such a loser.
'Scuse me? And what's
wrong with giving him
a friendly nudge in
our direction? Well?
We have to be on the offensive!
That makes no sense!
This ain't one of
your judo matches!
At least I can fight.
What's that mean?
[SATSUMA] If we're ever going
to recruit more members,
we need to be aggressive.
[RYO] Okay, four-eyes,
I don't need you telling me
how to run a club!
Satsuma does raise a good point.
If we sit on our hands,
he'll join a different club.
Again, I asked, and he said no.
We have to push harder!
Strategic and swift,
like the winds of conflict
blowing over a
war-torn battlefield!
Sounds good to me.
I'll leave it in your hands.
Right. I'll do my best, Mitsuki.
You can count on me.
[KAI]
You're wondering where Saku is?
Hmm. Y'know, I could have
sworn that he was just here.
Sorry, but you guys
barely missed him.
He just left school
to go to work.
Right! He's at the curry shop!
You mean Volcano?
I'm always in the
mood for curry!
Especially when I'm hungry,
and I'm hungry all the time!
He's actually working
somewhere different today.
[SAKU]
Excuse me.
I have your order of an
iced coffee and an oolong tea?
[gasps]
Hey, Saku!
[SAKU] Wait. What are all
of you guys doing here?
We're surprising you!
Floppy hand wave!
We just tagged along.
I'm the one that
wanted to meet you.
Let me introduce myself.
My name's Satsuma Kadonooji,
from Class 2-C.
I'm a member of
the Singing Club.
But I'm not here
to talk about myself.
Hinata has told us
a lot about you.
So, let's just get to
the point, shall we?
Our club could use
a guy like you.
So why waste your vocal talent?
You should utilize it
in the Singing Club.
But, uhh, you've never
heard him sing.
[SATSUMA clears throat]
That's beside the point.
We know that we need you, Saku.
Hey! If you're not
gonna use your sweetener,
then that means I can
take it, right? Thanks.
I didn't say that
I wasn't. But sure.
[SATSUMA] You've already gone
out with the Archaeology Club.
Why not open yourself up
to giving the other
clubs a go, too?
[SAKU]
But that was--
Just give us one chance!
[SAKU]
I, uhh...
You'll like it!
Satsuma, I think
you're scaring him!
Just let the poor
guy do his job.
Here. Please enjoy your drinks.
[SATSUMA]
Hold on a sec.
Um... Yes, sir?
I'd like some honey toast.
Oh! One honey toast. Sure.
Yeah! I want one of
those, too, please!
The most, honey toast, stacked
as high as the eye can see!
We'll take two, then!
That sounds good to me!
Okay, coming right up.
♪ There lies a valley hidden
deep beyond an ocean of waves. ♪
♪ Where you can hear the music
of the dolphins resonate. ♪
♪ Once you pass by the
"Hill Ballet" on your map. ♪
♪ The sight lies
between you.... ♪
Honey toast, yay!
And it's all for me!
[SAKU]
Please enjoy.
[SOSUKE gasps]
Hey, Saku. Can I bend your ear?
It would just be for a
minute or two, I swear.
I guess that'll be fine.
I appreciate it.
Your teenage years don't
last forever, y'know.
You have to find your own ways
to make them worthwhile.
They're fleeting, and precious.
We seek to ascribe meaning
to such a limited time-frame.
However, if you join
the Singing Club,
I can promise you
will be able to
look back on your youth fondly
and remember more than just
the toils of school and work!
Aren't you gonna eat that?
[SATSUMA]
If you insist.
[HINATA]
♪ ...will I ever reach you? ♪
♪ Right on cue, I can't stop the
tears from slipping through ♪
♪ Set the coordinates. ♪
♪ Hey, I think that's it - ♪
♪ And with that I'm
back on my way... ♪
[SATSUMA]
In the next singing competition,
our club wants to
enter using a song
that Sosuke here has composed.
A singing competition?
[HINATA] Uh-huh!
It's an event that happens
every year in the fall.
Anyone in the student body
is allowed to participate
if they want to.
No matter if it's a solo
or a number done in a group.
The winners get a ton of club
points as the grand prize.
What are club points exactly?
Extremely valuable commodities
for any student.
They can improve your club,
general school life.
There's no limit to their
benefits, when used correctly.
[SAKU] And even students
not in clubs can use them?
Yeah, they're essentially part
of the "unaffiliated" club.
[SAKU]
Huh.
[SATSUMA] Save up enough
and you can use them
for a variety things.
They can be used
to greatly improve
the budget of club field trips.
You can even upgrade
to a five-star hotel!
They'll actually let you
do that? That's amazing!
For the unaffiliated, you can
use your individual points
towards meal discounts on
anything in the cafeteria!
Whoa!
And on top of all that,
you can even get up to a
week of excused absences!
[SAKU] I can't believe they'll
just give you time off!
Also, if you really want to,
you can go over and use
the teacher's lavatory
up to twice a day!
I don't really get the
appeal of that one, but okay.
That being said,
everyone is out to win when the
potential payoff is so enticing.
Even though we're the Singing
Club, we can't slack off.
We have to approach even
a singing competition
as if we don't have it on lock.
It's imperative not
to leave anything
up to chance when it
comes to winning points.
But this also gives our club
a unified purpose and drive.
Something that we can work
towards year after year!
Now do you understand us?
Why we are trying so
hard to recruit you?
I came up with these lyrics
while watching Satsuma eat!
Look, these're
pretty sweet, huh?
Those are way too
literal. I'll pass.
Listen to me. The Singing
Club truly needs you, Saku!
Do you really?
Uhh, okay, man. I think
you've made your point.
Join together with us!
Then you'll understand!
Sorry! But I have to--
I have to get back to work now.
--[SATSUMA] Wait!
--Uh-- huh?
[SATSUMA] Another honey toast,
if you'd please.
More toast! Most toast!
More honey toast!
Let's make that two, then!
Seriously?
[SAKU]
Coming right up.
I wouldn't mind
helping them. I guess.
[gasps]
[SAKU]
A white shadow?
[SAKU gasps]
Excuse me! I--
The other day,
I wanted to meet you!
[SAKU]
What?
--[CAT meows]
--Uh--
Oh. Hey there, kitty. [chuckles]
Did you get lost?
Looks like you're not a stray.
I'm sure your owner
must be worried sick.
Well, you should head
home when you can.
[SAKU]
Uh--
Hey!
I guess you can stay here.
I'd better keep an eye
out for lost cat posters.
You do have a collar.
Hey, not my sister's room.
[gasps]
[SAKU]
Nozomi.
[SATSUMA]
Saku, morning!
[HINATA]
Thanks for yesterday.
We'll be waiting for you.
And feel free to drop by
whenever you want, 'kay?
Okay...?
[SAKU gasps]
[RYO]
Hm?
[SAKU gasps]
Uh, oh, sorry about that!
--[RYO] Hey.
--[SAKU] Huh? Uh, hello.
Question for ya.
Huh?
[RYO] Are you eating
cat food for lunch?
Huh? These are, uh...
You shouldn't have to
eat that kinda crap!
[SAKU]
Huh?
Take these.
[SAKU]
No, actually, I--
Don't argue with me!
[SAKU]
Uh...
You need to eat people food.
Oh, I do. This cat
food's for a cat.
[RYO]
You do? Cat?
[SAKU]
Uh, yes? I'm sorry?
[RYO]
So you own a cat then?
I... suppose you could say that?
Okay! I get it now! [giggles]
That's great. You're a good guy.
See ya.
What just happened?
[SOSUKE] So, you're not gonna
join the singing club then?
[SAKU]
Mm...
[SOSUKE] Is it 'cause you don't
like singin' in front of people?
No, that's not
exactly the reason.
Well then, if you're not gonna
be joining the Singing Club,
how about the three
of us form a band?
Seriously?
Come on! With you? It'll rock.
I'm not so sure.
I'll be in charge of
composing the music,
Uta will write
the lyrics for it,
and then you'll do the singing.
With those combined,
the songs'll sell.
We'd be selling these?
I mean they'll make a splash.
You can sing as well
as a VOCALOID can.
So you're something special.
Oh. Yeah.
[SAKU]
In the first four days,
I had two different clubs
ask me to join them,
and someone even wanted to
form a band with me. Uh--
[SAKU]
What is it?
[NOZOMI] Oh, it's nothing.
I've just never seen you
get so excited when talking
about school before. It's new.
Yeah? I guess I didn't notice.
Things'll be fine.
Huh?
It's nice to be included, right?
There're people who need you.
You're never alone.
That's wonderful.
I'm happy for you.
[SAKU chuckles]
I have to go now,
but you rest and
get better, okay?
That bag. Make sure
to take that with you.
[SAKU]
What is it?
I put something
important in there.
Look through it carefully
when you get back home, okay?
[door opens]
[SAKU]
I'm back.
Kinda nice to come home
to someone. Right, cat?
[SAKU humming]
[NOZOMI] It's nice to
be included, right?
There're people who need you.
You're never alone.
And feel free to drop by
whenever you want, 'kay?
I mean they'll make a splash.
You can sing as well
as a VOCALOID can.
So you're something special.
[SATSUMA] However,
if you join the Singing Club,
I can promise you
will be able to
look back on your youth fondly
and remember more than just
the toils of school and work!
So I can either join the
Singing Club or form a band.
[ALL laughing]
This is awesome!
I love our lil group!
We wrote a new song,
you wanna check it out, buddy?
Sure do!
[ALL laughing]
No way. That'd be crazy.
[gasps]
[HINATA]
Wow, Saku! You actually came!
What wonderful news!
I see our passion moved you.
Now then, we'll welcome you
with open arms and we can--
[SAKU]
I can't!
[SATSUMA, HINATA gasp]
[SAKU]
I came here to decline.
I apologize.
[SATSUMA]
Are you sure?
[HINATA]
Don't worry about it.
[SOSUKE] I see. You decided
not to go with the club, huh?
Then we should
start up the band!
[SAKU]
Sorry. I can't do that either.
But why not? You like singing,
so what's the problem?
I just can't.
[SAKU]
Have a good night.
Huh?
[SAKU]
What are you...?
[HINATA] There's a song in here
that we did in the Singing Club.
I told you. I can't.
It's okay. Just listen to it.
[HINATA] Promise that you'll
talk to me again after you do.
I came up with these
while watching Saku.
What do you think?
[SOSUKE]
Hm?
Uta. Those are way too macabre.
[NOZOMI] Saku. Things
aren't looking good for me,
so we don't have much
time left together.
But I'm sure you must
be aware of that by now.
That's why I'm giving you these.
So that you can continue
living your life without me,
the way I want you to.
[SAKU]
Then... it's true.
Three to six months. At best.
[NOZOMI] I already spoke
to the Mitsutsukas.
They agreed to take care
of you after I'm gone.
If you ever need anything,
don't be afraid to
reach out to them.
[MITSUKI]
How long are you planning on
being an absentee member?
Will you just come
back to us already?
[KEISHI]
Why should I bother?
The Singing Club appears to be
doing just fine without me.
[MITSUKI] I suppose,
but aren't you bored by now?
Not at all.
[MITSUKI] So, you're
still observing, then?
[KEISHI]
Yeah. Basically.
I'm so sorry, guys.
I wish I could join you.
[ASHIHARA]
Koya Ashihara on the scene!
And we're bringing you a special
breaking news program today!
[SOSUKE] We're here because Uta
saw those white shadowy things
a bunch of times in this room.
[UTA]
Yup, it's true!
Sometimes they peek inside
through the windows,
or suddenly teleport behind you!