'Kay. I'm all set now!
Let's head out!
We're counting on you.
Your music's our last hope.
--You got it!
--[SAKU, UTA] Right!
Ushio and the others should be
making their moves
right now as well.
Time for us to head inside.
[ALL]
Mm.
Yeah!
Dude! Shut the hell up!
Parkour!
You good, Uta?
Yeah! No problemo!
Cool. I'm gonna start passing
the equipment over to you.
[UTA]
Okie-dokie!
[SOSUKE]
I'm letting it down.
[UTA]
Gotcha!
[SOSUKE] Saku, hand me
the keyboard next.
[SAKU]
Uh, right.
'Kay. I can take it from here.
All right. Here it comes.
[UTA]
Gimme!
[SOSUKE]
You got it?
[UTA]
Yup!
[AGENT 12A] What was that?
Hey, show yourselves, now!
[SATSUMA]
Ryo!
[AGENT 12A]
I heard someone. Who's there?
[RYO meows]
[AGENT 12A] And what do you
think you're doing here, kid?
Hey. Have you by
any chance seen
my cat somewhere
around this area?
Your cat?
[RYO]
Yeah, that's right.
[MITSUKI]
Ryo. Thank you.
[RYO] I used to always
be able to find 'em
roaming around here
when it got out.
[SATSUMA] Ryo!
What are you doing in there!
We're not supposed to
be on school grounds!
C'mon don't you remember?
But what about my cat?
[AGENT 12A] Listen, kid.
You need to leave immediately.
For real? Leave without my cat?
There's no way your cat could
be here, so don't argue.
[RYO]
Huh? You sure?
I am, so shut up and get out!
Before I really get pissed off!
If you stay any longer,
I'll have you arrested.
'Kay. Guess I'll get going.
Well, bye.
[ASHIHARA] What?
You expect me to climb that?
Quite the whining!
We must make haste,
get up this rope, now!
Uh...
[ASHIHARA] Do you guys think
we should really be doing this?
[USHIO]
Well, you know what they say.
Nothing ventured,
nothing gained!
[ASHIHARA scoffs]
Seriously?
Oh, come on!
You call yourself
a Japanese man?
Okay, what does that
have to do with anything?
[USHIO] Once you've dedicated
yourself to something,
you need to see it through!
Hurry up! We don't have time!
You're the only one that knows
how to use the
broadcasting equipment!
Cease with your useless
babbling! Get a move on!
This is nuts.
[alarm blaring]
[AGENT 12B] Thrive Central
management to security.
We have spotted intruders
entering from the southwest
onto the middle school grounds.
All agents are to move in and
capture the intruders
immediately! I repeat.
We have spotted
intruders entering from...
We're about to have company.
Time for phase two.
[SAKU, HINATA]
Mm.
[UTA, SOSUKE]
[AGENT 12C] Stop!
All of you are under arrest!
This is exactly why I said
I didn't wanna do this!
[USHIO]
Ei, Ya, Toh!
[AGENT 12D groans]
Fear not, knaves, I will only
use the back of my sword on you.
But despite that mercy,
you still shall not pass!
[KAORU gasps]
Ushio!
Leave me! Please,
don't look back.
[KAORU]
Mm. Come on!
[ASHIHARA]
Huh?
[USHIO]
Perhaps you didn't hear me
when I said that
you shall not pass?
[ASHIHARA] I've changed
my mind, I wanna go home!
[BOSS]
These Actors are obsolete,
so it's fine if we lose a few.
No one will miss them.
I'm authorizing
the use of firearms.
Make sure you clean up
this mess completely.
[AGENT 12G]
Yes, sir!
We're going to use the
data we gathered here
and apply it to the
next world we create,
so it won't be a total loss.
[KEISHI] You think that they're
just data to be harvested?
I'll show you what
this "data" can do.
Drop your weapon!
Uh. This isn't an
honorable match -up.
I won't say it again!
Drop your weapon, now!
Didn't you hear me!
[gasps]
[USHIO]
What the--?
[AGENT 12G] Otherwise
I'll be forced to fire--
Drop your weapon.
[USHIO]
I see.
It seems that I've finally
awakened my true power!
[USHIO giggles]
[PLAYER 12A] Whoa, something
crazy is going on in Cat Walk!
[PLAYER 12D]
Look at that action!
[PLAYER 12E] Why are they
doing an event like this
when no one can
get into the game?
[PLAYER 12B] Someone hack around
the limited access filter!
[PLAYER 12C] What happened
with the singing contest,
anyone know?
[PLAYER 12F] Wait. I think
the server's back online,
try logging in!
[SOSUKE] Okay. We've
got power. Mic check!
[MITSUKI] Now. We just need
the outside world to notice us.
[gasps]
[MITSUKI]
Not good.
Everyone! Hide!
[UTA]
Saku, follow me!
This is no good,
we're locked out.
So what now? I'm not
gonna be able to use
the broadcasting
equipment from out here!
Tell me which floor
your club room's on.
Uh. The third floor, but why?
[ASHIHARA gasps]
Are you crazy? Hold on!
[KAORU] I'll climb up first.
And I'll pull you two up after.
Just wait here for a second.
'Kay?
[USUKI] How's the data
skimming on the Actors going?
[AGENT 12I]
There's a lot to account for.
So we only have
ten percent so far.
That's too slow.
Why don't you see if you
can speed things up.
Yes, sir.
[AGENT 12J] Excuse me,
do you have a moment, sir?
[USUKI]
Hm?
[STUDENTS shouting]
[TAKATO] How long do you
plan on keeping us locked out?
Open the gates!
We have a right to get into
our own school grounds!
The government can't keep us
out of our dorms forever!
Silence! Get away from here!
Disperse immediately!
Quit trying to tell us
what to do, you bastard!
Open these gates, right now!
[STUDENTS]
Open up! Open up! Open up!
What is going on out there?
Sir, it would seem
the students have gathered in
a crowd near the front gates.
And those barricaded in
the broadcast room?
Still at large.
We can't flush them out.
Good. The players are
starting to log back on.
Now it's time to
let them all loose.
[BOSS]
What do you think you're doing?
[gasps]
[AGENT 12L] Sir, we're
getting bug reports from
players who've gained
unauthorized access!
I don't want them interfering,
cut off all electrical power
to Thrive Central, now!
[AGENT 12L]
Are you sure about that, sir?
[KEISHI] That would
be unwise. Come now.
You'd be wasting all that money
and development time you spent!
You'll have to make your
new Actors from scratch
if you do that.
Mr. Harumoto. You really
shouldn't eavesdrop like that,
it's rather unbecoming.
Wow, you have some nerve
saying that to me, "Boss."
After all, I'm supposed to be
Thrive Central's manager,
but you cut me off
without any warning.
It had already been decided that
Thrive Central was
to be shut down.
We knew you wouldn't
accept that decision,
so there was no point
in telling you.
You'd do something foolish.
You've got me pegged!
Anyway, if that's the truth,
you must be backing up all
the data you can right now,
is that correct?
I don't see how that's
any of your business.
Oh my, why do you seem
so flustered, sir?
Is there something that you
don't want the higher-ups
to know about Thrive Central's
main system and operations?
That's utterly preposterous.
Now do me a favor and
stay in your room--
though, not like you
have any choice.
So do you boys want to
tell me what it is
you think you can
accomplish here?
We could ask you the same.
Do you care to explain yourself?
This world is going to
meet its end very soon.
You lot can't be
saved as you are.
But if we back up your data, we
can make better versions of you.
What are you talking about?
This doesn't make any sense.
[USUKI] It's a waste of
time trying to fill you in
on all the details.
In any event,
you're coming with me.
[gasps]
Is that my cat? But how?
[USUKI]
You little!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[AGENT 12N]
Are you all right, sir?
[gasps] What are you--?
You goons have got some nerve
using me as your puppet!
Mr. Usuki!
[USHIO yelling]
Take that, ne'er-do-well!
Taste my steel!
It's Chiguma!
Hey, boys. Sorry we're late.
[HINATA]
Mike's here, too!
Didja miss me?
Thank goodness!
Mitsuki! You guys have
an audience waiting!
Show them what you all can do!
Wait. Keishi?
[chuckles]
[AGENT 12Q]
Open up! Get out here right now!
That's an order!
What're you guys waiting for?
C'mon, hurry up and start!
[STUDENTS]
Open up! Open up! Open up!
[booming]
[ALL]
Huh?
[STUDENT 12A]
Wait, what is going on?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MITSUKI] And now we shall begin
the Tensho School's annual
Autumn Festival
Singing Competition!
They're on the loudspeakers?
Heck yeah!
[music playing]
All right!
[STUDENT 12B]
It's Sakutasuke!
[GIN]
Seriously?
[TAMOTSU]
Way to go, Mitsuki!
[SATORU]
All right!
♪ From the loneliness
blossoms a flower of hope ♪
♪ The wind blowing
fiercely and strong ♪
♪ Stand up straight and tall ♪
♪ So you're not pulled along ♪
♪ As the world sways ♪
[STUDENT 12D gasps]
What was that?
[CATS meowing]
[AGENT 12R]
What do we do?
I wasn't trained for
a cat invasion!
Look! My feline friends!
All right, let's go!
We're getting in there, too!
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
Push!
No, don't! Stop it!
[KAKERU]
All right! We're in!
[ODAWARA]
Excellent!
Whoa, is Sakutasuke on TV?
It sure looks that way!
Sit, Haruna! Watch with me!
It looks like your brother's
gonna perform, too!
[HARUNA]
Huh? Okay.
[SAKU, UTA, SOSUKE]
♪ ...to take ♪
♪ I don't care what world
you may be living in ♪
♪ Music will follow
where you go ♪
[SAKU] ♪ 'Cause in the future
you're the voice of hope ♪
[STUDENTS cheering]
[STUDENT 12D]
You guys are the best!
[PEDESTRIANS chattering]
[CROWD chattering]
They really are
amazing. Good job.
[BOSS] Hurry up! These Actors
aren't worth saving!
Just cut the power
and shut it down, now!
[MYSTERIOUS VOICE] If that's
true, would you care to
explain to us
"clueless higher-ups"
why Thrive Central lost money
not from lack of players,
but from "internal meddling"?
[BOSS]
No, I mean. I just--
[MITSUKI]
And now, for our next song.
We have something
special for you!
An all-students performance of
a brand new, original song!
"Inazuma Shock"!
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL] ♪ DON'T BE SHY,
get crazy NUMBER ♪
♪ Raise your hands,
raise em up higher ♪
[SAKU] This is what
the white shadow wanted.
A song that shows the
world what we're worth!
[ALL] ♪ Limit, limit,
push right through ♪
♪ To free the impulse in you ♪
--[CROWD] Short!
--♪ Break it, break it, ♪
♪ These nerve endings ♪
♪ Til they're
short-circuiting ♪
♪ Not yet, not yet ♪
[CHIGUMA, SATSUMA]
♪ We're still not done ♪
[ALL]
♪ Needs more stimulation ♪
[CROWD]
Shock!
[RYO] ♪ Can you call
a plain life living ♪
♪ Doesn't that get boring? ♪
[ALL]
♪ Our history ♪
[MIKE, SAKU, HINATA]
♪ (SO CRAZY) ♪
[ALL]
♪ Is shaking me inside ♪
[MIKE, SAKU, HINATA]
♪ (Like a dream) ♪
♪ Can you tell me what fun ♪
♪ Destination ♪
♪ Lies for us beyond? ♪
[ALL]
♪ INAZUMA SHOCK is rising ♪
♪ like a million
lightning bolts ♪
♪ Let's ROCK out our brains ♪
♪ and we'll give it the
SHOW it's desperate for ♪
♪ HURRICANE SHOCK, go wild
with excitement in your soul ♪
♪ Til it's all that
you can think of, ♪
♪ leaving you to
only crave it more ♪
♪ Those at the top ♪
♪ Are always fighting
for that spot ♪
♪ To challenge what we love ♪
♪ Let's chase that thrill
and aim high above ♪
♪ DON'T BE SHY,
get crazy NUMBER ♪
♪ Raise your hands,
raise em up higher ♪
♪ DON'T BE SHY,
get crazy NUMBER ♪
♪ Raise your hands,
raise em up higher ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[MITSUKI] Next up we have
Mike Enjoji and Kai Akizuki
from the Archaeology Club,
singing their song, "Checkmate!"
[KEISHI]
Mitsuki. Everyone. Thank you.
Good morning, Nozomi.
Good morning, Saku.
[USHIO]
You know how in baseball,
they say that once you go pro,
you can see the ball as if it's
stopped moving in mid-air?
That's exactly
what I experienced!
Clearly I awakened to
some innate abilities
that I didn't even
know I possessed!
Wow, that sounds crazy!
If that's actually true.
It's pretty impressive,
dontcha think?
[USHIO]
What? Why're you asking him?
Are you implying that
you don't believe me?
I am telling you, I dodged
their bullets in slow-mo!
[yelps] Excuse me,
what was that for?
I figured that you would
be able to stop it.
With your new skills.
Oh, um, I simply wasn't ready!
If we were to engage in
real man-to-man combat,
of course I'd be able to!
[USHIO]
There!
[MINORI laughing]
Once again, that was practice.
[KAORU]
Hmm.
[USHIO]
There!
[MINORI laughing]
[MIKE] All right! I finally
pulled the new ultra-rare!
Wow! Way to go!
That's so awesome!
Looks like I can get a good
pull from boxes you bought!
[KAI]
I'm happy you're happy, Mikey!
[CATS meowing]
[HINATA]
Well, they're back.
I don't know what we
were so worried about.
A catnip junkie is
nothing without his cats.
So I suppose I'll allow it.
It's so good to see you
all safe and sound!
Eat as much as you like!
[chuckles]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[USUKI]
Mitsuki. Do you have a minute?
Mr. Usuki. Sure, I've got time.
[USUKI] Great, then I'll
cut to the chase.
Would you mind filling
me in on whatever happened
the other day,
I can't seem to recall.
Oh, my. You're saying
you don't remember?
But you practically rescued
all of us by yourself, sir.
In short,
you were the savior of
the singing competition.
I see. Interesting.
I suppose it's good to
know I was useful, then.
Yes.
My back is killing me!
Why is this our job?
Stop whining.
Do not sully the name of
the Beautification Club.
Yeah, sure, you got it, Pres.
After we're done with this,
we have to fix the door to
the Broadcasting Club's room.
And I expect it done right.
Bruh. Just let me die.
[TAKATO] All right! Keep up
the pace! You're almost there!
Good. Nicely done.
Saku! Uta! I've got big news!
Oh yeah? What happen?
--Listen up!
--I'm listening.
It's time!
For what?
Sakutasuke is getting
our very first CD!
--Whoa!
--Huh?
Are you serious?
'Course I'm serious, why would
I lie about somethin' like that?
Aww yeah! Now a buncha people
all across the whole wide world
will get to hear Saku singing!
That's right! We'll get
to show off our vocalist!
You're putting a lot of pressure
on me right now, you guys.
[SOSUKE chuckles]
Well, you'll have our support!
I'll work hard to write
you great new songs.
You go, Sosuke-Bosuke!
Hey, you're gonna have
to work hard, too, y'know.
Huh? What do you mean?
Who do you think's gonna
write the lyrics, weirdo?
Oh! Duh!
I mean, who knows
what's gonna happen next.
I can't wait to see
whatever it is!
[SAKU]
I'm so happy I met you two.
I never knew I
could enjoy anything
as much as our time together.
Uta, Sosuke.
Thank you, from the
bottom of my heart.
Although our feelings,
they're always hard to see
They're still here,
living on inside of me
Just like the light that's
shining on within us
There's a warm embrace
enveloping this world
until it burns bright
Just look up into the sky
Look up to the sky
And as tomorrow gently
shines on today
Showing us the path
that we should take
And we pray these
dreams left in our hands
They will live
Like the birds on the wind
La La La La La.
La La. La La.
La La La.
La La La La La La La.
Ahh.
Tensho School Song