[CAT 5A meows]
Kinda seems like there are
more stray cats than usual.
And they all congregate
here because
our local catnip junky
keeps on feeding them.
Hewwo there!
Eat as mwuch as you want!
Oh, you are the cutest!
I don't even care anymore.
I'm used to it by now.
[chuckles]
[CHIGUMA]
Huh?
Is everybody taking
the day off or something?
--[phone chimes]
--[gasps]
[MINORI]
I found this awesome new game
that you should totally try!
I'll be waiting!
No one else is here, so...
I guess... I'm gone!
[CHIGUMA] Ohh. It's called
Cat Walk , huh.
I wonder what kind
of game it is.
[CHIGUMA] Guess I'll
go ahead and make an ID.
'Kay, now I'm gonna log on.
All right, I gotta come up
with a good display name.
Lemme think... um...
How about... Kuma... twice.
The avatars are actually
pretty cute! Huh?
Wait, do I have to pay
just to use one of these
character creator options?
No, that can't
be right. Hang on.
"If you bypass the
character creator,
you can play the
demo of the game,
which doesn't require
purchasing an avatar.
When playing the
game's demo version,
you are able to utilize the
chat function to interact
with the other
players around you.
However, because the Actors
in the game space cannot see
those of you playing
with the free version,
you'll be unable to
interact with them.
If you're enjoying
playing in this world,
please consider purchasing
a cute cat avatar,
and enjoy your life as
a cat interacting with
your favorite Actors up
close and personal."
Cool! I get it now.
Time to give the demo a shot!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[CHIGUMA]
Hang on, isn't this the school?
[PLAYER 5A]
Hey, what do you wanna do now?
[PLAYER 5B] Well, there's still
time before school ends. I know!
Why don't we go visit Ryo to
recover some Life Points?
[PLAYER 5A]
Sounds good to me!
I wonder where Minori is hiding.
[ringing]
[MINORI]
Hello?
Hey! Minori! I signed up for
that game you recommended,
and I'm trying to find you.
Hey, Chiguma!
I'm right over by the school's
clock tower at the moment.
Look for the brown tabby with
the name "Oppain," okay?
Come find me.
Brown tabby?
Guess I'm not surprised you
already bought an avatar...
I'll come and find you.
I'm playing the demo,
so I'm some kind of low poly
character in a white cloak.
Really? But you won't be able
to interact with everyone
in the demo version.
[CHIGUMA] Yeah, well, I wanna
try it out and see if it's fun
before I put money into it.
I'm heading over to you now,
wait for me, okay?
[MINORI]
Can do!
[NIKOMI-UDON]
Where's your cat avatar?
[TORORO-SOBA]
I can't afford one yet.
[CHIGUMA] Huh? The teachers
are coming this way!
[HOZUMI]
Good work today!
[CHIGUMA]
Huh? Whoa.
Wait, what's happening?
[CHIGUMA]
That's weird...
Maybe the collision
doesn't register properly
if I'm only playing
the demo version.
Huh? [gasps]
[MINORI gasping]
[MINORI giggling]
[CHIGUMA] Up to no good
as usual, I see.
You probably shouldn't
be using the game
to look up girls'
skirts, y'know.
[MINORI]
Uh... Hang on...
Chiguma? Is that you?
[CHIGUMA]
Yup.
Well, I'm a cat now.
And when I'm this small,
I can't help what I can see!
Might as well enjoy
the view, right? [laughs]
[CHIGUMA] But what's
going on with this game?
Everything is super realistic.
Mr. Usuki and Mr. Odawara
even showed up.
I know, right?! There are
so many people I recognize!
When I saw them
for the first time,
I was pretty surprised, too!
[CHIGUMA]
This is crazy.
I can't believe
a game like this exists!
[MINORI]
Ooh, I found the president
of the Tea Ceremony Clu!
Hello, gorgeous!
[CHIGUMA]
Minori...
[CHIGUMA] Excuse me!
Umm, floaty person!
[SASA]
Who? Me?
[CHIGUMA] Yes...
How are you floating exactly?
[SASA] If you push the F key as
the demo character, you float.
And you can go back down with D.
[CHIGUMA]
Oh, I got it! I'm floating!
[SASA]
Way to go!
[SASA] Also, try using the arrow
keys while you're in the air.
That way, you can get
a better look at things
while you're flying around.
[CHIGUMA]
Those are very helpful tips.
Thank you so much, Sasa.
[SASA]
You're very welcome!
[SAKU]
Well, Nozomi said I should go.
[SOSUKE] So... then there
shouldn't be problem?
[SAKU sighs]
Not quite.
That's pretty rough, man...
How so?
[UTA] Saku probably has a
lotta things to take care of.
Like living expenses
and hospital fees, yeah?
[SAKU]
Mm.
That's a lot of pressure...
[CHIGUMA] So this is
the illusive spot where
Saku and his friends go
to eat during lunch time.
Maybe I should
tell Kai this info
the next time he's
looking for him.
[UTA] So what do we
have to do to turn his
no-mon times into fun times?
Good question.
If he could make a
buncha money, I guess...
Then he'd be able to come on the
school trip with us for sure.
Yeah...
[NIAMIKA]
What do you think he'll do?
[YUFUMIN]
Who knows...
If he doesn't make enough money,
he'll won't be able to go.
[CHIGUMA] Hey, um...
what are you doing up there?
What?
Oh, we're stans!
Of these boys over here!
[CHIGUMA]
What's a "stan"?
These guys are really good
singers, if you didn't know!
They just come up with great
new songs out of nowhere.
So we always have to
keep an eye on them!
I know, right! They even
announced a new song just the
other day. Pretty sure it was
right over by the spawn point!
[CHIGUMA]
I guess that makes sense.
[UTA]
I know! You, and then... ta-da!
Yeah! Good idea!
I'll compose a new song and
Uta will write the lyrics.
You can sing it.
And then we'll sell it online!
With ad revenue
and sales galore!
You think? Would that work?
[SOSUKE] We haven't sold any of
our VOCALOID songs yet,
but they're pretty popular.
And if we have your vocals...
We'll get super rich
super quick!
Okay...
Great! Time to get to work, Uta!
[SENAKOBA]
Aren't they the best?
I actually just pulled another
gacha roll for these boys today!
[CHIGUMA]
I see...
[MINORI screams]
Help! Chiguma, please save me!
Hey! Is something wrong, Minori?
[MINORI] Hey! Cut it out!
Let go! Stop pulling that!
You okay?
[MINORI] You gotta come help!
These little brats captured me!
[CHIGUMA]
Where are you right now?
[MINORI] I'm behind the west
side of the school center.
[CHIGUMA] Gotcha.
I'll be there right away.
[BOY 5A]
Hey, quit squirming!
[BOY 5B]
Hurry up and tie it!
Almost got it!
[BOY 5A]
There we go!
[BOY 5D]
That's perfect!
Okay! Come with us, kitty!
[MINORI]
You can't do this to me!
I'm not a pet, I'm a person!
Chiguma can tell you,
if he was here!
[CHIGUMA]
Minori, are you okay?!
[MINORI]
No... Do I look okay?!
[BOY 5B]
...if you don't walk, Mr. Cat.
[BOYS chattering]
[CHIGUMA]
'Scuse me, kids.
Would you please stop
messing with that cat?
You're not much fun, are you?
Hey, come on, why won't you
just get up and walk, kitty?
Don't just float there! Help!
[CHIGUMA] I guess the demo
avatar won't work for this.
I can't interact with
them physically,
and I'm pretty sure that
they can even see me,
so I'm not sure what to do.
You've gotta be "kitten" me!
[RYO]
Hey, you brats.
[BOYS gasp]
Your lunch period
is almost over.
Shouldn't you guys be
getting to your next class?
[BOY 5A]
Aw man, he's right!
[BOY 5B]
Let's get outta here!
[BOY 5C]
Hey, wait for me!
[BOYS panting]
One sec. I'll get this thing
off of you in a jiffy.
Try to stay away
from rowdy kids.
[RYO]
Here.
[MINORI] Whoa, look!
That's pretty neat!
Food recovers life points!
I didn't know there
was a way to do that
without doing a gacha pull!
[RYO]
Eat as much as you want.
Later, cat.
Wow, he's such a great guy.
I owe him my nine lives!
[REI]
Oh, gross...
Who left an open tin
of cat food up here?
[gasps] Get back here!
That food was mine!
[REI]
Huh?
[MINORI growls]
[gasps]
Yeah, can you not?
Hey! Hold it!
Beautification Promotion
Club President!
Give me back my life
points, Rei Ichijodani!
[CHIGUMA] Wow...
Cats can be so helpless.
Dang it!
I'm totally gonna master
this game, and when I do,
no one'll be able to walk
over me ever again!
Just you wait and see!
[CHIGUMA] ♪ I wanna show you
this little device ♪
♪ Like a remote control
It switches up my life ♪
♪ It may look broken,
but it works just fine, ♪
♪ The shape is bent but I think
that helps the design ♪
♪ UP SIDE DOWN A B A B B... ♪
Heck yeah!
[MINORI]
♪ ...left. To the right ♪
♪ L R L R STOP AND DASH
AND UP AND TALK ♪
♪ It looks normal to me ♪
♪ I just need to find a break
and find escape out of here ♪
♪ But there is so much
I need to do ♪
♪ And it's never -
never - never enough ♪
♪ Just sit down, just sit down,
sit down please (yeah) ♪
♪ Just lean back, and relax
into the growing feedback ♪
♪ Turn around, Turn around,
turn it 'round ♪
♪ Because the motor's
truly roaring now ♪
♪ Keep dancing, keep dancing,
dancing night ♪
♪ You're in luck,
cause it's time now ♪
♪ for the complete mashup ♪
♪ Sing louder, sing louder,
singing now ♪
♪ I wanna sing better than
all the others ever did. ♪
[KEISHI] What's going on?
Why are they playing the game?
This is one headache
after another.
[KAKERU] Hinata! Stop what
you're doing! Hey! I got it!
Hi, Kakeru. What's goin' on?
Why're you so excited?
You're about to find out!
Look at this!
At what?
This message from my sister!
And?
"And" nothing, this is huge!
Go on, feast your eyes!
[HINATA]
Hm? Let's see...
"My friend wants to go see the
singing contest at your school,
so would you be able to
get us some tickets?
Please, 'kay thanks."
Don't you understand?
The this is my everything!
I thought my sister
was trying to avoid me!
But here she is,
asking me to help her!
Okay, sure!
[KAKERU] This is all
because of you! Thank you!
You are the greatest!
Wait... Hold on... Why me?
Don't you remember?
You told me how you wanted to do
one of Utasuke's songs for
the singing competition.
Uh... Yeah, I...
Well, I kinda remember
that part, I guess.
From there, I found out that
my sister loves Utasuke's music,
and I sent her a text about
you and your club, and then,
she finally returned
my messages.
I understand now!
If that's the case, she'll
probably be even more excited
to find out that Utasuke
goes to this school with us.
[gasps]
Who goes to what now?!
Utasuke goes to our school.
Was I not clear enough
the first time?
Are you being serious?!
Yeah... I am?
So?! Which class are they in?!
And tell me their
real name, too!
Um... What are you
gonna do if I tell you?
I'm gonna befriend
them, obviously!
That way, my sister
will think I'm
the coolest person ever! Duh!
[HINATA]
That makes sense...?
Right?!
I wonder if it's okay to...
You can trust me!
It's Sosuke Kagura.
He's from Class 1-B?
Uh--
[REI]
Mangy fleabag! Come back!
Stop running this instant!
You'll get your filthy
paw-prints everywhere!
[REI]
Dang it... Where did it go?
Is he gone nyao?
[CHIGUMA]
Yup.
[sighs]
[CHIGUMA] Huh? Wait.
Minori, where are you going?
Well, school's over now,
and I had a really rough day,
so I'm gonna go watch
the girls' swim team
change or something.
I gotta cheer myself up somehow.
[CHIGUMA] That makes sense.
All right, have fun then.
Wait, hang on, did you seriously
just say you're gonna
watch some girls
"change or something"?!
Yes. Yes I did.
[CHIGUMA]
That's not okay!
I can't let you go
do a lewd thing that!
Huh? But why, though?
I am a cat, so it's fine.
[CHIGUMA] I mean, just because
you're a cat in the game
doesn't mean you can run around
like a real life cat
with no boundaries!
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[CHIGUMA]
You mean it?
It'll be fine, Chiguma.
I'd only do something like this
in a game, not real life,
so try to chill out!
[CHIGUMA]
Oh, right. It's just in a game.
Wait.
[COACH 5A]
Go!
[CHIGUMA]
What's the matter, Minori?
You don't seem as peppy as
you did before. Are you okay?
Of course not.
The girls are all gone.
They're all done
changing already.
And the club room
was locked up, too.
[FUBUKIINU]
Oh my gosh, Itto's so hot!
Even when he's doing laps, he
looks like he's in a photoshoot!
Well, I'm totally
a Hozumi stan myself.
[RIEKOMACHI]
Yeah, me, too!
He can breaststroke
for me any time!
Aw! But I wanted to
swim a little bit longer!
No way! We agreed to swim
for an hour straight,
and then you said we
could take a breather.
I still have tons
of energy to burn.
Make sure you dry off
when you get out.
Wouldn't want you
to catch a cold.
Fine!
Wait... I think I left
my towel in the club room.
[HOZUMI]
You've gotta be kidding.
Lemme get it!
Wait! Stop!
You're gonna drip water
all over the place!
Hey, Itto!
He's gone... What am I
gonna do with him?
Aww...! So cute.
Don't give up on him!
You got this.
Let's check out their club room!
[NONOMIN]
Okay, let's go!
[CHIGUMA]
Hey, so... I'm a bit worried
about them following
Hozumi and Itto like that.
I think I should go, too.
[MINORI] Go ahead.
I'm going to sit right here
until it's time for the girls'
team to go and change.
Don't mind me!
[CHIGUMA] Wow, you're really
dedicated to this, aren't you?
--[door opens]
--[ITTO] I'm back!
Hey. Uh--wait!
Itto! You're still
wet and half naked!
Why did you come back
with your swimsuit still on?
What? I showered, so it's fine.
[TAKATO] You still don't
understand the issue, do you?
Hold it! Not another step!
[TAKATO] Hey, Ryunosuke,
could you get a towel for me?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Sure.
Will this one suffice?
But this one's mine!
Come on. It's fine, whatever.
[ITTO giggles]
Takato! That tickles!
[TAKATO]
Yeah, I know. Stay still.
Hey, you're gonna
mess up my hair!
So? Your hair's already messy
all the time anyway!
[ITTO]
But it really tickles!
[TAKATO]
Just deal with it!
Okay, there, you
can come in now.
[ITTO]
Yay!
[HOZUMI]
Hey, guys.
There you are!
I told you to look after Itto,
didn't I, Hozumi?
Why'd he come back here
all on his own soaking wet?
Sorry. But I did everything
that I could. I guess...
...he left his change of clothes
in here or something, so...
I can't believe this.
C'mon! Didn't I tell you
to bring your clothes
to the changing
room at the pool?
Yeah, but I don't like
changing alone.
Who cares? That's where you're
supposed to change. Got it?
Don't be a baby.
[RYUNOSUKE]
On the contrary,
he's rather intelligent
for his age.
Uh-- Seriously?
You're trying to tell me
that Itto is smart?
I'm just telling the truth.
He actually had better grades
than I did as a sophomore!
Yeah?! Prove it then.
What's your ranking? Overall?
From those tests the other day?
Overall? Hmm. Oh, that's right!
I think I got eighth!
There's no way!
It's the truth!
Okay. That doesn't make sense.
I'm not sure if he's a stupid
genius or a really smart idiot.
[RYUNOSUKE chuckles]
It's a mystery.
[TAKATO] You can say that again.
I'm completely stumped.
I don't get it. Did somebody
cut down your tree?
No, that's not exactly what I
meant with that expression.
I'm just saying, uh.
you're kinda like one of
those bizarre beings
that everyone's
been talking about.
Oh, yeah, I've seen one
of those things before!
[TAKATO]
Wait, you have?!
And you're only
telling us this now?!
--[RYUNOSUKE] Itto.
--Huh?
Do you happen to remember
where and when you saw it?
[ITTO]
Yeah. Of course I do!
[TAKATO]
Hang on a sec, Ryunosuke!
You aren't seriously
saying that you believe
in those weird things!
Are you scared?
You seem tense.
[TAKATO]
What?! Me?! Scared?!
Yeah, no way!
Why would I be scared?!
I dunno! It is
starting to get late.
Who knows what
comes out at night?
[TAKATO] Stop it!
You're doing that on purpose!
[RYUNOSUKE]
I wonder.
Could you describe what these
mysterious beings look like?
Please don't.
Well, lemme think.
They sorta look
like people, but...
Do you remember
what color they were?
[ITTO] Hmm. They were,
like, gray, maybe?
Notable features?
[ITTO]
Can't really say.
It looked like they
were smooth all over.
And they had these beady eyes.
[TAKATO]
That's enough outta you!
[CHIGUMA] Well, Minori,
are you feeling better now?
What? Is it that
obvious? [laughs]
[CHIGUMA] That is the
creepiest laugh I've ever heard.
Can I just say it was
totally worth the wait?
The boobies festival
was definitely worth
every single second! [laughs]
[KEISHI] Hey, I don't think
I've seen you two before.
[CHIGUMA] Oh, today is
our very first day of
logging in to the game.
Yeah? And are you two
having fun so far?
[CHIGUMA]
Yeah.
I'm amazed at how
realistic everything looks,
other than us, I guess.
Seriously! Not to mention,
I can see all the boobies
I could ever want in this game!
[KEISHI] To think that people
from Thrive Central are
accessing this system and
using their own world as a game.
[MIKE]
Hey! Wassup!
What's the matter?
You don't look so good.
Have you been slacking on
your self-care, Chiguman?
I had a hard time
waking up this morning.
My head hurts.
[MIKE] Lemme guess. You probably
played your video games
for too long.
Weren't you and Minori
gaming all day yesterday?
Yeah, come to think of it,
I thought we were playing
a really fun, new game,
but now I'm not sure.
What was it again?
I felt like I was almost
to the next mission,
but now it's kinda hazy.
[RYO]
Oh! Aren't you a cutie!
Are ya hungry, buddy?
[REI] Ryo Saotome.
Are you the one who's been
sneaking food to all
the strays on campus?
As the president of
the Beautification Club,
I cannot allow this to continue!
I demand you cease and desist!
Yeah? And how's
this your problem?
I'm just feeding some cats.
[REI] But you never
clean up after them!
Do you realize how
irresponsible it is
just to leave the food out?
I ought to get you arrested...
[SAKU] I can't keep
holding everyone back.
[SOSUKE] Hang on! It's true
we started this because of you,
but it's more than that now.
We're proud of this song, and we
want the world to hear it, too!
Don't you feel the same?