[USUKI chuckles] And then
I went through the door,
and it was crazy!
[ODAWARA] You are aware
that you're not supposed to
drink in the lab, right?
[USUKI]
Oh, don't worry 'bout it.
[MITSUKI]
'Scuse me!
[ODAWARA, USUKI]
Hm?
Follow me. This is urgent.
It's right over here.
[gasps] What? This is a...
[CAT chewing]
Uh?
[CAT purrs]
Must be nice to be a cat.
You don't have a
care in the world.
Hey! Stop it, that
tickles! [giggles]
[UTA]
Hello-suke, Sosuke!
[SOSUKE gasps] You're
actually showing up on time
for morning classes?!
Yes I am! I was up all night
listening to music, so...
Instead of sleeping,
I started the day over!
'Das wah happen.
Attending class really
isn't that high of a priority
for you, is it?
Also, you're pretty lively
despite pulling an all-nighter.
Don't tell me you
stayed up that long
because you had writer's block.
Yeah. You got me.
I'm a sham...
I soared through the
wonderland of my mind
into the early morning light,
but came up with nothing.
But you didn't come
across any issues
when you wrote "Cloudy Day."
Why's this one
giving you problems?
But as hard as I try,
I just can't fly.
Flightless dreams can't reach
imagination's wings. [gasps]
Maybe if I fly for real,
I'll find the
inspiration I need!
All right! Up, up, and away!
[SOSUKE]
Would you get down from there?!
[SOSUKE] You're worried
about Saku too, aren't you?
And here I thought we were
starting to become a
bit closer with him,
but then he drops us outta
nowhere for some reason.
But why not? You like
singing, what's the problem?
I just can't.
It seemed like something was
bothering him more than usual.
I wonder if there's more going
on with him than we know.
Well... It's not gonna
help if the two of us
act all weird about it.
Uta. I know it's hard for you,
but try to act normal, 'kay?
Be cool... Just casually
say 'good morning' to him
like there's nothing's wrong.
[SAKU]
Good morning.
[SOSUKE] Uh, same!
How long have you been there?
[UTA]
A causal good morning to you!
[SAKU] You're both here
on time? That's rare.
Hey, wait up!
He might be doin' just fine.
[UWAJIMA]
This is awesome!
[SOSUKE] Oh yeah? What are
you guys freaking out about?
Hey! What, you guys
haven't seen it yet?
[SAKU]
What's this?
[UWAJIMA]
They found this in the forest
by the university
section this morning!
Koya Ashihara, on the scene!
And we're bringing you a special
breaking news program today!
Take a look behind me...
There was nothing
here yesterday,
but now, there's this
circle of gigantic stones!
With us is Mitsuki Akika,
who first discovered this
alongside the teachers.
What are your thoughts?
It appears to
resemble Stonehenge,
and its origin is unknown.
I'm not sure what
to make of this.
[ODAWARA]
How curious.
Seems like we have
quite the mystery.
I can't wait to see
what we find.
This could give the
school's Seven Wonders
a run for their money.
I intend to give it a
thorough examination
from a purely
archaeological standpoint.
The Archaeology Club
wants to see it,
and we're heading there
after school today.
Are you two interested
in joining us?
Think I'll have to pass.
Don't really care for stuff like
the school's Seven Wonders.
[SOSUKE] I already do enough
wondering seven days a week
with that one.
Sorry, but I'm actually busy.
[KAI]
Aw, boo.
So bad news. About Saku.
He told me that he couldn't join
the Singing Club after all.
Aww, man!
Did you even make an effort to
tell him how cool the club is?
Well, we tried our best! Like,
Satsuma was super convincing,
but I guess Saku just didn't buy
it for some personal reason.
Knowing how pushy Satsuma is,
he prob'ly freaked him out.
Well, at least I'm making
an effort to help our cause.
You only complain and
take no action of your own.
I'd love to hear
what ideas you have.
Yeah, I've got plenty of ideas,
and they're great! I think?
Really?! Don't be
shy, Ryo! Tell us!
Hm?
That's weird. Guess he
doesn't have work today.
[SOSUKE]
The hospital?
[SAKU]
Hey, Nozomi. I'm here.
[SAKU] She has even
more medications now.
[NOZOMI]
It's nice to be included, right?
There're people who need you.
You're never alone.
[SAKU]
I know that... But still...
[DOCTOR 1A]
Oh, Saku. Back again I see.
Uh, Doctor.
It seems like every time I come
visit lately, she's asleep.
[DOCTOR 1A] It's a side
effect of her medication.
On the plus side,
her complexion seems to
be getting much better.
Hopefully,
her remission continues
going the way it has been.
Thanks for all your help.
[SOSUKE]
Hey, fancy meeting you here.
[SOSUKE] So that's why
you were at the hospital.
[SAKU]
Yeah.
[SOSUKE] Then you must have a
lot to take care of at home.
Guess that explains why you
don't have time for clubs.
[SAKU]
You could say that.
When do you think she'll
be able to be discharged?
[SAKU] That's the thing.
I don't know if she ever will.
So then... You're saying
there's no chance?
Not unless some white shadows
appeared and agreed to heal her.
Then maybe...
Some white shadows? [gasps]
I have to ask them...
For her... I need to.
Can you... tell me about them?
When I was little,
I heard a story...
They can even heal
injury and sickness.
If we need them to
and we ask nicely.
Sorry. Just forget it.
I know it's hard to believe.
I got it.
What do ya say we go looking
for shadows together?
[SAKU] Wait. But I
thought you said that
you didn't care for
weird stuff like this.
This is something you
believe in. So of course I care.
[SOSUKE]
Well, you know what they say,
two is better than one, right?
And three is better still.
I'll get Uta to help.
We'll meet up with you tomorrow!
[SOSUKE] Hmm. Looks like
a bunch of people
have seen these
white shadow things.
And yet, no one seems
to have any ideas
about they actually are. Huh.
[phone ringing]
[UTA]
Sosuke? What's up?
[SOSUKE] Hi. Listen, I met
up with Saku today, and...
Well, seems like he's got
a lot going on after all.
Thought so. The poor guy.
He's got it pretty rough.
[SOSUKE] Yeah... I've been
thinking about if there's
anything I can do
to help him out.
And I'm gonna need your
help with this one, Uta.
Do you know anything
about the white shadows?
THe white shadows?
This is something you
believe in. So of course I care.
I wonder if we can
find them together.
[SOSUKE] And we're here.
This is Uta's apartment.
[SAKU] Huh? Did you tell
him what we're doing yet?
Hewwo and welcome!
Thw two of you have
officially entered Uta Land!
[SAKU]
This sure is something...
[SOSUKE] We're here because
Uta's seen those white shadow
things a bunch of times
in this very room.
[SAKU]
Really?
Yup, it's true!
Sometimes they peek inside
through the windows,
or suddenly teleport behind you!
Wow... So how do you meet them?!
[UTA] They always show up
when I'm writing lyrics!
Great! Let's start
this investigation off
with writing some lyrics!
Roger that!
[UTA]
I'm getting performance anxiety.
Could you not look at me during?
[SAKU]
Oh, sure! Sorry!
'Kay, all done!
[SOSUKE, SAKU gasp]
[SOSUKE]
Nope! This method's not worth it
if the lyrics are
gonna be that bad!
[UTA cries]
Right here. The last time I saw
them was around this area.
'Kay. Let's split up and
try to search for clues!
[UTA]
Yeah!
[SOSUKE gasps]
Saku! Over here!
[gasps]
[meows]
Hey, how'd you get out?!
And what are you doing
all the way over here?!
Aw man, it's just a cat.
[SAKU sighs]
Is he your kitty cat, Saku?
[SAKU] Mm-hmm. Be careful
on your way back home!
[CAT meows]
They won't show when you
want them to, I guess.
Well... Guess we
can call it a day.
What? I'm not giving
up on you that easily.
But why? It's fine.
They're probably just
an urban legend.
And I really don't wanna keep
wasting your time like this.
Wasting our time?
Don't worry about it.
We're friends. We wanna help.
Yeah, friends! We'll
always be there for you!
Thank you, guys.
'Kay! New plan of attack!
We follow any potential
leads we can find online!
To the internet!
[UTA]
Still nothing...
[SOSUKE]
They were all dead ends...
[SAKU gasps] Oh, no.
I have to get to work soon!
That's fine! Just leave
the searching to us!
[SAKU]
But I...
Treat me to some curry
later and we'll be even.
[UTA]
Have fun!
All right. Now what do we do?
How to find white
shadows... [gasps]
I know! There's one
place we've gotta try!
[SOSUKE]
Is this really okay?
[UTA]
Gotta be in here somewhere,
just have to keep looking.
[UTA gasps]
Bingo!
[SOSUKE] I don't even know
what she looks like.
Hey, wait, what are you--?!
Who here uses red miso
as the secret
ingredient in her curry?
Raise your hand up high!
The heck?!
[NOZOMI giggles]
[NOZOMI] I see! So you're
the friends Saku mentioned.
Yes! I'm Sosuke Kagura.
And I'm Uta!
I'm glad. You two seem
like good friends.
Saku's always been a bit shy
and he's not open
about his feelings,
so I'm sure he's
been hard to read.
--Yeah!
--[SOSUKE gasps]
Sorry, he didn't mean that!
It's fine! His friendly side
is just playing a game
of hide-and-seek
with us right now!
It's like the sun peeking out
on a mostly cloudy day!
[laughs] Exactly. See, look.
If you leave a sunflower alone,
it'll grow towards the light.
But whenever I wake up, it's
always turned back towards me.
And I know Saku's
the one doing it.
He wants to make sure I can see
the flower's face at all times.
That's the just kind
of brother he is.
Oh, wow. I'm getting
the fuzzies!
So, um...
We're actually here to ask
you about the white shadows.
Do you know how
we can find them?
You two believe in them?
Well, recently, I've seen
some outside my window.
None right now.
[NOZOMI] Do you boys have
a wish you want granted?
Yeah, we do. We wanna wish for
whatever Saku wants to wish for.
Indeed!
Saku has wonderful friends.
I can't help but notice
that things are mellower
than usual today.
You think?
Oh! That must be because of
the added coconut milk!
It can make the spice
level pretty mild.
[MIKE] You dumbass.
I meant Saku, not the curry.
[KAI]
Really? What about him?
He's always pretty quiet,
but for some reason,
he just doesn't seem
as broody right now.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, Saku. You seem different.
Did something happen?
Really? No, not particularly.
[SAKU] I mean, I haven't
found the white shadows.
And I keep being a bother
to Sosuke and Uta, but...
[KAI]
Hm?
[MIKE sighs]
Okay, I'm full now.
Ready to get back
to investigating
that stone circle with me?
Here we are, back at
the scene of the stones!
There have been
reported sightings
of the fabled "white shadows"
near the mysterious henge.
They've currently begun
an intensive investigation..
Where is that happening?!
It's... uh... out in the back
woods on campus, remember?
[SAKU]
Sir, I'm really sorry!
But something came up and
I have to leave early!
Uh--Saku? Where are you going?!
How's this?!
It's like a purrfect little
kitty heaven now, right?!
[HINATA]
Yeah, but...
What exactly do a buncha
cats have to do with us
trying to get Saku to
join the Singing Club?
While you guys were taking
a more direct approach,
I did some digging of my own.
It's cats! He loves cats!
So if we had more cats,
then he'll join fur sure!
Well, I knew your idea would be
dumb, but this is a-paw-ling...
I won't have any part of this.
[SATSUMA]
Huh? He's here!
See! I told you cats would work!
Wow! He actually showed up!
How long I've waited for you!
The Singing Club is ready
for you to join our ranks!
We welcome you with open arms!
Aww yeah!
Nice... Saku really
blew me away.
Hurry up and put your shirt
back on, you creepy cat.
I've never seen Saku
run that fast before.
It's a classic game
of cat-and-mouse!
Right!
Wha? Are we seriously
doing this?!
[SAKU panting]
[SAKU] The white shadows...
I need to see them!
[SOSUKE] Saku really
cares about his sister
and does so much for her.
He's a great guy.
[UTA] But still... I wish
his fun side would come out
and play with us, too.
[SOSUKE singing]
[SOSUKE continues singing]
Sosuke, look over there!
[gasps] Is that a white shadow?!
It's right there!
Do you see it, too?
[UTA]
Mm.
[UTA gasps]
It's disappearing!
Hang on! Please don't
go! Stay, please!
Hold on a sec.
[SAKU] ♪ We quickly
lose track of time. ♪
I got it.
Those shadows--
The singing brings them out!
Uh, singing?
[SOSUKE]
We have to tell him!
[MITSUKI] Tell me, have there
been any new developments?
We were able to gather
a sample of these stones.
Apparently they're made of the
same material as the white wall.
[MITSUKI]
Is that so?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[USUKI]
Hey! What are you doing?
The tape says "keep out,"
can't you read?
Have either of you seen them?
The white shadows--
They have to be here around
here somewhere, I just know it!
I'm not sure what those are,
so I... guess I haven't. Hmm.
There sure are a lot
of cats, though.
[SAKU]
I heard it on the news stream.
There were some sightings here.
[MITSUKI]
Mr. Odawara was
looking into that
earlier, but...
Apparently, the person was
simply imagining things.
These stones may have
only appeared to be
white shadows from a distance.
I suppose that makes sense.
Hey, Saku! Did something
happen to you?
Don't worry. It's fine.
If something's going on
with you, you can tell me!
Are those cat ears?
[HINATA gasps]
Uh, hey, look! Mitsuki's here!
I didn't see you
standing behind us!
And I can explain the ears!
They're just, uh...
Calm down! There's no reason
for you to be embarrassed!
We're on a mission to
recruit new members! Right?
I must say, you're quite
resistant to Ryo's antics.
I'm rather impressed.
You're even more of a perfect
fit for the Singing Club now.
[SAKU]
Uh...
[KAI]
Hey!
[ALL panting]
[KAI] Saku! These two said
they needed to see you,
so I brought them
as fast as I could!
[MIKE, KAI panting]
I feel like I'm gonna
throw up right now.
[KAI]
That's what you get for having
the super-sized curry, Mikey.
Hey, Saku. We got it!
Uh--
Just sing.
And make sure that it
comes from the heart.
[BOTH inhale]
[SOSUKE] ♪ I thought everything
that I believed in. ♪
♪ Was real enough
to hold and touch. ♪
♪ So I, reached to the sky. ♪
♪ And I believed
that was enough. ♪
[UTA] ♪ Sometimes it's
hard to live your life. ♪
♪ Until you find someone
on whom you can rely. ♪
♪ Isn't that right. ♪
♪ That's the thing
that we call life. ♪
[SOSUKE]
♪ I can hear. ♪
♪ A faint voice growing clear. ♪
♪ A glowing light. ♪
♪ Like a pale illusion
in the night. ♪
♪ As its nearing. ♪
♪ It's resonating. ♪
[UTA, SOSUKE] ♪ If you'd
only close your eyes, ♪
♪ then you'd see. ♪
♪ So, please come
down from heaven now. ♪
♪ As you take on the form
of an angel. In this... ♪
I finally found you.
I have a request!
Please... I need you
to save my sister!
I don't want... to lose her.
[SOSUKE, UTA]
♪ I beg you. ♪
♪ I pray you'll give it life. ♪
What the?
Are you seeing all of this?
[SOSUKE, UTA]
♪ ...into the light. ♪
That song was
amazing! Way to go!
[SATSUMA] Those boys would
be excellent additions
to the club, too!
They can sing for us,
as well as write and
compose all of our songs!
What the heck was that
white floaty ghosty thing
supposed to be?!
Wait. Did you guys see
something that I didn't see?!
[UTA] We figured out
that the white shadows
seem to like it
when people sing!
Sosuke noticed it first.
All good? I'm positive
they heard your wish.
Thank you. It's all
because of your song.
We should be the
ones thanking you.
Our time together is what
inspired us to write that song.
That's the truth! And it's
all because of you, Saku.
The song... and you're
singing... I loved it!
[BOTH gasp]
[SOSUKE]
You better!
[ALL laughing]
[MINORI]
Hold it!
Beautification Promotion
Club President Rei Ichijodani!
Give me back my life points!
Get back here!
[CHIGUMA]
Wow, cats can be so helpless.
[MINORI] Dang it! I'm going
to completely master this game
and totally beat it!
Then we'll see who's stealing
whose cat food cans!