[KAKERU] Ya gotta
constantly reel in new fans
with a great hook!
So get ready.
The four of us are
gonna make a PV!
But how are the three of
us supposed to make a PV?
We're just a bunch of musicians.
We don't know anything
about filmmaking!
[KAKERU]
You just leave all that to me.
Your song made my
little sister so happy.
I just had to hunt you down
and return the favor! [laughs]
Hang on!
This thing isn't just about
the school trip anymore, Saku.
It's true, we started working
on it because of you,
but it's become
more than that now.
[SAKU] But... You don't
have to do that for me.
[SOSUKE] Do you think we're
only doing this out of pity?
Well that's not the case!
We're really proud of this song,
and we want the whole
world to hear it!
Don't you feel the same way?
Wouldn't that be incredible?
[gasps]
[KAKERU]
Here's my little sister
at our local shrine
for a festival.
There I am, standing
right next to her.
And this is her on the very
first day of elementary school!
Look at her little backpack!
And I'm next to her
in this one, too.
This was taken during
one of her sports festivals!
She was chosen as the
anchor for the relay.
She works so hard!
Of course, there I am,
cheering her on.
Aww. That's nice. She's a cutie.
Those sure were the days.
We used to spend so
much time together.
--But now...
--Yeah?
Things have changed.
She doesn't care
about me anymore.
All that matters to
her is Sakutasuke.
[gasps]
[KAKERU sighs]
I wanna die.
Why'd it end up like this?
Rough.
♪ We always envisioned what
we'd be like in the future ♪
♪ The people we... ♪
This is crazy!
This video's gotten
over 300,000 views now!
And the digital download
sales are still climbing, too.
And I helped with that!
Isn't that cool?
I mean, come on!
I helped out with my
sister's favorite band!
So she should think her
brother's awesome again!
That's why I worked so
hard to make this video!
And? How'd that work out?
[KAKERU]
Good question!
She told me that those
three were the real stars.
And that any loser could
have made them look good.
Can you believe it?
Why would she hurt me like that?
[chuckles]
[HINATA] There's the problem.
But why is he telling me?
[UTA]
♪ I can't see a thing ♪
♪ Everything's blurring ♪
♪ As my tears fall
to the deck floor ♪
♪ Oh "I LOVE YOU" but
will I ever tell you? ♪
♪ One day soon. ♪
Now I've got the last hook.
That key change feels great.
This is perfect.
♪ ...My dreams shining bright ♪
♪ So I will resume... ♪
That's it.
[UTA]
♪ ...and go on! ♪
The guitar riff they
use here is a nice touch.
[UTA]
♪ ...on! ♪
♪ Whoah oh Yeah ♪
Sosuke! Now it's your turn!
I'm not gonna sing.
I'm doing research.
[groans] Oh, it's no fun
if I'm the only one singing!
[music plays]
Not this one.
Pick a different song, Uta.
[UTA] Nope, too bad!
I wanna sing this one!
This isn't the type of music
I need. I'll change it.
[music stops]
[music plays]
'Kay. Sing this.
Hey! Why'd you stop the song?
Here's your honey toas-- Uh...
[SOSUKE, UTA growling]
Um. Is everything okay?
[music playing]
[SOSUKE]
So? What do you think?
It feels different from
your other songs.
But that's actually
what I like about it!
Uh-huh. So I think
it came out great!
Thought so! And you?
[SOSUKE] Hm? I could
really use your notes.
Then we can have you
write lyrics ASAP.
I don't wanna!
Huh?
Uta, why're you so
angry all of a sudden?
It's this song.
It's just a copy of the
one I sang at karaoke!
What? No, it isn't!
I only analyzed
the song's structure.
And then made a new melody by
adding my own techniques to it!
By using this method,
we can keep pumping
out quality content,
and consistently
produce a hit song!
What "hit song"? You big dumb!
Stop it, your sleeves
hurt! Cut it out!
Hey, no fighting! Please?
You're not even
playing music anymore!
You're just plagerizing now!
What?
[UTA]
Unless you're making remixes,
anything that isn't
made from scratch
isn't truly one of your songs!
I'm trying to become
a professional!
What's so bad about that?
I'm learning by studying others!
Well, I don't like it!
Well you're crazy!
And I'm outta here.
Fine, then go.
No, wait.
Our last song performed
extremely well.
I'm happy about that.
We need more.
I want to make sure our
next release is just as good.
[SAKU]
Mm-hm.
What's so wrong with
wanting to be successful?
There's nothing
wrong! It's just...
[SOSUKE] More people would
hear Uta's lyric-work, too,
if all our songs got out there.
[SAKU gasps]
Hey, Uta!
Forget him.
I wouldn't even bother.
But why not? Just apologize.
[SAKU]
Come back!
Saku.
I won't say sorry.
Uh-huh.
Sosuke knows what he did.
Sure. But...
Those songs are
supposed to mean more.
They do to me.
We should be pouring our
hearts into them together.
That's what makes them special.
I won't work on that cheap song.
My lyrics'll mean
nothing if I do.
Right.
[HINATA]
Hey, Saku!
Hey, Hinata.
Somethin' wrong?
[BOSS] It seems as
though we've been having
quite a bit of trouble with
certain Actors as of late.
Like them entering this world
on their own, for example.
As well as poking around
wherever they please
and entering the ninth ward
without any proper
authorization.
You should know that
management cannot
turn a blind eye to
these sort of incidents.
What are your thoughts on
the matter, Mr. Harumoto?
So that's it? They had a fight?
Yeah.
What now?
[KAORU]
Fighting leads to nothing good.
It increases aggravation,
which makes both parties
unable to process their
thoughts rationally.
Sugar can help ease
tensions at times like these.
Allow me to treat the
both of you to some sweets.
Oh, hey, Kaoru!
What do sweets have
to do with this?
[KAORU] Pleased to
make your acquaintance.
I'm Kaoru Narugo
from the Culture Club.
Now, come with me.
[KAORU]
Here you are, gentleman.
I brought some cannoli for you.
They're imported from Sicily.
Typically, they're served
with cappuccinos or espresso,
but matcha pairs
surprisingly well.
Now, then.
Please help yourselves.
Oh, wow! Don't mind if I do!
Whoa! Tasty!
Yeah!
Make sure you take
a sip of the matcha.
--That's great!
--[SAKU] Mm.
Heh.
So? What's the plan?
Do you just want those
two to make up, or what?
Well yeah.
Sosuke and Uta have both
helped me out so much
ever since I came
to this school.
Visiting my sister.
Pushing me to work
on songs. Everything.
We just became friends
but they're there for me.
--[HINATA] Right.
--[KAORU] Mm.
So then this time,
I want to help them.
By ending this fight.
[KAORU]
Hmm.
Do you believe that this
will resolve itself on its own?
I talked to them and
heard both of their sides.
[SAKU] Neither one of them are
necessarily in the wrong.
They're both right
in different ways.
It's hard. I don't see
how they'll reconcile.
That's how it can be
when they're that close.
You can't force them to make up.
Let them work it
out on their own.
[HINATA] Hm. Yeah, that's
a pretty good point.
I just don't like seeing
them fight. It's sad.
I'd like it...
...if they got along again,
even if it's selfish.
[USHIO]
Excellent!
[ALL gasp]
[USHIO] A passionate
friendship between men,
a bond found in its perfect
state only here in Japan!
And you, trying to do everything
you can to conserve this legacy!
Good sir!
You're the epitome of
the Japanese gentleman!
Oh, hello, Ushio.
Perfect.
Kaoru, you could learn
a thing or two from him!
How dare you pair these western
pastries with Japanese matcha!
Since ancient times,
it has been established that
matcha should be served with
Japanese confections only!
Have you never heard of
experimental flavor
profiles before?
No, I haven't.
That sounds gross.
All of your nonsensical
talk has made me hungry.
Good grief. You tend to be
far too old fashioned.
There's no shame in trying new
things from around the world.
Oh, please. I'm simply
more refined.
Ah. Japanese tea is the best.
Oh, yes.
But what you just drank is
black tea. It's from China.
Huh?
[USHIO]
How dare you deceive me!
It wasn't on purpose, I swear.
You need to question
your ordinary,
and broaden your
horizons, that's all!
You fool! Seems
your mind has been
poisoned by
inferior confections!
Should we stop them?
[HINATA] Nah, this happens
all the time. Don't worry.
If you're sure.
You need to question
your ordinary
and broaden your horizons!
[gasps]
[SAKU]
That's it! I get it now!
Thank you both very much!
I'm so lost.
[SAKU panting]
[UTA humming]
Meow, meow. Mrowowow, mrowww!
We're here.
[SOSUKE, UTA]
Hm?
What is the meaning of this?
You didn't tell me he'd be here.
[SAKU]
Hold on!
Both of you have good points,
but you need to work this out.
Come on.
Look, man. I understand
how you feel, all right?
But growth is important to me,
I'm not gonna budge on this one.
Stubborn even
when you're wrong.
I'm right!
No, guys, listen.
I think I know a way to
prove one of you is right.
[UTA, SOSUKE]
Hm?
[SAKU] Uta, you think we
should make original songs,
and we shouldn't borrow
ideas from others.
And Sosuke, you think
our music will get stale
if we don't study other
bands' styles, right?
Well, let's test those theories!
[BOTH]
But how?
Normally, when the two
of you work on a song,
Sosuke, you usually
compose first.
And Uta adds lyrics second.
That's how it's always been.
But what if you
did it backwards?
[BOTH]
By why?
Uta writes the lyrics
without music, from scratch.
Yeah?
[SAKU] And Sosuke has to compose
based on what Uta writes.
You'll have to match
his style this time.
Sure?
[SAKU]
You said it yourself that
you want to be a
professional musician,
and that being
versatile enough to
work off someone else's style
is part of that, right?
Uh. I guess so?
[SAKU]
Then I'll serve as the judge,
and listen to what
you come up with.
I'll figure out if
one of you is right.
Or if you're both right!
Or even if you guys
are both totally wrong.
It's worth a try. Isn't it?
Yeah, I'm fine
with that. Careful.
We've never worked
in this order before
because I know you
can't "Handel" it.
Oh, I'm going to make you
eat those words before long,
right along with
your trash lyrics.
Well I'm not feeding
you trash, only gold!
Okay, then!
If you're fine with these
conditions, then we're all set.
You each get three
days for your part.
All right? Sound good?
[BOTH]
Okay.
[chuckles]
[SAKU, HINATA]
♪ Even if we slowly grow apart ♪
♪ Even if we break
each other's hearts ♪
♪ It is always
waiting right here ♪
♪ Forever. ♪
♪ Our Answer ♪
[SAKU] ♪ This bitter-sweet
candy is filled with... ♪
[UTA]
Get that jerk out of your head.
You need the words!
The words! The lyrics!
The ear licks! [groans]
[HINATA] ♪ Please don't
trap yourself now, ♪
♪ you just gotta let it out ♪
♪ So just pick up your
guitar and play a chord ♪
[SAKU] ♪ We'll sing aloud and
make it up along the way ♪
[HINATA] ♪ And to the beat
our hearts are... ♪
Kitties?
Thanks for trying to help
me out with this, kit-kats.
But no amount of toe beans
can help me nyow.
Meowie, wowie, zowie.
That won't work.
[SAKU, HINATA]
♪ And I do believe. ♪
♪ This will be a
moment in time. ♪
♪ We will cherish and
always look back ♪
Uta finished writing
already? That was fast.
You didn't have to send them to
me through Saku, you big baby.
[SAKU, HINATA]
♪ ...we slowly grow apart♪
♪ Even if we break
each other's hearts ♪
These lyrics are...
[SAKU, HINATA]
♪ Forever. ♪
♪ Our Answer ♪
[HINATA] ♪ You're trying to
get through your boredom. ♪
♪ But what's new? ♪
♪ And that blank screen. ♪
♪ Right before you ♪
♪ You can stare all day
but it's no use ♪
[SAKU]
♪ That's not how you will find ♪
[SOSUKE]
♪ Yeah! Hey, hey... ♪
Ugh! Come on, Sosuke,
can you take this serious?
Or we're never gonna finish!
[SOSUKE]
♪ Yeah, hey, yeah, yeah, hey! ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah! ♪
[laughing]
[SCHOOLGIRL 8A]
Cut it out, you dumb boys!
[SAKU, HINATA] ♪ Although we
are far from perfect now ♪
♪ There's no way
we could count ♪
♪ the many futures ahead
that are waiting for us ♪
♪ Take that rainbow-
colored light ♪
♪ To the sky tomorrow,
and the days that follow ♪
♪ Though I goof around. ♪
♪ I have found that
although I'm acting tough ♪
♪ You're the one that
I'll always lean on ♪
♪ It's the truth,
I'm telling you, ♪
♪ I trust you more than anyone ♪
♪ Even if my voice
is fading out ♪
♪ You're the name that
I'll be screaming out ♪
♪ Take my hand -
a rush of feeling ♪
♪ Forever. ♪
♪ Our Answer ♪
[clears throat]
[SOSUKE]
Well?
[UTA]
How is it?
This song is exactly what
I expect from you guys!
So you're saying it's the
same as usual. Then I lost.
I guess... changing
up my technique
didn't affect things at all.
But still. Is that
really so bad?
I mean, think about it!
At the end of the day,
you two wrote a great song!
Personally, I can't
wait to sing it.
[SOSUKE gasps] Well, the final
product sounds good.
But it was way harder
than I thought.
[SOSUKE] I did my best,
but the whole time,
I felt like I was
a beginner again.
[UTA]
I've got a confession. Ta-da.
I kinda sorta cheated.
I just couldn't come up
with anything from scratch.
Huh?
Wait, what do you mean?
Well, you see,
these are test lyrics from
a different song of yours.
I ended up not
using them, but...
[sighs]
And that's what happen.
So you gave up?
It seemed like a
good idea at first.
But if I don't have
Sosuke's music,
the words don't come to me.
I feel the same way.
Getting inspired to compose
can be really tough,
but it's way easier when there's
great lyrics to look forward to.
[SAKU] I think when people
listen to our songs,
they can feel that we
all need each other.
When I sing,
I want everyone to hear what
your friendship means to me.
[UTA laughing]
[laughing]
[HINATA] That's good to hear.
I'm so glad those two made up.
Y'know, thanks to you!
Yeah. I'm just glad it's over.
[UTA]
Aww! No means no, ya big butt!
[SOSUKE]
Oh, come on, don't be like that.
Oh, Sosuke. Why would you
even say that to me?
I just want one little tweak.
This part's hard to
understand, that's all!
I'm not gonna change my
lyrics and that's final!
It's just this one spot!
Listen, this part doesn't
even fit with the melody!
[UTA]
Uh. Yes, it does!
[SOSUKE]
I'm telling you, it doesn't.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Uh--
Hey. Why don't we get
Saku's opinion on this?
He's gonna agree
with me for sure.
I'm done.
[SOSUKE]
Wait, Saku, hold on!
[UTA]
Aww. Come back!
Huh?
[SOSUKE]
Don't run away!
Ya gotta help!
[SOSUKE laughs]
What are you pouting about?
Aw, your face is so cute
when it's all puffy.
[UTA]
Pop!
[laughs]
That's good to see. I'm glad.
[RYO]
Love needs no words.
Cats express it
just with a look.
[SATSUMA] You idiot!
What were you thinking,
randomly going out and attacking
people on the street like that?
[KONISHI]
Which one of these jackets
do you think I'd
look the coolest in?