[STUDENTS chattering]
[SATSUMA]
This is perfect!
Since all grade levels are
permitted to go on school trips,
we can use this little outing
to gather our ranks
and foster some
club camaraderie!
We are singers, after all.
So why don't we all come
together in harmony?
[RYO] Who the hell plans club
activities during a school trip?
You nerds do what you want.
I'll be off hangin'
out with my friends.
Oh? You'll have to forgive me.
I had no idea
you were so popular.
Hell yeah, man,
you'd better believe it!
So. These "friends." Name one.
Well, I met this
cool cat on the street.
And a pigeon came and landed
on my head the other day!
So...
[laughs] A bird and a cat?
Perhaps the three of you
could form your own club,
and call it "The Town
Musicians of Bremen"!
C'mon, who are
your human friends?
Well, there's... you, I guess.
Then, let's "hang out"
together, friend.
[gasps] You mean it?
[HINATA]
Aw, how nice.
They can finally be honest with
each other about their feelings.
[sighs] Everyone here is insane.
[SOSUKE] You're really gonna
miss out on the school trip?
[SAKU]
Mm.
Angry face, frowny face, and me!
Angry face, frowny face, me!
Yeah. You sure look bummed out
for someone who
doesn't wanna go.
I do want to, it's just that...
Is it your sister?
That's not it.
Nozomi said I should go.
[SOSUKE] So, then there
shouldn't be a problem?
[SAKU sighs]
Not quite.
That's pretty rough, man.
How so?
[UTA] Saku probably has a lot
of things to take care of!
Like living expenses
and hospital fees, yeah?
[SAKU]
Mm.
That's a lot of pressure.
So what do we have to do to turn
his no mun times into fun times?
Good question.
If he could make a
bunch of money, I guess,
then he'd be able to come on the
school trip with us for sure.
Yeah.
I know! Eh. And then! Tada!
Yeah! Good idea!
I'll compose a new song and
Uta will write the lyrics.
You can sing it.
And then we can sell it online!
With ad revenue
and sales galore!
You think? Would that work?
[SOSUKE] We haven't sold any
of our VOCALOID songs yet,
but they're pretty popular.
And if we have your vocals...
We'll get super
rich super quick!
Okay...
Great! Time to get to work, Uta!
[SOSUKE] Hey, Tamotsu, mind if
I make some noise tonight?
[TAMOTSU]
Sure, dude, no problem.
Thanks, man.
It's nothing I'm not used to.
That's it!
[gasps]
I'm inspired!
These are the words!
I found this song's lyrics!
Yeah!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 6A]
Let's go grab some lunch!
[STUDENT 6B]
Yeah, it's beef bowl time!
[SOSUKE grunts]
[sighs]
Did I sing it wrong?
Nope. You totally took my lyrics
and nommed 'em right up!
Your voice gave them energy,
and a beautiful song
bloomed from it!
When he's right, he's right.
You did a great job,
as expected.
Your technique's
perfect, actually!
The real problem is...
[SAKU]
♪ We always envisioned ♪
♪ what we'd be like
in the future ♪
♪ The people we'd become,
they took shape-- ♪
[SOSUKE]
Our recording space sucks.
Not to mention...
This kind of microphone.
Well, you heard how it sounds.
Yeah.
[phone buzzes]
Hey, what's up?
Oh, great,
you picked up! Hey, man!
I wanted to see if you were
coming on the school trip.
Uh. Maybe?
So, us guys in
the Singing Club were
going as one big group,
you wanna come with?
Oh, I know! You should
invite Sosuke and Uta, too!
Actually,
we're having trouble with a
song, so it's up in the air.
Seriously? If it's
a song you're working on,
then is there something
I can help with?
--Uh--
--Yes, there is!
We're in the dorms and can't
record any clean vocals!
Well, you're welcome
to use the recording booth
in the Singing Club's
room if you want to!
We'll be there!
[RYO]
Got him miked up.
[HINATA]
We should be good to go!
How 'bout you? You ready?
Uh, sure.
Hey!
You've got this, Saku!
Show 'em what you've got!
Okay.
[music plays]
♪ We always envisioned what
we'd be like in the future ♪
♪ The people we'd become,
they took shape in our dreams ♪
♪ But did it come true? ♪
Wow.
Now I get why you were
talking him up so much, Hinata!
Unbelievable!
Told ya!
--[clapping]
--[gasps]
That was amazing, Saku!
I totes got goosebumps!
Well, for a guy
that eats cat food,
you've really got it together!
Might have to try some myself!
Such a great voice.
Now that all of us
have gotten to hear
your wonderful
singing voice in person,
we're going to have to pursue
you more aggressively.
[SAKU]
Uh--
We want you, Saku!
Thank you. But, I, uh...
[SOSUKE]
No, no, no! Damn it!
Can we help you, Sosuke?
What seems to be the problem?
The instrumental track
is weak and soulless.
His vocals don't match it,
they're too good!
Well, I'm afraid that
can't be helped.
I'm sincerely sorry
our digital suite
isn't up to your standards.
But I promise you.
With Saku's voice,
your composition,
and Uta's lyrics,
the final mix we
produce for this piece
will truly be
music to your ears.
I don't care how good
of a mixer you are.
There's no way you can match
these pre-recorded loops
to the quality of Saku's voice!
Nothing beats live sound!
Live, live, live, sound!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
We're gonna record a
custom backup track!
[UTA]
Saku! Let's go!
On an instrument quest!
[SAKU]
Wait!
Sorry. Um, Mitsuki?
Could we have the
room for a while?
We'll be extra careful
with it, I promise.
Please, be my guest.
Thanks, I owe ya one!
Good luck!
Those three really do seem to
have fun together, don't they?
[CHONO]
Okay, so as all of you know,
tomorrow's the start
of summer vacation.
Now, I do want you all
to enjoy your break.
But don't go slacking off
too much, all right?
Your school trip this year falls
during the second half
of your time off.
So make sure to do your
homework before you go! Got it?
[STUDENT 6C]
Yes, sir!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[SOSUKE gasps]
No way.
[SOSUKE]
It's not selling at all.
Five whole downloads, wow!
You know those are just from the
guys in the singing club, dude.
Maybe you'd be better off
if you just used VOCALOIDS.
[SOSUKE]
Don't you dare say that!
Saku, your performance
was amazing!
You did great. Both of you did.
I'm proud of our work.
I just don't understand
why it's underperforming.
I'm not surprised.
It's too shy right now.
The song is hiding in its shell.
How can it be "shy"?
Because it takes
after Saku here!
Sorry.
Will you two focus
for five seconds?
What are we supposed to do now?
[KAKERU] Well, for starters,
you could come down off the roof
and start talking to people!
[ALL]
Huh?
So how about it then?
It's time you three ventured
into the magical
world of marketing!
[SAKU]
Uh...
Who are you?
Kakeru Iimori of the
Beautification Promotion Club.
Hinata said you guys would
most likely be hiding up here.
Wait, he did?
But why was your club
looking for us?
Heh, heh.
[music plays]
[SAKU singing]
[ALL gasp]
Hang on a sec.
Yeah that's right. I heard
your song while I was cleaning,
which is our club's forte,
as you know.
So I recorded it for inspection.
Can't be too careful with
possible noise pollution.
So, he's a pirate!
A song thief who gets
all of his music illegally!
Without a care in the world!
What? I'm not some
filthy scallywag!
This is my sister!
Isn't she a cutie?
[ALL]
Huh?
[KAKERU] I had her listen to
this recording of your song.
She loved it so much,
she wanted a copy!
So I bought her one,
a hundred percent legally.
[UTA, SOSUKE]
We get it now! Thanks!
[SAKU]
Thanks.
To think that you guys were
Utasuke this entire time.
Your song made my
little sister so happy.
I just had to hunt you down
and return the favor! [laughs]
Favor? I'm not sure
that I follow.
[KAKERU] When you're
trying to sell new music,
you can't just expect
old fans to carry over.
You have to constantly reel in
new fans with a great new hook!
And I know just what you need.
The four of us are
gonna make a PV!
PV?
You mean a real
promotional video?
[KAKERU]
We'll make the perfect vid.
And then we'll upload it to all
the hottest streaming sites.
Never underestimate
what one great video
can do for a band's sales.
It's practically
free advertising!
That's how you move
singles in today's market!
But how are the three of
us supposed to make a PV?
We're justa bunch of musicians.
We don't know
anything about filmmaking!
[KAKERU chuckles]
You just leave all that to me.
[SAKU, SOSUKE, UTA]
Huh?
Not only am I a member
of the Beautification Club,
I'm also in the Drama Club, and
with me in the director's chair,
this video's gonna
be a smash hit!
--[SOSUKE, UTA] Huh?
--[SAKU] Uh...
[KAKERU] And then I'll
show the finished piece
to my beloved sister!
Weird flex, but I don't care,
we get to make a video!
I take it you're
the lead vocalist.
Which means you're gonna
be my shining star!
No pressure, but my masterpiece
lives and dies with you, 'kay?
'Kay...
[music plays]
[SAKU] ♪ Whoa ooh, whoa ooh-oh,
whoa ooh, whoa ooh-oh ♪
And...
[KAKERU]
Action!
Cut! You're way too stiff, Saku!
One more, from the top, boys!
[KAKERU]
Cut!
Damn it, cut!
I suppose that's usable.
Gonna have to hack it
in post, I guess.
'Kay.
[KAKERU] Rolling in for
scene three, take one!
And... action!
♪ But did it come true? ♪
♪ Did we see all of
our dreams through? ♪
♪ That's all that I ask,
says the me from the past-- ♪
[gasping]
Huh?
Man. So close.
Let's get that one again!
[SAKU panting]
I'm so sorry!
Take a little break,
okay? Breathe.
Just relax! You can do it!
[chuckles]
[BOTH panting]
♪ That your tears,
as they flow. ♪
♪ Know they will always
lead to hope! ♪
[KAKERU]
Cut! That's not gonna work.
You're way off tempo again.
[SAKU sighs]
That's 40 unusable takes, boss!
I think he might be
hitting a wall.
You're getting closer,
but I need you to really start
putting your whole body
into this performance.
It's time to show me
what you've got!
[SAKU panting]
All right,
let's give it another go!
'Kay, here comes take 41!
[SAKU groans]
[KAKERU]
Hm?
Wait, everyone, hold!
It looks like
we're losing light.
Better call it a day soon.
Saku has to go to work now, too!
All right, that's
a wrap, everyone!
[door opens]
Hi, welcome to--
Moshi mosh!
[SOSUKE] Kakeru said he'd
edit everything in post later.
Anyway.
Tomorrow we're gonna shoot
the actual performance scene.
And everyone from
the singing club
said they'd swing
by and be extras.
Of course, we'll be there, too.
I believe! It'll be great!
Sorry. You guys are
all doing so much, but...
[SOSUKE sighs]
No matter what I did or
how hard that I tried,
I just couldn't ever
get it together!
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You're allowed to struggle.
I can't keep holding
everybody back.
Saku.
Both of you are going
through a lot of trouble
to make sure I can
go on this trip.
If I just don't go, then...
Hang on!
This thing isn't just about
the school trip anymore, Saku.
It's true, we started
working on it because of you,
but it's become
more than that now.
[SAKU]
But...
You don't have to--
[SOSUKE] Do you think we're
only doing this out of pity?
[gasps]
Well we aren't!
We're really proud of this song,
and we want the
whole world to hear it!
Don't you feel the same way?
Wouldn't that be incredible?
[gasps]
This song. The three
of us made it together.
And that's why we've
gotta finish this PV!
[gasps]
You guys. I'm getting so hungry.
[stomach grumbles]
[SAKU, SOSUKE chuckle]
Can we get two Volcano
Curries, please?
[SAKU]
Mm-hm.
[RYO clears throat]
[KAKERU]
All right, places, everybody!
Scene nine, from the top!
And...
[music plays]
[KAKERU]
Action!
♪ Just a little more
Let's see what's in store ♪
♪ 'Cause tomorrow is
where we will see ♪
♪ all of our dreams
coming true ♪
[SAKU gasps]
♪ So don't over... ♪
[SAKU] I messed up again.
Can I... really not do this?
[KAKERU]
Cut!
No, Saku.
[SAKU]
I'm sorry.
[SOSUKE]
♪ We always envisioned ♪
♪ what we'd be like
in the future ♪
♪ The people we'd become,
they took shape in our dreams ♪
[UTA]
♪ But did it come true? ♪
♪ Did we see all of
our dreams through? ♪
♪ That's all that I ask,
says the me from the past ♪
[UTA, SOSUKE] ♪ So whenever
you're feeling down ♪
♪ just remember this one thing ♪
♪ That your tears,
as they flow ♪
♪ Know they'll always
lead to hope ♪
[SAKU]
That's right.
We're gonna show the world
this song together!
Sosuke! Uta!
[ALL]
♪ So don't overthink ♪
♪ Don't you change a thing ♪
♪ Cause I like you
just the way ♪
♪ that you are ♪
♪ Stay true to your heart! ♪
[SOSUKE]
♪ Our dreams were always ♪
♪ nothing more than
perfect stories, ♪
♪ Like worlds we could
walk through... ♪
This is awesome!
The view count
keeps on climbin'!
[UTA]
♪ How many long nights ♪
You guys. Our band is real now!
And we're doing the thing!
How are the downloads doing?
Let's take a look.
The sales are...
...off the charts! Oh, wow!
[ALL cheer]
Happy face, happy face, and me!
Now the three of us can all go
on the school trip together!
[SAKU]
Mm-hmm!
Thank you both for everything.
[UTA]
I wasn't. I was just hungry.
[SAKU, SOSUKE, UTA]
♪ Get back on your feet ♪
♪ We've got dreams to meet ♪
♪ Let's go make our
story non-fiction ♪
♪ and we'll turn it to song ♪
[HINATA, SATSUMA, MITSUKI laugh]
[RYO] I haven't seen a spread
like this in forever!
Delicious!
I love purple yam.
Mm. Nice, indeed.
Looking back now,
I can't believe how clear and
blue the ocean was that day!
It was gorgeous!
I can't believe that we
were right frickin' there
and I didn't get to pet
one damn Iriomote cat.
Well, well!
I take it the Singing Club
went to Okinawa, then?
Yeah, where'd you guys go?
To Hokkaido!
But in the end the trip
was completely pointless.
I went and bought
my little sister
a whole armload of souvenirs
I thought she'd love,
but she didn't even
look at them!
She was too busy
re-watching our PV.
[HINATA laughs]
But it's great that the PV's
doing so well online.
You four should be really happy!
You're right about that!
But where are they anyway?
--[footsteps]
--Huh?
--[UTA] Hey-o!
--[SOSUKE] Hello again!
Hi, boys!
Did you have a good time
on your school trip?
Yeah! It was awesome!
I'm glad.
We made memories!
And got some memorabilia!
Wow!
[SOSUKE] Check out what
I bought! It's a Shisa!
[NOZOMI]
Oh, how cute is that?
[SAKU] The ocean was
beautiful there, too!
I wish you could have seen it!
[NOZOMI giggles]
[MIKE]
What a crazy prank.
Is this some kind of
cosplay contest?
My name is Mitsuse.
A woman of Yoshiwara.
[KAI]
You can't leave me like this!
I would have apologized
sooner if I knew!
Open your eyes, please!