[FESTIVAL GOERS chattering]
[NOZOMI]
There are beings in this world
called "white shadows."
They hide in the nooks and
crannies of pale-washed walls,
trees, plants,
and in the twisting alleys
around every corner.
These entities watch
over and protect us all.
[alarm clock beeping]
[SAKU grunts]
[yawns]
[SAKU]
The "white wall."
It's been so long.
[SAKU]
After ten years, I'm back.
Whoa! You seriously
outdid yourself today!
[NANAKO] I guess you like
my new omelet recipe!
[HINATA]
Mm. It came out super fluffy
and the rich flavor's
nothing to sneeze at either!
I heard fancy hotels make
their omelets like this,
so I thought I'd give it a try.
I'm so glad it worked out.
Certainly tastes fancy!
Hats off to the chef!
Since when were you
such a connoisseur, dear?
[YOSUKE] Well, uh,
you know. Since always!
Oh! Right!
I wanted to ask you
about Saku's sister.
I heard that she was
in the hospital!
Do you have any idea
if that's true?
[HINATA] Mm. I'm not sure
about the details, but yeah.
That's where Saku's been.
So the school ended up
delaying his transfer date.
But he's gonna
start class today.
[YOSUKE]
Hinata.
He might need some help.
Make sure you're there for him.
Don't leave him hanging.
[HINATA]
Yeah! I know, Dad.
I was already planning on
walking with him
to school today.
--[footsteps]
--[HARUNA groaning]
Hey! Mom! Why didn't
you wake me up?
I tried, but you
said, "Go away!"
and went back to sleep, so I did
what you asked and went away.
You're so useless.
This is your fault! Jerk.
Mine?
[NANAKO] Wait, Haruna,
what about breakfast?
[HARUNA] I don't have
time to sit and eat!
[NANAKO]
Hold on!
You're not leaving
without eating some toast!
[HARUNA]
Put it in my mouth, then!
[NANAKO]
Fine, just be careful!
[HARUNA]
Okay, I'm off!
Never a dull moment with her.
Aw man, talk about cliché.
Running to school with
toast in her mouth. [gasps]
'Kay! I'm gonna
get going now, too!
[SAKU]
Thanks for the food.
Oh, right.
Can't forget to bring a
change of clothes for Nozomi.
--[CATS meow]
--Uh, sorry 'bout that!
Hey, Saku! Mornin'!
Huh? Were you waiting for me?
What's up?
Well, it's your first day
at a new school, right?
So, I figured I'd walk you there
and give you a tour. Ha, ha.
Yeah. Thanks.
[HINATA]
No problem, man.
Also, random question,
but do you still sing?
Huh? Uh, yeah?
[HINATA]
Okay, great! Good to know!
[SCHOOLGIRL 1A]
Morning!
[SCHOOLGIRL 1B]
Hey, how're you?
So, whaddya think?
It's pretty fancy, right?
Sure.
[HINATA]
We have kindergarten all the way
up through post-graduate
programs here,
and they put a
really big emphasis
on everyone
participating in clubs.
Oh! And I'm in the
Singing Club, myself.
[SAKU]
I see. That's interesting.
[HINATA] I know! Anyway,
how 'bout we start off
the grand tour with a little
visit to the high-school office?
That works for me.
[CHONO]
All right, allow me to introduce
the new transfer student,
Saku Otonomiya.
'Kay, class, let's make
him feel welcome.
So, is there anything
you wanna say?
Uh--
My name is Saku.
Nice to be here.
Is that all?
Well, suit yourself.
Hey, Kai!
[KAI]
Uh, yes?
[CHONO] You can go ahead and
grab the seat next to him.
[SAKU]
Mm.
[CHONO]
Take care of him, will ya?
[KAI]
You got it!
I'm Kai Akizuki.
If you need any help,
just let me know.
[SAKU]
Yeah.
One more thing.
Be sure to fill him in
about the clubs.
Can do, sir!
That's it for homeroom today.
Good luck with your
classes and study hard!
[STUDENTS]
'Kay!
[KAI]
Hey, Saku.
I'm in the Archaeology
Club. You wanna join?
Huh? Well, uh...
[RYO snoring]
Hey, Satsuma!
Yeah? Is something up?
You gotta check out
this song, it's awesome!
[music plays]
[SATSUMA]
Ooh. It's a VOCALOID song.
[HINATA]
What if we performed this
for the next
singing competition?
I bet it'll be a huge hit!
So, what do you think?
Let's see. I do like the lyrics.
And the melody's nice.
Mix is good.
But do we know anyone who can
sing with this kind of range?
Sure do! I know a guy
who'd be perfect for it!
Someone who's not in the club?
Yeah. He's actually someone
I went to middle school with.
And he just
transferred here today!
That's wonderful to hear!
Have you asked him if he
wants to join the club?
[HINATA] Well, I haven't
gotten around to that part yet,
but I'm workin' on it!
This guy's an amazing
singer though, trust me!
I'm gonna convince him to join
our club in no time, you'll see!
[RYO] I gotta say, this new
recruit you're scouting
sounds pretty promising.
Good goin', Hinata!
[HINATA]
Ah! Hey, Ryo!
Oh, great. He's finally up.
And what do you mean by that?
Allow me to explain!
That's what's called "sarcasm."
While the words used are
nice, the tone and context
show that I'm displeased
with your presence.
Oh. Makes sense.
Wait, no, that's rude!
That is some
next-level disrespect!
Seriously! You didn't
just sass me,
you had to rub it in
with your explanation, too!
Relax! He was just
messing around!
Anyway, do me a favor.
Listen to this song
real quick, wouldja?
Here.
Oh, wow.
I've never heard lyrics with so
much raw emotion behind them.
[HINATA]
See what I mean?
[RYO]
Mm.
[SAKU] What's the deal with
that white wall, anyway?
[SAKU] It looks like it's
grown in the last ten years.
[KAI sighs]
That's weird. I wonder
where he ran off to?
[ODAWARA] Do you mind
taking these with you and
distributing them for my
class later this afternoon?
I'd greatly appreciate it.
[MIKE] Yes, sir,
that's no problem at all.
Consider it done, Mr. Odawara.
[KAI]
Hey, Mikey!
[MIKE gasps]
Wassup? Bring it in, buddy!
Kai? Wassup yourself.
Get offa me!
How nice.
Well, you boys have fun.
[MIKE]
Uh, yes, sir.
We will! Right, Mikey?
Shut up, you idiot! And get off!
Anyway,
have you seen that new
transfer student around here?
Huh? What transfer student?
You know. Saku?
Mr. Chono asked me
to look after him,
show him around campus,
and tell him about
club activities and stuff.
But as soon as lunch
started, he ran off,
and I haven't seen him since!
How would I know where he went?
Oh, Mikey.
Also! Quit it!
My name isn't pronounced
"Mikey," It's Mike! You got it?
So, make sure you get it right.
If you say so, Mikey!
Screw you. Now you're
doing it on purpose.
[KAI]
Huh?
Fine, go ahead and play dumb.
At least make yourself
useful and carry these.
[KAI] Hang on, Mikey,
I don't have time right now!
I'm supposed to be looking
for the transfer student.
[MIKE] I told you not to
call me that at school!
[KAI chuckles]
[SOSUKE] Hey, Uta.
Where are you right now?
What?
What do you mean you're
already back at the dorm?
Don't you remember?
We were supposed to
work on our new song today.
And after I went out of my way
to get you lunch and everything.
Huh?
[SAKU]
Hm?
[SATSUMA] The song is nice,
but we can't do anything with it
if we don't have the original
creator's permission.
[RYO]
That's true.
Do you have a plan for how
you'll get the go-ahead?
I actually follow the
composer on social media.
So I'll reach out. That might
be the easiest way to do it.
Uh-huh. Yeah. Fine.
'Kay, then, I'll call you later.
So, you must be
Saku, the new kid.
And you're eating up
here all by yourself?
Y'know Kai's lookin' for you.
Uh?
Just relax. I get it,
you're probably wondering
who the hell I am, right?
[SAKU]
Mm.
We're in the same class,
if you didn't know.
The name's Sosuke Kagura.
Okay?
Yeah. Pleasure's mine.
Uh, likewise.
Hold on. Is that really
all you have to eat?
You want one of these?
Uh, sure, I guess.
If you're offering.
It's no problem.
I actually brought it for a
friend of mine, but he bailed.
[SAKU]
I just took it without thinking,
but maybe I shouldn't have.
[phone buzzes]
[SOSUKE]
What the?
[USUKI]
Mitsuki. Do you have a minute?
[gasps] Mr. Usuki.
Sure. I've got time.
[USUKI] Great.
Then I'll cut to the chase.
I'm wondering. Have you
made any progress so far?
[MITSUKI] Are you referring
to the "white wall"?
[USUKI]
I am.
Apologies. Nothing to
report yet, unfortunately.
That said, I did find the
"conduit" you were looking for,
if that's any consolation.
Conduit?
You mean the one
to the 9th ward?
That's right.
Mr. Odawara assisted
me in tracking it down.
The information
is quite limited,
but I do have access to
enough for a good lead.
Well, that's incredible news.
But, sir, I know you're
aware that the 9th ward
rarely shares any
information at all.
So if there's a leak, the source
will be easily identified
and then quickly cut off.
[MITSUKI] That's why
we don't hear much about
their internal affairs,
which makes things difficult.
That makes sense. Such a strict
information management
system was to be expected,
so I suppose that's no surprise.
I understand. Please continue
on with your research.
Absolutely, sir.
[HINATA]
Get a loada this!
That song's composer
goes to our school!
Wow! In that case, it should be
easy to talk to him in person.
Yeah! I'll message
him and see if he'll
meet up after class.
Have a good one Mr. Usuki!
Thanks! You two get home safe!
[JUDO STUDENT 1A groans]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[SOSUKE]
Uh, hi?
Hey! Are you that "Utasuke" guy?
Yeah. I am.
So then... I assume
one of you is "S-U-N."
Oh! "SUN." That's me.
But my IRL name's Hinata.
Nice to meet you!
Sure. Same.
So, you guys wanted to sing
one of my songs. That right?
But which one?
[HINATA]
Uh-huh!
We all listened to
"Cloudy Day" and loved it!
The next singing
competition's soon,
and we were hoping that
we could sing your song!
So your club wants to
do a cover? For real?
[HINATA]
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
Is that... a "no"?
It's not a "no," but... I just
don't think it's possible.
Nothing personal, guys.
[SATSUMA] Are you worried
that none of our singers
have the range?
I'm Satsuma Kadonooji.
And you are?
Sosuke Kagura.
It's a pleasure.
You're a freshman, right?
Yeah.
And have you ever heard our
Singing Club in action before?
Can't say that I
have. But still,
that song was made for
VOCALOIDs with unlimited range,
and wasn't exactly written
with the human voice in mind.
Like I said before, it's nothing
personal, I'm just saying.
Yes. That's true.
I wonder, are you capable
of singing, Sosuke?
Uh? I can.
Perfect! In that case,
would you be interested
in joining our club?
Seriously? Me?
That's right.
[SAKU]
Hey, Nozomi.
I'm gonna put your clothes
in here. That okay?
[NOZOMI]
Mm. Thank you, Saku.
[DOCTOR 1A] So, how are
you doing, Miss Otonomiya?
I'm feeling much better now.
My fever has gone down,
and I have more energy today.
That's certainly
wonderful to hear.
It looks like the new meds
are working like we'd hoped.
[NOZOMI]
Yes. Thanks so much, doctor.
And, of course, it's always good
to see your dear little brother
stopping by every
day to support you.
I agree. He's been
incredibly helpful.
Thanks, sis.
I have to get to work
now, so I better go.
[NOZOMI]
It was good seeing you.
--[NOZOMI] Get there safe.
--Yeah.
Oh, it was "Saku," right?
[SAKU]
Hm?
Could I have a moment with you?
Uh, sure.
Well, I consider myself more of
a composer, even if I can sing.
Also I'm not really
interested in clubs.
Regardless, I'll think about it.
Before you go.
If we practiced and were able
to sing your song, what then?
Would you let us perform it
at the next competition?
If you can hit all
the notes, then sure.
Okay! Great!
We'll do our best!
[SOSUKE]
Mm.
[SAKU]
Ow! It hurts!
[NOZOMI]
Saku, it'll be all right.
I asked the white shadows
to make all the pain
go bye-bye, okay?
[gasps] The "white shadows"?
[NOZOMI]
Mm-hmm! Over there.
You'll see them if
you look real hard.
Where?
Well, I guess you can't
see them just yet.
[NOZOMI]
There are beings in this world
called "white shadows."
They hide in the nooks and
crannies of pale-washed walls,
trees, plants,
and in the twisting alleys
around every corner.
These entities watch over
and protect us all.
Wow.
They can even heal
injuries and sickness,
if we need them to
and we ask nicely.
[SAKU]
They can fix anything?
[NOZOMI] Mm-hm! And they've been
watching over the two of us
your entire life!
This all started when
I was about your age.
See? It doesn't
hurt anymore, right?
[gasps] It went away!
[NOZOMI giggles]
[DOCTOR 1A]
It looks like she has...
...three to six months, at best.
[SAKU]
Nozomi.
Yeah, and then they
invited me to become
a part of the Singing Club.
It was nice of them
to make the offer,
so I'm flattered, I guess.
[SAKU] ♪ We quickly
lose track of time. ♪
♪ Another today's slipping by. ♪
♪ And it's much too late
before we realize. ♪
♪ That it's our hearts
we've left behind. ♪
♪ Cloudy Day. ♪
Wow.
♪ The words that
we gave up on. ♪
♪ And all of the
words we have spun. ♪
♪ They're now
disappearing into the sky. ♪
♪ What d'we do
when all is done? ♪
♪ Upon a song, I soar. ♪
♪ It may be only
in my dreams now. ♪
♪ But someday I know it. ♪
♪ Will turn into
something more. ♪
♪ Shining through the clouds! ♪
♪ Forever, it flies eternally. ♪
♪ And we are left picking up. ♪
♪ The broken pieces
of our dream. ♪
♪ Let's take this loneliness. ♪
♪ And turn it into
a spark of hope. ♪
♪ Something is calling me. ♪
♪ A whisper, that shows
the right way to go. ♪
♪ Just like a song. ♪
♪ Guiding me on. ♪
♪ To take the step
that leads me ahead. ♪
♪ And that is where
our story will begin. ♪
--[SOSUKE] Hey, Saku!
--[gasps]
You're perfect!
Wait. I'm what?
That song.
The way you sang it was amazing!
[SAKU]
Uh, thanks. I guess?
And I would know!
The song is mine!
Huh?
[SOSUKE] The Singing Club
just asked me about it today.
They wanted my permission to use
it for an upcoming competition.
But I didn't think anyone
could sing it properly
since I wrote it for VOCALOIDs!
If you joined their club,
then it'd be no problem!
I would totally let them use it,
but only when they have you!
[gasps]
[SAKU grunts]
Somethin' wrong?
[SAKU] The white shadows.
I saw them standing there!
[SOSUKE]
What?
I have to ask them.
For her. I need to.
Ha. We might be able to
use this one. Perfect.
[alarm clock beeping]
[yawns]
--[CATS meow]
--Oh, sorry.
Aww man.
I can't believe he
disappeared on me again!
--[CHIGUMA] Kai.
--Huh?
[KAI]
Hey, it's the Chigu-man!
Is everything okay?
You looking for the
transfer student again?
Yeah. He's slippery.
Have you seen him
around, Minori?
Well, we just came
from the school store,
and he wasn't there.
Maybe he's checking out
the clubs that aren't yours.
[KAI]
What?!
Yep! Right where
I thought you'd be!
I brought somebody I've been
meanin' to introduce you to.
Hey! Are ya there?
--[UTA] Here!
--[BOTH] Huh?
[SAKU shrieks]
Nice entrance, ya weirdo.
So! This is Uta Outa.
He's the one who
writes my lyrics.
Uh--
Nice to meet you.
My name's Saku.
Saku, huh? My name's Uta.
Let's all have some
fancy, flavorful fun!
Uh, 'kay? [gasps]
From this day forward,
it's gonna be the three of us,
and I hope the two
of you are ready
to take the music
world by storm!
Huh?
[UTA]
Okay!
[SAKU] Wait. What are
you talking about?
[KAI]
I don't accept this.
[MIKE]
What are you doing, Kai?
[KAI] Saku, it's nothing
personal. I'm sorry.
But my pride is on the line,
and I have to do whatever
I can to defend it!
I challenge you to a
culinary cookoff of curry.