- Lottie: THIS IS IT, GUYS.
SPREAD OUT.
- CREW, REPORT.
- Both: IN POSITION.
- ( beeping )
- HERE WE GO. LET'S GET
IN THERE AND KICK SOME ASS!
( yelling )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( Lottie grunts )
- GOOD. LOOKS LIKE
WE MADE IT THROUGH
THE FIRST CLUSTER OF TUMORS.
IT'S ABOUT TIME TO BRING ON
THE NEXT BATCH.
THEY WERE PLAYING DEAD AGAIN.
- ( siren blaring )
- I'VE GOT ONE READY
TO SELF-DESTRUCT. DAMN IT.
- Sara: LOOKS LIKE
YOU NEED A HAND.
- SARA? WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?
ALL UNITS PREPARE
FOR CHANGE IN FORMATION.
MARTHA, TAKE THE RIGHT WING.
ERMY, THE LEFT.
LAVINIA, YOU'RE
BRINGING UP THE REAR.
- Laivina: ROGER.
- Lottie: UNITS, GO.
- I WILL STOP YOU, BROTHER.
- ( siren blaring )
- ( breathing heavily )
- Automated voice: EXACTLY
THIRTY MINUTES TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
ALL HANDS,
EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY.
- WAIT FOR ME, EMILY.
I'M COMING.
- Craven: WHAT IS THE STATUS
OF THE ENEMY SHIP?
- THE DEAGUE SHIP
IS STILL FOLLOWING
THE LIBERTAD CLOSELY, CAPTAIN.
- SO FAR THE STRAINS HAVE
NOT YET BEEN ABLE TO
BREAK THROUGH THE WALL OF TUMORS
SURROUNDING THE ENEMY VESSEL.
- DAMN. CAN'T WE SHAKE THEM OFF?
- WITHOUT FURTHER REPAIR,
WE STILL CAN'T ACCELERATE
ENOUGH TO LOSE THE DEAGUE SHIP.
- Dufarge: ALL RIGHT, PREPARE
THE REAR CANNONS FOR ATTACK.
AND FIRE.
- Lottie: WE HAVE CANNON FIRE
FROM THE LIBERTAD.
ALL UNITS EVADE.
- ( buzzing )
- ARE WE ON TARGET?
CONTINUE WITH THE
CANNON ASSAULT.
WE'RE TAKING THESE
BASTARDS DOWN.
WE HAVE TO EVADE.
SHIFT COURSE DOWNWARD.
- THERE'S NO TIME. WE HAVE
LESS THAN FIFTEEN SECONDS
BEFORE THE COLLISION, SIR.
- ALL HANDS, BRACE YOURSELVES
FOR IMMEDIATE IMPACT.
- WHAT THE... RUN.
- ( siren blaring )
- Operator: MAJOR DAMAGE
SUSTAINED IN PORT QUARTER BLOCK.
ALL CREW MEMBERS
EVACUATE AT ONCE!
- WHAT IS THIS?
- Martha: THE LIBERTAD.
- ( gasps ) DAMN IT!
- ( gasps )
- I'VE FINALLY FOUND YOU,
RALPH WEREC!
WEREC!
HEY, SARA! DON'T JUST SIT THERE
AND STARE, GO AFTER THAT STRAIN.
GET OUT THERE AND FINISH HIM
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
- Operator: THE ENGINE BLOCK
IS COMPLETELY DESTROYED.
WE CAN'T MOVE.
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- Operator: ENEMY INTRUSION ON
STARBOARD BLOCK D TWENTY-FOUR!
LOWERING DEFENSE BARRIERS.
THE TUMORS HAVE BOARDED.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE WE CAN DO.
- IT'LL TAKE AT LEAST
TWENTY MINUTES
TO REPAIR THE
DAMAGE TO THE ENGINE.
BUT IF THE DEAGUE SHIP
SELF-DESTRUCTS AT THIS RANGE,
WE'LL BE DEAD BY THEN.
- ( grunts ) THIS IS IT.
ALL HANDS MAKE READY
TO EVACUATE THE SHIP.
BEGIN PREPARATIONS TO BOARD
AND LAUNCH THE ESCAPE PODS.
- Melchi: NOT SO FAST.
- Both: HUH?
- UNTIL I HAVE FAILED TO
ACCOMPLISH THE TASK AT HAND,
PLEASE HOLD OFF
ON ABANDONING THE SHIP.
- HOLD OFF? WHAT TASK?
EXPLAIN YOURSELF?
- IF THAT DEAGUE WOMAN
WAS TELLING THE TRUTH,
WE HAVE TEN MINUTES LEFT.
PLENTY OF TIME FOR ME
TO STOP THE SELF-DESTRUCT.
AND WITH MY SKILLS, THIS
MISSION IS BARELY EVEN RISKY.
- BUT...
- ONCE MELCHI GETS A DUMB IDEA,
THERE'S NO STOPPING HIM.
- THANKS FOR THE OUTPOURING
OF SUPPORT.
- THEN I WILL HAVE
TO ACCOMPANY YOU.
- FINE. JUST TRY YOUR BEST
TO STAY OUT OF THE WAY.
- Automated voice:
EXACTLY FIFTEEN MINUTES
TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
ALL HANDS, EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY.
- COME ON!
WHERE ARE YOU, DAMN IT?
- ( rumbling )
( rumbling continues )
- Ben: DAMN! THIS ISN'T GOOD.
GET FIVE MORE TRANSFUSION PACKS.
- NO, ON SECOND THOUGHT
YOU'D BETTER MAKE IT EIGHT.
- RIGHT.
- CADET MISERY, GO GET THE
CARDIAC MASSAGE PREPPED.
IMMEDIATELY.
BECKY, GO ASSIST THE EMERGENCY
TEAM OVER IN E BLOCK.
- I'LL DO WHAT I CAN.
- I'M GONNA KILL RALPH WEREC.
- HMM.
- BUT THAT'S BROTHER.
- HUH?
- WHO WAS THAT?
- ( gasps )
- Man: HURRY UP! WORD
IS IN THAT THE TUMORS
HAVE ALREADY
BREACHED AREA FIFTEEN!
- ( loud explosion )
- OH, NO. NO MORE.
PLEASE NO MORE.
- ( explosion )
- ( gasps )
- EXACTLY WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
- HEY, DON'T GRAB HER LIKE THAT.
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT SHE'S SCARED?
- YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
- YEAH, DON'T BE SCARED.
BECKY AND I ARE GONNA
TAKE YOU SOME PLACE
YOU WON'T GET HURT, OKAY?
- ( all gasp )
- IT'S EMILY!
- ( all exclaiming in fear )
- STAY BEHIND ME.
- DO SOMETHING.
- ( loud explosion )
- SARA.
- LOOK WHO FINALLY
DECIDED TO SHOW UP.
- SARA, SARA, SARA,
I'M GLAD YOU CAME BACK.
- EMILY. I'M GLAD
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( gasps )
EMILY.
- Becky: YOU KNOW,
LOOKING AT HER LIKE THIS,
SHE SEEMS LIKE
SUCH AN ORDINARY LITTLE GIRL.
- I WONDER WHAT'S
SO SPECIAL ABOUT HER.
- YEAH, RIGHT?
- ( gun shot )
- NO! DICKON,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
- RALPH. IT'S YOU.
- ( siren blaring )
- Automated voice: EXACTLY
TWO MINUTES TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
ALL HANDS,
EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY.
- ALL RIGHT. WE MADE IT
ON BOARD SOONER THAN I THOUGHT.
CAN I GET A ROUND OF APPLAUSE
FOR OUR LOVELY TOUR GUIDE?
- OH, SHUT UP.
- HURRY UP, MELCHI. WE DON'T
HAVE VERY MUCH TIME.
- I HAVE THE SITUATION
UNDER CONTROL.
WE HAVE PLENTY OF TIME.
THERE'S NO NEED TO RUSH THIS.
- Automated voice:
EXACTLY FORTY-FIVE SECONDS
TO SELF DESTRUCT.
ALL HANDS,
EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY.
- YES! HERE WE GO.
- ( siren stops )
- SEE, I TOLD YOU THERE
WAS NO REASON TO PANIC.
ALL WE NEEDED WAS MELCHI'S
PATENTED HANDY HELPERS
AND WE FINISHED
WITH ROOM TO SPARE.
- ( siren blaring )
- Automated voice:
MANUAL DISARM DENIED.
TEN MINUTES
TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
- OH, NO. THE COUNTER
JUST RESET.
- HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
- I SWEAR.
I HAVE NO IDEA. UNLESS...
- I HAVE TO ADMIT I'M IMPRESSED.
NICE WORK, RALPH WEEREC.
- THAT'S IT. I'M LEAVING.
I AM NOT GOING TO DIE IN HERE.
- STOP RIGHT THERE.
- ( gun clicking )
- DAMN IT.
- GOOD LUCK GETTING
THAT WEAPON TO FIRE
THROUGH A PRESSURIZED,
STEEL-REINFORCED PANEL.
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN,
THERE'S A FAR EASIER WAY
OF GETTING OUT OF HERE.
- YEAH? AND WHAT'S THAT?
- YOU'LL SEE.
AS LONG AS WE'RE HERE, I THINK
WE OUGHT TO GIVE IT A TRY.
- Automated voice:
MANUAL DISARM DENIED.
EXACTLY NINE MINUTES
TO SELF-DISTRUCT.
- RALPH. ALL OF THIS
IS HAPPENING BECAUSE OF HIM.
IF I HAD NEVER MET THAT MAN,
MY LIFE WOULD BE SO MUCH...
EVERYTHING WOULD BE SO...
SON OF A BITCH!
- ( buzzing )
- THAT BASTARD ACTIVATED
THE SECURITY UNITS.
MY SECURITY CODE. IN THIS SUIT,
THEY'LL THINK I'M THE ENEMY.
STAY BACK.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'M CAPTAIN VIVIAN MEDLOCK.
I'M NOT WITH THEM.
( exclaiming )
STOP. PLEASE GOD, STOP.
- ( screams )
- GIVE THE LITTLE GIRL TO ME.
- NO WAY. EMILY IS GOING
TO STAY RIGHT HERE WITH ME.
- GIVE HER TO ME.
- RALPH.
- ( rumbling )
- THE DEAGUE SHIP. WHAT THE...
BUT HOW?
- THIS IS NOT POSSIBLE.
- WE WERE UNABLE TO DISARM
THE SELF-DESTRUCT MECHANISM.
- WE'RE GOING TO
PULL AS FAR AWAY
FROM THE LIBERTAD AS WE CAN.
- NOW, WAIT ONE MINUTE HERE.
- Melchi: I'M NOT SURE HOW BIG
OF AN EXPLOSION TO EXPECT,
BUT WE MUST AVOID FURTHER
DAMAGING THE LIBERTAD.
FORTUNATELY,
BEING ON THE BRIDGE
GRANTS US THE CHANCE
TO LIMIT THE IMPACT.
- MAYBE FORTUNATELY
IS NOT THE WORD.
- NOT AT ALL.
- MELCHI, THIS ISN'T THE TIME.
STOP PRETENDING TO BE BRAVE.
- SHUT UP, CARMICHAEL.
- Lottie: INSTRUCTOR MELCHI.
- Ralph: LET'S GO, EMILY.
- MMM-MMM.
- CHILD, I SAID COME HERE!
- ( gasps )
- THAT'S...
- DON'T TELL ME.
IT'S NOT...
- Sara: THAT'S RIGHT, BROTHER.
THE OTHER EMILY
YOU'VE BEEN SEARCHING FOR
IS NOW MY PARTNER, MY MIMIC,
AND MY BEST FRIEND.
- THAT CANNOT BE.
AH, YES. I UNDERSTAND.
- ( chuckles )
GIRL! COME DOWN HERE AT ONCE!
BRING THE DOLL AND COME WITH ME.
AND THE THREE OF US
WILL GO BACK TO YOUR HOME.
ALL OF THIS CAN BE OVER
IF YOU JUST TAKE THAT DOLL
AND COME BACK WITH ME.
THERE ISN'T ANY NEED
FOR YOU TO STAY HERE
AND ALLOW THESE
HUMANS TO ABUSE YOU.
COME ON. IT'S DONE.
IT CAN ALL BE DONE.
YOU COME BACK WITH ME!
GET OUT OF THE WAY, SARA.
I WARNED YOU BEFORE.
ANYONE WHO CHOOSES TO
STAND IN MY WAY
WILL BE DESTROYED.
VERY WELL.
- Emily: NO!
- ( gasps )
- STOP. NO MORE.
- EMILY.
- I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME.
I WANT TO STAY.
I WANT TO STAY HERE WITH SARA.
- BUT YOU CAN'T.
WHY WOULD YOU?
YOU WOULD DO THAT TO ME?
AFTER ALL I'VE DONE
FOR YOUR CAUSE?
- ARE YOU GOING TO KILL A LOT?
LIKE YOU DID BACK THEN?
- ( gasps )
- YOU KNOW YOU DID.
I WISH YOU HADN'T.
WE NEVER WANTED THAT.
- YOU DIDN'T?
BUT THAT'S NONSENSE.
AFTER ALL THAT, WHAT THEY...
WHAT THEY'VE DONE TO YOU.
ESPECIALLY NOW THAT
WE'VE COME THIS FAR.
WE'RE CLOSE. WE'RE SO CLOSE.
LET'S GO!
- NO. NOT THIS TIME.
- OF COURSE, YOU
WANTED THEM ALL DEAD.
THE HUMANS DESERVE TO DIE.
HOW CAN YOU FORGO YOUR REVENGE?
THE HUMANS HAVE TO DIE!
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- EMILY.
COME HERE. RIGHT NOW.
EMILY. COME HERE!
- SARA!
- ( gasps )
- SHE'S RIGHT.
NO ONE ELSE HAS TO DIE.
NOBODY WANTS THIS, RALPH.
NOBODY BUT YOU.
- YOU DON'T KNOW.
HOW COULD YOU UNDERSTAND?
- I KNOW HER. I KNOW EMILY.
BELIEVE ME.
I KNOW SHE HURTS,
BUT SHE DOESN'T WANT THIS.
- Dufarge: WE HAD SOME
INCREDIBLE STUDENTS THIS YEAR.
- I GUESS. BUT I
THOUGHT A LOT OF THEM
WERE JUST BEING SMARTASSES.
- ( loud explosion )
- DON'T BE STUPID. YOU KNOW
NOBODY WANTS TO SEE YOU DO THIS.
"I WON'T LET ANYONE ELSE DIE."
REMEMBER SAYING THAT, SARA?
- BROTHER, IT'S TIME
WE PUT AN END TO ALL OF THIS.
- SHUT UP. SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
- ( loud explosion )
- THE LAST FEW TUMORS
ARE BEGINNING TO REGROUP.
I THINK WE SHOULD HEAD BACK NOW.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- I SAY LET'S GO AND FINISH OFF
THE REST OF THOSE SUCKERS.
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING TO
GET THESE TUMORS OFF THE SHIP.
- FOR WHAT? WHY HAVE YOU
DONE THIS TO ME?
WHY AM I THE ONE
WHO GETS THE BLAME?
- BROTHER!
- SARA!
- SARA.
- I'M OKAY.
- BECKY, DICKON, WOULD YOU LOOK
AFTER HER FOR ME?
- HUH?
- JUST FOR NOW.
- IT'LL BE OKAY.
I WILL COME BACK FOR YOU.
- ( engine revs )
- DON'T GO.
- SARA.
- RALPH. THIS IS IT.
NO MORE HURT AND LONELINESS.
I'M FINALLY GOING TO PUT
A STOP TO IT, RIGHT NOW.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sara: MY BROTHER
IS DEAD WRONG.
AND I SWEAR I WILL STOP HIM.
ON THE NEXT STRAIN, LAST WALTZ.
LET'S GO, EMILY.