- Sara: SARA WEREC. AT ONE TIME
THAT WAS MY NAME, BUT NO MORE.
I AM NOW KNOWN AS SARA CRUZ,
MOBILE TROOPS CADET AT THE
BASION TACTICAL TRAINING SCHOOL.
THIS IS THE NEW ME.
- Jake: TEAM SIX INTERCEPT.
TUMORS AT T SIX-FIVE-THREE.
- Isabella: SIX-OH-ONE, ROGER!
- Female Student 1:
SIX-OH-TWO, ROGER!
- Female Student 2:
SIX-OH-THREE, ROGER!
- Male Student 1:
SIX-OH-FOUR, ROGER!
- Male Student 2:
SIX-OH-FIVE, ROGER!
- Jake: SIX-OH-SIX!
CADET CRUZ, RESPOND!
- SIX-OH-SIX, ROGER!
- WAKE UP AND DO
YOUR JOB, NEWBIE!
- Jake: STRAIN CONTACT.
COMMENCE EXERCISE!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Female operator: EXERCISE
DURATION, TWENTY-THREE MINUTES.
STRAIN AND GAMBEE
CASUALTIES ZERO.
- Dufarge: HEADMASTER CRAVEN.
ANOTHER SUCCESSFUL EXERCISE.
THAT IS GOOD NEWS.
- HMM. YES, BOTH DIVISIONS
ARE DOING WELL.
- WAIT.
- WHAT IS IT, SIR?
- Craven: IT LOOKS LIKE
SOMEONE'S DECIDED TO
GO OFF ON THEIR OWN.
JAKE, WHO IS THAT?
- THAT'S SARA CRUZ.
SHE PILOTS GAMBEE SIX-OH-SIX.
SHE'S A TRANSFER,
GOT HERE THREE MONTHS AGO.
SHE'S A BIT BEHIND THE
OTHERS IN TERMS OF SKILL.
- INTERESTING.
SHE'S PERFORMING QUITE
WELL NONETHELESS.
- ( panting )
I COULD TAKE THESE OUT
SO EASILY IN A STRAIN.
UNFORTUNATELY THAT'S
IMPOSSIBLE NOW,
SINCE I LOST MY ABILITY
TO PILOT A STRAIN
WHEN MY MIMIC WAS DESTROYED.
MY BROTHER BETRAYED ME THAT
DAY, AND I LOST EVERYTHING.
ALL THAT REMAINS,
NOW ARE QUESTIONS.
WHY DID MY BROTHER,
WHO WAS ALWAYS SO PATRIOTIC,
COMMIT TREASON?
WHAT IS IT,
THAT MADE HIM CHANGE?
WHAT HAVE THOSE COLD EYES
SEEN, SINCE HE'S BEEN GONE?
- EXERCISE COMPLETE.
ALL SHIPS RETURN TO BASE.
- Sara: IN ORDER TO
FIND THE TRUTH,
I'LL NEED TO CONFRONT MY
BROTHER FACE TO FACE.
THE ONLY WAY TO DO THAT,
IS TO GET TO THE FRONT
LINES OF THE WAR.
THAT IS WHY I'M HERE.
- Isabella: HEY CRUZ!
EVER HEARD OF TEAMWORK?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING THE
OTHER WAY SINCE YOU'RE NEW,
BUT NOW, I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
YOU CAN WIPE OUT
EVERY TUMOR BY YOURSELF?
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOOD
AT PILOTING A GAMBEE.
OR MAYBE YOU'RE IN
DESPERATE NEED OF APPROVAL.
IS THAT WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- NO.
I DID IT FOR A REASON,
BECAUSE THE TEAM WENT
AFTER WEAK TARGETS.
THAT'S HARDLY A
REALISTIC COMBAT SCENARIO,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
- YOU'VE GOT SOME NERVE!
- IT'S COMMON KNOWLEDGE
THAT IN REAL COMBAT,
TUMORS ATTACK IN GROUPS.
SO, TO WIN YOU HAVE TO
TAKE THE FIGHT TO THEM.
- HOLD ON.
- (grunts)
WHAT IS IT, MARIETTE?
- Isabella: LOTTIE GELH FROM
THE ARMORED DIVISION!
- WOULD YOU CUT IT OUT,
DOWN THERE?
NOBODY LIKES A BULLY, ISABELLA.
- IT'S "MOBILE TROOP
DIVISION'S" BUSINESS,
SO BUTT OUT.
- WELL EXCUSE ME,
IT'S JUST THAT SARA CRUZ'S
STRATEGY IS CORRECT, SO I DON'T
SEE WHY YOU WOULD CHALLENGE IT.
BUT, IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE A
GAMBEE PILOT OF YOUR CALIBER
WOULD ACTUALLY CHOOSE
YOUR TARGETS.
IF THAT WERE THE CASE,
THEN OUR SHIP'S DEFENSES
WOULD BE PUT AT GREAT RISK,
WOULD THEY NOT?
- ( scoffs )
- GEEZ, LOTTIE. WHY DID
YOU HAVE TO GET INVOLVED?
- WHY? BECAUSE
I CAN'T STAND IGNORANCE.
BUT SARA CRUZ,
SHE PILOTS HER GAMBEE
AS IF SHE WERE A REASONER.
STRANGE, ISN'T IT?
- Roommate 1:
SHE IS SO NOT CUTE.
- Roommate 2: WHY'S SHE
SUCH A DOWNER ALL THE TIME?
- Roommate 3:
I THINK SHE'S CREEPY.
- ONCE YOU'VE DECIDED
WHAT YOU WANT IN LIFE,
IT'S UP TO YOU,
TO ACCOMPLISH IT.
AS LONG AS YOU
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF,
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN'T DO.
- Cadet: I HEARD YOU HAD A
LITTLE CONFRONTATION WITH
THE QUEEN OF SPATIAL
ARMOR YESTERDAY.
- YEAH, I DID.
THAT ANNOYING BITCH.
ALL I DID WAS GIVE THE NEWBIE
SOME ADVICE AND SHE SNAPPED.
- WHICH NEWBIE?
- HER. THE SMART ASS
BLONDE OVER THERE.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE
SHE CAME FROM.
EITHER WAY SHE'S USELESS.
- WHAT ABOUT THE
SUB-LIGHTSPEED TEST?
YOU THINK SHE'S GOOD
ENOUGH TO MAKE IT?
- HEY! YOU KNOW,
THAT REMINDS ME.
I HEARD HER ARGUING WITH JAKE
ABOUT SPEEDING UP HER TRAINING.
- SHE JUST TRANSFERRED HERE.
THERE'S NO WAY SHE'LL CATCH UP.
OR MAYBE SHE'LL DECIDE
TO START FLIRTING
WITH ALL THE INSTRUCTORS.
- ( cadets laugh )
- FORGET IT. HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU?
I CANNOT CHANGE THE TRAINING
SCHEDULE FOR ONE PERSON.
- BUT, SIR...
- ( sighs ) I DON'T
GET YOU, CRUZ.
WHY ARE YOU IN SUCH A RUSH
TO FINISH YOUR TRAINING?
- BECAUSE, I...
- HERE'S WHAT I CAN DO.
PASS THE BASION DESCENT
EXERCISE IN FOUR WEEKS.
IF YOU CAN MANAGE THAT,
I'LL CONSIDER YOU FOR
THE SUB-LIGHTSPEED TEST.
- Dufarge:
THINK SHE CAN PULL IT OFF?
- Jake: I DOUBT IT.
BUT I HAVE A FEELING THAT
GIRL WILL REFUSE TO GIVE UP,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
- ( grunts )
- ( beeping )
- THE THRUSTERS!
- ( alarm wailing )
- ( screams )
( breathes heavily )
- BEHIND ME IS A TUMOR.
THEY ARE THE GRUNTS
OF THE DEAGUE ARMY.
- DONE.
- Lottie: WAIT.
- IS THAT...
- IT'S THAT SARA CRUZ GIRL.
LET'S GO TALK TO HER, JESSIE.
- Female automated voice:
SWITCHING TO REQUESTED GRAVITY.
- WOW. YOU'RE REALLY
AT FOUR G'S?
LET'S TRY THAT.
- Female automated voice:
SWITCHING TO REQUESTED GRAVITY.
- WHY AM I DOING THIS?
- SO, I HEARD A RUMOR.
SOMETHING ABOUT A GAMBEE
PILOT REALLY PUSHING THE EDGE.
WHAT ARE YOU IN
SUCH A HURRY FOR?
- I'M REALLY SORRY, BUT
THAT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- WELL, YOU HAVE
GOT A POINT THERE!
YOU UP TO A CHALLENGE,
LIKE WHO GETS TIRED FIRST?
- SO THEN, I TOLD HER
THAT IT WAS ABSOLUTE...
IT'S HER!
- LET'S JUST SAVE
IT FOR ANOTHER TIME.
- Isabella: WHY'S LOTTIE
IN THERE WITH HER?
I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
SHE THINKS SHE CAN MOCK ME.
- ISABELLA, WAIT.
- ( panting )
HOW ARE YOU TWO ABLE
TO KEEP GOING LIKE THAT?
MY HEART'S ABOUT TO EXPLODE!
- SHEER WILLPOWER
IS THE ONLY THING
KEEPING ME UP AT THIS POINT.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- IF YOU CAN'T KEEP UP, THEN YOU
BETTER STOP BEFORE YOU FAINT.
BESIDES, THIS IS
MY DAILY ROUTINE.
- I'M NOT GOING TO FAINT!
I'M FINE!
- ( both panting )
- ( sighs )
( yawns )
- UH...
ALL THAT WORK FOR A TIE?
HOW LAME.
- YEAH. SHE'S GOT GUTS.
- LOTTIE, HAVE YOU EVER
HEARD OF THE SAYING,
"ALL THINGS IN MODERATION"?
HOW ARE YOU FEELING MISS CRUZ?
- EASY, YOU NEED TO STAY IN BED.
- BUT...
- YOU STILL HAVE AT LEAST AN
HOUR UNTIL YOUR IV IS DONE.
JUST TRY TO RELAX
UNTIL THEN, OKAY?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO LIKES TO PUSH
THE LIMITS, EH LOTTIE?
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- Female Operator:
INSTRUCTOR BEN HUGHES,
PLEASE REPORT TO THE
BRIDGE IMMEDIATELY.
- THAT'S ME. LIKE I SAID,
TRY TO GET SOME REST.
- YOU KNOW I NEVER ACTUALLY
THOUGHT YOU WOULD GO THAT FAR.
- MY NAME'S LOTTIE GELH.
AND YOU ARE?
- SARA. SARA...
- Female newscaster: WE'RE
JUST GETTING NEW INFORMATION
ON THE ATTACK OF GRABERA IN
- SARA CRUZ.
- THE YEAR SEVEN THOUSAND EIGHT.
- SARA, HUH? NICE TO MEET YOU.
- A VIDEO SHOWING RALPH WEREC,
THE SUSPECTED DEAGUE DEFECTOR,
HAS JUST BEEN RELEASED
TO THE MEDIA.
THE VIDEO WAS RECOVERED
FROM A SURVEILLANCE CAMERA
ON THE GROUNDS OF THE MILITARY
RESEARCH AND TRAINING FACILITY
THAT WAS DESTROYED
IN THE ATTACK.
YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE RALPH WEREC,
WHO APPARENTLY LED THE ATTACK,
MOVING THROUGH THE FACILITY,
THOUGH IT IS STILL UNCLEAR
WHY THE ONCE NATIONAL
HERO AND PROLIFIC REASONER
DECIDED TO TURN ON HIS COUNTRY.
THE DISASTER CLAIMED
THE LIVES OF THOUSANDS
OF STAFF, AS WELL AS YOUNG
RECRUITS STILL IN TRAINING.
- RALPH WEREC.
- TODAY YOU WILL BEGIN
YOUR DESCENT EXERCISE
INTO THE GAS CLOUDS
OF PLANET BASION.
AFTER TODAY, THE SUB-LIGHTSPEED
EXERCISE WILL BE THE ONLY TEST
REMAINING BEFORE GRADUATION.
FOR THOSE WHO HAVE YET
TO QUALIFY FOR ADVANCEMENT,
THIS IS YOUR LAST
CHANCE TO DO SO.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU ALL.
THE OBJECTIVE IS TO
RETRIEVE A FLOAT
INSIDE THE GAS CLOUD
AND RETURN TO BASE.
- ONCE YOU'VE DECIDED
WHAT YOU WANT IN LIFE,
ONLY YOU CAN ACCOMPLISH IT.
AS LONG AS YOU
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF,
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN'T DO.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I CAN DO ANYTHING!
- Jake: NO ONE HAS SUCCESSFULLY
FINISHED THIS EXERCISE
IN THE LAST SIX WEEKS
DUE TO THE EXTREMELY HARSH
ENVIRONMENT OF THE PLANET.
POWERFUL ELECTROMAGNETIC
STORMS ENGULF THE GAS CLOUDS
AND WILL MOST LIKELY INTERFERE
WITH THE ELECTRONICS
ON BOARD YOUR GAMBEE.
YOUR RADAR AND COMMUNICATIONS
UNIT WILL BE USELESS.
YOU MUST RELY ON YOUR OWN SKILLS
AND INSTINCTS TO SUCCEED.
- Melchi: ALRIGHT, THERE WE GO.
HEY, WILL YOU HAND
IT TO ME ALREADY?
( screams )
- GEEZ MELCHI. I TOLD YOU,
YOU HAVE TO BE MORE SPECIFIC.
- WOULD YOU SHUT UP, CARMICHAEL!
A.I. IS SUPPOSED TO LEARN
FROM REPEATED MISTAKES,
SO BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
THAT WAS ACTUALLY PRODUCTIVE.
ALRIGHT, NOW GIVE ME THAT THING.
( screams )
- I THINK YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SHOULD BE LEARNING.
- ( Lottie chuckles )
SO, IS THAT A TECHNIQUE YOU
LIKE TO TEACH TO EVERYONE
IN THE ENGINEERING DIVISION?
- ( sarcastic laugh )
SO, WHAT EXACTLY BRINGS
THE QUEEN REASONER,
DOWN TO THE GREASE
MONKEY DUNGEON?
- WELL, I HAVE A
SMALL FAVOR TO ASK.
- I'M AT THE RIGHT
COORDINATES BUT...
- I FOUND HER.
- NO PROBLEM AT ALL!
- NICE.
- SO, WHY DO YOU
WANT TO WATCH THIS?
- I'M JUST CURIOUS
TO SEE HER IN ACTION.
- CONTACT!
WHAT THE...
- I'M GOING TO DO WHATEVER
IT TAKES TO STOP YOU, SARA.
- DAMMIT! WHY DID YOU
DO THAT, ISABELLA?
- IS IT NOT OBVIOUS?
IT'S BECAUSE I HATE YOU
AND I WANT TO SEE YOU FAIL.
- I WON'T BE BEATEN BY
A CONDESCENDING BITCH
WHO SUCKS UP TO REASONERS
WHENEVER SHE CAN.
- Carmichael: UH-OH, LOOKS
LIKE WE HAVE A CAT FIGHT
ON OUR HANDS.
- ISABELLA! WHAT IS SHE DOING?
- IT'S MINE!
NO!
- ISABELLA!
- ( alarm blaring )
- Carmichael: SHE'S IN
A CRASH ORBIT NOW.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU ACT RECKLESS.
- THE UNIT DOESN'T
APPEAR TO BE DAMAGED,
THOUGH IT LOOKS LIKE THE
PILOT IS UNCONSCIOUS.
- WELL, IS THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT IT
FROM WHERE WE ARE?
LIKE REMOTE CONTROL?
- NO, THE GAS CLOUDS
ARE TOO THICK FOR THAT.
JAKE PROBABLY ISN'T EVEN
AWARE OF THE SITUATION YET.
- THEN?
- YEAH.
- Jake: EXCELLENT
WORK, CADET CRUZ.
I NEVER WOULD HAVE THOUGHT YOU'D
BE THE FIRST TO PASS THE TEST.
AS PROMISED, YOU
CAN NOW TAKE PART
IN THE SUB-LIGHTSPEED EXERCISE.
WITH YOUR
PERMISSION, HEADMASTER.
- YES. LET'S SEE
WHAT SHE CAN DO.
THIS IS EXACTLY THE TYPE
OF PILOT WE'RE IN DESPERATE
NEED OF ON THE FRONT LINES.
- YOU'RE GOING TO PAY FOR THAT.
YOU HEAR ME?
WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU THINKING
ATTACKING ME OUT THERE?
WERE YOU REALLY THAT DESPERATE
TO BEAT ME ON THE TEST?
SAY SOMETHING, DAMMIT!
DON'T WALK AWAY!
- I'LL BE REPORTING THIS
TO THE INSTRUCTOR.
- Lottie: YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
I THINK YOU'D END UP
FEELING EMBARRASSED
CONSIDERING THE FACTS.
- Mariette: EXCUSE ME?
- YOU COLLIDED WITH A METEOR
AND LOST CONTROL OF BOTH
YOURSELF AND YOUR
UNIT DURING A MISSION.
TELL ME, WHAT WOULD BE
THE MOST EFFICIENT WAY
FOR HER TO SAVE YOU?
- WHAT THE...
- SARA SAVED
YOUR LIFE, ISABELLA.
- ISABELLA!
- WAIT!
- HOLD ON!
- WHY DIDN'T YOU STAND
UP FOR YOURSELF?
- OH NO!
WHERE IS IT? WHERE'S MY PENDANT?
IT MUST BE HERE SOMEWHERE!
OH, NO. DON'T TELL ME!
- ALRIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
WE HAVE TO WORK TO DO.
COME ON, GET OUT OF THERE.
- GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
- HUH!
- OH, WOW. IT'S A STRAIN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
ALL ALONE IN THE DARK.
YOU'RE SO DIRTY.
OH, YOU POOR THING.
NO WAY. YOU'RE A MIMIC!
EMILY.
I GUESS, YOU DON'T HAVE A
REASONER ANYMORE DO YOU?
YOU'RE ALL BY YOURSELF.
YOU MUST BE LONELY.
I KNOW, HOW YOU MUST BE FEELING.
IT'S AWFUL, ISN'T IT?
EVERYONE THAT WAS IMPORTANT
TO ME. I'VE LOST THEM ALL.
( crying )
IN MANY WAYS, WE'RE ONE AND
THE SAME, AREN'T WE, EMILY?
( sobs )
- EMILY. MY NAME IS EMILY, ALSO.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sara: THE UNCHANGING
DAILY ROUTINE GROWS THIN,
WHILE A MIRACLE OCCURS DURING
THE SUB-LIGHT SPEED BATTLE.
NEXT TIME ON STRAIN,
SUB-LIGHT SPEED NIGHTMARE.
I'LL BE SEEING YOU
SOON, BROTHER!