- Melchi: WOW.
I KNEW IT WAS OLD, BUT...
THE CONNECTORS USE A STANDARD
THAT'S BEEN AROUND
FOR GENERATIONS.
STILL.
- YEAH, SIX HUNDRED
YEARS OLD, HUH?
THAT KINDA MAKES MY HEAD HURT.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T
NOTICE ANYTHING
WHILE YOU WERE
TINKERING WITH HER?
- WHY WOULD THAT EVEN CROSS
MY MIND WHILE I'M WORKING?
I WAS FOCUSED
ON OTHER THINGS, YOU KNOW.
- LET'S TRY TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
STRAINS WERE FIRST
DEVELOPED, ABOUT WHAT,
A HUNDRED AND FIFTY YEARS AGO?
- YES, BUT I BELIEVE
I HEARD THAT
MIMICS WERE ENGINEERED MUCH
EARLIER THAN THE STRAINS.
- AND THAT COULD MEAN
THAT WE'RE LOOKING AT
ONE OF THE VERY FIRST MODELS.
- Ben: SO CAN WE ASSUME
THAT THE ENEMY'S ATTACKS
ARE AIMED AT GETTING THIS MIMIC?
- Melchi: WE CAN'T SAY
THAT FOR SURE, YET.
MAY I TAKE A LOOK INSIDE?
- GO AHEAD, PLEASE.
- I HEARD THAT
SARA TESTED NORMAL,
WHICH MEANS THERE
HAS TO BE SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS MIMIC
WE DON'T KNOW.
SEE, I REALLY HADN'T
GOTTEN THE CHANCE
TO CLOSELY EXAMINE
EITHER ONE OF THEM, YET.
( gasps )
- ( all gasp )
- MY WORD.
- WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
- Ben: THIS IS NOT
FROM A HUMAN BEING.
- WELL THEN,
WHAT THE HELL IS IT?
- IT'S DEFINITELY A BRAIN,
BUT WHAT KIND IS IT?
- Carmichael: SO SARA ACTUALLY
LINKED WITH THAT THING?
- Melchi: NO WONDER
IT ACTED DIFFERENTLY
AND WE COULDN'T FIGURE
OUT HOW IT HAPPENED.
SARA DIDN'T LINK WITH THIS.
IT PROBABLY LINKED WITH HER!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ben: I MUST SAY.
I KNOW OF NO CREATURE
THAT HAS A BRAIN LIKE THIS.
- Craven: WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU SUGGESTING?
- YOU THINK IT'S FROM AN ALIEN?
CAN THAT BE POSSIBLE?
- Melchi: ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE,
AND WHAT ELSE COULD IT BE?
BUT REALLY, THE MORE
PRESSING QUESTION IS
WHY THIS WOULD EVEN EXIST.
- IF THE DEAGUE KNOW ABOUT IT,
THAT EXPLAINS WHY THEY'D WANT
TO GET THEIR HANDS ON HER.
- I THINK I NEED TO PERFORM
A DETAILED EXAMINATION.
GIVE ME A HAND, WOULD YA,
BEN? CARMICHAEL?
- Emily: NO.
NO. NO!
( gasps )
( staggered breathing )
- Ralph: WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S HER!
OH, PLEASE, HELP HER!
SHE NEEDS US!
HURRY!
PLEASE!
HELP HER!
PLEASE HELP!
- IF WE DON'T HURRY, THEN...
- I ALREADY KNOW.
- Medlock: OUR TIME IS UP.
IF WE DON'T FINISH
OUR COURSE CHANGE
BY TWELVE HUNDRED HOURS TOMORROW
AND RENDEZVOUS
WITH THE MAIN FLEET,
WE WILL MISS OUR OPPORTUNITY
FOR THE NEXT ASSIGNMENT.
SO, WE CAN'T ALLOW OURSELVES
TO BE SIDETRACKED ANYMORE.
I WILL GUARANTEE YOUR
STATUS, OF COURSE.
AFTER ALL,
WE'VE OBTAINED A COMPONENT
OF INSTANT INTERSTELLAR
COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY.
I WON'T LET ANYONE QUESTION YOU.
I PROMISE I'LL PROTECT
YOU NO MATTER WHAT,
SO DON'T WORRY, RALPH.
I'M GOING TO USE
A SHOWER FIRST, ALRIGHT?
( gasps )
( exhales )
- ( clicking )
IT'S LOCKED.
IS THAT YOU, RALPH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
RALPH? RALPH?
- HM?
WELL, NOW.
RALPH. I TAKE IT
YOU'VE COME TO COMPLAIN?
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE TOO LATE.
YOU'VE BEEN ALLOWED TO HAVE
YOUR WAY UP UNTIL THIS POINT,
BUT FROM NOW ON...
( gasps )
( grunts )
- ( women scream )
- ( beeping )
- ( woman gasps )
- ( gunshots )
- ( gunshot )
- Ralph: I'M CLOSING IN.
I SHOULD SEE IT ANY MOMENT NOW.
THE TARGET! I SEE IT!
NO SIGN OF THE ENEMY,
I'M MAKING CONTACT.
LOOKS LIKE THE HULL HAS
SUSTAINED CONSIDERABLE DAMAGE.
( gasps )
- Ralph: WHAT WAS THAT THING?
MAYBE IT WAS THE NEW ENEMY MODEL
WE'VE BEEN TOLD ABOUT.
THESE THINGS ALMOST
LOOK LIKE STRAINS.
HOW DID THE DEAGUE MANAGE TO
GET THEIR HANDS ON
STRAIN TECHNOLOGY?
ONLY ONE LEFT.
( thinking ) ONLY ONE LEFT.
- NO!
PLEASE DON'T!
- WHAT?
THERE'S A PERSON?
THEY'RE NOT UNMANNED?
IT'S A...
IT'S A KID. A KID!
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( exclaims )
STAY IN YOUR ROOM.
- ( footsteps departing )
- ( exhales )
( breathes heavily )
( grunting )
STOP IT! STOP IT!
( grunts )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( gasps )
- ( switch clicking )
AH!
- GET OUT.
- CAN I GET DRESSED?
- I'VE DISPOSED OF YOUR CLOTHES.
- RIGHT. YOU MEAN
YOU DISPOSED OF
ANYTHING THAT HAS MY
IDENTIFICATION ON IT
TO PREVENT ME
FROM GETTING AWAY.
A SINGLE TOWEL, REALLY?
I HOPE SOMEONE DOESN'T
HAPPEN TO SEE ME.
- THERE'S NO ONE LEFT
TO SEE YOU.
- ( gasps )
RALPH.
( gasps )
RALPH, WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO US?
- WE WILL CONTINUE
IN OUR PURSUIT.
ONE PERSON SHOULD BE ABLE
TO PILOT THIS SHIP.
QUICKLY. THERE'S
NO TIME TO WASTE.
- YES. YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS POSSIBLE FOR ONE PERSON
TO PILOT THE KUNRUN.
AND LUCKY FOR YOU I'M EVEN
SKILLED ENOUGH TO CONDUCT
SUB-LIGHT SPEED TRAVEL WITHOUT
ASSISTANCE FROM ANYONE ELSE.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAD TO...
WHY, RALPH?
WHY DID THIS HAVE TO HAPPEN?
TELL ME WHAT I DID
TO DESERVE THIS?
I'VE BEEN ON YOUR SIDE
FROM THE BEGINNING!
I'VE DONE NOTHING
BUT HELP YOU IN ANY WAY I COULD!
WHY WOULD YOU DO
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
TELL ME WHY!
WHY, RALPH?
- Female operator: TEN SECONDS
TO COMMENCE ACCELERATION.
NINE. EIGHT.
SEVEN. SIX.
FIVE. FOUR.
THREE. TWO.
ACCELERATION.
- Craven: WE ARE CURRENTLY
TRAVELING AT SUB-LIGHT SPEED
TOWARD PLANET BREGMA,
WHICH WAS OUR
ORIGINAL DESTINATION.
WE ARE SCHEDULED TO ARRIVE THERE
IN TWO DAYS' SHIP TIME.
UNION FORCES ON BREGMA
ARE REPORTEDLY CONDUCTING
SEVERAL LARGE SCALE EXERCISES,
AND WE WILL CONSULT WITH HIGH
LEVEL MILITARY OFFICERS THERE.
AFTER RESUPPLYING AND
REPAIRING THE LIBERTAD,
AS WELL AS TAKING CARE OF
OTHER NEEDS AND OPERATIONS,
WE PLAN TO RETURN HOME.
- WHAT DOES "OTHER NEEDS
AND OPERATIONS" MEAN?
- HE MEANS SARA, OBVIOUSLY.
- WELL, WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO HER?
- WHO KNOWS.
THEY'LL PROBABLY JUST
HAND HER OVER TO THE ARMY
AND LET THEM WORK IT OUT THERE.
- SOMETHING JUST DOESN'T
SEEM RIGHT ABOUT THIS,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- OKAY, ALL DONE.
- HEY, YOU WOULDN'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO SARA,
WOULD YOU, BECKY?
- UH. NO, I HAVEN'T HEARD.
- DAMN IT!
- ( gasps )
- Craven: THE UNEXPECTED
AND MULTIPLE INCIDENTS
ON THIS VOYAGE HAS SADLY LEFT
US WITH MANY CASUALTIES.
HOWEVER, I WOULD ASK THAT YOU
TAKE THIS EXPERIENCE WITH YOU,
AND USE IT WELL IN YOUR
POST GRADUATION DUTIES.
THAT IS ALL.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- Melchi: COME ON, CRAVEN!
I'VE COMPROMISED
AS FAR AS I CAN
AND I'VE DONE EVERYTHING
SHORT OF DISSECTING IT
TO GET A GOOD ANALYSIS!
HOW CAN YOU REFUSE SUCH
A TINY REQUEST, HUH?
- ( grunts )
ALRIGHT, FINE, BUT ONLY
UNTIL WE REACH BREGMA.
- THANK YOU!
THAT'S THE CRAVEN
I KNOW AND LOVE!
I'VE GOT TO GET TO WORK!
- ( door humming )
- ( grunts )
HE'S TOO MUCH.
I GIVE UP.
- ( door humming )
- COME ON.
OKAY, I BROUGHT HER.
- GOOD WORK.
- WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN
DOING TO EMILY?
- WE WANTED TO TAKE A CLOSER
LOOK AT THE MIMIC INSIDE HER.
SARA.
DID YOU KNOW THAT THIS MIMIC WAS
CREATED SIX HUNDRED YEARS AGO?
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
- YEAH, AND THIS WOULD
ALL MAKE A LOT MORE SENSE
IF YOU WERE ALSO BORN
SIX HUNDRED YEARS AGO,
BUT SINCE YOU'RE
RALPH WEREC'S SISTER
I THINK WE CAN
SAFELY RULE THAT OUT.
- EMILY, WHO ARE YOU?
- ( beeping )
- COURSE PREDICTION COMPLETE.
THE ENEMY SHIP'S
DESTINATION IS PLANET BREGMA.
AFTER THE INCIDENT AT
THE GALL SUPPLY DEPOT
I'M GUESSING THEY'RE AWARE
THAT WE'RE FOLLOWING THEM.
I SHOW MILITARY
PRESENCE ON BREGMA.
ARE WE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO TRACK?
- WE ARE.
- WE'RE AT A DISADVANTAGE
IF WE ENGAGE IN COMBAT.
AS SECOND IN COMMAND, BARROW HAD
THE TUMOR ACTIVATION PASSWORD.
IF WE CAN'T ENGAGE TUMORS
WE MIGHT AS WELL BE
CONSIDERED UNARMED.
- YES, I KNOW.
- WHAT IN THE HELL
ARE YOU THINKING?
WHAT WOULD POSSESS YOU
TO DO SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
- I DON'T GET HOW IT IS
THAT I CAN LINK
WITH A SIX HUNDRED YEAR
OLD MIMIC LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, STRAINS DIDN'T EVEN
EXIST BACK THEN, DID THEY?
- THAT'S WHY I CALLED YOU IN
HERE SARA, TO FIGURE THAT OUT.
YOU DO WANT TO KNOW, DON'T YOU?
- WELL, I...
- I BELIEVE EVERYTHING THAT'S
HAPPENED TO THE LIBERTAD
HAS TO REVOLVE
AROUND THIS MIMIC.
THEREFORE, I NEED TO
INVESTIGATE THOROUGHLY.
BESIDES, IF DON'T LEARN
WHO THIS MIMIC IS,
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
YOU MAY NEVER DISCOVER
WHAT YOUR BROTHER
IS TRYING TO DO.
- YOU'LL NEVER MOVE FORWARD
UNLESS YOU ACT, SARA.
- Melchi: LISTEN, WE'RE NOT
JUST RANDOMLY SEEING
WHAT HAPPENS AFTER
START UP THIS TIME.
YOUR GOAL IS TO LINK
EVEN DEEPER THAN USUAL,
AND GET ANY INFORMATION
YOU CAN FROM THE MIMIC.
I'VE HONESTLY NEVER DONE
ANYTHING QUITE LIKE THIS BEFORE,
AND I'M NOT SURE
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN,
SO BE EXTRA CAREFUL.
- ALL SENSORS ARE GO.
ACTIVATION SET UP COMPLETE!
- ALRIGHT! LET'S GET TO IT THEN!
- MELCHI.
I'M WONDERING IF
WE SHOULD TELL HER
THE BRAIN INSIDE
EMILY ISN'T HUMAN?
- I DON'T THINK
SHE NEEDS TO KNOW YET.
I'M PRETTY SURE
IT WOULD ONLY FREAK HER OUT.
SARA, PREPARE TO BEGIN.
- RIGHT.
- ( machine whirring )
- EMILY?
- ( alarm beeping )
- OH NO,
THE LINK LEVEL IS TOO HIGH!
THREE TIMES MORE THAN PREDICTED!
- BUT HOW?
- YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WEIRD
WHEN YOU WERE
DISSECTING IT, DID YOU?
- NO! WAIT.
COULD IT BE POSSIBLE THAT
THE MEMORY CORTEX
HAS BEEN STIMULATED?
- WHAT IS THIS?
ARE THESE HER MEMORIES?
- ( clanking and clattering )
- WHAT THE...
- OH, WOW.
WHY DO THEY ALL LOOK
EXACTLY THE SAME?
- CLONES!
COULD THESE ACTUALLY BE
THE NEWEST DEAGUE WEAPONS?
- Sara: NIEREN SIX.
SIXTY THREE SIXTY ONE.
OVER SIX HUNDRED YEARS AGO.
- Scientist 1: FROM ALL
OUTWARD APPEARANCES,
THEY APPEAR TO BE LITTLE
GIRLS FROM OUR WORLD,
BUT THEIR INTERNAL COMPOSITION
IS FUNDAMENTALLY
DIFFERENT FROM OURS.
THESE ARE ACTUAL ALIENS.
- ARE WE SAYING THAT THIS IS
MANKIND'S FIRST CONTACT?
- YES, BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
EVEN MORE FASCINATING THAN THAT.
- Scientist 3:
THEY ALL SEEM TO SHARE
A COLLECTIVE
CONSCIOUSNESS.
- Scientist 2: SHARE?
- Scientist 3: THAT'S RIGHT,
AND WITHOUT ANY TIME LAG.
- Scientist 4:
BUT WHAT IF THEY'RE FAR AWAY
FROM ONE ANOTHER?
- Scientist 3:
IT MAKES NO DIFFERENCE,
EVEN LIGHT YEARS APART.
- Scientist 4:
THAT'S EXTRAORDINARY!
- NONE OF OUR ANESTHETICS
SEEM TO BE WORKING ON THEM,
NOW DO THEY?
- Doctor 1: NO,
THEY'RE STILL RESEARCHING IT.
- Doctor 2: BUT IF THEY ALL
SHARE THE SAME CONSCIOUSNESS,
THEY'LL GET USED TO BEING
DISSECTED ANYWAY, RIGHT?
- ( burbling )
- YOU SEE, SHARING CONSCIOUSNESS
IS SYNONYMOUS WITH
SHARING INFORMATION.
IF WE CAN CLARIFY HOW
THIS ABILITY WORKS
THROUGH OUR RESEARCH,
IT COULD MEAN A NEW
SYSTEM OF COMMUNICATION
THAT WOULD LITERALLY
CHANGE EVERYTHING.
JUST IMAGINE,
INSTANT COMMUNICATION
BETWEEN STAR SYSTEMS
LIGHT YEARS APART
WOULD BE MADE POSSIBLE!
- Army officer: IF WE CAN
MAKE THIS A REALITY,
IT WILL MEAN GREAT THINGS
FOR FLEET OPERATIONS.
- Guide: AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
IF INSTANT COMMUNICATION
BECOMES ACHIEVABLE,
THEN THE SUGGESTION THAT IT
WOULD ACTUALLY BE POSSIBLE
TO SURPASS THE SPEED OF LIGHT
WOULD FUNDAMENTALLY CHALLENGE
EVERYTHING WE THINK WE KNOW.
- ARE YOU SAYING WE COULD MOVE
OUR TROOPS FASTER THAN LIGHT?
- ACTUALLY, IT WOULD
MAKE DISTANCE ITSELF
COMPLETELY MEANINGLESS.
INSTANT TRANSPORTATION WOULD
BECOME A POSSIBILITY, AND...
- IS IT USABLE?
- WELL, THIS IS ALL YOU NEED
FOR INSTANT COMMUNICATION.
ANYWAY, WE'RE LOW
ON SAMPLES NOW, SO.
- Doctor 3: YOU'RE GOING TO BE
SENT TO GRABERA NOW.
DON'T WORRY, YOU'LL GO TO SLEEP
AND BE THERE IN A FLASH.
OH, YEAH.
I HEARD THEY'RE WORKING
ON A SPECIAL WEAPON
THAT USES YOUR
TECHNOLOGY AND ABILITIES.
WHAT'D THEY CALL IT? A STRAIN?
- Sara and Emily:
I'M BEING TAKEN TO THAT PLANET.
AND I CONTINUED TO FOLLOW ME,
SO THAT I COULD TAKE ME BACK.
BROTHER.
- WHAT WAS THAT THING?
MAYBE IT WAS THE NEW ENEMY
MODEL WE'VE BEEN TOLD ABOUT.
- Sara and Emily:
HE CONTINUED...
TO...
KILL ME...
IN THE DISTANT FUTURE.
- ( gasps )
BUT, WHY? WHY A LITTLE GIRL?
- ( giggles )
- HOW COULD I...
WE DO SOMETHING SO UNFORGIVABLE?
- Sara: THAT'S HOW
MY BROTHER LEARNED.
- Emily: WHAT HE...
WHAT THE UNION PEOPLE...
- Sara and Emily:
WHAT THE UNION HAD DONE TO US.
- HOW CAN I EVER MAKE
ATONEMENT FOR DOING THIS?
- YOU CAN, BROTHER. YOU CAN.
- ( gasps )
- YOU CAN IF I OPEN
THE BAXTER GATE INSIDE OF ME.
- SHE NEEDS US!
HURRY!
PLEASE!
- ( alarm beeping )
- WE'VE TOTALLY
LOST CONTROL HERE!
HER MENTAL LOAD
IS GOING TO HIT THE RED ZONE
IF WE DON'T DO
SOMETHING QUICKLY!
- ( panting )
- ( beeps )
SARA! ARE YOU OKAY?
- Sara: I SEE NOW.
SO THAT'S WHY MY BROTHER IS...
( sobs )
- ( beeping )
- ( machine thrumming )
- Barrow: THERE, SO HE IS A MAN
WHO BETRAYS HIS ALLIES.
I KNEW THIS WOULD
HAPPEN EVENTUALLY,
BUT IT ALL ENDS TODAY.
- I'M ASSUMING THE TUMORS
WILL ACCEPT MY ORDERS
IN THEIR CURRENT STATE?
- DAMN YOU! YOU PLANNED
THIS FROM THE START!
- ( gunshot )
- Girl: FINAL
DECELERATION COMPLETE.
- Female operator 1:
SYNCHRONIZATION WITH
OBJECTIVE TIME COMPLETE.
- Female operator 2:
HAILING THE STATIONED FLEET.
- Craven: MM.
IT'S FINALLY OVER NOW.
- Dufarge: YES.
- Male operator 1: COMMANDER,
I'VE GOT SOMETHING!
- WHAT IS IT?
- THE FORCES.
ALLIED FORCES AREN'T HERE!
- WHAT?
- ARE YOU CERTAIN? CHECK AGAIN.
- YES, SIR. I DON'T SHOW ANY...
SIR, THERE'S NOT A SINGLE CRAFT
IN THE PLANET'S VICINITY!
- Craven: WHAT? HOW CAN THAT BE?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sara: HE MADE A HEAVY PROMISE.
TO PAY THE PRICE OF ATONEMENT.
ON THE NEXT STRAIN,
THE BEGINNING OF REVELRY.
ALL OF MANKIND
IS MY BROTHER'S ENEMY.