- ( siren blaring )
- Male operator: GAMBEE SIX
TO PLATFORM NINE.
- GET SOME RETARDANT
ON THAT FIRE.
- SHE'S ABOUT TO
GO UP IN FLAMES.
LET'S GET THE
PILOT OUT, QUICK.
THE COCKPIT RELEASE
IS MALFUNCTIONING.
- STAND BACK,
I'VE GOT THE E.M. CUTTER.
- ( buzzing )
- MEDIC!
- ( gasps )
- HURRY UP!
- OKAY.
- OKAY, THE PILOT HAS MAJOR
HEAD TRAUMA. CHECKING HER PULSE.
HER PULSE IS WEAK, AT BEST.
EMERGENCY PROCEDURES
ARE REQUIRED.
I NEED TO PERFORM
A MANUAL SEAT BELT RELEASE.
OH, CRAP. WHERE WAS IT AGAIN?
THE SWITCH, THE SWITCH.
WHERE'S THE STUPID SWITCH?
WHERE IS IT? OH, NO.
OH. WHAT SHOULD I DO?
HEY, HELP ME. WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- DOWN.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- HURRY BECKY. THE TIME.
- ( bell ringing )
- Ben: THAT'S ENOUGH
CADET BALBOA.
IT'S OVER. CADET CRUZ IS DEAD.
- ( gasps ) NOT AGAIN.
( crying ) I KILLED ANOTHER ONE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( crying )
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I LET IT HAPPEN AGAIN.
- IT'S ONLY A DRILL, BECKY.
DON'T BE SO HARD ON YOURSELF.
- OH, YOU'RE RIGHT. THANKS
FOR BEING SO UNDERSTANDING.
- SO. WHAT DID YOU TRY
TO SAY TO ME EARLIER?
- YES, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I TRIED TO TELL YOU THE SWITCH
IS ON THE LOWER LEFT-HAND PANEL.
- HEY, WHAT THE HELL IS GOING
ON? GET THAT BODY OUT OF THERE.
- HEY, COME ON ENGINEERING.
PICK UP THE PACE.
- Carmichael: NEXT TEAM MOVE IN.
GO! GO! ARE YOU GUYS EVEN READY?
- Both: YOU, PEOPLE,
ARE MISSING THE BASICS.
PUT OUT THE FIRE, OPEN THE
COCKPIT AND SAVE THE PILOT.
HOW HARD IS THAT?
- I'M SORRY, I ALWAYS PANIC
IN HIGH PRESSURE SITUATIONS.
- LOOK GIRLS,
IT'S A FUNERAL MARCH.
POOR SARA CRUZ
HAS BEEN KILLED IN ACTION.
IF ONLY WE WERE LUCKY ENOUGH
FOR THAT TO BE TRUE.
- ( sniggering )
- THIS CONCLUDES THE RESCUE
AND RECOVERY JOINT EXERCISES.
SINCE I OVERSAW THIS
AS THE CHIEF INSTRUCTOR,
I HAVE SOME WORDS
FOR EVERYONE.
( clears throat )
YOU'RE PATHETIC!
ONLY FOUR DAYS HAVE PASSED
SINCE WE TOOK THE TACTICAL
TRAINING SCHOOL'S MOTHER SHIP,
THE LIBERTAD, FROM PORT FOR
THE SUB-LIGHTSPEED EXERCISES.
FOUR DAYS FOR YOU THAT IS.
BUT BACK ON BASION,
AN ENTIRE MONTH HAS GONE BY.
THOSE CADETS WHO STILL HAVEN'T
MASTERED THE DESCENT EXERCISE,
ARE FALLING WAY BEHIND
THE REST OF THE CLASS.
THE SUB-LIGHTSPEED
EXERCISE IS COMING UP.
YOUR GOAL SHOULD NOT BE
TO SIMPLY PARTICIPATE IN IT,
BUT TO PERFECT IT.
KEEP FOCUSED, ESPECIALLY
SOME OF YOU GAMBEE PILOTS,
WHO SEE THIS AS A GAME.
THAT TYPE OF THINKING
WILL GET YOU KILLED.
- GEE, DO YOU THINK HE
COULD BE REFERRING TO
THE CORPSE STANDING BEHIND ME?
- Jake: HE WAS REFERRING
TO YOU, ISABELLA.
- ( gasps )
- Ben: THAT IS ALL. DISMISSED.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- THAT'S AN INTERESTING LOOK.
ARE YOU TRYING TO START
A NEW FASHION TREND?
SO, ARE THOSE IDIOTS
BACK THERE HASSLING YOU AGAIN?
DID THEY HIDE YOUR CLOTHES
OR SOMETHING?
STOP. I THINK I MAY BE
ABLE TO HELP YOU OUT.
YOU CAN SQUEEZE INTO MY SPARE.
OH, YOU KNOW YOU MIGHT FIT
BETTER IN JESSIE'S UNIFORM.
- ( gasps ) WHY IS IT
HAVE TO BE MINE?
- OH, ALL RIGHT, HERE YOU GO.
- NO, THANK YOU.
- AH, YOU SURE?
- THAT GIRL JUST NEEDS TO LEARN
HOW TO LIGHTEN UP A BIT.
- WHY ARE YOU MAKING SUCH
AN EFFORT TO BE NICE TO HER?
EVEN THE OTHER DAY, YOU...
- JESSIE. I'VE BEEN SEEING
A LOT OF MYSELF IN HER.
SO, I'M CURIOUS.
- YOU ARE? I DON'T KNOW.
- LUCKY ME RUNNING INTO A PRETTY
GIRL STRIPPING IN THE HALL.
- DICKON, HANDS OFF HER.
- HEY, WAS THAT THE GAMBEE PILOT
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT?
- WHAT DO YOU CARE? YOU SPYING?
- I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
THE QUEEN GETTING
THE COLD SHOULDER.
YOU KNOW
THAT'S A RARE OCCURRENCE.
- ( chuckles ) THAT WAS HER
AND HER NAME IS SARA CRUZ.
SHE WAS A LATE TRANSFER.
SHE'S BEEN TRAINING BY HERSELF
AND EVEN GOT PERMISSION
TO TAKE PART IN THE
SUB-LIGHTSPEED BATTLE
WEEKS AHEAD OF SCHEDULE.
THE GIRL'S GOT GUTS, MAN.
AND I RESPECT THAT.
- SOUNDS LIKE A PRODIGY.
NOT BAD.
- QUIT IT!
- ( laughing )
- HEY, WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING
COMING IN HERE COVERED
IN BLOOD LIKE THAT?
- DO YOU NOT HAVE ANY RESPECT
FOR YOUR ROOMMATES?
- OBVIOUSLY NOT.
- OH WAIT, SHE PLAYED
A CORPSE, RIGHT?
- FUNNY 'CAUSE IT'S KIND OF
LIKE TALKING TO A CORPSE.
- I THINK IT'D BE
BEST FOR EVERYONE
IF SHE SLEPT IN HER
GRAVE INSTEAD.
- MAYBE SHE'S ACTUALLY A ZOMBIE.
- GROSS.
- HMM.
- ( all sniggering )
- ( whirring )
- THAT IS NOT WHAT WE
AGREED TO EARLIER, MELCHI.
WHY ARE YOU CHANGING IT?
- WOULD YOU SHUT UP CARMICHAEL?
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS
'CAUSE MY WAY'S COOLER.
- WHATEVER.
- YOU'RE NUTS.
- FIX IT, DO IT NOW.
- COME UP HERE AND MAKE ME.
- YOU JERK. HEY, I'M NOT
DONE WITH YOU.
- WHERE'S EMILY?
- THE SAME PLACE SHE ALWAYS IS.
- UM, WHO'S EMILY?
- IT'S THE DOLL WITH
THE MIMIC INSIDE.
HOW CAN YOU STILL
NOT KNOW HER NAME?
SHE COMES HERE EVERY DAY.
- HMM, I COULD CARE LESS
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE NAME HER.
AFTER ALL, I'M THE ONE
WHO CREATED HER, REMEMBER?
- HEY HOW'S IT GOING, EMILY?
I HAVE A GIFT. I HOPE
YOU LIKE SURPRISES.
I MADE IT MYSELF.
IT LOOKS CUTE.
- HMM. I DON'T KNOW, SARA.
IT DOESN'T MATCH
HER OUTFIT AT ALL.
- CONTRARY TO WHAT SHE SAID,
I THINK YOU LOOK ADORABLE.
AND SO WHAT IF YOUR
CLOTHES DON'T MATCH.
I'LL JUST MAKE YOU
SOME NEW ONES.
HMM, THERE'S AN IDEA FOR A TOP.
- ( screams ) THAT'S NOT
GOING TO WORK EITHER.
WHY CAN'T THIS THING
SUPPORT A HEAVY LOAD?
- YOU KNOW WHY? IT'S BECAUSE
YOU KEEP FIDDLING
WITH THE SETTINGS TO INCREASE
THE REACTION TIME.
- THAT'S IT'S BEST FEATURE.
I CAN'T PUT IT BACK THE
WAY IT WAS BEFORE.
- OKAY. WHY NOT
TEST IT WITH HER?
YEAH. THAT MIGHT JUST WORK,
SINCE SHE'S NOT
A STANDARD MIMIC,
IT MIGHT OUTPERFORM
A NORMAL UNIT.
- NO WAY.
IN ORDER TO DO THAT I'D HAVE TO
RECONFIGURE THE ENTIRE COCKPIT.
- THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING WE CAN DO.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO GET ANYWHERE
IF THAT JALOPY WON'T START?
- IT'LL BE SO AWESOME
IF WE CAN GET IT WORKING.
IT COULD POTENTIALLY BE
THE KEY TO WINNING THE WAR.
- WITH THE KEY WORD BEING "IF".
- Jake: THIS IS THE MOMENT
YOU'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR.
THE SUB-LIGHT SPEED
BATTLE EXERCISE.
NOW, SINCE YOUR GAMBEES
ARE FAR LESS MANEUVERABLE
THAN THE STRAINS,
YOUR UNITS WILL BE USED
AS STATIONARY GUN
BATTERIES THIS TIME.
- BUT IN A REAL SUB-LIGHTSPEED
BATTLE WE'D BE FLYING,
SO, ISN'T THIS EXERCISE
A COMPLETE WASTE OF OUR TIME?
- NO, IT'S NOT.
USING GAMBEES AS
STATIONARY BATTERIES
IS A COMMON DEFENSIVE TACTIC,
WHICH IS PRECISELY WHY
WE ARE TRAINING FOR IT TODAY.
ANY OTHER QUESTIONS? THEN GET
TO YOUR STATIONS. MOVE OUT!
- ( engine revving )
- HEY, WORK.
CRUZ TO CONTROL.
GAMBEE SIX-OH-SIX WON'T
ACTIVATE. IT'S DEAD.
- Jake: WHAT? THEN COME
ON UP TO THE BRIDGE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO WATCH FROM THERE.
GAMBEES, STAY PLANTED.
IF YOU BECOME DISLODGED
FROM THE SHIP,
YOUR UNIT WILL BE
SWEPT INTO DEEP SPACE,
AND YOU WILL DRIFT AWAY.
REMEMBER, NEVER
ATTACK FORWARD, GOT IT?
AT SUB-LIGHT SPEED, ALWAYS FIRE
TOWARDS THE REAR OF THE SHIP
NO MATTER WHERE THE ENEMY IS.
AT THOSE SPEEDS,
SHOOTING FORWARD WILL
SPRAY YOUR OWN AMMO
BACK INTO YOUR FACE,
WHICH YOU DO NOT WANT.
- Male cadet: TUMORS?
- THE MOBILE TROOPS DIVISION IS
CONDUCTING THEIR SUB-LIGHT
SPEED TRAINING TODAY.
- IS IT POSSIBLE THOSE
ARE THEIR TARGETS?
- BUT THERE'S SO MANY.
- ENCOUNTERING THE ENEMY
DURING ANY FORM OF
LIGHT-SPEED TRAVEL
IS ALMOST UNHEARD OF.
- LET'S DOUBLE CHECK
THE RADAR SIGNATURES.
- YES SIR.
- ( beeps )
- SURELY THE ENEMY WOULD KNOW
WE'RE JUST A TRAINING
SCHOOL RUNNING EXERCISES.
IT WOULDN'T BE WORTH
THEIR TIME TO ATTACK.
- ( gasps ) HOLD ON,
LET ME SEE THAT.
- ( beeps )
- NO WAY. IT'S THEM.
- THE ENEMY'S APPROACHING.
THEY'RE DIRECTLY IN FRONT OF US.
- WHAT?
- ESCORT SHIP NUMBER ONE
HAS BEEN DESTROYED.
- ALL SHIPS ENGAGE COMBAT
DEPLOYMENT PROTOCOLS AT ONCE.
- INCREASE ACCELERATION.
MOVE OUT IN FRONT OF THE ENEMY.
- ENGAGE MERCURION REACTOR.
INCREASING OUTPUT.
- UH, CAPTAIN. WOULDN'T A
BETTER COURSE OF ACTION BE
TO DECELERATE THE FLEET SUDDENLY
AND THEN ALTER OUR VECTOR?
- BOY ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
THE SHIP WOULD
BE CRUSHED TO BITS
IF WE JUMPED OUT OF LIGHT SPEED
WITHOUT TAKING
THE PROPER STEPS FIRST.
THE SAME APPLIES
TO CHANGING COURSE.
WHAT THE HELL DID THEY
TEACH YOU IN SCHOOL?
- ONE PERCENT ACCELERATION.
WE'RE MOVING AHEAD.
- PREPARE TO ATTACK.
- REMEMBER, DON'T SHOOT
FORWARD. ONLY BACKWARDS.
- AH, THE ENEMY'S ATTACKING?
- ( gasps )
- WE'VE ALREADY LOST
AN ESCORT SHIP.
WE EXPECT THEM TO CONTINUE
THE ATTACK MOMENTARILY
SO, BE READY.
GET TO THE BRIDGE,
AND TAKE COMMAND OF
THE MOBILE TROOPS
DIVISION AT ONCE.
- YES SIR.
DID EVERYONE HEAR THAT ORDER?
THE DEAGUE HAVE BEEN
KIND ENOUGH TO GIVE US
SOME REAL-LIFE COMBAT EXPERIENCE
SO, BE READY TO FIGHT
'CAUSE THIS WON'T BE EASY.
REMEMBER YOUR TRAINING.
OKAY, I WANT YOU TO SUPPORT
THE GAMBEES FROM HERE
WHILE I HEAD TO THE BRIDGE.
- RIGHT.
- WAIT, SIR. IS THERE
ANYTHING I CAN DO?
WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO PREPARE
ANOTHER UNIT FOR YOU. STAY HERE.
- ALL STRAINS LAUNCH NOW.
DON'T LET THE ENEMY GET ANY
CLOSER THAN THEY ALREADY ARE.
JUDGING BY THE WAY
THE FIRST SHIP WENT DOWN,
WE SHOULD BE EXPECTING TUMORS
TO SMASH INTO THE HULL.
IS THAT?
- SIR, I'VE GOT A VISUAL
ON THE ENEMY.
- NO. IT'S A GLOIRE TYPE.
COULD THAT REALLY BE
THE STRAIN OF RALPH WEREC?
- ( gasps )
- ( siren blaring )
- ANOTHER ONE. DEAR GOD.
- WHAT? HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
- THEY'RE ABOUT TO CROSS OUR
SHIP'S SECONDARY DEFENSIVE LINE.
STAND BY.
- GLOIRE TYPE STRAIN CONFIRMED.
IT'S DEFINITELY THE SAME
ONE THAT ATTACKED GRABERA.
- IT'S HIM, RALPH WEREC.
WHAT IN THE WORLD WOULD CAUSE
HIM TO ATTACK A TRAINING FLEET?
- ATTENTION CADETS, REPORT
TO BATTLE STATIONS AT ONCE.
ALL STRAINS ATTACK
THE GLOIRE TYPE.
GAMBEES KEEP THOSE DAMN TUMORS
OFF THE HULL OF THE SHIP.
THIS IS NOT A DRILL.
I REPEAT, THIS IS NOT A DRILL.
IT'S THE REAL THING, CADETS.
WE'RE UP AGAINST TUMORS
AND A GLOIRE TYPE STRAIN,
THE MOST ADVANCED OF IT'S KIND.
THEY'VE ALREADY DESTROYED
OUR TWO ESCORT SHIPS
AND ARE NOW GUNNING FOR US.
EVERYONE REMEMBER
WHAT YOU LEARNED
IN YOUR SUB LIGHT SPEED
TRAINING YESTERDAY,
BECAUSE THIS IS WHERE
IT WILL COUNT.
- NEVER SHOOT FORWARD. ONLY TO
THE SIDE OR REAR, CORRECT?
- CORRECT. THERE'S JUST
ONE LAST THING.
TWO-WAY COMMUNICATIONS WILL BE
IMPOSSIBLE AT SUB-LIGHT SPEED.
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
COMMUNICATE WITH EACH OTHER
BUT NOT WITH THE MOTHERSHIP.
JUST DON'T BE RECKLESS.
- WE'RE ABOUT TO FIGHT
IN OUR FIRST COMBAT OPERATION.
IT DOESN'T GET ANY MORE
RECKLESS THAN THAT.
- Operator: ALL STRAINS
HAVE LAUNCHED.
- TRY TO STAND YOUR GROUND.
YOUR GAMBEES WILL BE
UNABLE TO FUNCTION,
IF YOU'RE KNOCKED INTO SPACE.
MOVE TO THE OUTER TRENCHES
AND ENGAGE ANY TUMORS THAT
ATTACH TO THE HULL OF THE SHIP.
- Student 1: THIS SUCKS.
- Student 2:
OUR FIRST REAL BATTLE
AND IT'S AT SUB-LIGHTSPEED.
- Jake: IF YOU WANT TO AVOID
A BODY BAG, THEN FOCUS.
- Student 3: STOP PUSHING.
- Student 4: MOVE IT.
- YOU PEOPLE ARE IN MY WAY.
IF WE KEEP STANDING AROUND
THE REASONERS WILL HAVE ALL
THE GLORY AND I CAN'T HAVE THAT.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PLATOON SIX-ZERO ALREADY
HAS ROUTE ONE-ONE-FIVE.
- PLATOONS EIGHT-ONE
AND FIVE-FOUR CONTINUE
TO THE UPPER PATHWAY
FROM CURRENT LOCATION.
- Operator 1:
PROCEED TO THE DETOUR ROUTE
MARKED ON YOUR H.U.D.
AND STAND BY.
- Operator 2: LOWER STARBOARD
PATHWAY IS OPEN. PROCEED.
- Operator 3: DID YOU GUYS HEAR?
THE ENEMY HAS ONE OF THOSE
GLOIRE STRAINS WITH THEM.
- ( gasps )
- Operator 2: WAIT,
THEN THAT MEANS WE'RE GOING
UP AGAINST RALPH WEREC.
- Operator 1: THIS IS TURNING
INTO A NIGHTMARE.
- Sara: MY BROTHER IS HERE?
RALPH WEREC IS HERE. HE'S
OUTSIDE. THIS IS MY OPPORTUNITY.
BUT I'M STUCK ON BOARD THIS SHIP
INSTEAD OF OUT THERE WITH HIM.
WHAT'S THE POINT
OF EVEN BEING HERE
IF I CAN'T GET TO MY BROTHER?
( grunts )
- YOU IDIOT. YOU'RE GOING
TO GET YOURSELF KILLED
IF YOU FIGHT LIKE THAT.
I TOLD YOU SO.
FIGHTING THESE STUPID TUMORS
IS JUST WASTING MY TIME.
OKAY, WHERE THE HELL
ARE YOU HIDING, WEREC?
- Jake: THE FIRST WAVE OF TUMORS
HAVE ARRIVED. DESTROY THEM ALL.
BE PATIENT AND WAIT UNTIL
THEY'RE WITHIN RANGE TO FIRE.
- YES. I CAN TAKE CARE
OF ALL THESE MYSELF.
- ABOVE YOU. LOOK.
- ( gasps )
NO, STOP. GET OFF!
( screams ) HELP,
SOMEONE HELP ME.
- ISABELLA!
- ( screams )
- ( loud explosion )
- Craven: THE SHIP'S RATE
OF ACCELERATION IS DROPPING.
- SIR, THE NUMBER
OF STRAIN CASUALTIES
JUST PASSED THIRTY PERCENT.
- WE'VE LOST OVER TWENTY
PERCENT OF OUR GAMBEES.
- THIS IS A BLOODBATH.
THESE KIDS HAVEN'T EVEN HAD
A CHANCE TO GRADUATE YET.
- ( loud explosion )
- DAMN. WHERE ARE YOU GUYS?
- Dickon: CARRIS, YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HEY, DID YOU HAPPEN TO SEE
ANYONE ELSE OUT THERE?
- YEAH ERMY, MARTHA AND
LAVINIA ARE ALL FIGHTING
OVER THE STARBOARD WING.
- GOT IT. WHAT ABOUT JESSIE AND
THE QUEEN? HAVE YOU SEEN THEM?
- I'M RIGHT HERE, YOU GUYS.
BUT WHEN LOTTIE HEARD THAT
RALPH WEREC WAS AROUND,
SHE WENT OFF TO LOOK
FOR HIM ON HER OWN.
- ( screaming )
WHERE ARE YOU WEREC?
- THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
- I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE
ACTUALLY BEING ATTACKED.
PRETTY CRAZY, HUH?
- I DON'T GET WHY THE DEAGUE
WOULD ATTACK A TRAINING SHIP.
I MEAN THEY'VE REALLY
CROSSED THE LINE
WHERE THE MORALS OF
WAR ARE CONCERNED.
- ( gasps )
- ( rumbling )
- Lottie: THERE HE IS.
I FOUND YOU, BASTARD.
IT'S TIME I PUT A STOP
TO THIS TRAITOROUS SCUM!
- HMM.
- OH, HI.
- WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE OF A PITY
PARTY, SO, SAVE IT FOR LATER.
UNLESS YOU WANT TO JOIN US,
OF COURSE.
BUT WE'LL PROBABLY BE DEAD
LATER, SO, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
- THAT STRAIN THERE.
IT IS FULLY OPERATIONAL, RIGHT?
BECAUSE I WANT TO FLY IT, NOW.
- BUT YOU'RE JUST A GAMBEE
PILOT. WHAT ARE YOU STUPID?
YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
DO ANYTHING WITH IT
SINCE YOU DON'T HAVE A MIMIC.
- YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT,
I DO HAVE A MIMIC. IT'S EMILY.
- OH, PLEASE. EVERYONE KNOWS
YOU CAN'T PILOT A STRAIN
WITH SOMEONE ELSE'S MIMIC.
- IT'S IMPOSSIBLE. IMPOSSIBLE.
- GO AHEAD.
- IT'S WORTH A SHOT.
AND IT'S YOUR LUCKY DAY
'CAUSE I JUST RECONFIGURED THE
COCKPIT SO THE DOLL WOULD FIT.
IF NOTHING ELSE, IT'LL BE GOOD
FOR TESTING PURPOSES.
- YOU READY, EMILY?
- Melchi: WHAT A DOWNER.
THIS SHIP WON'T LAST MUCH LONGER
UNLESS A MIRACLE HAPPENS
AND THAT STRAIN STARTS,
WE'RE BREATHING
OUR LAST BREATHS, CARMICHAEL.
- DO YOU THINK IT'LL START?
- DOUBT IT.
- OH, WELL. BUMMER.
- Sara: TO PILOT A STRAIN,
YOU CAN ONLY USE THE
MIMIC ASSIGNED TO YOU.
THAT'S THE RULE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT IT FEELS LIKE THIS GIRL
CALLED OUT FOR ME BACK THERE.
YEAH. YOU DID IT, RIGHT?
YOU KNEW I NEEDED YOUR HELP
SO, YOU SUMMONED ME HERE?
NOW THAT I'M HERE,
I'M BEGGING YOU. TAKE ME.
TAKE ME TO MY BROTHER. TAKE ME.
- Melchi: I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
- Both: IT'S WORKING.
- THAT LIGHT IS
FROM THE MERCURION.
- NO WAY!
- Both: THEY'RE LINKED.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- Melchi: A MIRACLE REALLY
DID HAPPEN.
- ( siren blaring )
- ( both gasp )
- BROTHER, I'M COMING FOR YOU.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sara:
AS A NEW DAILY ROUTINE SETS IN,
I LEARN WHY THE QUEEN
DESPISES MY BROTHER SO MUCH.
ON THE NEXT STRAIN, REASONER
SARA. MY BROTHER IS MY ENEMY.