- Female operator:
I DON'T SHOW ANY...
SIR, THERE'S NOT A SINGLE
CRAFT IN THE PLANET'S VICINITY!
- Craven: HOW CAN THAT BE?
- BUT WE WERE TOLD THERE'S AN
EXERCISE HAPPENING ON BREGMA,
WITH OVER A
HUNDRED-THOUSAND SHIPS!
- I KNOW THAT, BUT I'M NOT
PICKING UP ANYONE OUT THERE!
WE'RE THE ONLY
ONES SHOWING UP!
- BUT, THEN, WHERE COULD
THE FLEET HAVE GONE?
- AND THIS MEANS THAT
THE LIBERTAD IS...
- ( beeping )
- IT'S A MESSAGE FROM AN
UNMANNED BREGMA BASE!
SENT BY THE UNION'S EXERCISE
MANAGEMENT DIVISION.
IT'S CODED LEVEL ONE, SIR!
- GOOD! LET'S DECIPHER
IT AT ONCE!
MEDICAL AND
TECHNOLOGY INSTRUCTORS
REPORT TO THE CONFERENCE ROOM.
WE'VE ONLY JUST
LEARNED THAT THE DEAGUE
ARE PLANNING AN ASSAULT
WITH A MILLION-SHIP ARMADA.
- BUT THAT'S AN
INCREDIBLE SCALE, SIR.
- THE LARGEST IN HISTORY.
- THESE ARE THE ENEMY'S
ESTIMATED STAGING POSTS.
IN RESPONSE TO THIS ATTACK,
THE UNION DECIDED TO
INTERCEPT THEM HERE,
AND PROMPTLY NOTIFIED
ALL FLEETS.
IT SEEMS THE FORCES AT BREGMA
CEASED THEIR EXERCISES
AND HEADED FOR AN
INTERCEPT POINT AS WELL.
- WELL, THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
WHY THERE'S NOT ANYONE HERE.
- SO, LET ME GUESS. OUR ONLY
CHOICE IS TO HEAD BACK TO BASION
WITHOUT ANY NEW
SUPPLIES OR REPAIRS.
- BUT, IT'S NOT ALL
BAD NEWS NOW, IS IT?
SOUNDS LIKE THE
ENEMY'S TRYING TO
DEVOTE EVERY SHIP IN THE
AREA TO THIS MISSION.
- EVERY SHIP?
SO, DOES THAT MEAN?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- I THINK IT'S SAFE TO
ASSUME THE DEAGUE SHIP
THAT'S BEEN CHASING
US WAS SENT OFF
TO JOIN THE REST OF THEIR FLEET.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Ralph crying )
- HOW COULD WE DO
SOMETHING SO UNFORGIVABLE?
HOW CAN I EVER
MAKE ATONEMENT?
- Emily: YOU CAN,
BROTHER. YOU CAN.
- YOU CAN IF... IF I OPEN
THE BAXTER GATE INSIDE ME.
- SARA? ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
- I DON'T...
- YOUR MENTAL LOAD
HAD A HUGE INCREASE
WHILE YOU WERE LINKED TO HER,
AND YOU BLACKED
OUT PRETTY QUICK.
- Carmichael: DON'T WORRY.
EMILY'S JUST FINE.
- IT WASN'T A DREAM,
IT ALL REALLY HAPPENED.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY PAIN ANYWHERE?
- I'M FINE.
- GREAT! THEN WE CAN GET
BACK TO THE EXPERIMENT!
WE NEED TO INVESTIGATE THE CAUSE
OF WHAT JUST HAPPENED TO YOU.
- INVESTIGATE?
I THOUGHT I WAS BEING
HANDED OVER TO THE MILITARY.
- THAT PLAN'S BEEN PUT ON
HOLD FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- Martha: WHAT A LETDOWN!
- YEAH, WE WORK SO
HARD TO GET TO BREGMA,
JUST TO FIND OUT THAT
NO ONE'S HERE TO HELP
AND THE DEAGUE'S NOT
CHASING US ANYMORE.
- ARE WE REALLY SURE
THEY'RE NOT COMING?
- WELL, THE TIME LIMIT
WAS REALLY TIGHT
AND IF THEY WERE
GOING TO MAKE IT,
THEY'D HAVE TO HAVE
GONE STRAIGHT TO
THE STAGING POINT
FROM GALL'S DEPOT.
- I SEE.
- I'M TELLING YOU,
MY BROTHER WILL SHOW UP!
- OH, COME ON NOW!
THEY'RE STAGING AN INCREDIBLY
MASSIVE OPERATION!
JUST BECAUSE HE'S
RALPH WEREC DOESN'T MEAN...
NO, ACTUALLY, THE FACT THAT
HE'S A PROVEN TRAITOR ENSURES
THEY'D NEVER ALLOW HIM
TO ACT ON HIS OWN!
SO EVEN IF HE WANTED
TO COME HE COULDN'T!
- HE'LL DO IT ANYWAY!
I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND,
MY BROTHER IS OBLIGATED
TO COME HERE.
- WAIT, LET'S GET CRAVEN.
- HE HAS TO, BECAUSE HE
MADE A VERY SERIOUS PROMISE.
AND THAT'S WHY,
I KNOW HE WILL.
- BEGINNING OUR THIRD
DECELERATION NOW.
COUNTDOWN. THREE.
TWO. ONE.
- ( rumbling and clanging )
- ( groaning )
- ( whines )
- BROTHER!
- I'M FINE.
- Craven: SARA,
PLEASE TELL US EVERYTHING.
EVERYTHING YOU
SAW AND LEARNED,
WHEN YOU WERE
LINKED TO THE MIMIC.
- WELL, SIR. IT HAPPENED
OVER SIX HUNDRED YEARS AGO.
THE SPACESHIP WAS INDEPENDENT.
IT DIDN'T BELONG TO
THE UNION OR THE DEAGUE,
BUT, IT LANDED ON
THE UNION RESOURCE
SATELLITE OF NIEREN SIX.
- THEY WERE ALIENS THAT
ALL LOOKED EXACTLY ALIKE?
- THEY WERE REFERRED
TO AS UKs.
"UNKNOWNS," AND THEY WERE PLACED
UNDER MILITARY SUPERVISION.
AND THEN, THE RESEARCH BEGAN,
IN ABSOLUTE SECRECY.
- UGH! THAT'S UNFORGIVABLE.
- ONE OF THE IMPORTANT
THINGS THEY DISCOVERED,
WAS THAT THE GIRLS ALL
SHARED SOME OF THEIR SENSES.
- THEY SHARED...
- Sara: SIGHT, HEARING,
AND EMOTION.
- WHEN YOU SAY ALL
THE GIRLS, DO YOU MEAN?
- EVEN LIGHT-YEARS APART
THEY COMMUNICATE,
WITHOUT ANY DIFFICULTY
OR TIME-LAG.
- BUT THAT COULD
HAVE APPLICATIONS
IN ALL SORTS OF FIELDS.
THINK ABOUT IT. INSTANT
INTERSTELLAR COMMUNICATION!
- THAT'S THE POINT, IT WAS FOR
EXACTLY THAT KIND OF GAIN.
ALL OF THOSE GIRLS WERE...
- SORRY.
SO THAT EXPLAINS
THE MIMIC EMILY.
SHE WAS ONE OF
THE ALIENS THEY FOUND.
- AND, IF THEY WERE RESEARCHING
INSTANT INTERSTELLAR
COMMUNICATION,
THEN WHY ISN'T
IT POSSIBLE YET?
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED?
- NIEREN SIX WAS NEVER INTENDED
TO BE A RESEARCH FACILITY.
TECHNOLOGY COULD
ONLY DEVELOP SO FAR.
SO, THEY DECIDED TO MOVE
THE WHOLE OPERATION
TO PLANET GRABERA.
- Carmichael: THEY'D BE FAR
FROM THE FRONT LINES THERE.
IT'S A PERFECT PLACE FOR
DOING SECRETIVE RESEARCH.
- ( turbines whirring )
- Sara: BUT,
ALMOST IMMEDIATELY...
- ( indistinct shouting )
- Melchi: THE BAXTER GATE?
- Sara: A GATE THAT
CONNECTS LOCATIONS IN SPACE,
AND OUT OF IT CAME...
- Dufarge: THEY CAME TO
RETRIEVE THEIR COMRADES.
- Ben: INCREDIBLE.
A SUB-LIGHTSPEED BATTLE IN
AN ERA WITHOUT STRAINS.
THE UNION'S ONLY
OPTION WOULD BE TO RUN.
- Melchi: BUT THERE WOULD
BE ONE WAY TO SURVIVE.
SEND AS MUCH OF THE RESEARCH
AS POSSIBLE TO GRABERA
AND USE IT TO CREATE A WEAPON
CAPABLE OF DEFEATING THEM.
- YEAH! A FEW HOURS
OF SUB-LIGHTSPEED TRAVEL
WOULD EQUAL CENTURIES
OF OBJECTIVE TIME!
- IF THINGS GO WELL,
REINFORCEMENTS COULD BE
ARRIVING IN MERE MINUTES!
- THEN WHAT WE'RE SAYING IS
THAT'S HOW STRAIN TECHNOLOGY
CAME TO BE DEVELOPED.
- YES.
- AND THEN, THEY
MUST'VE SENT OUT
THE UNION'S BEST TO
DEFEAT THE UNKNOWNS,
AND THAT MEANT RALPH WEREC.
- MY BROTHER DIDN'T HAVE
ANY IDEA WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
HE WASN'T TOLD ANYTHING.
HE WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THEY WERE UNMANNED DEAGUE UNITS.
IT WAS ONLY AFTER
MY BROTHER DESTROYED
THE LAST MOBILE WEAPON
THAT HE LEARNED THE TRUTH.
- ONE TO GO.
NOW IT'S DONE.
( gasps )
- WAIT A MINUTE, SOMETHING
DOES NOT MAKE SENSE.
RALPH LEFT GRABERA IN
SEVEN THOUSAND THREE
STANDARD ERA, RIGHT?
WHICH MEANS HE SHOULD
STILL BE TRAVELING
AT SUB-LIGHTSPEED NOW!
HE HASN'T EVEN CAUGHT UP TO
THE TARGET AUXILIARY VESSEL YET!
- Carmichael: I GET IT.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
RALPH ACTUALLY CAUGHT
UP WITH THE TARGET
IN SEVENTY-FIVE SIXTY-FOUR
STANDARD ERA.
- BUT IF THAT'S TRUE, THEN HOW
DID HE MANAGE TO SHOW UP HERE?
HE COULDN'T HAVE!
- YES, HE COULD,
BECAUSE THE LAST GIRL
MY BROTHER DEFEATED
OPENED A GATE.
- Carmichael: BUT I THOUGHT
THE GATES WERE FOR
INSTANT TRANSPORTATION
THROUGH SPACE,
NOT TIME.
- Melchi: OF COURSE!
MULTIPLE TIMES EXIST WHEN
TRAVELING AT SUB-LIGHTSPEED!
AND SHE CHOSE RALPH'S SUBJECTIVE
TIME OF SEVEN THOUSAND FIVE!
- SO, THAT WOULD MEAN
THE BAXTER GATE CONNECTED
WITH SPACE IN SEVEN
THOUSAND FIVE, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- AND THAT'S HOW RALPH WEREC
WAS CAPABLE OF RETURNING HERE.
- AMAZING. SIMPLY AMAZING.
- THIS IS ALMOST
IMPOSSIBLE TO BELIEVE.
- WHEN IT HAPPENED, THE SUM
OF ALL OF THE MEMORIES AND
FEELINGS OF THE GIRLS.
THEY CAME, THEY FLOWED
STRAIGHT INTO MY BROTHER.
- ( Ralph screaming )
- Sara: AND THAT'S WHY,
HE WILL COME WITHOUT FAIL.
- Medlock: FINAL DECELERATION
COMPLETE. TARGET CONFIRMED.
AM I USELESS TO YOU NOW?
YOU WANT TO KILL ME?
- ( beeping )
- HEY. I NEED TO GO
TO THE RESTROOM,
OR IS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK?
DON'T TRUST ME?
( thinking ) WHAT COULD
THIS MAN BE THINKING?
IF I'D HAD ANY IDEA THIS
WAS GOING TO HAPPEN,
I WOULDN'T HAVE...
AN OLD MODEL UNION SHIP?
STRANGE, HOW DID IT COME
THIS FAR IN THAT CONDITION?
- WE HAVE VIDEO FOOTAGE FROM
A RECONNAISSANCE TUMOR UNIT.
- GOOD.
- Barrow: A SURVIVOR?
- I WISH TO DEFECT.
LET ME SPEAK WITH
YOUR COMMANDER.
I WISH TO DEFECT.
LET ME SPEAK.
I AM A REASONER OF
THE UNION, RALPH WEREC.
- Medlock: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- Barrow: I HAVE
A HARD TIME BELIEVING
INSTANT INTERSTELLAR
COMMUNICATION IS POSSIBLE,
BUT, THERE IS
A CHANCE IT'S REAL.
IF IT'S WITHIN OUR
POWER TO OBTAIN IT,
I ADVISE WE GIVE IT A TRY.
- Medlock: INDEED.
- Barrow: IF WE
RETURNED HOME NOW,
WE WOULD HAVE THREE YEARS
UNTIL OUR NEXT OPERATION.
AND I DON'T DOUBT THEY WOULD
GIVE US A FULL VACATION.
- Medlock: SO YOU'RE SAYING
YOU WOULD RATHER
TAKE A SHOT AT GAINING GLORY?
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- YOU'RE IN NEED
OF ANOTHER ONE?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID THIS
ONE WOULD BE SUFFICIENT
TO DEVELOP INSTANT
INTERSTELLAR COMMUNICATION?
- IN ORDER TO COMMUNICATE,
A SENDER AND RECEIVER
ARE NECESSARY.
ONE OTHER EXISTS THAT
WOULD PARALLEL HER,
AND SHE WISHES FOR IT, TOO.
- ANOTHER TO PARALLEL HER.
WELL, WE'VE COME THIS FAR.
WE MIGHT AS WELL
SEE IT THROUGH.
THOSE EYES.
THOSE EYES ARE WHAT
CONVINCED ME TO...
DAMN IT!
I WAS SUCH AN IDIOT.
HOW COULD I LET HIM...
- ( thudding )
- ( gasping )
- ( groaning )
- Computer: YOUR IDENTIFICATION
HAS NOT BEEN AUTHENTICATED.
- THIS IS MY SHIP, YOU IDIOT!
- Computer: YOUR IDENTIFICATION
HAS NOT BEEN AUTHENTICATED.
ADMITTANCE INTO THIS
SECTION IS FORBIDDEN.
- COME ON!
I NEVER DREAMED I WOULD
ACTUALLY HAVE TO USE THIS.
- ( alarm blaring )
- Computer: THE SELF-DESTRUCT
MECHANISM HAS BEEN ACTIVATED.
- LETS GO.
- Computer: ALL PERSONNEL,
EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY.
THE SELF-DESTRUCT
MECHANISM HAS BEEN ACTIVATED.
- ( cries ) NO,
- ALL PERSONNEL,
- BROTHER!
- EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY.
- LISTEN, THIS SHIP
IS ABOUT TO EXPLODE
AND WE HAVE TO ESCAPE NOW!
- WHERE'S BROTHER? BROTHER!
- COME ON, SURELY EVEN
YOU CAN TELL THAT
YOUR "BROTHER"
HAS GONE CRAZY?
HE CAN'T TELL WHO'S ON HIS
SIDE AND WHO'S THE ENEMY!
IN FACT, IT WOULDN'T
SURPRISE ME IF
HE ATTACKED HIS OWN FLESH
AND BLOOD RIGHT NOW.
- ( whimpers )
- ( alarm blaring )
- ( coughs )
- Sara:
WHAT'S DRIVING MY BROTHER NOW
IS OVERWHELMING GUILT.
HE'S MADE A PROMISE,
AND HE FEELS BOUND BY A DUTY
TO SAVE ANY SURVIVORS.
I KNOW HE WILL DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
HE HAS NO ALLIES OR ENEMIES.
- THEN, THIS SHIP
CAME UNDER ATTACK,
BECAUSE WE HAVE POSSESSION
OF THE MIMIC?
- IT WOULD'VE COMMUNICATED
TO THE OTHER ONE,
SO THEY WOULD KNOW
SHE WAS HERE.
- BUT, IT'S ONLY THE BRAIN NOW!
- Sara: I SUSPECT MY BROTHER
PROBABLY DOESN'T KNOW THAT.
- DOES THAT MEAN THIS
SHIP WILL BE SAFE
IF WE GIVE EMILY TO THEM?
- HEY, THAT BELONGS TO ME!
- SHUT UP, MELCHI!
- I TOLD YOU, MY BROTHER
IS BEING MOTIVATED NOW
BY AN INTENSE FEELING OF GUILT.
HE DESPISES ALL OF MANKIND
FOR THE TERRIBLE THINGS
THEY DID TO THE GIRLS.
IN HIS EYES, VENGEANCE MEANS
THE ANNIHILATION
OF ALL HUMANS.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- Lottie: I TAKE IT YOU HEARD?
- DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
I HEARD, BUT IT
DOESN'T CHANGE THE...
IT DOESN'T MEAN
CARRIS HAD TO...
- ( alarm blaring )
- YOU THINK THIS COULD
BE A REAL ATTACK?
- LET'S GO!
- RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- Dufarge: IS IT A SHUTTLE?
- Female operator: YES, SIR!
IT'S SENDING A DISTRESS
SIGNAL AND CLOSING IN!
- Craven: IT'S NOT EVEN
THREE LIGHT-SECONDS AWAY!
TELL ME, WHY WASN'T
IT NOTICED SOONER?
- BECAUSE, SIR, WE WEREN'T
AT GALL LONG ENOUGH
TO REPAIR THE SENSORS!
- SIR, IT'S A MESSAGE
FROM THE SHUTTLE!
( exclaims ) IT SAYS
THEY WANT TO SURRENDER!
- SURRENDER?
- Male operator:
THE SENDER IS VIVIAN MEDLOCK,
CAPTAIN OF THE
DEAGUE SHIP KUNRUN!
- A DEAGUE CAPTAIN?
BUT WHY WOULD SHE SURRENDER?
- CONNECT US, SO I CAN
SPEAK WITH HER DIRECTLY.
- YES, SIR!
- THIS IS CRAVEN SPEAKING,
ACTING HEAD OF THE UNION
EXERCISE SHIP, LIBERTAD.
- I'LL SAVE THE DETAILS
FOR A LATER BRIEFING,
FOR NOW I REQUEST PERMISSION
TO COME ABOARD.
- Craven: TELL US WHAT HAS
HAPPENED, CAPTAIN MEDLOCK.
- I HAVE BEEN BOTH BETRAYED AND
THREATENED BY RALPH WEREC!
AND SO I'VE ESCAPED!
- ( alarm blaring )
- Medlock: THE MAN
HAS GONE INSANE!
HE MURDERED ALL OF MY CREW
AND TOOK CONTROL OF THE SHIP.
ALL TO GET TO THE
OTHER ONE YOU HAVE.
- ( buzzing )
- OTHER ONE?
- IT DOES SEEM TO MATCH UP
WITH THE ACCOUNT SARA TOLD US.
- AS LONG AS YOU CAN
GUARANTEE ME MY LIFE,
I'LL RETURN THE SAMPLE WE STOLE
FROM GRABERA LABORATORY.
- CAPTAIN MEDLOCK.
IF WE AGREED TO THOSE TERMS,
I HAVE NO DOUBT RALPH WEREC
WOULD COME AFTER US EVEN
MORE FIERCELY THAN BEFORE.
- Medlock: OH, I WOULDN'T
WORRY ABOUT THAT IF I WERE YOU.
THE KUNRUN IS ABOUT
TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
- HEY, DO YOU THINK ALL DEAGUE
SOLDIERS WALK AROUND LIKE THAT?
- SURELY NOT!
- THEIR PHYSICAL CHECKUPS
MUST BE A BREEZE.
- EXCUSE ME, IS IT
THE UNION'S POLICY TO
KEEP CAPTURED OFFICERS NAKED
OR ARE YOU GOING TO
PROVIDE ME SOME CLOTHES?
- SO, THAT'S REALLY EMILY!
- ( beeping )
- ENEMY SHIP IS DETECTED!
IT'S CLOSING IN, SIR,
IT'S ON A COLLISION COURSE!
- HE'S TRYING TO TAKE THE
LIBERTAD DOWN WITH HIM.
- Dufarge: CAN WE SHAKE HIM OFF
WITH EMERGENCY ACCELERATION?
- MERCURION LEVEL RISING!
THREE MINUTES FORTY
SECONDS TO ACCELERATION!
- HE'S GOING TO CATCH UP TO US!
- Dufarge: ALL HANDS
TO BATTLE STATIONS!
YOUR MISSION IS TO DESTROY
THE APPROACHING ENEMY SHIP!
- Melchi: SARA, YOU STILL
HAVEN'T BEEN CLEARED FOR BATTLE.
BUT IF RALPH WEREC IS REALLY
OUT THERE GUNNING FOR US
THEN I BELIEVE YOU HAVE
THE RIGHT TO FIGHT HIM.
- Sara: THANK YOU.
- Melchi: WE'LL GO
GET THINGS READY.
- Dufarge:
COURSE PROJECTION INDICATES THAT
IT'S COMING AT US IN
SUICIDE ATTACK MODE.
WE MUST DIVERT IT AT ALL COST!
- I'M AMAZED THAT YOU CAN
SLEEP AT A TIME LIKE THIS!
- DAMMIT. I DON'T
WANNA STAY HERE!
- STOP COMPLAINING!
JUST LEAVE THIS TO US AND FOCUS
ON WHAT YOU CAN DO TO HELP!
EASY ENOUGH, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH, THIS IS A DRAG BUT
I'M BEHIND YOU ALL THE WAY!
- THANKS A LOT.
- Craven: PREPARE FOR
EVASIVE MANEUVERS!
OPERATOR, HOW ARE
THE ENGINES HOLDING UP?
- OUTPUT INCREASING FOR BOTH
SECOND AND THIRD
AUXILIARY ENGINES!
ONE-TEN TO MAIN ENGINE DRIVE!
- ( clanging )
- ( whirring )
- ( whooshing )
- Male operator: GAMBEE
E-ZERO-ONE TO LAUNCH POSITION!
- ROGER!
- ( crackling )
- ( whirring )
- ( whooshing )
- ALL UNITS PREPARE TO STAY
CLOSE TO THE LIBERTAD
OR YOU'LL GET LEFT BEHIND!
- Lottie: ONLY FIVE OF US LEFT.
THE SPATIAL ARMOR DIVISION
LOOKS A LITTLE LONELY TO ME.
- Jessie: LOTTIE! IF THAT GLOIRE
SHOWS UP WITH US OUT HERE...
- I KNOW, JESS.
LIBERTAD BRIDGE,
DO YOU READ ME?
SEND HER OUT.
SEND SARA WEREC INTO BATTLE.
WE NEED HER HELP!
SHE CAN HELP STOP
THE DEAGUE SHIP.
SEND OUT SARA WEREC'S STRAIN!
- LOTTIE, ARE YOU SURE?
- THINK ABOUT IT,
SHE'S RALPH WEREC'S SISTER!
- I KNOW AND SO WHAT?
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES
IT MAKE WHO SARA IS?
I JUST KNOW THAT SHE'S A MEMBER
OF THE SPATIAL ARMOR DIVISION.
AND THAT FACT ALONE
MAKES HER A FRIEND
WE CAN TRUST
WITH OUR LIVES.
- OH, LOTTIE!
- WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT WAY.
- ALRIGHT, QUEEN, LET'S DO IT.
- WELL, HOW ABOUT WE GIVE
THEM A RUN FOR THEIR MONEY
UNTIL SHE CAN CATCH UP, OKAY?
- DID YOU GET THAT, BRIDGE?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- UM-HM.
CALL SARA NOW.
- STRAIN EX WILL PREPARE
TO LAUNCH IMMEDIATELY!
- WE MADE A FEW ADJUSTMENTS,
IF ALL GOES WELL THE LINK
SHOULDN'T MALFUNCTION AGAIN.
- HERE.
- THANKS VERY MUCH.
- ( siren blaring )
- BROTHER.
RALPH, I KNOW WHAT YOU SAW.
I UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU FELT,
BUT STILL...
I HAVE TO STOP YOU,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sara: I KNOW THAT THE
BROTHER IN FRONT OF ME NOW,
ISN'T THE BROTHER I KNEW.
ON THE NEXT STRAIN,
ATTACK ON THE LIBERTAD.
- BROTHER, LET'S PUT
AN END TO THIS.