- ( panting )
- OH SARA, BELIEVE ME,
I'M SO SORRY!
OH, WHAT DO I DO NOW?
FORGIVE ME, SARA!
- Lottie: YOU DID WHAT?
YOU IDIOT!
I MEAN HOLY HELL, LAVINIA,
LIKE WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH
ISSUES WITHOUT YOU
CAUSING TROUBLE!
- Lavinia: ( crying )
I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
- Lottie: WELL, WHERE'D SHE GO?
- Lavinia: I THINK SHE'S
GOING INTO TOWN.
I DON'T THINK SHE HAS
HER DAY TRACER, THOUGH.
- OKAY, STOP CRYING
AND GET OVER HERE NOW!
LET'S GO AHEAD
AND CALL THE OTHERS.
WE NEED MORE PEOPLE
TO HELP SEARCH.
- GOT IT.
- Carris: YEAH, CARRIS HERE.
I'M SORRY, WHAT?
HOW IS EMILY GONE?
- Lottie: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT SARA'S MIA TOO.
SHE WENT LOOKING BY HERSELF.
- Carris: OH, MAN.
- Lottie: LISTEN, WE NEED TO
FIND HER IMMEDIATELY, GET IT?
- Martha: SARA OR EMILY?
- Lottie: OH COME ON!
BOTH OF THEM, OBVIOUSLY!
NOW, WE THINK SARA'S HEADED
FOR A WASTE COLLECTION POINT
SOMEWHERE IN THE CITY.
LET'S SPLIT UP AND CHECK OUT
ALL OF THEM UNTIL WE FIND HER.
- Lottie: UNDERSTOOD?
- Team: ROGER!
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Worker: HEY!
YOU CAN'T COME IN HERE!
- EMILY!
- ( grunts )
- SARA, STOP!
- LET GO.
I CAN SEE HER,
SHE'S GETTING AWAY.
I HAVE TO SAVE EMILY!
- EMILY!
- STOP IT!
LOOK CLOSER.
THAT'S NOT EMILY!
LOOK, SARA, I KNOW SHE
MEANS A LOT TO YOU.
IF YOU WANT TO FIND HER,
YOU HAVE TO CALM DOWN.
- BUT I'VE GOT TO...
EMILY IS OUT HERE.
- JUST STOP FOR A
SECOND AND BREATHE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
BE ANY GOOD TO HER
IF YOU'RE JUST RUNNING ALL
OVER THE CITY LIKE THIS.
- BUT I...
- HEY, DON'T WORRY.
WITH ALL OF US LOOKING,
WE'LL FIND HER.
I ACTUALLY LIVED HERE
UNTIL I LEFT FOR BASION,
SO I KNOW MY WAY
AROUND PRETTY WELL.
AND I HAVE SOME CONNECTIONS
THAT MAY HELP US OUT.
- WELL, HELLO THERE!
HOW MAY I HELP YOU TODAY?
- CAN YOU CALL DONNY?
PLEASE, IT'S URGENT
THAT I SPEAK WITH
DONALD RADOFRICS
IMMEDIATELY!
- YOU'RE ASKING TO SEE
THE CHIEF ADMINISTRATOR?
MAY I ASK WHY YOU...
- THIS IS AN EMERGENCY!
JUST TELL HIM CARRIS IS
WAITING AND HE'LL UNDERSTAND!
- CARRIS, DON'T.
- BUT SIR, I'M NOT...
- YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
GET IN TROUBLE.
HE'LL TELL YOU THAT I'M HIS...
- Radofrics: BROTHER?
- CHIEF ADMINISTRATOR!
- CARRIS, BIG BROTHER.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S YOU!
WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
I'VE MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
- Sara: SO, HE'S YOUR
YOUNGER BROTHER?
- YEAH, BUT SEE, I'VE DONE SO
MUCH SUB-LIGHTSPEED TRAVEL THAT
HE IS ACTUALLY
OLDER THAN I AM NOW,
WHICH IS REALLY
WEIRD TO THINK ABOUT.
ANYWAY, HE'S CHIEF SATELLITE
ADMINISTRATOR HERE
AND KNOWS ABOUT EVERYTHING THAT
COMES IN AND OUT OF THIS PLACE,
SO DON'T WORRY, WE SHOULD
KNOW SOMETHING SOON.
PLUS ALL OF THE OTHERS ARE
OUT LOOKING FOR EMILY, ALSO.
- ALL OF THE OTHERS?
- ( watch device beeps )
- OH, UH, CRAP.
- YOU FREAKING JERK!
WHY DIDN'T YOU LET
THE REST OF US KNOW
AS SOON AS YOU FOUND HER!
- LISTEN SARA. DON'T EVER DO
SOMETHING LIKE THIS AGAIN.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
WORRIED WE'VE ALL BEEN?
WHEN BAD THINGS HAPPEN
YOU NEED TO CALL US, OKAY?
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
- YOU BETTER BE,
BECAUSE ALL WE'VE BEEN
DOING IS TRYING TO BE...
- HEY, LAVINIA. CAN YOU PLEASE
COME OVER HERE AND HOLD HER?
- UH, SURE!
- HEY, STOP! I'M NOT DONE!
- SORRY BOUT THAT.
- SHE NEEDS TO KNOW EXACTLY...
- SARA, YOU STILL THERE?
- WE'RE ALL RIGHT BEHIND
YOU HELPING OUT,
- SO DON'T WORRY
ABOUT A THING, OKAY?
- YEAH. THANKS A LOT.
- ALRIGHT, WE'LL KEEP
LOOKING FOR EMILY OVER HERE.
YOU GUYS LET US KNOW IF YOU
FIND ANYTHING. OVER AND OUT.
I'M HUNGRY. WE SHOULD
GO GET SOME FOOD.
YOU HAVEN'T EATEN AT ALL
SINCE THIS MORNING, HAVE YOU?
- UH, NO.
- ( stomach grumbles )
- WELL, THAT DECIDES IT.
I REMEMBER A RESTAURANT
NEARBY. LET'S GO!
- BUT SHOULDN'T WE...
- Carris: GALL IS QUITE A WAYS
FROM THE NEUTRAL ZONE,
SO THE CIVILIANS WHO LIVE
HERE HAVE A LOT OF SAY
ABOUT HOW THINGS HAPPEN.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED AT
HOW PEACEFUL IT IS,
AND WHEN YOU GROW UP HERE
EVERYBODY TENDS TO TURN
OUT PRETTY LAID-BACK.
- ( clock strikes five )
- WOW, THAT REALLY
TAKES ME BACK.
- HI, THERE!
SO WHAT'LL IT BE?
- WELL...
- CARRIS?
OH MY GOODNESS, IT IS YOU!
WOW, HOW MANY
YEARS HAS IT BEEN?
- YOU DON'T MEAN, JANET!
"SKINNY AS A TWIG" JANET?
- YOU SWEET THING!
HOW LUCKY ARE YOU
TO STILL BE SO YOUNG?
AND TO HAVE USED
THOSE GOOD LOOKS
TO GET HITCHED TO
SUCH A PRETTY GIRL.
- HITCHED?
UH, HOLD IT, JANET.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
- OH, YOU DON'T HAVE TO PUT
ON A BIG SHOW FOR ME, CARRIS.
YOUR DADDY IS
BEING SHY, ISN'T HE?
- DID YOU SAY "DADDY"?
- Janet: UH-HUH.
- ( both gasp )
- SHE IS JUST ADORABLE!
WHO DOES SHE FAVOR?
- IS UPSTAIRS OPEN?
- Carmichael: SO, WE'RE LOOKING
UP INFO ON SARA, RIGHT?
THEN SHOULDN'T WE BE DOING
THIS FROM A MILITARY FACILITY?
- I DON'T LIKE HOW STRICT
EVERYTHING IS THERE.
ALL THOSE RESTRICTIONS
AND PROCEDURES.
YES, WE'RE IN!
NOW THEN, THIS IS WHERE
THE GOOD STUFF STARTS.
- WOW, THIS IS ALL
SARA'S BIO-DATA?
- I'M CHECKING IT
AGAINST THE DATA
OF HUNDREDS OF BILLIONS OF
PEOPLE ON JOINT HQ RECORDS.
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY TO
NARROW DOWN HER REAL IDENTITY.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, AGAIN.
BUT THAT COULD TAKE FOREVER.
- Janet: HERE YOU GO!
- HEY THERE, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- AND TELL US.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE?
- ( both chuckle )
- Sara: SHE MUST BE LOST.
- Carris: WE'LL TAKE HER TO
THE ADMINISTRATION BUREAU
AFTER WE FINISH EATING.
- ( whimpers )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- HERE. DRINK THIS!
- ( breathing rapidly )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
HEY, WAIT!
LOOK OUT!
- SARA, DON'T!
- ( honking )
- ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
YOU'RE NOT HURT, ARE YOU?
- ( chuckles ) I'M OKAY.
- I WANT YOU TO PROMISE ME
YOU WON'T RUN OFF ANYMORE.
- THAT WAS CLOSE!
ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
- YEAH.
( gasps )
WAIT UP!
- ( both laughing )
- OH, MAN.
WHERE SHOULD WE EVEN BEGIN?
- Lavinia: THERE ARE EIGHT
PLACES JUST ON THIS FLOOR!
- COME IN, ERMY!
WHAT'S HAPPENING ON YOUR END?
- NO LUCK. WE'RE ON OUR
WAY TO THE NEXT STATION.
- Lottie: DICKON?
- YEAH, I GOT NOTHIN' HERE.
NONE OF THE DOLLS I'VE
SEEN LOOK LIKE EMILY.
- Carris: UH-HUH.
SURE, OKAY.
YEAH, THANKS, JUST KEEP AT IT.
IT SEEMS. IT'S GOING TO TAKE
DONNY A LITTLE MORE TIME.
- I SEE.
- HEY, CHEER UP!
THEY'VE REALLY NARROWED DOWN
THE PLACES SHE COULD BE,
AND LOTTIE AND THE OTHERS
ARE ON THEIR WAY HERE NOW.
WOW, SHE REALLY SEEMS
SO INNOCENT, DOESN'T SHE?
- YES, SHE DOES.
- YOU HAVEN'T HAD
THE EASIEST DAY.
- MAYBE. BUT YOURS
WAS CRAZY, TOO.
- YOU KNOW, I MANAGED TO
HAVE A PRETTY GOOD TIME.
- WELL, I THINK YOU'LL
MAKE A GOOD DAD SOMEDAY.
- YOU THINK SO?
YOU'LL MAKE A GREAT MOM.
I MEAN...
DEGAUSSING.
YOU SEE, MAGNETIC
ENERGY HAS ALWAYS
BUILT UP EASILY IN THIS CITY.
IF IT'S NOT CHECKED,
IT'LL TURN ELECTRONICS
INTO USELESS JUNK. LOOK!
WAIT FOR IT.
THEY EXPEL THE BUILT-UP
MAGNETIC ENERGY
EVERY 24 HOURS BY DOING THAT.
OH, ALMOST FORGOT.
I PICKED SOMETHING UP.
- IT'S A LITTLE
PRESENT FOR EMILY.
- FOR EMILY?
- YEAH. IT'S JUST A NEW DRESS.
SHE MIGHT BE DIRTY FROM
ALL OF THE GARBAGE
AND I THOUGHT SHE COULD
USE A SET OF NEW CLOTHES.
- THANKS, CARRIS.
BUT WHY?
WHY IS EVERYONE...
WHY DOES EVERYONE KEEP
LOOKING OUT FOR ME?
IT'S NICE BUT, I GUESS I
JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- IT'S BECAUSE WE'RE FRIENDS,
AREN'T WE SARA?
- BUT, I...
- DO ME A FAVOR?
QUIT TALKING ABOUT YOURSELF
LIKE YOU DON'T DESERVE
GOOD THINGS.
THE TRUTH IS,
EVERY TIME I SAW YOU
SITTING OFF BY
YOURSELF SOMEPLACE,
I ALWAYS WISHED THERE WAS
SOMETHING I COULD DO FOR YOU,
TO MAKE THINGS BETTER.
I HOPE WE HAVEN'T BOTHERED
YOU OR ANYTHING.
- NO, YOU HAVEN'T, NOT AT ALL.
- ( chuckles ) THAT'S GOOD.
SARA.
- ( watch device beeps )
- DAMMIT, DONNY,
YOU HAVE CRAPPY TIMING.
YEAH, IT'S ME.
UH, WHAT?
- ( gasps )
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
THE DEGAUSSING HASN'T
ENDED HERE YET!
- OH, SO YOU'RE AWAKE!
WHAT'S BOTHERING YOU?
WHAT IS IT THIS TIME, HUH?
DID YOU DISCOVER
SOMETHING OVER THERE?
WAIT.
- SECTION S-THIRTY-FIVE-B?
AH! YEAH YOU MEAN THE ONE WITH
THE WEIRD-SHAPED NEON LIGHT?
THAT'S GREAT. SARA!
- SARA?
- Radofrics: HOLD ON, CARRIS,
YOU NEED TO STAY AWAY
FROM THERE FOR NOW.
WE'VE JUST RECEIVED
AN ODD REPORT.
IT'S SHOWING THAT
SOMETHING HAS HAPPENED
IN THE OUTER WALL OVER THERE.
- HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN
SOMETHING'S HAPPENED?
- NOT SURE, JUST BE CAREFUL.
I'LL CALL AGAIN SOON
AS I CAN. BYE.
- HEY, DONNY!
- ( watch device beeps )
- WHAT? ORDERS TO GET BACK
TO THE SHIP?
- ( siren buzzing )
- AN UNREGISTERED UNIT?
- THE LOCAL GARRISON
HAS REQUESTED,
THAT WE SEND STRAINS
OUT TO CONDUCT RECON.
I'VE ISSUED ORDERS FOR
ALL CADETS IN THE CITY,
TO RETURN TO THE SHIP.
THEY'VE ALREADY DISPERSED ALL OF
THEIR AVAILABLE MANPOWER
TO PATROL THE PORTS.
SO, CONSIDERING THE FACT
THAT WE'RE THE CLOSEST,
- WE GET TO DO THE DIRTY WORK.
- AFFIRMATIVE.
- UGH. YOU'RE USELESS!
I TOLD YOU NOT TO TAKE
YOUR EYES OFF HER!
- UH, SORRY.
- OKAY, HE SAID S-THIRTY-FIVE-B.
THEN I'LL HEAD OVER
THAT WAY NOW.
YOU GUYS GET BACK TO THE SHIP
AND GET READY TO MOVE OUT.
- JESSIE, YOU'RE IN
CHARGE, UNDERSTOOD?
- YES, MA'AM.
- LET ME GO.
- DON'T BE AN IDIOT!
WE CAN'T SPLIT UP
OUR TEAM ANY FURTHER!
- LET'S GO.
COME ON, CARRIS.
- YEAH. YEAH!
HEY, JESSIE!
THIS IS MY HOMETOWN,
- IF YOU'LL FOLLOW ME,
I KNOW A SHORT CUT!
- OKAY!
- ( panting )
- A WASTE COLLECTION POINT?
WHY WOULD SHE COME
TO A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- JUST A LITTLE BIT MORE.
- IT REALLY DID TAKE FOREVER.
AND MELCHI, WHAT ABOUT
GETTING BACK TO THE SHIP?
- IT'S PROBABLY NO BIG DEAL.
BESIDES, I'M ALMOST DONE.
- Martha: WHERE'S LAVINIA?
- Ermy: SHE'S WITH LOTTIE.
SHE SAID THEY WERE GOING
WITH SARA TO LOOK FOR EMILY.
- MAN, I SHOULD BE DOWN
THERE WITH THEM HELPING!
- WHOA NOW, ARE YOU WORRIED?
DOESN'T A TORTURED BOY IN LOVE
JUST TUG ON THE HEARTSTRINGS?
- YEAH. I AM WORRIED!
SO SHUT IT!
- THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH
WITH THE CHIT CHAT,
THIS IS THE SITUATION WE HAVE.
THE SIGNAL OF AN
UNIDENTIFIED UNIT
WAS LOST NEAR SECTOR
S-THIRTY-FIVE-B.
- BUT, THAT'S...
- Dufarge:
THE RECENT DEGAUSSING HAS
JAMMED THE VARIOUS
SENSORS OUT THERE,
SO, EXERCISE
EXTREME CAUTION.
- WE'RE OUT HERE
FOR RECONNAISSANCE.
DON'T GET ANY CLOSER
THAN NECESSARY!
EVERYBODY GOT THAT?
- WHERE DID SHE GO?
- ( gasps )
- THERE SHE IS!
- ( gasping )
( gasps )
SARA!
( chuckles )
- EMILY?
EMILY!
THANK GOODNESS.
THANK GOODNESS!
( sobbing )
- ( digital beeping )
- THAT'S THE TENTH REMINDER
TO RETURN TO THE SHIP!
- FORGET THAT! THIS IS
MUCH MORE IMPORTANT.
- ( computer beeps )
- HERE WE GO.
- YOU'RE SAFE NOW, EMILY.
I'M SO SORRY,
I LEFT YOU ALL ALONE.
- OH, THAT'S OKAY.
SEE, I ALWAYS KNEW YOU'D
FIND ME AGAIN SOMEDAY, SARA.
IT WAS SO DARK
FOR A LONG TIME,
AND NO ONE WAS THERE.
I WAS SCARED,
AND COLD, AND LONELY.
BUT THEN, YOU CAME AND
FOUND ME IN THE DARK, SARA.
AND THAT'S ALSO WHEN
YOU GAVE ME A NEW NAME,
AND YOU TALKED TO ME EVERYDAY,
SO, I WASN'T LONELY ANYMORE.
- I DON'T... WHAT ARE YOU
SAYING? WHO ARE YOU?
- EMILY.
MY NAME IS EMILY.
SARA. SARA WEREC.
- Jessie: WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
BE CAREFUL, EVERYONE!
CARRIS!
- LOOK, SARA MIGHT
STILL BE SOMEWHERE
IN THE VICINITY, JESSIE!
I CAN'T HANG BACK, UNDERSTAND?
FOUND 'EM!
I'VE LOCATED TUMORS!
THEY MIGHT BE THE
UNIDENTIFIED UNITS.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT SARA.
- LET'S TAKE CARE
OF THIS, DICKON.
- Jessie: WAIT!
- BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- EMILY IS...
- THIS GIRL IS ME.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR
HER FOR A LONG TIME.
I MISSED HER.
IT WAS SO LONELY.
FOR HER, AND FOR ME.
BUT YOU WERE ALWAYS
SO NICE TO ME,
SO, I CAME TO SEE YOU.
BUT HOW CAN YOU, BE HER?
- Ralph: EMILY.
- ( gasps )
- Sara: IT CAN'T BE!
- Carris: LET'S JUST DRAW
THEM OUT OF HERE FOR NOW.
- Dickon: ROGER THAT!
- THAT'S IT, BOYS.
JUST KEEP FOLLOWING ME.
WHAT IS THAT?
A HOLE?
CRAP, THEY'RE FALLING
INTO THAT THING!
- ( screams )
- WHAT THE HELL IS GOING
ON IN THIS DAMN PLACE?
WHERE'S SARA?
- ( metallic creaking )
- BROTHER.
BUT HOW?
SHE'S THAT GIRL!
RALPH, WAIT!
TELL ME WHAT IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
ANSWER ME!
- DO NOT INTERFERE.
FORGET ABOUT ME.
AND FORGET ABOUT
THIS LITTLE GIRL.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE DECIDED TO DO,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES.
YOU CAN'T STOP ME!
- ( gasps ) THE GLOIRE!
- THAT'S RALPH WEREC'S!
WHY'S HE HERE?
- I'LL SHOW NO MERCY
TO ANYONE IN MY WAY.
NOT EVEN TO YOU,
MY OWN SISTER.
- NO. STOP!
ANSWER ME!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
WAIT!
PLEASE, WAIT!
BROTHER!
- WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
WHAT THE HELL DID
YOU JUST SAY, SARA?
- THERE, I THINK THAT
IS MOST OF THEM.
- YEAH, BUT I'M
STILL WORRIED ABOUT
THAT HOLE WE SAW DOWN THERE.
- YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
- Jessie: NOT TOO CLOSE
CARRIS, THAT'S AN ORDER!
- SORRY, JESSIE, BUT I'VE
GOT TO CHECK IT OUT!
WHAT THE...
- CARRIS!
- Martha: DICKON!
COME IN, ARE YOU ALIVE?
- Ermy: JESSIE! JESSIE!
CARRIS... CARRIS IS DEAD.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU FIND THE UNIT?
WHY DID WE LOSE CARRIS'
SIGNAL? SQUADRON REPORT!
- ( siren wailing )
- ANSWER ME. SARA.
WHAT DID YOU MEAN WHEN YOU SAID
THAT TRAITOR RALPH
WEREC IS YOUR BROTHER?
IS IT TRUE?
ANSWER ME!
- ( closing theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sara: HER HEART SEETHES
WITH DESIRES OF REVENGE.
A BLOODTHIRSTY GUN BARREL
IS POISED.
ON THE NEXT STRAIN,
"LIKE LOOKING AT MYSELF."
I CAN'T DIE.