- DAMN, LOOK AT THAT GIRL GO.
SHE RUNS LIKE A CHEETAH.
- SARA.
- THE SHRIMP HERE IS JUST
AS GOOD AS IT IS BACK HOME.
- I AGREE, ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY
BATTER IT AND DEEP FRY IT.
- IT'S TOO FATTY.
- Lavinia: SARA CRUZ.
SHE'S ONLY BEEN IN THE
SPATIAL ARMOR DIVISION
FOR A FEW WEEKS NOW
AND SHE'S ALREADY
THE CENTER OF ATTENTION.
- WE'LL SEE YOU SOON GUYS.
- LATER ON.
- YEAH, WE'LL SEE YOU AT CLASS.
- BYE BYE, SARA!
- BYE, LAVINIA.
- ( giggles )
SHE SPOKE TO ME!
( happy gasp )
OH, SWEET SARA!
I SAW THE WAY YOU
WERE GAZING AT ME
WITH THOSE BEAUTIFUL
BRIGHT BLUE EYES OF YOURS.
I THINK I'M IN LOVE!
( giggles )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Purple haired operator guy:
TEN SECONDS UNTIL
FULL DECELERATION IS COMPLETE.
EIGHT. SEVEN.
SIX. FIVE.
FOUR. THREE.
TWO. ONE.
- ( beeps )
- Purple haired operator guy:
SUB-LIGHT SPEED TERMINATED.
- Female operator:
TIME SYNCHRONIZATION COMPLETE.
- TRANSMIT THE MESSAGE NOW
TO THE GALL SPACE SUPPLY DEPOT.
- YES, SIR.
- WE CAN FINALLY
CATCH OUR BREATHS.
- BUT WE DON'T KNOW
THE ENEMY'S OBJECTIVES.
WE SHOULD KEEP THE CREW ON
GUARD AND EXPECT THE WORST,
JUST TO BE SAFE, SIR.
- SO YOU THINK
THEY'LL FOLLOW US, HUH?
- I DO.
- Male enemy operator:
WE'VE JUST JUMPED OUT OF
SUB-LIGHTSPEED.
- Female enemy operator:
ENEMY VESSEL AHEAD.
- RIGHT ON COURSE.
GOOD.
- SHOULD WE PURSUE,
CAPTAIN MEDLOCK?
- WE'LL PROCEED
ACCORDING TO PLAN.
- ARE YOU SURE THAT IS
THE RIGHT APPROACH TO TAKE?
- YOU HAVE YOUR ORDERS, BARROW.
SO DO YOUR DUTY
AND EXECUTE THEM, NOW.
- CONTINUE PURSUING
THE ENEMY VESSEL
ON OUR PRESENT COURSE
AT COMBAT SPEED TWO.
- Male enemy operator:
UNDERSTOOD.
- Ralph: EMILY. GO BACK
TO YOUR ROOM NOW.
- ( keys beeping )
- ( gasps )
- ( alarm buzzes )
- Female computer voice:
ID AUTHENTICATION FAILED.
ADMITTANCE TO THIS WING
IS FORBIDDEN.
- YOU DO UNDERSTAND, RIGHT?
TIME'S WORKING AGAINST US.
WE'LL NEED TO STRIKE
WITH NO HESITATION
ONCE THE SHIP LEAVES PORT.
OH, RALPH.
RALPH.
- ( alarm buzzes )
- Female computer voice:
ID AUTHENTICATION FAILED.
ADMITTANCE TO THIS WING
IS FORBIDDEN.
- ( alarm buzzes )
- I'M BORED.
- ( rapid beeping )
- ALRIGHT. LOOKING GOOD.
BRING IN THE DOLL.
- HEY, EMILY!
- YOU HAD TO YELL.
- SARA! SORRY TO
KEEP YOU WAITING!
- I TRIED INCREASING ITS
REACTION TIME BY TEN PERCENT.
NOW IT MAY FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
BEING THROWN AROUND A BIT,
BUT DON'T WORRY.
THAT'S PERFECTLY NORMAL.
- ( mechanical whirring )
- Melchi: OKAY,
LET'S BEGIN THE SIMULATION.
START HER UP, CARMICHAEL.
- Carmichael:
BEGINNING SIMULATION.
- READY, EMILY? HERE WE GO.
- ( loud thudding )
- ( coughs )
- SORRY 'BOUT THAT.
- IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
WE SHOULD HAVE THIS FIRE
CONTAINED ANY MINUTE NOW.
- OH, GET REAL!
SARA, YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
WE'LL CALL YOU BACK
WHEN WE'RE READY.
I THINK THIS IS GONNA
TAKE A WHILE TO FIX.
- OKAY. I'M GONNA
HIT THE SHOWERS.
- ( gasps )
OH, YAY! THIS IS PERFECT!
( giggles )
SARA.
- LAVINIA. HI.
- OH MY, WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU SARA? YOU'RE FILTHY.
AND LOOK AT YOU, POOR EMILY,
YOU'RE ALL COVERED IN SMUDGE.
- YEAH, WE HAD
A BIT OF AN ACCIDENT.
WE'RE ACTUALLY HEADING
TO THE SHOWER RIGHT NOW.
- OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
WELL IN THAT CASE,
I'LL TAKE EMILY OFF YOUR HANDS
AND GET HER ALL CLEANED UP
WHILE YOU'RE IN THE SHOWER.
IT'S NO BOTHER, REALLY.
I WOULD LOVE TO
HELP YOU OUT, SARA.
- LAVINIA.
- SARA.
- THANK YOU, LAVINIA.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
- IT WORKED PERFECTLY.
NOW I'LL HAVE
SARA ALL TO MYSELF!
- Lottie: WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU, SARA?
YOU'RE COVERED IN DIRT!
- OH, HEY. WHAT'S GOING ON?
- AND LOOK AT EMILY!
SHE'S ALL DIRTY TOO!
- ( gasps )
- GO TAKE A SHOWER ALREADY!
- BUT WAIT! THAT'S MY JOB!
I ALREADY VOLUNTEERED!
- AND WHILE YOU'RE DOING THAT,
JESSIE WILL TAKE CARE OF EMILY
AND GET HER CLEANED UP FOR YA.
- I WILL?
- BUT...
- IT'S TOTALLY COOL.
JESSIE'S REALLY GOOD WITH
ALL THAT MOTHERING CRAP.
YOU'LL BE IN GOOD HANDS.
- Jessie: GEEZ LOTTIE,
I HAD NO IDEA I
WAS GOOD AT THAT.
- Lottie: STOP THINKING ABOUT
IT. YOU JUST ARE, OKAY?
- Lavinia: WAY TO STEAL
MY THUNDER.
( chuckles )
A MUST HAVE FOR ANY WOMAN.
A CRYSTAL THUMB-TACK!
THEY CAN BE PLACED ANYWHERE
WITH EASE AND THEY'RE INVISIBLE!
( groans )
THERE, THAT OUGHTA DO IT.
IT'S GENIUS!
( chuckles )
- OW!
- SARA, I WILL SAVE YOU!
YOU'RE BLEEDING, YOU POOR THING!
- LAVINIA.
- ( sucks loudly )
GOTCHA ALL PATCHED UP.
( giggles )
- LAVINIA.
YOU'RE AMAZING!
- ( muffled giggling )
AND THEN SARA WILL BE ALL MINE!
THAT'S HER!
( gulps )
- OW!
- YES!
- HEY ARE YOU ALRIGHT, SARA?
OH MY, LOOK YOU'RE BLEEDING!
WE NEED TO GET YOU
TO THE INFIRMARY.
- IT ISN'T THAT BAD.
- BUT WHAT KIND OF A MEDIC
WOULD I BE
IF I CAN'T EVEN ADDRESS A
SIMPLE CUT ON MY PATIENT?
- ( exhales )
OKAY, LET'S GO.
- THANKS, SARA. WE'LL GET YOU
PATCHED UP RIGHT AWAY.
- GREAT.
- ( grunts in frustration )
( screams )
( grunts )
I DON'T DESERVE THIS.
HELLO.
( giggles )
I HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE
BUT TO SHOW YOU HOW CHARMING
I AM UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL!
( giggles )
( grunts )
THERE'S NOTHING TO BE AFRAID OF.
I'LL TAKE REALLY
GOOD CARE OF YOU.
YES! SHE LIKES IT! SARA'S MINE!
- Lottie: I LOVE THAT SHAMPOO!
BEEN USING IT FOR YEARS!
YOU SHOULD TRY SOME, SARA.
YOUR HAIR WILL THANK YOU.
- Sara: IT'S OKAY,
I'M FINE WITH WHAT I USE.
- Lavinia: OH, NO.
( screams )
JESSIE?
- YOU SHOULD AT
LEAST GIVE IT A TRY.
IT'S GOOD TO MIX
THINGS UP NOW AND THEN.
- STOP IT, JESSIE! ENOUGH!
THIS IS A BIG MISUNDERSTANDING.
- LAVINIA.
- LAVINIA. JESSIE. WHAT'S THIS?
- NO! THIS ISN'T WHAT YOU THINK!
IT'S JUST A BIG
MISUNDERSTANDING.
I'M TELLING YOU THE TRUTH!
SARA!
( screams )
( cries )
- LAVINIA, WAIT!
I DON'T WANT TO STOP!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
NOTHING EVER WORKS OUT!
( crying )
WHY ME?
( cries )
- Carris: LAVINIA?
- ( gasps )
( screams )
- I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
IT LOOKS LIKE I HAVE NO OTHER
CHOICE BUT TO SHOW YOU
HOW MUCH OF A CHARMING STUD
I AM UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL!
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
COME AND GET IT!
- NO!
( crying )
- I HAVE RECEIVED WORD
OF A CERTAIN STUDENT
RUNNING AROUND THE HALLS
ACTING STRANGE RECENTLY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
ACTING STRANGE?
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED?
- YOU MEAN THAT.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- I THINK HE'S REFERRING TO
LAVINIA RUNNING
AROUND THE SHIP NAKED.
- HMM? YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
- NO, IT'S TRUE,
I SAW IT MYSELF.
- WHAT A DISGRACE!
SHE'S AN EMBARRASSMENT!
- COMMANDER. I BELIEVE LAVINIA
MAY NOT BE THE ONLY ISSUE.
THE LEVEL OF STRESS IN ALL
THE CADETS IS GROWING RAPIDLY.
- HE MAY HAVE A VALID
POINT HERE, SIR.
THIS ROUTINE MISSION
BECAME A BATTLE.
THEY LOST OVER HALF
OF THEIR FRIENDS,
AND THEY'RE AWARE
OF THE LIKELIHOOD
OF US BEING FOLLOWED
BY THE DEAGUE.
STRESS IS AN ISSUE.
- ON THE FRONT LINES OF WAR,
SURPRISE ATTACKS LIKE THEY WENT
THROUGH HAPPEN ALL OF THE TIME.
THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE FOR
RELIEVING THEIR OWN STRESS.
IT'S PART OF BEING A SOLDIER.
- THEY'RE CADETS,
NOT BATTLE-HARDENED SOLDIERS.
- IN MY OPINION
THIS SHOULDN'T BE OVERLOOKED.
IF THEY'RE GIVEN THE CHANCE TO
LET OFF A LITTLE BIT OF STEAM,
I THINK THIS WILL
ALL WORK ITSELF OUT.
- THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
- Dufarge:
THE SHIP WILL BE DOCKING
AT THE GALL SPACE
SUPPLY DEPOT SHORTLY.
THE ORIGINAL PLAN WAS TO
CONDUCT A TRAINING
EXERCISE ON BOARD THE SHIP
WHILE WE RE-SUPPLIED
AND MADE REPAIRS
BUT WE'VE NOW DECIDED TO CANCEL
ALL TRAINING FOR THE FIRST DAY.
THE TIME IS YOURS.
SHORE LEAVE ON GALL BEGINS
IMMEDIATELY AFTER WE DOCK.
- ( all cheering )
- Martha: THIS IS GONNA RULE!
- ( slurping )
- WE MADE IT!
- Male cadet operator:
THIS IS THE LIBERTAD,
REQUESTING IMMEDIATE
DOCKING FOR RESUPPLY, OVER.
- Male controller: THIS IS
GALL CONTROL, WE CONFIRM THAT.
ENTER PORT THROUGH GATE THREE
AND THEN PROCEED TO DOCK.
- Male cadet operator:
ROGER THAT.
- DIRECTOR RADOFRICS!
THE CONSTRUCTION BUREAU
HAS SENT A COMPLAINT.
THEY'RE SAYING WE CAN'T
USE GATE THREE RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE IT WILL DELAY
THE SENSOR INSTALLATION.
- TELL THEM TO WAIT.
THIS IS A PRIORITY INBOUND AND
IT WAS THE ONLY GATE AVAILABLE.
- Chief controller: THEIR MAIN
BRIDGE IS TOTALLY DESTROYED!
IT'S AMAZING THEY'RE
STILL OPERATIONAL.
- Male controller: IT MUST BE
BEGINNER'S LUCK.
IT'S A TRAINING SHIP
FULL OF CADETS!
- NOW DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID
WHILE YOU'RE ON LEAVE, CADETS.
YOU'RE LUCKY TO BE ALIVE,
SO DON'T LET THE
OPPORTUNITY GO TO WASTE.
- RIGHT. OH, HEY, LOOK!
IT'S THE QUEEN AND HER SUBJECTS!
- WE WERE JUST ABOUT TO LEAVE.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO JOIN US, GUYS?
- I'D LOVE TO,
BUT FORTUNATELY FOR ME,
THE LADIES OF GALL
ARE WAITING, SO...
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
- IS SARA...
- SHE TOLD ME SHE WAS
GONNA STAY ON THE SHIP.
YOU KNOW I'M MAKING AN ATTEMPT
TO INCLUDE YOU IN THE GROUP.
FINE, SUIT YOURSELF.
- BYE, SARA.
- SHE SAID SHE NEEDED SOME ALONE
TIME TO FOCUS ON HER TRAINING.
- SHE WORKS HARD.
- LET'S GO.
- Dickon: THAT SUCKS, CARRIS.
- Carris: ENOUGH ALREADY!
- YAY FOR ME!
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE ALL READY TO GO.
JUST GET BACK HERE
ON TIME, ALRIGHT?
- WAIT, LAVINIA'S NOT HERE.
- WHERE'D SHE GO?
- I WOULDN'T BE THE
LEAST BIT SURPRISED
IF SHE WANTED SOME
TIME TO HERSELF.
IT SEEMS HER THREE NAKED
LAPS AROUND THE SHIP
HAVE TAKEN HER CONFIDENCE AND
THROWN IT OUT OF THE AIRLOCK.
- YEAH, SHE WAS
PRETTY EMBARRASSED.
- I GUESS ONLY ONE LAP WASN'T
ENOUGH TO SATISFY HER LIBIDO.
- SHE'S PROBABLY
ITCHING FOR MORE!
( chuckles )
- THREE LAPS?
I THOUGHT IT WAS ONE.
I GUESS THE CADETS ARE
MORE STRESSED THAN I THOUGHT.
- I'VE SET IT UP SO
EVERY SIMULATION MODE
CAN BE CONTROLLED
FROM INSIDE THE COCKPIT.
YOU DO HAVE CONTINUAL OPERATION,
BUT I RECOMMEND A FIFTEEN
MINUTE REST EVERY HOUR.
- YOU KNOW THERE'S NO SHAME IN
TAKING A BREAK EVERY
NOW AND THEN, 'KAY?
- HURRY UP, CARMICHAEL.
OLD BEN IS NOTORIOUS
FOR CLOSING UP SHOP
WITH NO NOTICE
WHILE WE'RE DOCKED.
- GOOD LUCK, SARA!
( giggles )
- ( gasps )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( water flowing )
- Barrow: WHO JUST LEFT?
- Male enemy operator:
RALPH WEREC, SIR.
- SO HE'S GOING ROGUE AGAIN?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL
CAPTAIN MEDLOCK WAS THINKING
WHEN SHE AUTHORIZED
HIS LEVEL E ID.
- Medlock: IS THERE
A PROBLEM HERE?
- NO, I WASN'T REFERRING
TO YOU, CAPTAIN.
( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WHO'S IN THE TRANSPORT?
- OKAY. WE'LL BE
TOGETHER SOON, SARA!
- ( exhales )
I'M GOING TO TAKE A
QUICK BREAK, EMILY.
- SO YOU MUST BE
THE BEST FRIEND OF SARA'S
THAT'S BEEN MONOPOLIZING
ALL OF HER SPARE TIME!
IT WOULD BE A SHAME
IF YOU SUDDENLY WENT MISSING!
( giggles )
- ( crying ) WHERE ARE YOU,
POOR EMILY?
I MISS YOU SO MUCH!
- I AM SO SORRY!
DON'T YOU CRY, DARLING.
I'LL HELP YOU FIND HER,
OKAY BABY?
GREAT!
HEY, LOOK WHO I FOUND, SARA!
HERE YOU GO!
- THANKS, LAVINIA.
YOU ARE SO AMAZING.
- AFTER THIS THERE'S NO WAY
SHE CAN RESIST ME!
( giggles )
SIT TIGHT, OKAY?
I'LL BE BACK TO GET YOU ONCE
I WIN OVER MY TRUE LOVE, SARA!
LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA!
- EMILY?
EMILY!
- SHE'S WORRIED AND VULNERABLE.
LIKE I PLANNED.
TIME TO SAVE SARA. HERE GOES.
- EMILY, WHERE ARE YOU?
- SARA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU OKAY?
- LAVINIA.
HAVE YOU SEEN EMILY?
THE GIRL I...
THE MIMIC THAT I USE.
SHE'S MISSING!
- THAT'S TERRIBLE, SARA.
LET ME HELP YOU FIND HER.
- SHE'S THE ONLY THING
I HAVE LEFT.
I CAN'T LOSE HER,
NO MATTER WHAT.
WHERE IS SHE?
THAT GIRL IS MY ONLY HOPE!
- SARA.
YOU'RE IN LUCK.
I THINK I KNOW WHERE SHE MAY BE!
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT THIS, SARA.
I NEVER MEANT TO MAKE YOU
WORRY LIKE THIS.
- ( both panting )
- YOU SEE? THERE!
( gasps )
WHAT THE CRAP?
I'M POSITIVE I PUT HER RIGHT
UP THERE JUST A MINUTE AGO!
- EMILY WAS HERE?
WHAT WOULD YOU
BRING HER IN HERE FOR?
( gasps )
- I'M SORRY.
- MAYBE SHE COULD HAVE...
OH, NO!
- WHAT IS IT?
- ( grunts )
WHERE'S THE TRASH?
- THEY JUST HAULED IT
OUT OF HERE A FEW MINUTES AGO.
- SARA! I ACTED
ON A SUDDEN IMPULSE!
I FIGURED YOU'D
BE BORED TRAINING
WHILE EVERYONE'S ON LEAVE!
- ( closing theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sara: WHERE COULD EMILY BE?
DURING MY SEARCH, A STRANGE
LITTLE GIRL APPEARS BEFORE ME.
ON THE NEXT STRAIN,
"GALL SPACE SUPPLY DEPOT."
WHO ARE YOU, ANYWAY?