- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- I MEAN LOOK AT THIS
PILE YOU'RE DRIVING.
SURE IT'S AN EIGHT-SIX
BUT IT'S NOTHING SPECIAL.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN BOTHER
TO PUT NEW TIRES ON.
- ( laughing ) OH, MAN,
THAT IS FREAKIN HYSTERICAL!
YOU GOTTA BE PRETTY HARD
UP TO BE DRIVING AN
EIGHT-FIVE NOWADAYS!
- IT'S PERFECT FOR YOU, KID.
SUITS YOUR PERSONALITY.
- CAREFUL ON YOUR WAY BACK DOWN.
DON'T WANNA GET YOUR ASS
HANDED TO YOU BY A SCOOTER.
- THAT'S ENOUGH. NOW I'M GONNA
MAKE THOSE JERKS PAY. LET'S GO!
- ( Itsuki yelling )
- TAKUMI, WAIT!
I CAN'T HANDLE THIS!
DON'T YOU DO THIS, THIS IS
MY NEW CAR, YOU JERK!
SLOW DOWN, MAN.
IT'S NOT WORTH IT!
HEY, ARE YOU LISTENING?
TAKUMI!
HIT THE FREAKING BRAKES!
NO!
- ( tires screeching )
- YOU NAILED THAT CORNER!
- ( laughing )
- WHAT THE HELL?
THAT CAR BACK THERE IS FLYING UP
ON OUR TAIL PRETTY FAST, MAN.
- MUST BE ANOTHER AKINA LOSER.
YOU PICKED THE WRONG GUY
TO SCREW WITH TONIGHT.
TOO BAD FOR YOU, PAL.
- ( car honking )
- HUH?
I GOTCHA. YOU WANNA PLAY
A COUPLE ROUNDS, HUH?
- DUDE, STOP THE CAR! TAKUMI!
PLEASE. I DON'T WANNA DIE!
WHY WON'T YOU STOP? TAKUMI!
( Itsuki screaming )
UNBELIEVABLE. IS THIS ACTUALLY
MY PIECE OF CRAP EIGHT-FIVE?
- DAMN!
- I GOTTA BE HONEST WITH YOU,
MAN. THIS SUCKER IS GOOD.
HOLD UP A SEC. DUDE,
ISN'T THAT THE EIGHT-FIVE?
THE SAME ONE WE SAW
BACK AT THE TOP?
- NO WAY AN EIGHT-FIVE COULD
KEEP UP WITH THESE WHEELS.
GOTTA BE SOMEBODY ELSE
MESSING WITH US.
IT IS THEM! HOW THE HELL DID
THEY CATCH UP TO US, MAN?
- THOSE LITTLE RAT-BAGS LIED
RIGHT TO OUR FACES!
THAT THING'S NOT WHAT THEY SAID!
IT'S GOTTA BE AN EIGHT-SIX!
- ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
WHAT THE... IT'S NOT WANTING TO
ACCELERATE DOWN THE HILL AT ALL.
THAT'S WEIRD.
AND THESE WHEELS,
THEY'RE NOT BALD,
BUT THEY'RE NOT GRIPPING,
EITHER. WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
- ( screaming )
- DAMN! HE'S SO FAST!
ARE YOU SEEING THIS GUY, DUDE?
- ITSUKI SURE HAS A SLOW ONE
ON HIS HANDS.
OKAY. I GUESS IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO PULL OUT MY OLD STANDBY MOVE.
♪ DON'T LET ME GO AGAIN ♪
♪ BABY I WANT YOU ♪
♪ NIGHT FEVER NIGHT FEVER ♪
♪ DISCO IN TOWN IS ON FIRE ♪
♪ NIGHT FEVER HI-FEVER ♪
♪ BURNING WITH ME
'CAUSE THE NIGHT'S ON FIRE ♪
♪ NIGHT FEVER NIGHT FEVER ♪
♪ DISCO IN TOWN IS ON FIRE ♪
- TRY WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU AIN'T PASSING ME, JERKWAD.
WHAT?
♪ NIGHT FEVER NIGHT FEVER ♪
WHAT IN THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?
HOW DID HE DO THAT?
THAT RIDE IS NOT AN EIGHT-FIVE.
THAT MUCH IS OBVIOUS.
HE MUST BE DRIVING AN EIGHT-SIX.
A WELL-TUNED EIGHT-SIX AT THAT.
THERE'S NO OTHER EXPLANATION!
BUT, CHECK OUT THAT ROLL.
AN EIGHT-SIX WOULDN'T DO THAT.
MAYBE IT WAS AN EIGHT-FIVE.
MAYBE. I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
♪ HERE WE GO HERE WE GO ♪
♪ NIGHT FEVER NIGHT ♪
HE BLEW THROUGH US
LIKE WE WERE A FOG BANK.
- THAT EIGHT-FIVE WAS FAST.
TOO FAST.
- MAYBE IT WAS A...
- ( Itsuki screaming )
- A GHOST!
- Takumi: YOU WANT SOME COFFEE?
IT'S ON ME.
- Itsuki: YEAH, SURE.
- HERE YOU GO.
- THANKS.
SO, IKETANI WAS
TELLING ME ABOUT
HOW YOUR DOWNHILL SKILLS
WERE KIND OF...
WELL, HE TOLD ME YOU WERE SOME
KIND OF FREAK OF NATURE, DUDE.
- A FREAK, HUH. WOW,
I SURE HOPE HE MEANT
THAT AS A COMPLIMENT.
- 'COURSE HE DID AND HE'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE TOO CLOSE.
CAN'T SEE THE FOREST
FOR THE TREES.
( laughs ) I NEVER THOUGHT
A CAR COULD RUN LIKE THAT.
IN THE PAST HOUR,
YOU COMPLETELY CHANGED
MY WHOLE PERSPECTIVE ON RACING.
IT WAS SCARY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I EXPECTED,
BUT IT WASN'T THAT.
- WELL, SORRY IT SCARED YOU.
I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN FOR IT TO.
- NO, IT'S COOL.
YOU KNOW, I HONESTLY DON'T THINK
I'VE EVER BEEN THIS
HAPPY BEFORE.
- HUH?
- I JUST REALIZED THAT IT'S
NOT ABOUT WHAT MY CAR CAN DO.
NOT ENTIRELY, ANYWAY. IF THE
DRIVER HAS WHAT IT TAKES,
THEN, MAN, HE CAN BRING OUT
THE BEST IN HIS RIDE,
LIKE YOU BEHIND THE WHEEL
OF MY EIGHT-FIVE.
I FELL IN LOVE
WITH MY CAR TONIGHT.
I'M GONNA TAKE
REALLY GOOD CARE OF HER.
AND FIRST THING TOMORROW,
I'M GONNA START TRAINING,
HARDER THAN YOU'VE
EVER SEEN ANYONE HIT IT!
LET PEOPLE LAUGH. IT DOESN'T
BOTHER ME ONE LITTLE BIT.
I'LL BE AWESOME SOMEDAY. WITH
HARD WORK AND MY EIGHT-FIVE!
HEY, HOW ABOUT THE NEXT TIME
WE GO OUT FOR A DRIVE,
WE GRAB A COUPLE HOT BABES
TO COME WITH US!
- SURE.
- AND NO BLOWING ME OFF
THIS TIME, TAKUMI, EH?
YOU HEAR WHAT I'M SAYING?
- I HEAR YOU, MAN. I HEAR YOU.
- OKAY.
THE OCEAN, THE CHICKS, THOSE
HOT BIKINIS. I CAN'T WAIT!
- YEAH!
JUST LOOK AT HER.
MY BEAUTIFUL S-THIRTEEN.
BACK IN MY LOVING ARMS
AND LOOKING AS SWEET AS
THE DAY I BROUGHT HER HOME
FROM THE DEALERSHIP.
I THINK I MIGHT SHED A TEAR.
MAYBE TWO.
- ITSUKI, YOU MANIAC!
YOU TRYING TO RUN ME OVER!
- WE'RE GONNA START
TRAINING AGAIN TODAY, BABY.
PRACTICE DRIFTING ON SOME
LOWER GRADE TIRES
TO GO EASY ON YOUR NEW BOD.
- Itsuki: YOU CAN
COUNT ME IN, TOO.
SEE? CHECK OUT
MY TOTALLY SWEET STICKER!
- ( grunting )
- CUT IT OUT.
YOU SAID I COULD JOIN.
- YEAH, SURE.
I GUESS I DID, HUH.
- SWEET! I'M OFFICIALLY A
MEMBER OF THE SPEED STARS.
AND YOU CAN'T DO
ANYTHING ABOUT IT!
OH, YEAH. I SHOULD
PROBABLY START PRACTICING
BEFORE I FORGET
ALL THOSE KILLER MOVES
TAKUMI SHOWED ME LAST NIGHT.
- Both: WHOA, WHAT? YOU RODE
WITH HIM? IN THE EIGHT-SIX?
- THAT'S RIGHT,
I RODE WITH HIM.
( chuckling ) EXCEPT THAT
WE WEREN'T IN THE EIGHT-SIX.
- WHAT'RE YOU LAUGHING ABOUT?
YOU KNOW SOMETHING WE DON'T?
- Iketani: YEAH,
FESS UP. WHAT IS IT?
- Itsuki: I'LL NEVER TELL!
- Iketani: THEN YOU'RE DRINKING
HIGH OCTANE FOR LUNCH.
- Itsuki: OKAY, OKAY
I'LL TELL YOU. GEEZ!
CHECK IT, I RODE SHOTGUN WHILE
TAKUMI DROVE MY EIGHT-FIVE
ON THE AKINA
DOWNHILL LAST NIGHT.
IT BLEW MY MIND THROUGH
THE BACK OF MY SKULL.
MAN! I'VE NEVER SEEN
DRIVING LIKE THAT.
IT WAS LIKE WATCHING
A MAGIC SHOW!
BEFORE WE EVEN HIT THE CORNERS
WE WERE DRIFTING SIDEWAYS.
ALL I COULD SEE WAS THE
MOUNTAIN BLURRING BY ME
IN THE WINDSHIELD.
IT WAS THE COOLEST EVER.
YOU GUYS TOTALLY MISSED OUT.
FEEL REAL BAD FOR YOU.
- TAKUMI WAS OUT THERE
DRIFTING IN YOUR EIGHT-FIVE,
WITHOUT A LIMITED
SLIP DIFFERENTIAL?
- IT ALL HAPPENED SO FAST
IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
THERE WERE THESE TWO JERKS
THAT WERE MESSING WITH US,
BUT WE PASSED THEM BACK TO
BACK ON THE DOWNHILL HAIRPINS!
I'VE NEVER FELT MORE ALIVE THAN
I DID ON AKINA LAST NIGHT!
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DO YOU BELIEVE HIM OR DO YOU
THINK HE'S FULL OF CRAP?
I KNOW TAKUMI'S GOOD,
BUT COULD HE REALLY DO THAT
WITH AN EIGHT-FIVE?
- IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT ANY DRIVER
COULD DRIFT AN EIGHT-FIVE.
EVEN SOMEBODY
WITH TAKUMI'S SKILLS.
- I KNOW YOU THINK
I'M OUT OF MY GOURD.
BUT I SAW WHAT I SAW.
I MIGHT BE A CAR IDIOT,
BUT I'M NOT BLIND.
- HMM. IF THAT'S THE TRUTH
WE'RE DEALING WITH
SOMETHING ELSE HERE.
AND IT MEANS THAT
TAKUMI'S ADAPT ABILITY
IS FAR BEYOND WHAT I
IMAGINED IT TO BE.
- Iketani: WELL, THE CARS
DON'T LOOK ALL THAT DIFFERENT.
MAYBE SINCE THEY BOTH
GOT THE SAME BODY,
THEY HAVE SIMILAR
MANEUVERABILITY.
- I HIGHLY DOUBT THAT.
BUNTA'S BEEN WORKING
ON THAT EIGHT-SIX OF HIS
SINCE BEFORE YOU WERE BORN.
THE EIGHT-FIVE IS A JOKE
IN COMPARISON.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
YEARS OF IMPROVEMENTS
AND MODIFICATIONS.
- JOKE?
- Iketani: SO YOU'RE SAYING
TAKUMI CAN PRETTY MUCH DRIVE
ANY CAR WE THROW AT HIM.
- Yuuichi: YEAH. AS LONG AS
THEY GOT THE FR LAYOUT.
THAT'S HIS GROOVE.
IT'LL LET HIM PULL OUT
THEIR FULL POTENTIAL.
NOT JUST ANYBODY CAN
DRIVE AN EIGHT-SIX.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE MASTERY
OF THE BASIC DRIVING SKILLS
TO KEEP IT UNDER CONTROL.
BUNTA USED TO HAVE
A SAYING ABOUT IT, IN FACT.
HE SAID "AN EIGHT-SIX
TRAINS THE DRIVER."
- INITIAL D.
- INITIAL D!
- OH, WEIRD.
I MUST BE SEEING THINGS.
OR DID THAT CAR
HAVE A NIGHT KIDS STICKER?
- Man: YEAH. IT'S GOT 'STREET
RACING' WRITTEN ALL OVER IT.
YOU CAN REALLY TELL
A MODIFIED CAR
FROM THE REST OF THE DAY RUNNERS
JUST BY LOOKING
AT HOW IT ROLLS.
- AND THAT ONE'S
DEFINITELY MOD-ED OUT.
- YEAH.
- I NOTICED THAT THOSE
NIGHT KID PUNKS
HAVE BEEN COMING UP
TO AKINA A LOT LATELY.
I SEE THEM LIKE EVERY DAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT'S ALL ABOUT?
- I DON'T KNOW, BUT SINCE THEIR
LEADER GOT HIS ASS HANDED TO HIM
THE OTHER NIGHT,
I SERIOUSLY DOUBT
ANYBODY FROM THEIR TEAM'S
GOING TO WANT TO COME OUT HERE
SCOUTING FOR A REMATCH.
- I GOTTA SAY,
I FEEL BAD FOR HIM.
SINCE TAKESHI LOST
TO THAT EIGHT-SIX
HE CAN'T WALK AROUND LIKE HE'S
THE KING OF THE WORLD ANYMORE.
TOO BAD.
- Waitress: HEY, GUYS.
CAN I HELP YOU?
- YEAH. TWO COFFEES
- SURE.
- YOU KNOW, I HEARD THAT THE GUY
FROM THE SPEED STARS
WHO WAS DRIVING THE EIGHT-SIX
IS SOME PUNK KID
WHO'S STILL IN HIGH SCHOOL.
- I DON'T HAVE A CLUE
HOW GOOD THIS KID IS,
BUT I KNOW THAT WHEN I BEAT HIM,
I'LL BE BETTER THAN TAKESHI.
AND THAT'S ALL I REALLY CARE
ABOUT IN THE WORLD RIGHT NOW.
I'LL BE THE FASTEST NIGHT KID.
HANDS FREAKING DOWN.
- I DON'T KNOW, SHINGO. YEAH,
YOU'RE FAST ON THE DOWNHILL,
BUT I HEARD THIS KID'S
OFF THE CHAIN.
- I KNOW I CAN TAKE HIM
FAIR AND SQUARE,
BUT I'VE GOT A MUCH MORE
INTERESTING IDEA.
SOMETHING TO ENSURE MY VICTORY.
- ( choking )
- YOU'LL SEE WHAT I MEAN.
I'LL GIVE HIM A DOWNHILL
RUN THAT'S SO DANGEROUS
HE WON'T KNOW
WHAT BLEW PAST HIM,
'CAUSE THIS WORLD ONLY NEEDS
ONE DOWNHILL SPECIALIST.
THE EIGHT-SIX? AN OUTDATED
PIECE. TIME TO SEND THAT
THING TO A MERCIFUL
GRAVE IN A NICE SCRAPYARD.
- UH-OH.
I'LL SHOW THEM ALL THAT
SHINGO SHOJI OF THE NIGHT KIDS
IS THE FASTEST
DOWNHILL RACER IN GUNMA.
- ( car approaching )
- Fumihero: SO WHERE'S RYOSUKE?
- WHERE DO YOU THINK?
MY BROTHER'S LOCKED HIMSELF
IN HIS ROOM AGAIN,
STARING AT THAT DUMB ASS
COMPUTER SCREEN OF HIS.
HIS FAVORITE PASTIME.
AS FAR AS I KNOW, HE'S THE ONLY
STREET RACER IN GUNMA
WHO DOES MOST OF HIS TRAINING
IN AN OFFICE CHAIR
IN FRONT OF A COMPUTER.
HEY, I WAS WONDERING... WHAT
DO YOU THINK WOULD HAPPEN
IF MY BROTHER AND AKINA'S
EIGHT-SIX WERE TO RACE.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, MAN?
NO WAY RYOSUKE WOULD
LOSE TO THAT GUY,
YOU KNOW THAT.
RYOSUKE KNOWS EVERYTHING
THERE IS TO KNOW
ABOUT THE EIGHT-SIX BY NOW.
HE'S GOT ALL THE DATA HE NEEDS
TO CREATE A SIMULATION
OF A WINNING RACE IN HIS HEAD.
IF HE CAN JUST APPLY THAT
KNOWLEDGE IN AN ACTUAL RACE,
I CAN'T THINK OF A DRIVER WHO'D
EVEN MAKE HIM BREAK A SWEAT.
SHORT OF THE PROS, ANYWAY.
- I GET IT. NO STREET RACER
KNOWS MORE ABOUT CARS THAN HIM.
I CAN'T IMAGINE HIM LOSING
EITHER, NOT TO ANYONE.
AND CERTAINLY NOT WHEN I THINK
ABOUT THE SKILLS HE'S PACKING.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- BUT I DON'T THINK
THAT THE EIGHT-SIX
IS GONNA LOSE A
RACE EITHER, SO...
- ( tires screeching )
- THAT HIGH-SPEED DRIFTING
IS REALLY SOMETHING SPECIAL.
NOT TO MENTION THE
DUDE'S CRAZY BRAKE CONTROL.
HE MIGHT BE AS GOOD
AS MY BROTHER.
BESIDES, HE'S ANOTHER FR DRIVER.
AND THE WAY THAT EIGHT-SIX
RUNS IS INCREDIBLE.
CAN'T HELP BUT BE IMPRESSED.
- SERIOUSLY?
- IF THEY EVER BATTLE, ONE OF
THEM IS GONNA END UP SECOND.
AND I SURE AS HELL DON'T
WANT IT TO BE MY BROTHER.
BUT I DON'T REALLY WANNA
SEE THE EIGHT-SIX LOSE
ANY MORE THAN RYOSUKE, YOU KNOW.
MAN, I'M TORN ON THIS.
- OH, SORRY!
I'M SUCH A KLUTZ!
HOLD ON A SECOND,
I'LL CLEAN IT UP.
YOU KNOW, I HAD FUN
AT THE BEACH.
WHY DON'T WE GO
SOME PLACE TOGETHER AGAIN?
MAYBE THE MOUNTAINS,
OR THE HIGHLANDS,
OR EVEN THE BEACH AGAIN.
I MEAN WE ARE ON SUMMER
VACATION. COULD BE FUN!
- YEAH.
- WE SHOULD BE LIVING IT UP
AND MAKING NEW MEMORIES.
- YEAH, WE SHOULD.
- AND TAKUMI,
IF YOU HADN'T FIGURED IT OUT,
I WOULDN'T MIND IF YOU WANTED TO
TAKE ME ON AN OVERNIGHT TRIP.
SO WHEN IS YOUR NEXT DAY OFF?
THIS SUNDAY?
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU WORK
ALL THE TIME.
- TELL ME ABOUT IT. IT JUST
DEPENDS ON WHAT THE BOSS NEEDS.
- DO YOU WANT TO TAKE ME
FOR A DRIVE AGAIN OR NOT?
I JUST FELL IN LOVE
WITH YOUR CAR, SO...
- NO BLOWING ME OFF.
BACK OUT AND YOU CAN KISS
OUR FRIENDSHIP GOODBYE!
- SO, HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
IF MAYBE ITSUKI TAGGED
ALONG WITH US?
- THE THREE OF US?
- WELL, ACTUALLY, IF IT'S
NOT TOO MUCH TROUBLE,
I WAS HOPING YOU COULD
FIND HIM A DATE.
- OH.
- HE'S A GREAT GUY
WHEN YOU GET TO KNOW HIM.
HE'S JUST KIND OF SHY, YOU KNOW?
- I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE
SUCH A CARING FRIEND,
ITSUKI'S LUCKY TO HAVE YOU.
I JUST THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE A STEP
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION FOR HIM.
- THEN I'LL START ASKING AROUND
AND SEE WHICH OF MY FRIENDS
WANTS TO COME.
- YOU'D DO THAT FOR ME?
- ITSUKI'S A REALLY SWEET GUY.
I KNOW PLENTY OF GIRLS WHO WOULD
ENJOY SPENDING TIME WITH HIM.
- ( car brakes screeching )
- Itsuki: THAT WAS KICK ASS!
MAYBE I SHOULD GIVE THAT A SHOT!
- THINK I'M FINALLY
GETTING A GRIP
ON SLIDING THE REAR SIDEWAYS.
YEAH, NOW I'VE GOT THE TIMING
IT'S REALLY COMING TOGETHER.
- YEAH, ALL YOU GOT TO DO
TO START OFF THE DRIFT
IS PULL UP
ON THE EMERGENCY BRAKE.
- I'M PRETTY
SURE THAT'S WRONG.
I WAS WATCHING REAL CLOSE
WHEN I WAS RIDING
ALONG WITH TAKUMI,
AND I DIDN'T SEE HIM TOUCH
THE EMERGENCY BRAKE
THE ENTIRE TRIP, SO...
- 'CAUSE TAKUMI
USES THE FOOT BRAKE.
NOT THE HANDBRAKE
LIKE MOST DRIVERS USE
TO SHIFT THE CARS WEIGHT.
DON'T WORRY, PAL. YOU'RE
A LONG WAY OFF FROM THAT.
- YEAH.
- WE USUALLY BARREL INTO A
CORNER AND THEN ACCELERATE.
THAT SKIDS THE REAR TIRES
BEFORE COMING OUT OF IT...
BUT THAT'S AN ELEMENTARY
TECHNIQUE CALLED POWER SLIDE.
IT'S NOT A TRUE DRIFT.
TAKUMI DRIFTS INTO A CORNER
AND CONTROLS THE SKID
AT THE END TO STABILIZE THE CAR.
THAT'S A TRUE DRIFT.
IT'S THE FASTEST WAY
TO TURN
AND IT LOOKS PRETTY
FREAKING SWEET TOO.
LOT TO BE SAID FOR SHOWMANSHIP.
- WELL, MY MAN.
I SEE YOU'VE DONE A LITTLE BIT
OF STUDYING UP ON THE SUBJECT.
GOT SUPER BORED
WHILE MY S-THIRETEEN
WAS LAYED UP
IN THE CAR HOSPITAL.
SO I DID A LITTLE
EXTRACURRICULAR READING.
- I CAN'T WAIT TO GIVE THAT
SIDE-SPIN A SHOT MYSELF.
- OH, MAN.
THIS IS SO EXCITING!
- I THINK I'M JUST ABOUT READY
FOR THE NEXT STEP
IN THE PROCESS, GENTLEMEN.
INSTEAD OF HITTING IT
IN A STRAIGHT LINE,
I'M GOING TO TRY IT IN
A LOW-SPIN TURN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- GOOD LUCK OUT THERE, IKETANI!
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT, DUDE!
- TRY NOT TO HIT ANY
OTHER CARS OUT THERE!
- WE'LL BE WAITING RIGHT HERE,
SEE YOU WHEN YOU GET BACK!
- ( tires screeching )
- IT'S A HELL OF A THING TO BE
IN TOTAL CONTROL OF YOUR CAR.
CHALLENGING LIKE
I'VE NEVER KNOWN.
MAN, I WISH I COULD BE
MORE LIKE TAKUMI.
I WANNA RIDE WITH HIM
JUST ONE MORE TIME,
THEN I'LL HAVE IT DOWN.
WATCHING HIM DRIVE MY CAR,
IT'LL BE THE BEST WAY
FOR ME TO LEARN THIS STUFF.
AND HONESTLY,
IT'S THE ONLY WAY I KNOW.
- ( low-pitched chuckle )
- CRAP! GOT LOST
IN MY OWN HEAD!
I WASN'T PAYING ATTENTION
TO THE ROAD!
♪ I WANT TO DANCE ♪
WHAT THE HELL?
YOU HIT MY BUMPER.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GOING
TO JUST LET YOU DRIVE OFF
INTO THE MOONLIGHT.
YOU'RE MINE, DUDE.
I DARE YOU TO PASS ME NOW!
♪ I WANT TO DANCE ♪
- ( tires screeching )
♪ DANCING ♪
- ( chuckling continues )
- ( Itsuki yelling )
- SPEED STARS, HUH?
- ( tires screeching )
- ( panting )
- THAT WAS CLOSE.
-WELL, JUST A TINY LITTLE TAP
ON THE BUMPER
RIGHT BEFORE THE TURN
AND THAT'S ALL SHE WROTE
FOR YOU, PAL.
FR'S ARE SO EASY
TO DESTABILIZE.
WHAT A PATHETIC RIDE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
♪ RAGE MY DREAM ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- Natsuki: YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT I WANT RIGHT NOW?
- Announcer: YES.
- TO SPEND MORE TIME
WITH TAKUMI, REALLY.
GO OUT MORE OFTEN, MORE DATING.
JUST MORE TIME AS A COUPLE.
WE ARE ON SUMMER VACATION.
MIGHT AS WELL MAKE
THE MOST OF IT.
BUT HE'S TOO BUSY
WORKING ALL THE TIME.
EVEN WHEN WE ARE TOGETHER,
IT SEEMS LIKE ALL HE DOES
IS STARE OFF INTO THE DISTANCE.
HIS MIND ALWAYS SOMEPLACE ELSE.
- Announcer: WE ARE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME, SO, ANYWAY,
NEXT ON INITIAL D,
"THE FR KILLER."
- Natsuki: ...I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETIMES, I HAVE A TENDENCY
TO OVERTHINK THESE THINGS.
- Announcer: DON'T MISS IT!