- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- I SURE AS HELL AIN'T GONNA
FEEL BAD ABOUT IT.
HEH, THAT EIGHT-SIX'LL
BE A PILE OF JUNK
WHEN I GET THROUGH WITH IT.
- ( tires screeching )
- THAT WAS ON PURPOSE.
NOW I'M PISSED.
I REFUSE TO COME IN SECOND
TO A CHEATING SCUMBAG LIKE YOU.
- ♪ MOVE YOUR BODY ♪
♪ I NEED YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M ON FIRE ♪
♪ AND EVERY TIME I WALK ♪
♪ AND EVERY TIME
I SEE YOUR FACE ♪
♪ IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ I TRY TO BE ALONE ♪
♪ BUT I CANT STOP
MYSELF TODAY ♪
♪ THINK YOU'RE MINE ♪
♪ MOVE YOUR BODY ♪
♪ TO THE END OF TIME ♪
♪ I GO CRAZY ♪
♪ THINKING ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ I NEED YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M ON FIRE ♪
♪ COME ON RUN TO ME ♪
♪ I NEED YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ I'M GETTIN HIGHER AND HIGHER ♪
- WOAH! I DON'T KNOW WHY
BUT I THINK HE JUST
HIT THE GUARDRAIL ON PURPOSE!
AND THEN HE USED THE REBOUND TO
PULL OFF THE REVERSE-DRIFT!
- THAT'S INSANE!
WHAT THE HELL IS HE THINKIN'?
- ♪ I'M GETTING HIGHER
AND HIGHER ♪
♪ GONNA BE SO FREE ♪
♪ I NEED TO FEEL YOUR HEART ♪
♪ I NEED TO SHOW YOU
I'M THE ONE ♪
♪ FOR YOU NOW ♪
♪ I'M GONNA FIND THE WAY ♪
♪ TO TELL YOU
WHAT TO DO MY LOVE ♪
♪ HERE SOMEHOW ♪
- ARE YOU FRIGGIN' KIDDIN' ME?
HE'S ON MY TAIL AGAIN?
HOW IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE!
♪ I NEED YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M ON FIRE ♪
- THAT GUY'S GOT A DEATH WISH!
- THAT PSYCHO DRIVIN' THE
EIGHT-SIX IS LOSING HIS COOL.
- WHEN AN AVERAGE
RACER LOSES HIS COOL
HIS CHANCES AT WINNING ARE GONE.
HE STARTS MAKING MISTAKES.
AND HIS SPEED SUFFERS.
BUT THIS GUY IS DIFFERENT
HIS INNATE DRIVING SKILLS TAKE
OVER ON A SUBCONSCIOUS LEVEL.
ALLOWING HIS EIGHT-SIX
TO PERFORM AT FULL THROTTLE.
THE ANGRIER HE GETS,
THE FASTER HE GOES.
WAY TO GO, SHINGO.
YOU JUST HANDED HIM THE RACE.
- ♪ AND EVERY TIME I WALK ♪
- DAMN IT. MY CAR'S BEEN RUNNING
AT 99% THIS WHOLE RACE,
AND I STILL CAN'T SHAKE HIM.
WHAT THE HELL'S GOIN' ON?
- ♪ MOVE YOUR BODY ♪
♪ I GO CRAZY ♪
♪ THINKING ABOUT YOU ♪
- I'VE GOT THE SWEATS.
I'VE NEVER FELT THIS EDGY
IN A DOWNHILL RACE BEFORE.
♪ I NEED YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ I'M GETTING HIGHER
AND HIGHER ♪
- DUDE'S GLUED TO MY BUMPER!
MY EG-SIX IS THE BEST
IN ITS CLASS,
SO HOW AM I BEING PUSHED AROUND
BY A FRIGGIN' EIGHT-SIX?
IT'S NOT EVEN ABOUT
SPEED ANYMORE.
IT'S MORE THAN THAT NOW.
THAT EIGHT-SIX IS
OUT OF THIS WORLD.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS MAKE
SURE HE DOESN'T PASS ME.
THERE ARE ONLY A FEW HAIRPINS
TO GO BEFORE IT'S OVER.
I JUST GOTTA HOLD HIM OFF
A LITTLE LONGER.
I'M NOT GIVING YOU
THE INSIDE THAT EASY!
OH NO! HE'S NOT GONNA
BUMP ME BACK, IS HE?
CRAP!
I THOUGHT HE WAS GONNA HIT ME!
I WAS SURE OF IT! BUT...
THAT CORNERING! SOMEHOW HE
SLIPPED THROUGH THE INSIDE.
BASTARD PASSED ME.
DAMN IT!
HOW THE HELL DID THIS HAPPEN?
- MAN, I HOPE
TAKUMI'S DOIN' OKAY.
MAYBE WE'RE JUST WASTIN'
OUR TIME WORRYIN' ABOUT HIM.
- HUH?
- HE'S MADE IT THIS FAR
WITHOUT CRASHING.
WHICH MEANS HE'S ALREADY
ADAPTED TO THE SITUATION.
AND KNOWING TAKUMI
HE'S PROBABLY EVEN GOT
A HUGE LEAD ON THE EG-SIX.
- I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND IF THAT'S THE CASE
THAT NIGHT KID'S SWEATIN'.
HE MUST FEEL LIKE A COW
AT A BURGER JOINT.
- YEAH. THAT'S FUNNY. HE MUST
REGRET CHALLENGING TAKUMI.
BIGGEST MISTAKE HE EVER MADE.
- THIS DEATH MATCH WAS MY IDEA.
AND IF I LOSE, I'LL
LOOK LIKE A REAL CHUMP
TO THE REST OF THE TEAM.
AT THIS POINT I NEED
TO PROTECT MY PRIDE,
EVEN IF IT MEANS NEITHER
OF US FINISHES THE RACE.
WE'RE ON THIS STRAIGHTAWAY
FOR ANOTHER MILE OR SO.
SHOULD BE ENOUGH TIME TO
PULL SIDE BY SIDE WITH HIM
SO HE CAN'T ESCAPE.
ONLY ONE SHOT LEFT.
A TWO-CAR COLLISION!
- ♪ I GOT NO IMPRESSION ♪
♪ THIS TOWN
IS MADE BY THE IMITATION ♪
♪ WANTING YOUR SENSATION ♪
♪ IN THIS SILLY SIMULATION ♪
♪ I WANNA RAGE MY DREAM ♪
- AW, MAN. WHO'S IN THE LEAD?
- IT'S GOTTA BE THE EG-SIX.
CRAP! IT'S THE EIGHT-SIX!
- ( singing in Japanese)
- HOLY CRAP, DID HE HAVE
TO COME THAT CLOSE?
- I THINK HE WAS TRYING TO
KILL ME! WHAT THE HELL?
- WOW, DUDE, I GUESS
THE EG-SIX ISN'T COMIN',
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HAPPENED TO SHINGO?
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ DI-DING DANG ANOTHER ROUND ♪
♪ NEVER SLOWDOWN ♪
- MY POOR BABY.
- HEY IS THAT TAKUMI?
- I DON'T THINK SO!
- YO, ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU GOT OFF EASY.
COULD'VE BEEN A LOT WORSE.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, DUDE?
IT'S OKAY, YOU CAN TELL US.
HOP ON IN.
WE CAN GIVE YOU A LIFT.
YOU SHOULD GO TO A HOSPITAL.
I'LL GET YA THERE FASTER
THAN AN AMBULANCE WOULD.
- SORRY. I CAN'T ASK YOU
TO DO THAT.
JUST LET ME MAKE A CALL
WITH YOUR CELL REAL QUICK.
- YOU CAN GIVE UP THE ACT.
WE KNOW YOU'RE HURT.
- WHENEVER WE CRASH WE'RE HERE
TO HELP EACH OTHER OUT.
WE LIVE BY THE RACER'S
CODE, SO LISTEN,
NO HARD FEELIN'S,
ALL RIGHT, MAN?
- THANKS A LOT.
I REALLY OWE YOU GUYS ONE.
YOUR FRIEND'S UNBELIEVABLE.
WHO IS HE, ANYWAY?
I'D NEVER HEARD OF HIM BEFORE.
- ( announcer reading )
- Bunta: TAKUMI? HEY, TAKUMI!
WAKE YOUR SORRY BUTT UP!
I'VE GOT TO TALK TO YOU!
- WHAT ARE YOU YELLING ABOUT?
IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
WHAT'S SO IMPORTANT IT CAN'T
WAIT TILL TOMORROW?
- JUST COME DOWN. MOVE IT!
WOULD YOU MIND
EXPLAINING THIS TO ME?
YOU RACED LAST NIGHT AND YOUR
EMOTIONS GOT THE BEST OF YOU.
I COUNT THREE
SCRATCHES THAT WERE MADE
BY SWIPING THE GUARDRAILS.
- WOULD YOU BELIEVE ME
IF I TOLD YOU I DON'T REMEMBER?
MAYBE YOU DID IT.
- I DIDN'T DRIVE THE DAMN CAR
AT ALL YESTERDAY!
YOU'RE THE ONLY
ONE WHO HAD IT! SEE?
WOULD I HAVE SCRATCHED
THE BUMPER AND FENDERS?
- HUH?
YOU AREN'T KIDDING! WHAT THE?
HOW THE HELL COULD
THIS'VE HAPPENED.
- YOU dTELL ME!
- OW. WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
- GOT SOMETHIN' TO SAY?
- IT'S COMING BACK TO ME.
I THINK I MAY REMEMBER BUMPING
IT A LITTLE BIT ON MOUNT AKINA.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU, SON?
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO BE
LOSING YOUR MEMORY ALREADY.
- LAST NIGHT I, SORTA,
RACED AGAINST THIS JERK WHO
HAD CHALLENGED ME.
I GUESS I MUST HAVE.
LOST MY COOL.
BUT HE BUMPED ME FROM BEHIND.
AND ONCE I GOT HOME I
WAS SO FLUSTERED
I JUST WENT RIGHT TO BED.
- I WASN'T THERE, BUT SEEMS
TO ME. IT WAS AVOIDABLE.
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU
THAT YOU'RE STILL A BEGINNER.
IF I'D BEEN DRIVING, THAT
WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED AT ALL.
SO HOW'D YOU DO?
DID YOU WIN OR WHAT?
- YEAH. YEAH, I WON.
- THAT'S MY BOY.
- ( grunting )
- TAKE IT EASY, HERCULES.
NOW'S NOT THE TIME TO BE
WORKING ON YOUR BICEPS.
- IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
THE DOC SAID I'M OKAY.
I'LL BE ABLE TO LEAVE
IN THE NEXT DAY OR TWO.
- I BROUGHT YOU SOME FLOWERS
TO SPRUCE UP THE ROOM WITH.
I'LL PUT 'EM IN SOME WATER.
- THANK YOU!
SO I HEARD THE BIG NEWS MAN!
ABOUT THE BIG GUM
TAPE DEATH MATCH!
YOU KICKED HIS BUTT!
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT! THAT'S AWESOME!
YOU RULE!
NOT ONLY DID YOU PUT
THAT JERK IN HIS PLACE,
YOU BEAT HIM IN AN FR!
THAT'S BEYOND EPIC!
- MAYBE SO. BUT I BARELY THOUGHT
ABOUT WHAT CAR I WAS DRIVING,
I WAS TOO FOCUSED ON WINNING.
YEAH HE PISSED ME OFF
BUT THAT ISN'T WHAT DROVE ME.
IT WAS SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
I MEAN, ALL I COULD THINK ABOUT
WAS COMING IN FIRST PLACE.
IT WAS CRAZY, I'D NEVER FELT
THAT WAY DURING A RACE BEFORE.
- TAKUMI. YOU'RE
BECOMING MORE AND MORE
LIKE A STREET
RACER EVERY DAY.
- A STREET RACER? NO WAY, MAN.
YOU'RE GETTING' THE WRONG IDEA.
- AS SOON AS I GET OUTTA HERE I
CAN WORK ON MY DRIFTIN' SKILLS!
I'VE GOT TO STAY
ON TOP OF MY GAME
FOR OUR UNSTOPPABLE
LEVIN-TRUENO TEAM!
- WHAT ARE YOU BOYS
TALKING ABOUT?
- NOTHING. OH. AND BY THE WAY,
HOW'S SAORI DOIN'?
I WAS GETTING' A LITTLE WORRIED,
I HAVEN'T HEARD
ANYTHING FROM HER.
- OH, SHE'S FINE.
I ALMOST FORGOT, SHE
TOLD ME TO TELL YOU HI.
- AH. THAT'S COOL. YA KNOW.
ONCE I GET OUTTA HERE
THE FOUR OF US'LL HAVE TO
GET TOGETHER FOR A DRIVE!
- UH-HUH.
- I'M GLAD ITSUKI'S
FEELING ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH, ME TOO. AND HE SHOULD
BE GETTING HIS EIGHT-FIVE BACK
ANY DAY NOW.
- SO, I WASN'T TOTALLY HONEST
WITH HIM BACK THERE.
- HUH?
- SAORI WAS REALLY SHAKEN UP
AFTER THE ACCIDENT.
IT SOUNDS LIKE SHE'S STILL
NOT COMPLETELY OVER IT.
SHE TOLD ME SHE HASN'T SLEPT
A WINK EVER SINCE IT HAPPENED.
SHE SAID SHE HAD
A REALLY FUN TIME WITH HIM
AND THAT HE'S A REALLY NICE GUY
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT SHE DOESN'T THINK
IT'S GONNA WORK OUT.
- NO. I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S REALLY OVER BETWEEN US.
DAMN IT!
I DON'T CARE! STREET RACERS
DON'T NEED GIRLFRIENDS ANYWAY!
( sobbing )
- WELL, LOOK WHO IT IS.
WHAT BRINGS YOU BY HERE?
- THE ATM. PLUS I NEED
SOME SUPPLIES.
SO I THOUGHT I'D SWING BY
AND SEE WHAT YOUR UGLY MUG
WAS UP TO TONIGHT.
- TAKUMI SCRATCHED
THIS UP PRETTY GOOD.
OF COURSE THE WAY THE
OTHER GUY WAS DRIVING IT
WOULD'VE BEEN A MIRACLE
IF HE'D FINISHED
COMPLETELY UNSCATHED.
- THAT'S THE BREAKS, I GUESS.
ALTHOUGH HE HAS BEEN
GETTING BETTER.
- WHAT'RE YOU SMILING ABOUT?
YOUR SON, JUST BEAT THE LIVING
HELL OUT OF YOUR FENDER.
- HIS STYLE IS EVOLVING.
HE WAS GOOD BEFORE,
BUT THERE WAS
ALWAYS SOMETHING MISSING
FROM THE EQUATION.
LATELY HE'S BEEN GOING FASTER
THAN EVER. SEEING THE ROAD.
HE'S REALLY STEPPED
IT UP A NOTCH.
- HOW WOULD YOU KNOW?
YOU NEVER WATCH HIM RACE.
- WHEN YOU SEE THIS EIGHT-SIX
DAY IN AND DAY OUT LIKE I DO,
YOU CAN TELL HOW HE'S DRIVING
BY HOW SHE FEELS.
- AH. I NEVER WOULDA
THOUGHT OF THAT.
- ( engine starting )
- WELL. I'M OUTTA HERE, BUT I'LL
COME BACK BY WHEN I'M DONE.
WE'LL GRAB A DRINK!
- ( tires screeching )
- I GUESS CRAZY RUNS
IN THE FAMILY.
TAKUMI NEVER EVEN
HAD A CHANCE. POOR KID.
( song playing on radio )
- I CAN'T HELP MYSELF.
I'M SUCH A JUNKIE
WHEN IT COMES TO CARS.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW THIS PERSON
BUT I JUST CAN'T PASS BY A
MOTORIST IN NEED.
- ( clears throat )
HEY THERE. I'M NOT SOME CRAZY
SERIAL KILLER OR ANYTHING,
BUT I NOTICED YOU'RE HAVING
TROUBLE WITH YOUR CAR
AND THOUGHT MAYBE
I COULD GIVE YOU A HAND.
- I'M SURE YOU KNOW
MORE THAN I DO.
I CAN DRIVE 'EM
BUT NOT FIX 'EM.
I CAN'T GET IT STARTED. I TURN
THE KEY BUT NOTHING HAPPENS.
- I'M NOT PROMISIN' ANYTHING,
BUT I'LL TAKE A
LOOK AT IT FOR YA.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
- IF I WERE TO GUESS IT'S
SOMETHING WITH THE ELECTRICAL.
LET'S SEE HERE.
- AN S-THIRTEEN.
SPEED STARS.
- OW!
- SO WHAT DO YA THINK?
- THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
IN MY LIFE I'VE BEEN
THIS CLOSE TO A WOMAN
THAT WASN'T MY MOM!
I THINK MY HEART'S
GONNA EXPLODE!
SHE'S SO FRIGGIN' CUTE!
SHE SMELLS AMAZING!
I NEVER KNEW THE SCENT OF A
GIRL COULD DRIVE ME THIS WILD!
OH, NO, I'M ALL SWEATY!
I HOPE I DON'T STINK!
- OKAY, I THINK I GOT IT.
GO AHEAD AND CRANK HER UP.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
- ( engine starting )
- SWEET.
- IT'S WORKING!
YOU FIXED IT! WOW!
I'M SO GLAD YOU STOPPED!
THANK YOU. I OWE YOU ONE.
- NO, FORGET ABOUT IT.
IT WAS NO BIG DEAL, REALLY.
- THAT IS SO NOT TRUE.
YOU KNOW. I'VE ALWAYS
HAD A THING FOR GUYS
WHO ARE GOOD AT FIXING THINGS.
I HAVE TO RUN, BUT I'D LOVE TO
THANK YOU AGAIN SOMETIME.
MIND IF I GET YOUR NUMBER?
- OH. I JUST FIDGETED
WITH SOME WIRES, THAT'S ALL.
- OH, ALL RIGHT THEN.
- YOU IDIOT!
THIS IS THE ONLY CHANCE YOU'LL
EVER GET AND YOU JUST BLEW IT!
YOU'RE SUCH A DUMBASS, IKETANI!
I HOPE YOU DIE A LONELY OLD MAN!
- UM, EXCUSE ME.
- HUH?
- HERE.
THANKS AGAIN. I'M MAKO SATO.
CALL ME SOMETIME!
- ( Japanese song playing)
- I MUST'VE STOOD THERE AFTER
SHE LEFT FOR A SOLID HALF HOUR.
I COULDN'T WRAP MY HEAD AROUND
WHAT HAD HAPPENED.
I HOPE THIS ISN'T A DREAM.
WHO KNEW YOU COULD RUN
INTO AN ANGEL IN THE AFTERNOON.
UNDERNEATH THE
KAMAMESHI BILLBOARD?
- ( rock music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- YOU APPEARED BEFORE ME
IN THE PENETRATING LIGHT
OF THE SUMMER SUN.
AND I INSTANTLY BECAME A PUPPET
TO YOUR BLINDING BEAUTY,
A SLAVE TO YOUR EVERY WHIM!
- Announcer: IKETANI,
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
- Iketani: I SEE NOW THAT
I CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT YOU!
YOU ARE MY QUEEN, MY ANGEL,
THE OWNER OF MY HEART!
YOU ARE MY EVERYTHING!
- Announcer: DON'T MIND HIM.
HE'S IN HIS OWN WORLD RIGHT NOW.
NEXT TIME ON INITIAL D.
THE ANGEL OF USUI!
- Iketani: ANGEL?
YOU MEAN MY SWEET MAKO?
DON'T MISS IT!