- ( theme song playing )
♪ GET READY YO!
NOW WE BLOW UP THE HORN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ BREAK INTO THE NIGHT
IT'S THE TIME ♪
- ♪ LOST IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ MISSING MY HEART ♪
♪ LOVE ME SO MUCH ♪
♪ LET'S ROCK ♪
- ( engines revving )
- ( tires screeching )
- ( bells chiming )
- I'M GOING AT FULL POWER
AND HE'S STILL ON MY TAIL.
NO MATTER HOW FAST I GO,
I CAN'T SHAKE HIM.
THIS SUCKS.
AT THIS RATE I'M GONNA LOSE.
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
THIS GUY'S THE BEST.
NO WAY I CAN COMPARE TO HIM.
I WISH IT WEREN'T TRUE,
BUT, I'M GONNA LOSE THIS!
- ( tires screeching )
- THIS WHOLE RIDE IS SENDING
CHILLS DOWN MY SPINE.
TO SEE THIS KID FOLLOWING
A PERFECT LINE
IS LIKE WITNESSING A MIRACLE.
IF I WEREN'T RIGHT ON HIM,
SHADOWING HIS EVERY MOVE,
IT WOULD BE DAMN NEAR IMPOSSIBLE
FOR ME TO PULL THIS OFF.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THERE'S
ANYONE ABLE TO DO IT.
BEGINNERS CAN DRIVE FAST ON A
STRAIGHT LINE. THAT'S CAKE.
INTERMEDIATE DRIVERS START
TO WORK IT A LITTLE BETTER
BY MASTERING THE CORNERS.
BUT THE TRULY ADVANCED
DRIVERS FIND THEIR OWN COURSE.
THE MAIN OBJECTIVE OF MY
'FASTEST DRIVER' THEORY
IS TO FIND THAT ULTIMATE COURSE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE AFTER
SEARCHING FOR SO LONG
THE BEST EXAMPLE I'VE FOUND OF
MY THEORY IS HERE,
TONIGHT, IN THIS KIND OF A RACE.
THIS KID HAS SOME
AMAZING TALENT.
- ( engine revving )
- HEY, HERE THEY COME.
- WHO'S IN FRONT?
IS IT THE EIGHT-SIX OR THE FC?
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING!
- ( tires screeching )
- ( engine revving )
- WHOA! THAT'S INTENSITY!
- IMPRESSIVE THEY CAN PULL
IT OFF SO CLOSE.
- ( tires screeching )
- THIS ISN'T WORKING.
I CAN'T WIDEN THE LEAD.
- ( tires screeching )
- Blondie Redsun: THIS IS IT.
HERE THEY COME.
JUST THE SOUND OF THOSE SQUEALS
GIVE ME THE FREAKIN WILLIES.
- Kenta: THAT STRAIGHT LENGTH OF
TRACK BEFORE THE HAIRPIN TURN,
IS A LONG SECTION FOR THE
GUYS TO SHOOT THROUGH.
BET THERE'S ABOUT TO BE SOME
HARD-ASS BRAKING COMIN' ON.
- CHECK IT OUT!
THE EIGHT-SIX IS IN FRONT!
- Kenta: RYOSUKE!
- Boy 1: THIS IS THE ENTRANCE
TO THE FIVE HAIRPINS.
I GOT MY EYES ON BOTH CARS NOW
AND THE EIGHT-SIX IS LEADING.
- ( engine revving )
- HE SCREWED UP,
HE'S GOING IN TOO FAST.
- ( tires screeching )
- DAMMIT! TURN!
- ( crowd gasping )
- ( tires screeching )
- HE COULD'VE POWERED THROUGH
IT AND BROUGHT IT BACK AROUND,
IF HE WERE DRIVING
A MORE POWERFUL CAR.
BUT TRYING IT WITH AN EIGHT-SIX
IS NOTHING SHORT OF RECKLESS.
-Boy 1: RYOSUKE'S FC
TOOK THE LEAD!
- HE WHAT?
- THE EIGHT-SIX
OVER-ACCELERATED.
THEN WHEN HE UNDERSTEERED,
RYOSUKE DROVE A NAIL IN HIS
COFFIN AND PASSED HIM.
- Keisuke: THE EIGHT-SIX
UNDERSTEERED?
- RYOSUKE'S BETTER
THAN I'VE EVER SEEN HIM.
NO ONE CAN MATCH
THE TALENT THAT GUY'S GOT.
- Boy 1: DUDE, AIN'T
THAT THE TRUTH!
HE'S TOTALLY DRAGGIN'
HOME THE WIN.
♪ NIGHT AND DAY
I'M FEELING EMPTY AND LONELY ♪
♪ YOU GET ME OUT OF THIS
GIMME ONE KISS ♪
♪ NIGHT AND DAY
I'M LIVING SO SADLY ♪
♪ I STAND ON MY KNEES
GIVE ME ONE PLEASE ♪
♪ NIGHT AND DAY
I'M FEELING EMPTY AND LONELY ♪
- Ryosuke: THE GUY'S SO ODD.
AND SUCH A STRANGE WEAKNESS.
MY PLAN WAS TO HANG
BACK AS LONG AS I COULD
TO HIDE MY STRENGTHS.
BUT NOW THAT I'M IN FRONT,
I DON'T WANT HIM TO GET RIGHT
UP ON ME AND SCOPE ME OUT.
SO BEFORE HE RECOVERS ANY
GROUND, I NEED TO WIDEN THE GAP.
THAT'S HOW I'LL SECURE THE WIN.
- ( engine revving )
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M DOING ♪
♪ BABE, IT'S THE TIME
TO LET ME GO ♪
♪ I THINK TOO MUCH
OF WHAT YOU SAID ♪
♪ THAT OUR LOVE
WILL NEVER DIE ♪
♪ GO AWAY AND DON'T FORGET
ALL THE DREAMS THAT WE HAD ♪
- THE FC JUST
BLEW PAST US HERE.
THE EIGHT-SIX IS DRAGGIN'
A LITTLE BEHIND.
- Boy 2: WHOAH! RYOSUKE'S TIME
IS KILLER THOUGH.
I'M THINKIN' HE COULD BEAT
THE COURSE RECORD BY LIKE
12 SECONDS IF HE PUNCHES IT.
- TWELVE SECONDS?
THIS RACE IS OVER.
I KNOW THE WAY
MY BROTHER PLAYS.
NEXT THING HE'LL DO
IS WIDEN THAT GAP.
♪ ...I AM LIVING SO SADLY ♪
♪ I STAND ON MY KNEES... ♪
- HEARING ABOUT WHAT HE'S
DEALING WITH FREAKS ME OUT.
EVEN IF HE LOSES THIS, I DON'T
THINK IT'LL HURT HIS REPUTATION.
I MEAN, HOW COULD IT
WHEN YOU'RE UP AGAINST
AN INCOMPARABLE DRIVER?
- HEY CAN THAT CRAP, DUDE.
THIS RACE AIN'T OVER YET.
I GOT ALL THE FAITH IN THE WORLD
THAT TAKUMI CAN STILL
COME BACK AND WIN.
- HOW YA FIGURE?
- CUZ IN EVERY RACE HE'S RUN,
HE ALWAYS HAS, RIGHT?
NO MATTER HOW MUCH THE ODDS
HAVE BEEN STACKED AGAINST HIM,
HE'S ALWAYS COME OUT ON TOP.
I CAN FEEL IT IN THE PIT
OF MY STOMACH
THAT HE'S GONNA DO
IT AGAIN TONIGHT.
- ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS YOU GETTING
TO THE BOTTOM SAFELY, TAKUMI.
DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID.
♪ AND DON'T FORGET
ALL THE DREAMS THAT WE HAD ♪
♪ SOMEDAY YOU WILL COME AND... ♪
- THE MERIT OF A LIGHT AND
COMPACT ROTARY ENGINE
ISN'T IN THE POWER
IT INNATELY HAS.
IT'S IN THE AGILITY YOU GET
FROM AN IDEAL FRONT
AND REAR END WEIGHT
DISTRIBUTION.
I JUST LOVE THE CONSISTENT
SPIRIT OF THE ROTARY ENGINE.
IT'S LIKE MAGIC ON THE STREET.
EVEN IF I HAVE TO PUT
MY PRIDE ON THE LINE,
THE ROTARY ENGINE CAN'T FALL
BEHIND THE EIGHT-SIX
ON THESE CORNERS.
- ( tires screeching )
- LOOK AT THOSE BOYS.
THEY'RE SOMETHING ELSE
ON THAT ASPHALT TOGETHER.
THE DRIFT PUNKS 'ROUND HERE
CAN'T EVEN COME CLOSE
TO THE SPEED THOSE GUYS
EFFORTLESSLY HAVE.
- I KNOW. SO WHO DO YOU THINK
IS GONNA WIN THIS THING?
- WELL, IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO PASS RYOSUKE
ONCE HE'S TAKEN THE LEAD.
THAT'S A FACT.
BUT THEN AGAIN, THIS IS
TAKUMI HE'S RACING AGAINST.
I MEAN HE HASN'T
GIVEN UP THE GOLD.
HE'S CHOOSING BETTER LINES
THAN THE FC FOR SURE.
YOU CAN TELL HOW OFTEN
HE'S DRIVEN AKINA PASS.
- ( tires screeching )
- I FIGURED AS SOON AS HE
GOT OUT IN FRONT OF ME,
HE WOULD'VE LEFT ME IN THE DUST.
LOOKS LIKE I'VE
STILL GOT A CHANCE.
I'VE GOTTA GET CLOSER.
ALMOST THERE.
- WHAT THE HELL?
ALL OF THE SUDDEN MY FRONT TIRES
AREN'T STICKING TO THE ROAD.
COULD IT BE HEAT WEAR?
FOLLOWING THE EIGHT-SIX AND
COPYING HIS DRIVING MIGHT HAVE
PUT MORE OF A STRAIN ON THE
FRONT TIRES THAN I EXPECTED.
HE'S GAINING.
I WONDER IF HE'S HAVING THE
SAME PROBLEMS WITH HIS TIRES
THAT I'M HAVING WITH MINE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER. A LITTLE
WEAR ON THE TIRES
WON'T AFFECT MY
TECHNIQUE ONE BIT.
- INITIAL D!
INITIAL D!
- I'LL NEVER CATCH HIM
AN INCH AT A TIME.
I'VE GOT TO GET CLOSER FAST.
- ( engine revving )
- ( tires screeching )
DAMN! IS THIS THE BEST I CAN DO?
MAYBE I SHOULD TRY THAT MOVE
DAD WAS TELLING ME ABOUT.
"THE OTHER
GUTTER DRIVING" THING.
- YOU'RE BACK. THAT WAS QUICK.
- HEY, DAD. I THINK I FIGURED
OUT A PRETTY COOL TRICK TO AVOID
SKIDDING OUT ON A CURVE
IN SNOWY WEATHER LIKE THIS.
HOOK THE TIRES ON ONE
SIDE INTO THE GUTTER
ON THAT SIDE OF THE ROAD.
IT MAKES CORNERING SO
EASY IT'S NOT EVEN FUNNY.
- "GUTTER DRIVING". I USE THAT
TECHNIQUE A LOT MYSELF.
- WELL, DAMMIT.
YOU KNOW ABOUT IT TOO?
- LISTEN UP. THERE ARE TWO WAYS
TO USE THE GUTTERS ON
AKINA'S ROADS.
THE METHOD YOU STUMBLED
ONTO IS TO USE THE GUTTER
AS YOU ENTER THE CORNER
SO YOU CAN
PREVENT UNDER STEERING.
BUT...
THERE I'S ANOTHER ONE AND THIS
ONE EMPHASIZES RECOVERY
AFTER A CORNER.
THE TIMING USED FOR
GETTING IN AND OUT
OF THE GUTTER IS DIFFERENT.
IT'S ACTUALLY
A PRETTY TOUGH DEAL.
BEST FOR YOU
TO FIGURE IT OUT YOURSELF.
- ( engine revving )
- I HAVEN'T EVEN
TRIED THE MOVE YET.
IT'S ONE HELL OF A GAMBLE.
SHOULD I GO FOR IT?
- ( tires screeching )
- SCREW IT, HERE GOES!
- WHAT THE HELL DID HE
JUST PULL OFF?
I GOTTA KNOW WHAT HE JUST DID.
- Takeshi: HEY SHINGO,
IT SOUNDS LIKE THEY'RE COMIN'.
- AND JUDGING FROM
THAT SKIDDING SOUND,
THEY'VE GOTTA BE RIGHT ON
TOP OF EACH OTHER.
- I'D EXPECT AS MUCH
FROM THESE TWO.
- THIS IS IT. THE PLACE
TO GO FOR THE WIN.
THE STRAIGHTAWAY
LETS YOU SPEED UP
FOR THE BRAKING YOU
GOTTA DO COMING UP.
IT'S NOT NARROW AS HELL
LIKE THE REST OF THE PASS.
THIS CORNER'S GOT THREE LANES.
YOU CAN CHOOSE YOUR OWN LINE.
ON TOP OF THAT
THIS IS A COMPOUND CORNER
WHERE YOU GOT TWO LINES
OVERLAPPING EACH OTHER.
THE FINISH LINE'S
RIGHT OVER THERE.
WHERE ELSE IS EITHER
OF 'EM GO FOR THE WIN?
NO OTHER CHOICE.
- SO THE ONE WHO LEADS
AFTER THIS CORNER,
HE'S GOTTA BE THE ONE
WHO WINS THE RACE.
- ( tires screeching )
- DUDE, HERE THEY COME!
THE FC'S IN FRONT!
- BUT CHECK IT. THE
EIGHT-SIX IS RIGHT BEHIND!
- THIS IS OUT THERE!
WHAT'LL THEY DO!
- THERE'S NO WAY TO PASS
FROM THE OUTSIDE!
HE'S GOTTA GO INSIDE!
- Takeshi: I DON'T KNOW, MAN!
- Both: HE'S TAKIN' THE OUTSIDE!
- RYOSUKE DIDN'T LEAVE HIM
ANY ROOM ON THE INSIDE!
THERE WAS NO WAY
FOR HIM TO GO THERE!
THIS IS ALL HE CAN DO!
♪ I SAY TO YOU
IT'S ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND I
WE GOTTA FLY ♪
♪ BABY, FEEL IT
MUSIC IS POWER ♪
♪ I WANNA STAY ALL THE NIGHT ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU TONIGHT ♪
- THAT'S CRAZY!
THE FC'S STILL IN FRONT!
- THE INSIDE LINE'S
GOT THAT ADVANTAGE!
- THE FC IS SKIDDING
TO THE OUTSIDE OF THE CURVE!
IS THAT FOR REAL!
- I'M TELLIN' YOU,
HE'S GOING WAY TO FAST
TO PULL OUT OF THAT CORNER!
♪ YOU GOTTA FEEL THE DANCE
IT'S ALWAYS IN YOUR HEART ♪
♪ FEELING THE TIME TO COME
BEAT OF THE RISING SUN ♪
♪ I WANNA FEEL YOUR HEART
THE POWER OF THE SUN ♪
HE'S HISTORY!
- THEIR LINES ARE GONNA CROSS!
- THIS IS IT! HERE THEY COME!
- ( pop music playing )
- NO WAY!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE RYOSUKE
IS GONNA LOSE THIS!
- HEY THAT'S TAKUMI'S CAR!
TAKUMI. HE WON.
- Boy 1: IT'S THE EIGHT-SIX!
THE EIGHT-SIX WON IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
AND ON TOP OF THAT HE SET
AN AMAZING COURSE RECORD.
- MY BIG BROTHER LOST.
I CAN'T WRAP MY HEAD
AROUND THAT.
THE LEGEND OF THE UNBEATABLE
MAN WAS JUST CRUSHED.
- HE DID IT!
TAKUMI WON!
HE ACTUALLY WON THE RACE!
- Both: OH, KILLER!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
- Yuuichi: BUNTA,
ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
I SAID, TAKUMI WON
THE DAMN RACE!
- DON'T GET
SO WORKED UP, YUUICHI.
OF COURSE HE WON THE RACE.
- AND THE COURSE RECORD
HE SET IS CRAZY!
- GREAT. GOOD.
NOW I'M GONNA HANG UP.
- I DON'T GET HIM.
- SO HE WON. THAT'S MY BOY.
- THAT'S ONE HECK OF A RACE
WE JUST WITNESSED.
- HONESTLY, I'M STILL IN SHOCK.
I GOTTA SHAKE IT OFF.
HEY, SHINGO.
YOU MIND MOVIN' AWAY?
PEOPLE SEE US SITTIN' TOGETHER
THEY MIGHT THINK
WE'RE FRIENDS AND I DON'T WANT
ANY PART OF THAT.
- THEN YOU GET AWAY!
- TAKUMI DID A HELLUVA THING.
BEATING RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
- THAT'S SOMETHING
TO BE PROUD OF.
- YOU KNOW, MAYBE I'LL SEE IF HE
FEELS LIKE GOING OUT SOMETIME.
WHY DON'T YOU ASK OUT
THAT OTHER GUY?
WHAT WAS HIS NAME ANYWAY?
I FORGET. IKA...
- IT'S IKETANI.
- BINGO! IKETANI,
THAT'S THE ONE!
SO HIT HIM UP. WE COULD
DO THE DOUBLE DATE THING.
- SO, UH...
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT I'VE
BEEN WANTING TO ASK YOU
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
AND IT'S GONNA BUG ME
IF I DON'T.
I JUST DON'T GET WHY YOU WAITED
FOR ME TO TAKE CHARGE TONIGHT?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
- OH, SO YOU THINK I SLOWED
DOWN DURING THAT LAST HALF
OF THE RACE ON PURPOSE, UH?
THAT'S NOT HOW IT HAPPENED
AT ALL, I HATE TO TELL YOU.
- THEN WHAT DID HAPPEN?
YOU MUST'VE PICKED UP
YOUR PACE A NOTCH.
I TRIED MY BEST
NOT TO SLOW DOWN,
BUT MY FRONT TIRES
KEPT ACTING UP.
DON'T KNOW WHY.
DIDN'T EXPECT IT.
- YOUR TIRES?
- DON'T WORRY. I'M NOT
USING THEM AS AN EXCUSE.
CONDITIONS WERE THE
SAME FOR BOTH OF US
AND I WAS CLEARLY THE LOSER.
- RYOSUKE.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I DON'T THINK THAT I'M...
WELL THAT I'M LIKE A FASTER
DRIVER THAN YOU OR ANYTHING.
- YOU REALLY ARE
A WEIRD KID YA KNOW.
I HAVE NEVER MET ANYONE
LIKE YOU BEFORE.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
CONTENT WITH WINNING
ON SUCH A SMALL STAGE
LIKE THIS ONE.
THERE'S A MUCH BIGGER
WORLD OUT THERE.
YOU WERE A FAST DRIVER TONIGHT,
TAKUMI FUJIWARA.
I'LL SEE YOU AROUND.
- ( engine revving )
- ( rock music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S ALREADY FALL.
- I KNOW.
- SO DO YOU THINK
IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE SHOULD START HEADIN' BACK?
- YEAH, SURE.
- THIS CAR MIGHT BE A SMALL ONE
BUT IT SURE IS FAST.
I GET A PRETTY BIG
KICK OUT OF IT.
IT'S PROBABLY MY FAVORITE.
- TAKUMI! TAKUMI! TAKUMI!
YOU GOT ANOTHER CHALLENGE, DUDE!
IT'S FREAKIN' CRAZY!
THIS TIME IT'S REALLY BAD,
THOUGH, YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE IT!
- Bunta: NOW GET OUTTA HERE.
- YOU KNOW DAD, IF YOU GIVE ME
ANOTHER SIX MONTHS OR SO,
I MIGHT EVEN BECOME
A BETTER DRIVER THAN YOU.
- WHAT A LOAD OF HORSE CRAP.
I'LL ALWAYS BE
BETTER THAN A BABY.
- IT'S A BIG WORLD OUT THERE.