- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY TAKUMI. YOU DON'T LOOK
LIKE YOU'RE READY FOR THIS.
YOU SURE YOU'RE GONNA BE
COOL DOIN' YOUR THING
IN ALL THIS FREAKIN' RAIN?
I MEAN I NEVER SEEN
YOU DO IT BEFORE.
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW? I CAN'T
GO TOO FAST IN THE RAIN,
SO I GUESS I'LL JUST
DRIVE NORMALLY TO START
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
I CAN'T SAY YET IF I'M GONNA BE
FAST OR SLOW OUT THERE
UNDER THESE CONDITIONS.
ALL I KNOW IS I'M GONNA TAKE IT
EASY CUZ IF I CRASHED THIS CAR
MY DAD'S GONNA
CUT OFF MY HEAD
AND USE MY SKULL FOR AN ASHTRAY.
- HERE'S THE COUNTDOWN BOYS!
FIVE! FOUR. THREE.
TWO. ONE. GO!
- THAT SUCKS. THE S-FOURTEEN
GOT OFF TO A FASTER START.
- IT'S NOT EVEN A TURBO.
HE'S GOT A TWO-LITER IN THERE.
- YEAH BUT IT'S NOT JUST
THE SIZE OF THE ENGINE.
IT'S THE CLUTCH TECHNIQUE
HE USED ON THE WET SURFACE.
NO WONDER HE'S
GOIN' INTO THIS RACE
WITH SO MUCH CONFIDENCE.
- THAT WASN'T THE
EIGHT-SIX'S BEST START,
BUT I THINK HE
MEANT IT THAT WAY.
HE KNOWS HE CAN MAKE
UP TIME LATER ON
SO WHAT'S THE POINT OF
RUSHIN' AT THE TOP?
- CRAP, HE TOOK THE LEAD!
HIS S-FOURTEEN'S GOT SOME
SERIOUS POWER
AND HE COULD TOTALLY
WIDEN THE LEAD TO THE POINT
THAT WE'DNEVER CATCH UP!
- DAMN, HE'S WAY BEHIND!
LOOKS LIKE THIS HILL'S
A BIT TOO MUCHFOR AN EIGHT-SIX!
- SURE BUT FROM HERE
TO THE FINISH, IT'S ALL DOWNHILL
AND THAT PUTS THE EIGHT-SIX
AT THE ADVANTAGE.
DUDE'S GOT SOME OF THE MOST
KILLER DOWNHILL TECHNIQUE
I'VE EVER SEEN.
SO DON'T COUNT HIM OUT JUST YET.
- (cell phone rings )
- YEAH, HELLO?
OH, HEY THERE BRO.
- Ryosuke: SO THE EIGHT-SIX
AND KENTA ARE BATTLING
IN THE RAIN, HUH?
- THEY SURE ARE.
YOU SHOULD SEE KENTA.
HIS CONFIDENCE
IS THROUGH THE ROOF.
BUT THIS IS THE EIGHT-SIX, AND
I KNOW IT WON'T BE EASY FOR HIM.
- I WOULD AGREE.
NO MATTER HOW YOU LOOK AT IT,
DRIFTING THROUGH
CORNERS AT LOW SPEED
IS AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT ANIMAL.
AT LEAST WHEN COMPARED
TO NORMAL RACE CONDITIONS.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
AND IT CAN GET REALLY TRICKY
WHEN YOU HAVE TO
FLOOR THE GAS PEDAL
TO FULLY COMPLETE THE DRIFT.
- WHILE YOU CAN
RELY ON TIRE GRIP
FOR COMPENSATION
ON A DRY SURFACE.
- IT'S SEVERELY LIMITED
WHEN YOU'RE DRIVING IN THE RAIN.
- YOU HAVE TO BE REAL CAREFUL
AND SHIFT THE CAR'S WEIGHT
WHILE USING PRECISE TIMING.
OTHERWISE YOU'LL LOSE CONTROL
AND FIND YOURSELF
WRAPPED AROUND A TREE.
- IT MAKES ME WONDER IF
THOSE TWO REALLY KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE IN FOR.
WET CONDITIONS CAN BE HELL
ON THE CAR AND THE DRIVER.
WE'LL SEE.
- THOSE TWO, HUH?
LIKE YOU REALLY EVEN CARE.
THE ONLY THING YOU'RE
INTERESTED IN IS THE EIGHT-SIX.
NOT THAT I BLAME YOU.
- (screaming)
TAKUMI, PLEASE! LET ME
OUTTA THIS CAR!
I'M NOT READY TO DIE!
- DAMN IT, THE RAIN' IS REALLY
STARTIN' TO COME DOWN NOW.
THE GUY DRIVIN' FOR THE
RED SUNS IS FROM AKAGI.
MEANING NEITHER HE NOR TAKUMI
HAVE THE HOME TURF
ADVANTAGE TONIGHT.
THE BIG WILD CARD IS THE RAIN.
- HOLD ON. DOES HE EVEN KNOW
HOW TO DRIVE IN THE RAIN?
- Iketani: WELL,
I'M SURE HE KNOWS HOW.
I MEAN, HE MAKES
HIS DELIVERIES EVERY DAY.
THIS COULDN'T BE THE FIRST TIME
HE'S EVER GOTTEN
BEHIND THE WHEEL
OF THAT CAR
WHEN IT'S BEEN RAININ'.
- DUH OF COURSE!
THAT MAKES PERFECT SENSE!
- WHICH MEANS
TAKUMI'S TECHNIQUE,
IT SHOULD BE JUST AS EFFECTIVE
IN THE RAIN.
- I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU
CATCH UP WITH ME.
TIME TO WIDEN THE GAP SOME MORE.
I'M SO GOOD IN THE RAIN
I CAN OUTRACE SOME
OF THE BEST
TURBO-CHARGERS AROUND!
- ( audience cheering )
- WHOA! HE ALMOST
STARTED FISHTAILING!
- Boy 1: LOOKS LIKE
THE S-FOURTEEN'S RUNNIN' FAST
IN THESE WET CONDITIONS!
- ONE OF THE HARDEST THINGS TO
DO IN AN FR IS CONTROLLING IT
WHEN IT'S WET OUT.
- THE ONLY PLACE IT
EVER WANTS TO SPIN
IS TO THE SIDE AND NOT FORWARD.
- LOOK! HERE COMES
THE EIGHT-SIX!
- WOW! THATS INCREDIBLE!
HE'S DRIFTIN' LIKE
IT'S NOT EVEN RAININ'!
- I DON'T BELIEVE
WHAT I JUST SAW.
- THAT DRIFT HE JUST MADE
WAS DOWNRIGHT SCARY.
- I GOT CHILLS RUNNIN' DOWN ME.
- IS THIS REALLY THE SAME DUDE
I'VE BEEN PLOTTING TO BREAK OUT
OF HIS DAYDREAMIN' FUNK?
I THOUGHT HE WAS GONNA
TAKE IT EASY ON ME,
NOT BEING STRAPPED IN BACK HERE,
BUT HE'S DRIVIN'
LIKE A FRIGGIN' MANIAC!
IS THIS HOW HE NORMALLY IS?
PLUS, I CAN'T SEE JACK
OUTTA THIS WINDOW
WITH ALL THE RAIN COMIN' DOWN,
SO HOW THE HELL
IS HE SEEIN' THE ROAD?
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE FLYIN' THROUGH
A BLACK HOLE OR SOMETHIN'!
- ( ringing )
- WHAT'S WITH THAT
GOD-AWFUL RINGING?
I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE!
I KNOW WHAT'S GOIN' ON.
HE ISN'T HUMAN.
HE'S A FRIGGIN' MONSTER!
THIS IS EPIC. MAN I'M FEELIN'
GOOD. I'M IN THE ZONE!
BEFORE THE NIGHT'S OVER,
I'M GONNA BE THE ONE
TO FINALLY DETHRONE
THE EIGHT-SIX
AND END HIS WINNING STREAK!
NOT RYOSUKE OR KEISUKE. BUT ME!
I'LL BE THE NEW KING!
WHAT THE?
THE EIGHT-SIX IS RIGHT ON
MY TAIL! THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
SOMETHIN' WRONG WITH MY CAR?
I DON'T GET IT.
WE'VE ONLY GONE THROUGH
A COUPLE OF CORNERS
IN THE DOWNHILL,
SO HOW'D HE CATCH UP TO ME?
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
HE CAUGHT ME.
AND IT WAS NOTHIN' TO HIM!
IT'S AS IF THE RAIN
DIDN'T MAKE A DIFFERENCE AT ALL.
BUT THIS ISN'T OVER YET!
♪ WELCOME TO THE BROKEN LOW
♪ WELCOME TO
THE FAMOUS DISCO LIVE
♪ COME ON LADY COME AND GO
♪ COME ON LADY GET ME ONCE
AND RIGHT
♪ NOT A DANGER
NOT A BLACKY STREANGER
- Trucker Hat Man:
WHOA! THEY'RE ONLY INCHES APART!
♪ NIGHT OF FIRE
YOU BETTER BETTER STAY
♪ COME OVER OVER THE TOP
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN HERE
- THE EIGHT-SIX
IS MAKIN' A MOVE!
- INITIAL D!
INITIAL D!
- HE'S DOIN' IT!
HE'S PASSIN' THE S-FOURTEEN!
DID YOU SEE HOW EASY
HE MADE THAT LOOK?
- NO WAY. YOU'RE KIDDIN'!
- OH DUDE, THIS RACE WAS SO
WORTH WAITIN' IN THE RAIN FOR!
- TOTALLY!
- I CAN'T EVEN KEEP UP!
HE KEEPS INCREASIN' HIS LEAD
AFTER EVERY DAMN TURN!
I'M JUST NOT GETTING THAT KINDA
SPEED THROUGH THE CORNERS.
MY CAR'S SPECS BURY HIS
IN EVERY WAY!
SO WHAT'S MAKIN' THE DIFFERENCE?
I THOUGHT THE RAINY CONDITIONS
WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
TO MY ADVANTAGE.
- GOT IT. KEEP ME POSTED
- I JUST GOT A CALL
FROM THE HALFWAY POINT.
THE EIGHT-SIX PASSED YOUR GUY
AND IS NOW IN THE LEAD.
- OKAY. I GUESS KENTA NEVER
REALLY STOOD A CHANCE AFTER ALL.
- BUT, YOUR GUY WASN'T
A COMPLETE DISASTER.
THE EIGHT-SIX IS UNSTOPPABLE
EVEN WHEN IT'S
POURING DOWN RAIN.
- IT WAS OBVIOUS
BEFORE THE RACE EVEN STARTED.
WEATHER CONDITIONS PLAY NO PART
IN GAINING THE ADVANTAGE ON HIM.
- NOW IT'S YOUR BROTHER'S CHANCE
AT DETHRONIN' THE NEW KING.
-Iketani: HOW YA DOIN' TODAY!
-Itsuki: WELCOME!
- GOOD AFTERNOON.
ANYWAY.
AT LEAST WE KNOW HE'S
JUST AS DOMINATING RACIN'
IN THE RAIN AS HE IS
WHEN IT'S DRY OUT.
- I'M TELLIN' YA DUDE,
THAT BOY'S BECOMIN'
MORE AND MORE LIKE A TRUE
RACER EVERY DAY.
YOU SAW HOW HE ACCEPTED
THE S-FOURTEEN'S CHALLENGE
LAST NIGHT LIKE IT WAS NOTHIN'.
- AND IT LOOKS LIKE HIS
DAYDREAMIN' PHASE
IS OVER FOR NOW.
I GUESS OUR OPERATION
WAS A SMASHIN' SUCCESS,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY FELLAS?
All: MM-HMM.
- I GOTTA ADMIT, ITSUKI, I'M A
LITTLE JEALOUS OF YOU,
YA LUCKY BASTARD.
BEING ABLE TO EXPERIENCE
A RAINY DOWNHILL BATTLE
FROM INSIDE HIS CAR
MUST'VE BEEN AWESOME.
- IT FLIPPED MY LID!
I MUST'VE HAD MY LIFE
FLASH BEFORE MY EYES
LIKE A MILLION TIMES!
PLUS HE TOLD ME
TO SIT IN THE BACK
SO I WAS BEING THROWN AROUND
LIKE A RAGDOLL!
- HE MADE YA SIT IN THE BACK?
- DID HE SAY WHY?
- NO. I DON'T THINK TAKUMI
EVEN KNEW WHY HE SAID IT.
HE WAS ACTIN' LOONEY
THE WHOLE NIGHT.
SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
- WHOA WHOA. LET'S BACK UP.
YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG DUDE.
I KNOW WHY HE PUT YOU
BACK THERE.
- YOU DO? TELL US!
- YEAH, SPILL IT ALREADY!
- IT'S QUITE SIMPLE.
WELL, BECAUSE...
- Both: OUT WITH IT!
- ITSUKI'S ANNOYING.
IT'S GOTTA BE FRUSTRATIN'
AS HELL HAVIN' ITSUKI WHININ'
AND CRYIN' NEXT TO YA
WHILE YOU'RE TRYIN'
TO FOCUS ON THE ROAD.
- I CAN TOTALLY SEE
THAT HAPPENIN'!
- ALRIGHT! LAY OFF!
- ( all laughing)
- GEEZ, TALK ABOUT
A COUPLE OF BONEHEADS.
THAT'S NOT THE REASON WHY.
HE HAD ITSUKI SIT IN THE BACK
BECAUSE HE WAS HOPING TO GET
SOME EXTRA TIRE TRACTION.
AND KNOWING TAKUMI, HE
PROBABLY KNEW THAT INTUITIVELY.
HE DOESN'T STRIKE ME AS THE KIND
OF KID TO READ THAT IN A BOOK.
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- THAT BOY. THERE IS JUST
NO TELLING HOW MUCH BETTER
HE'LL GET OVER TIME.
- Natsuki: TAKUMI!
- ( bell ringing )
- WHO IS THAT?
- LOOKS FAMILIAR.
- IT'S TAKUMI'S GIRLFRIEND.
- Both: HIS GIRLFRIEND?
- SO I DON'T REALLY HAVE
A REASON FOR COMING BY.
I WAS JUST RIDING AROUND IN
THE AREA AND DECIDED TO STOP.
- YEAH?
- IS THIS A BAD TIME?
- UH, NO.
- HE LOOKS LIKE A LITTLE PUPPY
IN LOVE!
- THIS ISN'T GOOD.
( thuds)
- WELL YOU PROBABLY
HAVE STUFF YOU'VE GOTTA DO,
SO I BETTER HEAD OUT.
- OH, SURE.
- NO! YOU GUYS.
WHAT IF HE STARTS DAYDREAMIN'
ABOUT HER AGAIN!
HIS RACIN' CAREER
WILL BE TOTALLY SCREWED!
- YOU BETTER DO SOMETHIN'
ABOUT IT.
- WHAT DO YOU EXPECT ME TO DO?
IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S A BUNCH
OF OTHER RACES LINED UP
FOR US TO CHECK OUT.
- WELL WE SURE AS HELL CAN'T
HAVE HIM SPACIN' OUT
WHEN THE BIG SHOWDOWN
AGAINST RYOSUKE IS NEXT WEEK.
WE NEED HIS FOCUS
ON THE RACE.
- YOU THINK I DON'T KNOW THAT?
HEY, TAKUMI! HOW 'BOUT YOU AND I
GO FOR A SPIN AT AKINA TONIGHT?
- WHAT A MESS. MUST BE
FROM ALL THE RAIN LAST NIGHT.
- ( pop song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( phone ringing )
- TOFU SHOP.
YEAH. I'M SORRY, WHO IS THIS?
- Mr. Tsuchiya: IT'S ME.
BEEN AWHILE, HASN'T IT BUNTA?
- HEY. TSUCHIYA. SURE HAS.
SO WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
LET ME GUESS, YOU'RE
IN THE HOSPITAL
AFTER ONE OF YOUR CRASHES?
- DON'T YOU WISH.
HEY, SO I'VE BEEN HEARING
A LOT OF CHATTER RECENTLY
ABOUT YOUR SON.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
QUITE THE PRODIGY.
KNOW ANYTHING 'BOUT THAT?
- WHAT? THIS SATURDAY?
AND IT'S AGAINST
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI?
SHOULD I KNOW WHO THAT IS?
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
EVEN MY PEOPLE KNOW WHO HE IS.
WORD IS HE'S THE BEST
STREET RACER IN ALL OF GUNMA.
- Bunta: AND HE'S RACING
MY SON, HUH?
- SO LET'S HEAR IT.
WHO DO YOU THINK'S GONNA WIN?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
WE'LL HAVE TO FIND OUT
SATURDAY WITH EVERYONE ELSE.
- ( laughs ) YOU HAVEN'T
CHANGED A BIT.
I'M CURIOUS TO SEE THIS DRIFT
YOUR SON GOT FROM YOU.
IT'S ALL I HEAR ABOUT.
YOU KNOW YOU
SCARRED ME FOR LIFE
WITH THOSE MONSTROUS DRIFTS
YOU USED TO PULL.
I STILL CAN'T SLEEP
THROUGH THE NIGHT.
- THAT WAS YEARS AGO.
- Woman: MR TSUCHIYA,
WE NEED YOU.
- Tsuchiya: BE RIGHT THERE!
GOTTA RUN, BUNTA.
- YA KNOW, ITSUKI, YOU'VE ONLY
BEEN DRIVIN' A FEW MINUTES
AND I CAN ALREADY
TELL YOU'VE IMPROVED.
- NO WAY! YOU REALLY THINK SO?
THANKS DUDE!
THAT MEANS A
WHOLE HELLUVA A LOT
COMING FROM A CHAMPION
LIKE YOU, TAKUMI.
I HAVEN'T TOLD ANYONE YET
BUT I'VE BEEN WORKIN'
ON MY 'GRIP RUN'.
IT'S BADASS.
HERE'S A TECHNIQUE I CAME UP
WITH ALL ON MY OWN.
IT'S TAKEN COUNTLESS HOURS
OF PRACTICE TO MASTER IT
AND YOU'RE THE ONLY PERSON
I'M WILLIN' TO SHOW.
- HUH?
- HERE IT IS! ILLUSIONARY
HELL AND TEAR!
WHOOPS, SORRY! THAT'S MY BAD!
FUNNY, I DIDN'T HAVE ANY TROUBLE
AT ALL WITH IT YESTERDAY.
ALRIGHT, LETS TRY THAT AGAIN!
THAT ONE WAS
'INCREDIBLE BRAKING'!
- Takumi: WAIT, ITSUKI.
LET'S TAKE A BREAK OK?
- I'M SO GLAD I CAN RELAX NOW
THAT YOU'RE OUT OF
YOUR SILLY DAYDREAMIN' CRAP.
I JUST HOPE IT DOESN'T COME
BACK, KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
- HOLD ON A SECOND!
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
I WASN'T DAYDREAMING.
- WELL WHATEVER IT WAS
YOU WERE DOIN'
YOU WERE ACTIN' ALL, WHATEVER.
- HUH?
- DON'T YOU GET
WHAT I'M SAYING, MAN?
OR DO I HAVE TO SPELL IT OUT?
- BETTER SPELL IT OUT. SERIOUSLY
IT MAKES NO SENSE TO ME.
WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY
NEED AFTER THE RACE
THAT'S SO IMPORTANT?
FACT IS YOU DON'T NEED ANYTHING.
YOU'RE ALREADY FAST AS IT IS
SO IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO PROVE YOURSELF AGAIN.
- DUDE, I'M NOT THAT FAST.
- ARE YOU CRAZY? YES YOU ARE!
REMEMBER, YOU'RE STILL
UNDEFEATED,
I'D SAY THAT'S PRETTY FAST.
- I DON'T KNOW.
ALL I KNOW IS' MY WHOLE
FUTURE IS IN FRONT OF ME
AND I HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE I'M HEADING.
- TAKUMI, YOU'RE WASTING
YOUR TIME.
CAN'T YOU JUST FOCUS ON THE RACE
FOR NOW AND FORGET THE FUTURE?
THE RACE IS GONNA BE
HERE BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, DUDE.
- RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- RYOSUKE, WE'RE COMING UP
ON THE MOMENT OF TRUTH
FOR YOUR FASTEST
RACER THEORY.
- Ryosuke: YES, AND I'M LOOKING
FORWARD TO THE OPPORTUNITY
OF PROVING IT RIGHT.
- SO, WHAT EXACTLY IS THE
THEORY?
CAN YOU EXPLAIN IT FOR US?
- I'M SURE YOU'RE ALL
FAMILIAR WITH THE TERM
E EQUALS M-C-SQUARED, RIGHT?
IT'S KNOWN AS EINSTEIN'S
THEORY OF RELATIVITY.
I'VE TAKEN THAT PREMISE AND
ADDED MY OWN SUB-THEORY TO IT.
E SYMBOLIZES THE
OPPONENT'S AVERAGE SPEED
THROUGHOUT THE RACE
FROM BEGINNING TO END,
Announcer: NEXT ON INITIAL D.
AKAGI'S WHITE COMET.
DON'T MISS IT!