- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing on Japanese )
♪ BREAK INTO THE NIGHT,
IT'S THE TIME ♪
- ( yawning )
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO GUYS.
BUT WE GOTTA PULL TAKUMI'S HEAD
OUT OF THIS DAYDREAMING FUNK
HE'S BEEN STUCK IN.
- THE RACE IS ON THE FIFTEENTH.
SO THAT ONLY LEAVES US
A WEEK TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT THE HELL WE'RE GONNA DO
- IT'S A GOOD THING THIS ISN'T
GOIN' DOWN TOMORROW.
- WAIT A SECOND. I HEARD
THAT THE RED SUNS
ARE SUPPOSED TO BE RACIN'
THE NIGHT KIDS.
THAT'S HAPPENING TOMORROW
NIGHT, ISN'T IT?
- THAT'S IT! WE HAUL TAKUMI OUT
THERE, PLANT HIS ASS,
AND MAKE HIM WATCH
THOSE TEAMS RACE EACH OTHER!
YES! GENIUS! THAT COULD BE
EXCITING ENOUGH
TO SNAP HIM OUT OF THIS
DAYDREAMING ABOUT NATSUKI CRAP!
- I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING
BETTER THAN A RACE
TO GET HIM TO STOP THINKIN'
WITH THE WRONG HEAD.
- MIGHT BE A BIT OF
A RUDE AWAKENING
BUT THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
THIS GUY NEEDS RIGHT NOW.
- ( yawning )
- HEY, DAD. I'VE BEEN THINKIN'
ABOUT SOMETHING.
- 'BOUT WHAT?
- THE OTHER NIGHT, A COUPLE OF
US WENT UP TO USUI
AND I RACED THESE TWO CHICKS.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT EXPERIENCE
FROM RACING HERE.
BUT YOU KNOW,
WHEN I WAS DRIVING IT,
I NOTICED HOW SIMILAR IT WAS
TO DRIVNG ON AKINA PASS.
- THAT SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- SURE USUI'S A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT COURSE
FROM AKINA IN EVERY WAY.
BUT THE RACE YOU RAN,
WAS THE SAME ONE
YOU WOULD'VE RUN ON AKINA.
THINK OF IT LIKE THIS.
IT'S ALL ABOUT HOW MUCH
AKINA YOU TAKE WITH YOU
TO THE OTHER COURSES.
GOOD LUCK WITH THE DELIVERIES.
- THANKS.
- HOW MUCH AKINA I TAKE WITH ME.
- ( car revving )
I THINK I KINDA GET WHAT THE
OLD MAN'S TRYING TO SAY.
- ( yawning )
I NEED A NAP.
- HE'S COMPLETELY LOST IN
ANOTHER ONE OF HIS DAYDREAMS.
RIGHT! IT'S TIME TO LET
THIS OPERATION BEGIN!
WASSUP, TAKUMI, MY MAIN MAN?
HOW'S THINGS GOIN'?
( laughs ) GOT SOME BIG
NEWS FOR YA DUDE!
NOW DON'T FREAK OUT WHEN
I TELL YA, 'KAY?
BUT THE RED SUNS AND
THE NIGHT KIDS,
THEY'RE HAVIN'A HUGE THROW DOWN
TONIGHT! CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
- YEAH, SO?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "SO"?
IT'S A HUGE DEAL, BUD!
YOU'RE TAKIN' ON RYOSUKE
NEXT WEEK.
WATCHIN' WHAT THESE GUYS DO
ON THE ROAD TONIGHT
IS A NO BRAINER.
YOU GOTTA GET OUT THERE.
GREAT! THEN IT'S SETTLED.
LET'S TAKE YOUR EIGHT-SIX.
IT'D JUST BE A WASTE OF
GAS TO TAKE TWO CARS UP THERE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I DO. PERFECT.
- YOU WANNA TAKE MY CAR?
- ( exclaiming excitedly )
TELL ME YOU'RE EXCITED TOO!
UH. YEAH.
- EXCELLENT! THEN I'LL MEET YOU
AT YOUR PLACE AT SEVEN SHARP!
DON'T FORGET TO TALK TO YOUR DAD
ABOUT BORROWIN' THE EIGHT-SIX.
THIS'LL BE SO AWESOME!
- ( people chattering )
- THEY GOT A BIG CROWD
PACKED IN TONIGHT.
HEY, YOU SEE TAKUMI AND
ITSUKI HERE YET?
- UH UH. BUT THEY SHOULD
BE HERE SOON.
- I HOPE ITSUKI
WORKED SOME MAGIC.
WE NEED TAKUMI TO SEE THIS.
- Itsuki: IF YOU CAN'T FIND
THE ROAD SOON, DUDE,
WE'RE GONNA MISS THE RACE.
AND FOR THE RECORD,
WE GOT LOST BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T
WANNA TAKE THE TOLL ROAD
AND HAD TO TAKE
THE SIDE STREETS.
YOU'RE JUST TOO DAMN
CHEAP SOMETIMES.
- LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO DIDN'T DRIVE
BECAUSE YOU SAID WE WERE
GONNA SAVE MONEY ON GAS
COMING UP HERE TOGETHER.
- DUDE, I'VE NEVER EVEN
HEARD OF A RACER
WITH NO SENSE OF
DIRECTION BEFORE.
( sighs )
MUST BE A SIDE EFFECT
OF HIS DAYDREAMING.
- COOL. THINK I GOT IT.
- GO, GO, GO! WE GOTTA FLY
TO MAKE IT THERE!
- ( thunder rumbling )
- YOU MADE ME WAIT.
- COME ON DUDE, DIDN'T YOU KNOW
THE MAIN CHARACTER
ALWAYS SHOWS UP LAST?
- MYOGI'S RAVINE IS
PRETTY STEEP.
SO TRY NOT TO FLY OFF AND DIE
WHILE YOU'RE TAKIN' HER CURVES.
- ENOUGH B.S. TRASH TALKIN'.
I CAN SEE YOUR
HANDS ARE SHAKIN'.
YOU DON'T GOTTA WORRY
ABOUT A THING.
IT'LL BE A QUICK VICTORY FOR ME.
NO NIGHT KID CAN TOUCH
WHAT I BRING.
- YOU SHOULD LOSE
THAT ARROGANCE.
THAT KINDA THING COULD GET YOU
KILLED UP HERE TONIGHT, KEISUKE.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- LET'S GET ROLLIN' BEFORE THESE
CLOUDS OPEN UP HUH?.
YEAH.
- Man: YOU GUYS SEEIN' THAT?
WHO THE HELL IS THAT?
- ( tires screeching )
- AN EIGHT-SIX?
- Itsuki: CHECK OUT THE SIZE
OF THIS CROWD, BRO.
- YEAH, THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE.
JUST FOCUS ON FINDING
OUR FRIENDS, OKAY?
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I WAS DOING.
GEEZ. IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S THE
EASIEST THING TO DO
WITH ALL THESE
FREAKIN' PEOPLE HERE.
- HEY, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE WE SHOULD GO
TO PARK THE CAR?
- WHAT ABOUT GOIN' UP
TO THE TOP?
THE PARKING LOT UP THERE
SHOULD HAVE PLENTY OF ROOM.
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
TOP OF THE MOUNTAIN IT IS THEN.
- I KNEW YOU'D SHOW UP TONIGHT.
JUST WHAT I NEEDED TO
GET ME REVVED UP.
- I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW MUCH I'VE IMPROVED
SINCE THE LAST TIME
WE MET, EIGHT-SIX.
- DUDE, AN EIGHT-SIX.
- YOU MEAN AKINA'S?
- YEAH, MAN.
- NO KIDDIN'.
- OKAY, TAKUMI.
IS IT JUST ME OR DO
YOU GET THE FEELIN'
THAT PEOPLE KEEP STARING AT US
- AS WE GO THROUGH HERE LIKE
WE'RE CELEBRITIES OR SOMETHIN'.
- YEAH.
- "YEAH"? THAT'S ALL
YOU HAVE TO SAY?
DO YOU EVEN REALIZE HOW MUCH
THEY TOTALLY RECOGNIZE US
IN THIS RIDE?
AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX IS LIKE
MOVIE-STAR FAMOUS.
ISN'T THAT COOL?
EVERYONE'S GOT THEIR
EYE'S ON YOU NOW.
THEY ALL WANNA KNOW
WHAT YOU GOT PLANNED NEXT.
I THINK IT WAS A SUPER IDEA
TO BRING THE EIGHT-SIX UP HERE,
IF I DO SAY SO.
- WHY DO YOU KEEP ON BABBLING?
- OKAY! BRING 'EM FORWARD GUYS!
COME ON!
- ( engines revving )
- COOL. I GOTCHA. WE GOT A
CLEAR ROAD AHEAD OF 'EM!
- I'LL START THE COUNTDOWN!
FIVE. FOUR. THREE. TWO. ONE. GO!
- WOW! THAT WAS A
HELLUVA FAST START!
- I HAVE ALL THE
FAITH IN THE WORLD
THAT KEISUKE'S GONNA
WIN THIS THING.
DON'T YOU FREAKIN' LOSE THIS.
IT'S NOT AN OPTION
ON OUR OWN TURF.
- MUST HAVE STARTED BY NOW.
RAIN TONIGHT.
THE FD'S BEST WEAPON IS
ITS HIGH CORNERING SPEED.
YOU CAN'T FORGET THAT
WHEN YOU'RE BATTLING KEISUKE.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- HEY TAKUMI.
DO YOU EVER GET THE FEELIN'
THAT MYOGI PASS HERE
IS ACTUALLY KINDA SIMILAR
TO AKINA PASS?
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
FOR ME, USUI PASS
SEEMS MORE LIKE AKINA
THAN ANYTHING ELSE
I'VE DRIVEN BEFORE.
- YOU'VE GONE INSANE.
IT'S NOTHING LIKE AKINA PASS.
THIS IS USELESS. HE'S TOTALLY
LOST IN THAT SEA OF DAYDREAMS.
'DUDE SERIOUSLY. COME ON. LOOK.
IT'S NOT NEAR AS NARROW AS USUI,
AND THE UPHILL IS JUST LIKE THE
UPHILL AT AKINA. ARE YOU BLIND?
- YOU'RE NOT TOTALLY WRONG.
I GUESS, THE RHYTHM
IS KINDA SIMILAR.
- THE RHYTHM?
- BE CAREFUL! YOU KNOW HOW QUICK
THE FD IS AROUND THE CORNERS.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D
FIND ANOTHER DRIVER
WHO'D BE ABLE TO FOLLOW ME
UP MYOGI'S HILL.
- HE'S STARTING TO
ABUSE HIS STEERING.
THAT'S JUST HIM TRYING TO
SPEED AWAY FROM ME.
IF HE DID THAT ON A DOWNHILL,
THE TIRES WOULD COMPRESS
IN NO TIME FLAT.
- INITIAL D!
- RYOSUKE, THEY JUST PASSED
THE MID-POINT.
THE THREE-TWO' IS IN FRONT.
I GOTTA TELL YA, THOUGH MAN,
THEY' ARE TIGHT.
- COURSE, THEY ARE.
TELL ME ONE OTHER THING.
HOW DID KEISUKE LOOK TO YOU
COMING OUT OF THE TURN?
- MAYBE 'BOUT A FRACTION
SLOWER THAN TAKASHEE.
BUT, OVERALL, HE'S UNDER CONTROL
AND MOVING SMOOTH.
JUST WHAT YOU'D EXPECT.
NOTHIN' LIKE TAKASHEE.
HE'S ALL OVER THE PLACE.
AGGRESSIVE AND INCONSISTENT.
- GREAT. THAT 'WAS ALL I NEEDED.
THANKS FOR CALLING IN.
THAT'S A DRAMATIC IMPROVEMENT
YOU'VE MADE, KEISUKE,
BEING ABLE TO HANDLE
YOURSELF LIKE THAT.
- Man: THE THREE-TWO
IS IN FRONT
BUT THESE GUY'S
ARE RIDIN' CLOSE!
I MEAN THEY JUST PASSED ME,
LOOKING LIKE ONE CAR.
NAKAZATO IS BARELY LEADIN'
AT THIS POINT.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE OUR
BOY'S MANAGING
TO HOLD HIS OWN OUT THERE.
- HE'S BEEN TRAINING HARDER THAN
I'VE EVER SEEN HIM BEFORE.
- HE TURNED INTO A DIFFERENT
GUY AFTER LOSING HIS ASS
TO THE EIGHT-SIX LIKE HE DID.
- I'VE ALWAYS CONSIDERED
TAKESHI TO BE MY ENEMY.
THAT'S NO SECRET.
BUT RIGHT NOW, JUST KNOWING THAT
HE'S FIGHTING FOR OUR PRIDE,
I FINALLY FEEL THIS BIT
OF CAMARADERIE
INCHING UP INSIDE FOR HIM.
NEVER FELT THIS BEFORE.
NOT FOR THAT GUY.
- I HAVE THE THREE-TWO
IN THE LEAD!
- RIGHT, TAKESHI! WIN THIS.
YOU CAN DO IT!
- ( tires screeching )
- I CAN HEAR THOSE SQUEALIN'
TIRES LOUDER THAN FIREWORKS,
BUT I CAN'T SEE THEM
ANYWHERE DOWN THERE.
- WAIT.
- WHAT'S UP?
- RAIN.
- ( rain pattering )
- OH, CRAP. AND THOSE
GUYS ARE OUT THERE
KICKIN' IT AT FULL SPEED!
- AND THE ROAD'S
DANGEROUS AS HELL
WHEN IT FIRST STARTS RAININ'.
THAT RAIN HITS THE ASPHALT
LIKE A SPONGE
AND SUCKS OUT
ALL THE DIRT AND OIL
MAKIN' IT SLICKER
THAN FRESH GREASE.
THEY COULD CRASH ANY SECOND.
- RAIN, GREAT. COULDN'T IT HAVE
WAITED 'TIL WE WERE DONE?
- I GOTTA BE ON MY GAME.
I COULD LOSE CONTROL WITHOUT
ANY WARNING IN THIS DOWNPOUR.
- DAMN, IT'S POURING.
I DIDN'T EXPECT THIS.
I HOPE THEY DON'T JUMP THE GUN
AND STOP THE RACE BECAUSE OF IT.
- ITSUKI, I GOT A QUESTION.
- YEAH?
- SINCE THAT'S THE FINISH LINE
OVER THERE,
THIS HAS GOTTA BE THE
LAST CORNER IN THE RACE, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- SO THAT'S THE HIGHEST
POINT IN MYOGI.
AND THIS OVER HERE.
THIS IS A DOWNHILL CORNER.
- IT'S THE ONLY DOWNHILL CORNER.
- ( tires screeching )
- THEY'RE COMIN' UP!
- THIS IS IT! HERE WE GO!
THAT'S SUICIDE. HE'S GONNA CRASH
INTO THE WALL AT THAT SPEED.
IF HE DOES,
HE COULD KILL BOTH OF US!
- I KNOW I CAN DO THIS.
I'M LISTENING TO MY FD,
AND SHE'S TELLING' ME I CAN!
♪ A DIAMOND LIFE
IS JUST WHAT I NEED ♪
♪ PLEASURE AND JOY FOREVER ♪
THEY'RE COMING RIGHT AT US!
♪ NO PLEASURE AND
PAIN TOGETHER ♪
♪ BUT YOU KNOW FOR SURE
THERE IS SOMETHING I MISS ♪
♪ 'COS I WOULD FORGET EVERYTHING
FOR A KISS ♪
♪ BUT IF YOU'VE GOT SOME MONEY
I KNOW IT WOULD BE BETTER ♪
- THE FD WON!
- KEISUKE TAKAHASHI KICKS ASS!
I GOTTA TELL YOU, I AM JUST
SO IMPRESSED WITH HIS DRIVING!
- THIS IS THE FIRST TIME THAT
I'VE EVER FOUND MYSELF
INSPIRED BY WATCHING
ANY OTHER RACERS.
STANDING HERE AND
WATCHING A RACE LIKE THAT
HAS MADE ME MORE
RESTLESS THAN EVER.
- YOU MAY HAVE WON THIS ONE,
BUT IT'S CUZ YOU GOT LUCKY.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
THAT WAS SKILL, DUDE.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- IN CASE YOU DIDN'T NOTICE,
THE LAST CORNER OF THE RACE
WAS ON THE DOWNHILL.
SO BEING WHO I AM I KNEW THAT
THAT CORNER WOULD COME DOWN
TO THE FRONT TIRES.
YOUR PROBLEM WAS, YOU COULDN'T
QUITE CONTROL THEM
CUZ THEY WERE TOO COMPRESSED.
I KEPT UP MY SPEED
AND IN DOING SO,
MAINTAINED MY TIRE PRESSURE
THROUGHOUT.
THAT'S WHY I'M TELLING YOU
IT WAS SKILL.
- WAY TO GO, KEISUKE!
YOU DID IT, MAN!
- SO YOU THINK WE SHOULD DO
A DOWNHILL RACE?
- WE CAN'T KEEP RUNNING IN
THIS RAIN. IT'S TOO HEAVY.
- RIGHT.
- WAIT, KEISUKE, BEFORE YOU
DECIDE TO CALL IT OFF
FOR THE NIGHT, WHY DON'T YOU
LET ME RACE THE EIGHT-SIX?
- DO WHAT?
- THIS ISN'T AKAGI MAN,
THIS ISN'T HIS HOME COURSE,
SO I FIGURE AS FAR AS FAIR GOES,
THIS IS AS CLOSE AS
IT'S GONNA GET.
- HEY!
- YO, WHAT'S UP?
- WHO IS THAT GUY
TALKIN' TO KEISUKE?
- NO IDEA.
- IT'S KENTA!
AND YOU'RE TAKUMI FUJIWARA,
THAT RIGHT?
I AM KENTA NAKAMURA
OF THE RED SUNS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO YOU AND ME
TAKIN' A LITTLE
SPIN IN THIS RAIN?
- WE GOTTA RUN THIS
BY MY BROTHER FIRST.
- MAYBE WE SHOULD ASK
THE PEOPLE HERE, KEISUKE.
SEE WHAT THEY WANNA SEE.
HOW ABOUT IT, FOLKS?
WANNA SEE ME TAKE ON THIS GUY?
BATTLE IT OUT IN THE RAIN?
- Crowd: ( whooping ) YEAH!
- WELL, THIS KINDA SUCKS.
IT'S HARD TO SAY NO
TO A SCREAMING MOB.
- BUT HE'S RACING AGAINST
RYOSUKE LIKE NEXT WEEK.
WHAT ABOUT THAT?
DO WE JUST IGNORE THAT?
- I'M STANDING HERE NOW.
AND IF YOU CAN'T BEAT ME,
THEN THERE'S NO REASON
YOU SHOULD EVEN BOTHER
WASTING A SECOND OF
RYOSUKE'S TIME.
WHAT DO YOU SAY? YOU IN?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I LOVE RACIN' IN THE RAIN.
DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE SCARED OF IT? ARE YA?
- NO, OF COURSE HE'S NOT.
HE'S JUST KINDA NOT BEEN
HIMSELF LATELY.
A LITTLE OUT OF SORTS.
SOMETIMES, IT'S LIKE
HE'S NOT EVEN HERE.
- SURE, WHY NOT. I'M IN.
- WOW!
- Crowd: ( cheering ) WHOA.
- HOLD IT.
- NO ONE CAN STOP IT NOW.
THE TRAIN'S LEFT THE STATION.
- BUT...
- GET OVER IT.
THAT EIGHT-SIX ISN'T ANYONE'S
PRIVATE TARGET TO TAKE DOWN.
HE'S THE TROPHY OF THE HOUR.
EVERY RACER WHO'S EVER HEARD
OF HIM WANTS A PIECE.
LIKE YOU. SHOULDN'T BE
SUCH AN ALIEN CONCEPT TO YOU.
- COOL, THEN,
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
WE'RE GOING DOWNHILL
IN THE RAIN,
AND WHAT'S GREAT ABOUT
THAT IS IT'LL MAKE IT A RACE
ABOUT PURE SKILL.
PUT YOUR KILLER EIGHT-SIX
RIGHT UP AGAINST MINE
AND SEE WHO COMES OUT ON TOP.
- LET'S GO, ITSUKI.
- I'M GOING WITH YOU?
IF I LEAVE YOU HERE,
THEN I'M JUST GONNA HAVE TO
COME BACK UP AFTERWARDS,
AND I DON'T WANNA DO THAT.
SO COME WITH ME, WE'LL RACE,
AND THEN WE CAN GO STRAIGHT
HOME ONCE ITS OVER.
- SO, I GUESS I'M GOING?
- THAT'S THE PLAN.
BUT DO YOU MIND, UH...
COULD YOU SIT IN THE BACK
WHILE I RACE?
- WHAT? THE BACK?
YEAH, SURE, I GUESS.
IS THIS SOME KIND OF STRATEGY?
- I DUNNO. MAYBE IT IS
AND MAYBE IT ISN'T.
BUT, I'LL LET YOU KNOW WHEN
I FIND OUT ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
- ARE YOU TELLIN' ME YOU
DON'T EVEN KNOW WHY
YOU GOT ME SITTIN' BACK HERE?
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO HOLD STILL
WHILE YOU'RE DRIFTIN' ALL
OVER THE ROAD? HUH?
TELL ME THAT!
- OH, I'M SURE YOU'LL
FIGURE IT OUT.
- THANKS FOR THE
VOTE OF CONFIDENCE.
IT'S ONLY FROM HERE TO THE
BOTTOM OF THE MOUNTAIN, MAN.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE GOT A ROAD TRIP
IN FRONT OF US.
- Man 1: DUDE 'IT'S NOT OVER!
THEY GOT ONE MORE
RACE STARTIN' UP.
- Man 2: YEAH, AND I HEAR ONE OF
THE CARS IS AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX!
- THIS IS IT. WE GOT NO ONCOMING
TRAFFIC. LET'S ROLL 'EM OUT!
- THIS IS SOMETHIN' I CERTAINLY
DIDN'T SEE COMIN' DOWN THE PIPE.
- YEAH. AND THERE'S NOT A DAMN
THING WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ME, KEISUKE.
REALLY, DRIVIN' IN THE RAIN
IS ONE OF MY FAVORITE THINGS.
BEFORE I JOINED UP WITH THE
TEAM I WAITED FOR RAINY DAYS
ON PURPOSE TO
PRACTICE MY DRIVING.
THAT WAS MY FAVORITE TIME
TO GET ON THE ROAD
AND WORK MY DRIFTING TECHNIQUE.
THE RAIN ACTUALLY DOES
A GOOD JOB OF KEEPIN' THE TIRES
FROM GETTING WORN OUT TOO FAST.
- IT'S GOOD YOU GOT
ALL THIS CONFIDENCE
BUT DON' TAKE THIS
RACE TOO LIGHTLY.
- I'M JUST SAYIN' I'M MOST
EXPERIENCED IN THE RAIN.
AND I SURE AS HELL KNOW
I'M BETTER THAN THIS SUCKER
IN THIS KINDA WEATHER.
KNOW WHY?
CUZ THIS RAINIS ON MY SIDE.
- HEY, UH TAKUMI. YOU DON'T LOOK
LIKE YOU'RE READY FOR THIS.
YOU SURE YOU'RE GONNA BE
COOL DOIN' YOUR THING
IN ALL THIS FREAKIN' RAIN?
I MEAN I NEVER SEEN
YOU DO IT BEFORE.
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
I CAN'T GO TOO FAST IN THE RAIN,
SO I GUESS I'LL JUST
DRIVE NORMALLY
TO START AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
I CAN'T SAY YET IF I'M GONNA BE
FAST OR SLOW OUT THERE
UNDER THESE CONDITIONS.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
I'M GONNA TAKE IT EASY,
CUZ IF I CRASHED THIS CAR,
MY DAD'S GONNA CUT OF MY HEAD
AND USE MY SKULL FOR AN ASHTRAY.
- YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT THERE.
- ( gasps ) BUT IF HE LOSES
THIS RACE, THEN IT'S ALL OVER!
HE'LL NEVER GET HIS CHANCE
TO RACE AGAINST THE GREAT
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
- HERE'S THE COUNTDOWN, BOYS!
FIVE! FOUR. THREE. TWO. ONE. GO!
- ( screaming )
THIS IS NOT NORMAL DRIVING!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Announcer: YOU REALLY SEEM
CONFIDENT IN THIS RAIN, KENTA.
- Kenta: I SURE AM.
I'VE DONE IT A LOT.
AND I'LL WIN THIS CUZ I GOT
KEISUKE WATCHING ME.
- Announcer: BUT YOU'RE AWARE
THAT EVEN KEISUKE
LOST TO THIS EIGHT-SIX.
- Kenta: WHICH IS WHY I'M HERE.
I'M AVENGING THAT
LOSS FOR KEISUKE!
- Announcer: AND THIS IS YOUR
FIRST TIME ON THIS COURSE.
- Kenta: NO PROBLEM FOR ME.
I GOTTA GIVE IT MY BEST FOR HIM.
- Announcer: KENTA, DO YOU HAVE
SOME KIND OF PENT UP FEELINGS
FOR KEISUKE?
- Kenta: I, UH...
NEXT ON INITIAL D,
"THE RAINY DOWNHILL!"
DON'T MISS IT!