- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- ( tires screeching )
- ( groans )
- Iketani: CRAP!
GO TO THE INSIDE!
NO!
- ( crashing )
- Suv Driver: THAT WAS THE
CRAZIEST DRIVING I'VE EVER SEEN!
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
OH, NO! KID, YOU ALRIGHT?
JUST HANG IN THERE!
I'LL GET YOU SOME HELP!
- I'M SORRY.
IT WAS ALL MY FAULT.
I'M SO...
- JUST KEEP IT
TOGETHER, OKAY?
I'M CALLING AN AMBULANCE
RIGHT NOW!
- ( screams ) WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
IKETANI WRECKED HIS CAR?
WHEN DID THAT HAPPEN?
- LAST NIGHT. HE SLAMMED INTO A
GUARDRAIL DOING A DOWNHILL RUN.
- THAT SUCKS. WAS HE HURT?
- YEAH, BUT HE'LL PULL THROUGH.
CUTS AND BRUISES.
MINOR CASE OF WHIPLASH.
YOU KNOW, THE USUAL,
BUT MAINLY, HE'S JUST
REALLY PISSED OFF
ABOUT THE WHOLE THING.
I HADN'T SEEN IT, BUT I HEARD
HIS CAR GOT PRETTY JACKED UP.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT THE BATTLE
ON SATURDAY?
HE'S SUPPOSED TO
ANCHOR THE RACE.
- WELL, I GUESS
THAT'S IN THE TOILET.
WE GOTTA FIND A SUB-IN FOR HIM
NOW. I JUST DON'T KNOW WHO.
- WELCOME, SIR. OH, IKETANI?
HEY, ARE YOU SURE YOU SHOULD
BE UP AND WALKING AROUND?
- YEAH, DOC SAID IT'S OKAY.
SO HOW'S MY CAR DOIN'?
- STILL IN THE BACK GARAGE.
WE HAVEN'T DONE
ANYTHING TO HER YET.
OUR HANDS ARE TIED UNTIL
ALL THE PARTS ARE SHIPPED.
- EXCUSE ME? CAN I GET
SOME FRIED TOFU PLEASE?
- Bunta: SURE. BE RIGHT THERE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- JUST A LITTLE ACCIDENT.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BATTLE HERE PRETTY SOON.
WHAT DO YOU PLAN ON DOING?
- THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
I WANTED TO ASK YOU FOR A FAVOR.
- OH, YEAH?
- YEAH.
THE BATTLE'S ON SATURDAY.
I'D LIKE FOR YOU
TO DRIVE IN MY PLACE.
I'M BEGGING YOU.
I NEED YOUR HELP.
( grunting )
MY FREAKIN' NECK, MAN!
- DON'T DIE HERE.
- MR. FUJIWARA, YOU REMEMBER
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
TO BE A STREET RACER.
YOU KNOW I CAN'T LET THOSE
OUTSIDERS BEAT US HERE.
- OF COURSE I UNDERSTAND.
BUT IF SOME OLD GEEZER LIKE ME
SHOWED UP WITH ALL THOSE KIDS,
THEY'D THINK I WAS SENILE.
- I'VE SPENT MY LIFE RACING
THOSE CURVES ON AKINA.
RIGHT NOW THE RED SUNS
ARE MAKING ALL OF OUR DRIVERS
LOOK LIKE UNLICENSED
SCHOOL KIDS.
IT'S PISSIN' ME OFF!
I CAN'T LET THIS GO ON!
I WANNA SHOW THEM THAT
AKINA'S GOT MORE THAN THAT!
THAT WE'VE GOT
DRIVERS UP HERE
WITH SKILLS LIKE
THEY'VE NEVER SEEN!
YOU CAN DO THAT! YOU'VE
ALREADY DEFEATED THEIR FASTEST,
THE YOUNGER TAKAHASHI BROTHER.
THIS'D BE NOTHIN' FOR YOU.
I DON'T HAVE ANYONE ELSE
TO TURN TO!
- ( car honks )
- CAN'T YOU SEE THE LIGHTS
ARE OFF. WE'RE ALREADY CLOSED!
- AH, SHUT UP GREASE MONKEY.
FILL HER UP WITH HIGH OCTANE.
- YOU'RE CRAZY IF YOU THINK
I'LL DUMP GOOD HIGH OCTANE
IN THIS OLD EIGHT-SIX!
- HAD TO BE YOU.
WHO ELSE WOULD'VE TOLD THAT KID
ALL THOSE OLD STORIES ABOUT ME?
- YEAH, IT WAS ME.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
I WAS LYING ABOUT IT.
I JUST COULDN'T SEE
THE HARM IN TELLING HIM.
- HE CAME INTO MY STORE TODAY
WITH A BANDAGE AROUND HIS HEAD
AND A NECK BRACE ON
ASKING ME TO DRIVE IN HIS PLACE
AT A BATTLE SATURDAY NIGHT.
GOTTA SAY, I WAS
ACTUALLY A LITTLE FLATTERED.
- IF YOU WERE FLATTERED,
THEN GO FOR IT.
NOT LIKE YOU'VE GOT OTHER PLANS.
I KNOW THE KID.
HE'S GOOD PEOPLE.
- NO, THANKS.
STICKING YOUR NOSE
INTO THESE KIDDIE FIGHTS
IS A GOOD WAY
TO GET IT KNOCKED OFF.
ANYWAY THAT'S NOT MY STYLE.
- SO... THEN IT WOULDN'T BE A
PROBLEM IF ANOTHER KID SHOWED UP
FOR THE KIDDIE FIGHT?
- WHAT... YOU MEAN TAKUMI?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THE KID'S DEVELOPING
SOME REAL SKILL.
- YEAH, BUT HE'S STILL GOT
A WAYS TO GO.
IF IT'S AKINA'S DOWNHILL
HE'S RACING ON,
THEN IT'S FOR DAMN SURE
HE WOULDN'T LOSE TO ANYONE.
WELL, ANYONE EXCEPT ME.
- ALWAYS THE COMPETITIVE SPIRIT.
- TAKUMI'S THE SAME WAY. BUT HE
WON'T GET OUT THERE AND RACE
UNLESS HE WANTS
TO DO IT FOR HIMSELF,
AND HE SURE AS HELL WON'T GO
IF I SAY I WANT HIM TO.
BUT SEEING IKETANI ALL BEAT
UP MADE ME FEEL BAD
FOR SOME REASON.
MIGHT BE WORTH TRYING.
- ( news report playing )
- THIS COUNTS AS A VERBAL
CONTRACT, I HOPE YOU REALIZE.
IF THERE'S ANYTHING
I HATE MORE THAN SMOKERS,
AND I HATE SMOKERS,
IT'S PEOPLE WHO CAN'T
KEEP THEIR WORD.
- HEY, DAD. I WAS THINKING I'D
TAKE THE CAR OUT THIS SUNDAY
IF IT'S COOL BY YOU.
- NOPE. NOT THIS
SUNDAY YOU CAN'T.
- WHY NOT?
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THE MORNING
DELIVERY AND EVERYTHING,
JUST LIKE I ALWAYS DO.
- OH, I KNOW YOU WILL.
THAT'S NOT THE ISSUE.
I GOTTA USE THE CAR TO GO TO A
TOWN MEETING I HAVE ON SUNDAY.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
YOUR TIMING SUCKS.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW MUCH
I NEEDED THE CAR THIS WEEKEND.
- ( grunts )
MUST BE ABOUT A GIRL, HUH?
- THAT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
COME ON. QUIT BEING SUCH A PAIN
AND LET ME TAKE IT OUT.
IT'S JUST
A CRAPPY OLD CAR ANYWAY.
AND I'LL TAKE IT IF I WANT TO.
- THAT CAR ISN'T GOING ANYWHERE
WITHOUT A KEY.
AND THAT KEY IS GONNA BE
ON A STRING AROUND MY NECK.
- WHAT'S YOUR DEAL?
- FINE. YOU WANT IT THAT BAD,
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
- THANKS, DAD.
- ON JUST ONE CONDITION.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- GO TO AKINA THIS SATURDAY,
FIND SOME PUNK IN AN FD PEOPLE
SAY IS THE FASTEST ON AKAGI.
AND BEAT THE FIRE OUT OF HIM.
- HOLD ON, YOU WANT ME TO...
WHAT?
- DO THAT, AND I'LL LET YOU TAKE
THE CAR OUT, NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
I'LL EVEN PUT A FULL TANK
OF GAS IN HER FOR YOU.
- A FULL TANK OF GAS?
WOW, A FULL TANK.
THAT'S TOO GOOD AN OFFER
TO WALK AWAY FROM.
AFTER ALL, I AM DEAD BROKE.
- SO? WHAT'S THE VERDICT?
I'M GONNA NEED A FEW MINUTES
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
- YOU TAKE ALL THE TIME
YOU NEED TO, BUDDY.
- ( sighs )
- ( knocking on door )
- I'M COMING IN.
- KEISUKE, PERFECT TIMING.
I HAD A QUESTION I WANTED
TO ASK YOU.
- YEAH, SURE.
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
- THE EIGHT-SIX
THAT YOU RAN INTO
WHEN YOU WERE DRIVING ON AKINA.
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD DESCRIBE
THE SPEED OF THE CAR,
THEORETICALLY SPEAKING?
- SERIOUSLY? COME ON, GIMME A
BREAK, BRO... I'M NOT LIKE YOU.
I CAN'T RATTLE THAT KINDA CRAP
OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD.
- LIKE I'VE ALWAYS SAID,
THE MOST IMPORTANT INSTRUMENT
WHEN IT COMES TO DRIVING
TECHNIQUE IS RIGHT HERE.
- ALL I KNOW IS THAT WHENEVER
YOU'RE BATTLING SOMEONE
YOU CAN LEARN PRETTY
MUCH WHATEVER YOU NEED
BY DRIVING BEHIND 'EM.
YOU CAN GET A GOOD GAUGE ON
THEIR HABITS, THEIR WEAKNESSES.
EVEN HOW THEIR
SUSPENSION IS SET UP.
HOW YOU GET ALL THAT STUFF OUT
OF YOUR COMPUTER SIMULATIONS,
I'LL NEVER KNOW.
- IN MY OPINION, THE FACT
YOU CAN GET OUT THERE
AND DRIVE THE WAY YOU DO
WITHOUT THINKING ABOUT IT
AND STILL KEEP UP WITH ME
MAKES YOU THE SCARY ONE.
IF YOU COULD JUST APPLY
THEORIES TO YOUR SKILLS,
YOU'D BE THE PERFECT
DRIVER.
- I ONLY LOST BECAUSE
I WAS CARELESS
AND I DIDN'T KNOW THE ROAD.
THAT'S ALL IT WAS.
I'VE NEVER BEEN EMBARRASSED
LIKE THAT BEFORE.
I'M TELLING YOU, THAT EIGHT-SIX
HAS SOME KIND OF A MONSTER
UNDER THE HOOD.
- A MONSTER, YOU SAY?
THIS GETS MORE INTERESTING
BY THE SECOND.
MAYBE I ACTUALLY SHOULD SHOW UP
AND SEE HOW THE BATTLE GOES.
- ( bells chiming )
- TAKUMI!
( laughs )
IT'S SATURDAY!
THE BIG DAY IS HERE!
- OKAY, WHAT'S TODAY?
- ( groans )
WHAT DO YOU MEAN WHAT'S TODAY?
IT'S THE DAY OF THE BATTLE
BETWEEN THE AKAGI RED SUNS AND
THE AKINA SPEED STARS!
YOU SAID YOU WERE GONNA
BORROW THE EIGHT-SIX
SO WE COULD WATCH 'EM
THROW DOWN, REMEMBER!
- WELL... I WANTED TO TALK TO
YOU ABOUT THAT. IT'S JUST
THAT IT'S GOTTEN A LITTLE
MORE COMPLICATED.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU HAD BETTER NOT BE
TELLIN' ME THAT
YOU'RE GONNA BAIL ON ME 'CAUSE
YOU DON'T HAVE TIME!
- TIME DOESN'T HAVE
A THING TO DO WITH IT.
LIKE I SAID, IT'S COMPLICATED.
- YOU BACK OUT ON ME AND
I'M STUCK HERE TONIGHT,
YOU CAN KISS OUR
FRIENDSHIP GOODBYE!
I'VE COUNTED THE DAYS, HOURS,
AND MINUTES UNTIL THIS RACE.
I CAN'T WAIT.
I'M CHOMPIN' AT THE BIT HERE!
- REALLY, I COULDN'T TELL.
- SHOPOWNER!
BOX OF FRIED TOFU.
- WELL, WHADDYA KNOW, IT'S THE
RETURN OF THE MUMMY...
YOU SURE ARE A PERSISTENT ONE,
AREN'T YOU?
- I STILL HAVEN'T GIVEN UP ON
TRYING TO CONVINCE YOU
TO RACE FOR ME TONIGHT.
- I THOUGHT IT OVER AND I MIGHT
RACE FOR YOU.
- YOU HEARD ME SAY MIGHT, AND
THAT'S ALL YOU HEARD ME SAY,
I MIGHT RACE FOR YOU.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA REGRET THIS!
( groans ) MY NECK, AGAIN...
- REMEMBER WHAT I SAID
ABOUT DYING IN MY SHOP.
- WAIT... SO YOU'RE REALLY GONNA
SHOW UP TONIGHT?
- I'M NOT MAKING YOU A
PINKY-SWEAR...
BUT YOU CAN COUNT ON ABOUT
A FIFTY-FIFTY CHANCE
OF ME SHOWING UP...
WHAT TIME DOES
THIS PARTY KICK OFF?
- EVERYBODY SHOWS UP
ABOUT EIGHT.
BUT THE TIME ATTACK STARTS AT
TEN ON THE NOSE.
- TEN O'CLOCK SHARP.
IF YOU HAVEN'T SEEN THE
EIGHT-SIX SHOW BY TEN,
YOU CAN STOP WAITING.
ANY LATER THAN THAT AND
IT'LL BE UP TO YOU
TO CLINCH THE WIN FOR AKINA.
- UNTIL THEN, I'LL BE
WAITING ON YOU, SIR.
I GOT ALL THE FAITH IN THE
WORLD THAT YOU'LL SHOW UP.
- IT'S NOT FOR SURE, KID.
I SAID FIFTY-FIFTY.
- THAT'S WRONG.
I CAN TELL YOU'VE ALREADY
DECIDED YOU'LL BE THERE.
AND OUR TEAM WILL BE THERE TO
CHEER YOU ON THE WHOLE WAY.
SO, MR. FUJIWARA, GUESS WE'LL BE
SEEING YOU AT THE TOP OF AKINA
AT TEN O'CLOCK SHARP.
( door closes )
- I CAN'T FIND IT IN ME TO
BE MEAN TO SUCH AN EAGER KID...
I WONDER IF I SHOULD GO
UP THERE IF TAKUMI WON'T...
NAH, I'LL STAY HERE. I'M JUST
EXCITED FOR 'EM.
- INITIAL D!
- ( car honking )
- The Man : YOU HAVE A GOOD
DAY TODAY, SWEETHEART?
YOU SEEM... DIFFERENT. BRIGHTER.
- REALLY? I DO? I THOUGHT I WAS
ALWAYS CHEERFUL AROUND YOU?
- THERE'S SOMETHING MORE,
I CAN TELL.
- ACTUALLY, I'M SUPPOSED
TO TAKE
A ROAD TRIP TO THE BEACH WITH
A FRIEND OF MINE TOMORROW.
I'M REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO IT.
- FRIEND, EH? IS IT A BOY?
- WHAT? NO. IT'S JUST
A GIRLFRIEND OF MINE.
I'VE KNOWN HER FOR YEARS.
- OH. WELL, IN THAT CASE, WHY
DON'T WE GO TO THE MALL?
WE CAN GET YOU A NEW BATHING
SUIT TO SHOW YOU OFF.
- OH, NO, THAT'S ALRIGHT.
I ALREADY HAVE ONE BATHING SUIT.
I CAN'T IMAGINE WHY
I WOULD NEED TWO OF 'EM.
- BUT I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU TRY A
FEW OF THEM ON, AT LEAST.
- YOU'RE FUNNY, YOU KNOW?
YOU'VE SEEN ME IN A
BATHING SUIT BEFORE.
YOU'VE GOT A ONE TRACK
MIND, DON'T YOU?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, ITSUKI?
IS IT GONNA BE SUNNY TOMORROW?
- WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE?
THE WEATHERMAN?
DON'T ASK ME
STUPID CRAP LIKE THAT.
THE WEATHER'S
GREAT THIS TIME OF YEAR.
WHY? YOU PLANNING ON
GOIN' SOMEWHERE?
- YEAH, TO THE BEACH.
- THE BEACH?
WHAT?
I WANNA GO TO THE BEACH!
WHY DIDN'T YOU ASK ME TO
GO WITH YOU? HUH?
WAIT... YOU'RE GOING WITH A
CHICK AREN'T YOU? JERK!
- YEAH, KINDA.
- WHO IS IT? DO I KNOW HER?
IS SHE CUTE?
DOES SHE HAVE BIG KNOCKERS
OR MAYBE A HOT AVAILABLE
SISTER?
- NO SISTER, BUT SHE'S CUTE.
- NO... NOT NATSUKI?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME.
- SORRY, BUT IT'S NOT EXACTLY
THE KIND OF SITUATION
WHERE I COULD HAVE
INVITED A FRIEND,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
MAYBE NEXT
TIME, OKAY?
- ( crying )
- YOU DON'T HAVE
TO CRY ABOUT IT.
- SO WHATTYA THINK'S
GONNA HAPPEN TONIGHT?
I HEARD THE RED SUNS HAVE
NEVER LOST A BATTLE,
AT HOME OR ON THE ROAD.
DOESN'T SOUND TOO GOOD FOR
THESE SPEED STAR CHARACTERS.
- NOT LIKE THERE'S
ANY BIG MYSTERY
ABOUT WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
AKINA'S GOING DOWN.
IT'S PRETTY MUCH
COMMON KNOWLEDGE
THAT THE FASTEST TEAM IN GOONMA
ISN'T THE DAMN RED SUNS,
IT'S THE ME-OH-GEE NIGHT KIDS.
- IT'S ABOUT THAT TIME, TAKESHI.
- THEN LET'S GO.
THIS CAR WAS DESIGNED
FOR PURE SPEED.
A REAL THOROUGHBRED.
THE R32.
AKAGI'S ROTARIES
DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT.
THE MOUNTAIN'S LIT UP
LIKE NEW YEAR'S TONIGHT.
RUMORS ABOUT THIS BATTLE
BETWEEN IKETANI'S TEAM
AND THIS TEAM THAT'S
CALLING THEMSELVES
THE FASTEST ON MOUNT AKAGI
SEEM TO HAVE
SPREAD FROM COAST TO COAST.
WONDER WHO'S TAKING
HOME THE GOLD?
I MEAN, TAKUMI'S EIGHT-SIX IS
ACTUALLY BUNTA'S EIGHT-SIX.
AND BUNTA'S
EIGHT-SIX CAN'T LOSE.
IT FEELS GOOD TO BE EXCITED
ABOUT A RACE AGAIN.
- ( tires screeching )
- WOW, THERE'S SO
MANY PEOPLE UP HERE.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN THIS SIZE A
GALLERY HERE IN MY LIFE.
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
- THE RED SUNS BROUGHT 'EM OUT
HERE TO SHOW OFF, INTIMIDATE US,
FORCE US INTO A MISTAKE.
WE LOSE TONIGHT,
WE'LL LOOK LIKE THE BIGGEST
BUNCH OF BONEHEADS.
- SO, UH, IKETANI, THAT EIGHT-
SIX YOU WERE TELLIN' US ABOUT...
DO YOU REALLY THINK
IT'S GONNA SHOW UP?
- YES!
- ALL I KNOW IS IF
I WAS THAT EIGHT-SIX,
I'D STAY AS FAR AWAY FROM THIS
PLACE AS I COULD.
I HEARD KEISUKE'S FD THREE-S
IS ONLY LIGHTLY TUNED
FOR MOUNTAIN DRIVING.
NOT LIKE IT MATTERS
FROM WHAT I'VE HEARD,
'CAUSE EVERYONE SAYS
IT'S KICKIN' OUT
LIKE OVER THREE
HUNDRED AND FIFTY HP.
THERE'S TOO MUCH OF A POWER
DIFFERENCE.
- EVEN ON THE DOWNHILL,
THE EIGHT-SIX COULD NEVER
COMPETE WITH THAT KINDA POWER.
HOW HARD YOU'D SMACK YOUR HEAD
WHEN YOU WRECKED ANYWAY, MAN?
- AN EIGHT-SIX IS JUST AN
EIGHT-SIX, YEAH.
BUT THIS ONE'S NOT NORMAL.
KEISUKE SAID IT HIMSELF.
ON THE OUTSIDE, THE THING'S
A NORMAL PANDA TRUENO,
BUT ON THE INSIDE, IT'S A BEAST
LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN.
TRUST ME, GUYS. HE'LL SHOW.
- AND IF HE DOESN'T?
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO THEN?
- THERE'RE MORE PEOPLE UP HERE
WATCHING THAN I'VE EVER SEEN
WATCH ANYTHING AND I CAN'T HAVE
THEM SAYIN' WE BACKED OUT...
- BUT IF HE DOESN'T SHOW...
- THAT'S WHAT I ASKED...
- I WANT YOU TO REPRESENT US
AND DRIVE LIKE YOUR LIFE
DEPENDED ON IT, GOT ME?
- YOU GOTTA BE OUTTA
YOUR FREAKIN' MIND, DUDE!
- HEY, I THINK I HEAR
'EM COMING NOW!
- YEAH, THOSE ROTARIES
ARE KICKIN' HARD, AREN'T THEY?
- ( engines sounding )
- THE RED SUNS ARE HERE!
- THIS NIGHT'S ABOUT
TO GET PRETTY WILD, MAN!
- TOOK 'EM LONG ENOUGH.
- ( engines revving loudly )
- ( crowd cheering wildly )
- I NEVER REALIZED HOW POPULAR
THE TAKAHASHI BROTHERS ARE.
- YEAH, I HEARD THEIR DAD OWNS A
BIG HOSPITAL IN TAKASAKI,
SO YOU KNOW THEY GOT
CASH TO BURN.
- WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST RICH GUYS...
OTHER THAN TIME SPENT
BEHIND THE WHEEL,
DRIVING SKILL IS BASED
ON NOTHING MORE
THAN HOW MUCH DOUGH YOU CAN DROP
ON GASOLINE AND TIRES.
- ( dog howling )
- WHAT'S TAKING TAKUMI
SO LONG?
THE BATTLE IS PROBABLY
STARTING AS WE SPEAK.
HE KNOWS WHERE TO PICK ME UP AND
WHAT TIME I'D BE HERE!
WHAT AN ASS! I HATE THAT GUY!
I'M GONNA KICK HIM SQUARE IN
THE NUTS WHEN I SEE HIM!
I CAN'T WAIT ANYMORE!
I GOTTA GO!
I'LL JUST TAKE MY
STUPID SCOOTER IF I HAVE TO!
- LET'S BEGIN THE TIME ATTACK
AT TEN O'CLOCK,
ACCORDING
TO THE SCHEDULE.
IT'LL BE LATE ENOUGH
SO THERE SHOULD BE
FEWER CONVENTIONAL
CARS ON THE ROAD.
WE'LL USE RADIOS AT THE START
AND AT THE FINISH LINE SO WE CAN
COORDINATE AND TIME THE RUNS.
ALSO IN ORDER TO ALLOW THE
DRIVERS TO CUT LOOSE
AND GO AS FAST AS THEY WANT,
WE'LL PUT OFFICIALS
AT ALL OF THE BLIND CORNERS.
IN THE EVENT OF ANY
ONCOMING TRAFFIC,
WE'LL USE LIGHTS TO SIGNAL
THE DRIVERS.
- SOUND LIKE A PLAN?
- WORKS FOR ME.
- I'M GETTING' THE FEELIN'
THEY'VE DONE THIS BEFORE.
- NO JOKE. THEY PROB'LY RUN THIS
TIME ATTACK GAMBIT
ALL OVER THE REGION.
- NOW WE'VE GOTTEN ALL OF THE
PROTOCOL OUT OF THE WAY,
LET'S TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE
TIME AND ENJOY SOME FREE RUNS
UNTIL TEN O'CLOCK HITS.
THE GALLERIES ARE PACKED.
- ( cars starting )
- WHERE'S THE EIGHT-SIX?
I FIGURED IT'D BE HERE.
- I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF THEY WERE TRYING
TO KEEP THEIR SECRET
WEAPON UNDER WRAPS
UNTIL THE BIG
REVEAL AT THE START.
- WHAT'S UP? THINKING ABOUT
HEADING UP THERE?
- NAH, I'M THINKIN' I DON'T
REALLY WANNA GO.
- WHY NOT? THINK YOU'LL LOSE?
'CAUSE IF SO, JUST LOOSEN UP,
DRIVE LIKE YOU USUALLY DO.
YOU'LL DO FINE.
- HEY GUYS! IT'S HERE!
KEISUKE'S FD THREE-S!
♪ DON'T STOP THE MUSIC ♪
♪ MUSIC ♪
♪ DON'T STOP ♪
- SWEET! YOU SEE HOW FAST
HE WENT INTO THAT CORNER?
RYOSUKE'S RIGHT BEHIND HIM!
♪ DON'T STOP THE MUSIC TONIGHT ♪
- LOOK OUT! MOVE IT!
- ( tires screeching )
- WELL, THAT'S
RYOSUKE FOR YOU...
A REAL SHOW OFF WITH THE SKILLS
TO BACK IT UP.
♪ JUMPING WITH EMOTION ♪
♪ CRAZY LOCOMOTION ♪
♪ MOVE AND DANCE
AND TAKE MY FEELING ♪
♪ JUMP AND GO ♪
♪ THE POWER OF THE NIGHT ♪
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY CAN GET
THEIR CARS THAT CLOSE TO EACH
OTHER WITHOUT TOUCHING!
- THAT'S THEIR SIGNATURE!
THE PARALLEL DRIFT!
- APPROACHING THE OTHER CAR AT
FULL TILT IS THE TOUGHEST PART,
BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T
HAVE THE DRIVING SKILLS
TO CHANGE YOUR SPEED AND
YOUR LINE DURING THE DRIFT,
THERE'S NO WAY YOU'RE
GONNA BE ABLE TO PULL IT OFF.
♪ YOU CAN SHOW YOUR EMOTION ♪
♪ YOUR SECRET SIDE
ALL THE NIGHT ♪
BUT WHAT THOSE GUYS'RE
DOING NOW IS JUST FOR SHOW.
WHEN YOU'RE
COMPETING FOR BEST TIME,
IT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT STORY.
- ( tires screeching )
- COME ON OUT, GHOST OF AKINA!
I'VE GOT A RACE TONIGHT,
AND YOU'RE THE OTHER HALF!
SHOW YOURSELF, EIGHT-SIX.
- ( engine revving )
♪ JUMPING WITH EMOTION ♪
♪ CRAZY LOCOMOTION ♪
♪ MOVE AND DANCE
AND TAKE MY FEELING ♪
♪ JUMP AND GO ♪
♪ THE POWER OF THE NIGHT ♪
- DO YOU WANT ME TO TAKE THE
PAPER CUP WITH ME TONIGHT?
- YOU DON'T NEED IT. THERE'S
NOT ANY TOFU IN BACK,
AND YOU'RE OFF THE CLOCK
'TIL MORNING.
THIS ISN'T A REGULAR DELIVERY,
SO DRIVE THIS OLD BIRD AS
HARD AS YOU CAN.
- DON'T FORGET, IT'S A FULL
TANK OF GAS WHEN I WIN.
- WE'LL TALK WHEN YOU EARN IT.
- FINE. I'LL SEE YOU
WHEN I GET BACK.
- YEP.
♪ DON'T STOP THE MUSIC TONIGHT ♪
♪ DON'T STOP THE MUSIC ♪
♪ MUSIC ♪
♪ DON'T STOP THE MUSIC TONIGHT ♪
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
♪ TO DREAM MY DREAM! ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
♪ NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- OKAY, LADIES AND GENTS,
YOU'RE IN FOR A REAL TREAT.
TODAY'S GUEST IS FAMOUS
FOR HIS AGGRESSIVE DRIVING.
A MEMBER OF THE RED SUNS,
KAY-SKAY TOCKAHASHI...
- GIVE ME THAT!
HURRY UP AND SHOW YOURSELF,
GHOST OF AKINA!
OR DID YOU GET SCARED
AND RUN OFF?
- SO, DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL WIN THIS TIME?
- SHUT UP! 'COURSE I WILL!
WHATEVER IT TAKES, I
WILL GET MY REVENGE!
- NEXT TIME ON INITIAL D,
FINALLY, "INTO THE BATTLE!"
WHO WILL WIN?
IT'S A HIGH TENSION BATTLE
BETWEEN THE FD AND EIGHT-SIX!
DON'T MISS IT!