- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- WHAT'S GOING ON? IT'S LIKE
I'M SUFFOCATING I'M SO TENSE.
MOUNT AKINA IS CALLING MY NAME.
I'VE NEVER WANTED TO GET BEHIND
THE WHEEL OF THAT CAR
SO MUCH IN MY LIFE.
AM I LOSING MY MIND?
NO ONE KNOWS THAT PASS
LIKE I DO.
I'VE DRIVEN THAT THING
RAIN OR SHINE EVERY DAY
FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
IT'S BECOME A PART OF ME.
- ( engine revving )
I'LL SEE YA LATER. THANKS
FOR BEIN' ALL COOL
WITH ME TAKIN' THE
CAR OUT TONIGHT.
I OWE YOU.
TAKUMI. WE'D BETTER PUT THE
PEDAL TO METAL.
WE'VE DON'T HAVE
A WHOLE LOT OF TIME LEFT.
- Man: HEADS UP, THERE HE IS!
- ( exclaims in horror )
- IT'S TOO LATE!
THEY'VE LOCKED IN ON ME!
THERE'S NOWHERE TO HIDE NOW
GOODBYE, CRUEL WORLD.
- ( car approaching )
- HEY ITSUKI. WHAT'S GOIN ON?
YOU MIND GETTIN' OUT OF THE WAY
OR DO I HAVE TO RUN OVER YA?
TA. TA.
DUDE, SERIOUSLY. GET OUT OF
THE WAY. YOU WANNA DIE?
- ( laughs )
- TAKUMI! I'M SO HAPPY
YOU'RE HERE!
- YEAH. MY BAD. I'M LATE.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- IT'S OKAY. I'M...
- IT'S LIKE YOU SAID.
I'M A STREET RACER AND
I'VE BEEN CHALLENGED.
SO, THIS IS WHERE I'M
SUPPOSED TO BE. RIGHT?
- ( crying ) THANK YOU. TAKUMI!
- HEY, DON'T SNOT ALL OVER ME!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- MAN, THIS DUDE'S JUST A KID.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF HE'S HAD HIS LICENSE
FOR LESS THAN A YEAR NOW.
HE CAN'T HAVE TOO MUCH
EXPERIENCE UNDER HIS BELT.
HOW'D HE LEARN HIS TECHNIQUE?
GO-CARTS?
CRAZY. I WOULDA FIGURED I'D BE
FACING SOMEONE OLDER THAN ME.
- SO THAT'S A GT-R.
- GOOD DOESN'T EVEN COME CLOSE.
IN A CLASS BY ITSELF.
IT'S TOP OF THE LINE
DRIVING SYSTEM
MERGES EVERY PERFECT
THING ABOUT THE FR
AND THE FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE.
MAKES IT AN UNSTOPPABLE BEAST.
- I'M TAKESHI OF THE NIGHT KIDS.
YOU GOT A NAME, DONTCHA KID?
- IT'S TAKUMI FUJIWARA.
- I'LL REMEMBER THAT. FUJIWARA.
LET'S GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
- ( people chattering )
- SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT A HEAVY
UNDERSTEER DURING FULL THROTTLE
IS A BETTER SETTING IF YOU HAVE
THE SKILLS TO HANDLE IT.
MAKES SENSE. BUT IF THE CAR
STARTS HANDLING DIFFERENTLY
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
TAKUMI COULD PANIC WHEN
HE'S PUSHIN' INTO THE CORNERS!
DON'T YOU THINK IT WOULD'VE
BEEN A WISE DECISION
TO WARN HIM ABOUT
IT AHEAD OF TIME?
- Bunta: I COULD HAVE
BUT IT WOULDN'T
HAVE MADE A DIFFERENCE.
TAKUMI'S NOT EXACTLY WHAT
YOU'D CALL A CEREBRAL DRIVER,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- Yuuichi: WHAT? THAT'S REASON
ENOUGH TO TELL HIM ABOUT IT!
- JUST WAIT AND SEE, YUUICHI,
IT'LL BE ALRIGHT.
I KNOW MY SON MIGHT NOT BE
THE SHARPEST KNIFE IN THE DRAWER
WHEN IT COMES TO USING HIS HEAD.
BUT THE BOY HAS
CAT-LIKE REFLEXES,
AND THAT'S WHAT WINS RACES.
THERE'S NO TIME TO THINK FIRST
AND THEN REACT TO THE NUANCES
YOU FEEL THROUGH THE SEAT.
YOUR ARMS AND LEGS HAVE MOVE
TOGETHER ALMOST INSTINCTIVELY
IN ORDER TO CONTROL THE DRIFT.
SO DON'T WORRY.
TAKUMI'S GOT A KNACK FOR SENSING
WHEN AND HOW TO ACCELERATE
WHEN HE'S IN THE
MIDDLE OF A DRIFT.
SO IF THE SUSPENSION
SETTINGS ARE ALTERED
A LITTLE HERE AND THERE,
IT WON'T MATTER.
HE'LL MAKE MINOR ADJUSTMENTS
WHEN HE NEEDS TO.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO
DRIVE AN EIGHT-SIX.
THAT CAR TRAINS ITS DRIVER.
- WE'RE AT THE FINISH.
ROAD'S CLEAR, SO IF THEY'RE
READY TO GO, SEND 'EM DOWN.
- ( static )
- IKETANI, WE JUST GOT THE
GO-AHEAD TO START.
- GOTCHA.
ALRIGHT, WE'RE ABOUT TO START
THE COUNTDOWN!
WE GO IN TEN SECONDS!
- ( engines revving )
- COME ON, TAKUMI!
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT!
- HEY, KEISUKE.
WHILE THE WANNABES
WATCH FROM THE SIDELINES
WE'LL HAVE THE BEST SEATS IN THE
HOUSE. HOP IN. THEY'RE STARTING.
- FIVE. FOUR. THREE. TWO. ONE.
GO!
- ( tires screeching )
- THE THREE-TWO'S IN THE LEAD!
- BUT TAKUMI ISN'T
TOO FAR BEHIND HIM.
- Keisuke: HERE THEY COME!
- Ryosuke: YOU BETTER BUCKLE UP.
- ( tires screeching )
- HOLY CRAP, LOOK!
IT'S RYOSUKE'S FC!
HE'S NOT TRYING TO
JOIN THE RACE, IS HE?
- WHAT THE HELL'S HE DOIN'?
NO ONE SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT THIS BEING A 3-WAY!
- EPIC! THIS WILL DECIDE WHO THE
FASTEST DRIVER IN GUNMA IS.
- THE GUY IN THE GT-R
IS SLOWING DOWN.
IS HE WAITING FOR ME
TO CATCH UP?
I COULD LOSE HIM ON
THE STRAIGHTAWAY
AND BE DONE WITH IT,
BUT WHERE'S THE FUN IN THAT?
I CAME HERE TO BATTLE.
THE RACE STARTS AS SOON AS
WE HIT THE FIRST CORNER.
- ARE YOU SEEIN'
WHAT I'M SEEIN'?
HE'S SLOWIN' DOWN AND WAITIN'
FOR THE EIGHT-SIX TO CATCH UP.
- WE'LL SEE IF HIS
OVERCONFIDENCE
ENDS UP COSTING HIM
IN THE LAST HALF OF THE RACE.
- HERE THEY COME!
THEY'RE AT THE FIRST CORNER!
ALL THREE CARS ARE
IN A TIGHT PACK!
- WOW. BUNTA CALLED IT ALRIGHT.
- WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
NO WAY.
THE ONLY REASON YOU'RE
THIS CLOSE IS BECAUSE I LET YOU.
BUT IT'S THE CLOSEST YOU'LL GET
TO MY BUMPER, JUST WATCH!
- WATCHING THIS KID
DRIVE UP CLOSE.
IT'S CLEAR TO ME NOW.
HIS DRIFT'S AN ART.
HE'S PULLING A FOUR-WHEEL
DRIFT WITH FULL THROTTLE
AND BARELY USING ANY
COUNTER-STEERING.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW INCREDIBLE THAT IS?
HE'S USING EVERY BIT OF POWER
THAT EIGHT-SIX HAS,
AND HIS CONTROL IS PHENOMENAL,
LIKE IT'S AS EFFORTLESS AS
CONTROLLING HIS HANDS
OR HIS FEET.
I CAN'T EVEN CONTROL MY OWN FC
WITH THAT LEVEL OF
PRECISION HANDLING.
THIS IS GETTING INTERESTING.
- YEAH, MAYBE SO, BUT TAKESHI'S
PULLING AHEAD OF HIM AGAIN.
IF THE EIGHT-SIX CAN WIN, THEN
HE'D BETTER MAKE HIS MOVE SOON.
- YES! THIS IS WHAT I LIVE FOR.
THIS IS THE KINDA THING THAT
REALLY GETS MY BLOOD PUMPING!
I'VE BEEN WAITING A LONG TIME
FOR A GOOD BATTLE.
ALRIGHT KID.
TIME TO CUT YOU LOOSE.
FOLLOW THIS!
- WAIT A SECOND.
SOMETHING FEELS DIFFERENT.
I'M NOT LOSING AS MUCH CONTROL
WHEN I FLOOR THE GAS.
MAYBE I CAN ACCELERATE SOONER
THAN I NORMALLY DO.
WHEN I WAS AT WORK,
WAS DAD MESSING WITH IT?
THAT'S THE ONLY EXPLANATION
I CAN THINK OF.
CAUSE IT SURE WASN'T LIKE THIS
WHEN I MADE DELIVERIES
THIS MORNING.
I GET IT.
THAT'S WHERE HE WAS EARLIER.
HE WAS TWEAKING THE CAR FOR ME.
WHATEVER HE DID, I LIKE IT.
I'M NOT SLIDING NEARLY AS MUCH
AS I USUALLY DO,
AND THAT MEANS I CAN
PUSH IT ALL THE WAY!
- Man 1: WOAH! CHECK IT OUT!
- Man 2: AWESOME DRIFT!
- I'VE NEVER SEEN SOMEONE
TAKE THAT TIGHT OF A CORNER
WHILE MAINTAINING A SOLID DRIFT.
- THAT DUDE IS A MANIAC.
YOU'D HAVETA BE PERFECTLY
IN CONTROL OF YOUR SPEED
TO PULL THAT OFF.
- DID YOU SEE THAT?
- YEAH, BUT I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
NOBODY DRIFTS LIKE THAT!
- FREAKIN' INCREDIBLE! I TELL
YA', MAN, THAT WAS LEGENDARY!
DON'T YOU FORGET IT!
- INITIAL D.
- INITIAL D!
- ( static )
- Man: THE EIGHT-SIX IS RIGHT
ON THE THREE-TWO'S TAIL!
- HE'S REALLY DOIN' IT!
TAKUMI'S GIVIN' THE THREE-TWO
A RUN FOR ITS MONEY!
- YES!
SERIOUSLY, NOCKAZATO'S GOT
SOME MAD SKILLS ON HIS OWN,
BUT PUT RYOSUKE BEHIND HIM
AND YOU GOT YOURSELF A
SUPERSTAR BATTLE ROYAL!
AND MY BEST FRIEND'S RACING
AGAINST BOTH OF 'EM
AT THE SAME TIME!
THAT IS SO FREAKIN' SWEET!
- I'M WITH YOU MAN,
IT'S PRETTY EXCITING,
BUT RYOSUKE AND HIS FC
AREN'T ACTUALLY IN THE RACE,
THEY'RE JUST
FOLLOWING ALONG.
HE'S JUST A SPECTATOR WITH A
REALLY SWEET VIEW OF THE ACTION.
- YEAH. JUST TAKUMI AND TAKESHI.
- THE THREE-TWO
HAS THE EIGHT-SIX
AT A HUGE DISADVANTAGE.
BUT I KNOW TAKUMI'LL FIND A WAY
TO PULL THROUGH.
- Itsuki: YEAH!
TAKUMI'S GOT THIS, RIGHT GUYS?
AM I RIGHT?
AH, YOU KNOW I'M RIGHT.
- MAN, THE THREE-TWO'S LEAD
IS GETTIN' BIGGER.
- NAKAZOTO'S GOT A BIG MOUTH,
BUT AT LEAST HE HAS
THE SKILLS TO BACK IT UP.
JUST LOOK AT THE WAY
HE DISTRIBUTES THE LOAD
AND EASES THE UNDERSTEER
IN THE TURNS.
HE REALLY KNOWS WHAT IT TAKES
TO DRAW OUT EVERY OUNCE
OF THE GT-R'S POWER.
IT ISN'T PRETTY TO LOOK AT,
BUT THIS ISN'T THE TIME
TO PLAY IT SAFE.
- I GOTTA ASK YOU, BRO. WHOSE
SIDE ARE YOU REALLY ON ANYWAY?
IF THE KID LOSES THIS RACE,
THEN OUR CHANCE AT
REDEMPTION IS OVER.
- THIS BATTLE HASN'T EVEN BEGUN.
THE FIRST HALF IS ALMOST
ALL STRAIGHTAWAYS
WITH LOTS OF GENTLE SLOPES.
THE EIGHT-SIX DOESN'T PERFORM
WELL IN THAT SORT OF TERRAIN.
BUT THE DECLINES ARE GONNA BE
GETTING ROUGH HERE SOON,
A PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
FOR A DOWNHILL SPECIALIST
TO REALLY SHINE.
- ( tires screeching )
- OKAY, HERE WE GO.
THE THREE-TWO WAS MADE
FOR THIS NEXT CORNER.
A LOW-GEAR HAIRPIN.
ALL I GOTTA DO IS CUT MY SPEED
BY SLAMMIN' ON THE BRAKES.
- ( engine revving )
WHEN I'M ON THE DOWNHILL
THE FRONT WHEELS
STILL HAVE TO BEAR THE LOAD.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY TO
KEEP THE UNDERSTEER
FROM PUSHIN' TOO HARD.
BUT COMING OUT OF THE
TURN ACCELERATING
FROM A LOW GEAR IS A BREEZE.
IT'S NO SECRET THIS IS FASTEST
MACHINE ON THE RACING CIRCUIT.
AND IT DOMINATES ON THE
OPEN ROADS, TOO!
THE GT-R LOGO ON THE BACK MEANS
THIS IS THE BADDEST SET
OF WHEELS YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
TOO BAD YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GET
CLOSE ENOUGH TO READ IT, KID!
- Kenji: HEY, IKETANI.
- Iketani: YEAH?
- WELL. I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT SOMETHING.
UP UNTIL NOW I'VE
ALWAYS SEEN TAKUMI
AS THE KIND OF DRIVER
WHO'S ONLY REALLY FAST
WHEN HE'S RACING ON HIS HOME
TURF, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
BUT WHAT IF HE RACED
ON A DIFFERENT PASS.
HOW WELL YOU THINK
HE WOULD REALLY DO?
YOU EVER THINK ABOUT THAT?
- WELL, SURE. I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT
THAT A FEW TIMES ACTUALLY.
BUT RIGHT NOW WE JUST
NEED TO FOCUS.
C'MON TAKUMI. WIN.
- HELL YEAH!
- ( tires screeching )
- MAN, I CAN BARELY
KEEP HIM IN SIGHT!
( chuckles ) LOOKS LIKE THE REAL
ACTION'S ABOUT TO GET STARTED.
HE'S GRIPPIN' THE EDGE OF
THE ROAD WITH HIS INSIDE TIRES.
THIS IS IT.
THE MOVE THAT BEAT ME.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D GET
THE CHANCE TO SEE IT AGAIN
WITH MY OWN EYES.
RYOSUKE'S GONE QUIET.
I BETTER DO THE SAME, I DON'T
WANNA BREAK HIS CONCENTRATION.
I'VE RIDDEN SHOTGUN WITH HIM
FOR YEARS NOW.
AND HE'S NEVER DRIVEN WITH
SUCH INTENSITY BEFORE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM SO FOCUSED.
- HE'S GAINING ON ME!
HOW THE HELL IS THE
EIGHT-SIX CLOSING THE GAP?
IMPOSSIBLE!
- ( tires screeching )
- IT'S AMAZING, CATCHIN' UP
TO ME AFTER SUCH A HUGE LEAD.
NOW I SEE HOW WRONG I
WAS THINKING THE 8-6
COULDN'T HANDLE THIS.
THAT THING IS A
TRUE FIGHTING MACHINE
RIGHT UP THERE WITH MY GT-R!
ALRIGHT, PLAY TIME IS OVER. MAN,
I'M GETTING SUCH A RUSH!
THIS FEELS GREAT! I HAVEN'T BEEN
IN A FIGHT THIS INTENSE
SINCE I BOUGHT THIS CAR!
- ( tires screeching )
- WHEN IT COMES TO MANEUVERING
THROUGH HAIRPIN TURNS,
THE POOR KID DOESN'T HOLD
A CANDLE TO THE THREE-TWO.
THEY'RE CLOSE GOIN'
INTO THE TURN,
BUT THE EIGHT-SIX
LOSES GROUND AFTER A HAIRPIN.
CAN'T FORGET ABOUT
NAKAZATO THOUGH.
ATTACKING THE DOWNHILL
IN A HEAVY THREE-TWO.
TAKES SOME SERIOUS GUTS!
- NO WAY!
- THE EIGHT-SIX CAUGHT UP AT THE
FASTEST CORNER ON THE TRACK?
DOIN' OVER A HUNDRED
KILOMETERS AN HOUR
IN A FOUR-WHEEL DRIFT IS NUTS.
HE NEARLY GRAZED
THE GUARD RAIL!
THESE MOVES DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE CAR'S
CAPABILITIES.
IT'S THE DRIVER.
HE'S GOT A SCREW LOOSE.
JUST ONE SLIP UP AND
HE'LL BE SPLATTERED
ALL OVER THE MOUNTAIN.
NOW I KNOW HIS SECRET.
A LIGHTWEIGHT CAR LIKE THE
EIGHT-SIX HAS WEAK ACCELERATION,
WHICH MEANS IT TAKES FOREVER
TO GET BACK UP TO
SPEED AFTER BRAKING.
SO HE NEVER SACRIFICES MORE
SPEED THAN HE ABSOLUTELY HAS TO.
IT MAKES TOTAL SENSE NOW.
WHEN I RACED HIM, I'D LOSE HIM
ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS
AND THEN, SURE ENOUGH,
HE'D BE BACK ON MY TAIL
AFTER EACH TURN.
♪ I WILL PRAY NOW ♪
- DAMN.
♪ TO BE WITH YOU ♪
♪ TO MAKE YOUR SKY
MORE THAN BLUE ♪
♪ TIME GOES BY ♪
♪ IT USE ME UP INSIDE ♪
♪ I WANNA SOMETHING NEW ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET THROUGH ♪
♪ I'M BURNING UP FOR YOU ♪
CRAP, I CAN'T SHAKE HIM.
THE FARTHER DOWN
THE COURSE WE GET,
THE HARDER THE LITTLE PUNK
IS PRESSING ME.
HE'S FREAKIN' RELENTLESS!
♪ I'M BURNING UP FOR YOU ♪
♪ I NEVER LOVE ANYBODY
THE WAY I DO ♪
- NAKAZATO'S CLEARING EACH
OF THE GUARDRAILS
BY A GOOD TWENTY OR
THIRTY CENTIMETERS.
I DON'T CARE HOW FAST YOU ARE.
THAT'S SOUND TECHNIQUE
ANY WAY YOU LOOK AT IT.
AND YET THE EIGHT-SIX
IS CLOSE ENOUGH
TO LEAVE PAINT ON THE RAIL.
MAYBE A CENTIMETER OR TWO
AT MOST.
IT'S AMAZING,
BUT HOW'S HE DO IT?
I WOULDN'T THINK ANY MAN
COULD CONTROL A DRIFT
WITH THAT LEVEL OF PRECISION.
♪ CAN YOU WAIT FOR ME? ♪
♪ THERE'S SO MUCH FOR WE TOO ♪
♪ I KNOW THAT WE CAN DO ♪
♪ I'M BURNING UP FOR YOU ♪
- I'VE BEEN USING THE ABS HARD
AND FORCING THE STEERING
TO DO WHAT I NEED IT TO DO.
PROBLEM IS IT'S MAKING THE
LOAD ON THE FRONT TIRES
A LOT HEAVIER THAN I'D HOPED.
THIS RACE JUST GOT
A WHOLE LOT HARDER!
♪ I'M BURNING UP FOR YOU ♪
♪ I NEVER LOVE ANYBODY
THE WAY I DO ♪
♪ I'M BURNING UP FOR YOU ♪
- THE FIVE HAIRPINS ARE
COMING UP SOON.
- ( Keisuke exclaims )
IT'S THE EXACT SAME SPOT WHERE
HE LEFT YOU IN THE DUST.
AND HE'S ABOUT TO DO
THE SAME THING TO TAKESHI.
♪ I'M BURNING UP FOR YOU ♪
- A THREE-TWO VERSUS
AN EIGHT-SIX.
WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT THE RACE
COULD BE THIS CLOSE?
BOTH CARS ARE BEING PUSHED
TO THEIR LIMITS,
BUT WHICH ONE WILL IS
GONNA EDGE OUT THE VICTORY?
- ( static )
- Man: I'M AT THE HAIRPINS.
I CAN HEAR 'EM COMIN', FAST!
( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- RYOSUKE, MOST PEOPLE
EXPECTED THE THREE-TWO
TO HAVE A HUGE ADVANTAGE, RIGHT?
THE R THIRTY-TWO IS
IS FORTY-SIX HUNDRED
FORTY MILLIMETERS LONG,
AND SEVENTEEN HUNDRED
TWENTY MILLIMETERS WIDE,
AND WEIGHS IN AT ABOUT...
- SO IN OTHER WORDS.
- IN OTHER WORDS,
THE R THIRTY TWOIS
FORTY-SIX HUNDRED FORTY
MILLIMETERS LONG
AND SEVENTEEN HUNDRED
TWENTY MILLIMETERS...
- Announcer: THEN WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING IS THE DOWNHILL
PUTS TAKUMI AT A...
-WHAT I'M SAYING IS
THE R THIRTY-TWO
IS FORTY-SIX HUNDRED...
- Annoucer: ENOUGH ALREADY!
NEXT TIME ON INITIAL D, THE
FIVE CONSECUTIVE HAIRPINS!
DON'T MISS IT!