- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- ( car tires screeching )
- ( car approaching )
- ( rock song playing )
♪ EVERY NIGHT YOU LIGHT ME ♪
♪ WITH YOUR GASOLINE ♪
♪ EVERY TIME I FEEL DELIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN YOU RECALL MY NAME ♪
♪ SO YOU CAN BE
MY SHINING STAR TONIGHT ♪
♪ I'M NOT ALONE
WITH ALL YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ FLY ACROSS THE SKY
YOU WILL BE MINE ♪
♪ LIKE A REAL DREAM
WE BUILD, BABE ♪
♪ GONNA GET YOU
LIKE A SPACE BOY ♪
♪ WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA
I'M READY, BABE ♪
♪ GONNA GET YOU
I'M YOUR SPACE BOY ♪
♪ DIVE INTO YOUR HEART, BABY ♪
♪ I'M GONNA GET YOU
LIKE A SPACE BOY ♪
-( song continues on radio )
- Yuichi: THAT GUY
NEVER CHANGES.
- Itsuki: EVEN THE '91 MODEL
RUNS 1.3 MILLION YEN.
CRAP, MAN, THIS S-THIRTEEN IS
TOO EXPENSIVE.
LIKE I FIGURED, I'M GONNA HAVE
TO GO WITH THE EIGHT-SIX.
THAT BABY'S THE ONLY REAL
POSSIBILITY. CUZ NO MATTER WHAT,
IT'S GOTTA BE AN FR. RIGHT,
TAKUMI? TAKUMI!
ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
- OF COURSE I'M LISTENING
TO YOU, ITSUKI...
YOU WERE ABOUT TO TELL ME
HOW MUCH IT'S GONNA COST
TO GET THAT EIGHT-SIX
YOU'VE BEEN STARING AT.
- THIS ONE'S MARKED
AT 300 THOUSAND
BUT IT HASN'T PASSED INSPECTION.
- AND HOW MUCH MONEY DO YOU
HAVE SOCKED AWAY SO FAR?
- LIKE FIFTY THOUSAND.
- LONG WAY TO GO.
- I KNOW. IT'S DEPRESSING.
THERE'S GOTTA BE A
WAY TO MAKE A QUICK
BUCK AROUND HERE! EVEN IF WE
KICKED IT UP TO FULL TIME AT THE
GAS STATION DURING THE SUMMER
BREAK, WE'D STILL ONLY MAKE LIKE
A HUNDRED AND TWENTY
THOUSAND YEN AT MOST.
THERE'S GOTTA BE A BETTER
JOB AROUND HERE.
- I DIDN'T KNOW YOU GUYS
HAD PART TIME JOBS.
- NATSUKI...
- WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO ACT SO SHOCKED.
IS IT THAT WEIRD THAT
I'D TALK TO YOU?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
- SO YOU WERE SAYIN' YOU'D ONLY
MAKE A HUNDRED AND TWENTY
THOUSAND YEN WORKING
FULL TIME THIS SUMMER?
HOW MANY HOURS A DAY IS THAT?
- LIKE TWELVE. OR MORE!
- ( gasps )
A FULL MONTH'S WORTH OF WORK
AND THAT'S ALL YOU'RE
WALKING AWAY WITH?
- COULD BE WORSE.
LEAST WE GOT JOBS.
- WE'RE HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS.
WE GET PAID LIKE CRAP 'CUZ
THEY CAN GET AWAY WITH IT.
- I WOULDN'T KNOW...
I'VE NEVER WORKED A
PART-TIME JOB BEFORE.
I'VE NEVER HAD TO.
- ( bell chiming )
- HEY, GOOD LUCK WITH
YOUR SUMMER JOBS, YOU GUYS...
ALL OF US
SHOULD REALLY GET TOGETHER AND
HANG OUT ONCE FINALS ARE OVER.
- YEAH! DUDE, DID YOU HEAR
THAT? SHE WANTS TO GET TOGETHER!
ME OUT ON A DATE WITH
NATSUKI! SUH-WEET!
THAT'D BE SO COOL!
HEY, WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME SHE
DUG ME SO HARD? YOU NEVER EVEN
BOTHERED TO MENTION TO ME THAT
THE TWO OF YOU WERE SUCH TIGHT
BUDDIES. I FIGURED YOU AND I
WERE CLOSER THAN THAT.
- PROB'LY BECAUSE SHE AND I
HAVEN'T EVEN TALKED TO EACH
OTHER IN ABOUT A YEAR OR SO...
WE USED TO BELONG TO THE SAME
AFTER-SCHOOL CLUB. UP UNTIL
SOMETIME LAST SUMMER WE WERE
PRETTY MUCH STILL FRIENDS,
I THOUGHT.
- WHAT ARE YOU BABBLING
ON ABOUT BUDDY?
I MEAN, REALLY, NO ONE CARES...
OH, NATSUKI THE HOTTIE! I'VE HAD
MY EYE ON YOU FOR AS LONG AS
YOU'VE BEEN STRUTTIN' YOUR STUFF
AND BABY, ITSUKI'S READY FOR YA!
TAKUMI!
BACK TO PLANET EARTH, MAN!
WE'RE GONNA GET BUSTED
IF WE DON'T GET
TO GRAMMAR, FAST!
- THAT TEST IS IN
LIKE TWO MINUTES!
- CRAP, WAIT UP!
- I GOT AN IDEA. WHY DON'T YOU
AND I GO IN ON THE EIGHT-SIX
TOGETHER?
WE POOL OUR MONEY
AND WE'LL BE ABLE TO AFFORD
THE LOAN PAYMENTS EASY.
- THAT'S A TERRIBLE IDEA. WHY DO
YOU WANT A CAR THAT MUCH ANYWAY?
DOESN'T YOUR FAMILY
ALREADY HAVE ONE?
JUST USE THEIRS IF YOU
NEED IT SO BAD.
- THAT PIECE IS
NO FREAKIN' GOOD.
MY OLD MAN'S BEEN DRIVING THAT
AUTOMATIC FRONT WHEEL DRIVE INTO
THE GROUND FOR A DECADE PLUS.
NOT TO MENTION IT'S DIESEL.
THE THING SUCKS OUT LOUD.
CALLING IT A CAR IS AN INSULT
TO CARS EVERYWHERE...
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- IF IT HAS FOUR TIRES
AND GETS YOU
FROM POINT A TO POINT B
THEN IT'S A CAR.
- YOU DON'T GET IT, MAN.
I WOULDN'T CONSIDER
ANYTHING A CAR
THAT DOESN'T DELIVER A GOOD
TIME ON THE MOUNTAIN.
- WHAT SO MUCH FUN DRIVING
ON THE MOUNTAIN?
- WHATCHA THINK, DOOFUS!
YOU DRIVE AS FAST AS YOU CAN,
CHALLENGING THE CORNERS!
- THE CORNERS?
THAT'S REALLY THE KIND OF THING
YOU DO FOR FUN?
- I WOULDN'T BE DO IT IF IT WAS
BORING. LOOK, YOU'RE A DUDE,
RIGHT? AND YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU
DON'T FEEL THE UNQUENCHABLE
DESIRE TO TACKLE
THOSE RAGING HAIRPINS?
- Takumi: I DON'T KNOW MAYBE
I'M JUST BURNED OUT
ON THAT KIND OF STUFF.
- HOW COULD YOU BE BURNED OUT?
WE JUST GOT OUR LICENSES
LAST MONTH?
WE'RE BABIES
IN THE DRIVING WORLD!
- Man: LOOKING CUTE, SWEETHEART.
I ALWAYS LOVE THE WAY
YOU WEAR THAT OUTFIT.
- THANKS...
IT'S JUST MY SCHOOL UNIFORM.
I WAS TALKING WITH THIS FRIEND
OF MINE AT SCHOOL AND HE WAS
TELLING ME A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
THE JOB HE'S GOT LINED UP
FOR THE SUMMER BREAK...
HE SAID AFTER WORKING
THE ENTIRE SUMMER,
SOMETIMES WITH SHIFTS THAT ARE
OVER TWELVE HOURS A DAY, HE'S
PROBABLY ONLY GONNA
END UP BRINGING IN
LIKE A HUNDRED AND
TWENTY THOUSAND YEN.
- ( man laughs )
Man: YES, THAT SOUNDS
ABOUT RIGHT.
GUESS IT'S A LOT HARDER TO
EARN MONEY THAN I THOUGHT.
I SHOULD BE MORE CONSIDERATE...
I'VE SEEN YOU SPEND MORE
THAN THAT ON ME
IN A MONTH WITHOUT EVEN
BLINKING AN EYE.
IT MAKES ME FEEL KINDA BAD.
ARE YOU REALLY OKAY WITH
SPENDING THAT MUCH ON ME?
- Man: OF COURSE I AM,
SWEETHEART. YOU'RE WORTH IT.
- Natsuki: I AM?
MAYBE I JUST DON'T GET IT.
- Takumi and Itsuki:
THANK YOU FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- TAKUMI, I REALLY WANT YOU
TO PUT A LITTLE MORE THOUGHT
INTO GOING IN ON THE
EIGHT-SIX WITH ME.
DUDE, I'M TELLING YOU,
IT'D BE SERIOUSLY AWESOME!
- LET THE EIGHT-SIX GO!
- DIDN'T REALIZE YOU GUYS
HAD SUCH GOOD TASTE.
THE EIGHT-SIX IS A
TRULY DECENT RIDE.
- SEE? LISTEN TO IKETANI.
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S TALKING
ABOUT AND HE SAYS I'M A GENIUS.
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT. I SAID
THE EIGHT-SIX IS A GOOD CAR.
- YA HEAR THAT?
- YEAH I HEARD IT...
BUT IF I'M BEING
COMPLETELY HONEST,
I DON'T THINK I COULD PICK AN
EIGHT-SIX OUT OF A LINE UP.
WHO MAKES THAT THING ANYWAY?
- WHY DON'T YOU DRINK SOME
OF THIS HIGH OCTANE?
PUT SOME CAR POWER IN YOUR HEAD!
- HOW CAN YOU WORK HERE AND
NOT KNOW WHAT AN EIGHT-SIX IS?
DON'T YOU EVER OPEN
YOUR EYES AT WORK?
- Iketani: I DUNNO.
I GUESS I'M NOT SURPRISED.
YOU TWO WERE IN...
WHAT, SECOND
OR THIRD GRADE
WHEN THE NINE-TWO
MODEL CAME OUT?
ONLY CAR I KNOW IS THE OLD ONE
WE USE FOR DELIVERIES.
- WHICH IS A JUNKER! EVEN
IF AN EIGHT-SIX IS OLD,
IT'S NOT REALLY OLD,
IT'S 'VINTAGE'.
- Itsuki: SO, IKETANI,
WHEN WE BUY OUR EIGHT-SIX
YOU THINK YOU'D LET
US JOIN YOUR TEAM?
I'VE ALWAYS DREAMED OF
BEING ON THE AKINA SPEED STARS.
- YEAH, SURE.
OH, SPEAKING OF...
IT'S SATURDAY SO THE
TEAM'S GONNA MEET UP
AT MOUNT AKINA TONIGHT
FOR A COUPLE PRACTICE RUNS...
YOU GUYS SHOULD COME ALONG, TOO.
- YOU MEAN WE'RE
ACTUALLY INVITED?
BUT WE DON'T HAVE A
CAR TO GET US THERE.
- I CAN GIVE YOU A RIDE, STUPID.
- ( exclaims happily )
YOU'LL LET US RIDE IN
YOUR S-THIRTEEN?
I'M IN! I AM IN!
I AM SO TOTALLY FREAKIN' IN!
AND YOU'RE GOIN' TOO, TAKUMI!
I MEAN, THIS KINDA
THING DOESN'T JUST...
- DON'T KNOW WHY
HE'S SO EXCITED.
I NEVER SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT WANTING TO GO.
- WE'RE OUTTA HERE, IKETANI!
- COOL. PICK YOU DUDES UP
AT THE BUS STOP AROUND EIGHT.
- Itsuki: SEE YA THEN!
- YOU'RE TAKING THEM, HUH?
WHICH MOUNTAIN YOU GOING TO?
- C'MON, BOSS.
YOU KNOW MOUNT AKINA'S
THE ONLY MOUNTAIN AROUND HERE
WORTH RACING ON...
AND THE SPEED STARS ARE THE
FASTEST TEAM ON AKINA ANYWAY.
WE GOTTA DEFEND OUR TERRITORY.
- WELL, YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY
GUYS I'VE HEARD AROUND HERE
SAYING THAT, YOU KNOW.
BACK WHEN I WAS STILL RACING,
THERE WAS THIS ONE FELLA,
EVERYONE KNEW THAT HE
WAS THE FASTEST.
UNDISPUTED, COULDN'T BE BEAT.
AND AFTER ALL THESE YEARS,
HE STILL DRIVES MOUNT AKINA.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME...
I KNOW EVERY LAST DRIVER WHO
GOES UP AND DOWN THAT COURSE,
AND, NO OFFENSE, BUT NOT
A SINGLE ONE OF THEM
IS AN OLD TIMER.
- HE JUST DRIVES DURING A
DIFFERENT TIME OF THE DAY
THAN YOU AND ALL YOUR BUDDIES...
AND HE'S GOT A GOOD REASON...
HE HAPPENS TO OWN A TOFU SHOP.
- ( gasps )
- AT AROUND FOUR AM, HE ALWAYS
LEAVES ON HIS DELIVERIES.
HE HAS TO MAKE HIS
ROUNDS TAKING TOFU
TO ALL THE HOTELS AT LAKE AKINA.
THAT GUY'S DOWNHILL SPEED IS
SOMETHING OUT OF THIS WORLD.
AND BECAUSE THIS
IS HIS BUSINESS,
THE GUY'S OUT THERE EVERY DAY,
RAIN OR SNOW, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
HE KNOWS THE SMALLEST STAIN
ON THE ASPHALT OF THAT ROAD.
MARK MY WORDS, IKETANI,
THE FASTEST DOWNHILL CAR
IN AKINA IS AN EIGHT-SIX
THAT DELIVERS TOFU.
- THE TOFU SHOP EIGHT-SIX?
- WHADDYA THINK YOU'RE DOING?
SNEAKING OUT?
- GOT PLANS WITH ITSUKI.
WE'RE GONNA JUST
HANG OUT AND STUFF.
- DON'T CARE WHAT YOU DO.
JUST DON'T MAKE ME DRAG YOUR
ASS OUTTA BED IN THE MORNING.
- AFTER THE LAST TIME, I DON'T
THINK YOU NEED TO REMIND ME.
- SEE YA IN THE MORNING...
YEAH?
- YEAH.
- ( screaming )
- SLAM A CORK IN IT, TAKUMI!
YOU'RE TOTALLY BLOWING
IKETANI'S CONCENTRATION!
- YOU THINK I CARE...
I'LL SCREAM ALL I WANT, I'M
SCARED FOR MY FREAKIN' LIFE!
- I'M USED TO IT, MAN.
PEOPLE TEND TO GET SCARED
FIRST TIME THEY
RIDE WITH A REAL STREET RACER.
HERE GOES A HAIRPIN
TURN IN SECOND.
- ( screaming )
- TAKUMI, WOULD YOU
PLEASE SHUT THE HELL UP!
- TONIGHT I'M GONNA
CUT LOOSE OUT THERE.
FOR REAL, MAN. I'M SICK OF
KEEPING EVERYTHING BOTTLED UP...
- YOU OKAY, BUDDY?
YOU LOOK KINDA SICK.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D
FREAK LIKE THAT.
I'S JUST IN THE MOOD
TO PUSH THE CAR
SO I MAY HAVE DONE IT A
LITTLE HARD FOR YOUR TASTE.
- YOU'RE SUCH A FREAKIN'
BABY, TAKUMI!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
I BET YOU'D SCREAM
FOR YOUR LIFE
ON A ROLLER COASTER AT THE PARK.
- I LIKE ROLLER COASTERS,
ITSUKI. YOU KNOW THAT.
THIS IS SOMETHING
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
SOMETHING I DON'T THINK YOU
COULD POSSIBLY UNDERSTAND...
AND EVEN IF I COULD EXPLAIN IT,
YOU COULDN'T WRAP
YOUR HEAD AROUND THIS
CRAZY FEAR I HAVE INSIDE.
- I DON'T GET IT MYSELF.
- HUH?
- ( humming )
- ( car zooming )
- NEVER SEEN THESE GUYS BEFORE.
AND IF THEY'RE HEADED UP TO
AKINA AT THIS TIME OF NIGHT...
SOMETHING MUST BE GOIN'
DOWN ON THE MOUNTAIN.
- LOOKS LIKE WE GOT
SOME COMPANY, BOYS.
- WHY ARE THE RED SUNS HERE?
I'VE HEARD THOSE GUYS ARE
THE FASTEST DRIVERS IN AKAGI.
- INITIAL D!
- ALRIGHT, LISTEN UP, WE'RE
THE AKAGI RED SUNS.
MAYBE YOU HEARD ABOUT US...
I DON'T WANNA START OFF SOUNDING
LIKE A PRICK BUT THE ONLY
THING I WANNA KNOW IS
WHO THE FASTEST TEAM
OR THE FASTEST DRIVER IS
ON THIS MOUNTAIN.
ANYONE WANNA CLAIM THAT?
- ( chattering )
- WE'RE THE AKINA SPEED STARS
AND IF YOU CAME UP HERE LOOKIN'
FOR THE FASTEST DRIVERS
ON THIS MOUNTAIN...
WELL, YOU'RE STARIN'
AT 'EM, HOT SHOT. -
THAT WAS EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT IT'D BE...
HOW ABOUT WE HOLD A PRACTICE
BETWEEN OUR TEAMS...
WE COULD DO IT RIGHT
HERE ON AKINA, COULD BE FUN.
- THIS IS NUTS...
THEY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THEY'RE IN FOR.
- I KNEW THIS'D BE A
SWEET FRIDAY NIGHT!
- WHATTYA SAY GUYS...
WE'VE BEEN GOING UP AGAINST THE
SAME PEOPLE OVER AND OVER,
IT'S GOTTEN TO BE A LITTLE TOO
ROUTINE FOR OUR TASTE.
WE WANNA MIX IT UP.
RUNNING AGAINST NEW TEAMS
WILL GIVE US THE CHANCE
TO FACE A NEW CHALLENGE.
WE CAN EXCHANGE SOME IDEAS AND
MAYBE EVEN MAKE SOME FRIENDS.
SURE, WE'LL PROB'LY LET A FEW
TEAM SECRETS SLIP
HERE AND THERE,
BUT IN THE LONG RUN, I THINK
WE'LL ALL BE ABLE TO IMPROVE...
FIRST, LET'S DO A RUN TOGETHER.
AFTER THAT, EACH TEAM SENDS
ONE DRIVER HEAD TO HEAD
IN BOTH AN UPHILL AND DOWNHILL.
DOESN'T MATTER WHO WINS,
LET'S JUST BUILD SOME
SOLIDARITY BETWEEN TEAMS.
- IF HE'S GONNA PUT IT
SO DAMN POLITELY,
HOW ARE WE S'POSED TO SAY NO?
- ALRIGHT... WHAT DO YOU SAY WE
MEET UP NEXT SATURDAY,
RIGHT HERE, AT TEN O'CLOCK?
- SURE...
YOU GOT IT PAL.
- I THINK WE'RE JUST GONNA TAKE
IT EASY ON THE RUNS TONIGHT,
IF THAT'S COOL WITH YOU GUYS.
- I TOLD YOU THIS WAS
GONNA BE AWESOME, DIDN'T I?
- IF THOSE PUNKS THINK
THEY CAN INTIMIDATE US,
THEY'VE GOT ANOTHER
THING COMIN'.
- All: YEAH!
- WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO, IKETANI?
- I'M GONNA KEEP MY EYE ON
THE TAKAHASHI BROTHERS.
SEE WHY PEOPLE CALL
THEM THE FASTEST IN AKAGI.
- THE TAKAHASHI BROTHERS?
YOU MEAN THE DUDES WHO'VE
BEEN IN ALL THE MAGAZINES
WITH ALL THE PICTURES
AND ALL THE CRAZY HOT CHICKS?
- YEAH, THOSE'RE THE ONES.
THEY'RE ALSO KNOWN AS
"THE ROTARY BROTHERS."
- WHAT ABOUT US?
CAN WE COME WITH YOU?
- SORRY, ITSUKI.
WHEN I MAKE A SERIOUS RUN,
I DON'T LIKE TO GO AT IT
WITH PASSENGERS IN THE CAR...
YOU TWO WAIT HERE. I'LL PICK
YOU UP IN A LITTLE BIT.
- OH... THIS IS SO
FREAKIN' EMBARRASSING, MAN!
WHY ARE WE THE ONLY TWO LOSERS
UP HERE WITHOUT A CAR?
- HEY... ITSUKI...
IS IT REALLY AS MUCH FUN AS YOU
SAY IT IS TO BE A STREET RACER?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND. EVERYBODY
SEEMS SO EXCITED ABOUT IT.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
- NO, I'M THE ONE WHO
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU CAN HEAR THOSE CARS
SQUEALING AROUND
THE CORNERS, RIGHT?
TRYING DESPERATELY TO
CATCH UP WITH EACH OTHER,
PUSHING THE LIMITS,
AND THAT DOESN'T GET
YOU WORKED UP AT ALL?
- THAT SHOULD GET ME WORKED UP?
- ( phone rings )
- Bunta: FUJIWARA TOFU SHOP,
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
WELL, WHAT A SURPRISE...
YOURS WAS ABOUT THE LAST
VOICE I EXPECTED TO HEAR.
- IT'S GOOD TO TALK TO YOU, TOO.
IS THAT HOW YOU
GREET AN OLD FRIEND
YOU HAVEN'T TALKED TO IN AGES?
YOU KNOW THE OTHER DAY...
YOU PASSED ME ON YOUR WAY
BACK FROM A DELIVERY...
I SIGNALED YOU, BUT YOU BLEW
RIGHT BY ME LIKE I WAS NOBODY.
REAL SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU...
BUT THAT WASN'T ME.
- HAD TO BE.
IT WAS YOUR EIGHT-SIX.
- OKAY...
YOU CAUGHT ME...
IT WAS MY CAR THAT YOU SAW,
BUT I WASN'T THE ONE
DRIVING IT AT THE TIME.
MY SON TAKUMI'S DELIVERING
TOFU TO THE HOTELS NOW.
- ( coughing )
WAIT, WHAT DID YOU SAY?
SINCE WHEN?
- I GUESS ABOUT FIVE YEARS NOW.
- THAT KID'S BEEN RUNNING
DELIVERIES FOR YOU
SINCE HE WAS IN THE
SEVENTH GRADE?
- DAMN! I CAN'T KEEP UP
WITH THESE GUYS AT ALL!
THE RED SUNS ARE FASTER
THAN I THOUGHT!
I'M PUSHING MY LIMITS HERE,
AND I STILL CAN'T KEEP UP!
- SO, BROTHER, WHAT
ARE YA THINKIN'?
- I THINK IF THAT'S THE BEST
COMPETITION THEY CAN OFFER,
WE COULD BEAT THEM
WITHOUT A PRACTICE RUN...
WE'LL LEAVE OUR TOP DRIVERS
AT HOME NEXT WEEK.
I'M EVEN GONNA PASS ON THE RACE.
- WELL, IF YOU'RE NOT RACIN',
THEN I'M NOT GONNA
BOTHER EITHER.
- NO, YOU NEED TO DO IT.
I WANT YOU TO SET A RECORD
FOR THIS COURSE.
SOMETHING THESE LOCALS WILL
NEVER BE ABLE TO BREAK,
NOT EVEN ON THEIR BEST DAY.
WE DON'T DO THAT- THE NAME
OF THE AKAGI RED SUNS
WON'T EVER BECOME LEGENDARY.
- Keisuke: GOTCHA.
- FIRST THING WE DO IS SET NEW
RECORDS FOR EVERY SINGLE COURSE
IN THIS PREFECTURE.
THEN WE HIT SAITAMA,
CON-A-GAWA, TOKYO, AND CHEEBA.
AFTER THAT, WE'LL HAVE EVERY
RECORD IN THE CON-TOE REGION.
WHEN WE DO, WE'LL BE LEGENDS.
THEN WE CAN BASICALLY
KICK BACK AND RETIRE.
THAT'S MY PLAN FOR THE RED SUNS.
I CALL IT THE 'FASTEST
IN CON-TOE PROJECT'.
- THEY'RE PRETTY AWESOME.
AND THEIR STYLE IS COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT FROM OURS.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW BADLY WE GOT BEAT
ON OUR OWN HOME TURF.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
- THEY PUT SOME CASH INTO
THEIR SUSPENSIONS...
AND THEIR HORSEPOWER...
NO WAY WE CAN COMPETE WITH
THE RED SUNS, I'M TELLIN' YA.
- BUT WE CAN'T JUST
SAY 'NO,' EITHER.
- HE'S RIGHT. WE'LL LOOK LIKE
TOTAL COWARDS IF WE WALK NOW.
- I GET WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
BUT GUTS ALONE AREN'T
GONNA BEAT THESE GUYS.
- I KNOW THAT.
WE NEED SOMETHING MORE.
IT'S GETTIN' LATE GUYS.
LET'S GO AHEAD AND BAIL.
WE'LL GET TOGETHER TOMORROW
AND FIGURE THIS MESS OUT.
IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW, STREET
RACERS DON'T LIKE LOSING...
SOMETIMES WE GET WAY TOO
SERIOUS ABOUT OUR CHALLENGES.
AND THE ABSOLUTE WORST THING
THAT CAN HAPPEN IS TO
LOSE TO AN OUTSIDER
ON YOUR HOME COURSE.
IT'S AN UNWRITTEN LAW
OF STREET RACING.
- HEY, KEISUKE...
WHERE'S YOUR BROTHER?
- OH... HE WENT HOME.
BEEN GONE A WHILE.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
STILL LEFT UP HERE.
- LOOKS LIKE THE SUN IS
ABOUT TO START COMING UP.
- MAYBE IT'S TIME FOR US
TO START HEADING BACK TOO.
- IF I JUST STAY ON
TOP OF MY GAME,
I'LL BE DRIVING THE RED
SUNS ANCHOR POSITION
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
THEY'RE FINALLY CATCHIN' UP.
THAT'S NOT ONE OF OUR GUYS.
IS THAT AN MR-TWO OR
A ONE-EIGHTY?
- ( rock song playing )
♪ NO ONE SLEEPS IN TOKYO ♪
♪ ALL NIGHT CROSSING THE LINE ♪
NICE DRIVIN', CHIEF.
BUT AFTER TWO CORNERS,
YOU WON'T EVEN BE A SPECK
IN MY REAR VIEW MIRROR.
- ( tires screeching )
WHOA, IS THAT AN EIGHT-SIX?
YOU'RE KIDDIN' ME!
♪ ALL NIGHT IN THE FIGHT
I'M OK, COME ON! ♪
♪ COME ON! ♪
♪ HEY, DO YOU FEEL THE NIGHT
IS BREATHABLE? ♪
♪ LOOK AT THIS TOWN
IT'S JUST UNBELIEVABLE ♪
♪ NO OTHER PLACE IS LIKE
THAT IN THE WORLD ♪
IT SHOULDN'T BE THIS
HARD FOR MY FD
TO OUTRUN A JUNKED-OUT
OLD EIGHT-SIX...
THIS HAS GOTTA BE
SOME KINDA NIGHTMARE.
I JUST HOPE I WAKE UP SOON!
I'M THE NUMBER TWO DRIVER
OF THE AKAGI RED SUNS, DAMMIT!
♪ NO ONE SLEEPS IN TOKYO ♪
♪ ALL NIGHT CROSSING THE LINE ♪
DOESN'T THAT IDIOT
EVEN KNOW THIS ROAD?
AFTER THIS SLOW RIGHT
IS A SHARP LEFT.
THERE'S A RAVINE ON
THE OTHER SIDE,
HE'S GOTTA HIT THE BRAKES!
I KNEW IT! THAT FREAKIN'
IDIOT'S GOIN' IN WAY TOO FAST...
THERE'S NO ROOM TO SLOW DOWN!
HE'S GOING INTO THE GUARD RAIL!
WHOA!
WHAT THE HELL?
INERTIA DRIFT?
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
♪ TO DREAM MY DREAM! ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- Announcer: DRIFT FANS
AND EIGHT-SIX FANS,
I WANNA THANK YOU
PERSONALLY FOR WAITING!
IT'S FINALLY HERE! INITIAL D!
WHAT DID YOU THINK OF TAKUMI'S
SUPER DRIFT TECHNIQUE?
RACING THAT ONE POINT
SIX LITER NON-TURBO EIGHT-SIX
OF HIS AGAINST A HIGH-END THREE
HUNDRED AND FIFTY HORSEPOWER FD?
COOL, HUH? AND FOR THOSE
OF YOU OUT THERE
WHO DIG THE TECHNICAL TALK,
INITIAL D DELIVERS
ALL THE ESSENTIALS!
NEXT TIME, WE GOT
ANOTHER KILLER RACE
COMING YOUR WAY! DON'T MISS IT!