- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ BREAK INTO THE NIGHT,
IT'S THE TIME ♪
- ( Itsuki mimics
driving noises )
THEN WHEN I HIT THAT CORNER,
I WAS ALL LIKE...
( yelling )
AND I TOTALLY CLEARED IT.
IN THAT MOMENT I WAS
LIKE THE WIND,
LIKE A MYSTERIOUS
FORCE OF NATURE.
NOTHING BEATS AKINA PASS BOYS.
WHEN YOU GROW UP AND
GET YOUR OWN CARS
YOU REALLY GOTTA
GO CHECK IT OUT.
WHAT? OH, MY CAR?
IT'S EVERY RACER'S DREAM CAR.
AN EIGHT-FIVE.
BET YOU FELLAS
DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
- Itsuki: NOW THAT WAS WHAT
I'D CALL A KICK ASS SUMMER.
IT'LL STICK WITH ME
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
- WHY'S THAT?
- "WHY'S THAT?" BECAUSE A,
I BOUGHT A CAR DUDE,
AND B, YOU SHOT ONTO THE RACING
SCENE LIKE A FREAKIN' COMET.
DID YOU FORGET THAT?
- GIMME A BREAK.
I'M NOT THAT GOOD.
- WELL, ONE, TWO, THREE...
- ARE YOU TRYING TO REMEMBER HOW
TO COUNT AGAIN?
- NO, I WAS REMEMBERING
YOUR RACES.
YOU WON FOUR OF THEM OVER THE
SUMMER, IN CASE YOU FORGOT.
FIRST, THERE WAS KEISUKE OF THE
RED SUNS AND HIS BADASS FD.
- ( tires screeching )
- SECOND YOU WENT UP AGAINST
TAKESHI OF THE NIGHT KIDS
AND HIS THREE-TWO.
THIRD, YOU HAD THAT WHACKED OUT
GUM TAPE DEATH MATCH
WITH SHINGO'S EG-SIX.
THEN LAST YOU TOOK
DOWN MAKO AND SAYUKI
IN THEIR SIL-EIGHTY
AT USUI PASS.
FOUR OUTA FOUR, BUDDY.
YOUR START AS AN UNDEFEATED
LEGEND BEGAN THIS SUMMER,
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT.
YOU'RE NO LONGER JUST SOME
OTHER IDIOT HIGH SCHOOLER
TRYIN' TO SLIDE ON BY.
- WOULD YOU STOP EXAGGERATING,
YOU DOOFUS?
- ( laughs )
STOP ACTIN' EMBARRASSED BRO.
YOU'LL KEEP WINNIN',
YOU KNOW THAT.
UNTIL I BEAT THE PANTS OFF YOU,
AND BECOME THE FASTEST GUY
THAT GUNMA OR ALL OF
KANTO'S GOT TO OFFER
I'M JUST GONNA HAVE TO BE
YOUR CHEERLEADER.
CUZ THEN EVERYONE'S
GONNA CALL ME,
AKINA'S COMET.
- Natsuki: I WAS THINKIN' SINCE
SCHOOL ENDS EARLY TODAY,
WHY DON'T WE DO' SOMETHING
THIS AFTERNOON? COULD BE FUN.
- UH. I KIND OF HAVE TO
WORK THIS AFTERNOON.
- YOU DO?
WELL, THAT REALLY SUCKS.
I WOULDN'T MIND GOIN' FOR
ANOTHER RIDE IN YOUR CAR.
I HAD A LOTTA FUN LAST TIME.
IT'S A SUPER CUTE RIDE.
- WHATEVER, NATSUKI,
IF YOU SAY SO.
BUT I MEAN AT THE END
OF THE DAY, IT'S MY DAD'S CAR.
- I REMEMBER YOU SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT WANTING TO
BUY YOUR OWN CAR.
HAVE YOU SAVED UP MUCH MONEY?
- MOST OF THE CASH I'VE
MADE FROM WORK
HAS BEEN PUT INTO SAVINGS.
BUT I'M STILL LIGHT YEARS
AWAY FROM IT.
- SO HOW MUCH DO YOU NEED?
- AROUND A MILLION YEN,
IF I WANT SOMETHING GOOD.
- WOW. A MILLION, HUH?
AND HOW MUCH YOU GOT NOW?
- NOTHIN' CLOSE TO THAT.
- OKAY, TAKUMI, I JUST
HAVE TO ASK YOU.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO IF I GAVE YOU
THE MONEY YOU NEED?
YOU THINK I'M CRAZY?
BUT I BET YOU'D NEVER STOP
THANKING ME
AND TREAT ME LIKE
A PRINCESS EVERY DAY
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
IN FACT, WITH WHAT YOU'D OWE ME
AND THE AMOUNT OF
PAYBACK I'D NEED,
THEN YOU'D HAVE TO QUIT
WORKING YOUR DAY JOB
AT THE GAS STATION.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY YOU
COULD TAKE CARE OF ME!
( giggling )
- I'M SO EMBARRASSED!
I SHOULD SHUT UP, LIKE NOW!
LOOK THAT'S WAY TOO MUCH MONEY
FOR ANYONE TO JUST COME UP WITH
OUT OF NOWHERE.
- YEAH I KNOW. I WAS JUST
THINKIN' OUT LOUD, GEEZ.
YOU HAVE NO IMAGINATION.
CAN'T A GIRL HAVE SOME FUN?
- IMAGINATION IS ONE THING.
THAT'S CRAZY!
- Iketani: WE NOW BY THIS POINT
THAT TAKUMI'S TECHNIQUE
IS THE REAL DEAL AND IT'LL HOLD
UP ANYWHERE TO ANYONE.
- Yuuichi: YEAH, BUT IT'S MORE
THAN JUST TECHNIQUE.
YOU NEED A TIGHT GRIP
ON SOME NATURAL TALENT
TO BE ABLE TO RACE WELL
ON A NEW COURSE.
- HE'S BORDERLINE GENIUS FOR
BEING ABLE TO DEFEAT
ALL THOSE MODERN CARS
WITH A TEN YEAR OLD EIGHT-SIX.
THAT'S LIKE ROCKSTAR STATUS
DRIVIN', DUDE.
WISH I WAS AS GOOD AS HE IS.
- CHECK YOU OUT.
WEREN'T YOU THE ONE WHO SAID
HE'D NEVER BE ABLE TO COMPETE
ANYWHERE ELSE
BECAUSE ALL HE KNOWS
HOW TO DRIVE IS AKINA PASS?
- WELL, YEAH BUT THINGS CHANGE.
- YEP, THAT'S WHAT WE
ALL THOUGHT TOO.
TAKUMI'S A STRANGE ONE, THOUGH.
WHEN I HEARD ABOUT HIM
TROUNCING UP TO USUI,
I WAS SURE HE'D
LOSE TO MAKO'S SIL-EIGHTY,
BUT LOOK WHAT HAPPENED.
SORRY, IKETANI.
- DON'T EVEN WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'M COOL.
I'VE DECIDED FROM NOW ON
I'LL BE KNOWN AS IKETANI,
THE LONELY DRIVER.
- I THINK I'VE HEARD
THAT ONE BEFORE.
- JUST PULL RIGHT ON IN, SIR.
- FLOWERS? ARE YOU SURE
THIS ISN'T A MISTAKE?
THIS IS A GAS STATION,
IN CASE YOU DIDN'T NOTICE
WHEN YOU ROLLED IN.
THEY'RE FOR YOU, KID.
- WAIT. WHO'S SENDING ME
FLOWERS TO WORK?
- RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
- ( all gasping )
- RYOSUKE.
- TAKAHASHI.
- THE NUMBER ONE BADASS IN
ALL OF GUNMA WANTS YOU!
- HERE! IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA READ
IT TO US, THEN I WILL!
"SEPTEMBER 15TH AT TEN PM.
THE TOP OF MOUNT AKINA."
OH GET REAL.
IT'S GOTTA SAY MORE THAN THAT!
- IT SOUNDS LIKE HE...
- IT'S FINALLY HAPPENED.
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI HAS CHALLENGED
OUR BOY TO A DOWNHILL BATTLE.
- ( all exclaiming )
- SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO DUDE?
- DUH! HE'S GONNA ACCEPT! WHAT
THE HELL ELSE IS HE GONNA DO?
HE ALREADY SMOKED 'RYOSUKE'S
BROTHER LIKE A BIG FAT SAUSAGE!
- Iketani: THAT'S RIGHT.
AND AVOIDING A REMATCH
IS TEN TIMES MORE HUMILIATING
THAN LOSING ONE.
- WHAT'S GOIN ON?
YOU LOOK LIKE SOMETHING'S 'UP.
DO YOU NOT LIKE BEING WITH ME?
- NO. I MEAN, YES,
I LIKE BEING WITH YOU.
- YOU JUST SEEM LIKE YOUR MIND'S
OFF SOMEPLACE ELSE.
LIKE YOU'RE PREOCCUPIED.
WHICH. I GUESS IS KINDA NORMAL.
BUT YOU JUST SEEM SO FAR AWAY.
IF YOU'RE NOT
HAVING A GOOD TIME,
THEN MAYBE THE TWO OF US SHOULD
JUST GO BACK HOME.
- I'M' HAVIN' A GOOD TIME.
NATSUKI, LOOK, I'M SORRY.
- I'LL FORGIVE YOU ONLY IF YOU
TELL ME ONE THING.
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WERE
JUST THINKING ABOUT?
WELL, I, UH... ITS JUST, I DON'T
REALLY THINK YOU'D GET IT
IF I DID TELL YOU.
- LATER.
- OKAY, I'LL TELL YOU! YOU
DON'T HAVE TO FREAK OUT.
- A BATTLE?
- MMM-HMM.
- SO. LIKE A FISTFIGHT?
- NO. A BATTLE IS A RACE.
TWO DRIVERS GOING UP
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
- SO A CAR RACE. FOR REAL?
MAYBE I SHOULD'VE
FIGURED IT OUT,
BUT I NEVER KNEW RACING
CARS WAS YOUR HOBBY.
- IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S
ALWAYS BEEN MY HOBBY.
IT JUST KINDA BECAME ONE
OVER THE PAST COUPLE OF MONTHS.
AND, THE GUY I'M RACING NEXT IS
REALLY GOOD AND SUPER POPULAR.
IT'S ALL I'VE BEEN ABLE
TO THINK ABOUT
SINCE I WOKE UP THIS MORNING.
I GUESS THE PRESSURE IS
REALLY STARTING TO GET TO ME.
- WE BOTH KNOW YOU'RE A GREAT
DRIVER. I'M SURE YOU'LL BE FINE.
- HATE TO TELL YA,
IT'S NOT THAT EASY.
- IF YOU REALLY DON'T
WANNA RACE, JUST BLOW HIM OFF.
- NAH, IT'S NOT LIKE I DON'T
WANNA RACE THE GUY.
I MEAN, THERE'S A CHANCE
I MIGHT EVEN LOSE TO HIM.
BUT I DON'T WANNA
NOT RACE HIM YA KNOW.
- THAT BACK AND FORTH BUSINESS
SOUNDS SO MUCH LIKE YOU.
DEEP DOWN INSIDE IT'S WHAT YOU
REALLY WANT TO DO ISN'T IT?
EVEN THOUGH YOU WON'T SHOW IT.
YOU'RE A CRAZY
COMPETITIVE PERSON.
THAT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
I REALLY LIKE.
I'VE LIKED IT SINCE WE MET.
- ARE YOU READY TO GO?
- WELL, I WAS THINKING WE COULD
TALK FOR A LITTLE WHILE LONGER,
IF THAT WAS COOL WITH YOU.
- SURE.
- I THOUGHT YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT I KNOW, UH,
WHY YOU GOT INTO
THAT FIGHT WITH MIKI
IN THE LOCKER ROOM LAST YEAR.
IT WAS WELL AFTER
YOU HAD QUIT THE TEAM,
ONE OF YOUR TEAMMATES TOLD ME
WHAT HAD HAPPENED
AND WHY YOU DID IT.
YOU STOOD UP FOR ME.
THAT'S HOW IT HAPPENED.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
I'M SORRY. I DON'T MEAN TO
MAKE YOU UNCOMFORTABLE.
- YEAH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NONE OF THAT STUFF
EVEN MATTERS ANYMORE.
FORGET IT.
- INITIAL D.
- INITIAL D!
- ( yawning )
THAT'S TAKUMI'S EIGHT-SIX.
( gasps )
WHO'S THAT CHICK WITH HIM?
- ( car honking )
- ( exclaims ) DUDE,
KEIICHI TSUCHIYA'S DRIFT
TOTALLY ROCKS THE
FREAKING HOUSE.
CHECK THAT OUT.
LOOK AT THESE PICS, BRO.
TAKUMI? HEY. TAKUMI.
- WHAT, ITSUKI? TIME FOR LUNCH
OR SOMETHIN'?
- ( exclaims ) YOU IDIOT!
( laughs ) I WAS TALKING
TO MYSELF. I DO THAT SOMETIMES.
- Iketani: WHAT DO YOU MEAN
TAKUMI'S BEEN ACTING WEIRD?
- YEAH, WHAT'S HE BEEN DOIN'
THAT'S SO STRANGE?
- I DUNNO MAN.
HE JUST SEEMS OFF.
- RIGHT. LIKE EVERY DAY.
- SURE, YEAH I GUESS DUDE.
BUT HE WAS JUST A WHOLE LOT
BETTER DURING THE SUMMER.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PUT IT.
IT'S LIKE WHEN SCHOOL STARTED,
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
HE JUST, KINDA...
HE'S TURNED INTO A BIGGER SPACE
CADET THAN HE EVER WAS BEFORE.
- HE COULD BE WORN OUT
FROM ALL THE RACING.
- NO WAY. HE JUST
STARTED THAT STUFF UP
AT THE BEGINNING OF THE SUMMER.
YA KNOW IT MIGHT
BE SCHOOL ITSELF
THAT'S PULLING HIS FOCUS AWAY
FROM THE CIRCUIT.
- SOMETHING TELLS ME THAT
WE'RE MISSING THE MARK HERE.
IT'S LIKE THERE'S A GEAR
SOMEWHERE IN HIS HEAD
THAT'S BUSTED AND
NEEDS REPLACING.
- WHOA, HANG ON. YOU THINK HE'S
GONNA BE ABLE TO KEEP RACING
IF HE DOESN'T HAVE HIS HEAD
SCREWED ON TIGHT?
- WAIT, I GOT IT.
DOES HE HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
- 'CAUSE MAYBE HIS HEAD
IS STUCK IN THE CLOUDS
DAYDREAMIN' ALL DAY LONG.
- DAYDREAMING?
- LIKE HOW YOU WERE WITH MAKO.
CAN'T STOP THINKIN'
'BOUT HER HOT BOD.
- UH. KENJI YOU DUMBASS.
MIGHT NOT WANNA SAY
THAT NAME AROUND HERE.
- NO, IT'S ALRIGHT. I'M FINE.
- SO. ANYWAY, LIKE I WAS SAYIN,
I SAW TAKUMI DRIVING AROUND
WITH SOME CHICK EARLIER.
- WHAT! ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YEAH, I AM. I ONLY GOT
A GLIMPSE OF HER,
BUT SHE SEEMED PRETTY HOT.
- TAKUMI'S GIRLFRIEND.
- ( screaming )
- WELL. NO WONDER THE GUY KEEPS
DITCHIN' ME AFTER SCHOOL
LIKE I'M SOME KIND
OF DISEASED FREAK.
THAT TRAITOR! THAT JERK.
AND ALL WHILE I'VE NEVER EVEN
GOTTEN TO WALK AROUND
HOLDING A GIRL'S HAND.
- OH. YES! THAT HAS TO BE THE
REASON! I'M SURE OF IT!
- YOU JUST LEAVE IT ALL TO ME.
I'M GONNA INTERROGATE HIM
LIKE HE'S IN A PRISON CAMP!
WE RACERS, WE DON'T NEED CHICKS!
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, IKETANI!
- RIGHT!
- YOU AND ME, WE'RE 'THE
LONELY DRIVERS, MY MAN!
- WHY DO I HANG OUT
WITH THESE LOSERS?
- ( tires screeching )
- WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
YOU'VE BEEN QUIET.
- OH, HAVE I?
WELL BRO, YOU'VE BEEN DATIN'
NATSUKI BEHIND MY BACK,
SO WE'RE BOTH KEEPING SECRETS.
- THAT ALL?
- "THAT ALL?"
- IT'S NOT LIKE I'VE BEEN
KEEPIN' IT A SECRET.
BUT TO BE HONEST IT'S NOT
LIKE THERE'S REALLY MUCH
OF A STORY TO TELL EITHER.
- I DON'T GIVE A HOLY FLYING
CRAP, JUST ANSWER ME THIS...
HOW, UH... HOW FAR HAVE
THE TWO OF YOU GONE?
I'M ASKING YOU AN
HONEST QUESTION.
HOW FAR DID THE TWO OF YOU GO?
- HOW. HOW FAR'D WE...
- AND YOU HAD BETTER TELL
YOUR BEST FRIEND THE TRUTH!
- ITSUKI, KEEP YOUR EYE
ON THE ROAD, DUDE!
- ( screaming )
( tires screeching )
- FINE, I'LL TELL YOU!
- THEN TELL.
- LAST SUNDAY THE TWO OF US...
- ON SUNDAY.
- WE, UH...
YEAH. THE TWO OF YOU?
- WE WENT UP TO AKINA LAKE.
ITSUKI, SERIOUSLY!
GET YOUR HEAD OUT OF YOUR ASS!
WHAT I WANTED TO KNOW WAS
WHICH BASE YOU GOT TO.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN HOW TO
TALK TO A GUY? DAMN, DUDE.
- THE BASE I GOT TO.
- YEAH. DID YOU KISS HER?
OR DID YOU DO
SOMETHING ELSE, HUH?
- WE KISSED.
- YOU DID WHAT?
- ITSUKI, EYES FORWARD! COME ON,
YOU'RE DRIVING LIKE A MANIAC!
- HE'S DAYDREAMING
ABOUT HER RIGHT NOW.
- WHY ARE YOU STARING
AT ME LIKE THAT?
- YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
LIKE A FREAKSHOW.
- I HAVE?
- I KNOW YOU NEVER USE
THAT BRAIN OF YOURS
BUT HERE YOU ARE ACTIN'
LIKE YOU'RE THINKIN'
ABOUT SOMETHIN' CONSTANTLY.
- I GUESS I AM.
- HE PROBABLY CAN'T
STOP THINKIN' ABOUT
NATSUKI'S SOFT, SUPPLE LIPS,
HER WARM SKIN.
- I DON'T KNOW, LATELY
I'VE BEEN' THINKIN A LOT
ABOUT ALL OF THE
DIFFERENT 'THINGS
THAT COULD HAPPEN TO
US IN THE FUTURE.
- ( gasps ) YOU'RE THINKIN'
ABOUT THE FUTURE!
ONE KISS, AND IT'S A
SLIPPERY SLOPE AFTERWARDS.
HOW CAN EVEN THINK OF BRINGIN'
UP SUCH A SHAMEFUL
AND TRAGIC SUBJECT
IN FRONT OF THE MAN YOU KNOW
TO BE THE LONELY RACER?
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY GET WITH
THE PROGRAM BRO,
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING ALL THIS
KISSIN' IS GONNA LEAD TO!
- OH YEAH?
AND WHAT WOULD THAT BE?
YOU KNOW, DUDE! IT!
- YOU'RE INSANE. NOW GET
YOUR HANDS OFF OF ME.
WHAT I MEAN WHEN I'M TALKIN'
ABOUT THE FUTURE IS...
OH. NO. JUST FORGET IT.
YOU KNOW I DON'T EXACTLY
HAVE A WAY WITH WORDS,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- LOOKS LIKE THIS DAYDREAMING
THING ISN'T GONNA GET FIXED
IN JUST ONE QUICK SWIPE.
( tires screeching )
- Man 1: MAN! THOSE SUCKERS
ARE FLYIN'.
IT'S KEISKE'S FD AND
KENTA'S S-FOURTEEN.
- Man 2: KENTA'S FAST GOIN'
DOWN THE HILL.
THAT NON-TURBO S-FOURTEEN
OF HIS IS MADE JUST FOR THAT.
- Man 1: YOU KNOW, KEISUKE
TOOK HIM UNDER HIS WING
AND 'HAS BEEN TRAINING HIM
PERSONALLY EVER SINCE.
- Man 2: YEP, AFTER KEISKE,
HE'S OUR NUMBER TWO SUCCESSOR.
- THE BATTLE AGAINST THE NIGHT
KIDS IS ONLY TWO DAYS AWAY.
I DON'T THINK THAT
KEISUKE SHOULD BE WASTING
ANY OF HIS TIME WITH
KENTA RIGHT NOW.
- I GUESS HE MUST BE PRETTY
CONFIDENT THEN.
- WELL MAYBE TAKESHI IS THAT
CRUMMY OF A DRIVER.
YA KNOW EASY PICKIN'S.
- WOULDN'T DOUBT IT.
KAYSKAY'S BEEN ON FIRE LATELY.
- HE SEEMS ALMOST LIKE HE'S BEEN
DRIVIN' A LITTLE BIT MORE
LIKE REEOHSKAY THESE DAYS.
DON'T YOU THINK?
- MAYBE. I NOTICED
A LITTLE OF THAT.
RYOSUKE'S GOTTA BE FEELIN'
PRETTY CONFIDENT
ABOUT HIS BROTHER PUTTIN' HIM
IN THAT POSITION.
- I HEARD THAT'S WHY HE'S NOT
COMIN' BACK TO MYOGI.
- Kenta: CAN I ASK YOU
A QUESTION, KEISUKE?
- Keisuke: WHACHA GOT FOR ME?
- I JUST WANNA KNOW WHY WE'RE
NOT CHALLENGING THE EIGHT-SIX.
I MEAN, IT SEEMS TO ME WE
SHOULD'VE HAD HIM OUT TO AKAGI
SO WE COULD'VE GOTTEN OUR
REVENGE YA KNOW?
- AKAGI, HUH?
- THAT'S RIGHT, MAN.
THERE'S NOT EVEN THE SLIGHTEST
CHANCE ON THIS PLANET
THAT YOU'D LOSE TO HIM IF YOU
GUYS BATTLED ON OUR OWN TURF.
AND I'LL TELL YA, IF YOU'RE NOT
GONNA DO IT, THEN I WILL!
- FORGET ABOUT IT, KENTA.
- WHY? YOU THINK THIS GUY'LL
ACTUALLY BEAT ME?
NOT ON AKAGI'S DOWNHILL
HE WON'T.
THAT'S BESIDE THE POINT, BUDDY.
YOU'RE AN OFFICIAL RED SUN NOW.
DON'T YOU EVER LET THAT
SLIP YOUR MIND.
WE'RE IN THE BUSINESS OF RACING
ON OUR OPPONENTS' COURSES.
NOT ON OUR OWN.
- RIGHT. I KNOW THAT'S
WHAT WE DO.
IT'S JUST ALMOST TOO MUCH
FOR ME TO HANDLE SOMETIMES.
WITH THAT DAMN EIGHT-SIX
ALWAYS GETTING THE BEST OF US!
I JUST WANT US TO BE ABLE TO
BATTLE THOSE FREAKIN' LOSERS
FAIR AND SQUARE FOR ONCE!
PLEASE. PLEASE LET ME TAKE HIM!
- YOU CALM THE HELL DOWN!
DON'T FREAK OUT ABOUT IT.
WHEN THE OPPORTUNITY
SHOWS ITSELF,
THE PERSON WHO NEEDS TO
PUT AN END TO THIS MESS
IS GONNA DO JUST
THAT. I PROMISE.
- YOU MEAN.
RYOSUKE WILL DO SOMETHING?
- BE PATIENT AND
YOU'LL FIND OUT.
BUT FIRST, WE GOTTA RACE
THE NIGHT KIDS.
SO JUST LEAVE EVERYTHING ELSE
TO ME AND MY BROTHER.
- HE DOES SEEM KINDA WEIRD.
- YOU SEE? HE CONFESSED TO ME
EVERYTHING ABOUT HIM
AND THAT CHICK.
HE'S DAYDREAMING ABOUT
HER ALL DAY LONG.
- WE GOTTA DO SOMETHING.
THERE'S ONLY A WEEK
LEFT BEFORE THE BIG RACE
AND HE'S OUT TO LUNCH.
WE CAN'T AFFORD THAT.
- Kenji: THINGS STAY LIKE THIS,
WE'RE IN SOME SERIOUS TROUBLE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Itsuki: THIS IS SERIOUSLY
NOT A GOOD THING!
- Announcer: WHAT'S NOT
GOOD, ITSUKI?
I MEAN, THE BIG RACE IS...
- FORGET THE STUPID RACE!
TAKUMI'S BEEN DAYDREAMING ABOUT
THAT DAMN CHICK DURING A CRUCIAL
TIME IN HIS RACING LIFE!
- Announcer: DAYDREAMING?
- Itsuki: WHAT WITH HIM AND
NATSUKI DOING WHO KNOWS WHAT,
AND MAYBE EVEN
THE BIG FREAKIN' IT!
- Announcer:
NOT THIS CRAP AGAIN.
- Itsuki: HUH? NEXT TIME ON
INITIAL D,
"FIERCE UPHILL BATTLE!"
DON'T MISS IT!