- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- JERK.
HEY, PUNK! WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOIN' UP HERE?
YOU HIT MY CAR!
LAST NIGHT, REMEMBER!
- OH, SO THAT WAS MY FAULT?
IF YOU COULD HANDLE YOUR RIDE,
IT WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED.
- WHAT?
- I JUST KNEW THE CAR IN
FRONT OF ME WAS SLOW
AND I COULDN'T TAKE
FOLLOWING IT ANYMORE.
I DIDN'T THINK THINGS UP HERE
WENT THAT SLOW,
BUT WHATTAYA GONNA DO?
I TRIED TO BRAKE, BUT I
GUESS I NUDGED YOU A BIT.
SUCKS TO BE YOU
- YOU WANNA SAY THAT
TO ME AGAIN!
- CALM DOWN, IKETANI.
IT'S NOT WORTH IT!
- I'LL TELL YA WHAT,
YOU WANNA SETTLE UP,
WE CAN RACE UNDER MY RULES.
AND IF YOU WIN, THEN I'LL
DROP TO MY FREAKIN' KNEES
AND BEG YOUR FORGIVENESS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY YOUR RULES?
WHY WOULD I AGREE TO THAT?
- IT COULD BE
INTERESTING FOR YOU.
WE CALL IT A GUM
TAPE DEATH MATCH
AND IT'S ONE WILD ASS TIME, HUH.
- GUM TAPE WHAT?
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- I HEAR THE SPEED STAR'S
EIGHT-SIX IS SUPPOSED TO BE
A DOWNHILL SPECIALIST.
TELL HIM I'LL BE WAITING
RIGHT HERE FOR HIM.
HE JUST NEEDS TO MEET
ME HERE NEXT SATURDAY
AT TEN O'CLOCK SHARP.
SEE YOU LOSERS THEN.
- YOU BELIEVE THAT CRAP?
THAT PUNK JUST
CHALLENGED YOU, TAKUMI.
- DOESN'T KNOW
YOUR FACE, THOUGH.
DIDN'T SEEM LIKE HE
RECOGNIZED YOU.
- RIP HIM APART, DUDE.
GUM TAPE DEATH MATCH,
WHO GIVES A CRAP!
JUST CRUSH THAT WANNABE INTO
THE GROUND 'TIL HE'S BEGGING
FOR THE SWEET RELEASE OF DEATH!
- IT'S TOO RISKY FOR HIM TO TRY.
YOU DO REALIZE HE WON'T EVEN
BE ABLE TO STEER.
- DUDE, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKIN' ABOUT?
HE BEAT THE THREE-TWO
AND THE FD, DIDN'T HE?
THIS ONE LITTLE RULE CHANGE
WON'T MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
- LISTEN. THIS GUY'S BEEN
PRACTICING THIS RACE STYLE
WAY MORE THAT TAKUMI.
I'M TELLIN' YA, MAN.
IT'S TOO MUCH OF A RISK TO TAKE.
DON'T BITE ONTO THIS BAIT.
- YEAH. DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW THIS GUY,
SO, WHY WOULD I
WANT TO RACE HIM?
- Iketani: GOOD. HE'S JUST
ANOTHER LOSER,
AND YOU'RE BEST OFF
TO IGNORE HIM.
- Yuuichi: A GUM TAPE
DEATH MATCH? ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- Iketani: NO.
- Yuuichi: THAT'S CRAZY. HOW'S
TAKUMI HANDLING THE WHOLE THING?
- WITH HIS USUAL CALM AND LESS
THAN ENTHUSIASTIC DEMEANOR.
ALMOST LIKE IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
HE'S NOT INTO ANY OF THIS
BUSINESS. DOESN'T EVEN CARE.
- YEAH, BUT I STILL
WANT HIM TO DO IT.
IT'D BE AWESOME FOR HIM TO
CRUSH THAT GUY INTO POWDER
AND MAKE HIM APOLOGIZE FOR BEING
THE AWFUL PERSON THAT HE IS!
HE DRIVES A CIVIC, THE
HISTORIC RIVAL OF THE LEVIN
AND THE TRUENO. THAT
SHOULD BE ENOUGH.
- YOU KNOW. BACK IN MY DAY,
WE RAN RACES IN A LOT OF
DIFFERENT WAYS.
EVERY GUY HAD HIS OWN FAVORITE
SET OF RULES AND REGULATIONS.
BUT WE ALL STAYED AWAY FROM
GUM TAPE DEATH MATCHES
BECAUSE WE KNEW HOW
DANGEROUS THEY WERE.
- IS THIS GUM TAPE THING
THAT BAD?
IT SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING
IN A CANDY STORE.
IT ACTUALLY SOUNDS
LIKE IT'D BE TASTY.
- HEY, WHY DON'T YOU GO HOP IN
YOUR CAR FOR A MINUTE.
GIVE IT A SHOT,
SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
- OKAY. NOW WHAT?
NOW, GRAB THE WHEEL
WITH YOUR RIGHT HAND
AND TURN IT AS FAR AS YOU
CAN TO ONE SIDE.
JUST SEE HOW FAR YOU CAN GET.
- ( Itsuki grunting )
I DON'T THINK IT'LL GO
ANY FARTHER.
LEAVE THE WHEEL SITTING WHERE
IT IS NOW AND HOP ON OUT.
- YEAH, ALRIGHT.
- I WANT YOU TO SEE
HOW FAR YOU STEERED.
- PRETTY FAR, I BET.
( gasps ) NO WAY.
I TURNED IT AS FAR AS I COULD!
WHAT THE HELL, MAN?
- SEE?
- HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO CORNER
WITH YOUR WHEELS LIKE THIS?
YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT TAKING ON
THE WHOLE MOUNTAIN PASS.
- THE STEERING'S JUST USED TO
INITIATE THE TURN.
THE TURN'S COMPLETED
BY SLIDING THE REAR TIRES.
NOT AN EASY THING TO DO.
AND YOU DO IT EVERY CORNER.
- WHAT? BUT TAKUMI'S
A DRIFT EXPERT.
HE CAN MANAGE. HE KNOWS WHAT'S
HE'S DOIN' MORE THAN US.
- YOU'RE OVERSIMPLIFYING
THE PROCESS, MAN.
YOU CAN'T COUNTER,
WHICH MAKES IT WAY HARDER TO
CONTROL THE DRIFT.
IT'S NEXT TO IMPOSSIBLE.
IF YOU OVERSTEER THE SUCKER,
THAT MEANS YOU FLY INTO A SPIN.
BUT IF YOU UNDERSTEER
INTO THE TURN,
THEN YOU'RE JUST
FREAKIN' HISTORY,
LIKE 'BOOM' INTO THE ROCKFACE.
- THIS RULE OF HIS DEFINITELY
FAVORS THE FF OVER ANYONE ELSE.
THIS FELLA DRIVES AN EG-SIX?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THE ACCELERATOR ON THAT CAR
ELIMINATES OVERSTEERING,
SO HE CAN ATTACK THOSE
CORNERS AT FULL SPEED.
AND IF HE CAN USE
THE HAND BRAKE,
THAT'LL CUT OUT THE
UNDERSTEERING.
BUT THE EIGHT-SIX NEEDS TO
DRIFT CONSTANTLY
THROUGH A NARROW AREA.
LIKE IT'S WALKING A TIGHTROPE.
I'D SAY YOU GUYS ARE PAINTED
INTO A CORNER ON THIS ONE.
IT'S BETTER TO JUST AVOID
THE WHOLE THING.
- OH, NO. TALKING LIKE THIS
MIGHT GET HIM INTERESTED
IN RACING THIS GUY.
BETTER CLAM UP.
- UH. BOSS.
- ( car honking )
- HEY, THAT'S KENJI'S CAR,
ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
- IKETANI. I DID A LITTLE BIT OF
CHECKIN' UP ON THAT JERK
FROM THE OTHER NIGHT.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
WHAT I FOUND OUT.
TURNS OUT HE'S NONE OTHER THAN
SHINGO SHOJI OF THE
MYOGI NIGHT KIDS.
- WE GOT ANOTHER NIGHT KID
ON OUR BACKS?
- IN THEIR LINEUP,
HE'S THE NUMBER TWO DRIVER.
BUT HE'S GOT ENOUGH CONFIDENCE
TO CALL HIMSELF
THE FASTEST DOWNHILLER
THE NIGHT KIDS HAVE TO OFFER.
HE STOPS AT NOTHIN'
TO GET WHAT HE WANTS,
WHICH DOESN'T MAKE HIM THE MOST
POPULAR GUY WITH HIS TEAMMATES.
ESPECIALLY NOT WITH THEIR
LEADER, TAKESHI.
THEY TEND TO GO
FOR EACH OTHERS' THROATS.
- NOW IT'S ALL COMIN' TOGETHER.
HE'S CHALLENGING US IN A BID
TO KNOCK TAKESHI OFF THE THRONE
SO HE CAN TAKE OVER
HIS GROUP'S LEADERSHIP.
- AND TALK ABOUT
PRESSIN' THE ISSUE.
HE'S BEEN SPREADING RUMORS
ABOUT THE RACE ALL OVER TOWN.
- LIKE WHAT?
- SOMETHIN' ABOUT THE
SPEED STARS BEING SCARED.
DOIN' EVERYTHING THEY CAN TO
AVOID SHINGO'S CHALLENGE.
COURSE HE DOESN'T MENTION
ANYTHING ABOUT THE GUM TAPE.
- JUST A CRUMMY EFFORT TO
MAKE US LOOK AS BAD AS HE CAN.
- ( grunts ) I HATE THAT GUY!
- HE'LL DO ANYTHING HE CAN
TO DRAG TAKUMI INTO THIS RACE.
NOTHING'LL STOP HIM.
- TAKUMI?
GUYS JUST LET IT GO? REALLY I
DON'T WANNA RACE THIS GUY.
I NEVER HAVE AND I NEVER WILL.
( sighing in relief )
- THAT'S GOOD, MAN. YOU KNOW
THERE'S NO POSTED RULE THAT SAYS
YOU HAVE TO ACCEPT EVERY
CHALLENGE THROWN YOUR WAY.
YOU CAN DO WHAT YOU WANT.
LET HIM SPIN HIS WHEELS.
- I WILL.
- SO, WHAT EVER CAME OF THE
WHOLE RACING THE EIGHT-SIX CRAP?
- ( scoffs ) I'M READY TO ROLL
WHENEVER HE IS.
BALL'S IN THE
SPEED STARS' COURT NOW.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, FELLAS.
I'LL DRAG THIS IDIOT
OUT INTO THE OPEN.
- IT'LL BE A NICE BEATING
TO WATCH WHENEVER IT HAPPENS.
TAKESHI!
- HEY, SHINGO. LISTEN, I GET THE
FEELING THAT YOU'RE RAMPIN' UP
FOR SOMETHING PRETTY BIG.
SO JUST DO WHAT YOU WANT, OKAY?
I CAN'T STOP YOU.
JUST DON'T DO ANYTHING
THAT'LL TARNISH THE NAME
OF THE NIGHT KIDS.
- ( Shingo laughing )
- IS SOMETHING FUNNY TO YOU?
- I FIGURED YOU ALREADY
TRASHED OUR GOOD NAME
WHEN YOU GOT DUSTED
BY THE EIGHT-SIX.
WHAT?
- YOU GOT THIS MONSTER THREE-TWO
AND YOU STILL FELL FLAT
ON YOUR FACE IN
FRONT OF THAT GUY?
SERIOUSLY, YOUR FEET BROKEN
OR SOMETHIN'?
- SHUT UP.
- SHOULDN'T A LOSER BE OFF
CRYING IN A DARK
CORNER SOMEPLACE?
ACTING LIKE SOME LEADER,
AND GIVING ME A LECTURE.
YOU'RE WHAT'S FUNNY, MAN.
DON'T SWEAT IT. I'LL AVENGE YOU
ON THE MOUNTAIN, TAKESHI.
YOU CAN THANK ME LATER.
- ONE OF THESE DAYS YOU'RE GONNA
FIND OUT JUST HOW TOUGH
THAT EIGHT-SIX
ACTUALLY IS, SHINGO.
AND I HOPE IT'S SOON.
- LOOKS LIKE TAKESHI
HIT THE ROCKS.
I ALMOST FEEL BAD
FOR THE STUPID PUNK.
- I GOT NO SYMPATHY.
HE DID THIS TO HIMSELF.
SHINGO, YOU'RE THE NEW LEADER
OF THE NIGHT KIDS
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
- THANKS. BUT BEFORE I CAN THINK
OF TAKIN' THAT POSITION ON,
I GOTTA SEND AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX
TO THE SCRAPYARD.
- ( dialing )
- ( ringing )
- HI THERE. MY NAME'S ITSUKI,
CAN I SPEAK TO...
OH. HEY, SAORI, HOW'RE YOU?
- HI. GLAD YOU CALLED.
YES, OF COURSE I REMEMBER
WHO YOU ARE, SILLY.
UH, SURE.
A ROAD TRIP UP TO
LAKE AKINA? YEAH, I'D LOVE TO.
- ( gasps )
GREAT, I'LL MEET YOU AT THE
BUS STOP AT ONE O'CLOCK
AND WE'LL GO FROM THERE.
YEAH. I'LL SEE YA THEN.
ALRIGHT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
MY YEARS-LONG
NO-GIRLFRIEND DROUGHT
IS FINALLY COMING TO AN END!
( laughs ) I'M BACK, BABY!
- ( alarm beeping )
- HERE YA GO.
- HEY, DAD, I GOT A
QUESTION FOR YA.
- WHAT IS IT?
- IS A GUM TAPE DEATH MATCH...
UH, NEVER MIND.
- A GUM TAPE DEATH MATCH, HUH?
- ( engine revving )
( tires screeching )
- Natsuki: TAKUMI,
YOU KNOW SOMETHING.
YOU'RE A GOOD DRIVER.
A VERY GOOD ONE.
AND TAKUMI, IF YOU HADN'T
FIGURED IT OUT,
I WOULDN'T MIND IT IF YOU WANTED
TO TAKE ME ON AN OVERNIGHT TRIP.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS, BUT
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT HER
A WHOLE LOT LATELY.
INITIAL D!
- ( engine starting )
- Both: THANK YOU
FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- YOU FELLAS SEEN ITSUKI?
- YEAH. HE WAS JUST OUT HERE
WASHING HIS CAR.
- Iketani: I DON'T SEE HIM.
WHERE'D HE GO?
- OKAY, OKAY. THAT MAKES SENSE.
- THERE YOU ARE. SO THIS WHERE
YOU BEEN HIDIN' ALL DAY, HUH?
- I WASN'T HIDING.
I WAS RESTING.
I DIDN'T GET MUCH
SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
- SO. WHATCHA READIN'?
LET'S TAKE A LOOK!
- GIVE IT BACK! IT'S NOTHING!
IT'S JUST A...
- MY GOODNESS. LOOK AT THIS.
"LOVE MANUAL, HOW TO
IMPRESS YOUR DATE."
- C'MON, I WAS JUST
LOOKING AT THE PICTURES.
BE STRAIGHT WITH ME. THE REASON
YOU'RE READING THIS IS
'CAUSE YOU GOT A DATE?
- YOU CAN TELL ME.
- YES!
- COME HERE, GOOFBALL.
IS IT THAT SAORI CHICK
YOU WERE TALKIN' ABOUT BEFORE?
WHAT ABOUT ME?
YOU COULDN'T ASK FOR MY ADVICE?
- SORRY. I GRABBED
THE BOOK YESTERDAY.
I JUST WANT THE DATE TO GO
SMOOTHLY, SO I BEEN STUDYING.
BESIDES, WHY WOULD I COME TO YOU
FOR ADVICE ABOUT WOMEN?
- YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT ABOUT THAT,
DUDE, BUT IT STILL
HURTS TO HEAR IT.
- ( Itsuki grunting )
NO!
- THINGS SEEM TO BE
A LOT EASIER NOWADAYS.
WHEN I WAS YOUNG IT
WAS NOTHING BUT TRIAL
AND LOTS AND LOTS OF ERROR.
LET'S SEE. "YOU SHOULD HAVE HER
EATING OUT OF YOUR HAND
BY THE THIRD DATE.
"IF NOT, REPEAT STEPS
TWO AND THREE.
"STEP TWO, CREATE A ROMANTIC
SETTING FOR YOUR FIRST KISS."
- YEAH. DON'T WORRY, BOSS,
I GOT THAT COVERED.
AND SO, LIKE I MENTIONED
TO YOU BEFORE,
I'D LIKE A DAY OFF THIS WEEKEND,
IF THAT'S OKAY BY YOU.
- OH, THAT'S WHY YOU WANT
TIME OFF. THEN, SURE.
- Iketani: YOU KNOW ITSUKI,
I'M A LITTLE JEALOUS.
- I LOOK SO FREAKIN' COOL.
THIS IS GONNA BE AWESOME!
WAIT. WHERE IS SHE?
( Saori panting )
- ITSUKI, I'M RIGHT OVER HERE!
SORRY I'M LATE!
( giggles )
- ( exclaims )
THIS IS GONNA BE SO FUN.
- THANKS FOR COME...
- I DON'T NEED ANY GAS,
GREASE MONKEY.
I JUST STOPPED BY TO
GET AN ANSWER
TO MY CHALLENGE INVITATION.
YOU DID PASS ALONG
MY MESSAGE, DIDN'T YOU?
- UH. YEAH. BUT HE SAID
HE DIDN'T WANNA RACE YOU.
WASN'T INTERESTED IN IT.
- ( grunts ) THAT'S HILARIOUS
IF IT'S TRUE.
I DIDN'T REALIZE THE EIGHT-SIX
DUDE WAS SUCH A GIANT COWARD.
HE CAN'T BE SCARED OF
A LITTLE GUM TAPE, CAN HE?
FORGET IT. I'LL MAKE SURE HE
WANTS TO COME OUT AND RACE ME.
- MAN, SHE'S SO CUTE!
- ( Itsuki grunting )
SINCE WE'RE STREET RACERS,
WE USUALLY DON'T TALK ABOUT
TURNING A CORNER.
WE LIKE TO SAY
ATTACKING THE CORNER.
- MAYBE I SHOULD GET
MY DRIVER'S LICENSE.
- SURE. I COULD TEACH YOU
TO DRIVE IF YOU WANT ME TO.
- GIVE ME SOME TIME
TO THINK ABOUT THAT ONE.
WOW. MOUNT FUJI.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL FROM HERE!
- GIRLS ARE SUCH SUCKERS
FOR THIS ROMANCE THING.
AND THE BOOK SAID THE FIRST KISS
SHOULD ALWAYS BE AT
A ROMANTIC SETTING.
CHECK AND CHECK.
THE FIRST KISS.
( chuckling )
NOW'S THE PERFECT TIME.
GO FOR IT, ITSUKI!
- ( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( sneezing )
I'M SORRY.
( groaning )
- PERFECT, AWKWARD SILENCE.
WHAT NOW? THE BOOK DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS.
♪ COOL VIBRATIONS ♪
- ( low chuckling )
♪ I WANT TO DANCE ♪
- FOUND YOU.
- ( both gasping )
- THAT GUY JUST BUMPED ME!
AND HE'S IN AN EG-SIX.
WHAT, AM I GOIN' TOO SLOW
FOR HIM OR SOMETHING?
HE'S RIGHT ON MY TAIL. I CAN'T
LOOK BAD IN FRONT OF SAORI.
I GOTTA DO SOMETHIN'!
♪ DEEP INSIDE ♪
SAORI, I'M GONNA HAVE
TO SPEED UP.
YOU PROBABLY WANNA
HOLD ON TO SOMETHING.
♪ I'M FEELING
THE POWER GETTING HOT ♪
- ( Saori screaming )
♪ BY THE BACK DOOR ♪
♪ GET UP TONIGHT ♪
♪ MAKE UP YOUR LIFE
AND BRING IT ON ♪
♪ SINCE THE LIGHT
HAS GONE BABY ♪
ITSUKI! ITSUKI, STOP!
- NO WAY, WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF A STREET RACE!
I CAN'T STOP NOW!
♪ DANCING ♪
♪ WE GOTTA DANCE
UNTIL THE MORNING ♪
♪ I SEND MY KISSES
TO MY FRIENDS ♪
- ( laughing )
♪ WE GOTTA DANCE ♪
♪ I SEND MY KISSES
TO MY FRIENDS ♪
♪ WE GOTTA DANCE
UNTIL THE MORNING ♪
♪ I SEND MY KISSES
TO MY FRIENDS ♪
- ( screaming )
♪ DANCING ♪
♪ FLASHING TO MYSELF ♪
♪ DANCING MORNING ♪
♪ TO MY FRIENDS ♪
♪ DANCING ♪
- ( tires screeching )
- I'VE GOTTA PROTECT SAORI,
NO MATTER WHAT!
- ( crashing )
- BOYS, I JUST GOT A PHONE CALL!
ITSUKI'S HAD AN ACCIDENT!
- WHERE?
- AKINA PASS. THEY'RE OVER
AT THE CITY HOSPITAL.
CAN YOU GUYS HEAD OVER THERE
AND MAKE SURE HE'S OKAY?
- YEAH.
- SURE.
- ITSUKI, ARE YOU OKAY?
- HEY, IKETANI! TAKUMI!
- SO WHAT HAPPENED UP THERE?
- OH, IT ISN'T AS BAD
AS IT LOOKS.
THEY'RE JUST KEEPING ME HERE
FOR SOME TESTS.
YOU KNOW, THEY WANT
TO MAKE SURE EVERYTHING'S COOL.
LIKE MY STITCHES DON'T POP OUT
OR MY HEAD DOESN'T EXPLODE.
- WHAT ABOUT SAORI?
WASN'T SHE IN THE CAR, TOO?
- YEAH, BUT SHE ONLY
HAD A COUPLE OF CUTS
AND BRUISES ON HER,
SO THEY SENT HER HOME.
I TRIED MY BEST TO PULL
THE WHEEL TO PROTECT
THE PASSENGER SIDE
WHEN WE WRECKED.
- AND YOUR LEVIN.
HOW DID THAT THING HOLD UP?
- I ACTUALLY SPUN THE
THING PRETTY WELL,
SO IT LOOKS LIKE THE TRUNK AREA
TOOK THE BRUNT OF THE DAMAGE.
- THERE WE GO.
NOW GET SOME REST.
- OKAY. THANKS A LOT!
- ( Itsuki crying )
- I WAS HEADED DOWN THE PASS.
THEN IT HAPPENED.
THIS EG-SIX STARTED
TAILGATING ME.
- AN EG-SIX? WAS IT WHO
I THINK IT WAS?
- MAYBE. SAME MAKE, MODEL
AND COLOR ANYWAY.
HE BUMPED ME FROM BEHIND
RIGHT BEFORE A CORNER.
- Iketani: I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
BASTARD DID IT TO US AGAIN.
- Takumi: I'LL DO IT.
GUM TAPE DEATH MATCH OR
WHATEVER. I DON'T CARE.
I'M TAKING HIM ON.
- Iketani: TAKUMI,
HOLD UP! WAIT!
CRAP, I'M SORRY!
DON'T LET HIM DRAG YOU IN!
THIS WHOLE THING IS JUST
A SORRY EXCUSE FOR RACING!
DON'T FALL FOR IT!
IF IT'S A TRAP, FINE.
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
HE'S GETTING AWAY WITH THIS.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
♪ YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
♪ NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- Announcer: HEY, SHINGO,
DON'T YOU THINK IT
WAS WRONG OF YOU
TO DRAG ITSUKI
INTO THIS AND MAKE HIM
SPIN OUT LIKE THAT?
- HEY, I DON'T GIVE A CRAP
ABOUT ANYTHING AS LONG
AS I DRAG THE EIGHT-SIX
OUT TO RACE ME.
- YEAH, BUT...
- LOOK LOOK, I KNOW WITHOUT A
DOUBT I'M GONNA BEAT HIM
WITH THE GUM TAPE RULES.
BUT WINNING ALONE
ISN'T ENOUGH FOR ME, YOU KNOW.
I NEED TO PUT ON A SHOW.
THAT'S JUST THE KINDA GUY I AM.
- Announcer: NEXT TIME ON
INITIAL D, "EVOLVING DRIFT."
- I'M GONNA GET THAT
KID ON THE DOWNHILL
AND SHOW HIM WHAT FEAR IS.
DON'T MISS IT!