- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- ( tires screeching )
- HE CAUGHT UP TO ME? WHAT
THE HELL'S GOIN' ON WITH THIS?
I GOTTA BE LOSIN' MY MIND!
- OK, GUYS,
THIS IS THE STRAIGHTAWAY
IN FRONT OF THE SKATING RINK.
THEY JUST FLEW BY! HE'S CHEWIN'
ON KEISUKE'S BUMPER!
KEISUKE'S FD HAS NEVER HAD
ANYONE KEEP UP WITH IT THIS FAR
OR THIS TIGHT!
- ( all gasping )
- OH, MAN, I'VE GOT GOOSEBUMPS.
- Spotter 1: THAT EIGHT-SIX IS
ONE AGGRESSIVE BEAST
ON THE ROAD.
IT WAS SOME KIND
OF KAMIKAZE TECHNIQUE.
THIS GUY'S GOT NO FEAR.
- I KNOW MY OLD MAN.
UNLESS I PASS THAT CAR, HE WON'T
ADMIT THAT I WON THIS RACE.
WHICH MEANS, I DON'T
HAVE A WHOLE LOT OF CHOICE.
GUESS I'M GONNA HAVE TO DO IT.
I MEAN I'VE GOT A FULL
TANK OF GAS RIDING ON THIS.
THE SETUP FOR THE OVERTAKE
IS GONNA BE SOMEWHERE
IN THE NEXT FIVE HAIRPIN TURNS.
- THIS SUCKS!
- ( engine revving )
- WHAT'S GOING ON WITH MY RIDE?
WHY'S MY FD FEELIN' SO SLOW?
WHAT CRAP TIMING.
I WONDER IF THE SECONDARY
TURBINE IS STILL WORKING?
- TOP OF THE MOUNTAIN HERE.
YOU READ ME?
- Boy 1: ( on walkie-talkie )
GOTCHA, RYOSUKE.
- PRETTY SOON THEY'RE
GONNA BE REACHING
THOSE FIVE CONSECUTIVE HAIRPINS.
I WANT THE PLAY
BY PLAY ON THAT.
GIVE ME AS MUCH DETAIL AS YOU
CAN FROM YOUR VANTAGE POINT.
- NO SWEAT. OKAY. OKAY.
THEY'RE GETTING CLOSE.
I CAN ALREADY HEAR
THEIR TIRES SQUEALIN'.
THEY'LL BE ON US IN NO TIME.
HERE THEY ARE! THE FD'S
LEADIN' THE EIGHT-SIX,
BUT THEY'RE TIGHT!
OH, THEY'RE ALL OVER EACH OTHER!
THE EIGHT-SIX IS KNOCKING OUT
SOME SICK MOVES!
IT DID A PERFECT BRAKING-DRIFT!
KEISUKE'S LOSIN' SERIOUS GROUND!
SWEET RECOVERY!
OH, HE'S CLOSER TO THE GUARDRAIL
THAN I'VE EVER SEEN!
GOIN' INTO THE
SECOND HAIRPIN NOW,
NOT A GAP BETWEEN
THE TWO OF 'EM!
( whooping ) THEY BOTH RECOVERED
AT THE SAME TIME!
THE FD SLIPPED A LITTLE
CLOSE TO THE OUTSIDE,
AND THE EIGHT-SIX IS-- WHOA!
- HE'S NOT BRAKING FOR THE NEXT
HAIRPIN. WHAT'S HE THINKING?
- Boy 1: ( on walkie-talkie )
OH. OH, THE EIGHT-SIX IS HEADING
STRAIGHT INTO THE CORNER, FAST.
REALLY FAST! IT'S LIKE HIS
FREAKIN' BRAKES ARE OUT!
- ( scraping )
- ( exclaims ) WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT?
- ( all gasping )
- Boy 1: HE PASSED
ON THE INSIDE.
HE MADE KEISUKE
LOOK LIKE A GRANDMA
DRIVING HOME FROM CHURCH.
- YOU CANNOT BE SERIOUS.
WE ASKED FOR DETAILS, NOW TELL
US EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED!
- LOOK, DUDE, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
ELSE YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU.
ALL I KNOW IS A CAR SHOULDN'T
TURN LIKE THAT.
IT SHOULDN'T TURN
AT A SPEED FASTER
THAN THE TIRE'S GRIP WILL
LET IT, RIGHT?
BUT THE WAY THE EIGHT-SIX TURNED
WAS STRANGE.
LIKE A ROLLER COASTER.
HE EVEN MOVED THROUGH THAT
LINE ON THE INSIDE
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE BAD.
I HAVE NO CLUE WHAT
THAT WAS ALL ABOUT.
IT MAKES NO FREAKIN' SENSE!
- I KNOW WHAT THE GUY DID.
NOT A HALF-BAD MOVE
FOR AN OLD EIGHT-SIX.
IT'S RISKY, AND I BET THAT KID'S
THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN DO IT.
BELIEVE ME, YOU WON'T SEE
THAT TRICK AGAIN ANYWHERE
BUT MOUNT AKINA.
PROBABLY 'CAUSE THIS IS THE
ONLY PLACE YOU CAN FIND
A DRIVER THAT STUPID.
NOW I GOT SOMETHIN'
TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
YOU MIGHT BE THE HOTTEST RACER
ON AKINA TONIGHT,
BUT SOON ENOUGH,
YOU'RE GONNA GET SMOKED.
BY ME, TAKESHI NAKAZATO
OF THE MYOGI NIGHT KIDS.
- Spotter 1: (on walkie-talkie)
FINISH LINE HERE!
I CAN HEAR THE ENGINES
GETTING CLOSE.
THEY'RE RIGHT ON TOP OF US.
HERE THEY ARE.
WHO'S IN THE LEAD!
- Spotter 2: THE EIGHT-SIX!
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON!
KEISUKE'S PULLIN' UP THE REAR
BUT HE'S GOT TOO MUCH
GROUND TO COVER!
THE EIGHT-SIX WINS!
IT'S ALL HIS!
♪ IT'S THE SOUND OF YOUR HEART ♪
♪ THAT YOU HEAR DEEP INSIDE ♪
- CRAP! MY FD BEATEN BY
THAT STINKIN' TRUENO, AGAIN!
HOW'D I LET THAT HAPPEN?
350 HORSES AND I LOSE TO
A DAMN EIGHT-SIX!
♪ FEEL IT, FEEL IT BABY
FEEL THE FIRE ♪
- THE EIGHT-SIX JUST CROSSED
THE FINISH LINE! KEISUKE LOST!
- YES! WE DID IT! WE WON!
♪ DANCE TO THE HEARTBEAT ♪
♪ WOH OH OH ♪
♪ YOU BETTER TAKE
YOUR CHANCES RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ DANCE TO THE HEARTBEAT ♪
♪ AND LET IT GO ♪
♪ SEEK THE POWER THAT
IN YOUR BODY FLOWS ♪
♪ DANCE TO THE HEARTBEAT ♪
- ( exclaims ) I DON'T
UNDERSTAND IT.
THIS HAS GOTTA BE SOME KINDA
SCREWED UP NIGHTMARE!
HOW COULD I LOSE TWICE
TO THE SAME EIGHT-SIX?
- IF SOMEBODY AS DUMB AS TAKUMI
CAN BEAT KEISUKE,
THERE'S HOPE FOR ALL OF US!
- TOO COOL. DON'T THINK
I'VE EVER BEEN HAPPIER.
FEELS LIKE I'M GOING NUMB OR
MAYBE I'M JUST LOSING MY MIND.
- ( laughs ) NOPE, HE DID IT!
DON'T START CRYING
ON ME, IKETANI!
- I'M TRYIN' NOT TO, MAN,
BUT I'M HAPPY.
- YOU THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD TAKE
A FEW LESSONS FROM THE GUY?
WE COULD GET HIM
TO TEACH US DRIFT CONTROL
OR PICKING THE RIGHT LINE.
HOLD ON. LET'S PUT THE SPEED
STARS' STICKER ON HIS CAR.
- HEY! LET ME! LET ME!
I WANNA DO IT! CAN I?
- Iketani: COOL. THAT'S YOUR JOB
WHEN WE GET BACK.
ONLY 'CAUSE YOU BEGGED
LIKE A BITCH.
- TONIGHT WAS A CLEAR
LOSS FOR OUR TEAM.
LET'S OWN UP TO IT
WITH SOME CLASS.
- HOW ABOUT THE TIMED RUN FOR
THE UPHILL? WE STILL GOT THAT.
- THE UPHILL MEANS NOTHING
AT THIS POINT.
- BY TOMORROW, RUMORS ARE GOING
TO START SPREADING AROUND
ALL THE STREET
RACERS IN THE AREA.
IT WON'T BE LONG
BEFORE EVERYBODY KNOWS
THE UNDEFEATED REDSUNS LOST
TO AN EIGHT-SIX FROM AKINA.
- I GUESS THAT MEANS WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO EVEN THE SCORE SOON.
AND WE'LL DO IT WITH MY FC.
( engine revving )
♪ DANCE TO THE HEARTBEAT ♪
- ( dog howling )
- ( engine revving )
- ( Japanese song
playing on TV )
- ( door opens and closes )
- HMM?
- I DID WHAT YOU WANTED.
SO YOU OWE ME A TANK OF GAS.
JUST REMEMBER, YOU PROMISED.
- I COULDN'T BE
HAPPIER THAT HE WON.
BUT I CAN'T SAY I'M
TOO SURPRISED.
THIS IS THE SPOT.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHERE
THAT PRICK PASSED ME.
I JUST DON'T GET IT, MAN.
HIS CAR SUCKS AT RIDING
THOSE INSIDE CORNERS.
HOW'D IT SLIP THROUGH
FASTER THAN MY FD?
JUST REMEMBERING IT
GETS UNDER MY SKIN.
I TELL YA, BRO, THIS GUY
HAS GOTTA BE SOME KINDA GHOST.
- HEY, KEISUKE,
TELL ME WHAT WENT DOWN
RIGHT WHEN HE PASSED YOU.
WAS THERE ANYTHING WEIRD
ABOUT THE WAY HE DID IT?
- COME TO THINK OF IT, I DID
HEAR A STRANGE SOUND.
LIKE SCRAPING.
A SCRAPING SOUND?
- ( chuckles ) I GET IT NOW...
- WHAT?
- SO DO YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU
WHY YOU LOST?
BECAUSE I THINK
I HAVE IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
- INITIAL D!
- HE MUST'VE USED THIS PART
OF THE ROAD RIGHT HERE.
- A DRAINAGE DITCH?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HE DROPPED HIS INSIDE TIRES
INTO THE DITCH ON PURPOSE.
BY HOOKING THE
EDGE OF THE ROAD,
HE RESISTED THE
CENTRIFUGAL FORCE.
THAT WAY IT WAS POSSIBLE
TO GAIN MORE CORNERING FORCE
THAN THE TIRES
COULD GRIP ON THEIR OWN.
IT MIGHT SEEM LIKE
AN AMATEURISH SOLUTION,
MAYBE EVEN
A LITTLE BIT RIDICULOUS.
AND IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING
THAT HE WOULD
HAVE FAILED MISERABLY
IF HE'D NEVER DONE IT BEFORE.
I ASSUME THAT HE PROBABLY
PRACTICES LIKE THIS
ALL THE TIME.
HE'D NEED YEARS OF
PRACTICE TO PULL THAT MOVE OFF
SO NONCHALANTLY DURING A RACE.
- THAT LITTLE PUNK!
- LOOK, PART OF
THE FUN OF RACING
IS THAT THIS KIND
OF THING HAPPEN.
AND IF YOU'RE LIKE ME,
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN ABLE
TO GET EXCITED
ABOUT ANY OF OUR
POTENTIAL TARGETS.
WE'RE GOING TO CANCEL THE
EXPEDITION WE HAD PLANNED
FOR NEXT WEEKEND.
WE'RE NOT MOVING ON TO ANYTHING
UNTIL WE CAN LOCK DOWN A
COMPLETE VICTORY HERE.
I'M GOING TO BE THE ONE
TO BEAT THAT EIGHT-SIX.
"GREEN SHOPPING STREET"
- Yuuichi: YO, BUNTA!
YOU HERE? IT'S ME.
"CLOSED TODAY"
( sighs ) MAN, IT'S HOT.
- HEY, YUUICHI. PERFECT TIMING.
I HAVE A MEETING AT THE CHAMBER
OF COMMERCE I GOTTA GET TO.
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
CAN YOU GIVE ME A RIDE?
- COME ON.
WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE TO YOU?
YOUR PERSONAL TAXI SERVICE?
- ( horns blaring )
- Yuuichi: I HEARD
TAKUMI REALLY KNOCKED IT
OUT OF THE PARK ON THE DOWNHILL.
IKETANI AND THE OTHERS
HAVE BEEN GIGGLING LIKE GIRLS.
- IT'S NOT LIKE HE MOVED
THE MOUNTAIN, YOU KNOW.
MAN, KIDS THESE DAYS ARE
IMPRESSED BY ALMOST ANYTHING.
- ( Yuuichi laughs )
- TAKUMI DOESN'T EVEN LIKE
DRIVING CARS. DID YOU KNOW THAT?
- YOU'RE YANKING MY CHAIN.
HE'S A TEENAGE BOY, RIGHT?
AND HE HAS INCREDIBLE TECHNIQUE
FOR SOMEONE HIS AGE.
- TO HIM, DRIVING HELPS OUT
WITH THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING GLAMOROUS
ABOUT IT.
I'VE FORCED HIM TO DO IT
SINCE HE WAS A KID.
WHAT'D YA EXPECT?
HE JUST CAN'T SEE
THE FUN IN IT.
- I GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE.
- HE'S JUST CYNICAL
ABOUT DRIVING.
YOU KNOW,
TYPICAL REBEL TEENAGE BS.
BUT HE'LL HAVE TO GROW OUT
OF THAT SOONER OR LATER.
ALL HE NEEDS IS SOMETHING
TO GET HIS BLOOD BOILING,
AND THAT RACE LAST
NIGHT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
THE KICK IN THE PANTS HE NEEDS.
- SPEAKING OF WHICH, I ASSUME
HE TOOK THE EIGHT-SIX.
WHERE'D HE GO?
- NO IDEA.
BUT HE SCURRIED OFF SOMEWHERE
THIS MORNING IN A HURRY
AND IN A HELLUVA GOOD MOOD.
- ( chuckles )
( Natsuki giggling )
TAKUMI, YOU KNOW SOMETHING.
YOU'RE A GOOD DRIVER
A VERY GOOD ONE.
- OH. YOU THINK SO?
- TO TELL THE TRUTH,
USUALLY I GET CARSICK
WHEN I RIDE WITH SOMEONE.
SO I THOUGHT AHEAD THIS TIME
AND BROUGHT ALONG SOME
MEDICINE FOR THAT KINDA THING.
BUT I DIDN'T FEEL SICK ONE BIT
WHEN YOU WERE DRIVING US
OUT HERE. IT WAS COOL.
I CAN'T EVEN
REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
I RODE IN A CAR FOR
SUCH A LONG TIME
WITHOUT GETTING REALLY SICK.
- ARE YOU RIDING IN CARS A LOT
THESE DAYS?
- OH, NO. NOT THAT OFTEN.
YOU KNOW, JUST WHEN I'M
WITH MY FRIENDS.
OR LIKE WHEN MY FAMILY
GOES OUT FOR DINNER.
MY DAD DRIVES US AROUND,
BUT HE'S NOT AS GOOD A
DRIVER AS YOU. ( laughs )
- SHE'S A WEIRD ONE.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING SPECIAL,
JUST DROVE LIKE NORMAL.
MAKING SURE
I DON'T SPILL THE WATER.
EVEN THOUGH I DIDN'T HAVE A CUP
WITH ME TODAY.
- ( car engine revving )
- THAT WAS MESSED UP YESTERDAY.
THAT CAR RUNNING IN FRONT OF ME
KEPT GETTING CLOSER AND CLOSER,
AND THE NEXT THING I KNEW,
I FOUND MYSELF GETTING A CHARGE
OUT OF CHASING IT.
- ( tires screeching )
- UNTIL YESTERDAY,
I NEVER EVEN CONSIDERED THAT
DRIVING COULD BE FUN.
IT WAS ALWAYS WORK
BUT LAST NIGHT,
AND EVEN TODAY WHEN
I WAS DRIVING OUT HERE
WITH NATSUKI SITTING NEXT TO ME,
I HAD A LOT OF FUN.
DRIVING IS ACTUALLY KINDA COOL.
- ( waves splashing )
- Natsuki: HEY, TAKUMI?
HELL-OO? ARE YOU LISTENING?
YOU COMPLETELY SPACED OUT
JUST NOW. WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE SOMEWHERE ELSE.
YOU'RE ACTING KINDA RUDE.
I HOPE YOU REALIZE THAT.
WHEN A GUY IS WITH A CUTE GIRL
IN A BATHING SUIT,
DO YOU THINK HE SHOULD
BE STANDING THERE
STARING OFF AT NOTHING
OR STARING AT HER?
- I'M SORRY, I GOT DISTRACTED.
WHAT WERE WE TALKING ABOUT?
- I WAS JUST TRYING TO ASK
IF THERE'S ANY GIRL
YOU LIKE RIGHT NOW.
- I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS NOT NOW.
NOBODY IN PARTICULAR.
THEN AGAIN, THERE
IS THIS ONE GIRL
I CAN'T HELP THINKING ABOUT.
- OOH!
- HOW ABOUT YOU? DO YOU HAVE
ANYBODY ON YOUR MIND?
- WELL, SORT OF.
I MEAN, THERE IS THIS ONE GUY
I THINK OF SOMETIMES.
- YOU KNOW, IF I DIDN'T
KNOW ANY BETTER,
I'D THINK YOU WERE
JUST COPYING ME.
- ( Natsuki laughs )
- Iketani: ( laughs ) MAN!
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW MANY
TIMES THIS MORNING
I'VE BEEN ASKED THE
SAME QUESTION.
IT'S LIKE
AN ENDLESS BROKEN RECORD!
"WHO WAS THE GUY DRIVING
THAT EIGHT-SIX LAST NIGHT?"
- PEOPLE BEEN ASKIN' ME
THE SAME THING, TOO.
I JUST SAY, "WHO CARES.
HE BEAT KEISUKE TAKAHASHI."
THAT'S WHAT MATTERS.
IT'S NO SHOCK PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN BLABBIN' ABOUT IT.
- I MAY HAVE GOTTEN A LITTLE
WORKED UP ABOUT THE WHOLE THING.
I'VE BEEN TELLIN'
EVERYONE THAT THE EIGHT-SIX
IS THE SPEED STARS'
SECRET WEAPON.
WHICH MEANS WE
GOTTA FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET TAKUMI
TO JOIN US NOW.
IF NOT, WE'RE GONNA LOOK LIKE
IDIOTS LATER.
- NO SWEAT! YOU LEAVE THAT
TO ME. I CAN CONVINCE HIM!
I'M THE GUY'S BEST FRIEND
AND CONFIDANT.
HE'LL LISTEN TO WHAT I GOTTA
SAY. I'LL MAKE HIM DO IT.
- I DON'T KNOW.
YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN?
- I KNOW I CAN, MAN!
I KNOW ALL THE BUTTONS TO PUSH
ON THAT PARTICULAR MACHINE.
AND IN RETURN MAYBE YOU COULD
LET ME, UH, JOIN THE SPEEDSTARS?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, KENJI?
SHOULD WE LET ITSUKI IN
IF HE GETS TAKUMI
TO JOIN THE TEAM?
- SURE.
- ( giggles ) HELL, YEAH!
I'M GONNA BE A SPEED STAR!
- BUT DON'T YOU KINDA,
I DON'T KNOW, NEED A CAR?
- I'M GLAD
YOU ASKED ME THAT, KENJI.
I'VE ALREADY GOT MY GAME PLAN
ALL MAPPED OUT!
- OH! YOU'VE SAVED UP THE CASH?
- I'M GONNA ASK MY DAD
TO SIGN FOR THE LOAN
SO I CAN GET ENOUGH MONEY
TO BUY MYSELF AN EIGHT-SIX!
TAKUMI HAS HIMSELF
A PANDA TRUENO,
SO I'M GOIN' IN FOR
THE RED OR BLACK LEVIN!
AND SOMEDAY WE'LL BE KNOWN AS
THE EIGHT-SIX DUO!
THE FASTEST DRIVERS IN AKINA!
- ( crowd cheering )
- ( Itsuki laughing )
- YEAH, BUT, ITSUKI, UM,
TAKUMI'S EIGHT-SIX IS
NOT NORMAL. YOU KNOW THAT.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU KNOW THAT.
- IT'S CRANKED UP.
FASTER THAN THE FD,
AND THAT'S 350 HORSES.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW TAKUMI DOES IT,
BUT I'M WILLIN' TO BET,
HE'S GOT A PRETTY SLICK
TUNING JOB INSIDE.
I TELL YA, THAT IS ONE HOOD
I'D LIKE TO GET UNDER
FOR A LONG TIME.
- INSTEAD OF THAT, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TAG ALONG WITH HIM?
I DON'T THINK HE'D MIND.
RIDE ALONG WHEN HE GOES
TO BREAK THE RECORD
FOR AKINA'S DOWNHILL.
- COULD BE PRETTY SWEET.
- OH! THAT'S A GENIUS IDEA!
- I WANNA GO, TOO!
- OKAY, DUDE. WE CAN
ALL GO WHERE NO ONE
HAS EVER GONE BEFORE.
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE IT, MAN.
- Kenji and Itsuki: YEAH!
- Iketani: I BET IT'S BETTER
THAN THE BEST ROLLER COASTER
YOU COULD FIND
ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.
- Kenji and Itsuki: YEAH!
- Itsuki: CRAP! I FORGOT!
TAKUMI'S OUT ON HIS DATE
RIGHT NOW! ( laughs )
- Natsuki: TAKUMI, HOLD ON!
WAIT UP A SECOND!
HI, EXCUSE ME! BUT WOULD MIND
TAKING OUR PICTURE?
- SURE.
( laughs )
- WHAT'RE YOU DOIN'? I LOOK LIKE
I'VE BEEN BURIED IN SAND.
- WE CAME ALL THIS WAY.
YOU BETTER BELIEVE WE'RE
GETTING A PICTURE
TO TAKE HOME. NOW QUIT
COMPLAINING AND SMILE.
- Man: HERE WE GO, YOU TWO!
- GREAT! WOULD YOU TAKE ONE
MORE? JUST ONE MORE, PLEASE.
- Takumi: THE GUY'S GOT
HIS FAMILY WITH HIM.
COME ON, LET HIM GO--
- OH, JUST SHUT UP
AND LOOK PRETTY.
- ( car tires screeching)
- ( tires screeching )
- Boy 2: THAT'S ONE
WICKED WHITE FC.
- THAT'S RYOSUKE TOCKAHASHI.
HE'S THE BEST DRIVER THEY GOT.
NO WONDER THEY HAVE HIM
RACING NEXT.
- WHAT WOULD THEY DO THAT FOR?
- I'M THINKING IT'S A RUN FOR
REVENGE, DUDE. THINK ABOUT IT,
WHY THE HELL ELSE
WOULD HE BE HERE?
- BUT THAT WAS JUST LAST NIGHT,
AND HE'S ALREADY HERE? WOW.
THAT GUY MUST BE
FREAKIN' PISSED
ABOUT BEING BEATEN
BY THE EIGHT-SIX.
- ( engine revving )
- Boy 2: I NEVER SEEN
THAT RIDE UP HERE BEFORE.
A BLACK THREE-TWO. SOMETHING
ABOUT IT FREAKS ME OUT.
WHO'S DRIVIN' THAT THING?
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
♪ TO RIG MY DREAM ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ DEALING DOWN ANOTHER ROUND,
NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- Itsuki: YOU ARE
SUCH A TRAITOR, TAKUMI!
- HEY, YOU CAN'T
JUST BARGE IN HERE--
- HE WENT TO THE BEACH
WITH NATSUKI,
AND HE JUST LEFT HIS
BEST FRIEND, ME,
HERE ALL ALONE!
- REALLY? HE DID THAT?
AND ALL YOU WANTED WAS TO SEE
NATSUKI IN HER BATHING SUIT.
- OF COURSE I DID!
AND TAKUMI WAS ALONE WITH
HER THE WHOLE TIME!
HE DID SOMETHING WITH HER,
I KNOW IT! I KNOW THAT GUY!
- Announcer: NEXT
TIME ON INITIAL D,
A NEW BATTLE IS IN THE AIR.
DON'T MISS IT!