- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ BREAK INTO THE NIGHT
IT'S THE TIME ♪
- Yuuichi: THEY'RE FOR YOU, KID.
- WAIT, WHO'S SENDING ME
FLOWERS AT WORK?
- RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
- RYOSUKE.
- TAKAHASHI.
- LESS POWER EQUALS MORE SPEED.
IT MUST BE DUE TO THE
WAY HE ENTERS HIS CORNERS.
THERE'S NO WAY
MY BROTHER WILL LOSE NOW.
HE'S JUST TOO DAMN SMART.
- A BATTLE?
- MM-HMM.
- SO. LIKE A FISTFIGHT?
- NO. A BATTLE IS A RACE.
TWO DRIVERS GOING UP
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
- IF YOU DON'T WANNA RACE,
JUST BLOW HIM OFF.
- NAH, IT'S NOT LIKE
I DON'T WANNA RACE THE GUY.
I MEAN, I MIGHT
EVEN LOSE TO HIM.
BUT I DON'T
WANNA NOT RACE HIM.
- YOU STILL DON'T BELIEVE
TAKUMI HAS A CHANCE
AT WINNING THIS THING, DO YOU?
- NO. HE'S ONE OF THE MOST
TALENTED RACERS I KNOW,
BUT HE'S STILL IN HIGH SCHOOL.
NOT ONLY DO I THINK
HE'LL LOSE THE RACE,
I WONDER IF HE'LL
FINISH IN ONE PIECE.
- THE ONLY REASON I BELIEVE
TAKUMI HAS A CHANCE IS
HE HAS BUNTA'S BLOOD
PUMPING THROUGH HIS VEINS.
AND BUNTA'S ONE CRAZY
SON-OF-A-BITCH.
- KEISUKE. THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANTED TO RUN BY YOU
THAT I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
FOR SOME TIME NOW.
WHEN THE DAY COMES THAT I
LOSE MY FIRST STREET RACE,
I'LL RETIRE.
BY THE WAY, THERE ARE ONLY
TWO RACERS ALIVE WHO I FEEL
HAVE A LEGITIMATE CHANCE
AT BEATING ME SOMEDAY.
AND THE FIRST ONE ON THAT LIST
HAS TO BE YOU, KEISUKE.
- REALLY?
- AND THE OTHER
WOULD HAVE TO BE...
- ( car approaching )
- TAKUMI!
- GOOD LUCK OUT THERE, BUDDY.
- I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I BELIEVE IN YOU!
YOU CAN TAKE THIS GUY, DUDE!
AFTER YOU PUT RYOSUKE
IN HIS PLACE
YOU'LL BECOME THE FASTEST RACER
IN ALL OF GUNMA!
TAKUMI! TAKUMI!
- Iketani: OKAY, ITSUKI,
I THINK HE GETS THE GIST.
NOW GIVE HIM SOME
BREATHIN' ROOM ALREADY!
- Keisuke: YOU'RE LATE.
YOU'RE STILL AS IGNORANT
AS THE DAY I RACED YA.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
HERE BY TEN.
- I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
I FIND IT IMPRESSIVE THAT YOU'VE
BEEN ABLE TO LEARN SO MANY
ADVANCED TECHNIQUES
IN SUCH A SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME,
GIVEN OF COURSE THAT
YOU'RE STILL A TEENAGER.
- IT'S NO BIG DEAL. I'VE
PROBABLY DRIVEN AKINA PASS
MORE THAN ANYONE ELSE SO I'M
JUST REALLY USED TO IT.
I DON'T KNOW ANY SPECIAL
TECHNIQUES OR ANYTHING.
I JUST LIKE TO DRIVE.
HONESTLY, I THINK YOU'RE
OVERESTIMATING
WHAT I'M CAPABLE OF.
THE FACT IS, I'M NOT AS GOOD
AS YOU THINK I AM.
- ( scoffs )
THAT'S AN INTERESTING WAY
OF LOOKING AT IT.
EITHER YOU'RE EXTREMELY MODEST
OR YOU STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE EXTENT
OF YOUR OWN POTENTIAL.
YOU ARE QUITE A UNIQUE KID.
MAYBE SOMEDAY YOU AND I
CAN CHEW THE FAT TOGETHER.
- WE'RE DOIN' THIS?
- LET'S GET THIS RACE STARTED.
IT SHOULD BE
A FUN EVENING FOR US.
- Keisuke: ALRIGHT!
GET THESE CARS OFF THE ROAD!
- ( engines starting )
- ( engines revving )
- IS IT COOL WITH YOU IF THE
RED SUNS OVERSEE THE RACE?
- Iketani: SURE.
- Keisuke: LET'S GET SOME GUYS
FROM THE SPEED STARS
TO BE OFFICIALS TOO.
- Iketani: SOUNDS GOOD.
- Boy 1: IKETANI.
I'LL BE AT THE FINISH.
- Iketani: COOL.
BE AWAKE DOWN THERE.
- Boy 2: KEISUKE. I'LL SET UP
AT THE FIVE HAIRPINS.
- Keisuke: OKAY.
- Boy 3: RYOSUKE'S GONNA BLOW
THIS KID OUTTA THE WATER, RIGHT?
WE'RE GONNA GET THIS GUY!
- Keisuke: OF COURSE WE ARE.
I DON'T CARE HOW FAST HE IS,
THERE'S NOT A PERSON ON THIS
PLANET WHO CAN BEAT MY BROTHER.
- Boy 3: I HEAR YA.
ALRIGHT, I'M OFF!
- ( phone rings )
- ( grunts )
HELLO? FUJIWARA TOFU.
OH HEY,
IT'S YOU, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH, BUNTA, IT'S ME.
I JUST GOT TO AKINA
A FEW MINUTES AGO.
YOU'D BE AMAZED AT HOW MANY
PEOPLE ARE HERE TONIGHT.
IT'S CRAZY!
- YEAH? SO, IS THAT IT?
- SO. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
CAN TAKUMI PULL OUT
A WIN TONIGHT?
PEOPLE ARE SAYING HIS OPPONENT
IS A STREET RACING KING,
THE FASTEST IN ALL OF GUNMA!
- WHO GIVES A CRAP?
IF THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
YOU BOTHERED CALLING,
THEN I'M GONNA HANG UP.
- NO NO WAIT, DON'T HANG UP YET!
I'M NOT DONE TALKING!
- ( phone hangs up )
- DAMN IT, I TOLD YOU
NOT TO HANG UP!
- ( panting )
- ALRIGHT EVERYONE,
CHECK IN FROM YOUR POSTS.
HOW'RE THE CORNERS
LOOKIN'OUT THERE?
- Boy 1: COPY THAT. WE'RE ALL
GOOD HERE AT THE FIRST CORNER.
READY WHEN YOU ARE.
- Boy 2: SKATE CENTER
CHECKIN' IN.
THE STRAIGHTAWAY
IS LOOKIN' NICE AND CLEAR.
- Boy 3: SAME GOES FOR
THE SEVENTEENTH HAIRPIN.
WE'RE ALL SET.
- Boy 4: FIVE HAIRPINS HERE.
THERE'S NOT A CAR IN SIGHT.
WE'RE READY AND WAITIN'.
- Boy 5: THIS IS NUMBER SIX.
THE SPECTATORS'
CARS'VE BEEN CLEARED
FROM THE ROAD. JUST
WAITIN' FOR THE START.
- MAN. I'M SO NERVOUS!
MY THROAT'S TOTALLY DRY
AND MY HEART FEELS
LIKE IT'S GONNA BEAT
OUTTA MY CHEST!
- I'VE NEVER SEEN A CROWD ACT
THIS ANXIOUS BEFORE A RACE.
YOU COULD CUT THE
TENSION WITH A KNIFE!
- Itsuki: YEAH. I WONDER
IF TAKUMI'S FEELIN' NERVOUS.
- TAKUMI. YOU'RE RACING
AGAINST THE BEST OF THE BEST.
WHETHER YOU WIN OR NOT
DOESN'T MATTER,
JUST DRIVE YOUR HEART OUT.
- COME ON, TAKUMI!
I KNOW YOU CAN DO THIS!
BRING HOME A WIN
FOR THE SPEED STARS!
- I'M CONFIDENT MY BROTHER'S
GONNA WIN TONIGHT.
BUT WHENEVER THE EIGHT-SIX
IS ON THIS PASS,
SOMETHING UNEXPECTED
ALWAYS TENDS TO HAPPEN.
I JUST HOPE
IT'S IN OUR FAVOR.
- HEY THERE. DID I MISS IT?
- UH-UH. HASN'T STARTED YET.
- REALLY? GOOD. THANKS!
- WE'RE READY HERE
AT THE STARTING LINE.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS LOOKIN'
DOWN THERE AT THE FINISH?
- WE'RE GOOD. ROAD'S CLEAR
AND WE'RE JUST WAITIN' AROUND.
- 'OKAY, LET'S DO THIS. I'M
GONNA START THE COUNTDOWN.
- Keisuke: HOLD UP!
I KNOW IT'S USUALLY YOUR THING
BUT LET ME DO THE
COUNTDOWN THIS TIME.
YOU DON'T MIND, RIGHT?
JUST FOR THIS RACE?
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
BUT I HAVE TO BE RIGHT UP
FRONT WHEN THEY START.
START YOUR ENGINES!
- ( both engines revving )
- FIVE! FOUR! THREE!
TWO! ONE! GO!
- All: DO IT. TAKUMI!
- ( dance music playing )
- DAMN, LOOK AT HIM GO! HE'S
ABOUT TO FLY RIGHT PAST RYOSUKE!
HELL YEAH! TAKUMI JUST
TOOK THE LEAD!
DON'T LET UP!
BEAT HIS ASS, DUDE!
- I SEE MY BRO'S GOIN'
WITH HIS USUAL STRATEGY.
LET THE OPPONENT
TAKE THE EARLY LEAD
SO HE CAN STUDY THEIR MOVEMENTS,
THEN PASS HIM LATE IN THE RACE.
THAT'S THE WAY HE'S BEEN
WINNIN' RACES SINCE DAY ONE.
HIS "FASTEST RACER" THEORY
IS UNSTOPPABLE.
♪ BOOM BOOM JAPAN!
THAT'S WHAT I SAY ♪
♪ GO AND SEE WHAT I MEAN ♪
♪ BOOM BOOM JAPAN!
HAPPENING NIGHT AND DAY ♪
♪ NIGHT AND DAY YOU WILL
SEE AND LOVE IT ♪
♪ BOOM BOOM JAPAN!
THAT'S WHAT I SAY ♪
♪ GO AND SAY WHAT I MEAN ♪
♪ BOOM BOOM JAPAN!
HAPPENING NIGHT AND DAY ♪
♪ NIGHT AND DAY YOU WILL SEE
AND LOVE THE LAND ♪
- THESE GUYS ARE AMAZING!
SEE HOW CLOSE THEY'RE DRIFTIN'
WITH EACH OTHER?
- THOSE DRIFTS
THEY'RE TAKIN' ARE HUGE!
THAT AIN'T RYOSUKE'S
STYLE AT ALL!
I WONDER IF HE'S
STARTIN' TO FEEL THE HEAT!
- MAN THE RACE JUST STARTED
AND THEY'RE ALREADY
PUTTIN' ON A SHOW!
- INITIAL D!
Announcer: INITIAL D!
- Boy 1: IT'S DRIFT
VERSUS DRIFT!
EVEN RYOSUKE DRIFTED THROUGH
THE FIRST CORNER!
THAT'S UNHEARD OF!
- Itsuki: YOU KNOW WHAT?
I BET HE WANTS TO BEAT TAKUMI
AT HIS OWN GAME BY USING THE
SAME TECHNIQUE.
THAT WAY, IF HE WINS, HE'LL BE
THE UNDISPUTED CHAMPION.
- Boy 1: TAKUMI'S DRIVIN'
A HELLUVA RACE THOUGH.
THIS IS GONNA BE
AN AMAZING FINISH!
- YOU GOTTA WIN THIS, TAKUMI!
DO IT FOR THE SPEED STARS!
AIN'T THAT RIGHT, IKETANI?
- UH YEAH. I GUESS SO.
- ( dance music playing )
- I'M IMPRESSED ONCE AGAIN.
THE EIGHT-SIX HAS NEVER
DRIVEN LIKE THIS BEFORE.
I KNEW IT. HE HAS IMPROVED
SINCE I SAW HIM LAST.
HE BARELY USES
ANY COUNTER-STEERING
AS HE STABILIZES DURING THE
FINAL MOMENTS OF HIS DRIFT.
THAT HASN'T CHANGED
SINCE LAST TIME,
BUT HE'S USING LESS
COUNTER-STEER
RIGHT AFTER A
TURN-IN MANEUVER.
I DON'T GET IT. IT HASN'T BEEN
VERY LONG SINCE HIS LAST RACE
AND YET HIS WEAKNESS IS GONE,
AS IF IT HAD NEVER EVEN EXISTED.
IT'S AS IF HE IMPROVES
WITH EVERY RUN.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO ALTER
MY ORIGINAL STRATEGY A BIT
BUT THAT'S ALL IT SHOULD TAKE.
THE END RESULT WILL BE THE SAME.
MY "FASTEST RACER" THEORY
IS INVINCIBLE.
- Shingo: HEY, TAKESHI.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT
I DIDN'T PARK HERE
BECAUSE I WANTED
TO WATCH THE RACE
IN THE SAME SPOT AS YOU.
DON'T WANT YOU TO GET
THE WRONG IDEA OR ANYTHING.
I WAS PLANNING TO SET UP HERE
BEFORE THE RACE
EVEN GOT STARTED.
SO YEAH,
FIND ANOTHER SPOT.
DON'T THINK SO. I'M NOT STUPID.
I KNOW THIS IS THE BEST VANTAGE
POINT TO WATCH THE RACE FROM.
AND I WAS HERE FIRST,
SO WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A HIKE?
USUALLY ALL THE NEWBIES
AND FANS WANT TO WATCH
FROM THE MOST OBVIOUS PLACES.
THE FIVE HAIRPINS
IS A GOOD EXAMPLE.
- THAT'S TRUE, BUT RACES ARE
NEVER DECIDED IN THOSE SPOTS.
THIS TURN IS THE ONLY PLACE TO
MAKE A SOLID MOVE FOR THE WIN.
- GREAT MINDS THINK ALIKE.
I'M IMPRESSED SHINGO,
DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD IT IN YA.
- HUH. BACK AT YA.
- THIS PLACE IS DEAD.
WE'RE OUT HERE IN THE
MIDDLE OF NOWHERE, AREN'T WE?
- PROBLEM IS IF ANYONE DRIVES BY
AND SEES US STANDIN'
HERE TOGETHER
THEY'RE GONNA START THINKIN'
WE'RE ACTUALLY FRIENDS
OR SOMETHIN'.
- Both: SHOOT. CAN'T HAVE THAT!
- ( dance music playing )
- I CAN HEAR 'EM COMING!
- Boy 1: WHOA!
LOOK HOW CLOSE THEY'RE GETTING'
TO THE GUARDRAIL!
- HOLY CRAP! THAT WAS AMAZING!
UH, WHAT THE HELL
AM I WAITING FOR?
I'D BETTER GIVE BUNTA
ANOTHER CALL.
- ( phone rings )
- UGH, NOW WHAT?
HELLO? FUJIWARA.
- HEY BUNTA! IT'S ME AGAIN!
- OH GREAT, WHAT IS IT NOW?
- JUST LISTEN!
YOU GOTTA HEAR THIS!
SO I'M STILL HERE AT THE RACE
AND THEY JUST PASSED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
THEY WERE BOTH USING
SOME OF THE HEAVIEST DRIFT
I'VE EVER SEEN
THROUGH THIS TURN!
TAKUMI'S EIGHT-SIX
WAS IN THE LEAD
BUT THE FC
WAS RIGHT ON HIS TAIL.
SERIOUSLY, YOU'RE
MISSING ONE HELLUVA RACE!
- YOU SAID TAKUMI WAS
IN THE LEAD, RIGHT?
WELL THAT'S NOT VERY
PROMISING NEWS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOUR SON'S IN THE LEAD.
- YOU KNOW YOU'RE STARTING TO
SOUND LIKE A NEWBIE, YUUICHI.
IT'S COMMON RACING
KNOWLEDGE THAT THE DRIVER
DOING THE CHASING
HAS A BETTER CHANCE
OF BEING AGGRESSIVE BECAUSE
HE'S NOT ON THE DEFENSIVE.
- HE'S RIGHT.
- Bunta: WHILE BOTH RACERS
CAN STUDY THE COURSE,
THE DRIVER IN THE BACK
CAN ALSO MONITOR
THE RHYTHM OF THE LEAD DRIVER.
IF HE'S GOOD ENOUGH,
HE CAN ALSO COPY THE DRIVING
STYLE OF THE LEADER.
- Yuuichi: BUT WHOEVER'S IN
FRONT CAN ALWAYS JUST DRIVE OFF
AND INCREASE THEIR LEAD.
- THAT'S NOT EASY.
THE DRIVER IN THE LEAD IS UNDER
TREMENDOUS PRESSURE
TO HOLD OFF HIS OPPONENT.
TRYING TO RACE WHILE ANOTHER
CAR IS FOLLOWING YOU
AT THE SAME SPEED CAN PUSH
YOU INTO A MENTAL CORNER
THAT'S VERY HARD
TO GET OUT OF.
AS THE RACE PROGRESSES
WITH YOUR OPPONENT ON YOUR SIX,
THE HARDER YOU TRY
TO INCREASE YOUR LEAD,
THE MORE THREATENING
YOUR OPPONENT WILL SEEM.
TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE,
TAKUMI IS STILL RELATIVELY NEW
TO THESE ADVANCED
RACING TACTICS.
I'D HAVE TO IMAGINE HE'S
REALLY STARTING TO SWEAT
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
- YOU THINK SO?
WELL I'LL GIVE YOU
A CALL WHEN IT'S OVER
AND LET YOU KNOW
HOW YOUR BOY FINISHED.
- FINE.
- MY BOY.
WILL YOU LOSE YOUR COOL?
NAH.
- ( electronica playing )
♪ BLACK OUT ♪
♪ FEEL THAT BLACK OUT,
BLACK OUT ♪
♪ BLACK OUT ♪
- HERE THEY COME!
♪ EVERY NIGHT I SEE HER ♪
♪ BURNING, BURNING ♪
- ( timer clicks )
- WHOA, THEIR TIMES
ARE INCREDIBLE!
♪ YOU CAN BE WHAT YOU WANT
TO BE IF YOU FOLLOW YOUR HEART ♪
- Redsun Boy: WE'RE HERE
AT THE TWENTY-FOURTH CORNER!
THE EIGHT-SIX AND RYOSUKE'S FC
JUST CAME THROUGH!
THEY POSTED THE
MOST AMAZING TIMES
WE'VE EVER SEEN ON THIS COURSE!
IF THEY CAN HOLD
ONTO THIS PACE,
THEY'LL BOTH BREAK
THE EIGHT-SIX'S PREVIOUS RECORD
BY AT LEAST SEVEN OR EIGHT
SECONDS, IF NOT MORE!
THAT'S ALL WE'VE GOT. I'LL CHECK
BACK IN IF I HEAR ANYTHING MORE.
- THEY'RE RUNNIN' SEVEN
OR EIGHT SECONDS FASTER
THAN WHEN I RACED HIM?
GIMME A FREAKIN' BREAK!
SO THIS IS WHAT MY
BROTHER IS CAPABLE OF
WHEN HE GETS IN THE ZONE.
IT'S ALMOST SCARY.
MAN, THIS RACE
IS GONNA BE LEGENDARY.
- SWEET! IT SOUNDS LIKE
TAKUMI'S STILL IN THE LEAD!
- YES! HE'S REALLY GONNA
PULL THIS OFF.
- MAYBE SO.
BUT CAN HE KEEP THIS UP?
- REMEMBER. HE'S GOING UP
AGAINST GUNMA'S FASTEST.
SO...
I'LL BE SATISFIED
IF HE CAN FINISH THE RACE...
...WITHOUT CRASHING.
♪ YOU CAN BE WHAT YOU WANT
TO BE IF YOU FOLLOW YOUR HEART ♪
♪ YOU CAN DO
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO ♪
♪ IN THE DARK OF THE NIGHT ♪
♪ FEEL THE BLACK OUT,
BLACK OUT ♪
♪ KNOW YOU'VE GOT TO GET READY ♪
♪ MOVE ON, BABY ♪
♪ BLACK OUT, BLACK OUT ♪
♪ IN THE HEAT OF THE NIGHT... ♪
- I'M GOING AT FULL POWER
AND HE'S STILL RIDIN' MY TAIL.
NO MATTER HOW FAST I GO,
I CAN'T SHAKE HIM.
THIS SUCKS.
AT THIS RATE
I'M GONNA LOSE.
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
THIS GUY'S THE BEST.
NO WAY I CAN COMPARE TO HIM.
I WISH IT WEREN'T TRUE.
BUT I'M GONNA LOSE THIS!
♪ BLACK OUT ♪
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HANG IN THERE, TAKUMI!
I BELIEVE IN YOU! DON'T GIVE UP!
- I DON'T WANT TO LOSE.
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE.
- Bunta: IT TAKES YEARS
OF EXPERIENCE...
- ( overlapping voices talking )
- Announcer: WE'RE HEADING
INTO THE FINAL MOMENTS
OF THIS EMOTIONAL RACE.
WHO WILL BE THE VICTOR?
NEXT ON INITIAL D.
"THE NEW DOWNHILL LEGEND!"
DON'T MISS IT!