- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- Boy: THAT PRACTICE KILLED.
- DUDE, IT WAS A BEATING.
- WHO KNOWS, BUT I'M STARVING.
LET'S GO GRAB SOME SLICES.
- NO WAY? WITH NATSUKI MOGI?
- AH MAN, THAT IS ONE FINE
PIECE OF TAIL.
EVERYBODY I KNOW
WANTS TO HIT THAT.
- LIKE I WAS SAYING, SHE DOES
WHATEVER I TELL HER TO.
AND LIKE A GOOD DOG, I THINK
IT'S TIME TO BREAK HER IN.
- WAIT. WHAT DO MEAN
'BREAK HER IN'?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
HE MEANS, HUH?
( laughs )
- CHICKS ARE THE SAME ALL
OVER, MY BROTHERS...
THEY ALL ACT LIKE THEY
DON'T WANT IT,
BUT BELIEVE ME, THEY DO...
THE OTHER DAY I CALLED HER UP TO
THE ROOF AND I GOT HER TO, UH...
- ( loud bang )
- IF YOU DON'T SHUT YOUR MOUTHS
RIGHT NOW... I'LL DO IT FOR YOU.
- AND JUST, WHO
THE HELL, ARE YOU?
- THIS BEAN POLE DOESN'T KNOW
WHO HE'S MOUTHING OFF TO.
- DUDE, TAKUMI, SHUT UP.
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF LISTENING
TO YOU ASSHOLES.
- YOU'LL REGRET THAT!
- ( grunting )
- BACK OFF, TAKUMI!
- I'LL KILL YOU!
- ( panting )
- ( gasps )
YOU'RE ACTING KINDA RUDE. I HOPE
YOU REALIZE THAT.
WHEN A GUY IS WITH A CUTE GIRL
IN A BATHING SUIT,
DO YOU THINK HE SHOULD BE
STANDING THERE STARING OFF
AT NOTHING OR STARING AT HER?
I WAS JUST TRYING TO ASK...
IF THERE'S ANY GIRL THAT YOU
LIKE RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN, THERE IS THIS
ONE GUY I THINK OF, SOMETIMES.
- Yuichi: IKETANI? HEY, WHERE'D
IKETANI RUN OFF TO?
- I REALLY COULDN'T
TELL YOU, BOSS.
- OH, YOU MEAN THE MAN WHOSE
TERRIFIED SCREAMS ECHOED DOWN
FROM MOUNT AKINA AS
HE PASSED OUT...
THAT IKETANI JUST LEFT ON
A DELIVERY.
HE TOOK THE PICKUP TRUCK.
- OKAY... WELL,
IF IKETANI'S OUT,
THEN MAYBE YOU CAN
HELP ME, TAKUMI...
JUST DELIVER THESE PAPERS
TO THE YAMADA SHOP.
YOU CAN TAKE MY CAR.
- UH... SURE.
- HEY, BOSS.
QUESTION. YOU DO
REALIZE THAT I HAVE
A DRIVER'S LICENSE TOO, RIGHT?
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS ASK
THE OTHER GUYS TO DO DELIVERIES
AND LEAVE AN AWESOME FELLA
LIKE ME OUTTA THE LOOP?
- SINCE YOU ASKED,
I'LL TELL YOU.
PUT YOUR HAND ON YOUR CHEST
AND TELL ME WHAT YOU FEEL.
- DO YOU GET IT NOW?
- NO...
- TO PUT IT SIMPLY I CAN
TRUST THOSE TWO
TO BRING MY CAR
BACK IN ONE PIECE,
BUT WITH YOU, THERE'D BE A DENT
THE SIZE OF YOUR CAVED-IN CHEST.
- ( screams )
WELL, THAT'S THE LONG
AND SHORT OF IT.
- JUST WAIT. ONCE I GET MY OWN
EIGHT-SIX, I'M GONNA BE THE
FASTEST RACER AKINA
HAS EVER SEEN!
SWEET! A THREE-TWO!
CAN I HELP YOU, SIR?
WHAT A RIDE! THIS BAD
BOY IS THE BOMB!
- ( gasps ) NIGHT KIDS!
- 'SUP, KID. NAME'S TOCKASHI.
FRIEND OF MINE BACK HOME TOLD ME
I SHOULD SWING BY THIS PLACE...
I'M LOOKING FOR A MEMBER OF THE
AKINA SPEED STARS. MY BUDDY
TOLD ME THAT THE GUY I WANT
WORKS AT THIS GAS STATION.
SO TELL ME SOMETHIN',
YOU GOT ANY IDEA
WHERE I CAN FIND THAT
EIGHT-SIX THAT RIDES AKINA?
YOU HEARIN' ME, KID? HEY,
YOU LOOK FAMILIAR.
AREN'T YOU ONE OF
THE SPEED STARS?
- ME? ONE OF THE SPEED STARS?
HOW COOL...
- HIT THE BRAKES FOR THE
WRONG GAS STATION, I GUESS.
- WAIT! NO, YOU'RE AT THE
RIGHT PLACE, I PROMISE.
ACTUALLY, THE EIGHT-SIX DUDE,
WE'RE KINDA TIGHT.
PEOPLE MISTAKE US FOR BROTHERS.
- THEY DO?
- SURE. KNOWN AS
THE EIGHT-SIX DUO,
FASTEST DOWNHILLERS ON OUR TEAM.
HATE TO TOOT MY OWN CAR
HORN, BUT THAT IS THE WAY IT IS.
- WAIT, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- AS A HEART ATTACK. I MEAN,
YEAH, HE MIGHT BE JUST A LITTLE
BIT FASTER THAN ME, BUT AT THOSE
SPEEDS, WHO'S COUNTING?
- I DIDN'T REALIZE THE SPEED
STARS HAD ANYONE ELSE
WHO COULD RACE ON THAT LEVEL.
- WELL, NOW YOU KNOW WE DO.
IF YOU WANTED ME TO, I COULD
DROP OFF A MESSAGE TO HIM.
IT'S NO SKIN OFF
MY BACK, HEH, LIKE I WAS
SAYING, HE AND I PRETTY
MUCH INSEPARABLE.
- ( engine starting )
- ALL RIGHT, THEN, YOU COULD
TELL HIM SOMETHING FOR ME.
10 O'CLOCK THIS SATURDAY NIGHT.
- 10 ON SATURDAY...
I'LL PASS IT ALONG.
- WE'LL MEET UP ON TOP OF AKINA.
AND TELL HIM TO LOOK FOR
TAKESHI NAKAZATO.
- WHY ARE YOU GONNA MEET HIM AT
NIGHT UP ON THE MOUNTAIN?
- IT'LL BE A RACE TO THE BOTTOM.
- UH! NO WAIT! THAT'S, HOLD ON,
DON'T LEAVE! THERE'S SOMETHING
ELSE I GOTTA TELL YOU,
UH, DON'T, CRAP.
NOW I'VE REALLY DONE IT. THAT
GUY JUST CHALLENGED TAKUMI,
AND I STOOD HERE LIKE
AN IDIOT AND LET HIM!
I'M TOO DUMB TO LIVE!
WHAT AM I GONNA TELL TAKUMI!
- ( horn honks )
TAKUMI!
- WHAT ARE YOU ACTING ALL
FREAKED OUT ABOUT NOW?
- NOTHIN' OUT OF THE ORDINARY...
SO, MY MAN IF YOU'RE
FREE THIS SATURDAY
WANNA GO RACING ON AKINA?
YOU AND I COULD
HAVE SOME SERIOUS FUN.
- NOPE.
- WHY NOT?
- I'M SORRY, MAN, BUT THESE DAYS
I JUST DON'T LIKE GETTING BEHIND
THE WHEEL OF A CAR UNLESS IT'S
ABSOLUTELY NECESSARY.
- HEY, TAKUMI! COME ON INSIDE.
I GOT SOME FRESH
COFFEE BREWED UP.
- SURE.
- HEY! NOT GOOD...
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
- SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- TAKUMI, WAIT UP.
- SOMETHING I WANTED TO RUN BY
YOU, NOW SUPPOSE, JUST
SUPPOSE THAT A RACER YOU DIDN'T
KNOW WAS TO HUNT YOU DOWN AND
CHALLENGE YOU TO A RACE. YOU
WOULD ACCEPT IT, WOULDN'T YOU?
- NO WAY. THE RACING SCENE
REALLY ISN'T FOR ME.
- WHAT? DON'T SAY THAT!
- WHY DOES IT MATTER TO YOU?
- UM, WELL, THAT'S ENTIRELY
BESIDE THE POINT, SORTA...
YOU HAVE TO FOLLOW THE RACER'S
LAW. IF A RACER RECEIVES A
CHALLENGE THEN HE HAS TO FACE
THE MUSIC AND ACCEPT IT, DUDE!
- THAT SOUNDS RIGHT, IF YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT A STREET RACER...
BUT I'M NOT, AND
YOU SEEM TO BE HAVING
A HARD TIME
REMEMBERING THAT.
- YOU'RE CRAZY!
- BESIDES, YOU KNOW ME. BEING
FORCED INTO ACCEPTING CHALLENGES
ISN'T EXACTLY UP MY ALLEY.
- MAN, THIS IS NOT GOOD.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
OH, CRAP.
- ( engine revving )
- 2 DAYS LEFT. RYOSUKE AND
THAT PUNK EIGHT-SIX
WON'T KNOW WHAT HIT 'EM.
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
WHO'S NUMBER ONE!
- IKETANI!
WANNA TELL ME WHEN THE HELL
YOU ACCEPTED A CHALLENGE
FROM THE MYOGI NIGHT KIDS?
THAT'S HUGE, MAN! WHY WERE
YOU KEEPIN' THAT FROM US?
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKIN'
ABOUT? I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
- DON'T TRY TO DENY IT. THE
WHOLE TOWN KNOWS ABOUT IT.
THE EIGHT-SIX VERSUS THE
THREE-TWO ON THE DOWNHILL,
SATURDAY NIGHT!
- EIGHT-SIX? THIS IS THE FIRST
I'VE HEARD OF IT, I SWEAR, DUDE!
- THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE. WORD ON
THE STREET IS TAKESHI CAME TO
THE GAS STATION HIMSELF
TO ISSUE THE CHALLENGE.
WHO'D HE TALK TO?
THE PHANTOM SPEED STAR?
- WELL, TAKUMI. HAVE YOU HEARD
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS?
- NO, THIS IS ALL NEWS TO ME.
- HOW AM I THE ONLY ONE?
WHAT THE HELL IS GOIN'
ON AROUND HERE?
- I'M SORRY!
- ITSUKI, YOU DIDN'T, DID YOU?
- I DID IT. I ACCEPTED THE
CHALLENGE FOR YOU.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME! YESTERDAY,
TAKESHI NAKAZATO CAME BY HERE
AND I GOT ALL NERVOUS. I WAS
ALONE, I COULDN'T EVEN CONTROL
MY MOUTH. STUPID ME PRETENDED TO
BE A SPEED STAR. I JUST WANTED
TO BE COOL FOR ONE SECOND. THEN
BEFORE I KNEW WHAT WAS GOIN'
ON, HE HAD ALREADY ISSUED THE
CHALLENGE AND DRIVEN OFF.
- WHY DIDN'T OPEN YOUR
BIG FAT MOUTH
ABOUT THIS BEFORE YOU DUMBASS?
- I WAS GONNA TELL
YOU ABOUT IT.
I WAS, I WAS JUST WAITIN' FOR
THE RIGHT MOMENT, TAKUMI, I'M
SORRY, I SCREWED THE POOCH, I
KNOW, I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO HATE ME FOR THIS.
- I DON'T HATE YOU,
BUT GEEZ, DUDE...
- FORGIVE ME.
I SCREWED UP, BAD,
BUT I PROMISE IT
WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
- LOOKS LIKE THAT
THREE-TWO'S OUT AGAIN.
I HEARD SOMEBODY SAYIN'
THAT HE'S GONNA BE RACIN'
AGAINST THE EIGHT-SIX
TOMORROW NIGHT...
I AM GONNA BE ALL
OVER THAT RACE!
- IF THAT NAKAZATO GUY FROM THE
NIGHT KIDS IS CHALLENGING THE
EIGHT-SIX THAT BEAT KEISUKE,
YOU CAN BE DAMN SURE
I'LL BE THERE FOR
THAT THROW DOWN.
- IT MIGHT LOOK LIKE A RACE
BETWEEN THE SPEED STARS AND THE
NIGHT KIDS ON THE SURFACE BUT
IF YOU DIG A LITTLE DEEPER
YOU'RE GONNA SEE IT'S REALLY A
BATTLE BETWEEN THE TAKESHI
BROTHERS' PRIDE AND
NAKAZATO'S ARROGANCE.
- NO MATTER HOW THE RACE
UNFOLDS, I PROMISE YOU
RYOSUKE IS NOT GONNA SIT
BACK AND WATCH IT HAPPEN.
- YEAH, THESE SUMMER NIGHTS ARE
ALREADY HEATIN' UP! HELL YES!
- OH, MAN...
- NOW WHAT?
- EVERYONE AND THEIR
FREAKIN' DOG'S
TALKIN' ABOUT THIS RACE NOW.
IT'S TOO LATE TO BACK OUT.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST ASK TAKUMI
TO GO THROUGH WITH IT.
- I'D LIKE TO THINK HE'D
HAVE THE STONES
TO PUT THIS THREE-TWO IN
ITS PLACE, BUT I'M NOT SURE.
TAKESHI NAKAZATO OF THE NIGHT
KIDS IS AS FAMOUS A STREET
RACER AS EITHER ONE
OF THE TAKAHASHI BROTHERS.
- I'M NOT SAYIN' IT'D BE EASY.
HELL, IT COULD BE OVER FROM
THE WORD 'GO'.
ON SECOND THOUGHT...
MAYBE I WON'T ASK HIM AT ALL.
- Narrator: Initial D!
- ( car starting )
- HERE YOU GO.
- DAD, HOLD UP.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE 3-2?
- SHE CAN DO SOME DAMAGE.
FOR A CAR THAT SIZE,
IT'S PRETTY FAST.
- YEAH, BUT COULD YOU
WIN AGAINST ONE?
I MEAN IN A DOWNHILL?
- OF COURSE. I CAN'T THINK OF
ANY CAR THAT I COULDN'T BEAT,
3-2 OR NOT.
- HOW ABOUT ME?
DO YOU THINK I COULD I WIN?
- THAT I DON'T KNOW.
IT'D BE A CLOSE RACE,
I CAN TELL YOU THAT MUCH...
WHY YOU ASKING
ALL THIS ANYWAY?
WHY THE INTEREST?
RACIN' A THREE-TWO?
- NO, I'M, I'M JUST CURIOUS,
I GUESS, I'LL SEE YA.
- NOW HE'S UP AGAINST
A THREE-TWO.
I BETTER GET IN THERE AND ADJUST
THE SETTINGS ON THAT EIGHT-SIX.
- Bunta: IT'D BE A CLOSE RACE...
I CAN TELL YOU THAT MUCH...
- THE FIRST TIME I MET YOU WAS
ABOUT THIS TIME OF NIGHT, SO I
FIGURED IF I CAME UP HERE
AROUND THE SAME TIME,
I MIGHT RUN INTO YOU...
AND HERE YOU ARE.
SO YOU'RE GOIN' TOE-TO-TOE
AGAINST THAT NAKAZATO LOSER...
THAT'S ALL ANYONE IN THIS
TOWN'S BEEN TALKIN'
ABOUT THE LAST COUPLE OF DAYS.
- PEOPLE TALK, SO WHAT?
BESIDES, I NEVER EVEN ACCEPTED
THAT CHALLENGE IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
- WHAT?
- HE CAME TO CHALLENGE ME BUT I
NEVER SAW HIM FACE TO FACE...
AND IT'S NOT LIKE I PLAN
ON RACING THE GUY.
- THE HELL DO YOU MEAN YOU
DON'T PLAN ON IT, MAN?
HE ISSUED A PERSONAL CHALLENGE!
WHETHER YOU HEARD IT
FROM HIS LIPS OR NOT,
IT WAS THROWN OUT!
WHY DON'T YOU JUST ACCEPT IT!
SHOW HIM YOU'RE
FASTER THAN HE IS!
I KNOW YOU CAN BEAT THIS IDIOT!
- I JUST DON'T SEE WHY
IT MATTERS TO YOU.
LOOK, I'M SORRY, BUT
IT'S BETWEEN HIM AND ME.
- IT'S NOT JUST BETWEEN
YOU TWO.
MY INTEREST IN THIS IS
CUZ YOU BEAT ME.
IF YOU LOSE TO ANYONE, I WANNA
MAKE DAMN SURE THAT YOU LOSE TO
ONE OF THE TAKAHASHI BROTHERS.
UNTIL ONE OF US BEATS YOU, YOU
CAN'T LOSE TO ANYONE ELSE. NOT
EVEN TO THAT THREE-TWO!
- YOU MUST NOT HAVE HEARD ME,
SO I'LL SAY IT AGAIN,
I DON'T HAVE ANY REASON TO
RACE THIS GUY.
- WHAT? A REASON?
SINCE WHEN DOES A RACER
NEED A REASON TO GET OUT
THERE AND BATTLE?
- YEAH OKAY. AND WHERE DID YOU
GET THE IDEA I WAS A RACER?
- I'M NOT IN THE MOOD FOR JOKES.
DON'T BE SARCASTIC WITH ME,
YOU LITTLE PUNK.
FOR YOUR TECHNIQUE
TO BE AS SOLID AS IT IS, YOU'VE
GOTTA HAVE PRACTICED FOR YEARS.
WHY WOULD SOMEONE DRIVE LIKE
THAT IF HE'S NOT AN
HONEST-TO-GOD STREET RACER?
- LOOK, I DON'T DRIVE LIKE THAT
BECAUSE I LIKE TO DO IT, I
DRIVE LIKE THAT BECAUSE
THAT'S WHAT I HAVE DO
TO HELP OUT AT HOME.
- STOP DENYING IT, PAL. NO ONE
GETS AS GOOD AS YOU IF THEY HATE
DRIVING. YOU LOVE IT
AS MUCH AS I DO.
- NO, YOU'RE WRONG...
YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
- I UNDERSTAND FINE, IT'S YOU
THAT DOESN'T GET IT. YOU THINK
SOMEONE WHO HATES RACING
COULD EVER MASTER DRIFTING?
ONLY SOMEONE WHO LOVES THIS
CRAP COULD PULL THAT OFF!
SOMEONE WHO BREATHES EXHAUST
FOR BREAKFAST!
YOU MIGHT NOT KNOW IT. MAYBE YOU
CAN'T FACE IT. BUT YOU'RE A
RACER. LOOK DEEP DOWN INSIDE,
EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU LOVES
DRIVING. IT'S OBVIOUS, I DON'T
KNOW HOW YOU CAN'T SEE IT.
BUT SINCE YOU LOVE IT, THEN
YOU ARE A RACER.
AT LEAST ENOUGH OF
ONE TO DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
THAT'S SOMETHING YOU SHOULD BE
PROUD OF. YOU GOT THE SKILLS.
ACCEPTING CHALLENGES IS THE
PRIDE OF EVERY STREET RACER.
IT'S IN HIS HEART.
WHAT YOU'RE DOIN' JUST
STRAIGHT UP MAKES ME SICK.
- I WONDER IF HE'S RIGHT. MAYBE
I REALLY DO LIKE DRIVING.
STILL, BEING FORCED TO ACCEPT
EVERY CHALLENGE THAT COMES
ALONG, I DUNNO,
THAT JUST ISN'T FOR ME!
- YO! ITSUKI! WHERE'S TAKUMI?
- HE'S ON THE LATE SHIFT TODAY.
- GOTCHA.
- HEY, IKETANI...
I'M, I'M GONNA GO UP TO
MOUNT AKINA TONIGHT
SO I CAN APOLOGIZE TO
TAKESHI PERSONALLY.
- YOU SURE?
- YES. IF I GOTTA I'LL GET DOWN
ON MY KNEES. ONCE I TELL HIM THE
TRUTH, HE'LL HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, THE SPEED STARS HAVE
NOTHING TO DO WITH THIS.
IT'S ALL ON ME.
- YOU REALLY DON'T THINK WE CAN
CONVINCE TAKUMI TO RACE HIM?
- NO. I KNOW THE GUY BETTER THAN
ANYONE. HE'LL NEVER DO IT.
IT'S JUST THE WAY HE IS. HE
HATES BEING PUSHED INTO THINGS
OR HAVING TO FOLLOW OTHER
PEOPLES' ORDERS.
- ( chuckles )
HE'S A CHILL GUY MOST OF THE
TIME, BUT ONCE HE SETS HIS MIND
ON SOMETHING, THERE'S
NO TURNING BACK.
- STUBBORN...
JUST LIKE HIS FATHER.
- HE DOESN'T SEEM TO GET WHY
RACERS HAVE TO ACCEPT
CHALLENGES. I REALLY COULDN'T
TELL YOU WHY. BUT THE ENTIRE
CONCEPT REALLY SEEMS TO GET
UNDER HIS SKIN. WHEN SOMEBODY
TRIES TO FORCE HIM TO DO WHAT
HE DOESN'T WANT TO, HE SNAPS...
ONCE IN ELEVENTH GRADE, HE BEAT
THE HELL OUT OF SOME SENIORS
AFTER SOCCER PRACTICE.
WHAT? THAT DOESN'T
SOUND LIKE TAKUMI!
- HEY BOSS, I FINISHED
CLEANING UP OUTSIDE,
AND I LOCKED ALL
THE PUMPS FOR YOU.
- HEY! THANKS, KID.
- YEAH, SURE. WELL I'M OUTTA
HERE SO I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- TAKUMI.
HAVE A SEAT AND TALK
WITH ME FOR A SECOND.
- OKAY...
- YOU KNOW, I OVERHEARD SOME OF
THE GUYS TALKING EARLIER, THEY
SAID YOU'RE GONNA BE GOING UP
AGAINST A THREE-TWO TONIGHT.
- WHAT? THEY WERE WRONG.
- DON'T DO IT, KID. THAT GUY
HAS BAD MOJO.
- WELL. I GUESS IT'S A
GOOD THING I WASN'T...
- NO, NO, I ALREADY KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GONNA SAY, SO DON'T EVEN
BOTHER, I CAN TELL YOU EXACTLY
WHAT HAPPENED,
YOU GOT PRESSURED INTO
ACCEPTING THIS BATTLE
EVEN THOUGH YOU DIDN'T
REALLY WANT TO...
- ITSUKI RAN HIS MOUTH AND TOLD
THE GUY YOU'D RACE.
- YEAH...
- YOU KNOW, YOU'RE TOO NICE OF A
PERSON SOMETIMES, TAKUMI...
- IT'S ABOUT TIME YOU STARTED
LETTING YOUR FRIENDS
CLEAN UP THEIR OWN MESSES.
TRUST ME. DON'T RACE
THAT THREE-TWO.
THERE'S A LOT YOU DON'T KNOW
ABOUT CARS. I'M GUESSING YOU
DON'T EVEN HAVE A CLUE THE KINDS
OF THINGS THAT ONE'S CAPABLE OF.
- IS THE THREE-TWO
REALLY THAT GOOD?
- THAT'S IT. HE TOOK THE BAIT.
'GOOD' DOESN'T EVEN COME
CLOSE. IT'S IN A CLASS BY
ITSELF. IT'S TOP-OF-THE-LINE
DRIVING SYSTEM MERGES EVERY
PERFECT THING ABOUT THE FR
AND THE FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE
MAKES IT AN UNSTOPPABLE BEAST.
AN EIGHT-SIX OR A GT-R IS JUST
NO MATCH. IF THE DRIVER WAS AN
AMATEUR, THEN MAYBE,
BUT THIS GUY'S BIG TIME.
HE'LL BURY YOU OUT THERE.
- DAD NEVER TOLD ME ANY OF THIS.
ALL HE SAID IS THAT IT'D
BE A CLOSE RACE.
- TAKUMI?
YOU STILL HERE? YOU JUST BEAT
THAT TEAM FROM AKAGI, YOUR
REPUTATION AS A RACER IS AT A
HIGH POINT RIGHT NOW...
DON'T BLOW IT SO SOON.
IT'S NOT WISE TO GO UP AGAINST
SOMEONE YOU HAVE NO CHANCE OF
DEFEATING. THAT MAKE SENSE?
YOUR OPPONENT'S DRIVING A
THREE-TWO. NOT A MAN I KNOW
WOULD CALL YOU A COWARD
FOR BACKING OUT.
- A COWARD?
BOSS, I APPRECIATE THE
WARNING. I REALLY DO.
AND YOU KNOW YOUR OPINION
MEANS A LOT TO ME.
BUT TO BE HONEST...
I COULDN'T CARE LESS
ABOUT ANY FAME THAT I GET
OR DON'T GET AS A RACER.
- SO YOU AREN'T GONNA BACK DOWN?
- NO, HEARING YOU TALK ABOUT HOW
AMAZING THAT CAR IS ONLY MADE ME
WANNA SEE THE THING IN ACTION.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT IT CAN DO.
MAYBE STREET RACERS ARE AFRAID
OF GOING UP AGAINST A 3-2,
BUT NOT ME.
- THOUGHT THAT BIT MIGHT WORK.
HE REALLY IS EXACTLY
LIKE HIS FATHER.
- TEMPORARILY CLOSED?
DAD NEVER MENTIONED THIS TO
ME, HOW'S HE SUPPOSED TO MAKE
ANY MONEY WITH THE SHOP SHUT
DOWN? OH, NO! THE CAR!
IF HE WENT OUT DRINKIN'
WITH HIS BUDDIES
THEN I'M TOTALLY SCREWED.
HE WON'T BE BACK
UNTIL AT LEAST MORNING,
WHAT AM I GONNA DO NOW?
MAN, I CAN'T DO ANYTHING IF
I DON'T HAVE A CAR!
DAMMIT, I SHOULD HAVE
ASKED TO BORROW
THE STUPID THING BEFORE I LEFT.
- Boy: DUDE, WOULD YOU
LOOK AT THE CROWD,
THEY'RE PACKED IN LIKE CATTLE.
WAY MORE PEOPLE THAN
THE AKAGI RACE, MAN.
- THIS IS, LIKE, WHACKED OUT.
WHY DO YOU THINK SO MANY PEOPLE
CAME OUT HERE TONIGHT?
- YOU KNOW THEY'RE NOT HERE TO
SEE SOME LOUSY THREE-TWO.
- HELL, YES. THEY'RE HERE
FOR THE EIGHT-SIX DRIFT.
- I HEARD THIS DUDE SAY HE SAW
IT BARREL THROUGH A CORNER
LIKE IT WAS A STRAIGHTAWAY.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THIS!
- Takumi: OH, I SEE, OKAY, WELL
THANKS FOR CHECKING FOR ME.
IF HE HAPPENS TO SHOW UP COULD
YOU ASK HIM TO CALL HOME?
GREAT. THANK YOU.
CRAP. IT'S NO USE, I'M NEVER
GONNA FIND THAT JERK.
WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?
GIVE ME BACK MY EIGHT-SIX?
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
♪ RAGE MY DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- SO KENJI, WHO DO YOU
THINK'LL WIN THIS BATTLE
YOUR GOOD PAL ITSUKI
GOT YOU INTO?
- OF COURSE, I'D LIKE TO SAY THE
EIGHT-SIX, BUT I'M HONESTLY NOT
SURE IF EVEN TAKUMI
CAN BEAT A GT-R.
IT IS THE FASTEST DOMESTIC.
- BUT THE BIGGEST QUESTION RIGHT
NOW IS "WILL TAKUMI EVEN SHOW
"FOR THE RACE?".
IF HE DOESN'T, I GUESS IT'S
YOUR TURN AGAIN!
- SHUT UP!
- Announcer: NEXT TIME ON
INITIAL D, "TIME'S ALMOST UP!"
TAKUMI, DUDE YOU
GOTTA GET HERE SOON!
- Announcer: DON'T MISS IT!