- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD! ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- ( tires screeching )
- ( engine revving )
- WELL, WELL, WELL. HE'S GOT
SPEED ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS.
I'LL LET HIM CATCH UP.
R32, GTR. ALL RIGHT. LET'S SEE
HOW MUCH THIS GUY'S GOT TO GIVE.
- THAT'S HOW WE'RE PLAYING?
THAT'S ALL I NEEDED TO KNOW.
- ( tires screeching )
- YOU SURE IT'S ALL
RIGHT TO DROP YOU OFF
IN THIS NEIGHBORHOOD?
- Natsuki: UH, YEAH.
IT'LL BE FINE.
THAT'S MY HOUSE RIGHT
ACROSS THE STREET.
YOU SAID THIS WAS A PRETTY
JUNKY RIDE YOU JUST USED
FOR YOUR DAD'S WORK.
BUT I ACTUALLY LIKE IT.
IT RUNS REALLY GOOD AND IT'S
SMALL AND KIND OF CUTE.
LIKE YOU.
WHAT KIND OF CAR IS IT ANYWAY?
- A TRUENO.
- A TRUENO? WELL, WE SHOULD GO
FOR A SPIN AGAIN SOMETIME.
I HAD A REALLY GREAT TIME
WITH YOU TODAY, TAKUMI.
I'LL GIVE YOU A CALL
LATER, OKAY?
- DID YOU HEAR THAT, GIRL?
SHE CALLED US CUTE.
- ( tires screeching )
- KEEPING UP WITH RYOSUKE
TAKAHASHI AIN'T NOTHING.
I KNOW MY GTR IS BETTER THAN
ANYTHING THESE GUYS ARE PUSHING.
HE MIGHT BE A DECENT DRIVER, BUT
WITH THAT OUTDATED FC OF HIS,
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF HE
WAS ALREADY HITTING HIS LIMIT.
- NICE DRIVING. MY NAME'S
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
I'M WITH THE AKAGI REDSUNS.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
I'M TAKESHI NAKAZATO.
I RACE WITH A TEAM CALLED THE
NIGHT KIDS OUT OF MOUNT MYOGI.
- NAKAZATO OF THE NIGHT KIDS.
I'VE HEARD OF YOU BEFORE.
YOU'RE THE FASTEST STREET RACER
ON MOUNT MYOGI'S DOWNHILL.
- YOU KNOW, I'VE GOTTA
ADMIT IT'S A REAL HONOR
TO BE RECOGNIZED BY THE GREAT
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
- ONLY THING IS, I'M ALMOST SURE
I'VE HEARD YOU DRIVE
SOMETHING OTHER THAN THIS.
I BELIEVE IT WAS AN S13,
IF MEMORY SERVES.
( scoffs ) NOT THAT IT MATTERS,
BUT I'VE GOTTA ASK,
WHAT'S A STREET RACER FROM MYOGI
DOING HERE ON SUCH A NIGHT?
- YOU'VE ALWAYS SEEMED LIKE
A PRETTY SMART GUY, RYOSUKE,
SO LET'S CUT THE CRAP, OKAY?
YOU AND ME CAME OUT HERE FOR
THE SAME REASON,
AND I THINK WE BOTH KNOW
WHAT THAT REASON IS.
WE WANTED TO RUN INTO THE
EIGHT-SIX FROM THE OTHER NIGHT.
IT GOT YOU INTRIGUED, DIDN'T IT?
- ( scoffs ) WELL, WHAT DO YOU
KNOW, A GUY IN A SWEET THREE-TWO
TRYING TO TAKE A BITE
OUT OF THE EIGHT-SIX.
THINK YOUR 380 HORSEPOWER ENGINE
WILL BE ENOUGH?
- WHAT?
- I CAN TELL THAT
BY JUST LOOKING AT HER.
AT THE EXHAUST PIPE,
THE POWER SHE CAN REACH
ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS.
KIND OF THING'S HARD TO MISS.
ON THE UPHILL THE EIGHT-SIX IS
NO MATCH FOR THIS MACHINE.
BUT IF WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE DOWNHILL,
THERE'S NO WAY IN
HEAVEN OR EARTH
YOU'RE EVER GONNA BEAT
THAT EIGHT-SIX IN THE THREE-TWO.
- THE HELL ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT MY RIDE CAN'T HOLD UP
TO THE DOWNHILL?
THAT I'LL LOSE TO THAT WANNABE?
- IT'S NOT A PERSONAL ATTACK.
I'M JUST VOICING MY OPINION
BASED ON MY KNOWLEDGE
OF BOTH CARS.
- RIGHT. I THINK THE REAL
PROBLEM IS YOUR LACK OF NERVE.
YOUR KID BROTHER MIGHT'VE LOST
ON THE DOWNHILL,
BUT THERE'S NO NEED TO
GET ALL INTIMIDATED
BY SOME FREAKIN' RUST
BUCKET EIGHT-SIX.
- I THINK ONCE YOU RACE
AGAINST IT,
THIS'LL START TO MAKE A
LITTLE MORE SENSE.
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO'S
GONNA BE ABLE TO BEAT HIM.
- IF YOU'RE TRYING SOME KIND OF
REVERSE-PSYCHOLOGY THING ON ME,
YOU CAN FORGET IT. I DON'T EVER
WALK AWAY FROM A CHALLENGE.
I AM GONNA DESTROY
THAT EIGHT-SIX
AND WIPE THAT SMUG GRIN
OFF YOUR FACE!
I'LL MAKE YOU REMEMBER THE DAY
YOU MET TAKESHI NAKAZATO!
THAT CRAP ROTARY IS NO MATCH
FOR MY THREE-TWO!
- ( car door closes
and car drives off )
- I'M ALMOST SURE
I'VE HEARD YOU DRIVE
SOMETHING OTHER THAN THIS.
AN S13, IF MEMORY SERVES.
- DON'T ACT LIKE YOU KNOW ME.
I'VE CHANGED A LOT SINCE THEN.
- Takeshi: ( voiceover )
DAMN! I CAN'T PASS IT!
I CAN GET CLOSE IN THE CORNERS,
BUT HE LOSES ME
IN THE STRAIGHTAWAYS.
I HAVE BETTER TECHNIQUE
AS A RACER.
I KNOW IT! HOW AM I
LOSING TO THIS GUY?
WITH THIS S13 I CAN'T BEAT A
THREE-TWO, NO MATTER WHAT I DO.
I WAS THE FASTEST STREET RACER
ON MOUNT MYOGI'S DOWNHILL
AND LOOK AT ME NOW.
THIS IS PATHETIC. LOSING TO A
THREE-TWO THAT CAN'T EVEN DRIFT.
- Ryosuke: ( voiceover )
ALL CARS HAVE THEIR LIMITS.
NO MATTER HOW KILLER
THE DRIVER IS,
NO ONE CAN DRIVE BEYOND WHAT
THE CAR'S GOT SET IN ITS STEEL.
NOT EVEN THAT EIGHT-SIX.
- Takumiitsuki: MORNING, GUYS!
- HEY!
- Takumi: HERE,
GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
- COOL. SO, WHAT IS IT?
- Takumi: SOME FRIED TOFU.
IT'S LEFT OVER FROM YESTERDAY.
MY DAD TOLD ME I SHOULD BRING IT
TO YOU. HE SAID YOU LIKED IT.
- TELL HIM THANKS.
I'LL PUT THIS IN THE FRIDGE
FOR YOU.
- WOW. MADE A BETTER IMPRESSION
THAN I THOUGHT. ( laughs )
- HEY, TAKUMI?
- YEAH?
- IS IT TRUE YOU'VE BEEN
DELIVERIN' TOFU TO LAKE AKINA
FOR LIKE THE PAST FIVE YEARS?
- THAT'S RIGHT, ABOUT THAT LONG.
- COME ON, I THOUGHT YOU AND ME
WERE CLOSER THAN THAT, MAN.
SO, WHY THE BIG SECRET?
- BECAUSE IF I HAD
TALKED ABOUT IT AT ALL,
MY OLD MAN MIGHT'VE GOTTEN
INTO TROUBLE.
DON'T YOU THINK?
- YEAH, YOU'RE PROBABLY
RIGHT, I GUESS.
FIVE YEARS AGO WE STARTED
JUNIOR HIGH.
BACK THEN, I SEEM TO REMEMBER
THAT TROUBLE HAD A WAY
OF FINDING US ANYWAY.
- YOU'VE DRIVEN A LOT LONGER
THAN ME. SINCE JUNIOR HIGH,
YOU'VE BEEN DRIVING EVERY
DAY ON MOUNT AKINA.
SNOW, RAIN, NOTHING MATTERED.
YOU GOT OUT THERE AND YOU DROVE.
- SURE, BEFORE DAWN.
NOBODY ELSE IS ON THE
ROAD. NO BIG DEAL.
- I DON'T MEAN IT
LIKE THAT. THOSE CORNERS!
I MEAN, WEREN'T YOU SCARED?
I'D FLIP MY LID!
- OH. WELL, WHEN I FIRST
STARTED, YEAH, I WAS.
BUT IN SIX MONTHS,
THE FEAR WAS GONE.
I NOTICED RIGHT AWAY THAT
THE TIRES SLIPPED NATURALLY
WHEN I'D ACCELERATE,
BUT I THINK IT TOOK ANOTHER
SIX MONTHS OR SO BEFORE
I FELT LIKE I HAD
ANY CONTROL OVER IT.
- THEN YOU MASTERED THE DOWNHILL
IN ONLY ABOUT A YEAR.
IS THAT RIGHT?
- WELL, BEING ON IT EVERY DAY,
THE NERVOUSNESS VANISHED
PRETTY QUICKLY.
I HAD NOTHING ELSE
TO DO OUT THERE,
SO WHEN I STARTED GETTING
BORED WITH THE DRIVE
I'D SEE HOW CLOSE I COULD GET
TO THE GUARDRAILS
WITHOUT TOUCHING.
- ( gasps ) THAT'S INSANE!
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
- I WOULDN'T CALL IT INSANE.
I MEAN, I'VE NEVER WRECKED
AND AT MY BEST,
I CAN GET AS CLOSE AS A
CENTIMETER OR SO
TO THE GUARDRAIL.
- ARE YOU FOR REAL?
- Takumi: ( voiceover ) DRIVING
THE SAME ROUTE OVER AND OVER
FOR MY DAD EVERY DAY
GETS SUPER BORING.
UNLESS I CAN FIND SOMETHING
TO DO TO BREAK UP THE ROUTINE.
WHICH IS WHY I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D WANT TO IMPROVE AS A DRIVER.
DIDN'T CARE ENOUGH ABOUT IT
TO WANT TO.
BUT YOU KNOW, I GET IMPATIENT
AND I'D WANNA GET HOME
OR TO SCHOOL, WHEREVER, FASTER,
SO I'D TRY GOIN' AS
FAST AS I COULD.
- WAIT. THERE ONE THING
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- HOW IS IT YOU CAN DRIVE WITH
A CARLOAD OF TOFU?
GO TOO FAST,
YOU COULD DAMAGE YOUR HAUL.
- I DON'T HAVE MUCH SPEED
ON THE UPHILL, SO IT'S COOL.
AND MY DAD PUTS A PAPER CUP FULL
OF WATER IN MY CUP HOLDER.
SAYS IF I CAN DRIVE
WITHOUT IT SPILLING,
THEN I WON'T DAMAGE
THE TOFU IN BACK.
DOESN'T MATTER
HOW FAST I'M GOING.
- Yuuichi: AH.
- THE FIRST FEW TIMES
I TRIED IT,
I DIDN'T THINK I'D EVER GET
THE HANG OF IT.
EVEN DRIVING SLOW,
I'D SPILL WATER ALL OVER MYSELF.
- HMM. I'D IMAGINE SO.
- Takumi: THE BRAKE, STEERING
WHEEL, SHIFTER, GAS PEDAL,
IF EVEN ONE OF THEM MOVES A
LITTLE ROUGH, THE WATER SPILLS.
DAD WOULD SAY CRAP LIKE,
"ROLL THE WATER IN THE CUP."
DIDN'T MAKE SENSE AT FIRST,
BUT I LEARNED.
- WHAT'S "ROLL THE WATER
IN THE CUP" MEAN?
- SOMETHING TO DO WITH THE
SURFACE TENSION OF THE WATER.
IT'LL ONLY STRETCH SO FAR
BEFORE IT SPILLS.
SO YOU HAVE TO ROLL THE WATER
AROUND THE RIM OF THE CUP.
AT EACH CORNER I ROLL THE WATER
TO THE EDGE OF THE RIM
AS I DRIVE UP THE HILL.
IT DID TAKE ME A LITTLE WHILE
TO BE ABLE TO DRIFT
WITHOUT SPILLING THE WATER.
IT SEEMED LIKE FOREVER,
BUT I FINALLY FIGURED IT OUT.
- DRIFTING WITHOUT SPILLING?
YOU MEAN YOU CAN ACTUALLY
DO THAT CRAP?
- YOU BETTER NOT BE LYING TO US,
TAKUMI! YOU HEAR ME?
- THE PRIMARY CONTROL POINT
WHEN IT COMES TO ANY CAR
IS THE CENTER OF BALANCE.
THAT'S THE STARTING POINT.
- Iketani: ( voiceover ) THE
DRIFT KING, KEICHI-I TSUCHIYA,
SAYS SO IN HIS VIDEO.
- Yuuichi: ( voiceover ) IT'S
NOT AN EASY TRICK.
TO DRIVE WITHOUT
SPILLING THAT WATER,
TAKUMI WOULD HAVE TO
HAVE MASTERED
THE EIGHT-SIX'S
CENTER OF BALANCE.
FORGET ANYTHING ABOUT DRIFTING.
- ( grunting )
- THAT KIND OF THING
IS IMPOSSIBLE! LIAR!
- Takumi: I'M NOT LYING!
- YOU BEAT KEISUKE. SO?
WHAT, NOW YOU ACT LIKE YOU
KNOW EVERYTHING?
- ( screams )
- OH, A CUSTOMER.
HOW YOU DOING? CAN I FILL HER
UP WITH HIGH OCTANE FOR YOU?
- Customer: THANKS,
THAT'D BE GREAT.
- ( voiceover ) AMAZING, BUNTA.
YOUR BOY'S TECHNIQUE
IS WAY ABOVE
JUST A REGULAR MOUNTAIN RACER.
- GOODBYE, AND...
- ( both ) THANK YOU
FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- TAKUMI, I NEED TO ASK YOU
A FAVOR.
WOULD YOU LET ME RIDE IN
THE PASSENGER SEAT
WHEN YOU DO THE NEXT DOWNHILL
RUN AT AKINA?
- INITIAL D!
- Bunta: YOU WANT TO USE
THE CAR? AT THIS TIME OF NIGHT?
- I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D LET ME
ANYWAY. FORGET ABOUT IT.
NOT A BIG DEAL.
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
- DID YOU HEAR ME SAY, "NO?"
- WELL, I DON'T WANT TO TAKE IT
IF YOU WERE GONNA USE IT.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T NEED IT
FOR ANYTHING TONIGHT?
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE A MEETING
AT THE CHAMBER OF COMMERCE
OR SOME OTHER REASON.
MAYBE YOU NEED
A LITTLE TIME TO THINK.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
SOUNDS LIKE YOU THINK
YOU'LL BE IN TROUBLE
IF I DON'T HAVE TO USE IT.
- WHAT? NO. NO,
I DIDN'T MEAN IT LIKE THAT.
- FINE. THEN TAKE THE CAR.
BUT DON'T FORGET,
THAT MEANS I'M RELYING ON YOU
TO PICK ME UP
FROM MY MEETING LATER.
- UH, OKAY, SO YOU REALLY
DO HAVE A MEETING.
- ( engine starting )
- ( laughing )
- LOOK AT ME, MAN.
I'M ALL NERVOUS.
LIKE I'M ABOUT TO GET ON THE
HUGE ROLLER COASTER AT THE PARK.
- OH, MAN. I'M ALL JEALOUS.
YOU ARE SO LUCKY. SERIOUSLY.
- HE'S JUST RIDING IN
A CAR, YOU GUYS.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE
GOING TO THE MOON.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE GOT THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
- RIGHT ON! READY WHEN YOU
ARE. TEAR IT UP, MAN!
NOW BACK AWAY FROM THE
CAR, YOU LOSERS.
- ( engine revving )
- HE'S GONNA HAVE
THE TIME OF HIS LIFE.
- OH, MAN. I'M FREAKING JEALOUS.
YOU ARE SO LUCKY. SERIOUSLY.
- ( engine revving
in the distance )
- Iketani: ( voiceover ) THE
FIRST CORNER IS COMING UP SOON.
I'LL FIGURE OUT WHAT
HE'S DOING DIFFERENT FROM ME
AS SOON AS HE TAKES IT.
THEN I'LL STEAL THE TECHNIQUE.
HEY! WAIT! WHOA! TAKUMI, BRAKE!
( screaming )
( voiceover) HOW CAN HE CONTROL
THE CAR LIKE THIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS THIS REALLY HAPPENING?
- WHOAH.
- ( Iketani screaming )
THE SPEEDOMETER WARNING SOUND
IS ON. HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
THAT MEANS WE'RE MOVING AT
OVER 100 KILOMETERS AN HOUR.
AND WE'RE COMING UP
ON THE NEXT CORNER.
- HUH?
- HOLD UP. WHAT THE HELL
THEY DOING BACK HERE ALREADY?
- MAYBE SOMETHING HAPPENED.
IT'S WAY TOO EARLY TO BE BACK
FROM THE BOTTOM.
( both gasp )
- Itsuki: IS HE UNCONSCIOUS?
TAKUMI!
WHICH CORNER DID THIS HAPPEN
TO HIM ON?
YEAH? THE THIRD ONE?
AH! I KNEW IT!
THE AGONIZED CRY OF
HIS LAST MOMENT
DURING THIS HORRIFYING DOWNHILL
ECHOED ACROSS THE MOUNTAIN!
POOR IKETANI.
IN THE THIRD CORNER...
TOTALLY PASSED OUT!
- THEN ALL OF THIS
HAS TO BE TRUE.
- UH, HEY, BOSS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
- ( laughs ) SEEING WHAT
YOU WERE UP TO.
( laughs )
MAYBE I SHOULD
JUST HEAD ON HOME.
- Waitress:
TAKE YOUR TIME, BOYS.
- I'VE HEARD OF THAT GUY.
NAKAZATO OF THE NIGHT KIDS.
THERE'S NOBODY LEFT IN MYOGI
WHO'LL GO UP AGAINST HIM
ANYMORE. THE DUDE'S UNTOUCHABLE.
- IT'S HARD TO BE IMPRESSED
BY THE TECHNIQUE OF SOMEBODY
WHO DRIVES A THREE-TWO.
IN THAT RIDE, THE CAR DOES
MOST OF THE WORK FOR YOU ANYWAY.
- MAYBE NOT.
- WHAT? YOU THINK I'M
WRONG ABOUT THAT?
- HERE WE GO AGAIN.
WE KNOW YOU HATE THE
THREE-TWO, KEISUKE.
- DAMN STRAIGHT.
- AND RYOSUKE LIKES IT.
BUT I HAVE TO SAY, IT'S BAD FOR
NAKAZATO TO DEFEAT TAKUMI FIRST.
'CAUSE IF THEY TAKE
HIM BEFORE US,
THE NIGHT KIDS WILL BRAG
THEY BEAT THE CAR
AND DRIVER WE COULDN'T,
WHICH COULD LOOK TERRIBLE.
LIKE WE'RE ON A
LOWER RUNG THAN THEM.
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO HAVE THAT
KIND OF A HICCUP
ON OUR RECORD.
YOU KNOW HOW RUMORS
HAVE A TENDENCY TO SPIN
OUT OF CONTROL.
AND THAT, I THINK,
IS EXACTLY WHAT NAKAZATO WANTS.
- I DON'T THINK YOU NEED TO
WORRY ABOUT IT, FUMIHIRO.
NONE OF THOSE EXHAUST SUCKING
LOSERS IN THE NIGHT KIDS
CAN BEAT THE EIGHT-SIX.
NOT IN A MILLION YEARS.
AS LONG THEY'RE RIDING
THE DOWNHILL OF AKINA,
I CAN'T THINK OF
ANYBODY THAT COULD BEAT HIM.
EXCEPT OF COURSE,
MY BROTHER HERE.
THE EIGHT-SIX HAS GOT SPEED
ON A MUCH HIGHER LEVEL
THAN ALMOST ANY OF US.
- YEAH, I'M NOT FOLLOWING
ANY OF THIS.
THERE ARE A LOT OF NEW
STATE OF THE ART CARS OUT THERE.
WHY CAN'T ANY OF THEM
COMPETE WITH THE EIGHT-SIX?
- THE STRAIGHT TRUTH IS THAT
SOMETIMES A CAR
HAS TOO MUCH POWER TO
BE VERY EFFECTIVE.
- ( gasps )
- TURBO'S GREAT
ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS,
BUT WHEN YOU'RE COMING
OUT OF THE CORNERS
IT CAN SERIOUSLY HINDER
THE CAR'S BEHAVIOR
AND LIKE A DOUBLE-EDGED
SWORD, IT CAN CUT YOU
JUST AS EASILY AS IT
DOES YOUR ENEMIES.
THE EIGHT-SIX ON THE OTHER HAND
GETS FASTER
ONCE IT'S HIT ITS STRIDE.
WHEN THE STRAIGHTAWAYS
ARE SHORTER,
THE MORE POWERFUL CAR DOESN'T
ALWAYS HAVE THE ADVANTAGE.
SOMETIMES IT JUST BOILS DOWN
TO WHOEVER'S MORE AGGRESSIVE.
WHICH IS WHY KEISUKE'S TURBO,
CLEARLY THE FASTER CAR...
- Fumihiro: ( voiceover )
HAD THE OPPOSITE EFFECT.
- Keisuke: THAT'S RIGHT.
ON AKINA'S DOWNHILL,
THE AMOUNT OF TIME
I HAD TO USE ALL OF MY CAR'S
350 HORSES WAS NEXT TO NOTHING.
REALLY TICKED ME OFF.
THE SECOND I'D THINK I HAD
GAINED ENOUGH GROUND
TO LEAVE HIM BEHIND,
I'D HAVE TO BRAKE
FOR THE NEXT CORNER.
THEN IT WOULD TAKE ME TOO LONG
TO ACCELERATE AFTER THAT.
- OF COURSE IT DID, THAT'S HOW
IT GOES WITH THE FR.
IT GETS ALL ITS POWER FROM THE
REAR TIRES GRIPPING THE ROAD.
- WHOA, HOLD UP. THEN WHAT'LL
HAPPEN WITH THE THREE-TWO?
THAT'S A FOUR WHEEL DRIVE,
ISN'T IT?
AND IT'S GOT THE ATTESA E.T.S.
THAT THING CAN GIVE
STABLE TRACTION
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE
GIVING IT THE GAS.
SO HE CAN USE THE TURBO
AS MUCH AS HE WANTS.
NAKAZATO'S THREE-TWO MIGHT BE
ABLE TO BEAT THE EIGHT-SIX!
- ( both ) THANK YOU
FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- WELCOME!
HOW'RE YOU DOING TODAY?
- ( bell ringing )
- I DON'T KNOW,
I JUST FEEL KIND OF WEIRD NOW.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE SUDDENLY
THIS WHOLE OTHER PERSON
I'VE NEVER MET.
- WHAT? WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- UH, NEVER MIND. HERE.
HAVE ANOTHER HOT SPRING BUN.
- SURE.
- EH?
AND THEN YOU DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
AND YOU'RE BACK TO BEING
REGULAR OLD TAKUMI.
THE SPACED OUT DUDE WHO
ALWAYS LOOKS TIRED
AND EATS A BOATLOAD OF MANJU.
- PEOPLE REALLY THINK
I LOOK SPACED OUT?
- YEP.
BUT ONCE YOU'RE IN THE
DRIVER'S SEAT OF THE EIGHT-SIX,
BARRELING DOWN AKINA'S CORNERS
AT BREAKNECK SPEED...
YOU BECOME THE PRIDE OF EVERY
STREET RACER AROUND HERE, MAN.
WOMEN WANT YOU, MEN WANT
TO BE YOU, YOU'RE AWESOME!
- YOU THINK SO? THAT'S KIND OF
EMBARRASSING, BUT, YEAH... OW!
- I TOLD YOU I'M NOT
TALKING ABOUT RIGHT NOW!
RIGHT NOW YOU'RE JUST
THE SPACED OUT IDIOT, REMEMBER?
- I'M NOT SPACED OUT! BUT, WELL,
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DO FEEL KIND OF STRANGE.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- WELL, DURING THE LAST RACE,
AND EVEN WHEN I HAD IKETANI
RIDING WITH ME,
I WAS JUST DRIVING THE WAY
I NORMALLY DO.
I DON'T GET WHY EVERYBODY IS
SUDDENLY FREAKING OUT ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST DRIVING.
IT'S NOT IMPORTANT, NOT LIKE
I'M CURING SOME DISEASE.
I GUESS I'VE NEVER REALLY BEEN
THE KIND OF GUY WHO LIKES
ALL THE THINGS THAT SEEM
TO MAKE OTHER PEOPLE HAPPY.
BUT I'M STARTING TO THINK
MAYBE DRIVING ISN'T SO BAD.
- ( tires screeching )
- HEY.
- HUH?
A BLACK THREE-TWO?
I'VE BEEN SEEING THAT THING
ALL OVER THE PLACE!
- ANY CLOSER AND HE'LL BE
UP MY TAILPIPE!
- DON'T LET HIM PASS YOU, DUDE.
JUST KEEP YOUR SPEED UP.
- DUH! I'LL NAIL HIM
ON THE DOWNHILL.
I'VE GOT MORE HORSEPOWER
THAN THE EIGHT-SIX
THAT BEAT KAY-SKAY. BRING IT ON!
♪ WHEN YOU GET TO THE TOP ♪
- ( voiceover ) SMALL FISH.
♪ JUST LISTEN, LET ME TELL YA ♪
♪ WHAT YOU'RE MISSIN'
SHOW YOU WHAT YOU'RE MISSIN' ♪
- HOW THE HELL DID HE PASS US
ON THE OUTSIDE?
♪ SPENDING ALL THE MONEY
YOU GOT ♪
♪ NO MORE WOMEN
TO LOVE YOU NOW ♪
THAT WAS INSANE. THE WAY THAT
GUY ACCELERATED WAS UNREAL!
- NO CRAP. I SHOULD
HAVE KNOWN BETTER
THAN TO GO UP AGAINST
A MUSCLE CAR
IN THIS GUTLESS PIECE OF JUNK.
I NEVER HAD A SHOT
AT KEEPING THE LEAD
AGAINST THIS GUY!
♪ YOU GOTTA GO
AND LIVE FOREVER ♪
♪ BACK ON THE ROCKS ♪
- Takeshi: ( voiceover ) I GOT
ONE AMAZING MACHINE HERE.
OTHER RACERS
HAVE BEATEN ME IN THE PAST,
BUT NOW THAT I'M BEHIND
THE WHEEL OF A THREE-TWO,
I'D LIKE TO SEE 'EM TRY.
ANYBODY WHO MADE ME SWEAT BACK
THEN IS OFF MY RADAR, ANYWAY.
THIS DRIFT GAME MIGHT BE
POPULAR NOW,
BUT IT'S JUST A
FLASH IN THE PAN.
IT'S NOT MY STYLE ANYWAY.
I DON'T LIKE TO RIDE
UNLESS IT'S AN EXTREME BATTLE,
WHITE SMOKIN' TIRES AND ALL.
ANYTHING OUTSIDE OF THAT
IS A WASTE OF MY TIME.
SO COME ON OUT, EIGHT-SIX.
I GOT PLANS FOR YOU.
I KNEW IT THE SECOND I SAW YOU.
YOU'RE THE OPPONENT I'VE
BEEN WAITING FOR.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- Fumihiro: ( voiceover ) I'M
HERE WITH YUUICHI TACHIBANA.
SO, YUUICHI, I UNDERSTAND
YOU WERE A PRETTY FAMOUS
STREET RACER IN AKINA
BACK IN YOUR DAY.
- Yuuichi: ( voiceover ) YEAH.
I DROVE WITH BUNTA ALL THE TIME.
- Fumihiro: AND NOW,
HIS SON, TAKUMI,
IS GOING UP AGAINST TAKESHI OF
THE NIGHT KIDS.
- Yuuichi: RIGHT. ONLY PROBLEM
IS, TAKUMI DOESN'T WANNA RACE.
- Fumihiro: WHAT? THEN WE
DON'T GET TO SEE THEM GO AT IT?
- Yuuichi: DON'T WORRY. I THINK
I HAVE AN IDEA. LEAVE IT TO ME.
- I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
- Announcer: NEXT TIME
ON INITIAL D, "A RACER'S PRIDE."
DON'T MISS IT!