- ( engine starting )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
NO CARS AHEAD. SHOW THIS
LOSER WHAT YOU CAN DO!
GO!
- (engines revving)
- THAT DID NOT JUST HAPPEN.
- WE ALREADY KNEW
WHAT A BADASS THIS GUY WAS
BEFORE WE WENT INTO THIS RACE.
BUT, SINCE THIS IS
GONNA BE MY LAST ONE,
WE ARE NOT GONNA WALK AWAY
WONDERING IF WE REALLY GAVE IT
EVERYTHING WE HAD!
WHAT IS IT?
YOU SCARED?
YOU'RE FREAKIN' USELESS!
I SWEAR!
NOTHING BUT A SACK
OF DEAD WEIGHT RIDING SHOTGUN!
- HUH? DEAD WEIGHT?
- YOU HEARD ME! YOU'RE SCREWING
UP THE POWER TO WEIGHT RATIO!
- SHE TURNS INTO A REAL HARDASS
BEHIND THE WHEEL.
I'M NOT DEAD WEIGHT YOU BITCH!
I'M I'M HOT! I'M NOT FAT!
I GOT A KILLER BODY!
- FORTY-NINE KILOGRAMS
OF EXTRA WEIGHT.
- I WEIGH FORTY-SEVEN DAMMIT!
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE HERE
WITH SELF RESPECT.
READY FOR THIS MAKO. TIME TO
PUT OUR LIVES ON THE LINE.
- WELL, WELCOME BACK
TO THE PARTY.
- LISTEN, ON THIS NEXT ONE,
ENTER THE TURN SO THAT YOU
ALMOST SCRAPE THE INSIDE WALL.
- OKAY. I'M ALL OVER IT.
- THANKS. I HAD
A REAL NICE TIME TONIGHT.
- SO DID I.
NATSUKI?
WHEN WILL I BE ABLE
TO SEE YOU AGAIN?
- IT'S HARD TO SAY.
SCHOOL'S STARTING UP SOON.
- THAT GIRL.
- ( tires screeching)
- Sayuki: THE NEXT CORNER
LOOKS PRETTY DUSTY.
I WANT YOU HUGGING THE INSIDE.
- I'M ON IT.
- NO CARS COMIN' AT YOU.
START THE DRIFT NOW.
- I HAVEN'T BEEN MYSELF
IN THIS RACE SO FAR.
I'VE BEEN FOCUSING
TOO MUCH ON HIM.
I GUESS DEEP DOWN I DIDN'T
THINK THERE WAS ANY RACER
WHO COULD FOLLOW US
SO TIGHT.
THAT THERE WAS NO ONE THAT GOOD.
BUT NOW I SEE THE TRUTH.
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO RACE
AT THE TOP OF MY GAME
IF MY ATTENTION IS HONED IN
ON WHAT'S HAPPENING BEHIND ME.
SO I'M NEVER LOOKING
IN THAT REARVIEW AGAIN.
- YOU'RE GONNA WANNA DRIFT HERE!
- (tires screeching)
- THERE CAN'T BE TOO MANY
MORE CORNERS TO HIT.
- Kenji: YEAH. I WONDER
IF HE'S STILL CHASIN'?
IF HE IS, HE'S PROB'LY HANGIN'
ON BY A THREAD AT THIS POINT.
TO TELL THE TRUTH, I FIGURED
THIS THING'D BE OVER BY NOW.
- CALM DOWN! HE'LL DO IT!
EVEN IF HE CAN'T PASS
HER ON THIS RUN,
HE'LL BEAT HER ON THE NEXT ONE.
- NO WAY HE'S GONNA PASS 'ER.
IN FACT, I'M AMAZED THERE'S
STILL A RACE GOING ON AT ALL.
HE JUST HAD TO BE THE CAT.
THAT'S HIM.
NEW COURSE, SO TOSS OUT
THE ASS KICKER ATTITUDE.
- (engine revvs)
- IT'S WORKING!
YOU FIXED IT! WOW!
THANKS AGAIN. I'M MAKO SATO.
CALL ME SOMETIME!
- SORRY 'BOUT THAT, I JUST.
- I WANT MY LAST
RACE TO BE SPECIAL,
SOMETHING
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
I WANNA RACE THE EIGHT-SIX
HERE ON MY HOME TURF.
THAT'S MY FINAL WISH AS A RACER.
IF YOU HELP ME I'LL EVEN
GIVE YOU MY VIRGINITY.
IF THAT'S WHAT IT'LL TAKE. THEN
THAT'S WHAT I'M WILLING TO DO.
- Kenji: YO, IKETANI!
- YEAH, WHAT?
- GEEZ, MAN. BRING IT ON
BACK DOWN TO EARTH.
YOU WERE THINKING ABOUT MAKO,
WEREN'T YA?
YOU ARE SO FREAKIN' OBVIOUS.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT!
- NO POINT IN HIDING THAT
KINDA STUFF FROM YOUR BUDS.
I MEAN, I'LL BE REAL
WITH YA FOR ONCE.
I THINK SHE'S
A PRETTY SWEET CHICK.
- YOU DO?
- LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
THE DETAILS OF YOU GUYS.
BUT I'M THINKIN'
AFTER THIS RACE,
MAYBE YOU OUGHTA GIVE IT
THE OL' COLLEGE TRY.
YOU'D BE A GRADE A MORON TO LET
THAT SUPER HOTTIE SLIP AWAY.
- DUDE, I DON'T CARE.
- HUH?
- (tires screeching)
- ( electronica playing )
- Sayuki: OKAY, DRIFT IT!
♪ GOIN' TO DISCO PARTY ♪
- I'VE GOT A CAR SPOTTED
ON THE ROAD AHEAD.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE IT'LL
BE ANOTHER THREE TURNS
BEFORE WE REACH HIM.
SO HIT THIS NEXT CORNER HARD.
- OKAY. YOU GOT IT.
♪ I'LL BE FOREVER CRAZY ♪
♪ YOU GONNA GET ALWAYS READY ♪
♪ WE OVER THE WORLD TOGETHER ♪
♪ ON AND ON AGAIN ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S WARMING ♪
- HERE COMES THAT CAR
I WAS TELLIN' YOU ABOUT.
♪ GET YOUR BODY AND MOVE YA ♪
♪ ME AND YOU ♪
♪ LOVE YOU TOO ♪
- HEY, IT SOUNDS LIKE
WE'RE COMING UP ON A RACE.
- COOL! I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE IT!
- CHECK THEIR DOWNHILL TECHNIQUE
WHEN WE SEE 'EM.
THAT'LL SHOW YOU
HOW GOOD THEY ARE.
- (both exclaim in fear)
- BAD ASS.
- CALLED IT.
- SAYUKI CAN TIME ONCOMING
TRAFFIC PERFECTLY. IT'S A GIFT.
NOBODY ALIVE IS BETTER AT IT.
SHE ALWAYS CATCHES
THOSE DISTANT HEADLIGHTS
PEEKING THROUGH THE
TREE BRANCHES.
- EASE YOUR GRIP. AND YOU'LL
NEED TO STAY TO THE INSIDE!
NICE, MAKO. YOU'RE TOTALLY
NAILING THIS RUN.
YOU GONNA WANNA DRIFT
RIGHT THROUGH THIS ONE.
NO CARS AHEAD.
PULL ANOTHER DRIFT.
AMAZING. MAYBE TOO AMAZING.
THE BEST RACERS ALWAYS
LEAVE ROOM FOR ERROR
CUZ THEY KNOW THEY
CAN'T SEE EVERYTHING.
SO EVEN WHEN IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE EXCEEDING THEIR LIMITS,
THEY'RE STILL ONLY USING
FULL GRIP WHEN EXITING A TURN.
THEY EASE UP ON THE GRIP
WHEN BRAKING INTO ONE.
IT'S ONE THING TO BE FAST, BUT
SOMETHING ELSE TO BE RECKLESS.
ONE MISTAKE ON AN UNFORGIVING
COURSE LIKE THIS ONE
AND YOU'RE LUCKY
IF YOU WALK AWAY ALIVE.
BUT THE THING IS,
THE WAY SHE'S DRIVING,
SHE DOESN'T HAVE THAT
MARGIN OF ERROR.
AND SHE'S TOO FOCUSED
TO REALIZE IT.
SHOULD I BRING THIS UP TO HER
NOW? OR DO I JUST LET IT GO?
I MEAN, IT IS MY JOB
TO CLUE HER INTO THESE THINGS.
I DON'T KNOW!
THIS SUCKS. I DON'T
WANNA SAY ANYTHING
THAT'S GONNA THROW
HER OFF HER GAME.
SO FAR SHE'S PERFECT.
THERE'S ONLY ONE CALL
I CAN MAKE.
WE'RE THE BEST TEAM
OUT THERE.
HOW COULD I NOT BELIEVE
IN HER ABILITIES?
THIS IS EASILY THE BEST RACE
SHE'S EVER RUN. NO DOUBT.
- AH, MAN. THIS RACE IS GETTING
CRAZIER BY THE SECOND!
SHE'S SPED UP AGAIN.
IF SHE PUSHES IT ANY
FASTER THAN THIS,
I'LL BE SAILIN' PAST MY LIMIT.
HELL, I'M BARELY IN CONTROL
OF THIS SITUATION ALREADY,
ABUSING ALL FOUR OF MY TIRES.
I MAY NOT EVEN MAKE IT
TO THE END OF THIS THING.
- INITIAL D!
- GO TIME. THIS IS THE
LAST CHANCE WE'LL HAVE
TO SHAKE THIS GUY OFF OUR TAIL.
- I KNOW THAT!
- NO CARS AT ALL.
KNOCK THIS SUCKER OUT!
HE'S NOT FOLLOWING US ANYMORE.
WHY NOT?
- MAKO, WOULD YOU CHILL OUT!
YOU'RE GOIN' IN WAY TOO SHARP!
DAMN! WE CAN'T PULL OUT!
IF YOU CAN, SPIN AWAY FROM HIM!
OH, NO! DON'T HIT US, PLEASE!
- OH, YES, WE'RE ALIVE.
- THAT WAS BRILLIANT.
HE JUST BEAT US
ON THE FIRST RUN.
THIS GUY'S SO SKILLED
THAT I WANNA HATE
EVERY SINGLE
THING ABOUT HIM.
YOU DOIN' OKAY?
- WELL, WE LOST, BUT SOMEHOW
I FEEL PRETTY GOOD ABOUT IT.
IT TOOK ME BACK A BIT.
BACK TO THE TIME
WHEN I FIRST STARTED RACING
AND THIS WAS STILL
SO FOREIGN TO ME.
WE'D STAY UP UNTIL DAWN
PRACTICING ALMOST EVERY
DAY OF THE WEEK.
THERE WAS SOMETHING SO PURE
ABOUT THAT, SOMETHING WE LOST.
- I THINK YOU TOOK IT TOO FAR
AT THE END THERE,
BUT YOU WERE KICKING
SOME ASS UP TO THAT POINT.
IT REALLY WAS THE BEST
RACE YOU EVER RAN.
- YOU THINK SO?
- WHATEVER YOU DECIDE TO DO
WITH YOUR LIFE FROM NOW ON,
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOU HAVE MY BLESSING.
YOU'VE EARNED IT.
- THAT MEANS A LOT. THANK YOU.
- DON'T START CRYING
LIKE A GIRL ON ME, MAKO.
LET'S JUST TRY TO
ENJOY OUR MOMENT
BEFORE THE BOYS START THEIR
VICTORY DANCE.
- (tires screeching)
- HEY, THEY'RE BACK!
I WONDER HOW THE RACE ENDED UP.
THE GIRLS ARE IN FRONT.
YOU THINK THEY'LL BE GOIN'
FOR ANOTHER RUN?
- YEAH.
- Itsuku: TAKUMI!
- HOW'D IT GO?
PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
WHAT I THINK YOU'RE GONNA.
WE'RE NOT GONNA NEED TO PREP YOU
UP FOR A SECOND DOWNHILL ARE WE?
- THERE WON'T BE ANOTHER RACE.
IT'S ALL OVER, BOYS.
- I KNEW IT.
- I REALLY THOUGHT
HE COULD PULL IT OFF.
- MAN. THIS SUCKS.
I DIDN'T WANT TO SEE HIM
LOSE LIKE THIS.
IT'S JUST TOO TRAGIC.
- (chuckles) CHIN UP YOU GUYS.
WE LOST.
- WAIT. WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDIN'.
YOU LOST?
- THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE A TOTAL JERK
AND MAKE ME REPEAT
MYSELF ARE YOU?
YOU'RE BUDDY HERE'S THE WINNER.
- (all exclaim)
- (cheers)
- NEVER IN A MILLION YEARS DID I
THINK WE'D LOSE ON OUR OWN TURF.
- ALL I DID WAS FOLLOW YOU AND I
DIDN'T EVEN DO A VERY GOOD JOB
AT THAT UP UNTIL THE VERY END.
I WOULDN'T REALLY
CALL THAT A VICTORY.
YOU WON'T SEE ME
BRAGGING ABOUT IT, ANYWAY.
- DON'T BE SO MODEST, KID.
YOU WON FAIR AND SQUARE.
AND WITH THE SKILLS
YOU SHOWED OUT THERE,
YOU HAVE EVERY RIGHT
TO RUB IT IN IFYOU WANT TO.
- NO THANKS.
- WE'VE PUT IN MORE HOURS UP
HERE THAN ANYBODY ELSE WE KNOW.
WERE CONFIDENT
OF A VICTORY TONIGHT.
THEN YOU CHOSE TO CHASE US,
WHICH THREW US FOR A LOOP,
AND WE COULDN'T SHAKE YOU OFF.
WE ACCEPT OUR DEFEAT.
DON'T WE?
- MM-HMM.
- AH, MAKO.
- THAT WAS THE BEST RACE
I'VE EVER BEEN IN BY A MILE.
SO THANK YOU.
( giggles )
- CAREFUL, GIRLS ARE DELICATE.
- (all laughing)
- YOU'RE A MYSTERY TO ME,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YOUR NATURAL RACING
ABILITY IS GREATER
THAN ANYBODY'S I'VE EVER SEEN.
BUT OUTSIDE OF THAT YOU SEEM
JUST LIKE ANY OTHER KID.
- THAT'S WHAT WE ALWAYS SAY
ABOUT HIM.
WHEN HE'S NOT BEHIND
THE WHEEL RACING,
I SWEAR WE CAN'T TELL IF
THE GUYS ASLEEP OR AWAKE
OR THE LIVING DEAD.
- HEY. THANKS A LOT, MAN.
- Kenji: SHUT UP,
YOU KNOW HE'S RIGHT.
- EITHER WAY. I'M STILL AMAZED
AT HOW GOOD YOU ARE
CONSIDERING YOU'RE SO YOUNG.
- Kenji: I'M THINKIN'
AFTER THIS RACE,
MAYBE YOU OUGHTA GIVE IT THE
OL' COLLEGE TRY.
YOU'D BE A GRADE A MORON TO LET
THAT SUPER HOTTIE SLIP AWAY.
- Mako: IKETANI.
UH. THANK YOU, FOR TONIGHT.
MAKO, I... I... JUST UH...
- QUIT BEING SUCH A DEPRESSED
LOSER, IKETANI!
RACERS DON'T NEED CHICKS MAN!
ISN'T THAT RIGHT!
- NO. NO, WE DON'T.
- I DIDN'T NOTICE THIS BEFORE,
BUT THAT GUY'S ACTUALLY
PRETTY FREAKIN' CUTE.
SO. YOU GONNA TELL ME
YOUR NAME OR DO I HAVE TO GUESS?
- I'M TAKUMI FUJIWARA.
- I'M ITSUKI TAKEUCHI.
I'M EIGHTEEN! I'M AN AIRES.
MY BLOOD TYPE IS O,
AND MY FAVORITE CAR IS...
- UH, YEAH. I DON'T THINK
I ASKED YOU, SO JUST LET IT GO.
- (laughs wildly)
- ANYWAY, SINCE WE'RE
ALL FRIENDS NOW,
WHATTYA SAY WE GET TOGETHER?
MAYBE WE COULD GO OUT FOR A
SWIM OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- THAT SOUNDS AWESOME!
-WELL. KENJI YOU IN?
-MM-HMM.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU, BIG WINNER?
IKETANI, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- UH. YEAH, WHY NOT?
- SWEET! THIS IS GONNA ROCK!
THANKS FOR THE INVITE, SAYUKI!
- (exclaims in disgust)
- LET'S CUT LOOSE SUCKAS!
WE CAN ALL SQUEEZE IN AND
PARTY DOWN IN MY EIGHT-FIVE!
WHATTYA GUYS SAY?
- ( theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuuichi: WISE
WORDS HERE, KID,
IF MEN WERE NEVER HONEST
WITH THEMSELVES,
MANKIND WOULD HAVE GONE EXTINCT
A LONG TIME AGO.
- YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT, SIR.
- THE BEGINNING
OF A RELATIONSHIP
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT PART.
- MAKE SURE
THAT YOU DON'T, UH...
- YEAH, HI, HONEY.
SURE, I'M ON MY WAY.
- YOU'RE LEAVIN'? WAIT.
MAKE SURE THAT I DON'T' WHAT?
Announcer: NEXT ON INITIAL D,
THE END OF SUMMER
DON'T MISS IT.