- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ BREAK INTO THE NIGHT,
IT'S THE TIME ♪
- ( people chattering )
- AH, MAN. I'M SO GLAD WE CAME
OUT HERE. EVERYONE'S SO HOT!
- ITSUKI, MY FRIEND, THIS PLACE
IS PARADISE ON EARTH.
- Sayuki: HEY, TAKUMI!
GET YOUR CUTE BUTT OVER HERE!
ARE YOU GONNA GO SWIMMING
WITH US OR WHAT?
- UM, NO THANKS. I'M COOL.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU GUYS?
WE CAME HERE TO SWIM.
- Kenji: BE RIGHT THERE.
- I AM SO GLAD WE CAME.
THIS IS AWESOME!
- ME, TOO, MAN.
- YOU'RE COMING WITH US TOO,
AREN'T YOU, IKETANI?
- HEY, WHAT'S WRONG, BRO? YOU
ARE HAVING A GOOD TIME, RIGHT?
- YEAH, SURE.
THE TIME OF MY LIFE.
- LET'S GO HIT THE SUPER SLIDE.
IT LOOKS LIKE A BLAST.
- ACTUALLY I THINK I'LL JUST
HANG AROUND HERE IF THAT'S OKAY.
- THAT'S OUR TAKUMI.
ALWAYS HANGIN' AROUND'.
- MIND IF WE JOIN YOU
ON A TRIP DOWN THE SLIDE?
- COURSE YOU GUYS CAN COME.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE ALL HERE.
- Both: YES! THAT'S DEFINITELY
WHY WE'RE HERE, ALRIGHT.
- COOL, LET'S GO!
- NOW, GET YOUR BUTT
IN GEAR, DUDE.
- IT'S JUST THAT I'VE NEVER BEEN
REALLY GREAT WITH SLIDES.
- Sayuki: COMPARED
TO YOUR SUPER DRIFT,
I'M PRETTY SURE THIS SLIDE
SHOULD BE CAKE.
- SHE'S ALWAYS PUSHING
EVERYONE AROUND.
KINDA USED TO GETTING HER WAY.
- WELL, I GUESS IF THAT'S
THE WAY SHE IS,
I'M JUST GLAD THEY'RE
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
- SO WAS IT REALLY OKAY FOR YOU
TO TAKE TODAY OFF?
I KNOW WORK'S IMPORTANT TO YOU.
- I HAD TO USE A SICK DAY,
SO MY BOSS WASN'T TOO THRILLED
ABOUT IT, BUT IT'LL BE FINE.
- SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
MY HEART FEELS LIKE IT MIGHT
BEAT RIGHT OUT OF MY CHEST,
AND SEEING HER
IN HER BATHING SUIT
IS THE BEST SUMMER MEMORY
I COULD HAVE HOPED FOR.
SHE'S LIKE AN ANGEL.
YOU NEVER FORGET THE FIRST TIME
YOU REALIZE YOU'RE
STARING AT AN ANGEL.
BUT THIS MEMORY IS ALL
I'LL EVER HAVE.
SHE'S WAY OUTTA MY LEAGUE.
- Iketani.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING
YOU'VE DONE FOR ME.
- OH, NO NEED.
- I DON'T THINK YOU GET WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO BE IN MY SHOES.
I LEARNED A WHOLE LOT ABOUT
MYSELF THE OTHER NIGHT.
THINGS I NEVER EXPECTED.
- THAT'S GREAT.
- I'M SORRY THAT I DRAGGED YOU
INTO ALL THIS.
ESPECIALLY NOW I'VE DECIDED
TO CONTINUE RACING.
- THAT'S COOL.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
I WAS HOPING THAT YOU WEREN'T
JUST GONNA THROW IN THE TOWEL.
- I BECAME SO FULL OF MYSELF
OVER TIME.
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN PEOPLE START CALLING YOU
THE FASTEST IN USUI.
- ( tires screeching )
- MAKO, CHILL IT OUT!
YOU'RE GOIN' IN TOO SHARP.
- FACING TAKUMI FORCED ME
TO REALIZE
THAT TECHNIQUE IS A MORE
IMPORTANT ELEMENT IN DRIVING
THAN I HAD ALLOWED
MYSELF TO BELIEVE.
AND IF I WERE TO QUIT NOW,
I'D FEEL LIKE MY OWN DRIVING WAS
I DON'T KNOW, UNFINISHED.
- I'M GLAD YOU GOT
SOMETHING OUT OF IT.
AT LEAST WHAT I DID WAS
USEFUL TO YOU SOMEHOW.
- HERE GOES.
YOU REMEMBER THE
PROMISE I MADE.
THAT TIME WHEN WE WERE OUT
BY THE LAKE, DON'T YOU?
I THINK IT MAY HAVE
COME OUT WRONG,
OR YOU MAY HAVE
MISUNDERSTOOD ME.
BUT EITHER WAY
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO
GET THE IMPRESSION
I ONLY WANTED TO CUT A DEAL.
I DON'T.
I JUST WANT YOU.
- ( stuttering )
- MEET ME AT 8, AT THE KAMAMESHI
BILLBOARD WHERE WE MET.
I'LL BE THERE.
( Sayuki squealing )
- IS THERE ANY WAY
WE CAN SLOW DOWN?
- ( laughs ) YOU'RE SO CUTE!
- MY BACK'S PRESSED RIGHT UP
AGAINST HER BOOBS!
- ( whooping )
- THIS IS NOT WHAT I IMAGINED!
- I HATE MY LIFE!
- ( crying )
- Sayuki: Ah, crap!
MAKO. TOSS THE BALL BACK!
- HELP US OUT!
- OVER HERE!
- Iketani: RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI!
- Mako: READY, SAYUKI?
- Sayuki: YEAH, C'MON!
- Itsuki: THANK YOU!
- Sayuki: YOU THROW LIKE A GIRL!
- Mako: SORRY, MY ARM STINKS.
( laughs )
THAT WAS AN AWFUL THROW.
- I DON'T GET IT. WHY DOES SHE
CARRY HIS PICTURE AROUND?
- SOMETHING BOTHERING YOU?
- OH. IT'S NOTHING.
I WAS WONDERING...
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- OF COURSE.
- YOU SAID...
YOU TOLD ME THAT YOU'VE NEVER
BEEN IN A RELATIONSHIP BEFORE.
- YEAH.
- WHAT ABOUT A CRUSH?
YOU HAD TO HAVE LIKED
SOMEBODY LIKE THAT, RIGHT?
- SURE. I GUESS.
- WHAT I'M GETTIN' AT IS
WHY DIDN'T YOU EVER
GO OUT WITH THAT GUY
IF YOU LIKED HIM?
MOST GUYS I KNOW WOULD
KILL THEIR BEST FRIEND
TO GET A SHOT AT GOING OUT
WITH SOMEONE AS HOT AS YOU.
- OH, WELL. THANK YOU.
THAT'S FLATTERING, BUT I'M NOT
SO SURE ABOUT THAT.
- SO, WHAT DOES THIS GUY DO?
- HE'S A STREET RACER.
IT WAS ABOUT THREE YEARS AGO,
I GUESS.
I WAS STILL IN HIGH SCHOOL.
A FEW OF US FROM SCHOOL WENT UP
TO THE MOUNTAIN TO SEE A RACE.
I DIDN'T KNOW A THING ABOUT
STREET RACING BACK THEN.
TOTALLY IGNORANT.
BUT THERE WAS THIS ONE CAR THAT
LEFT A HUGE IMPRESSION ON ME.
EVEN I COULD SEE THAT THIS
GUY HAD SOME KIND OF
CRAZY TALENT FOR RACING.
FROM THAT POINT ON I WAS
ABSOLUTELY HOOKED
ON THE WHOLE IDEA
OF STREET RACING.
IT FASCINATED ME.
I GOT MY LICENSE.
I MANAGED TO BUY A CAR.
I PRACTICED EVERY SECOND OF THE
DAY MY SCHEDULE WOULD ALLOW.
I THOUGHT I'D FEEL CLOSER TO HIM
IF I DID THOSE THINGS.
IF I GOT BETTER, MAYBE IT
WASN'T THE PERFECT MOTIVATION.
I WENT TO WATCH HIM RACE
ALL THE TIME.
IT WAS LIKE GOING TO THE MOVIES.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I NEVER EVEN TALKED TO THE GUY.
I never had the nerve.
It was just an infatuation.
A fleeting attraction. It isn't
like it was very meaningful.
I WAS PROBABLY MORE ATTRACTED
TO HIS TECHNIQUE THAN ANYTHING.
- NO WAY. YOU HAD TO HAVE
LIKED HIM.
- YEAH, I GUESS I DID LIKE HIM.
A LOT.
- WHAT A JOKE. I SHOULDN'T
HAVE EVEN ASKED.
THIS THING BLEW UP
RIGHT IN MY FACE.
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
SHE FEELS SO DISTANT.
SHE WAS CRAZY ABOUT
A SUPERSTAR. A LEGEND.
THE NUMBER ONE DRIVER
IN ALL OF GUNMA.
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
EVERYTHING MAKES SENSE NOW.
NOW I GET WHY SHE
DIGS FC'S SO MUCH.
HOW CAN I POSSIBLY
COMPETE WITH HIM?
- Initial D.
- Initial D!
- ( engine starting )
- THIS IS IT. HE'S FINALLY
READY TO GO HEAD TO HEAD
WITH THE EIGHT-SIX.
- HOP IN. YOU AND ME ARE
GOING FOR A RIDE.
I'LL GIVE YOU A FIRST HAND LOOK
AT MY FASTEST RACER THEORY.
- OKAY.
- THAT WAS ONE OF THE BEST TIMES
I'VE EVER HAD IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
GOING TO THE WATERPARK IS
WAY COOLER WITH CHICKS,
I HAD SO MUCH FUN.
DID YOU, TAKUMI?
- YEAH, BUT NOT AS MUCH
AS YOU AND KENJI HAD
SPENDING THE DAY TOGETHER.
MAKO AND SAYUKI ARE LIKE
THE COOLEST CHICKS ALIVE,
DON'T YOU THINK, KENJI?
- YOU BOUNCE BACK FASTER
THAN ANYBODY I KNOW.
WASN'T IT LIKE TWO DAYS
AGO YOU WERE GOIN' ON
ABOUT HOW STREET RACERS
DON'T NEED GIRLS?
- WELL, YEAH. BUT THEY'RE WOMEN!
- Both: HI, ITSUKI!
- MY BRAIN IS TOTALLY
BLANK OTHER THAN THE IMAGE
OF THOSE TWO
IN THEIR BIKINIS.
LIKE A BLINDING LIGHT.
- SAYUKI'S GOT A RACK YOU
WANNA CURL UP AND SLEEP ON.
BUT MAKO'S BODY, DAMN.
THE THING'S A FREAKIN' MIRACLE.
Don'tcha think so?
- YEAH, SURE. I GUESS.
- YOU GUESS MAKO'S GOT
A SLAMMIN' BODY?
WHAT THE HELL'S UP
YOUR BUTT, DUDE?
WHAT, DID THE TWO OF YOU
HAVE A FIGHT OR SOMETHING?
- NO, WE DIDN'T HAVE A FIGHT.
- I'M JUST TIRED. THAT'S ALL.
- ( car door closing )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
MR. SICK DAY?
- YEAH, ABOUT THAT, BOSS,
I WANTED TO SAY I'M SORRY.
- JUST GIVING YOU A HARD TIME.
YOU'RE ONLY YOUNG ONCE.
YOU SHOULD TAKE THE TIME TO
ENJOY IT WHILE IT LASTS.
I'D BE MORE WORRIED ABOUT YOU
IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE A GIRLFRIEND
AND THE ONLY THING YOU CARED
ABOUT WERE CARS AND RACING
AND THE DUDES YOU PUMP GAS WITH.
- REALLY?
- WELL, BEST OF LUCK.
THIS GIRL'S NAME IS MAKO RIGHT?
I'LL BET SHE'S CUTE.
HOW'RE THINGS GOING?
- TO BE HONEST,
I REALLY DON'T THINK IT'S
LOOKIN' TOO GOOD, BOSS.
WHAT CAN I SAY, I SCREWED UP
AND GOT INTERESTED
IN ONE OF THOSE CHICKS WHO'S
JUST TOO GOOD FOR ME.
- DON'T BE SO PESSIMISTIC,
IKETANI.
WOMEN DON'T WANT A GUY
WHO'S NEGATIVE ALL THE TIME.
- HEY, I'M JUST BEING REALISTIC.
TRUST ME. I DON'T HAVE
A CHANCE ON EARTH.
I CAN'T COMPETE WITH
SOMEONE LIKE RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
I CAN BARELY KEEP UP WITH HIM.
I KNOW HE HASN'T JACKED
WITH HIS FC. SO WHAT'S THE DEAL?
- WITH EVERY NEW BIT
OF DATA THAT I GATHER,
MY THEORY EVOLVES.
BE PATIENT, EIGHT-SIX.
WHEN IT'S COMPLETE, YOU'LL BE
NOTHING BUT ANOTHER NAME
TO CHECK OFF OF MY
DEFEATED LIST.
- ( car door opening )
- GUESS I GOT HERE FIRST.
WOW. MY HEART'S BEATING SO FAST
I CAN HARDLY CATCH MY BREATH.
I FEEL LIKE I MIGHT JUST
FALL OVER AND DIE
WHEN IKETANI GETS HERE.
- Yuuichi: WHAT?
YOU'RE EVEN DUMBER
THAN YOU LOOK!
REALLY IT'S LIKE YOU'VE NEVER
MET A WOMAN BEFORE.
LIKE IT'S YOUR FIRST DAY.
NOW LISTEN TO ME. SHE WASN'T
ACTUALLY DATING THIS GUY.
SHE LIKED HIM FROM A DISTANCE.
IT'S JUST INFATUATION.
EVERY TEENAGE GIRL HAS A CRUSH
ON AN OLDER GUY AT SOME POINT.
IT'S WHAT THEY DO!
NO DIFFERENT THAN IF SHE THOUGHT
SOME GUY FROM SOME
TV SHOW WAS CUTE.
- TV?
- STOP AND THINK ABOUT IT
FOR A MINUTE, OKAY?
THE GIRL DECIDED TO OPEN UP
TO YOU ABOUT EVERYTHING
BECAUSE SHE CHOSE
YOU OVER SOME GUY
SHE'S NEVER EVEN TALKED
TO BEFORE IN HER LIFE.
AND SHE TOLD YOU ALL OF THIS
STUFF BECAUSE SHE TRUSTS YOU.
BECAUSE SHE'S INVESTING HERSELF
IN YOU. CAN'T YOU SEE THAT?
YOU GOTTA GET OVER THIS
PATHETIC INFERIORITY COMPLEX
YOU'VE GOT GOING ON.
BEING IN LOVE MEANS THAT
YOU ACCEPT EVERYTHING
ABOUT THE OTHER PERSON
THE WAY THEY ARE!
IF NO ONE'S TOLD YOU BEFORE,
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
LOVE'S ALL ABOUT!
DID YOU SAY EIGHT O'CLOCK?
IT'S ALREADY HALF PAST,
YOU IDIOT!
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO NOW?
- I DON'T THINK I'LL MAKE IT.
IT'LL TAKE AT LEAST AN HOUR
TO GET ALL THE WAY
TO YOKOKAWA FROM HERE.
NO WAY SHE'LL STILL BE
WAITIN' ON ME AFTER THAT LONG.
- GET OUTTA HERE!
YOU WON'T KNOW ANY
OF THAT FOR SURE
UNTIL YOU GET THERE WILL YA.
GO OR YOU'RE FIRED!
IF YOU CALL YOURSELF A RACER
THEN YOU WON'T LET
UP ON THE GAS.
YOU'D BETTER DRIVE THAT CAR
LIKE YOUR LIFE DEPENDED ON IT.
I TRULY HATE TO SAY IT, BUT HE
PROBABLY WON'T MAKE IT IN TIME.
WELL, DISAPPOINTMENT'S
A PART OF GROWING UP.
- ( pop music playing )
- BOSS IS RIGHT. I'M SO STUPID.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
IF I LIVE ANOTHER HUNDRED YEARS,
I'LL NEVER MEET ANYONE
LIKE HER AGAIN.
WHY COULDN'T I BE MORE
HONEST WITH HER?
- THANKS AGAIN. I'M MAKO SATO.
CALL ME SOMETIME!
IF THAT'S WHAT IT'LL TAKE,
MEET ME AT EIGHT, AT THE
KAMAMESHI BILLBOARD
WHERE WE MET.
I'LL BE THERE.
- SHE WAS ALWAYS
STRAIGHT UP WITH ME,
BUT I COULDN'T DO IT BACK.
I'M SUCH A JACKASS!
- ( pop music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( sighs )
MY FEET ARE KILLING ME.
I HATE HEELS.
- MAKO, I DON'T NEED TO DO
SOMETHING LIKE RUN OFF
TO A HOTEL WITH YOU.
I MEAN, YEAH, I WANT TO, SURE.
BUT I DON'T HAVE TO.
WHAT AM I SAYIN'?
I JUST WANNA SEE YOUR FACE.
THAT'S ALL I CARE ABOUT!
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE,
JUST ONE MORE CHANCE.
THAT'S ALL I'M ASKIN'.
JUST DON'T TAKE THIS
ANGEL AWAY FROM ME.
There's an accident? Now?
Oh, please, not now!
- NO! COME ON! THIS SUCKS!
- ( cars honking )
- I'M SORRY, MAKO.
I'M SO SORRY.
- I AM NEVER WEARING
HIGH HEELS AGAIN.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Announcer: AH, TAKUMI.
WHAT'S WITH THE BOUQUET?
- UH.
- OH, IT'S FROM
NOTSUKI, ISN'T IT?
- Takumi: NO.
- Announcer: ALRIGHT, I GET IT.
YOU AND THE 8-6 HAVE BECOME
PRETTY FAMOUS LATELY,
HAVEN'T YOU?
THOSE FLOWERS MUST BE
FROM SOME FEMALE ADMIRERS, HUH?
- Takumi: NO,
THAT'S NOT IT EITHER.
-Announcer: SO THEN SAYUKI MUST
HAVE GIVEN THEM TO YOU?
SHE'S PROBABLY LAYING IT
ON THICK.
- Takumi: ACTUALLY, I GOT THIS
FROM RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
- Announcer: AH.
NEXT ON INITIAL D,
CHALLENGE FROM A SUPERSTAR.
Don't miss it!