- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- ♪ LOST INTO THE NIGHT
♪ LOST INTO THE NIGHT ♪
♪ LOVE IS FIRE ♪
- SHE'S FAST.
♪ STAND BY ME NOW ♪
♪ MAKE ME FEEL ALRIGHT
♪ AND YOU GONNA TAKE ME HIGH ♪
♪ FEEL LIKE A BIRD IN THE SKY ♪
♪ AND NOBODY
I KNOW COULD LOVE YOU ♪
♪ MORE THAN ME TONIGHT ♪
I'M IN TROUBLE HERE.
HOPE I CAN KEEP UP WITH HER.
NO. IF SHE CAN DO THIS,
SO CAN I. DON'T DOUBT YOURSELF.
PUSH IT.
- ( tires screeching )
♪ GIMME LOVE TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND NOTHING IS GONNA CHANGE ♪
♪ LOVE IS FIRE ♪
- YOU NEED TO STAY HARD TO THE
INSIDE ON THE NEXT CORNER.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT!
SOMETHING'S IN THE ROAD.
YOU NEED TO CUT OVER.
THIS GUY'S NOT HALF BAD.
BETTER THAN
OTHER RACERS I'VE SEEN.
HE'S ACTUALLY KEEPING UP.
- MAYBE HE'LL GIVE US A RACE
THAT LASTS LONGER
THAN THE FIRST 5 CORNERS.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW HE'S GONNA
BE ABLE TO KEEP THIS PACE.
ESPECIALLY SINCE HE'S NOT
USED TO THIS COURSE
OR THE WAY WE RUN.
IT'S LIKE I'M NOT EVEN
RACING THESE CHICKS.
FEELS LIKE I'M IN THE FRONT SEAT
OF A ROLLER COASTER.
I'M JUST ALONG FOR THE RIDE.
IT'S SCARING THE HELL OUT OF ME
HOW OUT OF SYNC I AM.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
BUT THE SECOND I FALL BEHIND
THESE GIRLS, I'M DONE FOR.
I'VE GOTTA STAY CLOSE!
I'M SO USED TO AKINA.
I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW IMPORTANT
IT WAS TO KNOW THE COURSE.
IF I WAS TO LOSE FOCUS,
EVEN FOR A SECOND,
I'D SPIN OUT AND CRASH INTO THE
ROCKFACE OR SAIL OFF THE CLIFF.
- NOW I GET WHY SO
MANY PEOPLE ARE TALKIN'
ABOUT THIS EIGHT-SIX.
HE'S STUCK TO OUR BUMPER
LIKE A DAMN LICENSE PLATE.
GOOD FOR HIM.
NOT WHATTYA SAY YOU FOCUS ON THE
PART OF THE ROAD IN FRONT OF US.
NOT BEHIND.
- NARROW RIGHT TURN COMING UP.
- OKAY, I SEE IT.
- MAN, THIS GIRL'S
GOT SOME SPEED. DAMN.
I'VE GOTTA STAY ON HER,
NO MATTER WHAT.
IF SHE CAN DO THIS, SO CAN I.
- IT'S THAT OLD WHAT ONE MAN CAN
DO, SO CAN ANOTHER PHILOSOPHY.
TAKUMI SAID THAT IF SHE COULD
MAKE IT AROUND THE CORNERS,
SO CAN HE.
- YEP. THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE SAID.
- HOW'S THAT A PHILOSOPHY?
GEEZ. IT'S A LITTLE CHILDISH.
BUT BRAVE FOR SOMETHING
THAT SOUNDS SO GRADE SCHOOL.
- I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S MORE
IMPRESSIVE HE SAID IT
OR THAT HE BACKED IT UP.
SOMEBODY OF LESSER ABILITIES,
WOULDN'T HAVE EVEN TRIED.
- I GUESS HE CAN PROBABLY
CONTROL HIS RUN PRETTY WELL
AS LONG AS HE DOESN'T
PUSH PAST HIS OWN LIMITATIONS.
- OF COURSE HE CAN.
YEAH. BUT HAVE EITHER OF YOU
CONSIDERED THAT HE'S RACING
AGAINST NOT ONE BUT TWO CHICKS
WHO KNOW EVERY DETAIL
OF THIS COURSE.
THEY'RE GONNA ENTER
EACH CORNER LIKE A BULLET
AND HE'LL HAVETA DO THE EXACT
SAME IF HE WANTS TO KEEP UP.
AND TO TOP IT ALL OFF, HE KNOWS
NOTHING ABOUT THE COURSE.
HE'S DRIVING IT
COMPLETELY COLD.
IT KINDA FREAKS ME OUT.
I'M JUST GLAD IT'S TAKUMI
OUT THERE INSTEAD OF ME.
- YEAH. IT'LL TAKE
ALL HIS TECHNIQUE.
AND EVERY OUNCE OF HIS COURAGE.
JUST ONE MISTAKE,
EVEN A TINY ONE
AND TAKUMI COULD DIE OUT THERE.
- SO HE'S OUT RACING
A SIL-EIGHTY.
WHAT THE HELL IS A SIL-EIGHTY?
- ( engines revving )
- DAMN. HE'S STILL ON ME.
WHY? AM I NOT GOING
FAST ENOUGH FOR HIM?
- YOU'RE ROCKIN' IT.
JUST LEAVE HIM IN THE REARVIEW
WHERE HE BELONGS.
- I'M TRYING, BUT I CAN'T
SEEM TO SHAKE HIM OFF.
- YOU KEEP
WORRYING ABOUT HIM
AND YOU'RE GONNA SCREW
UP YOUR RHYTHM.
LEAVE ALL OF THE BUSINESS
WITH THIS EIGHT-SIX TO ME.
I GOT THIS KID'S NUMBER.
THIS RACE IS JUST
GETTING GEARED UP.
AND SINCE WE'RE JUST
GETTING STARTED,
WHAT SAY WE TRY
TO ENJOY IT SOME?
- SOUNDS GOOD. JUST MAKE SURE
WE DON'T GET KILLED.
- I'M YOUR PARTNER. THAT'S
EXACTLY WHAT I'M HERE FOR.
TOGETHER WE'RE THE FASTEST TEAM
IN USUI. DON'T FORGET THAT.
Sayuki: HOW ABOUT WE RUN
A CAT AND MOUSE RACE
DOWN THE MOUNTAIN?
THEY'RE FUN.
IT'S BASICALLY A CHASE.
IF THE MOUSE GETS AWAY,
THE RACE IS OVER.
IF NOT, WE KEEP SWITCHING
POSITIONS UNTIL SOMEONE WINS.
THINK OF IT AS A
'SUDDEN DEATH, DEATHMATCH.'
- WITH THIS KIND OF SET UP
I'M THINKING IT WILL BE BEST
IF YOU GO IN FRONT FIRST.
- HE'S RIGHT.
'CAUSE THERE'S NO WAY
THIS IS GONNA END WITH
JUST ONE RACE.
THAT WAY YOU AT LEAST
GET IN ONE PRACTICE RUN.
- THAT AND IT'S PROBABLY BETTER
TO LOSE IN THE SECOND RACE.
- Takumi: I THINK I WANNA
CHASE HER ON THE FIRST RUN.
YOU NEED TO THINK
THIS OVER, TAKUMI.
SORRY BUT THIS IS MY RACE
SO I'M GONNA RUN IT MY WAY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I CHOSE
TO CHASE HER.
AND ONLY BECAUSE
I DIDN'T WANT HER CHASING ME.
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
DAMMIT, THIS IS TOUGH.
- ON AN UNFAMILIAR COURSE,
IT'S CRUCIAL FOR A DRIVER
TO DETERMINE THE CORRECT SPEED
IN WHICH TO ENTER THE CORNERS.
KEISUKE'S LOSS TO THE 8-6,
AND NAKAZATO'S BOTH HAPPENED
FOR THE SAME REASON.
COURSE KNOWLEDGE GIVES THE RACER
A DEFINITE ADVANTAGE.
REGARDLESS OF HIS
TECHNIQUE OR SKILL LEVEL.
SO THE QUESTION IS,
HOW CAN I BEAT THE EIGHT-SIX?
UNLESS I'M MISTAKEN, I SHOULD
BE ABLE TO EKE OUT A WIN.
EVEN AT AKINA PASS.
- COMING INTO THIS I WAS
WAY TOO OPTIMISTIC.
I TOOK A RISKY CHALLENGE
AND IT'S NOT PAYING OFF.
THE DIFFERENCE OF A FEW INCHES
AND A LITTLE SPEED AT THE START
OF A CORNER MAKES A HUGE IMPACT
ON THE EXIT.
I WISH I KNEW
THE ROAD BETTER.
DAMN! TOO WIDE!
CRAP. I NUDGED THE GUARDRAIL!
THIS SUCKS! I'VE GOTTA FIGURE
OUT A WAY TO STAY CLOSER!
- EVERY HEART-POUNDING MOMENT
BEHIND THE WHEEL
SCULPTS THE RACER INTO A LEANER,
FIERCER DRIVER.
WITH MY KID'S EXCEPTIONAL
CONCENTRATION
AND REFINED TECHNIQUE.
AND OF COURSE,
WITH MY EIGHT-SIX UNDER HIM,
THE CAR I'VE SPENT
YEARS CRAFTING
INTO THE ULTIMATE
RACING MACHINE,
HE WON'T LOSE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE?
I WONDER IF IT'S ALL
OVER BY NOW.
- NOTHING IS OVER UNTIL THEY
GET THEIR BUTTS BACK UP HERE.
- THIS IS A ONE-SIDED RACE
NO MATTER HOW YOU LOOK AT IT.
THOSE CHICKS
GOT IT IN THE BAG.
- IKETANI, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
LET THAT ATTITUDE GO.
YOU KNOW TAKUMI'S NEVER BEEN
FAVORED IN A RACE BEFORE
AND HE'S COME OUT ON THE WINNING
END EVERY SINGLE TIME.
NAKAZATO'S THREE TWO WAS LIKE
AN ANVIL FALLING FROM THE SKY
BUT HE DODGED IT.
AND THE GUM TAPE DEATH
MATCH WAS HIS FIRST TIME
EVER TRYING SOMETHING LIKE THAT
AND HE BLEW THAT LOSER
OFF THE SIDE OF THE MOUNTAIN,
ALMOST LITERALLY.
- BUT THROUGH ALL OF THAT,
TAKUMI HAD ONE CONSTANT HE
COULD ALWAYS COUNT ON.
HE WAS ALWAYS ON AKINA PASS.
THE SAME ROUTE THAT HE'S
DRIVEN EVERY SINGLE MORNING,
YEAR AFTER YEAR.
SO YOU REALLY THINK
THE LOCATION OF THE RACE
MAKES THAT BIG OF A DIFFERENCE
ON THE OUTCOME?
IF THE GUY HAD DRIVEN THIS
PASS EVEN ONCE BEFORE
I WOULDN'T BE WORRIED,
BUT THIS IS HIS FIRST RUN.
HE'S NEVER EVEN
SEEN THIS PAVEMENT.
- Kenji: HEY, IKETANI.
I GOT A QUESTION.
WHAT IN THE HELL
WAS THAT BLONDE CHICK DOING?
THE ONE SITTING NEXT TO MAKO.
I THOUGHT CHICKS ONLY WENT
TO THE BATHROOM TOGETHER.
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT ISN'T LIKE I TRAINED THEM.
- I WAS WONDERING ABOUT THAT,
TOO. I MEAN, THIS IS A RACE.
IT'S SERIOUS. AND SHE
SLIPPED INTO THAT SEAT
LIKE IT WAS THE MOST
NORMAL THING IN THE WORLD.
- SHOOT, MAN.
I DON'T HAVE DETAILS.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT THE TWO OF
'EM ARE LIKE BEST FRIENDS,
HAVE BEEN FOREVER.
THEY'VE BROKEN
DOWN RACING STYLES
AND ANALYZED TECHNIQUE TOGETHER
SINCE THEY GOT INTO
RACING A FEW YEARS BACK.
DOING IT LIKE THAT IS THE ONLY
WAY THEY KNOW IT, I GUESS.
- SO SAYUKI'S LIKE THE
NAVIGATOR OR THE SPOTTER,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- OH, NO. THAT MAKES IT
A HECKUVA LOT WORSE FOR TAKUMI.
- NO, WAIT, I DON'T CARE.
HE'S NOT GONNA LOSE.
IT'S UNFATHOMABLE.
- I CAN TELL YOU'RE STRESSED
WHEN YOU USE BIG WORDS,
BUT YOU'RE RIGHT.
IF YOU GOT A GOOD NAV, YOU CAN
CONCENTRATE ON YOUR DRIVING.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
WHAT MAKO'S DOING.
- 'KAY. WE GOT SOMETHING
COMING UP IN THE LANE AHEAD.
CUT TO THE OUTSIDE. NOW!
- GOT IT!
- INITIAL D!
INITIAL D!
- THIS KID IS AMAZING. HE'S
KEEPING UP WITH MAKO'S BEST.
AND IT STILL ISN'T
FAST ENOUGH FOR HIM.
I'M BLOWN AWAY.
HEY. C-121 IS COMING UP
PRETTY QUICK.
WE CAN SHAKE HIM OFF THERE.
REMEMBER, WE NEED TO HEAD
INTO THAT CORNER DRIFTING.
DIVE INTO USUI'S TOUGHEST
CORNER HEAD FIRST.
THAT'LL SHOW THIS
LITTLE BUMPKIN
EXACTLY WHO HE'S
DEALING WITH OUT HERE.
- HELL YEAH. THIS'LL BE
THE END OF IT.
IT'S TIME YOU AND ME GAVE HIM
A LESSON ON HOW DRIFTING
IS REALLY SUPPOSED TO BE DONE.
NO ONE BUT ME HAS EVER CLEARED
THAT CORNER AT FULL SPEED.
NO ONE.
- ARE MAKO AND SAYUKI
UP HERE TONIGHT?
CAN'T FIND 'EM ANYWHERE.
- SORRY, MAN. I DON'T KNOW. I
HADN'T SEEN 'EM UP HERE ANYWAY.
- I WANNA CHECK OUT
THAT SIL-EIGHTY'S DRIFT.
IT KILLS.
EVERYBODY KNOWS C-121 IS
THE BEST PLACE TO CATCH IT.
SO I THOUGHT I'D COME HANG OUT.
- IT'S A HELLUVA THING
TO PULL OFF, ISN'T IT?
- NOTHIN' HARDER.
IF YOU'RE GOOD ENOUGH TO
DRIFT THROUGH THIS TURN,
YOU'RE GOLDEN.
YOU WON'T HAVE ANY TROUBLE WITH
ANYTHING USUI THROWS AT YOU.
- COURSE BEING THE BEST IN USUI
BASICALLY RANKS YOU
AS THE BEST ANYWHERE.
- REALLY?
- YEAH, THAT'S THE TRUTH.
AND IF YOU DON'T
HAVE THE CAJONES
TO FLY INTO THAT CORNER
AT FULL TILT,
YOU DEFINITELY DON'T
HAVE THE SPEED
TO DRIFT THROUGH TO THE END.
IT'S THE ONE CORNER WHERE NEWBS
ALWAYS SCREW UP. SUCKERS.
- BUT SOME OF 'EM CAN ACTUALLY
PULL IT OFF, CAN'T THEY?
I MEAN, THEY DON'T ALL CRASH.
- YEAH, SURE, I GUESS NOT.
BUT MAKO'S SIL-EIGHTY KNOCKS IT
OUT AT FULL SPEED EVERY TIME.
I DUNNO WHAT KINDA SPEED
SHE'S CLOCKIN' BUT THERE'S
NO ONE I EVER HEARD OF WHO'S
MANAGED TO PULL IT OFF BUT HER.
THAT GIRL IS NOT OF THIS WORLD.
- ( cars approaching )
- SOMEBODY'S BLOWIN' DOWN
THE ROAD FAST.
- YEAH, YOU AIN'T JOKIN'.
THAT'S SOME SERIOUS SQUEALIN'.
RIGHT THERE.
THE SIL-EIGHTY!
IT'S MAKO AND SAYUKI!
THAT DUDE IN THE WHITE CAR.
WHO'S HE?
NOBODY TOLD ME THERE WAS
A RACE TONIGHT!
- ( all exclaim )
- Boy 1: AN EIGHT-SIX?
- NO CARS AHEAD. SHOW THIS
LOSER WHAT YOU CAN DO!
GO!
- All: THEY'RE GOING
INTO THE TURN!
THAT DUMBASS JUST FLEW
INTO THE CORNER
AT THE SAME SPEED AS MAKO!
WHAT THE HELL IS HE THINKIN'?
DOESN'T HE REALIZE THIS IS ONE
OF THE MEANEST CORNERS
ON THE PLANET?
- JUST BEING DUMB ENOUGH
TO FOLLOW HER ALL OUT
ISN'T ENOUGH
TO GET HIM THROUGH THIS ALIVE!
- Sayuki: DAMN, HE'S GOT GUTS.
FOLLOWING MAKO
INTO THE CORNER LIKE THAT?
I WONDER IF HE EVEN
REALIZES THAT AT THIS SPEED
THERE'S NO TURNING BACK NOW.
THERE'S A HARSH EXIT
COMING UP AT C-121.
IT'S NARROWER THAN
MOST PEOPLE EXPECT.
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE COULD BE
A FEW GOOD LINES TO TAKE
BUT THERE'S ONLY ONE
THAT'S PERFECT.
WELL, KID. IT'S YOUR
FIRST TIME ON USUI.
CAN YOU FIND IT?
THAT DID NOT JUST HAPPEN.
- THE NEW GUY
CLEARED THE TURN.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
- WHO IS DRIVING
THAT EIGHT-SIX?
- YOU DON'T THINK IT'S ACTUALLY
THE FAMOUS EIGHT-SIX
FROM MOUNT AKINA WE KEEP
HEARING ABOUT, DO YOU?
- DUDE, I'VE TOTALLY
GOT THE CHILLS.
- THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
FOUR-WHEEL DRIFT AT FULL SPEED
IS RANKED AS ULTRA D DIFFICULTY.
EVEN MAKO MISSED THE PERFECT
LINE BY THREE INCHES
AND SHE KNOWS THIS COURSE
BETTER THAN ANYONE.
HOW WAS THIS GUY ABLE TO HIT
IT RIGHT ON THE MONEY?
I DON'T THINK WE
CAN WIN THIS ONE.
WE'RE UP AGAINST A MONSTER
THAT OUTCLASSES US IN EVERY WAY.
MAKO, YOU'VE GOTTA CHILL!
YOU CAN'T SWING THE CAR
THAT MUCH THROUGH HERE!
- YOU COULDN'T HAVE TOLD ME THAT
A LITTLE SOONER! THANKS A LOT!
FOCUS ON WHAT WE'RE DOING.
WHAT'S YOUR DEAL?
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU AT ALL!
- I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU CAN'T SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE MAKO.
WE HAVE TOTALLY UNDERESTIMATED
THIS EIGHT-SIX.
HE'S OUT OF OUR LEAGUE
BY A FREAKIN' LIGHT YEAR.
WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- WHERE'S YOUR ATTITUDE?
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT
USUAL STUBBORN BITCHINESS?
THIS THING ISN'T OVER YET
AND YOU'RE GIVING UP!
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA!
- I JUST DON'T SEE THE POINT
IF WE CAN'T WIN.
- WHATEVER. I GUESS I DIDN'T
REALIZE I'D BEEN RIDING
WITH A QUITTER ALL THIS TIME.
I'LL HAVE TO DO THIS MYSELF.
WE ALREADY KNEW WHAT
A BADASS THIS GUY WAS
BEFORE WE WENT INTO THIS RACE.
BUT SINCE THIS IS GONNA BE
MY LAST ONE,
WE ARE NOT GONNA
WALK AWAY WONDERING
IF WE REALLY GAVE IT
EVERYTHING WE HAD!
WHAT IS IT? YOU SCARED?
YOU'RE FREAKIN' USELESS!
I SWEAR!
NOTHING BUT A SACK
OF DEAD WEIGHT RIDING SHOTGUN!
-HUH? DEAD WEIGHT?
- YOU HEARD ME! YOU'RE SCREWING
UP THE POWER TO WEIGHT RATIO!
- SHE CAN TURN INTO A REAL
HARDASS BEHIND THE WHEEL.
I AM NOT DEAD WEIGHT, YOU BITCH!
I'M HOT! I'M NOT FAT!
I GOT A KILLER BODY!
- FORTY-NINE KILOGRAMS
OF EXTRA WEIGHT.
- I WEIGH FORTY-SEVEN, DAMMIT!
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE HERE
WITH SELF-RESPECT.
READY FOR THIS MAKO? TIME TO
PUT OUR LIVES ON THE LINE.
- WELL, WELCOME BACK
TO THE PARTY.
- LISTEN, ON THIS NEXT ONE,
ENTER THE TURN SO THAT YOU
ALMOST SCRAPE THE INSIDE WALL.
- OKAY. I'M ALL OVER IT.
- ( Japanese song playing )
- SHE'S NOT HALF BAD.
I'VE GOTTEN BETTER
JUST BY CHASING HER,
EVEN IF I HAVE BEEN RECKLESS.
I THINK I'M FINALLY GETTING
A FEEL FOR THE RHYTHM.
I'M IN SYNCH.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
NOT MANY CORNERS LEFT
IN THIS RUN.
I JUST GOTTA ATTACK EACH ONE
AS HARD AS I POSSIBLY CAN.
I WANNA WALK AWAY FROM THIS
WITH NO REGRETS.
MY PRIDE AS USUI'S FASTEST
IS ON THE LINE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Announcer: BUNTA, DO YOU
HONESTLY THINK TAKUMI
HOLDS A CHANCE AGAINST
THE SIL-EIGHTY?
- Bunta: I DUNNO.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU D...
- I SELL TOFU.
I DON'T PREDICT THE FUTURE.
- WHAT IF I BOUGHT
SOME GOONMO AND ATSO...
- I'VE REALLY WORKED UP
THAT EIGHT-SIX.
NO ONE CAN TOUCH IT
ON A DOWNHILL.
COURSE, IT'S ULTIMATELY
IN THE HANDS OF THE DRIVER.
GUESS WE'LL JUST SEE NEXT TIME.
- WHAT IF I BOUGHT SOME
MOMEN AND SOME KINUGOSHI, TOO?
- NEXT ON INITIAL D,
"SUPER DRIFT."
IT'S A MUST-SEE EPISODE.
- DON'T MISS IT!