- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- Iketani: COME ON, TAKUMI.
THERE'S NOT A CHANCE
I COULD BRING THIS UP
IN FRONT OF ANY
OF THE OTHER FELLAS.
BUT I KNEW IF I SAT DOWN
AND EXPLAINED IT TO YOU
THAT YOU'D UNDERSTAND
WHERE I'M COMING FROM.
- YEAH. BUT I DON'T
HAVE TO LIKE IT.
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT CHICK
BUGS ME.
- I KNOW. BUT DON'T BE ANGRY
AT MAKO FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT SHE'S LIKE.
- I JUST DON'T KNOW WHY YOU
THINK YOU HAVE TO DEFEND HER.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
OWE HER ANYTHING.
SHE'S NOT YOUR GIRLFRIEND
IS SHE?
- I'M BEGGING YOU.
PLEASE DO THIS!
- Itsuki: SO HEY, TAKUMI.
I KNOW YOU HAVEN'T DRIVEN
ANY OTHER PASSES BESIDES AKINA,
BUT I'M CURIOUS WHAT YOU
THOUGHT OF THIS ONE HERE?
SO TELL ME, COULD
YOU RACE HERE OR WHAT?
- I AM TELLING YOU, I DON'T
KNOW, I'D HAVE TO TRY IT FIRST.
FINE, YOU WIN.
I'LL RACE HER.
- YOU WILL? DUDE,
YOU'RE THE GREATEST!
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU AND
HER GOT GOING ON THE SIDE,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU
EXPECT TO GET OUT OF THIS,
BUT IT BETTER BE
WORTH MY EFFORT.
- OH, IT IS.
THEN I'LL GO OUT TO USUI.
AND I'LL TAKE THE EIGHT-SIX.
- YOU GOTTA BE MESSING
WITH MY HEAD, KENJI!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT TAKUMI
WOULD HAVE AGREED TO RACE
AGAINST USUI'S SIL-EIGHTY!
THAT'S THE DEFINITION OF CRAZY!
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- IT ISN'T LIKE HIM TO RUN OFF
TO ANOTHER PASS
AND HAVE A THROW-DOWN
WITH THE LOCALS THERE.
HE'S MORE OF A HOMEBODY.
YOU HEAR ANYTHING
ABOUT HOW IKETANI
MIGHT'VE TALKED HIM
INTO DOING IT?
- BEATS THE LIVING'
CRAP OUTTA ME.
IKETANI WON'T GO INTO
ANY DETAIL ABOUT IT,
SO I'VE BEEN JUST LEFT TO
MY IMAGINATION.
YOU AND I TALKED ABOUT THIS
BEFORE THOUGH.
REMEMBER WHAT WE SAID
WOULD PROBABLY HAPPEN
IF TAKUMI RACED AT ANOTHER PASS?
- YEAH.
- MAYBE IKETANI'S WANTING TO
SEE THAT BUSINESS GO DOWN.
CURIOSITY GOT THE BEST OF HIM.
- BUT HE DOESN'T HAVE TO
RACE THE SIL-EIGHTY
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
THAT'S NUTS. HE NEEDS
TO WORK UP TO HER.
- TAKUMI'S RACING
IN USUI, IS HE?
- YEAH, IT'S CRAZY, RIGHT?
SO. THIS SIL-EIGHTY'S
GOOD ENOUGH
TO TAKE HIM ON HEAD TO HEAD?
- SHE'S BETTER THAN GOOD,
SHE'S A ROAD WARRIOR, MAN!
I WATCHED HER DRIFT
LEFT AND RIGHT,
FAKE MOVES ON A NARROW COURSE.
I THINK HE'S BIT OFF MORE THAN
HE CAN CHEW THIS TIME.
TAKUMI WAS WITH US. HE SAW
HER BLISTER UP THOSE TIRES.
HE KNOWS JUST HOW MUCH
OF A MONSTER SHE IS.
- SO WHAT?
HE'LL DESTROY THIS CHICK!
- I ENVY YOUR SIMPLE MIND.
GOT THE MEMORY OF A GOLDFISH.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
THAT GAS PUMPER
TOLD US NO LOCAL HAD
EVER BEATEN HER?
- MAYBE THAT'S WHY THIS TIME.
IT ISN'T ABOUT WINNING
OR LOSING TO TAKUMI.
MAYBE IT'S SOMETHING MORE.
- WHAT COULD POSSIBLY BE
MORE IMPORTANT THAN WINNING?
- DAMMIT. OUT OF SMOKES
AGAIN. GUESS IT'S TIME
TO TAKE THE EIGHT-SIX
OUT FOR A LITTLE SPIN.
WHAT IN THE HOLY HELL?
MY EIGHT-SIX HAS BEEN
TURNED INTO AN EIGHT-FIVE.
- ( chuckling ) YOUR DAD MUST BE
SOILING HIS DRAWERS RIGHT NOW.
HIS EIGHT-SIX MAGICALLY
TRANSFORMING INTO AN EIGHT-FIVE.
I BET IT BLEW
HIS FREAKING MIND!
- Kenji: HEY, IKETANI. I KINDA
GOTTA ASK YOU A QUESTION.
- WHAT IS IT?
I JUST... I WAS WONDERING
WHICH SIDE OF THE RACE
YOU WERE FALLING ON.
- WHAT DO YOU
MEAN, WHICH SIDE?
I'M NOT MAKING
THOSE KINDS OF CALLS.
ALL I DID WAS COORDINATE
THE RACE. OKAY?
- AM I REALLY
SUPPOSED TO BELIEVE THAT?
WHAT ABOUT TAKUMI?
ISN'T HE YOUR FRIEND FIRST?
'CAUSE IF YOU ASK
ME IT KINDA SEEMS LIKE
YOU'RE THROWING HIM
ON THE COALS
JUST TO LOOK GOOD TO THIS
CHICK YOU'RE DIGGING ON.
- DUDE,
THAT'S A LOAD OF CRAP.
- OH, YOU THINK SO?
THEN YOU MUST ALSO THINK
THAT TAKUMI ACTUALLY HAS
A CHANCE OF WINNING THIS RACE
INSTEAD OF LEAVING WITH A
MARK IN THE LOSS COLUMN.
DOESN'T SOUND LIKE YOU GOT
MUCH TO SAY ABOUT THAT PAL.
TOO CLOSE TO HOME?
UH... I...
HE DOESN'T HAVE A PRAYER. THE
ONLY COURSE HE KNOWS IS AKINA.
AND USUI IS AN ALMOST
IMPOSSIBLE COURSE
FOR PEOPLE WHO'VE DRIVEN
IT FOR YEARS,
SO YOU CAN FORGET
ABOUT FIRST TIMERS.
I KNOW HE'S UNREAL WITH
HIS TECHNIQUE, BUT COME ON,
THAT'S NOT THE ANSWER TO
EVERY WIN ON EVERY COURSE
IN THE COUNTRY IS IT?
HE'S NEVER EVEN DRIVEN
ON THIS PASS, DUDE.
TAKUMI'S NOT A SUPERHERO,
AND WITHOUT A SINGLE PRACTICE.
THERE'S NO CHANCE HE'LL BE
ABLE TO HANDLE THIS COURSE.
EVEN IN YOUR LITTLE LOVE FOG,
YOU HAD TO HAVE PUT
THAT TOGETHER.
- BUT. I CAN'T...
- I GET IT. DUDES LOSE
IT WHEN THEY FIND A CHICK
THEY DIG LIKE THIS.
- I WANT MY LAST RACE
TO BE SPECIAL,
SOMETHING
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
I WANNA RACE THE EIGHT-SIX
HERE ON MY HOME TURF.
- YOU LIKE HER. FINE.
BUT DON'T SELL OUT
YOUR FRIENDS FOR A GIRL.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
HOW TAKUMI CAME TO YOUR RESCUE
AND DEFENDED OUR COURSE?
IT'S CAUSE OF THAT HE GOT TO
BE THE PRIDE OF MOUNT AKINA.
YOU BETTER CUT OUT
THIS BS, CAUSE...
MAN, IF YOU DON'T,
THIS FRIENDSHIP IS OVER.
- I KNOW IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, KENJI.
- I'M SORRY. I KEEP THINGS
BOTTLED UP SOMETIMES.
I SHOULD HAVE BROUGHT ALL OF
THIS TO YOU, LIKE, FOREVER AGO,
I REALIZE THAT. BUT ANYWAY,
I JUST NEEDED TO LET YOU KNOW.
- YEAH, I STILL
DON'T GET IT, MAKO.
WHY YOU WOULD EVER
QUIT RACING?
- IT WAS FUN.
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO WHEN WE
FIRST STARTED RACING TOGETHER
I HAD A REALLY AMAZING TIME.
BACK WHEN ALL WE EVER WANTED
WAS TO BE THE FASTEST RACERS
IN THIS AREA.
- BUT YOU ARE STILL HAVING FUN.
YOU ARE, AREN'T YOU?
- I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT.
I'M NOT AS INTO THIS AS I USED
TO BE. I DON'T KNOW WHY.
WISH I DID.
I GUESS... I GUESS I FEEL LIKE
IT'S TIME FOR ME TO MOVE ON.
SOMETHING TELLS ME
THAT I'VE DONE ENOUGH.
- YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
SORRY, BUT I CAN'T GET ON BOARD
WITH THIS WHOLE
QUITTING BUSINESS.
- I WANNA HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
NOTHING SPECIAL, JUST A NORMAL
RELATIONSHIP, YOU KNOW?
- YOU CAN RACE
AND HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
IT'S NOT SOME GREAT
UNACHIEVABLE GOAL.
- NO, I CAN'T. I COULD TRY
ALL DAY BUT I DON'T THINK
I COULD MAKE YOU UNDERSTAND.
- OKAY. THIS ISN'T SOME
HYPOTHETICAL GUY, IS IT?
- ( yawning )
- ( gasps )
IF I'M BEING HONEST WITH YOU.
I'VE HAD SOMEONE IN MIND
FOR A WHILE NOW.
- OH? YOU DON'T SAY.
YOU'RE JUST SO GOOD
AT KEEPING SECRETS
I NEVER WOULD HAVE KNOWN.
- WELL, UH.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT YOU COULD
HAVE KNOWN ABOUT THIS GUY.
HE'S NOT EXACTLY
FROM AROUND HERE.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY I'VE BEEN
ADMIRING HIM FROM AFAR.
- OH, MAKO. THIS INNOCENT
LITTLE GIRL ROUTINE OF YOURS
IS GETTING KINDA OLD.
YOU'RE FREAKING 20.
SLUT IT UP SOME.
- BUT THAT ISN'T ME.
I LIKE THE WAY I AM.
I DON'T NEED THE INTIMACY
LIKE YOU DO.
- YOU SHOULD BE REALISTIC.
OR AT LEAST A LOT MORE
REALISTIC THAN THAT.
- YOU AND I HAVE SPENT
THE LAST TWO YEARS TOGETHER
PERFECTING AND HONING
OUR TECHNIQUE,
IT'S MEANT A LOT TO ME.
I THINK WE OWE OURSELVES ONE
LAST RACE BEFORE IT'S OVER.
- YOU MEAN LIKE A FINAL EXAM?
SOUNDS LIKE A DECENT
ENOUGH PLAN TO ME.
AS LONG AS WE GO UP
AGAINST A WORTHY OPPONENT.
- HE IS.
- THAT'S FINE. BUT LET ME
TELL YOU SOMETHING, MAKO.
IF WE'RE GONNA BE
RACING AT USUI PASS,
THEN WE HAVE TO WIN.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO WE'RE UP AGAINST.
ANYTHING LESS THAN THAT
IS UNACCEPTABLE. PERIOD.
- I HEAR YA. WE DO THIS,
AND WE DON'T LET
ANYTHING STAND IN OUR WAY.
- EVEN IF WE'RE UP AGAINST
THE EIGHT-SIX.
- RIGHT. ABSOLUTELY.
- IF YOU'RE NOT INTO THIS,
THERE'S NO USE THROWING YOUR
REPUTATION ON THE LINE TO RACE.
IKETANI AND ME WILL LET THEM
KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
- YOU DUDES SHOULD TURN AROUND
AND HEAD BACK.
- GET OUTTA HERE.
I'M SORRY ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
- Kenji: HE'S SERIOUS MAN.
- NOT SO FAST, GUYS. I'M...
I'M NOT GOING BACK.
- ( gasping ) YOU'RE NOT?
- NO, BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO STICK AROUND.
I JUST CAN'T LEAVE
UNTIL I RACE THIS CHICK.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
I CAME OUT HERE TO BEGIN WITH.
- TAKUMI.
- BUT DUDE, YOU SAW
WHAT MAKO IS CAPABLE OF.
SHE'LL SMOKE YOU
ON HER HOME COURSE.
YOU DON'T HAVE A CHANCE.
LOOK, YOU SHOULD FACE IT,
BRO. SHE'S BETTER THAN YOU.
- YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
I ALSO KNOW THIS RACE
ISN'T ABOUT WINNING
OR LOSING ANYMORE.
- HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT? YOU
DRIVE THE EIGHT-SIX OF AKINA!
YOU'RE FAMOUS NOW! HAVE
SOME PRIDE FOR GOD'S SAKE.
THIS IS YOUR LEGEND
ON THE LINE.
- AND I'M SUPPOSED TO CARE
WHAT A BUNCH OF STRANGERS
THINK ABOUT ME?
LOOK, I WON A FEW RACES.
LOCAL RACES.
THEN THE RUMORS
FLEW AROUND LIKE CRAZY,
MADE ME SOUND LIKE I WAS A
BIGGER DEAL THAN I REALLY AM.
I THINK I'D FEEL A LOT
BETTER ABOUT DRIVING
IF PEOPLE WOULD STOP TALKING
ABOUT ME ALL THE TIME.
- FOR REAL?
- YOU SERIOUS?
I'M GONNA DO THIS.
I WANNA ATTACK A NEW PASS.
TRY SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
CHALLENGE MYSELF.
♪ - I CAN EXPRESS
MY BEST DESIRE! ♪
- I'M SORRY I WAS SUCH A JERK
TO YOU EARLIER.
HONESTLY HOW COULD WE
TALK HIM OUT OF ANYTHING
AFTER A SPEECH LIKE THAT?
- NO KIDDING.
- HE'S ONE STRANGE DUDE. NOBODY
ELSE LIKE HIM, THAT'S FOR SURE.
I CAN'T WRAP MY HEAD
AROUND THE GUY.
HARD TO TELL IF HE'S GOT A GIFT
OR HE'S JUST GOT A SCREW LOOSE.
♪ - I REALIZE HOW MUCH I CARE ♪
♪ BABY RECALL ALL THE TIME
YOU LEAVE MY HEART ♪
♪ I FEEL LONELY NIGHT AND DAY ♪
♪ I WANT TO BELONG
TO YOUR LITTLE PARADISE ♪
♪ AND BE YOUR LUCKY ANGEL
DARLING ♪
- Sayuki: TIRES LOOK GOOD.
PRESSURE SEEMS PERFECT
FOR THIS ROAD.
ALL THE ADJUSTMENTS
ARE LOCKED DOWN,
AND WE'RE READY TO ROLL
OUT FOR ONE LAST WIN.
- AS LONG AS YOU THINK
WE'RE READY, SAYUKI.
- LOOK, I KNOW YOU KNOW THIS,
BUT IN THIS KIND OF RACE,
YOU NEED TO AVOID
WIDE-ANGLE DRIFTS
AS MUCH AS HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
AND IT'S VITAL TO OUR SURVIVAL
THAT YOU KNOW WHEN TO DRIFT
AND WHEN NOT TO DRIFT.
I DON'T NEED TO REMIND YOU
ABOUT USUI'S CONTINUOUS TURNS.
THEY CAN THROW
YOU OFF SOMETIMES.
I'LL BE RIGHT BESIDE YOU.
JUST DRIVE LIKE USUAL
AND THIS PUNK
DOESN'T HAVE A PRAYER.
WE ARE NOT ABOUT TO LOSE
ON OUR OWN PASS.
- I'VE NEVER LET YOU DOWN
BEFORE AND I DON'T PLAN TO NOW.
LET'S SHOW THESE BOYS A
RACE LIKE THEY'VE NEVER SEEN.
- I'M READY TO DO THIS. I GET
EXCITED, BUT NEVER LIKE THIS.
- I'M EXCITED TOO.
BUT MOSTLY 'CAUSE I WANNA
SEE IF THIS GUY'S AS GOOD
AS EVERYONE SAYS HE IS.
♪ - UP IN A SKY A MORNING STAR ♪
♪ - I CAN EXPRESS
MY BEST DESIRE! ♪
- INITIAL D!
- INITIAL D.
- WHAT'RE YOU THINKING?
DO YOU HAVE A GAME PLAN ON
HOW TO WIN THE RACE?
LET ME IN ON THE INNER WORKINGS
OF THAT WINNING BRAIN.
- I DON'T REALLY HAVE A PLAN.
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, DUDE?
CAN'T YOU THINK OF SOMETHING?
I DON'T WANNA SEE YOU
EAT ASPHALT OUT THERE TONIGHT.
TALK ABOUT EMBARRASSING.
HEY, I GOT A GREAT IDEA.
USUI PASS IS NARROW, RIGHT?
AND THERE AREN'T ANY
STRAIGHT LINES. SO THEN...
YOU JUST BLOW PAST HER,
AND STAY THERE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THEN YOU JUST BLOCK THE COW
THE REST OF THE WAY,
HOLD YOUR POSITION UNTIL
YOU GET TO THE FINISH LINE,
AND BOOM, YOU WIN.
- I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT.
IT WOULDN'T BE A FAIR RACE.
YOU KNOW THAT, MAN.
- OKAY. BUT IF YOU LET HER GET
AHEAD OF YOU THIS THING'S OVER.
- DUDE, I KNOW.
- ( groaning ) LOOK, WE NEED TO
COME UP WITH A PLAN TO WIN.
IT'S NOT HOPELESS, HER CAR'S GOT
FOUR WHEELS JUST LIKE YOURS.
- Sayuki: ( laughing )
YOU'RE SCREWING WITH ME RIGHT?
THIS KID IS THE DRIVER
OF MOUNT AKINA'S
UBER FAMOUS, BIG, BAD EIGHT-SIX?
IS THIS LIKE A JOKE? HOW OLD
ARE YOU, LIKE SIX AND A HALF?
- IF YOU HAVE TO KNOW,
I'M EIGHTEEN.
- WHAT? COME ON.
HE'S IN HIGH SCHOOL.
- IT'S A TWO YEAR DIFFERENCE,
NOT LIKE THEY COULD BABYSIT HIM.
- AND BESIDES, THEY'RE CHICKS.
- NOW, WE REALLY CAN'T
LET HIM WIN.
TONIGHT THIS GUY IS
GOING HOME WITH JACK SQUAT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
PARAMETERS OF THE RACE.
ON THIS COURSE IT'S A
BAD IDEA FOR US TO START
SIDE-BY-SIDE OFF THE LINE
'CAUSE WHOEVER HAS A BETTER
START HAS THE CLEAR ADVANTAGE.
AND I DON'T WANNA ARGUE UNTIL
DAWN ONCE THE RACE IS CLOSED OUT
OR HAVE A STUPID REMATCH
BECAUSE SOMEONE THINKS
SOMEONE ELSE CHEATED
OR JUMPED THE GUN.
- CRAP, THERE GOES MY PLAN.
- THEN. WHAT DO WE DO?
- HOW ABOUT WE RUN A CAT AND
MOUSE RACE DOWN THE MOUNTAIN?
THEY'RE FUN.
IT'S BASICALLY A CHASE.
IF THE MOUSE GETS AWAY,
THE RACE IS OVER.
IF NOT, WE KEEP SWITCHING
POSITIONS UNTIL SOMEONE WINS.
THINK OF IT AS A 'SUDDEN DEATH,
DEATH MATCH.' COOL?
- YEAH, THAT'S OKAY WITH ME.
- SINCE WE'RE THE LOCALS HERE,
WE'RE GONNA LET YOU FELLAS
DECIDE WHETHER YOU WANT TO BE
THE CAT OR THE
MOUSE FIRST, OKAY?
JUST MAKE THE CALL,
AND WE'LL GO.
- HUH.
WITH THIS KINDA SETUP,
I'M THINKING IT'LL BE BEST
IF YOU GO IN FRONT FIRST.
- HE'S RIGHT. 'CAUSE THERE'S
NO WAY THIS IS GONNA END
WITH JUST ONE RACE.
THAT WAY YOU AT LEAST
GET IN ONE PRACTICE RUN.
- THAT AND IT'S PROBABLY BETTER
TO LOSE IN THE SECOND RACE.
- I'LL BET YOU A TANK OF GAS
HE CHOOSES TO GO IN FRONT
ON THE FIRST RUN.
- ALL THAT MEANS IS THAT I'M
GONNA WIN THE SECOND RACE.
- I APPRECIATE THE ADVICE GUYS.
I HATE TO JUST IGNORE IT.
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
DOES MAKE SENSE.
BUT I DON'T THINK I
WANNA RUN IT LIKE THAT.
- I KNOW YOU'RE SLOW,
BUT THAT'S INSANE!
- I THINK I WANNA CHASE HER
ON THE FIRST RUN.
- Both: WHAT?
- YOU NEED TO THINK
THIS OVER, TAKUMI.
- SORRY, BUT THIS IS MY RACE
SO I'M GONNA RUN IT MY WAY.
- DUDE, HOLD UP.
- I'VE DECIDED TO CHASE FIRST.
- ( gasping )
YOU'RE GONNA WHAT NOW?
IS HE TRYING TO INSULT US
OR IS HE JUST PLAIN STUPID?
- DON'T WORRY.
I'LL STILL SMOKE HIM.
- ( phone ringing )
- ( sighing ) OF COURSE.
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF ME
COOKING DINNER.
HELLO. FUJIWARA TOFU SHOP.
- Yuuichi: HEY, BUNTA?
- IT'S YOU. I'M BUSY,
SO, JUST MAKE IT SNAPPY.
WHAT DO YOU NEED, PAL?
- LISTEN, I THOUGHT I SHOULD
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IT'S ABOUT TAKUMI'S RACING.
- ARE WE GONNA LIGHT
THIS FUSE? LET'S GO!
- SO THE KID WENT UP TO USUI
FOR ANOTHER RACE. SO WHAT?
- SO WHAT? GREAT. THAT'S ALL YOU
CAN THINK TO SAY IS SO WHAT?
AREN'T YOU WORRIED
ABOUT YOUR KID?
- NOT REALLY. I MEAN,
I THINK I RAISED HIM RIGHT.
- WE'LL KEEP IT PRETTY
SLOW AT FIRST
SO JUST STAY BEHIND US, OKAY?
AFTER THAT FIRST TURN, THOUGH,
HOLD ON TO YOUR PANTYHOSE,
'CAUSE WE'LL KICK IT UP
TO FULL THROTTLE.
THAT'LL BE WHERE
WE START THE RACE.
- SO THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE TO SAY?
THAT'S REALLY IT?
- YEAH, THAT'S IT. NOW, I'M
BUSY, SO IF YOU DON'T MIND,
STOP CALLING ME
ABOUT THIS NONSENSE.
- BUNTA? WHAT THE HELL?
- TAKUMI, I WAS AN IDIOT
TO ASK YOU TO DO THIS.
I REALIZE THAT NOW.
AND I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE HERE.
SO, LOOK, I KNOW THE ONLY
REASON YOU AGREED TO THIS
IS TO SAVE MY EGO.
I'M REGRETTING IT NOW
MORE THAN YOU COULD EVEN KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE SUCH A JACKASS.
YOU'RE BEST RACER AKINA HAS,
MAYBE EVER.
YOU'RE THE PRIDE OF OUR REGION.
( sniffling ) IT WAS SUCH A HUGE
MISTAKE GETTING YOU OUT HERE.
I... I JUST DON'T WANT
TO SEE YOU LOSE
BECAUSE OF MY STUPIDITY.
- QUIT SAYING HE'S GONNA LOSE!
- SO WHAT'S IT LIKE LIVING
IN COMPLETE DENIAL?
- IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
- YOU WUSS.
- IKETANI. YOU CAN QUIT
FREAKING OUT, OKAY?
I DECIDED TO BE THE CAT ON
THE FIRST RUN FOR A REASON.
I CAN'T SAY FOR SURE IF
I'M GONNA WIN THIS THING,
BUT I SURE AS ALL HELL DIDN'T
COME ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
TO LOSE. RIGHT?
- DO YOU HAVE
A PLAN OF ATTACK?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WHEN IT STARTS?
- I WOULDN'T CALL IT
A PLAN, EXACTLY.
BUT SOMETHING'S BOUNCING AROUND
IN MY HEAD. I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS IT'S MORE
LIKE AN INSPIRATION.
- SHOOT, MAN, FILL US IN.
WHAT IS IT? HUH? TELL US!
- YEAH, IT SOUNDS AWESOME.
- ALL I KNOW IS THAT IT DOESN'T
MATTER HOW FAST THIS CHICK IS,
IT'S NOT LIKE HER CAR
CAN FLY OR ANYTHING.
SO IT'S AN EVEN PLAYING FIELD.
SHE'S ON FOUR WHEELS
JUST LIKE ME.
- ( all gasp )
THAT SAID. I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO TURN THESE CORNERS
AS FAST AND AS GOOD AS SHE CAN.
ESPECIALLY IF I KEEP
MY EYE ON HER MOVES.
HEY, SOUNDS LIKE I DO
HAVE A PLAN?
- HELL, YEAH! SWEET!
- SURE. I GUESS YOU HAVE
A POINT IN THEORY.
- YEAH, 'IN THEORY'
BUT IT'S CRAZY.
- Sayuki: LET'S ROLL OUT!
♪ LOVE IS IN DANGER ♪
- ( engines revving )
OKAY, ARE YOU READY? I WANT
THIS GUY KNOCKED OFF FAST.
- NO PROBLEM WITH THAT.
NOW GET READY FOR A BATTLE
LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN.
♪ LOVE IS IN DANGER ♪
♪ I DON'T WANNA HURT YOU ♪
♪ BUT I NEED TO TALK ♪
♪ TO TALK ABOUT OUR LOVE ♪
♪ I DON'T WANNA HURT YOU ♪
♪ BUT I NEED TO WALK ♪
♪ WALK AWAY, WALK FAR AWAY
FROM YOU AND I ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I'D LIKE TO FIGHT ♪
♪ TO GIVE OUR LOVE
ANOTHER CHANCE ♪
♪ A NEW ROMANCE ♪
- THEY HAVEN'T EVEN
MADE THE CORNER
AND THEY'RE ALREADY AT
FULL THROTTLE.
- TAKUMI'S FIRST AWAY RACE,
AND WE'RE ACTUALLY GETTING
TO WATCH THE WHOLE THING
FROM THE TOP.
- THIS ROCKS.
EVEN THOUGH THIS IS THE FIRST
BATTLE WE'VE EVER SEEN
WHERE TAKUMI'S BEEN
AT A SERIOUS DISADVANTAGE.
- NO FEAR. NOT ME. 'CAUSE
I KNOW HE'S GONNA WIN!
- ( laughing )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sayuki: COME ON, MAKO,
WE'RE STREET RACERS
AND THIS IS OUR TURF.
YOU KNOW WE CAN'T
LOSE HERE.
- Mako: YEAH, I KNOW.
- Announcer: HEY, SAYUKI.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
ONCE MAKO QUITS RACING?
- Sayuki: WELL,
I'M NOT QUITTING!
- Mako: SAYUKI.
- Announcer: SO, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO RETIRE?
- Sayuki: I'LL JUST BE
RACING AFTER MEN.
- Announcer: HUH?
- Sayuki: I MEAN, WHERE
ARE ALL THE GOOD MEN ANYWAY,
HUH? WHERE ARE THEY?
- Mako: SEE YOU LATER, SAYUKI.
- Announcer: NEXT ON INITIAL D,
HOT WINDS AND FURIOUS DRIVING!
- Sayuki: DON'T MISS IT!