- ( engine starting )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ INFORMATION! ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ MONEY CAN'T BUY MY LOVE! ♪
♪ IN THE MIDNIGHT DREAM! ♪
♪ NOW WE GOT IT! ♪
♪ SO LET'S GET MOVE! ♪
- ♪ AROUND THE WORLD! ♪
- ♪ TRIP TO THE WORLD ♪
♪ YO, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ SO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD ♪
♪ THAT'S OUR WORLD! ♪
- ( exclaims )
- ( tires screeching )
- THAT WAS CLOSE.
- ( laughing )
- CAN'T BELIEVE THAT GUY.
BASTARD HIT ME ON PURPOSE.
- ♪ I WANNA DANCE ♪
♪ I WANNA DANCE ♪
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THAT!
- I WONDER IF ANY OF
THESE LOSERS FROM AKINA
CAN KEEP UP WITH ME.
- ( tires screeching )
- HE'S NUTS.
- ♪ DEEP INSIDE THE BEATING
GOES LOUDER ♪
GOTTA CATCH THIS GUY.
♪ FEEL ALIVE I'M FEELING
THE POWER ♪
♪ GETTING HOT THE PHONES ♪
♪ GET UP TONIGHT ♪
♪ MAKE UP YOUR LIFE
AND BRING IT ON ♪
♪ SINCE THE LIGHT
HAS GONE BABY ♪
♪ NO WAY TO HIDE ♪
♪ TODAY YOU'LL FIND THE ANSWER
IN YOUR HEART ♪
♪ DANCING WE WANNA FEEL
THE LIGHT IS FLASHING ♪
♪ I SEND THE POWER TO MYSELF ♪
♪ DANCING WE GOTTA DANCE
UNTIL THE MORNING ♪
- HE'S GOT SOME FURIOUS
SPEED IN THAT RIDE.
WHY'S HE FIRING HIS BRAKES?
NO WAY HE SHOULD BE HITTIN' 'EM
WHILE HE'S CORNERING AT
THAT SPEED. DAMN!
I CAN'T KEEP UP WITH THIS GUY.
HIS ENDURANCE IS
OUTTA MY LEAGUE.
I HATE TO SAY IT BUT
THAT EG-SIX MAY BE FASTER
THAN TAKUMI'S RIDE.
BUT WHO'S BEHIND THE WHEEL?
- ( tires screeching )
- ( cars honking )
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- YEAH. IT REALLY TICKED ME OFF,
Y'KNOW?
- SO, YOU'RE TELLING ME HE WAS
BRAKING WHILE HE WAS CORNERING.
AND HE WAS GOING EVEN FASTER
THAN YOU WERE?
- I HAVEN'T SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE IT BEFORE.
NOT IN THE MAGAZINES,
VIDEOS, NOWHERE.
- YOU HADN'T SEEN THAT?
EVERYBODY DOES IT,
HOW CAN YOU NOT HAVE
SEEN THAT, DUDE?
I DON'T THINK I'VE DRIVEN
A DAY SINCE I'VE HAD MY LICENSE
WHERE I DIDN'T PUMP
THE BRAKE IN A CORNER.
- ( mimics driving noises )
UH-OH, I'M GOIN' TOO FAST HERE,
BETTER HIT THAT BRAKE.
AH, AH. THERE WE GO.
- NOT DRIVING SCHOOL BRAKING
TECHNIQUES, YOU MORON.
THIS EG-SIX CLEARED THOSE
CORNERS AT SPEEDS
YOU HAVEN'T RUN IN ANY CAR
THAT YOU'VE EVER BEEN
BEHIND THE WHEEL OF.
- SOMEONE WANNA TELL ME
WHAT AN EG-SIX IS?
- A HONDA CIVIC. GET WITH IT.
- OKAY.
SO WHY DON'T YOU GUYS JUST
CALL THE THING A HONDA CIVIC.
- WAKE UP, BRO. THE CIVIC IS
QUITE THE POPULAR RIDE
AMONG STREET RACERS, EVEN
THOUGH IT'S AN FF.
IT'S A NON-TURBO ONE POINT SIX
LITER LIKE YOUR EIGHT-SIX,
BUT ITS V-TEC ENGINE
HAS A BOATLOAD MORE POWER.
KINDA LIKE COMPARING
A FREIGHT TRAIN TO,
WELL TO A LESS POWERFUL TRAIN.
IT'S BEEN THE CHIEF
RIVAL OF THE TRUENO
AND THE LEVIN FOR YEARS NOW.
TALK ABOUT YOUR
GRUDGE MATCHES.
YOU DRIVE AN EIGHT-SIX,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE CIVIC, YOU SHOULD
KNOW IT ALREADY!
I MAY ONLY DRIVE A LOWLY LEVIN,
BUT I REFUSE TO LET A CIVIC
GET PAST ME!
( laughs )
- MY POINT IS, THE
SPEED IT HAD GOING
INTO THAT CORNER WAS RIDICULOUS.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
THEN IT BRAKED.
THE WHOLE INCIDENT THREW ME OFF.
- YEAH. THAT'S A MOVE CALLED
LEFT FOOT BRAKING.
IT'S A FAIRLY WELL
KNOWN TECHNIQUE.
- LEFT FOOT BRAKING, REALLY?
- YEAH. YOU DON'T KNOW IT,
'CAUSE IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU
WOULD USUALLY USE IN AN FR.
IT'S WHERE YOU BRAKE WITH THE
LEFT FOOT TO STABILIZE THE CAR
WHILE YOU'RE TRAVELING AT
EXTREMELY HIGH SPEEDS.
WITH AN FF LIKE THE EG-SIX,
YOU NEED YOUR RIGHT FOOT
ON THE GAS PEDAL CONSTANTLY
TO AVOID UNDERSTEERING.
SO YOU BRAKE WITH
YOUR LEFT FOOT
THAT TAKES THE WEIGHT OFF
THE REAR TIRES,
GIVING THE WHOLE BODY
A SHARPER TURN.
HE MUST BE A HIGHLY
EXPERIENCED FF DRIVER
TO TURN THAT TECHNIQUE.
HARDLY SURPRISING
THAT HE'S FAST, TOO.
- FASTER THAN I THOUGHT
ANYONE UP THERE'D BE.
IT BLEW MY MIND.
THE ONLY REASON I DIDN'T
CRASH IS BECAUSE
I JUST PRACTICED SPINNING
WITH THE EMERGENCY BRAKE.
IF IT WASN'T FOR THAT,
HE WOULD'VE PUT ME IN
THE GUARD RAIL.
I TELL YA, MAN, I'M GONNA
MAKE THAT EG-SIX PAY FOR THIS.
- Takumi: HEY, I'M HOME.
- YEAH. OH, SOMEONE CALLED
FOR YOU EARLIER.
- WHO?
- HMM...
- WELL. IT SURE SOUNDED LIKE
A PRETTY GIRL.
SAID SHE'D CALL BACK.
- HOW COULD YOU TELL IF
THIS GIRL WAS PRETTY
JUST BY HEARING HER
VOICE ON THE PHONE?
- I'VE LEARNED A LOT
OVER THE YEARS, BOY.
AND WITH WOMEN,
JUST LIKE WITH CARS,
EVERYTHING COMES DOWN
TO EXPERIENCE AND INTUITION.
BEST OF LUCK WITH
BOTH OF 'EM.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- ( sighs ) I GUESS I OUGHT TO
BE HEADING OFF TO MY MEETING.
- ( phone ringing )
- ( yawning )
- Takumi: FUJIWARA TOFU SHOP.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- Natsuki: TAKUMI? IS THAT YOU?
- YEAH.
- HOPE I DIDN'T WAKE YOU.
REMEMBER THAT LITTLE CHAT YOU
AND I HAD THE OTHER DAY?
- TAKUMI. THIS BETTER BE A
REAL DATE CUZ IF IT ISN'T,
I SWEAR ON MY LIFE,
I'LL STAB YOU WITH A SHOP-VAC,
DO YOU HEAR ME!
SHE'S REALLY BRINGING HER FRIEND
ALONG? AND SHE'S HOT TOO?
- I JUST KNOW NATSUKI SAID
SHE WAS BRINGING A FRIEND.
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST SHUT UP
AND STOP FREAKING YOURSELF OUT.
- WELL, SHE HAD BETTER BE CUTE.
( excitedly )
AND HAVE A REAL HOT BOD.
AND MAYBE SHE'LL FALL IN LOVE
WITH ME! EH? EH?
- LOOK, ALL I KNOW IS IT'S HER
FRIEND FROM JUNIOR HIGH.
THEY GO WAY BACK AND SHE'S NICE.
- I DON'T CARE IF
SHE'S A FREAKIN' SAINT
AS LONG AS SHE'S HOT.
BUT IT'S TOO LATE NOW, AND I
GUESS BEGGARS CAN'T BE CHOOSERS.
PAL 'O MINE.
I'M SO FLATTERED THAT YOU KEPT
YOUR PROMISE TO ME. YOU ROCK.
WHO HAS THE BESTEST BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WIDE WORLD?
I DO, THAT'S WHO!
- SERIOUSLY, BRO,
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
I'LL BE THE BEST RACER
ON ALL OF MOUNT AKINA,
AND I'LL HAVE A BEAUTIFUL GIRL
BY MY SIDE!
( laughs )
( exclaims in horror )
CRAP ON ANYTHING ELSE,
BUT NOT ON MY LEVIN!
AW, YOU STUPID BIRD!
- I KINDA FIGURED THEY WOULD
HAVE BEEN HERE BY NOW.
- Natsuki: HEY!
I HOPE YOU WEREN'T WAITING LONG.
- WHAT'S WITH ALL THE VIOLENCE?
- HI.
- ITSUKI, THIS IS MY FRIEND.
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET SAORI.
SAORI, THIS IS ITSUKI
AND THIS IS TAKUMI.
- WHAT'S UP.
- HEY, HOW'S IT GOIN'?
- ( chuckles ) NOW, THAT'S WHAT
I CALL A WOMAN.
- SO, NATSUKI TELLS ME
YOU'RE A STREET RACER.
- THAT'S RIGHT, I BELONG
TO A TEAM OF RACERS
CALLED THE AKINA SPEED STARS.
WE PRETTY MUCH OWN THESE ROADS.
I'M LIKE THE THIRD OR
FOURTH FASTEST DRIVER
IN THE WHOLE GROUP.
I'M KIND OF A LOCAL
LEGEND, REALLY.
THEY CALL ME "THE
LEVIN OF AKINA."
- THAT'S SO AWESOME!
- WHAT'S A STREET RACER
DO ANYWAY?
- WAIT. WHAT? C'MON, YOU REALLY
DON'T KNOW? A STREET RACER...
- AW, YEAH! THIS CHICK IS WAY
COOLER THAN I THOUGHT SHE'D BE.
- ITSUKI! WATCH OUT!
- ( honking )
- ( screaming )
- ( tires screeching )
- DO YOU WANT ME TO
TAKE THE WHEEL?
- NO, NO, I GOT THIS.
SORRY' BOUT THAT.
JUST SOME BAD STREET RACER
HABITS COMING OUT.
- ARE YOU DOIN' OKAY?
- YEP. I'M JUST PERFECT.
- IT'S JUST THAT RIDING
IN A CAR WITH ITSUKI
CAN BE A LITTLE ROUGH.
- Itsuki: HEY GUYS!
TAKUMI! NATSUKI!
CHECK US OUT!
WHAT DO YA THINK?
- YOU SHOULD COME TAKE
A RIDE WITH US!
- ( laughs )
Y'KNOW. I NEVER WOULD
HAVE EXPECTED IT,
BUT THEY'RE KINDA CUTE TOGETHER.
- YEAH.
- INITIAL D.
- INITIAL D!
- SO, EITHER OF YOU
NEED A RIDE HOME?
- NO THANKS. SAORI AND I
HAVE A LOT TO CATCH UP ON,
SO I THINK WE'RE GONNA WALK
THE REST OF THE WAY.
- BYE, ITSUKI, I HAD A REALLY
GOOD TIME WITH YOU TODAY.
LET'S DO IT AGAIN.
- SEE YA LATER.
- UH HUH.
- WAIT, SAORI.
TALK TO YA SOON! CALL ME!
( chuckling )
- ( engine revving )
- ( Itsuki humming )
( exclaiming excitedly )
- NOT BAD.
- THAT WAS FUN.
- SAORI'S ONE FINE CHICK.
I TELL YA SHE SENT AN
ELECTRIC CURRENT
SURGING THROUGH MY BODY. OH!
( whooping ) WOW! OH!
- DUDE. WOULD YOU MIND ACTUALLY
DRIVING THE CAR?
- CALM DOWN, YA
PANSY. I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW
HOW TO THANK YOU FOR
SUCH A KILLER DAY!
"WE SHOULD DO THIS AGAIN."
THAT'S WHAT SHE SAID.
AND HOPEFULLY WHEN WE DO,
IT'LL JUST BE THE TWO OF US.
- ( gasps ) DUDE, LIGHT!
- ( screaming )
- ( tires screeching )
- ( cars honking )
- ( engine starting )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE I DID THAT.
- ( honking continues )
- ( engine starting )
- Both: THANK YOU
FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- WHAT'S NEXT ON MY AGENDA?
- ( in sing song tone ) PETER
PIPER PICKED A PECK OF PETROL...
- 'SUP WITH HIM? HE'S IN
A PRETTY GOOD MOOD TODAY.
- DID HE MEET A GIRL
OR SOMETHIN'?
- YEAH.
- DAMN, NO WAY IS THAT IDIOT
GONNA BAG HIMSELF A GIRLFRIEND
BEFORE I DO.
OH, TAKUMI, I'VE BEEN
MEANING TO ASK YOU A QUESTION.
- DO YOU WANNA DRIVE
MY S-THIRTEEN?
- DO WHAT?
- IT CAN BE KINDA REFRESHING
TO DRIVE A NEW CAR
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
- NO, THANKS. I'M OKAY, REALLY.
I APPRECIATE THE OFFER.
BUT I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU LOVE
THAT CAR AND I WOULD HATE
TO SCREW IT UP OR SOMETHING.
- TAKUMI, DO YOU EVEN UNDERSTAND
HOW MUCH I CAN LEARN
FROM WATCHING
YOU DRIVE IT?
PLEASE, MAN, I'M BEGGING YOU.
- C'MON, SHINGO, YOU
CAN'T REALLY BE SERIOUS
'BOUT RACIN' AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX?
- ( chuckles ) YOU'LL JUST HAVE
TO WAIT AND SEE, BRO.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
( engine starting )
- ( laughs ) GET OUTTA THAT
HIDING SPOT OF YOURS, EIGHT-SIX.
YOU AND ME HAVE SOME
UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
- DO I REALLY HAVE TO DO THIS?
- PLEASE, DUDE! JUST DRIVE LIKE
IT'S ANY OTHER DAY OF THE WEEK.
IT'S LIKE A DRIVING CLASS,
EXCEPT I'LL BE PAYING ATTENTION.
MAN. I'LL OWE YOU MORE
THAN YOU'LL KNOW.
- WELL, TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I'M NOT REALLY VERY
GOOD BEHIND THE WHEELS
OF OTHER PEOPLES' CARS.
I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA BE THE
KINDA HELP YOU'RE LOOKIN' FOR.
- HE'S PRACTICALLY ON HIS KNEES.
CAN'T YOU JUST GIVE IN
TO THE GUY THIS ONE TIME?
- YEAH, IT'LL MEAN
THE WORLD TO HIM.
IS HE YOUR FRIEND OR ISN'T HE?
- FINE. ONLY THIS ONCE, OKAY?
JUST DON'T EXPECT IT
TO CHANGE YOUR LIFE OR ANYTHING.
- YOU WON'T REGRET IT. AWESOME!
- ( engine revving )
- OKAY, YOU'RE ALL SET, BUDDY.
JUST TRY NOT TO PASS OUT
THIS TIME OUT, HUH?
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
NOW GET AWAY FROM THE CAR.
TAKUMI, LET'S DO THIS THING.
- YEAH. COOL BY ME.
- SWEET!
- IS THERE ANY SPECIAL MOVE
YOU WANT ME TO SHOW YOU FIRST?
- UH, HOW ABOUT A BRAKING DRIFT?
- HERE WE GO.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
WAIT. NOW? ON THE FIRST TURN?
THINK MAYBE WE'RE MOVIN'
A LITTLE TOO FAST?
WE COULD SLOW IT DOWN.
( exclaiming in fear )
( tires screeching )
- ♪ A DIAMOND LIFE
IS JUST WHAT I NEED ♪
♪ PLEASURE AND JOY FOREVER ♪
♪ GET WHAT I CAN GET
'COS LIFE IS A BET ♪
♪ NO PLEASURE AND
PAIN TOGETHER ♪
- I HOPE HE'S ALL RIGHT.
WHADDYA THINK, MAN?
- WELL, UH...
( screams ) I KNEW IT!
THE AGONIZED CRY OF
HIS LAST MOMENT
DURING THIS HORRIFYING DOWNHILL
ECHOED ACROSS THE MOUNTAIN!
POOR IKETANI,
IN THE THIRD CORNER.
( wincing )
TOTALLY PASSED OUT!
CONSIDERING WHAT HAPPENED LAST
TIME, I WOULD BE SURPRISED.
- ( screaming )
- HE'S NEVER DRIVEN
THIS CAR BEFORE
AND HE CAN DRIFT IT
SO EFFORTLESSLY.
I NEVER KNEW MY
CAR COULD DO THIS.
DIDN'T EVEN KNOW IT WAS
CAPABLE OF THIS KINDA SPEED.
- YEAH, I CAN TELL IT HANDLES
A LITTLE DIFFERENTLY
FROM MY EIGHT-SIX.
BUT I THINK I'M FINALLY
STARTING TO GET USED
TO ALL THE MINOR DETAILS.
- DID I PASS OUT AGAIN
OR HAVE WE ONLY GONE
THROUGH THREE TURNS?
- I'M READY FOR A DRIFT.
ARE YOU?
- DRIFT? THE HELL'S HE BEEN
DOIN' THIS WHOLE TIME?
( engine revving )
( screaming )
- ♪ GIVE ME LOVE AND MONEY ♪
♪ GIVE ME YOUR LOVE MY BABY ♪
♪ GIVE ME KISSES HONEY ♪
♪ I DESERVE THE BEST
YOU KNOW IT ♪
♪ GIVE ME LOVE AND MONEY ♪
♪ I HAVE THE REST ALREADY ♪
♪ LOVE AND MONEY COMING FROM YOU
IS WHAT I NEED ♪
♪ GIVE ME LOVE AND MONEY ♪
♪ GIVE ME YOUR LOVE MY BABY ♪
♪ GIVE ME KISSES HONEY ♪
- THAT ONE FELT
PRETTY GOOD TO ME.
I THINK I GOT IT RIGHT ON THE
MONEY AT THAT LAST CORNER.
- I HAVE TO OWN UP TO IT.
THIS IS TOO ADVANCED A TECHNIQUE
FOR ME TO UNDERSTAND.
( screaming )
- I WONDER HOW THE RUN WENT.
- ( groaning )
- ( mocking ) CONGRATULATIONS,
SISTER. YOU MADE IT.
- AND CONSCIOUS, NO LESS.
- WAS IT EVERYTHING YOU
HOPED IT'D BE?
DID YA GET A GOOD LOOK AT
TAKUMI'S BRAKING DRIFT
LIKE YOU WANTED?
- ( groans ) NO.
NO CLUE WHAT JUST HAPPENED.
- THEN WHAT WAS THE POINT?
WHY BOTHER BEGGING LIKE A JERK
IF YOU'RE NOT EVEN GONNA
PAY ATTENTION?
- Iketani: IT'S JUST THAT
HE MAKES IT LOOK SO SIMPLE.
THEN WHEN WE WERE OUT THERE,
I HAD THIS CRAZY EPIPHANY.
IT'S LIKE THIS.
WHILE I'M NOT EVEN CLOSE
TO UNDERSTANDING
HIS TECHNIQUE,
I FEEL LIKE I'M ALREADY
A BETTER STREET RACER.
BETTER THAN ANY OF YOU.
- ( cars approaching )
- HEY, THAT'S THE EG-SIX.
THE ONE THAT BUMPED ME.
WHY IS HE HERE?
- ( grunting ) JERK.
HEY, PUNK! WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOIN' UP HERE?
YOU HIT MY CAR.
LAST NIGHT, REMEMBER!
- YEAH? WHO ARE YOU?
- AND DON'T TRY TO TELL ME
YOU FORGOT.
YOU REALLY FORGOT
HITTING MY S-THIRTEEN?
- OH, OH YEAH!
- YOU OWE ME AN APOLOGY,
YOU GOT THAT?
YOU COULD HAVE KILLED ME OUT
THERE, OR WORSE, WRECKED MY CAR.
- OH, SO THAT WAS MY FAULT?
IF YOU COULD HANDLE YOUR RIDE,
IT WOULDN'TA HAPPENED.
- Iketani: WHAT?
- I JUST KNEW THE CAR IN
FRONT OF ME WAS SLOW
AND I COULDN'T TAKE
FOLLOWING IT ANYMORE.
I DIDN'T THINK THINGS UP HERE
WENT THAT SLOW,
BUT WHADDYA GONNA DO.
I TRIED TO BRAKE, BUT I GUESS
I NUDGED YOU A BIT,
SUCKS TO BE YOU.
- YOU WANNA SAY THAT
TO ME AGAIN?
CALM DOWN, IKETANI.
IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
- AH, MAN. WHAT A DOUCHEBAG.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S ACTING LIKE
TRYING TO MURDER IKETANI
WAS NO BIG DEAL.
- ( laughs ) I'LL TELL YA WHAT,
YOU WANNA SETTLE UP,
WE CAN RACE UNDER MY RULES.
AND IF YOU WIN, THEN I'LL
DROP TO MY FREAKIN' KNEES
AND BEG YOUR FORGIVENESS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOUR RULES?
WHY WOULD I AGREE TO THAT?
- IT COULD BE INTERESTING
FOR YOU.
WE CALL IT A GUM
TAPE DEATH MATCH
AND IT'S ONE WILD ASS TIME.
- GUM TAPE WHAT?
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- OH, WE JUST TAPE THE
RIGHT HAND OF EACH DRIVER
TO THE STEERING WHEEL
AND THEN WE RACE.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
THE ONLY RULE.
THINK YOU'RE UP TO
HANDLIN' THAT, PRINCESS?
- WAIT, YOU TAPE YOUR HAND
TO THE STEERING WHEEL
AND THEN YOU RACE?
YOU'RE INSANE!
- HOW CAN YOU DRIVE
WITH JUST ONE HAND FREE?
- MY RIGHT HAND ON THE WHEEL.
BUT THEN YOU CAN'T SWITCH HANDS
TO MAKE ANY TURNS.
YOU CAN'T STEER
YOUR FREAKIN' CAR.
THAT'S TOO RISKY.
- ( scoffs ) FOR YOU,
I'D SAY DEFINITELY.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE
SPEED STAR'S EIGHT-SIX?
I HEAR THAT GUY'S SUPPOSED TO BE
A DOWNHILL SPECIALIST.
YOU GET HIM TO SHOW HIS FACE,
HE MIGHT EVEN BE ABLE
TO SAVE YOUR ASS.
TELL HIM I'LL BE WAITING
RIGHT HERE FOR HIM.
HE JUST NEEDS TO MEET
ME HERE NEXT SATURDAY
AT TEN O'CLOCK SHARP.
WE'LL HAVE ONE HELL OF A
GUM TAPE DEATH MATCH.
( laughs )
( sighs ) SEE YOU LOSERS THEN.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ MY PRIDE SAYS
YOU GOTTA BE WILD AND TOUGH ♪
♪ NEVER STOP ♪
♪ I'M NEVER GONNA STOP ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- ♪ ANOTHER ROUND,
NEVER SLOW DOWN ♪
♪ THE KNOCK DOWN ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT SOUND ♪
- ♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
♪ RAGE YOUR DREAM ♪
- YOUR HOROSCOPE FOR THIS WEEK.
ROMANCE, THIS WEEK
A NEW RELATIONSHIP
WILL DEVELOP FURTHER.
- Announcer: DID
SOMETHING GOOD HAPPEN
IN YOUR LOVE LIFE, ITSUKI?
- Itsuki: I'M GONNA HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND MAN!
- Announcer: REALLY?
CONGRATULATIONS!
WHO'S THE LUCKY LADY?
- Itsuki: OH, JUST THE
CHICK I WAS WITH
ON THE DOUBLE DATE WITH TAKUMI.
- Announcer: SAORI?
- Itsuki: MMM-HMM.
- Announcer: WAIT, THE
FORTUNE ALSO SAYS SOMETHING
ABOUT NOT PUSHING TOO HARD
OR YOU'LL FIND YOURSELF
IN TROUBLE.
NEXT ON INITIAL D,
"FIRST DATE!" DON'T MISS IT!