Long sought
by the greed of men
but bestowed
only upon the women
whose fate
it forever scars.
The Witchblade.
Righteous Sword of God,
or Hand of the Devil himself?
A new Bearer finds out,
seeking balance
between ecstasy and ruin.
[Music]
Man, how the crap did she
let herself get captured?
This can't be good.
Yes, ma'am. Understood.
Listen up, everyone,
Chief Nishida's on her way!
She's ordered us
to administer first aid
and make sure
the subject is restrained!
You boys wait in the van.
Yes, sir.
That was a rather bold move
they made.
I hope Masane's all right.
I mean, what if they try
to cut off her arm
just to get at the Witchblade?
I can only hope
they try something so foolish.
Any attempt to remove
the Witchblade,
and its defensive instincts
will take care of them.
I see.
Really?
The Witchblade, you say?
How interesting.
I understand.
I'll call again soon.
Takayama's luck
may have finally run out.
What did they say, sir?
Did something happen?
Evidently someone has stolen
the Witchblade from him.
Takayama.
What a stunning failure.
'Course it can't be that easy.
What're you doin'?
Only top level scientists
are allowed
through those doors, kid.
You should've known that.
Yeah.
I'm new.
Sorry 'bout that.
So hey,
what's goin' on in there,
like top secret stuff?
Nah, I doubt it.
It's some kinda
medical research lab
where they do complicated
surgeries and other crap.
A medical research lab?
For cryin' out loud.
Don't they teach you guys this
stuff at orientation anymore?
Hey, wait up!
You're takin' that trash down
to the collection facility,
right?
So how about
I give you a hand?
Is that cool?
Grandfather!
Ah, Maria.
I came to see you!
That make you happy?
Yes, it does.
It's been a while, dear.
Nishida's here, sir,
but she went straight to the lab
to see the Witchblade.
She's hasn't
changed at all, has she?
She said she would
come by later to say hello.
Tell her it's quite all right.
Once I've finished
my duties for the day,
I'll go down
to the lab myself.
That way, Nishida can--
I came all this way
to see you
and you won't stop
talking about Nishida!
Please stop, Maria.
Nora and I have
important business to discuss.
Whatever!
I would appreciate it
if you would try to be
a little more reasonable,
my child.
You are putting
your incredible IQ to shame.
So why don't you just tell me
you don't like me?
You know that's not true.
Nora.
Why don't you
take Maria somewhere
that would help
lighten her spirits?
Yes, sir.
No! Let me go!
Stupid Nora!
Where's the host body?
This is her?
She's rather unremarkable.
She's seriously injured
and her recovery
has been much slower
than that of the Neo-Genes'.
We need to treat her, ma'am.
Take samples from the Witchblade
and from the host body.
Then analyze
the gauntlet itself.
I've  got all the data
I need for now.
Riko.
Okay, Miss Rihoko,
time to take your temperature.
Was there somebody
in my room before?
I had this weird feeling like
someone was watching over me.
Could it have
been your mother?
Don't think so.
I'm pretty sure my mom
went home last night.
Maybe so, she did disappear
during your checkup.
But if she was going home,
don't you think
she would've
come in here and told you?
Well no, not necessarily.
Maybe it was her work.
Sometimes
she just has to leave.
Really?
Does her work
keep her that busy?
My mom's been working
really hard every day,
ever since we moved here.
But you know,
I need to hurry and get better.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, 'cause my mom
doesn't know how to cook at all!
This one.
And...
Look! This one's cute!
You want it?
C'mon, Mom!
How many times
do I have to tell you
I'm not a kid anymore!
Well, you'll always
be a kid in my eyes!
Mom.
Thank you.
You can take us
back to the hotel.
We're done shopping.
No, we're not!
I didn't even get
any stuffed animals!
I believe you've been taught
that creating a scene in public,
as you just did,
is unacceptable.
But she took it
right out of my hands!
What was I supposed to do?
You weren't gonna help me!
I'll inform Nishida
you're not ready
to visit the outside world yet.
I'd be more careful
if I were you, little girl.
Or I might lose
the ability to restrain myself.
I hate you!
Go ahead, driver.
I hope you die.
Getting Masane back is not
going to be an easy task, is it?
It's not like we can go
barging into NSWF Headquarters.
With any luck,
they'll come to their senses
and quietly hand her
over to us.
That would be
the best case scenario.
Director Takayama's office.
Ah, Director Wado.
Has Takayama made it back in?
He's away
from his desk right--
He must be having a hard time
sleeping lately.
What with the Witchblade's
recent theft.
I understand now
why he could never give
any clear information
regarding the Witchblade.
To think,
it was because he'd lost it.
With all due respect,
that's not really wha--
This is a huge failure
for us, Segawa.
I'm calling an emergency
board meeting immediately.
Pass the word on to Takayama,
will you?
Now how on Earth
did Wado discover
the Witchblade had been stolen?
And this "emergency board
meeting" does not bode well.
Do you have a plan?
Give this to the lab.
Sir, are you sure about this?
Taking back the Witchblade
is our top priority.
This is the end of the line,
Takayama.
Oh, man!
I feel like such a jerk
for not bein' here with you,
Miss Rihoko.
I've been so worried.
Actually, the doctor said
it's nothing serious.
I go home tomorrow.
Really?
Here's a lovely bouquet
from yours truly.
And this is from Mari.
She's pretty worried
about you too, kiddo.
Oh, and a get-well charm.
From Naomi.
Thanks a lot!
So tell me, where's Melony?
Oh, she's at work.
Yeah?
You must be feeling lonely,
Rihoko!
I've been doing okay!
Mr. Cho?
I was wondering.
Did you see my mom
come home last night?
Didn't see her.
Musta pulled an all-nighter.
That's gotta be rough
at a time like this.
Careful, Mom.
Don't push yourself too hard.
How are things coming along?
Forgive me for not coming up
to say hello to you, Father.
That's quite all right,
Nishida.
This must be
the Witchblade's latest host.
Yes.
I've taken samples
to determine
her level of assimilation.
Apparently,
she has no memory
of anything before
the Great Quake.
And she has a daughter.
Up until earlier this year,
she's been living
in a half-way house.
How pedestrian.
She shows no signs of being
a suitable bearer.
Why would it choose
someone like her?
Doctor?
Father.
The results from
the assimilation tests are in.
Aside from the obvious fact
that they're conforming
at a rapid pace--
What is it?
We ran an update on all
of our sample comparison data.
And Reina's numbers
have dropped significantly.
I was under the impression
her numbers
were exceptionally high?
I'm afraid
that's no longer the case.
What does that mean?
Something must have happened
in the last six years
to cause this change.
At present, Reina
is completely incompatible
with the Witchblade.
Very well.
I hate to admit it,
but I have started to lose hope
in Reina as of late.
And now that I've seen
the woman it chose,
it's obvious to me
the Witchblade is not perfect.
You're right.
I'm rather disappointed
with it myself.
The blade
currently in development
will far surpass
the original.
I have high hopes
for the future.
We will complete
this new blade.
And the perfect
Neo-Gene specimen
will be the one chosen
to wield it.
Once that has come to pass,
I will have obtained
the ultimate mother.
What?
"Reina is incompatible?"
What are they talking about?
Bingo!
This is the only way
I'm gonna make it inside.
Well, I guess
I got no other choice.
Crap!
Hey! Don't I know you?
Yes, I thought so.
You're that photographer
Masane hangs around with,
aren't you?
What a small world.
Did you come here
to rescue her, too?
You're Doji guy.
C'mon, you ready?
Hey now! Wait a second!
There's nothing
to be afraid of!
It's not like they ever check
for intruders at this place.
It's the "getting out"
that might be difficult.
What the hell?
And what am I supposed to do
if I can't get out?
Not a problem,
you'll have Masane with you!
You dumbass!
How's she s'posed
ta help me when she's wounded?
You'll be fine, I'm sure.
I'll teach you
the magic words
that'll get her
back on her feet in no time!
Magic words?
Son of a...
Well, that was
unbelievably convenient.
Now, if we fail,
I can blame it on him.
Speaking of,
it's almost time.
Hey, you think
she's gonna be all right?
Chart says she's a DNR.
Poor woman.
So much pain.
Someone, please...
...help me.
Spectacular!
All that's left to do
is analyze this data.
And I should be able to upgrade
the Cloneblades substantially!
Father.
Very soon, our greatest desire
will be achieved.
Yes.
Finally, I have
almost reached your level.
You were perfect
in nearly every way.
But there is one thing for
which you can never be forgiven!
If only
it could have been different.
Hey, Melony!
Whoa, this is not good.
Tozawa?
Get it together!
Listen, we're gonna
have to use your power
to get us outta here!
I can't do it.
I can't move.
Hey!
Rihoko's waiting for you!
We gotta go! C'mon!
Riko.
That's right! Riko!
Take care of her.
Mariko and Mr. Cho
will help you.
Please.
Come on!
Don't quit on me!
Jerk, this isn't funny!
Melony!
There's something
I've gone too long without.
There's somethin' savage
about this one.
Dammit!
"Magic words that'll get her
back on her feet in no time!"
Get up and walk outta here,
and Doji will pay you
10 million yen!
You listenin' to me?
10 million, Melony!
C'mon!
She's conscious!
Riko.
I'll do whatever I have to.
Yes! Now let's book!
Impossible!
A minute ago,
she couldn't even move!
Gotta be a scoop in these!
Father! The Witchblade host
has escaped!
She's what?
How many broads
they got workin' here?
No way
we're gonna get out now!
That's enough!
Hold your attack!
Any sudden movements,
and we will open fire!
What the hell is all this?
You will release
Masane immediately,
or Mr. Furumizu
will be blown to pieces!
Well, hello, Director Takayama.
It's been a while.
It's not like you to resort
to such violent threats.
You've caught me off-guard.
I thought it best
not to draw this out.
If you had just been this
assertive from the beginning,
my precious sisters
could have avoided injury.
If you had just pretended
not to have the Witchblade
in your possession, I may not
have gotten this chance.
I see.
So what will it be?
Shall we re-enact what happened
six years ago?
I think I'll pass.
Melony.
Ten million. Ten million.
Do it for her.
For Riko.
Hey, it's all good.
So, those magic words.
Told you they'd work.
What I still
don't understand
is how Wado
found out about Masane.
There must be some connection
between Wado and the NSWF.
Understood.
Is there something wrong,
Director Wado?
What happened?
The emergency board meeting
is canceled!
Damn you, Takayama.
You got lucky.
Very lucky.
Riko!
Mommy!
Oh, Riko!
Mom!
Welcome home from
the hospital, Rihoko!
The Natsuki Building
was a gloomy place
without your smile!
We're so glad
to have you back!
Well, thank you
for coming to visit me!
I just thank heaven
you're okay!
Speaking of heaven,
I noticed the hospital
was full of hot nurses and...
Hello again, Ms. Amaha.
It's nice to see you.
Hold on!
What's the Child Welfare
Ministry doing here?
I'm sorry to intrude,
but the Ministry
sent me to deliver
this notice to you.
Ms. Amaha, we have
obtained test results
which indicate that Rihoko
is not your biological daughter.
Impossible.
[Music]
No! I don't wanna
leave you, Mom!
I hate that stupid
Child Welfare lady!
Why would she make me leave you,
you're my mom!
Why does she always
wanna separate us!
Let's run away again!
If we ran away, we wouldn't
have to worry anymore.
We could go someplace
far, far away.
A place where
nobody would bother us.
We can build our own house
and live in it!
I already made
the blueprints!
I can't wait to show you!
We're gonna be together
forever.
Aren't we, Mom?