Long sought
by the greed of men,
but bestowed
only upon the women
whose fate
it forever scars.
The Witchblade.
Righteous Sword of God,
or Hand of the Devil himself?
A new Bearer finds out,
seeking balance between
ecstasy and ruin.
[Music]
Shiori!
Doctor, I...
Retract your Blade
this instant!
No!
I don't know how it...
I... Doctor!
Doctor, please help me!
I'm scared - I don't know
what's wrong with me!
Calm down, Shiori, it's okay.
Your body is simply
going through some changes.
Changes?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of you.
I... I know you will, Doctor.
Please, you have to believe me,
I never meant
for any of this to happen.
I just thought
it might feel nice.
I see.
So that was your reason?
Well, then...
why don't we
discuss this later.
When the time is right.
It felt so good.
I wish I could show you.
Shiori.
Hey, I'm lookin' for
this cabin cruiser.
Ya seen it?
Can't help ya, dude.
Hey, guys!
Ya got a minute?
You seen this boat around?
I've seen plenty of cruisers
like this out at sea.
Chances are I've even run
across this one at some point.
But I couldn't tell ya
where I saw it
or where it's docked.
Any information
you can give me would be great.
Okay.
Well, a boat like this
can go out pretty far,
so it could be anywhere.
I mean, it's not necessarily
docked here in Tokyo.
You could check
Yokohama or Chiba,
but it may be
even farther out than that.
It'll be difficult
to track down.
Just my luck.
Hey, thanks for your help.
Startin' to think I ain't
gonna find this thing on my own.
Yes, come in.
When were you gonna
tell me about this?
I can't believe you.
You treat me like
I'm the enemy!
Are you working together?
Trying to trick me?
That is that
"Lady" chick, isn't it?
Explain it now,
and make it good.
'Cause if you don't,
I quit doin' your dirty work.
Fine, whatever you say.
You remember when I told you
that at one time,
Doji Group Industries
and the NSWF
collaborated to conduct
research on the Witchblade.
And?
During that period,
a young woman
was sent over
from the NSWF to assist us.
You know her as Lady.
On behalf of the NSWF,
I look forward
to the advancement
of our research.
Doctor Reina Soho.
Reiji Takayama.
A pleasure to meet you.
She was a brilliant scientist.
Intelligent, refined,
and beautiful.
Everything about her
was breathtaking.
I was amazed that the NSWF's
Neogene experiments
could produce
such a perfect woman.
So, you really
cared about her, huh?
You make it sound
like a bad movie.
Geez, ya don't have to try and
be so damn macho all the time.
I just never thought of you
as the type to fall in love.
I don't know that you'd call
what we had "love."
Huh?
What do you mean?
One day she just disappeared
without a trace.
Disappeared?
About the time our research
had reached its climax,
Reina stole the Witchblade
and ran off.
The Witchblade is gone!
Could - could it have
been Doctor Soho?
At first, I thought she was
under orders from the NSWF.
But when we contacted them,
they were just as surprised
by her disappearance as I was.
Then why'd she do it?
Reina could be quite arrogant
and selfish at times.
I'm certain she wanted
the Witchblade's power
for herself.
But you told me
the Witchblade itself
had to choose its bearer.
That's correct.
However, Reina
was a suitable host,
and she knew it.
You're kiddin' me.
Something we discovered
during our research.
But the Doji Group
wouldn't hear of allowing
someone from NSWF
to have it.
Much of the staff favored
dropping her from the project.
But before we even
had the chance to talk to her,
Reina and the Witchblade
disappeared.
Betrayed by someone
you trusted.
Trusting each other was
never really our strong suit.
Damn, you two
have a hell of a history.
Father kept the Neogenes
fairly well sheltered.
Romantic feelings
were a new experience for her.
Reina was simply curious.
But how did you
feel about her?
It's all in the past.
She's showing increased
activity in the limbic lobe;
and particularly
in the cortical column.
This activity
directly correlates
to the activation of her Blade.
This must be what's bringing
out the animalistic instincts
and her desire to fight.
It's almost as if the subject
is in some sort of trance.
It's fascinating.
I don't wanna wear
this stupid outfit!
Aw, come on, Naomi, you don't
have to be shy around us!
Besides, I think
you look great!
Please come out, Naomi!
It looks really cute!
I don't care!
You guys don't understand,
this is gonna bring me
bad luck for years!
Why'd ya go and make her
put on that crazy get-up?
You know
she's a sensitive young thing.
She woulda been fine
if you hadn't laughed at her.
So it's my fault, huh?
Hey, Mr. Cho.
What's up?
Don't even bother askin'.
I don't have any money.
Chill, dude!
I wanna help ya.
Massage parlor.
Lady friends.
Really?
You better not be
pullin' my leg.
So what do ya need, huh?
We got a deal, old man?
You got it, kid!
Well, let's get goin'!
Right this way, young one!
Step into my office.
This is horrible.
I can sense it.
My aura is ruined.
Nice decor.
Hey! Get over here!
I need to scan that photo.
Bring it here.
So...
what do you wanna know?
Oh. Uh...
well, the owner,
and maybe where it's docked?
No prob.
But before I do,
I just wanna make sure
that you're gonna follow up
on your end of the bargain.
Look at this face -
would I lie to you?
I'll call 'em later,
I promise!
Or right now!
This can't be good.
All right.
Let's try to access
the worldwide network
and see if we can
get ya some info.
Check, check, 1, 2.
Anybody out there?
Mr. Cho! What up, yo?
Not a lot these days!
But I could use your help if--
Wow, Mr. Cho's
a computer genius.
Wow, Mr. Cho's a nerd.
Just as I thought.
It's trying to destroy her.
And it's succeeding.
Right now, Shiori
is no different than an X-Con.
Constantly seeking pleasure.
This can't continue.
If it does...
In order to fully understand
what's happening to the subject,
I need to run more tests.
It's imperative that we locate
and secure Shiori immediately
so we may obtain
the necessary data.
That's all for now.
Still not satisfied.
I need more.
Yes, her.
She can fill my needs.
Kahlua and milk.
Sorry, it's the only cocktail
I know how to make.
Too sweet.
I guess it's not
your kind of drink.
What're you doing?
Oh, there's an empty spot
on the shelf here -
I'm filling it in.
I'm uh, a little OCD
about stuff like that.
So, if Lady ran off
with the Witchblade
and she was a compatible host,
how did I end up with it?
I don't know the reason.
All we do know
is that somehow,
during the Great Quake,
the Witchblade chose you.
That day...
we finally got word
of Reina's whereabouts.
Armed with I-Weapons,
we attempted to take back
the Witchblade.
But the NSWF had the same idea,
and sent in Cloneblade Sisters.
I'd hoped to avoid
a public confrontation,
but there was too much
on the line.
The outcome was worse
than I could have imagined.
The Witchblade
was supposed to be dormant
but somehow it awakened.
The resulting power surge
is what caused the Great Quake.
So I just happened to be
in the wrong place
at the wrong time?
As far as we can tell, yes.
Some destiny.
Dumb luck!
Wait a minute, why didn't
Reina bond with the Witchblade
when she had the chance?
I mean, if she had--
Who can say?
At any rate, Reina was allowed
to return to the NSWF
and was given a Cloneblade.
But, wasn't that Father guy
upset with her?
It's quite rare
to find a woman
who's compatible
with the Witchblade.
Even if he was angry,
he'd never let her go
that easily.
Well, this thing
has hardly been a blessing.
Its immense power is a blessing
in and of itself.
Men, always trying
to rationalize!
Wearing this thing
scares the hell outta me.
And you'll never understand.
Director?
30 minutes 'til we reach
the Marina.
Thank you.
It'll be nice to get home.
Damn straight.
S'felt like forever.
Gotta hand it to ol' Cho
and his buddies.
Can't believe they found it
in just 10 minutes!
Ashina Marina, huh?
Well, all right.
Now all I gotta do
is try and figure out
who owns that damn boat.
And then what?
Whoa!
What're you doin' here?
Figured you were after
my mom again, Don Juan!
Wait, what did you
just call me?
Listen, kiddo,
I'm not chasing after your ma.
Well, I'm gonna keep
an eye on you just in case.
No way! No kids!
Too bad.
'Cause I'm not leavin'!
Gimme a break!
Man, I've gotta be
somewhere right now!
Just give it up.
My mom is so not into
loser guys like you.
Ya got it all wrong!
I told ya, I'm not into her!
Whatever you say.
Now, can we go?
All right, fine!
Have it your way!
It must be close.
I can sense its presence.
But this feeling is different.
I've got to hurry.
Now, before I lose my patience,
tell me where she is!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Miss me?
I need your power.
Satisfy me.
Director,
we have to do something!
Masane is still recovering
from--
Back her up!
Right!
This is what I want.
Finally.
Takayama.
Reiji.
The Doctor's lover.
Your fight is with me!
Come on!
Sorry, not feeling it.
You just don't
do it for me anymore.
Kind of disappointing.
Director!
You can't escape.
Please.
I'm begging you.
What the hell?
It's all over.
Where is she?
I was told
Shiori came to see you.
She did.
Director?
What should I do
with the Cloneblade?
My God, that's...
I see, I'm too late.
Please,
I'd like to examine the body.
There is no body.
That's impossible!
This is all that's left.
She crystallized,
then disintegrated.
May I take her remains
back with me?
Take this.
We're not handing
over anything else.
But Shiori was my assistant!
And?
Give it to me.
Hi, Mom!
Riko!
What are you doing here?
Did I surprise you?
I came with Mr. Tozawa!
Tozawa's here too?
Hey. What's up?
Okay, what do you want?
So, is that the guy
who owns the cruiser?
Introduce me, will ya?
Just so you know, I saw
what happened on that overpass.
Whatever.
We're not having
this discussion here.
Now, will you please
just take Riko and me home.
Fine, f'you say so.
We'll talk later.
That little girl.
Reiji, listen.
Shiori's death
was caused by the unstable power
of her Cloneblade.
As I assumed.
If I'm not careful,
I could end up like her someday.
But don't forget,
the same applies
to the Witchblade itself.
After all, the Cloneblade
is nothing more than a copy
of the original artifact.
You and I stumbled across
ancient data
during our research years ago.
Do you remember it?
How could I forget?
As the Witchblade's power
increases,
so too does the risk
of its host being consumed.
But we had no way
to test the theory.
I think Shiori's death
is proof enough.
Eventually, the Witchblade
will consume its host.
Reiji, the Witchblade
will not let go of that woman.
Not until she is dead.
I only wonder which one's
going to break first.
In any case, I'll be keeping
a lower profile from now on.
[Music]
I gotta say, Riko,
you were right all along!
It looks like Tozawa
really is after me.
Only in a different way
than you're thinking.
Man, that guy's a creep!
He's tryin' to sell a photo
I don't want anyone to see!
Can you believe him?
Why can't he
just leave me alone?
See if I'm ever nice
to that jerk again.
You know, Mariko told me
he actually used to be
a decent photographer.
Maybe so.
But I find it hard to believe
"Tozawa" and "decent"
could ever be used
in the same sentence.