Long sought
by the greed of man,
but bestowed only
upon the women
whose fate
it forever scars.
The Witchblade.
Righteous Sword of God,
or Hand of the Devil himself?
A new Bearer finds out,
seeking balance
between ecstasy and ruin.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Good morning.
Morning, Mom!
Smells good!
That's yours on the table,
all ready to go.
I have to go deliver this,
so you can start without me.
'Kay. See you in a bit.
That hit the spot!
Hello?
Anybody up?
What the hell's
wrong with you?
Why can't you knock?
Tryin' to sneak a peek
first thing in the morning?
Yeah, you wish.
I was up all night.
Where's Rihoko?
With Mr. Cho.
Well, in that case,
we can talk about this.
I dug up some documents
on Doji Group Industries
at the newspaper.
I got a connection
down there.
I'm tellin' you,
they're a big-time corporation.
So big in fact,
other top companies've
been tryin'
to take 'em down for years.
Why's that?
Ain't it obvious?
Doji manufactures
and exports weapons.
There's always money in death.
You've been hangin' out
with that Doji director a lot.
S'prised you didn't know
all this.
I wasn't really interested,
'til now.
Well, judging
from what you've told me,
these I-Weapons must be exactly
what they've been exporting.
While that may be a huge issue
for peace-freaks,
it doesn't make
for much of a story.
Unless, we can prove
how they're made.
Prove they're using
real people,
like Nakata's dead cop buddy.
Yeah.
I assumed the I-Weapons were
machines in human form but,
I'll ask Takayama about it
when I see him later.
Gettin' it
straight from the top, huh?
We want the truth, don't we?
Only way to get it.
True. Then I'll try attackin'
from a different angle.
I'm gonna look up
those Neo-Genes
you were talkin' about.
Deeper down
the rabbit hole, eh?
Lemme taste.
So good!
I wanted to try something
a little different this time
so I used maple syrup!
The sweetness
is so delicate and subtle!
And the fluffy-soft texture
is just perfect!
Everything you make
is so tasty, kiddo!
Oh, uh...
But of course,
you still make
a damn fine cup of coffee, Mari.
In fact,
it may be better than ever!
That's 'cause
I got a new coffeemaker.
Well, that may be, but I can
tell you really put your heart
into pressing that button.
Hey! It's Tozawa!
Hey! Don't forget my hot chicks
for the group date you promised!
I won't!
So, are group dates
better than regular dates?
Yeah!
They're miracles of destiny,
where a man can meet
all the women of his dreams!
Good morning!
Morning, Melony!
What's up?
Care for a cup of Mari's
delicious coffee?
Thank you, Mr. Cho,
but I'll pass.
I gotta get goin'.
Okay, Riko,
I should be home by tonight
but I'll give you a call later.
Wait a minute, Mom.
Are you going out like that?
Well, yeah.
But you still have bed-head!
You really should pay more
attention to the way you look.
Nah, it's fine!
See you later!
Have a good one!
The lab report meeting is
scheduled to end at 15:00 hours.
Then this evening you've got--
Cancel all of my plans
for tonight.
And what's this?
An invitation to
the Bio-Division's reception?
Ah, yes.
Wado sent e-mails to everyone
bragging about
his research team,
and how they won
this year's
International
Science Foundation Award.
But, sir.
This invitation isn't
even addressed to you.
That's right,
the head of Motor Vehicles
was nice enough
to give it to me.
I think you should take
a good look at the guest list.
You have got to be kidding?
These are all officials
involved with our division.
He's even invited top brass
from our affiliate companies.
Sounds exactly
like something Wado would do.
Oh, I get it.
The guest list
is full of people
he wants to add
to his clique.
Clever ploy.
Precisely.
While I doubt he'd do
anything stupid tonight,
I thought I might as well
drop by the party to make sure.
In an attempt
to keep him in check.
Understood.
I'll rework your schedule
for tonight.
Shall I arrange for
a high-profile escort
for you as well, sir?
An actress, perhaps?
An actress?
Yes, sir.
It says here
it includes a "plus-one".
So I would recommend
you bring somebody.
If you don't act the part,
they may question
your lack of invitation.
Don't want to seem
like a party-crasher.
Look at Wado.
Whenever he attends a function
he always has
some kind of arm-candy.
Like a famous actress
or a super model.
Good morning.
Good morning, Masane!
Something wrong?
I have a question.
Well then,
go ahead and ask it.
It's about the X-Cons.
And what do you want to know?
Are they...?
Are they human?
What makes you think that?
I met someone who knew
the X-Con from yesterday.
How unfortunate.
So you're not denying it?
And that goes
for all the I-Weapons?
Yes, you are correct.
Director...
There's no point
in hiding it any longer.
Tell her everything.
Right.
It's good to see you, Father.
It's been a long time.
Reina, my daughter,
is there something the matter?
Ever since Shiori's
unfortunate accident,
it has seemed that you have
lost your passion
for re-acquiring the Witchblade.
I am conducting other research
that is more
important to me, Father.
Even more than the Witchblade?
Yes, in my eyes it is.
I'm having a hard time
hiding my disappointment,
given your personal history
with the matter.
That's the only reason you
still care for me, isn't it?
Because the Witchblade chose me.
Of course not.
But what father wouldn't adore
a daughter who was so chosen?
So you adore me?
What kind of emotion
is that, exactly?
What is it, Reina?
Why are you questioning me?
I'm sorry, Father,
I didn't mean to offend you.
I'm afraid I must
leave your side for a while
to continue my research.
The other sisters can
search for the Witchblade.
Thank you, Father.
Goodbye.
It's my fault, really.
I've pampered her too much.
It certainly appears
that way, sir.
The question is,
what to do now.
Let me clarify.
Technically,
the I-Weapons and X-Cons
are not "human"
in the strictest sense.
"Former humans"
would be more appropriate.
What does that mean?
They're created from cadavers.
They come from
all sorts of backgrounds.
Most often,
we make agreements with people
while they're still alive,
but, sometimes,
we deal with their families
post-mortem.
You what?
How can you do that to people?
It's disrespectful!
Perhaps, but their families
are quite well compensated.
You're selling their loved ones
as weapons!
This is a business, Masane.
You guys are sick!
By manufacturing weapons,
you're only causing more wars
to break out--
Wars are not caused by weapons.
Mankind has fought
since prehistoric times.
Humans will never
be free from war.
Therefore we should try
to limit our casualties.
And I suppose you think
your I-Weapons do that?
An overwhelming show of force
can end a war quickly
or it can even
deter it all together.
Not to mention,
with an army of I-Weapons,
fewer live soldiers
are necessary.
Yeah, but...
you guys are still
using people!
That's true,
but you forget,
those people
are already deceased.
Isn't it an army's duty
to protect the living?
You talk a big game
when it comes to money,
I guess that's all
you can handle.
Never mind, there's something
I wanted to ask you.
According to
our recovery team's report,
there was a civilian with you
when you took care
of that X-Con yesterday.
That douche bag?
He's a guy who lives
in my building.
He was just...
well, he...
Does he know about you?
Yeah.
About that.
I take it that's a yes.
You know,
it would really help
if you told us
these things sooner.
You're not gonna go
hurt him or anything, are ya?
Nothing of the sort!
We simply wish to
grasp the situation.
A photographer or two
doesn't concern me.
Especially
if it's someone you know.
However...
you still have
to pay a penalty.
Segawa, I want you
to escort Ms. Amaha
to the best boutique in town.
Try to turn this primate
into something presentable.
What did you call me!
Well, you're nothin'
but a big gloomy gorilla!
Please, you should know
ladies don't talk like that.
And you might want to spend
more time on your appearance.
Don't tell me what to do!
I'm going home!
You have to pay your penalty.
Would you prefer
to pay financially?
Fine, I'll do it.
Segawa, please have them
charge it to my card.
Thank you.
Dammit! What's going on?
What is this "penalty"?
Don't yell when you speak.
Don't walk with long strides.
And always call me
"sir" in public.
You got that?
What is all this!
Woah.
Sorry
this always happens, baby.
It's not a problem, Mom!
Just make sure you don't
drink too much, 'kay?
Bye-bye!
Lemme guess,
Melony's workin' late again?
Since she's not here,
you wanna have dinner with me?
I'll make us
something really yummy.
Really? Lucky me!
I get to taste some more
of your delicious
homemade cuisine!
How 'bout this,
we'll invite the others
and make it a dinner party!
Your kitchen's big enough.
Ooh, I'd like that!
Hey Mari, that sound good?
I never miss a party.
In fact,
I'll make something too.
I know that pose!
Mari's out for blood!
Director Wado!
Congratulations
on winning the ISF Award!
Why, thank you.
Bio Division is the face
of the company now!
If only we could all be
as successful as you!
How flattering.
But my vision for the department
has yet to be fully realized.
You don't say.
I've not yet
had the opportunity
to work with your
Machines Division.
But I very much hope we can
collaborate in the future.
Great, just say the word.
Director...
Over there. Mister Takayama
has just arrived.
Has he now?
What nerve.
Waltzing in here.
Um, excuse me, sir, may I see
your invitation, please?
Takayama, Director
of the Special Section.
Don't tell me
you haven't heard of him?
Director Takayama!
Good to see you again!
Forgive my rudeness.
Congratulations to you
on winning the award, Wado.
Thank you.
How good it is of you to come.
You know, I never
received my invitation.
I just figured
it must have been
an unintentional oversight.
Absurd.
I can assure you my division
would never make such a mistake.
Remarkable!
Takayama, who is this
beautiful woman with you?
Wado, this young lady
is Masane Amaha.
She's a distant
relative of mine.
A distant relative?
Yeah, right!
So dressing me up and
showing me off is my "penalty"?
I bet he totally likes me!
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Mr. Wado.
Umm...
Listen.
I'm sure the invitation mix-up
was a clerical error on my part.
I apologize, Takayama.
And I forgive you.
Holy crap!
Look at that spread!
Oh, hell, yeah!
So, is all of this stuff free?
Please help yourself
to as much as you'd like.
I'll take that!
At your service, Miss.
What do you think
you're doing?
Please do not
embarrass the director,
especially not in front of
Wado and his colleagues.
What's the big deal?
I mean, can't a girl
have a little fun?
If I'm such an embarrassment
to him,
then why'd he make me come?
The director
had to bring a date
in order to keep up appearances.
I'm a trophy date?
It doesn't matter;
just please behave yourself.
Here you are.
Oh, nice.
So any woman
would've been fine.
What a jerk.
Director, I see the Former
Prime Minister is here.
Why would he come
to Wado's function?
Didn't you hear?
He served as the head judge
on the committee
for this year's award.
Really?
Do you think
Wado bought him off?
Let's just say
I have no doubt
that Wado has been contributing
to his political funds.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am honored to be here tonight
to present
the prestigious ISF Award
to Director Wado
and his research team.
Oh, wow!
I gotta bring
some of these home for Riko!
Hey, I don't suppose you could
box up a couple for me.
Take as many as you'd like.
Lucky me!
What else you guys got?
No! The crystal plaque!
What the hell?
I'm sorry, sir!
I hope it wasn't important.
Of course it was important!
Um, I'm really sorry!
Your half-ass apologies
mean nothing to me.
Do you know what you've done?
I'll pay for it.
What?
I said I'll pay you for it.
How much did it cost?
You must be kidding.
Pay me?
Just tell me
how much I owe you!
Far more than a primate
like you could ever afford!
No please, tell us.
I'll be covering her expenses.
She is my guest, after all.
That's very generous, Takayama,
but it's not something
that can be easily compensated.
No problem, Wado, I'll simply
ask the Honored Gentleman here
exactly how much
you paid him for the award.
I'm sure I can
have it to you immediately.
What did he say?
I'm kidding, of course.
What a zinger, director!
We're leaving!
Thank you, Miss,
but you needn't reimburse me.
It's not about
the value of the plaque,
however,
it is a matter of honor.
Thank you, Wado.
Your generosity speaks
to your great character.
Remember how we handled
our disagreements
when we were in college?
That's how
we'll settle this today!
Are they kidding?
Wado and Takayama?
Drinking?
Stop! Please.
Don't do this because of me!
Drinking like that
is really dangerous!
Don't tell me you're
worried about me now.
Keep dreamin', jerk!
Don't worry about him.
We used to do this
all the time.
Seriously?
That's right.
And Takayama was always
the first to go down.
Is he gonna be okay?
No, Wado is known for
his ability to hold his liquor.
The Director
is at a disadvantage.
This is bad.
What a breathtaking battle
between two
consummate professionals!
Wow. You can smell
the tension.
Sure can.
The food smells great too!
Amazing.
What's going on?
How is he still going?
My god, he won!
Director!
Are you all right?
Oh, my.
Segawa.
Go make sure
Director Wado isn't dead.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
I'm finished here.
There's no reason to stay.
Uh. Okay.
Slow down!
Wait for me!
So you are drunk,
I knew it!
But then,
how could you not be?
I never thought
I'd see you get wasted,
but it's kinda cute.
Did you just call me cute?
Cute.
Next to a primate like you.
Say what?
You're the one who forced
this primate to be your date!
How rude,
no wonder you're single!
I'm not tryin' to be rude.
I like primates.
They're cute.
Wait. You what?
Don't pass out on me!
Guess he didn't have
much of a choice.
Okay, I'm cold!
We've got Rihoko's omelet
and Mari's pizza!
It's hard to decide
which one's tastier!
This one is delectable,
and this one's scrumptious!
You're right!
You're pretty good, kid.
You're not so bad yourself!
Tell me,
how are the girls coming along?
Brilliantly.
We've made progress with the
Cloneblade improvements as well.
But I must have
the original Witchblade
to proceed any further.
I understand.
We should have it to you
very soon.
That's good,
thank you, sir.
The results will surpass
the original in every way.
I look forward to it, my dear.
And this girl
will surpass them all.
[Music]
Why do you drink so much
when you go out, Mom?
You know you shouldn't!
You get drunk so easily!
Look at you!
You're finally
wearing a pretty dress
and it goes to waste!
When you never came home
last night,
Mr. Cho and the others
got pretty worried.
But I'm glad I finally
got to meet your boss!
You talk bad about him
but I really like him!
He's way better than Tozawa!
Probably be even cooler
if he didn't have a hangover!
You should marry him, Mom!