Long sought
by the greed of men,
but bestowed
only upon the women
whose fate
it forever scars.
The Witchblade.
Righteous Sword of God,
or Hand of the Devil himself?
A new Bearer finds out
seeking balance between
ecstasy and ruin.
[Music]
Really?
That's all you've got?
How disappointing.
I expected
so much more from you.
I've got plenty more.
This little dance
is just gettin' started!
If you refuse
to take this seriously,
I won't enjoy killing you.
Then by all means...
let's get serious!
You've got nice moves.
In fact, I think
I'm starting to like you.
Thank you, I'll pass.
Suh-weet!
I won't miss again!
C'mon! Get up!
Those cracks.
I said, get up!
Fight me!
Ah, this is lookin' ugly.
She's gonna
get herself killed.
Wait, is she laughing?
Shiori.
What's the matter?
You can't give up while
we're having so much fun.
Damn. Melony!
Let's move!
Osada! We gotta roll!
We're gone!
She is my prey!
She will not escape!
Shiori! Come back here!
And I thought
I had a scoop before!
This should do it.
How's it look out there?
She's still on our tail.
As long as
the van's armor holds,
we should be fine.
Try'n buy us some time!
Roger that.
Pardon the intrusion.
Is there anything wrong?
No, not at all.
Nothing serious,
but it is urgent.
Accept my apologies,
I must return
to my office right away.
I understand.
I'm glad we had a chance
to talk after all this time.
And I as well.
Now if you will excuse me.
I pray we may
avoid our past mistakes.
And ensure
the tragedy of six years ago
does not repeat itself.
If there is ever a way
I might be able to help you,
please,
do not hesitate to ask.
That man is a lying weasel.
It is inconceivable to me
that he is unaware
of the Cloneblades'
attack on Masane.
However, we're still
claiming ignorance
in regards to the Witchblade.
So we couldn't
rightly call his bluff.
Regardless, we must avoid
direct confrontation
with the NSWF.
It's Doji Group policy.
Since when do you
follow the rules?
What's the current situation?
They're using Emergency
Extraction Route A.
That means they're headed
for the laboratories.
Is that bad?
In this case,
somewhere unaffiliated
with the Doji Group
would be best.
Have you sent
for my cabin cruiser?
I anticipated you might want
to leave before we docked, sir.
I've had her
following us all evening.
All right, we'll meet up
with you there.
And hurry!
Right!
We're on our way!
New plan: Crescent Bridge!
Ah, crap!
She's right on top of us!
See if you can shake her!
Okay, hang on!
Got a stubborn one!
Do it, now!
Damn it!
There's no time.
We're not gonna
make the rendezvous.
Come on!
I found you!
You won't slip away again!
Nine--
Eight--
Seven--
Six--
Five--
Four--
Three--
Two--
One--
Zero!
Oh, man.
It's rainin' scoops!
I gotta check out that van!
Let another team
retrieve the vehicle.
Yes, sir.
Transfer complete, Director.
Good. Move out.
That's enough!
Shiori!
Get a hold of yourself!
Do you know who I am?
Doctor.
Damn it! I can't get anything
through all o' this smoke.
'Sides, who the hell
are these people
with all their resources?
First, an armored van,
and now a cabin cruiser?
What's Melony
gotten herself into?
She's in pretty bad condition.
You'll have to
treat her here.
It's safer if we stay at sea
for a while.
Understood, sir.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine, Doctor.
Really,
you're overreacting,
this isn't necessary.
I just let myself get
a little too worked up, is all.
I hope so,
but I would like to run
a complete checkup.
It gives us important data.
Still...
to have you oversee
my treatment personally.
All right.
Try and get some rest.
'Kay.
Take that sample
down to the lab, if you would.
Make sure to use my name
so it gets priority.
Yes'm.
Oh.
Mom sure is working
really hard.
So I'll work hard too!
Here ya go.
Criminy!
He's got his own room
he doesn't even pay me for,
why's he sleeping out here?
C'mon, ya bum!
Wakey-wakey!
My cafe does not double
as your spare bedroom.
Did uh, Melony
come home last night?
What, you mean,
you were waiting up for her?
You dirty dog, I didn't know
she was your type!
Uh no, it's nothing
like that.
I assure you,
it's purely work-related.
What work?
Sorry, sweetheart,
can't say just yet.
Sounds like
a load o' B.S. to me.
Patience, you'll see.
Good morning, everybody!
You're all looking
a bit pale as usual!
But fear not,
for young Rihoko has prepared
the ultimate breakfast
for each and every one of you!
Voila!
I went a little overboard
and made way too much!
Hey! More is better!
Naomi, darling.
That plate in front of you
is as sad as your precious face!
You need a pick-me-up!
Now you just wait a minute!
Speaking of,
Mari, coffee, please!
Hellooo.
You in there?
Here! Try some!
Uhh, yo...
Do you know if your...
ma ever happened
to make it home last night?
Hm-mm.
She was at work.
At work, huh?
So, what kinda work
does she do exactly?
My mom does odd jobs.
Right now, she's working
at a big important company.
A big important company, huh?
What's it called?
Why are you so curious
about my mom?
Can't tell you now,
ask me later.
Tozawa, my boy!
Rihoko doesn't need to be
around your influence too much,
you're far too old for her!
Yeah, Cho,
you're one to talk.
Yes, but she and I
are friends, right?
Yeah!
Come along, Rihoko.
Let us sit together
and enjoy our meals.
Okay!
I don't care
what this story is.
Leave the kid out.
Got it?
Yeah right, I got it.
Divine!
Oh my, it's, it's delicious!
You think so?
I tried something new
this time,
I put in a touch of mustard!
You are quite the gourmet,
young lady!
Ooh, I tell ya, if only
I were 60 years younger!
Are you sure it's wise
to inhale your food like that?
Back off!
Using the Witchblade always
makes me freakin' starving!
You clearly don't eat
like a person
who almost died last night.
Didn't your mother
teach you how to knock?
Her recovery rate
is truly astounding, Director.
Far better
than we ever expected
of the Witchblade's
capabilities.
That is impressive.
Hey!
Get your hand off me!
Yes, I see.
Her healing rate has increased
rather dramatically.
Send the new data to the lab.
Yes, sir.
That's it!
I've had enough,
I'm not your damn hamster!
Not my hamster?
I believe she meant to say
"guinea pig."
Whatever.
I'm going home now!
Thanks, it's been real!
You might want to look
out the window.
What the hell is this?
We've been at sea all night,
so we're a considerable
distance from shore.
We're on a course
for the harbor now,
but we still have some time
before we arrive.
What the crap?!
I haven't even been able
to talk to Rihoko!
Then, by all means,
give her a call.
Ah, but first let me
change your bandages.
Remove your clothing, please.
I need to see how your wounds
are healing as well.
Are you telling me
you did this?
You needn't be concerned.
I am also a registered nurse.
That's not what I'm...
Oh, great.
And I suppose you were there
for all this too?
Would that have been preferred?
Did you want for me to watch?
Hell no, I didn't!
Wait! Masane!
Get out.
Scumbag-lecher-pervert-freaks!
Icky-icky!!!
I'm a bit concerned.
This type of laceration
should have completely
healed by now.
But it doesn't hurt, Doctor.
Not at all.
I see.
She's clearly undergoing
some kind of change.
But into what?
Are you certain?
Yes ma'am, one of the
groundskeepers just found it.
Call Cadaver Disposal
down in the morgue.
Father will not be pleased
if any commotion is raised
over an incident here.
Best to handle it
quietly in-house.
Y-yes, ma'am.
Doctor...
could it be an X-Con?
That is one possibility.
Then I can go--
Nowhere.
You stay put.
But, I...
That's an order, Shiori.
You're confined to bed
until we get your test results.
Doctor...
If an X-Con were this close,
you and I would have sensed it.
It's something else.
I'm comin'.
Odd Jobs Amaha!
Oh, hi, Mom!
Sure! Mister Cho
and everybody else is here,
so I'm not lonely!
But what about you, Mom?
Are you okay?
Are you eating right?
Uh-huh! Though the food
wasn't near as good
as your cooking.
Stuff at work is taking
a little longer than I expected.
so make sure and tell Mr. Cho
if you need anything.
'Kay. Thank you.
I'll work really hard.
Don't worry about it!
Bye, sweetie!
Y'know...
from this angle,
he's not half bad.
Yes, what is it?
Oh! Uhh...
No, nothing!
Uhh...
just I heard the salt air's
no good for your hair.
So, be careful!
You are one strange woman,
you know that?
Here you are, ensnared
by this bizarre weapon
called the Witchblade,
drawn into deadly battle
night after night,
yet you neither cry nor shout
about the lot you've been given.
Just the money.
Perhaps you simply don't have
the brains to wrap around it.
Wha--? Jeez, rude much?
Of course I wonder.
Every day, I wonder
why I was chosen for this,
whether I can handle it.
I wonder why everyone wants
the Witchblade for themselves.
And?
Well...
What can you do, y'know?
"What can you do?"
Yeah, "what can you do?"
What happens, happens.
What's important to me now
is trying to give Rihoko
the life she deserves.
Admirable.
Then again...
"Then again", what?
Nothin'.
But I'm curious,
does all o' this
qualify me for workers comp?
You want workers comp?
Damn straight I do,
I got injured on the job!
Don't I get
some kind of compensation?
Oh! Runnin' away, eh?
Don't you try'n stiff me!
It appears I was correct.
In the end,
you are simply brainless.
What'd you call me?
Well, you're nothin'
but a cheapskate.
Cheap-cheap-cheap-cheap-
cheap-cheap-cheap!
This pic's the equivalent
of snappin' a live alien or UFO.
Gotta be careful
how I roll with this.
I mean, this is the big scoop
I've been waitin' for, right?
A good first impression
is essential
in your line of work,
Naomi, darling.
Yeah, that's right!
We could do something
with your hair, Miss Naomi.
And I can show you
some makeup tricks
I learned
during my time in France.
They work like magic!
Criminy, he tore
outta here in a hurry.
Like the bum's
got somewhere to be.
Ol' Tozawa hasn't been
hangin' out with us much lately.
Still thinks
he's a reporter.
Figures.
All the signs I see are bad.
Melony's gotta have
some corporate backers
footin' the bill.
'Bout time I found out who.
Structurally, the Cloneblades
are virtually identical
to the Witchblade.
So what's gone wrong?
What is this?
My God!
Are you feeling any better?
Why, yes.
Much.
In fact...
this won't hurt a bit.
How dare he treat me
like some bimbo?
I'm so pissed at that...
that...
Holy crap, is that...?
Out of the way!
Shiori...
Shiori, look at me!
Doctor?
I-I feel weird.
[Music]
Hey, Mom.
I know you're super busy
with work right now,
so I just want to
make sure you know
that I'll be just fine!
I have Mr. Cho
and Miss Mariko here,
so I won't be lonely!
By the way, that Tozawa guy
is totally after you.
And let me tell you,
I do not approve!
I mean,
he's so not your type,
and you can so easily find
somebody way cooler.
But don't worry,
I'll keep an eye on him.
You just focus on your work,
and I'll see you real soon!