This is a DNA
maternity report we received.
What?
How can this be?
[Music]
After going through
the data in this report,
there's no doubt in our minds
that the woman
claiming to be Rihoko's mother
is in fact
her biological parent.
Riko and I aren't related?
Impossible.
This woman...
we'll call her "Ms. S" for now,
said you happened
to pass by her
when the Great Quake hit
six years ago.
In the chaos, she was
separated from her daughter.
She never imagined her child
would still be alive.
But recently,
Ms. S caught sight of Rihoko,
and became convinced
she was her long-lost daughter.
Usually we don't divulge any
information about either party
but I thought
you would want to know.
In any case,
the Child Welfare Ministry feels
it would be in Rihoko's
best interest
to return her
to her biological mother.
You can't.
Ms. Amaha,
I'm sure this must be
difficult for you.
The two of you have lived
as a family all this time.
But isn't it only fair to let
her live with her real mother.
She's my daughter!
My daughter.
And I'm not...
you know
I can never agree to this!
Ms. Amaha.
Her "real mother"?
That's crap.
You're the ones who said
Rihoko was my daughter
in the first place!
And now you wanna
take her away from me?
That was an unfortunate
mistake on our part.
But what else were we to assume
when you were found
with an infant
and a maternity diary?
At that time,
we weren't even aware
that the name "Masane Amaha"
was made-up.
Made-up?
Evidently you had
some problems.
And I'm afraid your memory loss
didn't exactly help the matter.
But I...
I've worked so hard!
Worked to make a life
for Riko and me.
Well, there's no need for you
to worry about that anymore.
What are you saying?
Riko is the only thing
that matters to me!
I understand that.
But please...
Rihoko is still young
and impressionable.
She needs to know the love
of her real mother.
Get out.
I've heard enough.
Get out!
You'll need time
to pack up her belongings,
so I'll leave Rihoko
with you today.
Ms. Amaha, I truly hope
you'll consider
what's best
for Rihoko's happiness.
Goodbye, Rihoko.
I'll be back tomorrow
to pick you up.
Then you'll finally
get to meet your real mother.
Doesn't that sound exciting?
Sorry to disturb you all.
Get the hell out, old bat.
This is just so horrible.
Rihoko, wait!
Mom!
Riko!
You're my real mom,
aren't you?
Tell me that lady
was just lying!
Riko.
I don't want another mom!
I wanna stay with you!
I don't want her
to take me away!
Oh, Riko.
I don't want to be
away from you either.
I never want to let you go.
Y'ask me, Melony,
you shouldn't have to.
Look, you're the one
who raised that child.
Who cares about some broad
that pops up outta nowhere!
She's your kid!
That's what I'm sayin'.
Mister Cho...
Mariko!
Mom, let's run.
That does it!
Don't worry 'bout a thing,
lil ladies!
Leave everything
to Mister Cho!
They're not related?
No, sir.
Apparently,
the girl's biological mother
ran a complete DNA test,
and took the results
to Child Welfare.
Who is she?
The biological mother?
That's kept confidential.
But, I am pulling a few strings
within the department.
Will Masane give the child up?
I assume she has to.
Yes, I see.
And I assume I'll have
that data relatively soon?
Wonderful!
I'll talk to you then.
Here you are.
Get all of my department
managers down here.
I'm starting up a new project.
What kind of project, Director?
I call it
"The Witchblade Project".
Man, it's nothin'
but financial reports.
Let's give this one a shot.
Knock-knock!
Hey there, kiddo.
Think you can
spare me a minute?
Good evening!
Whatcha doin'?
What?
I hate studying!
I'm not gonna!
Stop acting
like a spoiled brat!
Why do you always
have to be such a problem?
As if I'm not stressed enough
with the Cloneblade upgrade.
Who cares about you?
Jerk.
Don't tell me you're
neglecting your studies again?
Father!
Maria, you have
such spectacular intellectual
capabilities, my dear.
You know, if you study,
you can become an even more
exceptional young lady
than you already are.
Will that make you like me?
Of course,
I'll like you even more.
That means you don't
like me at all right now.
Maria.
I know.
What if we gave you
some sort of incentive?
We'll reward you for studying.
Reward?
That's a brilliant idea,
Nishida.
If you could have anything
in this world, Maria,
what would it be?
My Mom.
My mom!
That's what I want!
My mom would like me
no matter what.
I know it.
All right then.
Maria, promise you will devote
yourself to your studies,
and once you're able to wield
the Cloneblade,
I'll tell you all there is
to know about your mother.
How does that sound, dear?
You swear?
I'll do it!
Was that wise?
Making her that promise?
Don't worry, Nishida.
What harm
could there possibly be
in telling the child
about her mother?
Speaking of...
I heard her other child
turned up.
Yes.
Honestly, I cannot believe
she was so foolish.
A mother choosing to deliver
her own child?
How utterly primitive.
You think?
I find it rather intriguing.
Father?
Would you mind if
I borrowed Nora for a while?
Nora?
You have no idea
where they might have gone?
Nope, no idea whatsoever.
Why don't you give up already?
We can't tell ya somethin'
we don't know, lady!
Now listen to me!
If you intentionally
withhold information
about a child who is to be
taken into custody,
you are in violation
of Child Welfare laws.
Hey guys, I'm back.
Melony and the kid are--
Criminy crap.
I demand you tell me
where they are!
We already told ya.
We don't know.
Ahoy, Captain!
Look at all the goodies I got!
We should have a party, huh?
I hope we haven't put you
in a bad spot.
Don't sweat it.
It's kinda crazy.
Who'da thought you gals would
know an old geezer like Cho?
Small world, huh?
He said he was gonna
talk to an old friend but,
I had no idea it was you.
Well, it must be fate.
You ladies are welcome to stay
until things've cooled down.
I won't let anyone
on this boat.
No Child Welfare,
hell, not even the police.
Thank you.
Hey, Captain?
I was wondering.
Does he have a name yet?
Naw, I'm no good
at that kinda stuff, little one.
Then I'll think up
a good one for him!
Come over here, doggie!
She's such a cutie.
I can see why you don't
wanna give her up.
So what should we name you?
My daughter?
My daughter
means everything to me.
She ran away?
Yes, ma'am.
Ms. Sakurai
is looking for her now.
I understand.
Thank you for the call.
Ma'am--
What is she doing?
She knows
Rihoko isn't her child.
Why is she so afraid
of losing her?
I don't understand.
Bunta!
Am I too heavy?
Hey, Riko?
Yeah?
Mommy has to run by the bank
really quick.
Wait here, and I'll
bring ya back a present, okay?
'kay!
Are you certain?
Reina is her biological mother?
Yes.
Shocking, isn't it?
Who would have thought
the reason she vanished
six years ago was because
she was with child?
I don't have any data
on the father yet.
But I do wonder why she went
into seclusion to give birth?
Reina has always
shown an interest
in her own Neo-Gene nature.
Not just physically,
but mentally as well.
It often seemed like
everything about her
was the subject of research.
She wanted to assess
every situation on her own.
Even childbirth.
Oh! Speaking of...
It seems Reina
and the Witchblade
are no longer compatible.
What?
Evidently,
while she was being held,
Masane overheard
one of the scientists.
And she's positive?
I know, let's write a letter
to Mr. Cho
and everyone back home!
Let's see.
"How are you? I'm good."
Must be boring
stuck on this boat all day.
It's fun!
Actually,
I was just writing a letter
to Mr. Cho and the others.
Hey, that's great!
Ya know, my old buddy there's
been over to Cho's place
a whole bunch of times.
I bet he can deliver
that letter for ya.
Really!
You're such a good boy, Bunta!
So, that's his name?
Bunta?
Uh-huh!
Mom!
Back to living
in constant fear again.
I'm sorry, Riko.
Man, am I pooped.
I thought
she would never leave.
I dunno who that broad
thinks she is
bargin' in here like that.
Stupid old bat!
You can come out now, Naomi.
Coast is clear.
The wicked witch is gone.
Puppy!
Hey! How are ya, pal?
That's right.
Riko's supposed to
start school next year.
But the way things are now...
Can I help you find something?
Uh, no, thanks.
Well, that was fast!
Welcome back, Bunta!
Ms. Amaha,
I truly hope you'll consider
what's best
for Rihoko's happiness.
Riko has a "real" mother.
But I don't want
to give her up.
Does that make me selfish?
Then again...
She needs to know
the love of her real mother.
Mom.
Please, mom.
Help me.
Riko!
What do you think
you're doing?
Me?
Nothing.
My job is simply retrieval.
That is my child.
Keep your hands off her.
Father is quite displeased
with your recent behavior.
True.
But I'm still not going to
hand her over to you.
To be honest,
I've always wanted to
have it out with you, Reina.
They say you're the strongest
Neo-Gene on record.
Let's find out.
Ready or not.
Wait! Someone's fighting?
Impressive, Reina.
But I...
I've just begun!
It's beginning.
Goodbye!
Riko!
She's fine.
Did you come here
to save her?
It's only natural
to want to protect
one's own child.
You're Riko's--
Why are you trying
to keep her from me?
Um...
Well, I...
Time to accept
that you're not her mother.
Quite clearly.
Since you didn't care
about leaving her in danger.
I what!
I "didn't care?"
You weren't even there
when she had a cold
and fainted a few days ago.
You mean, you're the one
who helped her then, too?
I only did what
any caring mother would do.
What were you doing?
I was...
Mom.
That you?
Mom!
What's wrong?
Riko...
This lady...
She's your real mother.
You're going to live with her
from now on.
Why! But, Mom!
I thought we decided
to stay together?
C'mon, Mom!
Let's run away again!
I don't wanna live
with anybody else!
Please!
I changed my mind.
We're not really family,
so I'm not going to
take care of you anymore.
It'll be easier for me
if I'm alone.
I won't have to worry
about money so much.
I can go out,
have all the fun I want.
I'm tired of all this.
Hey!
What the hell are you sayin'?
Go.
Hey!
Riko...
I get it.
Listen, your mom...
We can't be together.
You can't be my mom anymore.
'Cause I'm not
really your daughter.
Am I right?
Take her and go.
Go!
So, you ready?
Riko.
If I stay with Mom,
she can never be free.
So we can
never be together again.
Because this lady
is my mom now.
My real mom.
[Music]