Holy crap, haven't seen
anything this rough in awhile.
Me either.
With all this damage,
gotta be automatic weapons.
But I tell ya, I got no idea
how they pulled this off.
Yeah, no kiddin'.
This ain't no ordinary murder.
There's gotta be a reason
they wrecked the place.
Detective Nakata!
[Music]
The ammunition found
at the crime scene
was a type specifically
used by the military.
And the only outfit
in Japan who uses 'em
is Doji Industries.
This ain't
the kinda firepower
just anyone
can get their hands on,
so that's what led me to you.
These recent murders
would've been impossible
for Joe Public.
In fact, the only way
that coulda been the case
is if the perps had access
to military-grade weaponry.
Follow my logic?
I must say
I'm quite impressed.
You sound just like
the detectives I see on TV!
Yeah, thanks.
Look, Director Takayama,
I'm not tryin' to accuse
any of your employees
of murder here.
I'm just sayin' there
may be some kinda connection.
Meaning what?
Meaning,
maybe weapons were stolen,
or an ex-employee
leaked some top secret data.
There could be
some psycho out there
building replicas
of your weapons right now.
That's absurd!
The Doji Group's security
is flawless.
Our corporate secrets would
never be leaked to the outside.
I'll advise our staff
to be more strict
with their
information management.
Is that all, Detective?
That could have gone better.
I don't think
he bought it for a second.
I'm sure he'll be back.
And he'll get the same answers.
Doji Industries
will never be prosecuted.
I imagine the detective
is aware of that.
He must enjoy wasting his time.
Forget him.
Back to the investigation.
Yes, sir.
Who did this?
If the killer wasn't
an X-Con or a Neo-Gene...
We heard anything
from the lab yet?
They're takin'
their sweet time as usual, sir.
Check that attitude!
Why you always
gotta pick on the new guy?
Damn.
Gotta find some
honest-to-god hard evidence.
Something this big
can't stay hidden forever.
I'm sure those Doji bastards
are corrupt.
I heard they're connected
to all kinds of politicians
and police officials.
I guess there's not
a whole lot we can do.
Do you not get
how this detective thing works?
Ass.
Ta-da!
Aren't you pretty!
That dress is absolutely
adorable on you, Rihoko!
Wow, not too shabby, Melony.
You actually did some
decent shopping for once.
The sales ladies picked out
pretty much everything.
I just paid for it.
Thanks, Mom.
I love it!
Just you wait!
We're not done yet, kiddo.
There's still
a whole 'nother bag!
Check it out!
I got you shoes, socks,
a scarf, and a hat!
Oh, my.
And take a look at this!
Holy cow, she must be
rollin' in the dough.
Criminy.
How much cash did you drop
on your shopping spree?
Well, I started out
with a hundred thousand yen,
and now there's this much, so...
Whoa! I've spent
a lot of money.
Hey, mom.
I really like
all the new clothes and stuff,
but don't waste
your money on me.
Don't be silly!
It's not a waste
if I'm buying something special
for my little girl!
But...
It's okay.
I promise everything'll be fine,
so don't get upset.
I would do anything for you,
so don't you worry
about a thing!
But, Mom...
Now, why don't you try
something else on?
Let's see Princess Rihoko
in this one.
Isn't it cute?
You're my little girl...
Oh man,
Melony sure is worried
about keepin'
that little one happy.
No kiddin'.
See? Now don't you think
it was worth it?
You'll never
defeat an opponent like that.
Apart from allowing yourself
to be hit first,
your problem is,
your recovery time
is too slow.
I gave you the chance to counter
and you didn't.
Just keep your cool and watch
your opponent's every move.
Thank you, ma'am.
I know you can do it.
You just need
confidence in yourself.
You are one
of the chosen ones.
Like me.
Yes!
I'll admit
I had my concerns about Maria.
But she is maturing
into a fine young woman.
It would appear that Maria
has finally reached adulthood.
Yes, splendid.
Using her as the new mother,
we'll create
an even more perfect being;
her genes will take us
to the next level.
You want to advance to
the next generation of Sisters?
Yes, begin the preparations
immediately.
I expect great things.
Then you'll be disappointed.
As long as we use
your paternal genes,
the results
will remain the same.
This is not what
I wanted to create.
But the true Witchblade's
chosen bearer...
what do her genetics
look like?
This was the only real evidence
found at the crime scene.
Man, talk about overkill.
Why would the killer
purposefully leave
those shell casings?
I mean, that's some
incriminating evidence, sir.
Maybe the killer ain't
afraid of gettin' caught.
Then he wouldn't care what
kinda evidence he left behind.
Detective. Here.
This was sent to the task force
this morning.
We checked. The contents
aren't hazardous.
Yeah?
Where's it from?
No return address.
The hell?
Some sort of data, perhaps.
Who knows, maybe
someone sent us a tip?
Dumbass!
Just check and see
what's on 'em!
They appear to be video files.
Watch.
Some sort of cleanup crew?
Whoa! Take a look at that!
What the hell is it?
Some kinda monster?
But check out their van!
Maybe they're some kind of
special effects crew.
But this obviously
took place in the city.
Hold on!
Look!
This is near crime scene
number five.
Damn it.
This is bigger than I thought.
Detective Nakata!
The media's in a frenzy
about somethin'!
In these recordings,
which seem to have taken place
at various crime scenes,
we can see multiple workers
recovering
some sort of machinery.
Now, who these workers
are affiliated with
still remains a mystery.
Like many other news agencies,
this footage,
which we received this morning,
was sent to our studio
by an anonymous source.
Wha--What does all this mean,
Detective?
Have those files
analyzed immediately!
I want IDs on every car
and every person, yesterday!
Uh, yes, sir!
Contact the D.A.
Start preparing for a raid.
A raid!
What's the target, Detective?
Wait.
You got it, kid.
If my hunch is right,
those bastards work for Doji.
About all we can verify
at this point,
is that this footage
was simultaneously sent
to all news media outlets,
and was also uploaded
to numerous major Internet
news sites and message boards.
But the question remains:
What exactly are we seeing here?
There are hundreds of people
on the 'net
attempting to identify
these workers
and the vehicles
involved.
Many are also claiming
that the vehicles
are somehow connected
to the military industry.
Well, it certainly seems
we're dealing
with a large-scale
investigation--
Who the hell leaked that video?
While we can't divulge the name
of the company just yet,
we have been told the machinery
being recovered--
Hey, wait a minute!
Aren't those our I-Weapons?
So they're employees
of the Special Section?
No, sir.
Well, yes, the footage does show
employees of our company.
Yes sir,
but it's not as bad as--
I refuse to cover up
for your mistakes any longer.
Now the whole world knows
what Doji is up to.
The police are
threatening to raid
the Doji Industries building!
I can't be involved.
But sir, if you would just--
Hello?
Damn.
Sure, no problem
taking the bribe,
but you run
as soon as things get tough.
What the hell
was Takayama doing?
Yagi.
Have you calmed down a bit?
Any new developments?
We administered
a strong tranquilizer
and it appears to be
restraining the Blade for now.
Terrifying.
To think it would go this far.
We've noticed
his physical breakdown
is progressing rapidly.
At its current rate,
his crystallization
should occur
in only a matter of days.
I suppose we've seen the limits
of what can be achieved
with an untrained civilian.
But the Ultimateblade itself
still has incredible
untapped power.
Uh, sir,
it's none of my business
but are you sure it was
a good idea to leak those files?
What if this becomes
a company-wide problem--
We had no choice!
There was no other way!
His escape caused us
a great deal of trouble
that we did not need!
Too late to change
anything now.
There's no turning back.
The Special Division
will take the fall for us.
And Takayama
will take the full blame.
Yeah. Uhh...
I got a search warrant, kid.
Lemme through.
Director Takayama.
This time I'm not leavin' 'til
I get a confession out of you.
Local police
have just made their way
into the Doji Group Industries
building.
According to officials,
the company is accused
of attempting to cover up
a string of murders
that were allegedly caused
by their special
top-secret weapons.
They do nothin' but build
murder weapons!
Doji should pay
for their crimes!
They're a threat not only
to this nation's citizens
but to the entire world!
Production of these
top-secret weapons
is handled by
Doji's Special Division.
Its director, Mr. Takayama,
is under fire
because officials believe
it was his recklessness
that led to this situation.
Sorry, kiddo, you must be pretty
bored watchin' the news.
Let's go to my place
and watch some cartoons.
Sure, but...
Yeah.
No luck. Can't seem
to get through.
Guess I'll have to go
down there myself, huh?
Go? Where, to Doji?
C'mon, Melony!
Dontcha think maybe you should
wait til this mess clears up?
It's a zoo
over there right now!
Well, I can't sit here
and hope somebody calls me.
I'm just gonna go
check it out real quick.
Not a good idea!
Hey.
Nice work there,
Detective Nakata!
You got no business here.
Scram!
C'mon, no need
to be like that.
Thanks to you and your boys
stickin' your noses in,
I already lost
the one big scoop I had.
You're not smart enough
to figure out
who was behind
those murders, Junior.
You're right,
'cause I'd never guess
rogue weapons from Doji
Industries were who did it.
"Who"
is not exactly appropriate.
We're talkin' about runaway
machines, not real people.
Not real people?
Somethin' you wanna tell me?
No, not at all.
So, can't you at least arrest
the Doji guys responsible?
They should get Gross
Negligence and Manslaughter.
But since all of this
was supposedly an accident
that happened
during the Quake,
I'm sure they'll use
the Great Quake Act
to escape any charges.
And that's why you're in
such a rotten mood today,
huh, Detective?
Better get outta here
before ya take it out on me.
Hey!
I guess they still haven't
figured out the craziest part.
That the X-Cons and I-Weapons
are created
using deceased humans.
That means my scoop
isn't completely dead yet.
But if this keeps up,
things could start to get
real ugly for Melony.
We have just been informed
that members of Doji Industries'
Special Division...
I can't believe
they got the names
of our entire recovery team.
I doubt the men in that footage
can avoid being arrested.
As for us,
it depends whether
the police feel
we're responsible.
Sorry I'm late.
Ah, Takayama.
They've finished
questioning you already?
Why don't we cut to the chase?
Takayama, would you explain
what's going on?
Mistakes like this
are not like you.
The damage this will have
on the Doji Industries brand
is unfathomable.
Our stocks are plummeting!
By this afternoon, we've already
lost well into the billions!
How do you intend to bring
this situation under control,
Takayama!
While I realize
the Special Division
is one of Doji's major branches,
they've always held
enormous sway in the company's
decision making.
But that man
and his reckless practices
are clearly the cause
of this dilemma!
If you do not trim back
its overgrown branches,
the growth of an entire tree
can be undermined!
What are you
so afraid of, Wado?
I'm not afraid!
Have I ever--!
Wado, please.
Try to calm yourself.
I know it's easy to be shaken
by all that's happened today.
But it is impossible
for Doji's foundation
to be weakened.
This situation is but one
of the scenarios I anticipated.
Are you saying you've
already devised a strategy?
Chopping off a single branch
will not kill the tree.
I am in agreement with Wado.
Takayama...
are you saying...?
'Scuse me!
Let me through, please!
Who're you, lady?
I don't suppose
you work for Doji, do ya?
You work for
those war mongering devils?
All you murderers
are gonna burn in hell!
Hands off, buddy!
What the hell'd
I ever do to you?
Leave me alone.
Why should we?
You wanna go!
What do you think
you're doing?
Honestly, trying to waltz
through the front door?
What has come over you?
Well, I wouldn't have had to
if I knew
where the back door was.
Then I'll show it to you.
All of the employees
are using it now.
You can't be so reckless.
So is Doji gonna be all right?
I mean, all this stuff
has gotten out.
Don't worry.
Large corporations like Doji
have their own
unique ways of survival.
Pardon the intrusion.
Hey, wait.
Aren't you that guy?
Ah, yes.
And you're the girl
from my award party.
Oh dear.
I'd never suspect you were
the bearer of the Witchblade.
Where's Takayama?
He's no longer with Doji.
What are you saying?
So it's true that weapons
from Doji Industries
are responsible for the murders
of innocent citizens?
What does the company
intend to do
to put the public at ease
after these attacks?
I have only one thing to say.
My name is Reiji Takayama,
Director of
Doji's Special Division,
and I accept
full responsibility.
As such,
I take this opportunity
to tender
my immediate resignation.
That is all.
Takayama quit his job?
Correct.
All Witchblade-related affairs
previously handled
by the Special Division
will be now handled
by my Bio-Division.
Segawa will continue on
to take care
of the business side of things.
I'm looking forward
to continuing our work together,
Masane.
Wait a minute.
So basically, I've been
switched from Takayama to you,
just like that?
We require the Witchblade
in order to continue
our research.
We'd like to mass produce
the UltimateBlade
but we still have
a few issues.
What we're saying
is that, for now,
we still have
plenty of work for you.
Isn't that great?
Screw a whole bunch of that.
I'm outta here!
What about Rihoko?
Doji will go on
with or without you.
If you quit now, the only one
who stands to suffer is her.
I understand you were
attached to Takayama.
But business is business
and we need you, Miss Amaha.
The Bio-Division
promises good pay
and that would benefit
both you and your daughter.
Rihoko.
Do it for her.
So in the end,
it looks like
the Director's
gonna take the fall,
and Doji's gonna stay
safe and sound.
Man, the corporate world
is cold-blooded.
Hey, mom!
Welcome home!
Why're you gettin' home
so late, Melony?
We were startin' to worry.
Sorry.
We had to talk over
what happens next.
Did you see Mr. Takayama there?
No, but I'm sure
he's just fine.
Don't worry
about a thing, Riko;
I promise
I'll take care of you.
Okay.
We'll be fine.
I know
we can make it through this
as long as the two of us
are together.
I'll always be here
to protect you.
[Music]
Hey mom, I don't wanna be mean
but I'm kinda mad at you.
Your boss, Mr. Takayama,
is in big trouble
and you don't even
seem to care!
Aren't you worried about him?
And why're you still
working for that company?
Have you forgotten
about Mr. Takayama?
You've been acting
real strange lately, Mom.
Somehow you're different,
not like your usual self.
Don't do something
you don't think is right
just for my sake.
Please, Mom.