Startin' today, I'm chargin'
for all the meals Rihoko makes.
Say what?
I'm sorry.
Mariko said making
all those meals for free
was hurting her business.
That's harsh!
You're damn straight.
Morning!
I'm off to work!
Mom! Wait!
Man!
[Music]
She skipped out
on breakfast again.
What's with the get-up?
It's so not her.
Melony said she got moved
to Secretary Division.
And man, is her wardrobe
sufferin' for it.
Her new boss is either
blind or dead.
My instincts
must've been way off.
I was sure Melony
and that Takayama fella--
Were gonna get married
someday?
Hold on, kiddo, don't ya think
you're movin' a little fast.
But I really liked him
that time
when he stayed the night
'cause he was too drunk.
So, you like
the strong, silent type,
is that it, Rihoko?
I'm a little surprised.
Don't be silly;
I just like him for Mom.
He's a nice man!
Oh! A nice man, huh?
Mom would always talk
about Mr. Takayama before bed.
How he's cheap,
and always gloomy,
and he's gonna go bald one day.
Are you sure
those aren't insults?
But now she doesn't talk
about him at all.
It's almost like she's
not worried about him anymore.
It's weird.
Breathtaking view, isn't it?
Takayama would often
stand there and--
Segawa,
I'd rather not hear that name
first thing in the morning.
My apologies, sir.
I'll get right into it:
at 10 am,
you're scheduled to meet
with the Bio Division
and Special Division personnel
to officially inform them
of the planned merger.
Though it's more like
the Special Division
is being "absorbed"
than anything.
It can't be helped.
It's company policy.
You know, I'm impressed
with your ability
to switch sides so quickly.
Especially after
your years with Takayama.
My job has always been
to act as an assistant
to Doji's Directors.
There was no "side" to "switch."
I see.
Well, this is
certainly convenient
seeing as my secretary
resigned recently.
Yagi quit so suddenly.
Do you know what happened?
I do not.
Good morning, I'm here!
You're three minutes late.
I'm sorry, sir!
Listen, Amaha, unlike
your previous employer,
I'm not paying you anything
if you don't follow my rules.
I'm sorry.
Your attire
is passable for today.
However, that will not work
for the party tomorrow.
What party?
I have to attend
a party tomorrow
for a teacher I'm indebted to,
and you shall escort me.
With you?
Are you serious?
What's the matter?
Having trouble
following orders?
No, sir.
I'll be there.
Shall I take care of her
clothing selection?
Yes, go see to it.
I did it!
If Takayama only knew.
The Witchblade, the woman,
and the secretary.
All of them belong to me now!
All finished.
I'll combine this
with Maria's genes right away
to create a new Sister.
This may be
the last time we do this.
I feel certain the next Sister
will be perfect.
Yes, Father.
I am inclined to believe
you are correct.
Aoi...
Do you know what Grandfather
is trying to do
by creating the Sisters?
Um...
He's trying to create the
perfect human being, isn't he?
No, that's what the NSWF
is trying to accomplish.
Grandfather has a different
reason for creating the Sisters.
Different?
You know Sister-related
research is top priority
for all Japanese NSWF branches.
Yes, ma'am?
They're doing all this
top-secret research
so that Grandfather
can have a mother again.
So he can have a mother again?
You mean--?
He was so cold
when I wanted to find my mom,
and all this time
he's been searching for his own.
Oh, Mother.
He's nothing but a pathetic,
selfish old man.
Miss Maria!
You really shouldn't talk
about Father that way!
Why not?
It's the truth.
All Grandfather really has
is power.
The power to get anything
and everything he wants.
But, you said
that we have power too,
because you and I
are the chosen ones.
Power comes in many forms.
Yo! So the big corporate
secretary's on her way home?
C'mon.
Don't ignore me!
What do you want?
I'm here to pick you up.
Now get in.
So, why're you even still
working at Doji?
Things're gettin' ugly
over there.
Might be a good time to quit.
You're the last person
I'd take advice from.
Hey, now.
I know the dirt
on those I-Weapons, too.
The X-Cons've caused
enough trouble as it is.
If word gets out that Doji's
turning corpses into weapons,
it's all over.
Well, I've got job security
until then.
The pay is real good.
I'm not gonna quit.
So it's for Rihoko?
Yeah. And from now on,
I'm doing things my way.
Ya know, you've kinda been
on edge the past few days.
Baby, I'm home!
Smells great!
I'm starving.
Hello, welcome home.
Good to see you again.
Kyoko, hey!
Hey, Mom!
Are you surprised?
Yeah, um...
I'm working on a story.
Since I was
in the neighborhood,
I figured I'd drop by.
So I asked Tozawa if he would
pick you up from work today
so you could get home faster!
There you have it.
C'mon, Melony!
Join us for a drink or two!
I suppose this merger means
you'll have twice the workload,
if not more.
Aren't you worried
you'll be overwhelmed?
No, I handled twice as much
before I even became a director.
Sounds as though
you've worked hard
to get where you are;
how inspiring.
I simply do the work that
nobody else wants to touch.
You could have an office
with a view like this yourself
if you worked hard enough.
I never acquired
a taste for hard work.
Besides,
if I ever made it this far up,
I'd always be worried
about who might push me off.
Are you suggesting I'll follow
in Takayama's footsteps?
I meant in general.
People in power always have
other people behind them,
and those who have fallen
often come crawling back up.
What are you
so afraid of, Wado?
So much responsibility,
and always
having to watch your back.
I could never do it.
Your ability to grasp power
so fearlessly is amazing, sir.
A person attempting to
"grasp power"
should always have
that level of resolve.
"Those who've fallen
often come crawling back up."
Don't even try it, Takayama.
Miss Kyoko,
how's Yuuki doing?
Oh, just great!
She really misses you though.
You should come
and visit her sometime.
That'd be fun!
We should plan another
group date soon, too!
Yeah.
One of these days.
So I'm curious.
Why's Chief Editor Kyoko
out workin' a story by herself?
Is it somethin' big?
More like a follow-up
to something big.
The guy who resigned from Doji,
Reiji Takayama?
A man at the very top,
who, in a single day,
lost everything.
Wouldn't it be
fascinating to know
what was going through his mind
at the time?
So I--
What's the matter?
Is there something wrong?
Oh no, no, not at all.
So tell me...
have you seen this Takayama?
No. He left the hotel
he was living in.
But I have an idea
where I might find him.
I want to talk to people
around town first,
get a better feel for the guy.
Is this gonna be
a negative write-up?
I'm not sure.
I haven't met him yet.
The media's been pretty harsh
on him so far.
Painting him
as this cold-hearted elitist;
a man who sees everything
as numbers.
They think his disappearance
could be evidence of suicide.
He would never do that!
I'm sure he must be
real depressed right about now,
but he's not the kinda guy
who would kill himself.
And he's not some elitist
who's never dealt with
suffering.
His mother died
when he was young,
so he's always felt alone.
Buuut, I wouldn't
call him cold-hearted,
a cheapskate, maybe.
I mean, he's a pretty decent guy
once you get to know him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Masane, did you just say
you know him?
And quite well,
it would seem.
Um. What?
Okay, I see what's going on.
I guess your instincts
were right on the money.
Of course they were!
Hey, no wait, what?
What instincts?
Oh, Mom! You really do like
Mr. Takayama after all!
What?
Riko!
What would make ya think that?
What a relief!
Since you don't talk
about him all the time anymore,
I thought you weren't
even worried about him!
Jeez, who says I'm worried?
Well, you were talking
about him awful passionately.
Suddenly
I can see a pink aura.
Quit makin' crap up!
What's going on?
C'mon, Mom. You should quit
working for that new boss;
he's a jerk.
Enough, Riko.
Before I get angry.
But Mister Takayama
is way better!
He is not!
Is too!
Is not!
You're too young to
understand these things!
No, Mom, you don't understand!
Stop trying to tell me
how to deal with my job!
But, Mom!
Rihoko!
Now calm down, you two!
Chill out, ladies.
That's enough.
C'mon, kiddo.
You're just being stupid!
I hate you.
Now, now, Rihoko.
That mouth!
Honestly, I feel like
I don't even know you anymore!
I don't know you
anymore either!
Melony, hold on!
Can't we be mature 'bout this?
Guess not.
Kyoko, hey.
Do you mind if I come in?
I really made an ass
o' myself out there.
Forget it.
Kids can be scary.
Especially little girls.
They tend to be
surprisingly sensitive
to their parents' emotions.
I don't have a thing
for Takayama, I'm just...
Concerned?
Well, like I said, I think
I have a pretty good idea
where you can find him.
No, I don't think
that's such a good--
It's because of Rihoko, right?
You know, there was a time
when I overworked myself
for my girl's sake.
All that did was make our love
into a one-way street.
She missed
having her mom around.
Sometimes it's good to listen
to what our children
have to say.
Riko?
Listen, Riko.
I think I'd like
to visit Takayama.
Would that be okay with you?
Yeah, Mom, of course!
I might lose my job.
Don't worry!
If they fire you, I can sell
box lunches to make money!
Riko.
Thank you.
Oh, brother.
Guess I got no choice.
C'mon.
I'll drive you over there.
No umbrella, sorry.
Ah, don't worry about it.
Thanks again.
Yeah, yeah,
just hurry inside.
You're getting soaked.
Yeah.
See ya later!
Uh, hi.
How's it goin'?
What could you possibly
want at this hour?
That's the greeting I get!
I came to visit
because I've been
worried sick about you!
Well, I must've hit rock bottom
if you're worried about me.
Come on in.
He is so not cute.
People are allowed to
get depressed - even you.
I'd be lying
if I said I wasn't upset.
Guess I really cared
for that company.
Never realized how much.
And you protected
the company you love.
That's a good thing.
Why not get a clean start
in a new business?
Sitting in an office,
barking orders all day
was only making you bald.
Besides, I just don't think
you're much of
a "suit and tie" kinda guy.
Is this supposed to be
making me feel better?
I dunno, is it workin'?
Not at all.
Maybe if you try not talking.
What!
I'm trying to help!
You can help by shutting up.
Oh, I see.
Fine, then. I'll leave!
You know it's pouring.
Maybe I like the rain!
Balding jerk!
What the hell?
Let me go!
I told you I'm leaving!
Goodbye!
What was--
This isn't why I--
Yagi.
I'm doing my best to turn you
back to a normal man again
but there's an obstacle
in our way.
And as long as
that obstacle exists--
Taka-yama. Taka-yama.
Yes! Good work;
you catch on fast, Yagi!
Hey! I'm back.
This one's on the house.
Heartbreak and alcohol
go hand-in-hand, right?
So where's your daughter
right now?
Riko?
The folks back at our building
are watching her.
Oh, I see.
Reiji...
Rihoko is your daughter,
isn't she?
Yes, she is.
Then I think
you need to tell her.
I can't.
I have no idea
how to interact with her.
And to be honest,
it doesn't even feel
like she's mine.
Pretty pathetic excuse
for a father, aren't I?
I used to be the same way,
you know.
But once you sit down
and talk with her,
I'm sure you'll feel better.
Get down!
Are you alright?
Masane!
I'm going!
Always in the way.
I'm gonna kill
Director Takayama!
I'll do it with my bare hands!
Why don't you
have a go at me first.
Why not?
Sounds fun!
Masane!
Damn!
No!
He's gonna kill me!
I need more.
More power!
Don't worry.
It'll all be over soon!
Masane!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Really, it was nothing.
I assume everything
went as planned?
Yes Father, in several months,
a new Sister will be born.
Maria.
My dear.
Nothing makes me happier than
to see how you have blossomed.
Maria...
It's time to reward you again
for all your hard work.
What do you want?
Anything at all.
There is one thing.
And what is that?
Your power.
Maria.
Sorry, Grandfather,
but I will obtain what I desire.
And I mean,
everything I desire.
Maria.
You are marvelous, my dear.
Truly marvelous.
I have no doubt the next
Sister born will be perfect.
You are a fool, Father.
That is not your genetic stock
inside those capsules.
We can't go on like this.
No further progress
can be made
with the continued use
of your genes.
What do you mean, Nishida?
Why didn't you use my genes?
Tell me!
Why?
It can't be!
How could you?
I was supposed
to be born again!
I need the perfect mother!
How else will my true self
be born?
How could you do this!
No!
You have to redo it!
Do it again!
You have to!
Mother!
So pathetic!
Aoi, we're done here.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, Chief Nishida.
Don't go anywhere.
You may still be
of some use to me.
Such ferocity.
Such unbridled power.
At last, you are complete.
Maria.
[Music]
Hey, Riko!
Wanna go on a date?
Well, not a date-date.
You wanna go to dinner
with Takayama?
Remember how you told me
you really liked him?
Well, he told me
he wants to be friends with you!
He said he'll take you
anywhere you wanna go!
And if you want anything,
I'm sure you'll have no problem
sweet-talkin' him out of it!
Just let him spoil you, okay?
And even though
it might be difficult,
try not to think of him
as my boss.
I know you guys are gonna
like each other a whole bunch!