What are all these?
They're the data files
on the mothers.
Check it out.
What? The mothers?
These are the women
who provided their genetic stock
to create the newest
generation of Neo-Genes.
This is her.
This is my mom!
Okay.
We've kept
our end of the bargain.
Now let us get our readings.
It's imperative now that you're
wearing the Cloneblade.
I have such high hopes
for you, Maria.
You may well be
the perfect Neo-Gene.
I know who my mom is.
I know now.
[Music]
I gotta try to stop
thinkin' about her.
My breakdown
is progressing quickly.
Deterioration of my mental
condition has also begun.
However, the sensation is not
as unpleasant as anticipated.
In fact, it feels rather nice.
Could this have been
how Shiori felt
when she began to break down?
Or is this sensation instead
a result of some other factor?
Perhaps my latent
maternal instincts.
It's unknown.
Sorry, no Kahlua.
This place...
It's so quiet.
Yeah.
That's why my old man
bought this place out here.
So...
all of this...
Was this just...
to comfort me?
Well, uh--
Never mind.
You don't have to tell me.
Hey, what's up?
Finally, I got through!
Where the hell are you?
Um, around.
Listen, you gotta
go get Rihoko right now!
Check this out.
The NSWF's sisters aren't
just a group of random chicks
with good breeding.
They put their own genes
back in the mix,
as the mothers
of the next wave.
It's some weird-ass,
jacked-up inbreeding thing.
Inbreeding? What?
This is what I got so far.
Basically, these "sisters"
are all created
using the genes
from the same "father."
So, each new generation
may have new mother genes,
but they keep usin'
the same dude.
This guy's like the father,
husband and grandpa
to all these girls.
See what I mean by jacked-up?
From what I can tell, there's
only one prime candidate.
The father's "Father."
Are you serious?
I dunno what
the old guy's up to,
but it can't be
anything good.
And though she may have
walked away from the NSWF,
that Reina Soho chick
is still one of the sisters.
She's still a part
of all this craziness.
You have got to
get Rihoko back!
There's no way you can
leave her with that monster.
Hey Melony,
are you listenin' to me?
If she's a monster, so am I.
What are you sayin'?
I'm not fit to be her mother,
I never was.
Melony!
Damn it!
What the hell
has gotten into her?
Not fit to be her mom, my ass.
What was that about?
He told me
I have to take Rihoko back
because Reina's a monster.
Like I can
really judge her for that.
Look at me.
Reina was there
to save Rihoko's life.
Not once, but twice.
Besides, Reina is rich.
She's a doctor,
and above all else,
she's Riko's biological mother.
I'm pretty certain
she can make Rihoko much happier
than I ever could.
If you truly think that,
you have nothing more
to worry about.
Yeah, right.
Here's your breakfast, Maria.
Dr. Nishida is going to be
out on business for the day.
So she told me
you can take today off.
Seriously?
I can get the car and take you
shopping if you'd like.
No thanks!
I'll just stay here and play.
Fine, I'll be back
to check on you later.
She's my mom.
So she has to be with me!
You do know
it's against regulations
to copy personal data,
don't you?
I'm just takin' a few notes.
That stuff is really
not supposed to be seen
by outsiders.
Like you weren't supposed
to be seen with that chick?
Bet your wife would love to see
the shots I got of you two.
Here we go!
Um...
are you feeling better now?
Y'know, 'cause you weren't
feeling good last night.
Oh, right.
It was nothing.
I'll be just fine.
Stay here.
Hi, Mom!
What is that?
Tell me.
I've never seen
that version of the blade.
And I don't recognize her.
She's a next generation
Neo-Gene.
What do you want?
What is that thing?
This girl is my daughter.
Your what?
No, she can't be.
And you can't be her mom
because you're mine.
My mom!
This one is dangerous.
She has no boundaries.
I remember from that file.
I get it now.
That must be
my big sister, right?
That's right.
Why is it so scrawny?
It's because
she was born naturally.
The file said it was dead.
Then the file is incorrect.
Or perhaps
it was altered on purpose.
I don't care
about your excuses!
Go to the garage
and wait in the car.
Go.
Why don't you try to calm down
and we'll have a nice talk.
I need to go out
and do some shopping.
Do you mind
waiting here for a while?
Okay!
Wow! Is all this stuff for me?
Wait a minute.
They belong to it.
They lied to me.
It's all a big lie.
This isn't the way
that everything
was supposed to work out.
Why?
Tell me.
I trained
and I studied so hard.
So I could find out
who my mom is.
I wanna know.
Why is my mom living here
with that thing?
Why won't she give me
a big hug and a kiss?
Why, Mom?
Why!
That girl.
Such incredible power.
No. No, damn it!
Don't die on me now!
Time to die.
Ah, dammit!
What is it?
I dunno.
Something just...
An X-Con?
Neo-Gene?
I can't really tell.
It's too far away.
But it's...
My god, it's powerful.
She's coming!
Should, um...
Should we maybe
just walk back?
We can't do that.
Why not?
I have little chance of
defeating someone so powerful.
But...
Stay right here, Rihoko.
Where are you going?
Do as I say. Stay here!
Okay.
It'll be all right.
I promise
I'll come back for you.
She kinda reminded me
of Mom just then.
A second generation
Neo-Gene has appeared.
And for some reason,
I am its target.
Therefore I have chosen
to split up with Rihoko.
It'll be all right.
I promise
I'll come back for you.
Why did I make a promise
that I cannot keep?
You're my mom.
That certainly
appears to be the case.
Genetically, at least.
That thing is over there,
isn't it?
I'm gonna
get rid of it forever.
No, little girl.
You will not.
You hate me, too.
Why, Mom?
You're not supposed
to hate me.
You're my mom!
Why? Tell me why!
Okay, fine.
I'll get rid of you too!
I can feel it, can you?
I can feel it!
Are those monsters?
Rihoko!
It's me!
Tozawa! Hi!
I'm so glad to see you.
But what're you doin'
all the way out here?
It's kinda hard
to explain, kiddo.
Stop the car!
What's wrong?
I can feel it.
Rihoko's in danger!
The same feeling
you had before?
So what now?
You said you were
an unfit mother.
Riko!
Well, that answers my question.
Stop dodging, Mom!
When you make me miss,
I get angry!
Aw man, way too easy.
Somethin' smells good over here.
Where's it comin' from?
Tozawa, are those...?
Yep, they're monsters, kiddo.
People say they don't exist
but I've seen plenty of 'em.
Don't worry, I gotcha.
Now, that looks good!
I will not let you
harm my daughter!
Hey?
You done already?
Guess I'll go and have my fun
with that other thing.
Let go!
Why're you trying to stop me?
Good question.
I wish I had an answer for you.
You're weak.
You can't be my mom.
Why'd you do that to me?
It hurts.
You have incredible power,
but you mustn't abuse it.
If you do not learn control,
it is pointless.
There she is!
Begin retrieval!
Ma'am,
what about the other one?
There's no need
to waste your time.
It'll be all right.
Your mom's on her way, okay?
Mom's comin'?
You bet she is.
Takin' care of nasty monsters
like them is part of her job.
No way.
I'm serious!
She's comin' here?
But she's not
comin' to see me.
'Cause she's not my mom anymore.
That's not true!
Why do you think
she's been out every night
doin' such dangerous work?
She does it for you.
She always has!
Don't you get it, kid?
The reason she fights
is to keep you safe.
Your mom loves you
more than anything.
Promise.
Riko!
Is that mom?
Mommy.
Mommy!
Mom!
Riko!
Are you all right?
I'm better now!
Mommy!
It hurts.
Mom.
Reina?
It is you!
Let's get you
to my recovery team!
Thank you,
but there's no need.
There's nothing they can do.
I'm almost out of time.
Where's Rihoko?
She's safe.
I'm glad.
Reina...
You have to give her back.
That's fine.
I've concluded my research.
Do whatever you want with her.
Thank you.
You know, that's the first time
I've ever felt pleasure
while fighting.
Was it because of my breakdown,
or because
I was protecting her?
I've spent all this time
studying myself,
and I still don't understand.
I thought I understood,
for a time.
Reiji...
I once felt this inexplicable
emotion for you.
Now I wish I had shared it
with you sooner
but this feeling,
I'll never forget it.
[Music]
Great news, Riko!
Mr. Cho's taking us
to the beach!
I'm sure he just wants to
see me in my swimsuit
but he's harmless, right?
Oh, and a friend of Tozawa's
is gonna come with us.
And she's bringing
her daughter,
who's just a few years
older than you.
This is gonna be so much fun!
I can't wait!
I could never take you
cool places before
but I'm gonna make sure we do
all kinds of fun stuff now!
I'm gonna work hard
so we can go wherever we want!