Sought by the greed of men
since the dawn of humankind,
but only bestowed upon the women
whose fate it forever scars.
The Witchblade.
Is it the Righteous Sword
of God,
or the Hand of the Devil
himself?
Now a new Bearer
has been chosen.
And she must discover
the answers for herself.
As she stands
on the brink of destiny,
she is forced
to seek the balance
between ecstasy and ruin.
[Music]
Wake up.
You gotta wake up.
Come on!
You hear me?
Wake up!
Mommy!
Come on,
wake up already!
Just a few more minutes, 'kay?
Wake up, Masane!!!
Cut it out, Riko.
I was actually comfy there
for a minute.
Yeah, sorry,
but you were the one
who told me
I should wake you up.
Huh?
You mean, you saw it?
Over there.
It looks just like
it did on TV.
Six years ago,
that wasn't an island.
There was no water--
just buildings,
streets and people.
Wonder if we can see
any houses down there.
Mom, be careful.
Don't worry
your little head.
Duckies?
Looks like one of 'em's
on his own.
Just don't jump in after him.
Go on, little ducky!
Back to your family!
Don't want to end up all alone
in this scary world!
Go on!
Doggie!
What's going on out there?
Yeah, sorry.
I slipped.
It was the, uh--
Pretty irresponsible behavior
for a grown woman with a kid.
What does it matter
if one rubber ducky
gets split from the rest?
I wouldn't call it an omen,
'cause that's weird.
But I've never liked
being alone.
Being apart from the group
or left out, I dunno.
Something about it
just always felt wrong to me.
I mean, don't things
like that bother you?
Nothing bothers me.
Except maybe
when a parent lets a kid
wear the pants
in the family.
Look at her.
She's even got the dog
eating out of her hand.
Your kid's something else.
Yeah, she's all I got.
The one thing
I can be proud of.
You should be proud.
We lost a lot of great children
in that disaster.
Never seen that kinda horror
in all my days.
Wasn't it in the wake of that
they established
some group to help the kids?
Yeah, Child Welfare.
What a load of crap.
Mom!
I don't think
you dried your hair enough.
You're gonna
catch a cold, you know.
I'll be fine, Lady Rihoko.
Princess of Worrywort Island.
We're just about there.
So, is this
a mother/daughter vacation?
Not, quite.
We're moving here.
The two of us'll be official
Tokyo residents.
Yay!
If you're going to make
your home in Tokyo,
ya gotta be careful.
'Course we will!
A lot of strange stuff
has been going down
over the past few weeks.
Watch your backs out there.
Thank you, Captain.
And this is for you.
Looks like you were missing
a flag on the back.
Put this up in its place.
Thanks again.
Thanks?
Bye-bye, Mr. Boat Guy.
Bye-bye, doggie!
See ya 'round.
What a strange woman.
So different from
how it used to be.
And so many people.
Careful, Mom.
I don't want you to get lost.
Aren't I supposed to
say that to you?
But you're right.
We need to find a meeting place
in case we get split up.
Tokyo Tower!
That's perfect.
If we get separated
for any reason,
we'll meet at the tower
as soon as we can.
'Kay.
Now. First things first.
Job and a place to live.
Don't be scared.
Before we do anything else,
we need to get some food.
And to celebrate our arrival,
we eat anything we want!
Yeah!
Morning, boys.
You're late.
Give me a break, Detective.
I was up late drinking.
Looks like the same M.O.
Disgusting, is what it is.
We'll need a power sander
to get the calcium deposits
out of the concrete.
What kinda sicko you got to be
to do this
to another human being?
Tozawa,
why'm I not surprised?!
Get down from there
before I have you shot down!
I got what I need.
Hell, I got more
than what I need.
And now...
Smells like cash.
Pulverizer Murder number four.
A National Science
and Welfare Foundation badge
is found at each scene.
'Course, NSWF runs
the Child Welfare Ministry.
Guess I'll pay 'em a visit.
Detective Nakata?
Detective Nakata!
What?
I'm busy.
We caught this creep
a few blocks over.
Yeah, he actually says
he's responsible for this mess.
No, not near enough
to satisfy this thirst.
Quit bringing me
every drunk off the street!
What are they teaching
at that academy?
A'right, what do you want us
to do with him?
I don't care!
Figure it out!
Yes, sir.
Right away.
You made us look stupid.
Shut up!
Very well.
Keep your eyes on him.
If the opportunity arises,
we'll make our move.
Understood.
Pardon me, Captain.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah, what is it?
Have any of your recent
ferry customers
been a woman
with a six-year-old girl?
Yeah, you missed them
by a couple hours.
It seems
they came to Tokyo after all.
Did they happen to say
where they were going?
Those ladies
weren't criminals.
Who are you people?
Why you looking for 'em?
No need to worry.
We're the good guys,
Captain, I promise.
My name's Sakurai,
with Child Welfare.
Wow, that hit the spot!
Our compliments to the chef!
Thanks.
Though I gotta say,
it was a little odd
that you made the broth
with bonito.
Uh. Oh!
Thanks.
We'll come back soon.
We've been looking for you,
Masane Amaha.
Mom!
Hold on!
Young lady, you know
that under the new laws,
if you continue to stay
on the run with Rihoko,
you will be charged
with kidnapping
and child endangerment.
You can't!
I cannot be
any clearer about this.
If the proper environment
does not exist,
the CWM is obligated
to take the child into custody.
Look at yourself, Masane.
You have no home, no income.
You evicted us from our home!
The maximum stay
at a domestic shelter
is six years.
Well, now we're out
and we're gonna make it work!
Rihoko is only six years old!
But I'm busy helping my mom
all the time!
She doesn't even cook,
so I have to be with her
to help!
She'll be lost without me.
You can't take her away.
Please don't take my Mommy!
Rihoko...
I know you're worried,
but can I talk to your mommy
alone for a sec?
I'm her mother.
Why that's a problem
with you people is beyond me.
You've changed, Miss Amaha,
more than I thought.
Six years ago,
when they started sifting
through what was left,
somehow you and Rihoko
were found alive,
at the Null Point--
the epicenter
of the earthquake--
where the magnetic field
achieves a state of zero.
When you woke, your memory
was completely erased.
You didn't even
know your name.
Were it not for the maternity
diary you carried,
no one would have known
you were the girl's mother.
Especially since upon
your arrival at the center,
you told the counselor
you had no maternal feelings
toward Rihoko.
Remember?
I was confused. I--
Of course, you were.
Your memory
was completely gone.
No! What I said
to that counselor
is what I felt at the time.
But that was six years ago.
Today, this girl
is my daughter!
If that's true, Masane,
then you need to stop
and consider the best
course of action for her.
Children need structure.
Do you realize
how detrimental it can be
to live each day
in uncertainty?
Could you even afford a doctor
if she was to get sick?
It's not a perfect plan.
With Child Welfare,
Rihoko will have
a nurturing environment.
They have doctors
and schools.
Which path do you feel
is better for your child's
development?
As her mother,
you know the answer.
You should feel it
in your heart.
Once we've determined you're
capable of providing for Rihoko,
you can be a family again.
All right, Rihoko,
time for us to go.
Where's Mom?
Mommy's not coming.
Why not?
She said
you should go with me.
No! Mom!
Please, Mom!
I want to live with you!
I'll cook for you,
and I promise to wake you up
nicer, I promise!
Mommy!
Let me go!
I wanna see my mom!
No!
Don't let them take me!
Mommy!!!!!
Riko!
Do you need an escort
to the center?
Mom!
Thanks,
but we'll be fine.
Riko!
Hey.
Mom!
Hurry!
Start the car!
Go now!
A'right!
Back it up!
Mommy!!!!
Mommy!
I'm not letting go
'til you calm down!
Get offa me!
If only you cared this much
about actually
taking care of her.
You can't understand.
A mother's rage!!
Let me out!
You'll see your mommy again
Rihoko,
but when the time is right.
You have no idea
what I'm going through!
So don't act like you care!
Riko!
Mom!
What kind of a lunatic
are you?
Stealing a police cruiser!
Now there's no chance
that woman is ever getting
her daughter back.
Stop the car!
Gotcha.
Mother's milk.
Sun's about to set--
maybe I should go
have a look around.
Riko.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry
I left you alone.
I'm sure you're happy
your mother wasn't hurt, Rihoko.
But what she did
was a very bad thing--
and very dangerous.
Stealing police cars
is not the example
we want to set for you.
I gotta pee.
Sure.
Take your time, okay?
Yeah.
I can smell it
in the night.
It's wonderful.
The flesh.
Aw, jeez, my back!
Oh!
Sorry about that.
Did I, um, hurt you?
Oh, no!
My camera!
Still works.
You're a lucky lady.
This sucker is my life-blood.
You gotta help me, mister.
Do you have a car?
Well, yeah.
So what?
Rihoko!
Where are you?
Rihoko, huh?
I'm guessin' that's you.
Please, help me
escape from this place.
What?
I've gotta save my mommy.
You nuts?
Don't you know
what they do to kidnappers?
Ma'am,
what's going on out here?
A little girl
just jumped out the window.
I need you to look for her
down there.
I'm gone.
You there!
Come on out,
or I'm dragging you out.
We're cool.
So, where do we find your mom?
South Asagaya
Detention Center.
What's wrong?
Don't you know where it is?
Yes, I know where the jail is.
Hit a home run
with this kid.
It's gone.
The glowing on my wrist.
What's that racket?
Sounds like it's that lady
who boosted the police car.
I'm not sure, but I think
she might be sick!
Go check her out.
On it.
Hey, what's your problem?
You bastard!
Stop it!
That tickles!
Shut up!
Bye.
This is it.
I'm coming in with you.
Not a chance.
You keep it parked
right there.
I'll scope out the situation
on my own.
You got a photo or something?
A picture of your mom?
So you're the one
I've been sensing.
Such a potent aroma!
It will feel so wonderful
to rip you apart.
All you have to do
is stay still for me.
Here we go.
Oh, how I love the sound
of crushing bone,
the smell of blood,
the taste of soft flesh!
What?
What the hell is that thing?
Die!
We can't have their
interruptions, can we?
It's just you and me now,
my darling prey.
I can't wait for the pain!
The sounds of ripping tissue--
the taste of fresh marrow!
You're with NSWF.
No wonder you smell so nice.
You're the best
I've ever had!
I can't wait
to tear into you--
and finish you in one blow!
Sorry,
you don't do it for me.
I'm not finished with--
What the holy hell?
Hey, what are you doing
back here?
Busted.
And, cut.
Got it.
Now...
to collect the specimen.
Riko--
Mommy.
No problem.
The retrieval unit will handle
the X-con debacle.
Have you seen the video?
I'm watching it now.
I have no doubt.
She has the Witchblade.
She has a tranq coursing
through her system,
we'll have her shortly.
I look forward to it.
Yes, sir.
Why now?
Riko.
I'm...
I'm coming.
Riko.
[Music]
Being forced away from you
the second
we arrived in Tokyo
was the worst thing
I've ever had to deal with.
And it keeps getting worse.
Anyway, how are you doing?
I know I gotta be a mother
so here's a piece of advice:
Don't talk to strangers.
That's a big one, okay?
I wish I could tell you
where I am,
or what's going on with me.
But I'm not sure.
All I know is
I've met someone--
a horrible, disgusting man.
But I will
get out of here, Riko.
I'll find you. Wait for me.