Long sought
by the greed of men,
but bestowed
only upon the women
whose fate
it forever scars.
The Witchblade.
Righteous sword of God?
Or Hand of the Devil himself?
A new bearer finds out,
seeking balance between
ecstasy and ruin.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Maria! Stop it!
Let her go!
First-aid! Quickly!
How many times must we
have this discussion, Maria?
This is training.
Your behavior is unacceptable!
Whatever.
Don't "whatever" me.
Chief Nishida, ma'am.
Really?
Wow. That was like, easy.
Kinda weird, huh?
Maria! That was
one of your sisters!
Try and show some remorse!
Fine then.
I'm sick of this.
And it's obvious you hate me.
I'm gonna go talk
to Grandfather.
I'm sorry.
Perhaps I spoke too harshly.
Tell you what, why don't
I take you shopping next week?
I'll buy you a whole bunch
of new stuffed animals!
Yeah, okay.
That makes five now,
doesn't it?
Yes, ma'am.
Then I have high hopes
for the future.
Once we equip her with
the new blade we're developing,
who knows what will happen?
Bo-rrring.
Ah, Nora.
Sir.
I believe I will let
the matter of the Witchblade
fall into your hands.
I will take care of it, Father.
With all due haste.
Morning, Mister Takayama!
Are you feeling all right?
Where am I?
Oh good, you're awake.
This is my place.
What?
You totally passed out
in the park last night.
I had to get my neighbors
to help carry you.
Yep, you were quite a handful!
You didn't
have to do all that.
You could've
just called the company.
Well,
I was a bit drunk myself.
Ah yes, right.
Then I sincerely thank you
for helping m--
The bathroom's
right over there for ya.
Wow, I've never seen him
look so vulnerable before.
Don't get any ideas, Mom.
He is still your boss,
you know.
What, you think I like him?
No way.
I don't see why you wouldn't.
He's a way better catch
than that Mr. Tozawa.
In fact,
you should marry him, Mom!
I wouldn't mind it
if he was my dad!
Marry him?
Ew, don't say that!
Here you go!
The sofa is all yours.
I really need to be going.
Running around now
will just make you sick again.
What you need is rest!
Move along, right this way.
Trust me, it's best
if you just do as she says.
Princess Rihoko
is always right.
Take this:
it's Mom's hangover medicine.
Now lie back and relax.
No, I, uhh...
Rest!
Want anything to eat?
No, not ready for food.
Thank you.
Aw! The Dreaded Hangover Beast
turned you into a human being!
Ooh, some miso soup
might help!
I gotta run
and buy green onions first.
Want me to go for you?
Thanks,
but no thanks, Mom,
you'd just buy
old, withered ones.
Gimme a break,
I'm not that bad!
Sorry, you are.
Anyways, be right back!
Whatcha got there?
Nothing!
Now I gotta know.
It's a secret.
Hey, you sneezed
last night too.
Riko, do you have a cold?
Your face looks
a little flush to me.
No way, I'm fine!
See ya in a sec!
I have to say, your daughter
is really something.
The one thing in my life
I'm truly proud of.
Yeah, I'll bet.
She's a lot more together
than you are.
This from the guy who couldn't
even stand up last night.
That only happened
because of your behavior.
You were like a child running
wild at an amusement park!
Well, if I'm such a child,
why'd you even make me go
in the first place?
Be quiet,
my head is throbbing!
You are impossible!
And after you were
so sweet last night.
Hello, Segawa.
Yes, it's me.
Director.
Where are you?
Something came up.
I'll be in this afternoon.
That's not
really advisable, sir.
What?
Wado came storming
into your office
a short while ago.
He's demanding to speak to you
about the Witchblade.
And he's clearly still upset
over the "incident"
at the party last night.
I felt it would be prudent
to turn him away for the day,
so I told him you were ill.
That wasn't necessary.
Honestly, sir,
I don't think you should risk
exacerbating the situation.
Wado is in rare form today.
Please accept
my apologies, sir.
And thank you for waiting.
Unfortunately,
Director Takayama
can't move a muscle.
Such a shame too,
since you've come all this way.
Oh! Speck of dust.
I've been watching you.
Segawa, right?
I must say,
from what I've seen,
I'm quite impressed
with your skill as an assistant.
I'm honored
to hear you say so.
It's said the make of a man
can be told by his appearance.
In that regard,
you are truly impeccable.
What concerns me is why
someone of your caliber
is wasting his time working
for a man like Takayama.
I like to surround myself
with strong people.
Is that it?
Maintain that philosophy, son,
you'll go far.
Yagi, we're finished here.
Ah, Wado.
Naturally, I plan on taking
the liberty of seeing
exactly how strong you are.
Aw, Rihoko!
You got a cold?
Oh, no! I'm fine!
Hey Rihoko, I got
some nice freshwater clams!
Perfect cure
for your mom's hangovers!
Really? I didn't know
clams were good for hangovers.
They go great
in a big pot of miso soup!
Hold on now!
It's not miso soup
without green onions!
Here ya go, Rihoko,
top quality, on the house!
I'm tellin' ya,
clams are the way to go.
Can it, sea-hag!
Rihoko clearly came
to my shop, not yours!
Don't you try'n monopolize
her, Mr. Selfish!
Rihoko, are you okay?
Rihoko, what's wrong?
Rihoko!
What do we do?
Somebody call a Doctor.
This is just weird.
Having Takayama
in my home like this.
Masane!
Rihoko fainted at the market!
I heard somebody
took her to the hospital,
but they said...
No!
Wait!
There's more,
I'm not finished!
You forgot your shoes!
Hold up a second!
Oh, Riko.
You really were sick earlier!
I'm so sorry!
I should've been
paying more attention!
Come-on-come-on-come-on,
I-do-not-have-time-for-this!
Um, excuse me, which way
is the nearest hospital?
What, are you, deaf!
The hospital!
Where is it?
Get in!
So you ran out blindly
with no idea where to go?
I cannot imagine
what you were thinking.
But, Rihoko! She's--
Calm down and
just listen for a minute.
It sounds like there's no need
to be in such a panic.
Apparently, there was a doctor
among the crowd at the market,
who treated her
and took her to the hospital.
Riko! Riko!
Are you the girl's mother?
Riko!
I mean, I'm, yes!
Is she?
Your daughter is fine.
It's acute enteritis
caused by her cold,
but she'll be better in no time.
She will?
Oh, thank god.
To be safe, we'd like to keep
her tonight for observation,
but she can go home tomorrow.
Great!
Thank you,
thank you so much!
Oh, before I forget,
I heard when she fainted,
there was a doctor passing by
who brought her in.
Yes, but she doesn't actually
work in this hospital.
She said she didn't do much
to treat your daughter,
so she left without
giving her name.
Aw, that's too bad.
I was hoping
I could thank her too.
Good day, ma'am.
Thank you again, Doctor.
Hi, Mom.
Riko! Are you all right?
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I just wish you would've told me
you weren't feeling well.
It's my fault too, though.
But I really
did feel okay earlier.
Then all of a sudden,
my tummy started hurting.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Oh, Riko.
I was so frightened.
Thank you, by the way.
For the taxi, my shoes.
You know...
there is such a thing
as overreaction.
The second I heard
Riko had fainted,
my mind just went
completely blank.
I suspect that would be
a natural response
from any good parent.
Well, I suppose
you have a good side, too.
You think?
Oh, yeah.
I would never guess
you were someone
who was in the business
of re-animating corpses.
Great.
Are you still on about that?
Yeah, of course I am.
So now what?
"So now what," what?
Your job with the X-Cons,
do you want to quit?
What'll it be?
Will you stop fighting?
Well, I...
What's the matter?
I feel something.
Not an X-Con,
something different.
A Neo-Gene?
Yeah.
But I'm pretty sure
it's not Lady.
It doesn't feel the same.
I have to go!
No, wait.
If it is a Neo-Gene,
there's no reason to fight her.
Just let it go.
I can't.
She's come looking
for a fight.
And I won't let that happen
anywhere near Riko.
Besides, I'm not the one
calling the shots!
But, what about...
What if...
What if the Witchblade...
I mean, I thought
you would be afraid
of what might happen.
Hell yes, I'm afraid!
But...
I know I'm not any good
at doing motherly-type things.
I have no job skills
and no family.
So I at least
want to make sure
I leave Rihoko some money
when I'm gone.
So, there's your answer.
I can never stop fighting!
I'll fight your X-Cons,
and if Neo-Genes want to attack,
I'll fight them, too!
I can't afford to worry
about dying right now.
For Riko's sake...
I fight!
What are you looking at
over there?
They're blueprints
for a house!
This is where my mom and I
are gonna live someday!
Yeah? I bet it's nice!
Father would like
a word with you.
I would appreciate it
if you'd come with me.
No thanks!
So be it.
Send a recovery team.
Our operative's made contact
with a Neo-Gene.
She may find herself
in need of backup.
Understood, sir.
Such wonderful resistance!
Like a nearly-ripe fruit
dangling from the vine.
You can stop running.
I promise I won't kill you.
Or you could just
stop running after me.
I'm afraid
that's asking for too much.
Now let's put an end
to this charade, shall we?
Yes.
Let's.
Once I've made my point!
Get her out of there!
I can't do it!
They're too close,
I don't have a clean shot!
Damn it!
Now then...
Shall we be going?
Father is waiting.
Damn it!
Oh, man.
And gettin' in
was just the first part.
Only place I'm gonna find
any straight answers
about the Neo-Genes is here.
Melony!
What the hell is goin' on?
Riko.
Rihoko.
[Music]
Riko...
I'm so sorry I didn't
realize you had a cold.
Is your tummy
feeling better now?
I have to work again.
And this time I don't think
I'll be coming home very soon.
I decided to work extra hard
for your sake,
but I'm so afraid
I'm going to disappoint you.
I know, I'm pathetic.
I just wish I could
see your face right now.
Hearing your voice
for even a second
would give me strength.
Listen to me.
I'm such a terrible mother.