She's lost a lot of blood
but her external injuries
aren't too serious.
The major problems
I've found are internal.
To be honest, I've never
seen anything like this.
Can you give me any insight
on what happened?
I'm sorry I can't.
It's uh...
Top secret, huh?
I had a feeling you'd say
something along those lines.
Sorry, at this rate,
she won't have long to live.
[Music]
Mister Takayama!
Is my mom...
Is she gonna be all right?
Yeah.
She's just exhausted
from all her work lately.
A little rest
and she'll be fine.
Really?
I'm so glad to hear that.
Mr. Takayama!
Ms. Amaha is awake
and she wants to see you!
She finally woke up?
Yes, but there's a problem.
You're checking yourself out?
I'm sorry I had you
so freaked out about me, Riko.
But I am feeling
a whole lot better now.
Really?
You're not pushing yourself?
Nope, not even a little.
Honestly, you don't have to be
such a worrywart all the time!
Why don't you go
wait for me in the car, 'kay?
Okay.
Are y--
It's happening.
Sooner than I thought.
When did it start?
A few days ago.
Right after the fight
at your villa, I guess.
Why didn't you
tell me about this?
You can't get up yet!
You need bed rest!
If all I need is sleep,
I don't need a hospital,
I can do that anywhere.
Masane...
I wanna go home.
Our home,
with you and Riko.
How could you have failed!
Could you please
not yell like that?
I supplied you with
one of our I-Weapons!
Now you tell me
it's been destroyed,
and I'm just supposed to say,
"Oh sure, no problem!"
Well, it wasn't
completely for naught.
I did manage to recover
some new data on the Witchblade.
Obviously a single I-Weapon
was no match for its power.
But with several,
I have no doubt
they could seize the 'Blade.
Then why didn't you
send multiple units
in the first place?
You know as well as I
that the preparation
of these units takes time.
We are scientists, Wado,
not magicians!
The new IU-Weapons
are progressing as planned.
You just worry about
your own responsibilities.
Fine. I'll do that.
Leave the groundwork
for the various
government sectors to me.
And keep in mind,
any further failure
will not be tolerated.
No, I'm sure it won't.
Goodbye, Wado.
Oh, how I long for a world
where I can immerse myself
in research.
I've never had
a subject so worthy.
You fainted from anemia?
That's rough!
Are you feeling
better now, Melony?
Criminy!
It's probably 'cause
you overwork yourself.
Sorry, I didn't
mean to worry you guys.
Tell me straight, Mom,
are you sure
you're gonna be okay?
I'm fine, I promise!
With some rest
and your cooking,
I'll be back on my feet
in no time.
Are you sure?
In that case,
why don't we whip up
an amazing 'welcome home'
meal for ya.
Whadya say, Melony?
Yay! That'd be great!
Yay!
Alright, everybody!
It's time to get cookin'!
Alright!
Hey, wait up.
Tell me the truth.
Is it really anemia
or is it somethin' else?
Hey!
Why won't you answer me?
I've heard that liver's
the best food to treat anemia.
From what I hear,
it's great for boosting
your stamina, too!
That's a good idea,
but I don't think
she'll eat liver.
She's never liked that stuff.
Well, what if we
deep-fried it Tatsuta-style?
She may not like liver
but I know she loves fried food.
You're right!
No.
Not now.
I'm not ready.
Not yet.
If I die, I-I'll
never be with Riko again.
If I remember correctly,
you were forced
into early retirement.
Never thought I'd see you
back at Doji's labs.
Why do I get the feeling
there's a major story here?
Maybe it's just a hunch.
But then again,
my hunches are usually right.
Don't get too excited,
I'm here on personal business.
I'm sure it's nothing
that would be
of any interest to you.
Personal business, huh?
Does it relate to Melony?
I'm comin' too!
And if you try'n stop me,
I'm callin' security!
I don't have time for this.
Do what you wish.
No cameras.
Tsh. Right.
Seriously though, what the hell
are you doing back here?
I thought you cut
all ties with Doji.
That's right, I have.
But unfortunately,
all of our research data
is still kept here.
What research data?
Everything we know
about the Witchblade
and its previous wielders.
So somethin' did happen
to Melony?
Call me crazy
but I got a feelin'
this data has nothing
to do with anemia.
Speakin' of security,
thought this place was
just a research facility.
Who's there!
Director Takayama,
what're you doing here?
They're members
of my old staff.
Former employees
who shouldn't be here either.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I thought Doji
fired you boys when I quit.
Oh, they did,
but something came up.
It sounds crazy,
but we received an SOS.
SOS?
From where?
Director Takayama!
What happened exactly?
Come have a look at this.
The I-Weapons
we rolled out last month
to send to Baradhi,
have started to act
on their own accord,
all of a sudden.
They were set
to "Sleep" mode,
but for some reason,
they'd automatically boot up,
react to commands
that were never given,
and then malfunction.
We've requested a recall
of all shipped units
so we can investigate further,
but the higher-ups flat-out
refused to listen to us.
Let me guess, Wado?
You got it.
Our hands are tied.
They won't let us do anything,
so we decided to secretly
call in Ota's team.
How many do we have left
in storage here?
300 units, sir.
Let me get this straight,
you're saying there's
hundreds of I-Weapons here
just waiting to malfunction?
When did this phenomenon start?
Just recently.
I'd say maybe two days ago.
But it was yesterday when they
really started to go haywire.
Sometime around five
in the evening.
What is it?
The Witchblade's doing this.
It was in combat mode yesterday,
right around that time.
Impossible.
The I-Weapons
have safeguards in place
to prevent them from
reacting to the Witchblade!
That was before the Witchblade's
power level spiked.
Those safeguards
are useless now.
We need something else.
Criminy!
Why did we buy so much?
Don't blame me
when you're eating left-overs
for the next week.
I don't think that'll be
a problem the way Mom eats.
She'll pretty much scarf down
anything
you put in front of her.
Oooo-kay!
I'm gonna make you the best
dinner you've ever had, Mom!
The Witchblade
and the I-Weapons
are undeniably connected.
I assume it's because
the latter are drawn
to immense energy sources.
Hold on a second!
You think these I-Weapons are
gonna start going after Melony?
Uh, yeah.
That's pretty much
what we're lookin' at here.
Let me have a look
at the computer.
There's some data
I need to check.
I've had it
with this damn thing!
If it weren't...
If it weren't for this,
Riko and I...
we could be together.
Why!
Why me!
And why Riko!
Why!
It's not fair!
We didn't ask for this power!
So why?
Why is this happening to us?
Hey.
She doesn't have a simple
case of anemia, does she?
The Witchblade's excess power
has been taking
a heavy toll on her--
it's eating away at her body.
At this rate,
she won't live much longer.
That can't be right.
I mean,
she can still be cured?
Isn't that why
you're checking this data?
This is the data
Reina Soho left behind.
I scoured her observational
records provided by the NSWF.
But, there's nothing
in her research
to suggest a way to prevent
Witchblade-induced breakdowns.
So what happens to her?
Tell me!
Like...
can't you just remove it?
If you can take
the Witchblade off her,
she'll be safe, right?
Unfortunately,
it's not that easy.
The only way to escape
the Witchblade is through death.
There's no other way
to save her?
That's a load of crap!
What the hell
is the Witchblade?
You're the one who's
responsible for this, you know.
She never wanted to fight!
She just wanted
to keep Rihoko safe.
But you had her tied
around your little finger,
didn't you,
you son of a bitch!
You ran her ragged
and this is the thanks she gets.
Now all of these I-Weapons
are gonna go berserk
and start going after her?
She never asked
for any of this.
Whether she asked for it or not,
this is her fate.
It is the fate of all the women
chosen by the Witchblade.
To attract danger,
to fight, and to die.
What!
There's nothing more I can do
except to continue
to support her
'til the bitter end!
It has been determined
that the recent scuffle
in the Bay Area
was instigated
by remnants of the X-Cons.
I was under the impression all
the X-Cons had been disposed of?
Is it possible
some of them survived?
To ease the concerns
of the public,
we should inform them
Doji is willing to take
full responsibility.
It would behoove us
to work publicly
with the local government to
eliminate any remaining X-Cons.
We must start our negotiations
with officials soon
to expedite the process.
You have some truly
amazing ideas.
Now we can capture
the Witchblade in the city
right under everyone's noses.
Just brilliant, Director!
As they say, a wise man
profits from his--
Shut up!
You're annoying me!
Aoi, go down to the Neo-Gene
training center
and find their most skilled
Sisters.
Yes, ma'am.
And how many do you
want me to bring back?
One will do nicely.
I'm afraid more than that
would only slow me down.
Miss Maria?
What's the matter?
It was nothing.
I will obtain
the power I desire.
The Witchblade will be mine.
Finally, I'll have the power
to have anything I want.
You're going to kill me,
and long after I die,
you'll still be here...
and then you'll do to Rihoko
what you've done to me.
No!
I refuse to let that happen.
I am gonna die,
but I won't let this continue.
I'm gonna take you with me.
Straight to Hell.
I'm going to stay here
and take care
of these I-Weapons.
We won't know
what's going on
until I take
a detailed analysis.
With thousands of these things
goin' kaiju on Tokyo,
man, you got your work
cut out for ya.
I'll do whatever I can
to prevent that from happening.
In the meantime,
Masane and Rihoko
are in your hands!
Oh hi, Tozawa!
Welcome back!
Hey kid, we missed ya;
where the heck you been?
C'mon, get yourself
something to eat!
So, Mom...
what do you think?
It's delicious!
I swear, you're the best chef
in the whole world, Riko!
I gotta say I'm impressed
to see you all spunky.
I didn't think
you'd get better so fast!
Is it good? Whatcha think?
Yeah! It's great!
There's plenty
for you too, Tozawa!
Come on!
What're you just
standin' around for, ya bum?
Better get in
on some of this quick,
before Masane eats it all!
Yeah, right.
So where's Takayama?
Yeah, uh...
he's kinda over
at the Doji Labs.
Doji?
What's he doing there?
Well... some uh,
stuff came up.
So anyway...
how are things?
Hey Tozawa,
is everything okay?
Did you eat
on your way home tonight?
No.
I'll eat, sure.
Hey! Why don't we
take some pictures?
What brought that on
all of a sudden?
Well, everyone
worked so hard
to make this
beautiful meal for me.
Let's commemorate it!
That's a great idea!
We can take one with
"Rihoko and Cho's special salad"
smack in the center!
That'd make a nice photo!
Riko, come sit on my lap.
'Kay, fine,
I'll get my camera.
Put all yer happy faces on!
Damn it.
I can't focus.
Okay,
everybody say "cheese"!
Cheese!
[Music]
That was so much fun, Riko!
We haven't had
a dinner party in a while!
I'm so glad Tozawa took
all those pictures for us!
We'll have to put some
up in the kitchen
once they're developed.
I love being with you, Riko!
I really do.
I always love seeing
your smiling face.
I mean, I love your face
even when you're crying
but it makes me so happy
to see you smile.
I hope you'll always have
that smile on your face.
That's the one thing
I wish for you.
I love you, Riko.