Next pairing.
Aoi!
We cannot allow the Sisters
to continue
such rigorous fighting;
they'll destroy one another
if this goes on any longer.
Did Father really
order you to do this?
Yes.
He sent me
to choose one Sister
to help him
seize the Witchblade.
But I...
I was under the impression
he wasn't interested
in the Witchblade anymore.
Circumstances have changed.
There's a rumor going around.
Word is, Father
was actually murdered
and the company executives
are trying to--
That's just ridiculous.
I assure you
Father is very much alive;
he sent me here himself.
You. What is your name?
Asagi.
Please come with me.
You are the chosen
Sister, Asagi.
What the hell's that mean?
As the chosen Sister,
it's your responsibility
to help us obtain
that which we have
longed to secure.
How simple it all is.
This enormous organization,
the near limitless budget.
And I can do
whatever I want with it.
And to think
I used to make such a fuss
over a single stuffed animal.
Now there's only
one thing left.
And once I have it...
I have no need for you anymore.
[Music]
I'm gonna ask ya
one more time.
Are you sure there's no way
to take that thing off?
Look, I've tried
everything I can.
But it's not comin' off, Tozawa.
The damned thing
never even budged.
There's no reason for you
to be depressed about it.
It'll be okay.
Yeah, how's it gonna be okay?
If you can't take
that friggin' thing off...
that means...
it means...
I know,
and I'm okay with it.
I've got no choice
but to accept it.
But, how am I
supposed to tell Riko?
I mean,
I know she's gonna be fine.
I've saved
lots of money for her.
And now,
she's got her father.
Her father?
Hmm-mm.
Takayama.
Hold on,
just 'cause you're an item
doesn't mean he's gonna agree
to take in your kid.
No, that's not
what I'm saying.
Man, we really
haven't talked in a while.
Takayama's
her biological father.
Aw, fer cryin' out--!
Isn't it a relief, though?
Well, dad or no dad...
you know it's not
gonna make this crap
any easier on Rihoko.
Yeah, I know that.
She's gonna lose
her mother, regardless.
It's gonna break
her poor little heart.
I love you, Mom.
But, I don't want it
to stay broken.
I want her to be able
to smile again.
I feel like if I say
something to her now,
maybe it'll make it easier.
But what can I say
to make it less painful?
I dunno.
What're you askin' me for?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I guess this is
kind of tough, isn't it?
Here ya go.
Ya want seconds?
Oh, Riko!
Damn it.
There's gotta be
something we can do.
Now, Ota!
It works!
Installing
this antibody program
onto the malfunctioning
I-Weapons
will block the Witchblade's
interference
and allow us
to control them again.
Good!
Now split up and get to work.
I'll get you boys
the access codes.
Three?
You only have three
IU-Weapons?
That's correct.
It should be enough.
We should have
at least five to be sure.
Are you insane, Wado?
They're going to fight
the Witchblade.
What do you want?
To destroy the whole city?
At any rate,
preparations are complete.
The rest is up to you.
I hope you've done your part
and laid the groundwork.
Don't underestimate me.
Doji is nothing like your
pathetic little organization.
Is that so?
And who was it who begged
said
'pathetic little organization'
to sell information to him?
You're the one
who came to me for money!
It doesn't matter now.
I look forward to possessing
the Witchblade very soon.
What a sniveling coward.
Once I control the Witchblade,
I'll cut him off for good.
She has finally
outlasted her usefulness.
Director?
The government has just approved
our X-Con Removal Plan.
Hm, really?
The areas we've specified
as danger zones
have been placed
under strict curfew.
Once we give them a location,
police and fire departments
will evacuate the citizens
in that area.
Shall I instruct the lab
to mobilize I-Weapons?
It's already
been taken care of.
I'm sorry, I wasn't aware.
Ah yes, speaking of the lab,
they've made a request
to halt the Baradhi shipment.
The I-Weapons in storage
experienced
only minor malfunctions.
Halting the entire shipment
would be excessive.
Regardless, I believe the ship
has already left port.
Yes, sir, two days ago.
Then there's no problem.
The Witchblade
is far more important anyway,
and failure
is not an option.
Good morning, baby!
What's going on, Mom?
You never get up before I do.
I always have to wake you up.
It's such a beautiful day
I didn't wanna sleep it away.
Hey, what do you say
the two of us go hiking?
You wanna go hiking?
Why not? It'll be fun.
And look,
I made you a lunch.
No way.
You made that yourself?
Not too shabby, huh?
It may not be pretty,
but I bet it tastes really good.
Wow, thanks!
Good morning!
Morning!
Looks like you ladies
are headin' out somewhere.
Yeah!
Mom and I are going hiking
at Sakuragaoka Park!
See you later!
Come on, Mom! Hurry!
Coming!
Hey, so where are
the two of them headed off to?
They're going hiking
at Sakuragaoka Park.
You don't look so hot.
S'matter, you not sleepin'?
I'm fine.
Tell me somethin', Mariko.
Do you believe in God?
'Cause if He really does exist,
I was thinkin' maybe
I should start praying to Him.
I couldn't tell ya.
But you know,
if He does exist,
he's probably been long buried
under all that rubble.
You're prob'ly right.
Miss Maria, I have selected
a Sister to help us.
Asagi, please say hello.
Good work, Aoi.
She's perfect.
Go have her fitted
with a Cloneblade.
Yes, ma'am.
Come with me please.
She says my job
as the "Chosen Sister"
is to help you
obtain what you desire.
Yes, that's correct.
So what is it?
Power.
Power, huh?
That doesn't interest you?
I dunno.
Asagi, you mustn't say
anything rude to Miss Maria.
That's unacceptable.
Yeah, yeah.
She's just pretending
to be an adult.
Watch your mouth!
She's so a kid
on the inside.
A spoiled little kid.
Oh, wow!
Mom! Come look!
These cosmos flowers
are so pretty!
Dontcha think?
Please, give me the strength
to tell her.
Thank you for the food!
Delicious!
You used just the right
amount of salt, Mom!
You see?
I'm not such a terrible cook
after all.
No, but you might've used too
much sugar in this tamagoyaki.
Think so?
Mom!
Hey, Mom!
It's so pretty,
don't you just love it out here?
Yeah.
The park is very pretty,
but I bet Heaven
is even prettier than this.
Well, you see...
Riko, when people die,
their spirits go to
a beautiful place called Heaven.
But it's not like
it's a sad thing or anything.
It's just...
Even though
they seem far away,
the people in Heaven
are always close by,
watching over you.
It's far in the sky--
What?
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Um...
Well, it's...
kind of uh...
you know...
oh, man...
Who cares!
Never mind that Heaven business;
I wanna live here.
Let's build our house
somewhere like this!
A two-story house
with a garden.
So we can have
lots of flowers!
Oh, and maybe a doggie!
Those blueprints might be
a little small now.
Whadya think?
Wouldn't be nice
to have a big house, Mom?
Rihoko...
That house of yours...
I can't.
Mom? What's wrong?
Listen, Riko...
Pretty soon,
I don't think
you're gonna be able
to see me anymore.
Don't worry.
I'm still gonna be around,
you just won't see me.
But I'm not gonna leave you.
I could never leave you, Riko.
I'm going to stay by your side
like I always have.
You'll never be alone.
I promise.
Don't ever forget that.
We interrupt this program
for an urgent news report.
Doji Industries has a critical
warning to all citizens;
they suspect
one of their weapons is loose.
No way! Is this for real?
...all of the devices
that were mistakenly unleashed
during their recent
security breach.
What's goin' on?
I thought all the X-Cons
had been recovered?
...but depending
on the situation,
evacuation orders
may be given.
Please pay attention
to news and police reports
for further instructions.
Hey, that includes us!
What about Masane and Rihoko?
My God, that's right!
They're still out there!
At Sakuragaoka Park, right?
I'm on my way.
We're just now getting
our first images of the weapon,
reportedly called an X-Con.
What the hell is that?
Looks like a woman,
but even I gotta pass
on that one!
So creepy.
I can't let it go down
like this.
This is the Metro Police.
This area is currently
under curfew.
Please evacuate
to a safe location immediately.
Hey, Riko?
I'll be fine, but I need you
to run on home, okay?
Mom!
Wait!
Tozawa!
Don't try and take this on
all by yourself!
Get outta here.
Take Rihoko now, and run!
C'mon, Melony!
I'm not doing this
to be stubborn.
There's a part of me
that can't resist
the desire to fight!
As long as I have this thing,
it'll be the same wherever I go.
I have to keep fighting.
Take Riko home.
Please.
Go now!
Rihoko.
Mom said soon I wasn't gonna
be able to see her anymore.
Tozawa?
That means...
it means she's gonna die,
doesn't it?
I'm sorry, Rihoko.
Mommy!
Director!
It's happening!
Just like before!
That must mean Masane is...
Bad news, sir.
Wado has been granted permission
to mobilize our I-Weapons
under the pretext of
removing an X-Con!
I knew it, the bastard
is after the Witchblade!
Director.
We're not gonna
make it in time!
No. We have to.
We can't let them
reach the city!
Yes, sir!
Masane!
If you keep fighting like this,
you won't last.
Try to suppress your power!
Even just a little.
The power inside me
keeps growing and growing.
So much, feels like
it could tear me apart!
She's incredible.
Her power
has increased immensely!
What exactly is happening
inside of her?
I must learn more.
I'll never see anything
this magnificent again!
What the hell...
is this thing!
No!
What happened?
Call the infirmary!
Don't stop!
Keep working!
Director!
That's all that's left.
It's almost like something
is calling out to them
from somewhere.
Ota!
Get one of the units
we've fixed, and attack!
In here? Are you sure?
Better here than outside.
Move it!
Yes, sir!
Osada. Oda!
Fire in the hole!
Get down!
Damn!
Are they at war or something?
Hold on a sec.
Is it possible?
How can this be?
All of our planning,
yet we still can't
capture the Witchblade.
This is atrocious!
Absolutely atrocious!
I'd have to agree.
Which reminds me,
given the I-Weapon malfunctions,
I wonder how the lab is doing.
I don't give a damn
about that, Segawa!
What's going to happen to me?
A little late
to worry about that.
Roger that.
We are headed back.
Could you have
a tugboat ready?
I have to go back.
I have to get home.
Riko.
[Music]
Mom! The rice balls
were delicious!
And the tamagoyaki
was a little too sweet,
but it was still good.
Our picnic at the park
was so much fun.
The flowers were so pretty!
But now I know
what people mean
when they say
"the picnic is over."
Why don't we go home and eat?
I'll make tons of yummy food!
We can go
to the bathhouse after,
and then we can stay up
and talk and talk
until we fall asleep.
So please, Mom, come home.
Okay?