[Music]
Now look at these shots
we're getting
and you see what we're
dealing with: I-Weapons!
Hordes of I-Weapons,
descending on Tokyo!
We have enough room
for all of you!
Let the children
and the elderly through first!
Please, people!
The thoroughfare is blocked!
Do not attempt
to evacuate by car!
Are we sure there's really
any need for all this?
The whole city's empty.
We better hurry.
Yeah.
Hey! What're you all
still doing here?
The I-Weapons
are comin'--
Tozawa!
What're you idiots up to?
Don't you know there's reports
of an X-Con in this area?
Y'gotta be more careful.
Dammit.
I-Weapons this, X-Cons that.
Tokyo's full o' monsters!
You're wrong.
She ain't a monster, Nakata.
Huh?
I said, she ain't
no friggin' monster!
Tozawa!
I'd ask
what you're talkin' about,
but I don't care,
just get movin'!
There's somethin'
I gotta go do.
Take care of Rihoko.
Tozawa!
Dammit!
I can't let this end with her
being treated like a monster!
It's overflowing.
Something inside me--
it's incredible!
The Witchblade.
It's close!
Miss Maria...
I'm gonna go
way out on a limb here,
and guess
that's who's after us.
It appears so.
These pathetic little things
dare to get in my way.
I will not allow it!
Neither will we!
High-strung much?
Maria!
Where'd she go?
Chief Nishida!
Ah, ma'am!
Maria's gone!
She took Aoi and Asagi
to fight the I-Weapons!
I see.
So they are drawn
toward each other.
Go!
Get the car--
and ready the equipment!
Yes, ma'am!
Such a rare opportunity!
And flames, everywhere,
climbing into the night sky!
Now, can you folks see this?
A number of rogue I-Weapons,
clashing with an X-Con.
And neither side shows
any signs of surrender!
Oh! There!
A clear shot of the X-Con!
And now, coming in
at Number Three--
What the hell you think
you're doing, old man?
Hey, I'm a big fan o' hers,
I never miss an episo--
Frickin' dumbass,
turn it back!
Oh my!
Another explosion!
Huge flames continue to
rise from the street!
Columns of fire, spiraling up
one after another!
How long will these
I-Weapons and this X-Con
continue to run amok?
Mom.
It's burning up.
My body.
I'm burning!
Well, we know where it is.
Time to get moving!
Right!
Yeah, okay,
but what're you gonna do
once you've gotten it?
"Do?"
Well, yeah.
Power is only a means,
not an end, right?
Ask yourself
what you really want, Maria.
Asagi!
You're being rude!
God, I was just askin'.
Let's go.
I like breaking stuff.
Ask yourself
what you really want, Maria.
Yeah, fine!
Whatever, just find out
what happened in there!
We're not a newspaper,
you don't have to
report to me in real-time!
Just stick close to Doji!
Now get on it!
Okay.
What's up?
Got a great scoop for ya.
Sorry.
If it's not about an X-Con,
I don't need it.
It's bigger than that.
Content guaranteed.
But I need your help
on this one--
for a friend.
The X-Con is on the move!
The battlefield keeps changing,
but the fighting continues!
Where's Rihoko?
I thought she went to
the restroom with you.
Not with me.
She musta gone after Melony!
Hold up!
Where are you going?
A little girl is missing!
Have y'seen her?
A little girl?
Yes!
We got this!
Now you folks get back inside
where it's safe, while we--
Screw leaving it to you guys!
Rihoko!
Wait!
It's not safe out there!
You're obstructing
police duties!
Then get out of our way!
Our Masane, really?
Are you sure
you're okay with this?
You've sat on it
for so long.
Yeah, well, what good is
sittin' on it gonna do me now?
Good point.
How many have we got left?
Fifty-six.
Strike that, make it 52.
The next wave of I-Weapons
is about to make landfall.
Rough count, 800.
Against our 50?
We're screwed.
Sir, it's no use!
Let's pull back!
No.
Ota, have our remaining
I-Weapons rush the enemy!
Take out as many as we can!
Yes, sir!
At last, I've found it.
The Witchblade.
I'll take it now.
I'm a little busy
at the moment.
But taking you on
does sound like fun.
Pull over!
Doctor!
We're not safe here!
Do not move this car.
We'll never get
another chance like this!
This is madness!
Oh, Mom.
Oh, yeah!
Thirteen--
Twelve--
Eleven--
Ten--
Nine--
Eight--
Seven--
Six--
Five--
Four--
Three--
Two--
One--
All units have self-destructed.
Opposing I-Weapons sustained
25 percent damage, sir!
They're proceeding as before.
North-northwest.
Approximately 550 units.
So, this is it.
Hi!
What're--
Hello?
I'm sorry for calling you.
But um,
I'm looking for my mom,
do you know where she is!
What?
You know,
where she's fighting.
Where is she?
You don't want to go there?
Rihoko!
Don't do anything foolish!
Do you know
how dangerous it is?
You absolutely cannot go!
Where are you now!
Is anyone with you?
Are you outside?
No, go back!
Rihoko!
Ri--!
Godspeed, Takayama.
Please...
Please be okay.
What happened
to all your vigor?
Thought you could go
all night.
I'm just gettin' started!
What?
You're already breaking up.
That may be so.
But I gotta tell ya,
it feels incredible!
Oh yeah.
How was that for you?
Muh-Miss Mariaaaa!
Damn you!
You stupid, filthy nothing!
Aoi!
Awww.
Couldn't keep herself
together.
Aoi.
Miss Maria...
It's all right.
Please go on.
Finish what you started.
Take the Witchblade.
You're the one most worthy.
So once you've taken it...
what are you planning
to do with it?
The tough girl act
doesn't fool me.
I can feel you.
You're empty too.
Enough!
What I seek
is for me and me alone!
No!
This girl is as savage
as the Witchblade
and the I-Weapons.
I can't leave it
for Riko to deal with.
Only one choice.
Take her with me.
Yes.
That seems appropriate.
Damn it!
Mommy!
What am I seeing?
This is beyond incredible!
It could level
all of Tokyo if--
That's right,
over here, guys!
Focus on me!
All that power,
and you use it for this.
It's incomprehensible.
Yeah.
I bet it would be, for you.
Not that it really matters.
I don't need to comprehend,
I just need the Witchblade!
No chance!
I won't allow it!
Up there, of course!
I don't know if you can tell
what you're seeing here.
But literally
hundreds of I-Weapons
have converged
upon Tokyo Tower!
Meanwhile, the figure
previously reported
to be an X-Con
appears to be fighting
atop the tower!
The other combatant
is a so-called "Neo-Gene"
created by the world-famous
welfare group, NSWF!
But, ladies and gentlemen,
we have exclusive breaking news.
These bizarre figures
are not monsters or machines!
They're human beings!
Additionally, we've learned
that the "Neo-Genes,"
also known as the "Sisters,"
were created by
the NSWF's Mr. Furumizu
through a process of
bio-technology and inbreeding!
We've also received evidence
that the I-Weapons
are in fact constructed
by Doji Industries,
using the bodies
of the deceased.
Detailed investigations
of these reports are expected.
Row, row, row your boat!
Good, Takayama!
This monster, previously
thought to be an X-Con--
No! Stop right there!
Don't say that!
She's not a monster!
She's a real person.
A mother,
with people who love her!
Admit it,
you're beaten!
Just hand over the Witchblade!
It belongs to me!
I deserve it!
Once it's mine, I'll--
You'll do what, Maria?
Mom.
I see.
That's all you really wanted.
A mother's love.
Tell me, Mom.
Tell me you love me.
A mother's love.
Is that it?
What all of you are--?
All right, then.
I suppose it's for the best.
Mommy!
Riko.
I will always be
by your side.
But this life...
this isn't where
you're supposed to be.
It's there.
Right beside you.
Rihoko!
Oh, thank God!
Mister Reiji.
It's Mom, she's--
Riko.
[Music]
Mom...