She doesn't seem
very powerful, Doctor.
Rather disappointing
since she's the one
the Witchblade has chosen.
I agree.
Quite disappointing.
Shall I do her?
What the hell is going on?
Who are you people?
We'll leave her for now.
I think we've
seen enough today--
we can test her
her abilities later.
Understood.
What the hell
was that all about?
[Music]
They found you earlier
than I anticipated.
What do you mean
"they found me"?
Their powers seemed
an awful lot like mine.
Who were they?
You know of the NSWF.
Yeah, aren't they like,
the Child Welfare
Ministry's boss?
Their boss?
Not quite the way
I would've worded it.
Segawa,
I think it's time she knew.
Tell her about the Cloneblade.
Yes, sir.
Cloneblade?
What's that?
There was a time when
the Doji Group and the NSWF
shared technological
information.
Together, we succeeded
in creating the Cloneblade.
It is a fusion of
our Witchblade research
and the NSWF's biotechnology.
When compared to
the actual Witchblade,
it's quite inferior
in performance
but it has the same
basic structure.
So those two women.
They're from the NSWF's
Neogene program.
As such, they are
genetically predisposed
to wield the Cloneblade.
Neogene?
A human sub-species
born from biotech.
One of the women
you encountered,
is the most advanced
Neogene on record.
She is known as Lady.
We have no intel
on the other woman.
But judging by the way
she destroyed those X-Cons,
she must be
rather advanced as well.
Wait a minute.
Were you the one
who ordered them
to take out those X-Cons?
Of course not.
we haven't collaborated
with the NSWF for six years.
So why would they choose
to fight them
if they didn't have to?
Because...
they understand
how the I-weapons work.
How they always look
for the strongest opponent.
A Neogene is more appealing
than a normal human.
It's very similar to the way
the Witchblade craves battle,
with which you are now
quite familiar.
You, of all people,
should be able to empathize.
One factor we cannot ignore
is the NSWF's director,
Mr. Furumizu.
He is determined to acquire
the Witchblade for himself.
Why?
Ultimately, his goal is to
unite the Witchblade
with one of his top Neogenes,
creating the most powerful
human in history.
A rumor's been circulating
for some time
that the Child Welfare
Ministry is just a cover.
That Furumizu's using it
to select future
Neogene candidates.
Seriously? He's experimenting
on those poor kids?
That's the rumor.
The lesson of course
is to never side with the NSWF.
Don't even worry about that.
I got a history
with those jerks.
Good.
You're free to go now.
Yeah, I'm not done.
What's the deal with
this money you gave me?
For your living expenses.
You'll also be earning
a regular salary.
That doesn't
really work for me.
I don't wanna be
a kept woman.
How 'bout
we do things my way?
I do a job,
and then you pay me.
Well, if you insist.
Not so fast, pretty boy.
I'm gonna call this one payment
for the last job I did.
Your last assignment
ended in failure.
So you get nothing.
What?
But I went to the scene!
And I got them to retreat,
so I should at least
get a percentage!
You were given orders
to eliminate the X-Con.
You did not--
therefore, you do not get paid.
Oh, come on!
Thirty percent?
Do you have
a hearing problem?
I am not going to pay you.
Gimme a break!
I'm sure you guys
are rollin' in dough!
You shouldn't stress
over chump change like this,
it'll make you bald.
'Fact, your hairline's
lookin' iffy already!
Masane,
I think that's enough.
Okay, fine.
Then how about
if you pay me
for that first job
I did back at the prison.
But that was before we even--
Whatever!
I killed the thing, didn't I?
Okay, enough.
Segawa, give her the money.
Why, thank you.
Oh, and by the way,
I am done
bein' this guy's bodyguard.
My goodness.
You almost gave me
a heart attack in there.
Oh, please.
I was just tellin' the truth.
Well, that's the first time
I've ever seen
Mr. Takayama concede.
So, how much does the job pay?
You mean, you don't even know
what you were negotiating for?
Well, I would guess.
I dunno,
like a hundred grand?
You've underestimated
Doji Industries.
You'll be making the same
as our top lab researchers,
over two million.
What?
Two million?
Ssshhh.
That woman'll be
the death of me.
Dim the lights.
And to think
the Witchblade chose her.
Yes?
It's time for the Board
of Directors meeting, sir.
You're exactly one minute
and 30 seconds late,
Mr. Takayama.
Well, this is it.
Wow!
Check it out, Mom!
Just look at this kitchen;
it's awesome!
Right? I'm sure my little chef
can make this work, huh?
You bet!
Next month's rent is due
at the end of this month!
And don't be late with it!
For this month,
it's 35,000 pro-rated.
Hey! Wait a minute!
You said this place
goes for 60,000 a month.
So half of that would be 30.
The extra five's
a surcharge for the kid.
How is that fair?
If you don't like it, get out!
Witch!
Sticks and stones.
Dun-da-da-daaaa!
Hey, sorry to keep
you ladies waiting!
I got ya
a housewarming present.
You like it?
Oh, wow!
A mattress!
Thank you so much!
That's a big help!
And I've got these.
Tickets to the bathhouse;
unfortunately,
we don't have one here.
You ladies care to join me?
Aw, yeahhh!
Can we, Mom?
Sure.
You know, I was just talkin'
to Kei from over there.
She said you were
in the women's bath
claiming to be senile again.
Terribly sorry,
I don't recall, uh.
So...
Bath time.
Damn it, Kei.
Let's get going, you two.
We're right behind ya.
See ya.
Yeah, sure.
Gonna be a long year.
Going down.
Heh.
I've never been
to a bathhouse before!
I'm excited!
Me too!
Hey!
How you doin' there, big guy?
This is Michael.
He lives on the top floor.
He just got himself an office
job somewhere around here.
Oh, really?
Very nice to meet you,
Mr. Michael.
Umm.
We're going to the bathhouse.
Wanna join us, Naomi?
"Nah-OH-mi"!
Yeah, it's what I said.
Naomi is kinda shy
so she goes in the morning
when it's not
as crowded, right?
Right.
Looks like the only resident
we're missing is Tozawa.
Oh yeah, is that the guy
Riko was tellin' me about?
You got it!
He hasn't been home
in a while.
Probably found
a lady friend.
Damn that geezer Nakata.
Bargin' in on me like that.
Oh God, not the cold sweats.
Can we put our clothes
in the same basket?
Go for it, kiddo.
Okay!
Uh, mom.
What is it, Riko?
It looks like
you've gained some weight.
What?
You think so?
I like my women with
a little meat on their bones.
Yeah, but then I'd have to
walk through the cold air.
My love.
You perverted old man!
It's so big in here.
Wanna go swimming?
Don't be silly.
Didn't you see
the sign out front?
It says no swimming allowed.
I know, but that's no fun.
I like this bathhouse, though.
Can we come here every day?
Why not?
Hey, you wanna go
shopping tomorrow?
Yeah! We're gonna need to buy
stuff for the kitchen,
like knives and bowls,
and we need--
No, I meant we should
go shopping for clothes.
You do need
some new clothes mom.
I really think you should
try to dress more ladylike.
Yes, ma'am.
Whatever you say.
Princess Rihoko.
Cut it out, mom!
Prepare yourself
for my shower attack!
So, she has a child.
A daughter?
Yes, that's right.
She's six years old.
Interesting.
That's all I need for now.
You can stop tailing them.
Got it.
Couldn't be.
Need more.
It's not enough.
Honey, I'm home.
Well, look what the cat
dragged in.
Man, I'm beat.
No way I was gettin'
any sleep in that place.
Where the hell were ya?
You don't wanna know,
just make me somethin' to eat.
How do you expect to make
a living doin' what you do now?
You'd make more money
serving Ramen.
Yeah?
Good morning, sir!
Oh.
Didn't think I'd be
seein' you again so soon.
Lemme guess,
still on the run, kid?
My mom and I
moved in here yesterday.
We're neighbors now.
That's nice.
You must be the man
who helped Rihoko.
Thank you so very much.
I'm Masane Amaha, by the way,
I'm Rihoko's mother.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, likewise, Melony.
What the... Melony?
That's a good one.
'Cause your boobies
are big like melons!
It's the perfect name for ya.
Mel-on-y.
My name is Masane.
Ma-sa-ne.
Wait! You're that chick
who disappeared
from her jail cell!
I've been lookin'
all over for you!
So hey, ya mind answerin'
a few questions?
Please. Did ya see
anything strange, that night?
I don't think so.
I'm not real sure
what you're askin'.
You know something.
I can tell by the look
on your face.
Tell me, please!
I'm beggin'!
C'mon, lady!
Gimme a lead!
Hands off, jerk!
I already answered
your question.
But...
I didn't see anything.
C'mon Riko,
ready for some shopping?
And you...
you better stop
harassing my mom!
What was all that about?
Somethin' happen at the jail?
That's an understatement.
No wonder you aren't
gettin' any sleep.
What'd you say?
No, no, no!
You got it all wrong, Mari.
Now quit bein' so nosey
and fix me somethin' to eat.
Tadaaa!
Forget it,
I'll pick something.
Wait here for a sec.
I'm sorry but we don't carry
a cup size that large here.
Well, I guess
I'll have to go without one.
No way!
They'll sag.
Ooh, can I get this?
Please?
Put it back.
I'm pooped.
I totally forgot
to buy aprons!
I'll be right back.
Where do kids find
all that energy?
Hey there, want some?
Wha-- Whaddaya think
you're doing--
Yusuke Tozawa.
I'm a freelance journalist.
Well, I haven't exactly
been published yet.
But that's why I'm here--
the scoop I'm workin' on's
gonna be my meal ticket.
So why bug me?
I don't have
any "scoop" for you.
'Zat right?
I don't know what that is.
So then you did see it.
You wanna tell me
'bout this monster?
Monster, huh?
C'mon, you were there
that night,
you had to have seen it.
Am I wrong?
How long you gonna play
the quiet game?
C'mon, lady,
throw me a bone 'ere.
I already told you,
I don't know anything.
But hey,
thanks for the coffee.
Melony, wait!
It's Masane!
Get it straight!
My bad.
Now leave me alone
and quit following us!
Hey, Mom!
Is Mr. Tozawa
gonna go shopping with us?
No, I just ran into him!
Funny, huh?
C'mon, let's go.
I bought us
matching aprons.
Oh yeah?
Does that mean I have to...
This ain't the last
you've seen of me.
So, Director.
Why are you attending
this charity function?
Typically, Doji doesn't send you
to these kinds of events.
I pulled the short straw
at the director's meeting today.
I imagine
you'll be quite popular
with the female stockholders.
Nonsense.
I see.
So you made contact with
the Witchblade's new bearer.
Anything else?
It seems Doji is involved.
Tell me about the woman.
Is she capable
of handling herself?
Honestly, I was
rather unimpressed.
You'll understand why
when you see her in action.
How unfortunate.
I heard another one of
the sisters has gone missing.
Do you think
it was an X-Con again?
Probably so,
although Doji is claiming
it was an accident
the X-Con escaped.
Regardless, I want you
to continue your research
on the Witchblade.
Isn't there a party tonight?
Some charity function?
Yes, sir,
but you are not
scheduled to attend.
No.
I will make an appearance.
Mr. Takayama!
We never see you
at these functions anymore.
It's been a while.
I'd like to introduce you
to a friend of mine.
The President
of FB Pharmaceuticals.
He's created a new hair
re-growth pill
that's bound to
double his stocks.
Riko, we finally have
a place to call our own.
Yes?
This is Ota
from the retrieval unit.
We've just spotted an X-Con!
On my way.
I'll be right back.
Mr. Takayama?
Mr. Furumizu
would like to see you.
If you'd like to follow me,
I'll take you--
I'm his assistant, you'll need
to schedule that with me.
Excuse me?
I'll speak with him.
Director?
I've obtained
a very rare vintage.
Would you care for a glass?
Thank you, but not tonight.
It's been six years.
Six long years
since the Witchblade
disappeared from underneath us.
Your daughter brought about
that course of events.
True, but it's in your
control now, isn't it?
You shouldn't believe
everything you hear.
Let's stop beating
around the bush, Takayama.
You are aware
that the Cloneblade
and I-Weapon are both products
of our collaboration
six years ago.
The NSWF should have no need
for the Witchblade.
Then you still insist
the gauntlet belongs to you.
Yes.
It is Doji Group property.
It's close.
The Witchblade can
only be worn by one woman.
Furthermore,
it is the Witchblade itself
which chooses its host.
As you may recall,
not long ago,
my daughter was the first
to be selected for this honor.
With all due respect,
the Witchblade has changed
hands many times in the past.
Changing hands.
Is that what you're afraid of?
The reason
you built the X-Cons?
That's a rather extreme
accusation.
Regardless.
The crown will always return
to the head of the deserving.
That may be true...
but only after
the current ruler is slain.
For the first time,
I'm satisfied.
Is that a fact?
Wish I could say the same!
She's really not as powerful
as we thought.
That's because
the host is weak.
Please.
Allow me.
Come on, Witchblade.
Why don't you show me
what you've got!
Are you sure
you can handle it?
No friggin' way!
Melony is the monster!
[Music]
I'm sorry, Riko.
I know you must be
worried about me.
I want nothing more
than to be home with you.
I'm just so busy with work.
I can't even enjoy myself
on this luxury yacht.
For the record, your cooking
is so much better
than anything I've had here.
I miss you like crazy,
but I have to make money.
For our future.
Make sure you keep
the doors locked.
I'll be home soon.