Long sought
by the greed of men,
but bestowed
only upon the women
whose fate
it forever scars.
The Witchblade.
Righteous Sword of God,
or Hand of the Devil himself?
A new Bearer finds out,
seeking balance
between ecstasy and ruin.
[Music]
Ohhh-kay.
I got so many questions for ya,
my head hurts.
I don't even know
where to start.
So, why don't you
just fill me in?
And don't try to
weasel out this time.
Please, just...
Leave it 'til tomorrow.
I can't do this
in front of her.
But...
A'right, fair enough.
Just don't go skippin' town
on me or nothin'.
This is the first real home
we've ever had.
You think I'm gonna
throw that away
'cause o' some jerk like you?
Lookin' forward to chattin'
with ya, sweet-cheeks!
Oh, Riko.
You worked so hard,
you cleaned the whole place.
I'm sorry, are you closed?
Long as I'm still up,
we're still open.
Kahlúa and milk then, please.
Hittin' the hard stuff.
I like it!
Is there somethin' wrong
with that?
Okay, so.
What do you do, exactly?
You say you do "odd jobs".
But what would make you
leave that kid alone all night?
Everything I do is to
keep her from being alone,
keep us together.
Yeah, well.
Heh. One thing's for sure
she's a whole lot more
"together" than you are.
Yeah, you're tellin' me.
I dunno, guess
she takes after her father.
What happened to him?
Wish I knew.
I don't remember him.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't remember anything
before the Great Quake.
If I didn't have Riko's
maternity diary
when they found me,
I wouldn't even know
my own name.
'Sides, it'd be a little awkward
if he showed up now,
and I don't know who he is.
Just about everybody lost
something in the Great Quake.
I guess for you,
your memory was that thing.
That's a nice photo there.
Tozawa took that back
when he wasn't such a bum.
Really?
It's so good!
I know.
I keep tellin' him he could
make a career with that eye,
but all he wants
is his elusive "scoop."
Yeah! You got that right!
I mean who the hell
does he think he is!
Eveni-- Heeyyy!
C'mon! Where's the love?
We're drinkin' with
Melony tonight?
How come nobody told me?
Mr. Cho, please,
my name is Masane.
Sure thing, Melony,
so, what're ya havin'?
Mari. My shochu, please!
Now it's your shochu,
not mine?
Lemme check, I don't think
your name is on it.
Details-schmetails!
Naomi, the usual?
Cup o' warm milk?
A little moo-moo boob juice?
Okay?
Michael!
Perfect timing!
Let's get our drink on!
It's in the air.
All-night fever!
Yeah!
Some call it a tavern,
but I call it home!
'Ey!
Tozawa!
Come have a drink or three!
Yeah, no.
Thanks, but, not tonight.
What, can't hold your liquor?
Heh, I said "liquor".
Hey, now.
Don't forget
what you promised me tomorrow!
I'm not listening!
Not until you drink with us!
Drink! Drink!
Damn it, drink!
Ah, jeez.
Look at yourself.
No, hey, Michael.
Tonight's not.
Come on, Tozawa!
You know you wanna
get drunk with us!
Aaaand, down the hatch!
Yeah! Go for it, Melony!
Chug! Chug!
Chugga-chugga!
One down, one to go!
Keep 'em comin', boys!
And the reigning champion,
Lady Melony,
steps up for another one!
The following is a statement
prepared by Father.
"In regards to Shiori Tsuzuki,
my sadness runs deep.
"I anxiously await
a full investigation and report
"into why this tragedy occurred.
Additionally, I expect the same
concerning the Witchblade."
As a side note, Reina,
Father is a bit unnerved
that no such report
or any explanation at all
has yet been given
by you personally.
That is all.
What, again?
Dis is a classy joint!
An' you reekin' o' smoke
don't help our reputation!
Yeah, yeah.
Fire me.
Please be the one.
Be the one to say it.
Who's there?
"Star light, star bright.
Let my love quicken
your heart tonight!"
Mom, c'mon, wake up!
It's time for breakfast!
Mom!
I don't feel good.
My head hurts!
No! You drank too much again?
I distinctly remember
telling you to take it easy!
I did take it easy.
'Least it went down easy.
Oh well, what can you do?
I have to go
to the supermarket anyway.
I'll getcha some medicine
while I'm there!
'Kay. Thank you, baby!
Yeah, come in.
Door's open.
Mornin'...
Melony.
All right, you promised.
Time to spill the beans.
About what?
Don't gimme that.
Now, what the hell's going on?
That thing you changed into,
what is it?
Why d'you wanna know?
Why do you think?
This is huge.
Buyers'll be trippin'
over themselves.
So you're tellin' me
you'd go public?
Course,
I'll give you a healthy cut.
A'right, truth is:
I don't know a thing!
Nope, don't have
the foggiest idea
what you're talking about!
Oh, come on!
Who do you think
you're foolin'?
I got photographic proof,
clear as day!
And you're just gonna
stand there and deny it?
Deny what?
That picture's not me.
How can you even say that!
No idea
what you're talkin' 'bout!
Sorry, completely lost me!
Liar!
No clue, dude!
That's not me!
To be continued!
Shinjuku Four-Ten.
Code Zero-Niner,
Chuo Building.
Squad Three, please respond.
Detain all possible
eyewitnesses.
A'right, I'm back.
Would you cut me a break
already?
You say you do
odd jobs, right?
'Cause I got an odd one.
Now if you're gonna work for me,
I expect you to work.
But you won't complain,
long as I pay ya, right?
Yeah, right.
He says she was fine when
she came into work last night.
How could this happen
in just a few hours?
The M.O.'s new,
but sump'm tells me
it's connected to the others.
So what?
Y'think it's all
the same perp?
Nah, not necessarily.
Tsh.
'Til this, I thought I had
all the victims connected.
Oh, God.
I hope my stomach holds out.
Looks like another one of
your creepy-crawlies struck.
Look, I've been all over
these horrific murder cases.
And just when I thought
I was onto a solid lead,
I found you, and it was you,
right in the middle of it.
I will figure out
what's going on here.
Tozawa!
Get the hell outta there!
See, there you go again,
Detective,
bossin' everyone around!
Bet it drives your fellow
boys in blue up the wall!
Oh, that's rich!
You want another ass-whoopin'?
Whoa, hey.
Wouldja look at the time?
Bye!
Detective Nakata
is the lead investigator
on all these cases
I'm following.
He's a bit of an asshat.
So you sell photos
of crime scenes?
'Zat a problem?
You talk tough, but really,
do you have fun
doin' that sorta thing?
You tell me, Amnesia Girl.
Is it fun for you?
I can't tell you
what I don't know.
Your call.
Yeah, it's his car.
Let's give him a warm welcome.
Been a long time.
Tozawa.
I'm sorry, sir,
have we met before?
One year ago, you sold
some photos to a magazine.
A valued customer entering
my establishment with a woman.
Yeah, it's ringin' a bell.
Surely you can appreciate
our humiliation,
when we were accused
of poor security.
Yeesh.
Tell ya the truth,
those pics really didn't sell
for all that much.
Guy just wasn't
a big enough deal.
What!
Y'know what?
I'll make it up to ya.
Melony, hon?
Be a dear and grab
that envelope off the dash.
Go ahead.
You catch on quick,
I like that.
I wasn't born yesterday.
It's not in here.
Are you sure about that?
I coulda sworn I...
Close the door!
Does this kind of thing
happen to you a lot?
No more than you'd think.
Pain in the ass!
What, are you tryin'
to get us killed?
'Ey, if you tell me yer story,
I might be persuaded
to slow down.
Is this really the time?
I need to hear it.
Please tell me.
Damn it! Where'd he go?
Best to play it safe
and lie low a bit longer.
Why don't you go to the cops?
Why bother?
Piggies've got a whole lot
better things to do
with their time
than chase down street thugs.
Wish you had better things
to do with your time.
Not a chance, sweet cheeks.
Why the hell not?
Ain't rocket science.
Who in their right mind
would sit on a story like this!
I see!
Too bad I don't know
anything about it.
Just drop it.
If I'm sure of anything,
it's that this is you.
You can deny it
'til you're blue in the face,
but the truth'll come out
as soon as
this thing sees print.
Stop this!
What're you doing?
I have the negative,
I can make copies!
Please, just don't.
I don't want Riko to find out.
Please.
Look, I get where you're
comin' from, it's just...
Director.
Per your request, I've sent
the crystallized remains
of the Neo-Gene
who attacked us to the lab.
And I have the file for your
Board of Directors meeting.
Is it true the Witchblade
ultimately consumes
and destroys its hosts?
If past records are accurate.
And it'll do the same to Masane?
The lab will investigate that.
If that is the case,
I feel sorry for her.
The Witchblade is on the agenda
for discussion.
There was pressure from
the director of Bio Division
to have it included.
Wado did this?
Seems he's beyond rivalry,
he truly views you as his enemy.
It may get ugly in there.
Arguments with him
always get ugly.
He doesn't know
when to give up, I take it?
Do you know
how all of us described Wado
back in our college days?
How?
"Like gum stuck to your shoe."
Actually, that's perfect.
Well, this is boring.
Gee, y'think?
Sorry 'bout
that "Amnesia Girl" crack,
Mari told me.
Is it true?
Yeah, it is.
I don't even remember
giving birth to Rihoko.
I'm amazed you can
get through each day.
Well, it gets easier.
Sure, it was hard at first.
But Riko and I are a family.
Somehow things work out.
By the way, I meant to tell you
how much I like your photograph.
The one hanging in the café.
Oh, that.
Pics like that...
can't take 'em anymore.
Back when I was
young and naïve,
I sold all
my earthly possessions
and trekked around
the worst parts of the world,
honing my photography skills.
I came home once I felt
I finally had enough experience.
But the people I was so anxious
to show my photos to,
family, girlfriend, teachers,
they were all dead.
The irony was overwhelming,
I couldn't cry or scream.
And then I realized,
all I had left
was the camera in my hands.
Everything I had,
everything I was,
was buried in that rubble.
So, that's my story.
When I talked to Mariko,
she told me that everybody lost
something in the Great Quake.
Ain't that the truth.
We're kinda the same.
Damn right.
Which is why
you should just tell me
'bout all the wacky stuff.
Huh! And how d'ya figure that?
Hey, work is work!
We were totally having a moment,
and you had to go an' spoil it!
Y'know, any normal person
would say,
"Here, lean on me!
Have a good cry!"
Dumbass!
What a bunch o'
sentimentalist crap!
Come on, out with it!
After you call me names?
Forget it,
I'll never tell you now.
What's wrong?
Please be the one.
Please!
Be the one to say it!
"Star light, star bright,
Let my love
quicken your heart tonight!"
Dammit! I shoulda been
paying attention!
C'mon, we can't just sit here!
Gee, y'think?
Please, I need you to say it!
What the--?
I should have changed by now.
Yeah, so...
you might wanna do somethin'.
It isn't working.
"Let my love quicken
your heart tonight!"
We gotta run!
Yeah!
Please, just say it!
"Star light, star bright!"
Aw, crap!
"Let my love
quicken your heart tonight!"
Whoa, Melony!
You all right?
T-Tozawa...
Make me a deal!
Huh!
What're you talkin' 'bout?
Take all the photos
of me you want!
But the catch?
I've gotta tell Rihoko myself!
And you don't go public
'til I do!
How long?
At least a year.
No way!
You have to give me this!
You won't be sorry!
All right, fine.
You got one year, that's it.
The pact has been sealed!
Help me.
I can't.
I can't take anymore!
Crap, he's gone!
He was different
from the others.
But how?
I got a bad feelin' about this.
'Kay, hope
I didn't forget anything.
Thank you, come again!
Let's see, got that,
and I got that and...
Yep! Got everything!
Hello there.
Um, hello.
Um, is there something
that you wanted?
Not really.
Do I need a reason
for coming to the market?
Yeah, uh...
My mom is waiting.
Your mom.
I see.
Well...
Goodbye, now!
They think that...?
What a piece o' crap.
How can you say that?
I love this car!
Hi, Mom!
Riko, hey!
Whoa.
Mom, what's going on?
Why're you with Mister Tozawa?
No biggie.
I had a little work to do
and your ma was
just helping me out.
I'd be careful, Mom!
I think Mister Tozawa's
got his eye on you!
Oh yeah, I'll be careful,
I'll be real careful!
Hey!
What kind of family are you?
Oh yeah, Mom?
Almost forgot.
Just a minute ago...
Yeah?
It was nothing.
Oh! I got your medicine!
Oh, awesome!
Thank you!
"My love,
let my love quicken."
No, please.
Don't make me do this anymore!
[Music]
Wow, Mom, there are
so many people in Tokyo!
I know we haven't been here
very long,
but I already have
so many friends.
Mister Cho, Miss Mariko,
Miss Naomi, and Mister Michael.
I guess I can include
Mister Tozawa too, huh?
And lately, there's this
pretty lady I keep seeing,
but I don't know her name.
Oh! And I met a nice man
at the park.
He's going to buy
a new house soon!
I hope we can get our own
cute little house someday!