Long sought
by the greed of men,
but bestowed
only upon the women
whose fate
it forever scars.
The Witchblade.
Righteous Sword of God,
or Hand of the Devil himself?
A new Bearer finds out,
seeking balance between
ecstasy and ruin.
[Music]
Wha-- Who?
I have a request.
Repeat after me.
I need to hear you say it.
"Star light, star bright,
let my love
quicken your heart tonight!"
Will you please say it?
That's all I'm asking.
What's the matter, Miss?
Can't you just say it once?
"Star light, star bright,
let my love
quicken your heart tonight!"
What the hell is this!
What kind of
crazy pervert are you?
Please, Miss.
Hurry and say it.
Say it!
Not again!
No, please.
No more!
Nooooo!
Dammit!
We've got three homicides
in a row!
And they're all young women
that are completely
unrelated to the NSWF.
What the hell's goin' on here?
Yeah, seriously.
Tozawa!
Stay right there!
I'm done playin',
you damn hyena!
Time to go.
Hey, if you're lookin'
for someone to blame here,
how 'bout, like,
the killer?
Assuming you can find 'im,
of course!
You! Good point.
All right!
Another toast, boys!
Cheers!
You sure can toss 'em back,
Melony!
I don't know
if I can keep up wit ya!
Hey, Tozawa!
Come have a drink with us!
We're celebratin'!
Join us!
Michael got a job today -
first one he's had
since he moved in!
You got a job, huh?
Doin' what?
I see it.
There's a dark shadow
hanging over Michael's head.
Sorry, guys,
I'll have to take a rain check.
Been so busy lately
I need some rest.
Oh, n-no!
Don't you run out on me, jerk!
Uh! S'cuse me?
I thought we were gonna be
working together as a team.
You better not
leave me in the dark!
Nuh! No.
It's not like that.
Oh! Now I get it!
You're afraid of me.
You saw me lookin' like that
and you can't handle it.
Please.
I'm not afraid of you.
Ooh! What'd you see?
Did one of 'em pop out?
Hey!
You wanna see?
Ha-hah!
This is awesome.
Hey, quit it!
Melony!
Take it easy!
Mom, don't you think
you've had enough already?
I think you should
call it a night.
Oh, Mom!
So, what did you see, kid?
Uh, it was this.
Yeah, I saw her pass out.
Oh, she does this a lot?
Hey, Mom,
do you want some water?
No, I'm fine.
Riko.
Gimme a kiss.
Wow, you're really drunk.
Okay kiddo,
make sure and tell your ma
we're getting back to work
first thing tomorrow morning.
Ok, fine.
I'll make sure and tell her,
Mr. Tozawa,
but you remember,
I'm keeping my eye on you.
Whatever you say.
Look at me!
I'm riding a whale!
It's Mr. Whale!
Oh honey, are you all right?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Please don't cry.
Excuse me.
More coffee, please.
No problem, ma'am.
Ugh, my achin' head.
I don't doubt it.
You do realize
you're on your 15th cup.
Have you even been
listening to me?
Yeah, of course I have!
What were we
talkin' about, again?
We were talking about
the recent murders.
There've been
three victims so far.
Now we know the second one
had a guy with her.
But for some reason,
he was left unharmed.
Which means there's a witness
we can talk to.
You think the killer is--
Sure looks that way.
But let's see what this guy
has to say first.
What was it?
I felt something different.
But what?
So how's it taste?
This is the first time I've ever
tried making my own white sauce.
Oh! It's delicious!
Like there's a flavor party
in my mouth!
Well, there's still plenty left
so you guys can have
as much as you want!
Somethin' wrong,
Rihoko, darlin'?
A sale's about to start
at the market!
I gotta go!
So it was 11:45 PM?
You're absolutely
sure about that?
Yes. I remember
checking my watch
to see if we could still catch
the late-night bus home.
But then--
You saw the killer's face,
didn't you?
I did.
I can never forget that face.
Never.
That's all I ask.
Please just say it.
I need to hear it.
"Star light, star bright,
let my love quicken your heart
tonight!"
It wasn't human!
That thing.
What does that even mean?
"Star light, star bright,
let my love quicken your heart
tonight!"
I got no clue.
And that's not the only thing
that's buggin' me.
Yeah?
Yeah, the time of the attacks,
11:45 at night.
All three were killed
at the same time.
Got any ideas?
That is weird.
Could it be a coincidence?
Wow!
Paprika's pretty cheap!
You know,
I always run into you.
Tell me something.
Do you always go
shopping by yourself?
Where's your mom?
Well, she's been kind of busy
with her work lately.
So, you like your mother,
right?
And why is that?
Duh!
Why wouldn't I like my mom?
She's family!
Um, I gotta go.
My street is this way.
Good to see you.
Bye-bye!
Oh!
Thank you so much, Mister!
No!
Please, wait!
This feeling.
It's different.
What is it?
Mister,
is there something wrong?
It's incredible.
No, I'm fine.
Would you like to
have a cracker?
Sump'm wrong?
It's nothin'.
I'm fine.
Not to be nosey,
but is that all
you're gonna have
for lunch, Mister?
Yes.
Why do you ask?
Don't ya have
a girlfriend or someone
who can make your lunch?
Well, I guess
I could ask my girlfriend,
but I hardly get to see her
anymore.
I've been doing
a lot of thinking lately,
and I think
I may buy a house.
If I did, then she and I
could live together.
Then I would be
able to see her everyday
and she wouldn't have to be
lonely ever again.
Wow! A house?
I would love to live in a house.
I hope my mom and I
can get one someday.
Hey, have you thought about
what you want your house
to look like?
It's got a big living room
with hardwood floors.
It should have a fireplace
right here.
Y'know, so we can relax
in front of it
after we have our dinner.
That's nice.
You like your girlfriend a lot.
Don't ya, Mister?
I'm very lucky.
She's incredibly beautiful.
And she's the nicest girl
I've ever met.
No one could ever
compare to her.
That means my break time's over.
Sorry, but I have to
get back to work now.
Mister,
you gonna be here tomorrow?
Yep, every afternoon.
In that case,
let's meet up tomorrow
and I'll bring you lunch!
That sounds great, thank you!
Director Takayama,
would you care to explain
why you have ignored
our repeated requests
for a progress report?
I believe we deserve
an explanation.
You're well aware
that the Special Section's work
is top-secret.
And must remain so to keep
sensitive information
from being leaked.
While quoting corporate policy
may provide you
a convenient excuse,
if you cannot prove your
section is obtaining results,
while it bleeds
the company's coffers dry;
its very existence
must be called into question.
Come now,
can't you give us anything?
We're not exaggerating
when we say
this company's future
depends on the Witchblade.
Let me put it this way.
We have uncovered
a veritable treasure chest.
All we need do is open it.
Why can't you be
any more specific, Takayama?
Because I have
yet to look inside, Wado.
I would hate to disappoint
you gentlemen if our findings
are less than stellar.
Another lame excuse.
I realize the boardroom is
no place to bring up the past,
but I feel it should be noted
that back in college,
when Takayama and I were
in the rowing club together,
he was always
in the position behind me.
He stared at my back
the entire time.
That may be.
But when rowing,
competitors face backwards.
In other words, Wado,
I was always closer
to the goal than you.
I was referring to rowing.
And nothing further.
All of these more recent murders
have taken place
near this radio station.
And they all happened
at exactly 11:45.
So unless it's all
one big coincidence,
we should see him soon.
Yeah, right.
Hey! Melony!
No! Get back!
What the hell are you!
Please Miss,
just say it once.
"Star light, star bright,
let my love quicken your heart
tonight!"
Hurry, run!
Go on, get outta here!
All righty.
Now that we know
who we're dealin' with,
we can find all the info
we need on him right here!
Is this legal?
I woulda thought the Police
Database was off limits.
This article.
"Honorable death
in the line of duty."
He was a cop?
It's dated the year
before the Great Quake.
Tozawa!
You've got some real stones.
You think you can just waltz
right into my station house?
Come to get your ass kicked,
huh? Huh?
Whoa, whoa, chill out!
Last time I checked,
the general public
was welcome
at all police stations.
The "general public" refers
to honest, upright citizens!
Not the likes of--
That's Muraki.
Muraki?
All right, you bastard!
What's the meaning of this?
Well, sir, you know
all those unsolved murders?
He's the guy behind 'em all.
Like hell he is!
You better tell me
what you're up to right now!
C'mon! Spill!
Easy, big guy!
There's no reason
for you to freak!
And now the kitchen.
Custom designed just for her.
My girlfriend
is an amazing cook.
And there.
So, who makes a better lunch,
me or your girlfriend?
Ah, good question.
I'd say you're
both equally good.
Oh no, looks like it's time
to get back to work.
Well, I'll be back tomorrow
with another lunch for you!
You haven't finished
drawing your house yet
and I wanna see it!
How is this even possible?
How can a dead man
go on a killing spree?
Maybe the killer
just looks a lot like him.
Mom!
Hey, you!
Guess what?
I made a new friend!
He's really cool!
You met a boy?
That's great!
Well, I wouldn't exactly
call him a "boy".
He's real nice!
I even made lunch for him.
Yeah? Then you'll have to
introduce me to him someday.
Yeah!
So, how's work going?
You guys figure it out yet?
No, no luck yet.
But a bunch of the same clues
keep poppin' up.
Like this phrase
we keep hearing:
"Star light, star bright.
Let my love quicken your heart
tonight."
Hey, now that brings back
memories!
"Sakura's Twinkle Date"!
I was a huge fan
of that radio show,
I listened all the time.
Radio?
It was the best show
on the air.
Every night, 11:45.
S-A-K-U-R-A--
Wait, it aired at 11:45?
S-A-K-U-R-A,
Sakura! Sakura.
Dah! Detective Nakata!
Look, I'm sorry I got
so worked up earlier.
But what you're tryin'
to do here is just wrong.
What're ya talkin' about?
Don't play dumb!
I know what you're up to!
You wanna expose the cover-up
we did on Muraki's death.
Well, that's never
gonna happen!
So just give it up!
Just leave it in the past.
What?
Yusuke, I'm askin' you,
please, let this go.
Muraki was
one of my best officers.
He was a devoted cop,
and sincere to a fault.
But that ethic
led him to suicide.
I lied and said
he died in the line of duty,
to preserve his honor.
What! Suicide?
Are you serious?
I told ya to quit
playin' dumb with me!
Sir, do you know if Muraki
was a fan of a radio show?
It was called,
"Sakura's Twinkle Date".
Damn, where the hell'd you
get all your information?
Muraki told us
he was trying to protect
some radio DJ named Sakura
from a dangerous fan.
But somehow
it backfired on him
and he wound up
being sued for stalking her.
And that's when...
Well, you know how it ends.
He was a victim
of his own emotions.
Then I heard
that Sakura girl was killed
during the Great Quake.
After talking to Nakata,
I'd say
there's no doubt about it.
Yeah, the person responsible
for these murders
has to be
the deceased Officer Muraki.
But why is someone
who's supposed to be dead...
I dunno.
All I do know is
there's gotta be
one helluva secret
bein' kept under wraps.
Our best bet now is to
try to talk to Muraki himself.
Please no more.
Make it stop!
I can't take any more of this!
Well, that's convenient.
What the hell are you?
What are you doing here?
I never should have
come back to life!
Please, set me free!
Destroy this cursed body!
Please!
I don't understand.
Is that what I...
Oh, God.
What the hell are they?
What are the X-Cons?
Maybe he's runnin' late.
Riko!
Oh, hi, Mom!
What's the matter?
Your friend couldn't make it?
I guess not because
he's never been late like this.
He's probably really busy
with work or something.
Yeah.
Hey, you want me
to walk you home now?
[Music]
What do I do?
All of a sudden,
I have to go to a stupid party!
And with Takayama,
of all people!
Yuck!
I bet it'll be nothing but
a bunch of high-class snobs.
How boring!
I'm no good
at that kinda stuff.
I can't make small-talk!
I'd rather be drinkin'
with everyone at Mariko's!
Man, I wanna go home!
Let's hit the baths
as soon I get back, okay?