I apologize about
what happened to Nora.
I'm not concerned.
I believe she had reached
the full extent of her power.
Regardless, I find no reason
to investigate
Reina's child any further.
But Father,
what if she possesses...
That is simply
not possible, my dear.
No mere human could ever
surpass the Neo-Genes.
It is inconceivable.
[Music]
So um...
We're going to your house,
right?
What's it like, exactly?
Well, it's not really a house.
I live on the top floor
of a condominium.
It may be different
from what you're used to.
Oh.
Okay.
It's all right.
There's no reason
for you to be concerned.
You're my daughter now and
I will take good care of you.
Yeah.
I have relocated
the child to my home.
As of today,
I shall begin a record
of our mother-daughter
relations.
Oh, wow!
This place is huge!
There is a bedroom
for you as well.
Here you are.
No way!
It's almost like
a toy store in here!
I wasn't sure
of your preferences,
so I purchased a variety.
If you find anything lacking,
please let me know.
It's more than enough,
thank you.
You can play until dinnertime.
Oh!
I can help!
I'm a good cook,
I do it all the time!
No thank you.
It is the mother's job
to prepare the meals.
Children need their playtime.
'Kay.
But if you change your mind,
just come and get me
and I'll be happy to help!
I'll let you know.
At this point in time,
the child's actions
appear to be normal.
Some minor agitation
is apparent,
but there's no cause
for concern.
I have yet to experience
any noteworthy changes myself.
Everything is proceeding
extraordinarily well.
This situation
is so screwed up!
This sucks!
They can't do that!
Real mother, my ass!
Melony is Rihoko's
real mother!
It's not right!
"Children become what
their parents make of 'em".
Man, people were pretty smart
back in the day.
Hey, Mari, ya ever
heard of Judge Ooka?
Betcha, foster parents
raised him.
It's not our place
to be buttin' in, old man.
Well, it still sucks.
Melony's made her decision.
You're right.
But she's sufferin' for it.
I hate seein' her
down in the dumps like this.
Man, there's gotta be
another side to all this.
Dammit!
The Cloneblade
is in its final stages, Father.
Once Maria
is outfitted with it,
we could achieve results
we never thought possible.
I must say
I've been impressed
with Maria's newfound
motivation to train.
The promise of a reward
for her efforts
has proven effective.
Great work today, Maria.
You've been in a good mood
lately, what's up?
Grandpa promised
once I finish all this,
he'd tell me about my mom!
So hurry up and put
the Cloneblade on me, okay?
I'm sorry, Maria,
but not yet;
the Cloneblade is still
in its fine-tuning stages.
Now there's one last thing.
This way.
Why not?
Why can't you put it on yet?
I've been working so hard
all this time!
I hate them all.
Hope they all die!
Hey, you know what?
My mom would do anything
for me.
Whatever I want,
and all I gotta do is ask.
She'd never do
anything bad to me.
And she'll always wanna be
with me no matter what!
Wonder what she's like.
I gotta meet her.
Her mental development
is progressing much slower
than her physical growth.
Each girl does develop
at her own rate.
Whoa, neat!
It's like at a restaurant!
Let's eat, shall we?
Okay, thank you so much!
Delicious!
Is it? I'm glad.
Soup's good too.
I can taste the butter
and milk flavors.
But there's no consommé,
is there?
I only put in
what the recipe called for.
You mean, you don't
normally cook like this?
No.
It's pretty impressive that
you can make such yummy food
when you don't really cook.
Isn't that what
a mother's supposed to do?
You're the best cook
in the whole wide world, Riko!
Is something wrong?
Oh, no!
Thanks for dinner!
Your bedroom's down the hall,
remember?
I know, but we haven't said
goodnight to each other yet.
Oh! Good night, Rihoko.
I can do that if you want!
Let me brush the back for you!
Thanks,
but I can do it myself.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Good night.
Mom! Quit movin' around!
Well, stop tickling so much!
No.
Not anymore.
Miss Reina is my mom now.
Day 1 of our cohabitation
has come to an end.
There are no incidents
worthy of report.
I have yet to experience
any changes physically or...
Revision:
It seems that my own
Blade-induced breakdown
has begun.
End report.
You don't seem to be
eating much, either.
Why are you ignoring my calls?
What if I need you
for an emergency assignment?
Don't tell me you've forgotten
about our contract.
I'm backing out.
You what?
There's nothing to fight for.
I quit.
Not like I need
the money anymore.
Don't be stupid!
Like it or not, you are
the bearer of the Witchblade!
You can't simply quit
whenever you feel like it!
Fine then, take it.
Go ahead!
Cut off my arm,
do whatever it takes.
I don't want it.
Come on!
What the hell
do you think you're doing!
Let go of me, you jerk!
I said, let go!
Woo-hoo!
Why'd you do that?
Like I said, you're the bearer
of the Witchblade.
I refuse to let you
sabotage yourself any further.
Yeah, well...
I did tell you to do
whatever you had to.
Hey.
You used to go out
with Reina Soho, didn't you?
You don't think
you could be Riko's father.
In all honesty,
it's not an impossibility.
That's it?
That's all I get?
Whatever.
Guess it's
none of my business anyway.
I shouldn't care.
I'm not Riko's mother anymore.
So...
How about we go outside?
What for?
Well, the weather's really nice,
we could take a walk,
or go shopping.
Don't worry about the shopping,
I'll do that later.
The only thing you should
concern yourself with
is playing.
'Kay.
What's the matter?
It's um...
Nothin'.
Umm...
What's wrong?
Stay back!
I'll be fine!
Go to your room and play!
'Kay.
Ladies and gentlemen of
the Witchblade Project, welcome.
You are the chosen few
who will carry the Doji Group
into the future.
I have the utmost faith
that you will make
mass-production
of the Witchblade a reality.
While I respect the efforts
of the Special Division
up to this point,
they've wasted a good deal
of our time and budget
with no real results.
The Bio Division will not
fall prey to those mistakes.
We will achieve
what others could not!
I don't know, Director.
He's serious about
taking us down.
Interesting.
So Wado and Bio Division
have formed their own
Witchblade research team?
It's already causing trouble
in our division.
Perhaps it would be a good idea
if you took Masane somewhere
and returned to the office.
No.
Let him do
what he wants for now.
But sir, Wado's confidence
makes me think
there might be something
to all his claims.
He's already failed once.
He won't do any better
this time.
Hello? Director!
When something happens,
don't blame me.
Need to get back to work?
I know you're pretty busy.
This is work.
For both of us.
We need you back on your feet
as soon as possible.
So, where're you takin' me?
To your old hometown.
We dug into your past life,
from before the Great Quake.
And that led us
to this place.
Here?
This is where you grew up.
You lived here
until you were 17.
What about
my parents or siblings?
We tried our best
to find that out.
But nothing turned up.
We did find out
that the children and staff
from this home
were caught in the Great Quake
while they were
on a field trip to Tokyo.
Every single one of them died.
Having lost
all of its residents,
the home was shut down.
I used to live here?
I don't remember it.
But you did live here,
for over 17 years.
It's only the last six
you've lived as Masane Amaha.
Yasuka Ohara.
That's your name.
Yasuka Ohara?
Now that you hear it again,
does it ring any bells?
Not really.
Nothing specific.
So none of this
is coming back to you?
Nothing looks familiar?
No, not a thing.
What's wrong?
There's a piece missing.
It's gotta be
around here somewhere.
I'll look for it.
The girl who lived here.
She was the real me.
But I don't know her.
I don't remember
that version of me.
It's no use.
I can't remember anything.
How naïve of me.
What do you mean?
You're simple-minded enough.
I thought
coming here would help.
Thanks, I think.
Did you find
the missing puzzle piece?
No.
But I found something.
This.
It's just like I am.
Rough around the edges.
Out of place.
This rock is me.
The family that I never had.
My old self that somehow
got erased in the Great Quake.
They're gone.
And they're never coming back.
And nothing can
ever make up for it.
It's kinda sad.
I shouldn't have
brought you here.
I knew this wasn't going to be
easy for you, but I'm sorry.
So...
what about your family?
I realized you've never
mentioned them.
Bet you were a spoiled rich kid,
weren't you?
Much like you, I'm not sure.
What do you mean?
I don't know my family.
My mother died
when I was very young,
and my father
was hardly home.
Always working.
We were connected by blood
and that was about all.
Wow!
Then I met you.
Seeing you and Rihoko,
I finally understand
what family is.
Wait.
We seemed like a family?
Really?
Yes.
Without a doubt.
You are mother and daughter.
You're right.
And I'm nothing without her.
She's all I have.
She's my...
my everything.
Riko.
Rihoko.
Isn't she magnificent?
I cannot express to you
how proud I am
that you've come this far.
My darling young child.
Grandpa!
Now tell me about my mom!
You promised!
Why do you want to know
so badly?
Knowing who your mother is
isn't going to change
anything, my dear.
Of course it will, Grandpa!
I've never had a mother,
so I wanna know all about her.
Come on!
This is my mom!
There it is again.
That's the same genetic code
from before.
Yeah. So that means
the father's genes are the same.
You got it.
From what I can tell,
all the Neo-Genes in this file
share the genes of one man.
Basically,
they've all got the same father.
Which means
they're all related.
Guess that's why
they call 'em Sisters.
Duh.
That's creepy.
Ya know, I'd like to get
some information on the guy
that's fathered
all these Neo-Genes.
Why dontcha pull up his file?
'Cause it's not here.
It might've gone missing,
but I bet the real deal
is that the NSWF is keepin'
his info top secret.
Yeah, figures.
Hey, take a look
at these chicks, kid;
what a bunch of hotties!
Ya know, there's not
a single one of 'em
I'd kick outta bed.
Hold it there!
What are these files?
What, these?
They're the data files
on the mothers.
The mothers?
These are the women
who have provided their genes
to create the newest generation
of Neo-Genes.
Hi, Mom.
I hope I get to see you soon!
I didn't ask you for that.
I know.
But I thought
you might like it.
Um, would you mind if
I helped you fix dinner tonight?
I'm still working real hard
at becoming a better cook.
And plus...
I wanna spend
more time with you.
You know, talking.
Getting to know you better.
Is something wrong?
It appears to be
a hyper-secretion of tear fluid.
It seems that the changes
occurring within
my endocrine system
have begun to affect
my bodily functions.
So, are you all right?
What is this?
This sensation?
I've never felt this.
What is it?
[Music]
How are you doing?
I hope you're okay.
I never got to show you
my plans for our house.
Guess it's too late now.
Don't forget,
your hangover medicine
is in that second drawer
in the kitchen.
And if you get hungry,
I left some Salisbury steak
in the fridge.
Oh!
And when you buy green onions,
make sure you get the good kind.
Please try not to
drink too much, okay?
And make sure you eat
so you can stay healthy.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.