So much for us to talk about.
Where to begin?
Suppose I'll tell you
how I've carried out
the Hoshin Project
from the shadows.
You what?
Well, I've been getting
my hands dirty for you.
You may not wanna admit it,
but you know that you've
gotta make a sacrifice
here and there if you
actually wanna get things done.
Whether you believe
it's right or wrong,
the efficiency is undeniable.
But you?
You're a good guy
and all that junk
so you can't bring
yourself to do it.
What in the hell are you saying?
[OHTENKUN] To be frank, I did
all the things you wanted to
but weren't capable of.
Not to get too poetic,
but I'm the mirror
that reflects the
darkness within you.
Conversely, you're the mirror
that reflects the light
within me.
[clock chiming]
[OHTENKUN] Time to make
up your mind, Taikobo.
What'll it be?
You've got a big choice
to make here.
Remember how you always
thought you'd be alone
after you lost your clan?
[TAIKOBO] Yes, but I also
remember being taken to
the Sennin world to
train as a Doshi.
[OHTENKUN] Right, and the first
thought that popped into
your head when you were
assigned the Hoshin Project was
"I'll show you."
[TAIKOBO]
But the allies I've made.
All of it.
Everything that I've ever done.
Everything that makes me me.
Am I just supposed
to throw it all away?
We're gonna die!
[TAIKOBO, SUPUSHAN gasp]
We've made barrier contact.
Significant damage endured--
29 percent surface destroyed.
The barrier is down!
He pulled it off!
Thanks, Yozen.
[YOKAI 7A]
Commander Bunchu!
Kongrong Mountain
has collided with us!
The Tsutenho...
It's been destroyed!
Damn you, Ohtenkun.
[YOZEN]
They followed through.
Taikobo.
Thank you for having
so much faith in me.
I've got to pull it together.
I'm so utterly exhausted
I can barely even maintain
my human form.
I need to find someplace
safe to hide where I can rest.
[OHTENKUN] Hey, sorry to
be the bearer of bad news,
Bunchu, but, well, Chotenkun?
Yozen totally annihilated him.
[chuckles]
The bastard tucked
that victory under his belt
and ran like hell.
[BUNCHU] I assumed as much,
as I assume you're Yozen.
[OHTENKUN]
Pardon?
[BUNCHU] Transformation is
the genius Doshi's specialty,
after all, and I'm certain
that the real Ohtenkun
would rather die in battle
with Yozen instead of
admitting to me that he failed.
And the other option
is even more farfetched,
but I can't believe
he would betray me
and let Yozen escape.
So then...
Simple deduction tells me
I should annihilate you.
[OHTENKUN]
Will you just relax, Bunchu?
I didn't wanna step out
of line and make the call
to kill him without you
giving me the direct order.
I mean, we all know who he is.
I'm not gonna just kill
Lord Tsuten Kyoshu's son
without the go-ahead.
[BUNCHU]
I see.
But, that's hardly
an acceptable excuse.
His lineage doesn't change
the fact that he's still
our enemy.
Well how does this
work for an excuse?
Yozen is so depleted he
can barely even hobble
right now.
There's no doubt his Kongrong
buddies will try to rescue him.
It'll be a small group
for the sake of stealth,
but they're gonna send their
best to get the job done.
I'd even wager that Taikobo
himself will join them.
And they'll walk right
into their own graves.
That's why I let him live.
We couldn't ask for a better
piece of bait than Yozen.
I never realized you
were just as cunning
as that fox, Dakki.
Although your devious
maneuvers could prove useful,
the rest of the Juttenkun will
handle things without you.
I have no intention of
letting you out of my sight.
Aw, Bunchu, you don't trust me?
[BUNCHU]
Don't take it personally.
I don't trust anybody.
We have full contact
with Kingo Island.
At the very least, we have the
chance for a fair fight now.
Unfortunately...
Kongrong Mountain's
drained of energy,
and my power is
just as worn out.
[TAIKOBO]
Koshu.
[KOSHU]
Save your pity, please.
You just stay focused
on what needs to be done.
Right.
Okay!
First things first,
we gotta rescue Yozen.
[GENSHI] And just how
do you intend to do that?
I'm infiltrating Kingo
Island myself this time.
Yozen's too important
to us to risk losing.
Whoa, hang on a sec! You're
our commander, aren't you?
It's not like we can
really risk losing you!
[TAIKOBO] I'm returning command
to Master Genshi Tenson
until I can make it back.
I owe Yozen big time,
and the last thing I'm gonna do
is leave him on
his own in there.
[GENSHI]
I understand.
Bring him back to us, Taikobo.
[GYOKUTEI]
I'd like to come along as well.
Yozen has become
like a son to me.
So I hope you don't
mind me joining you.
Of course you can.
So this is what it looks
like inside of Kingo?
[GYOKUTEI] I have to admit, it
certainly appears more advanced
than Kongrong.
Now that I'm here, it's really
no wonder we underestimated
the firing range
of the Tsutenho.
[GYOKUTEI] So, how do
you plan on finding Yozen?
[TAIKOBO]
Well, I figure we should find
the barrier control room.
If we're lucky, we'll find him
hiding somewhere close to it.
Something feels weird.
This place is supposed
to be crawling with Sennin,
so don't you think we should've
run into one by now?
[TAIKOBO]
Not necessarily.
Especially if they've
already realized we're here.
They've probably withdrawn
all of their Sennin
and Doshi as part of their plan.
So we've gotta stay alert.
Yeah! You've got a point!
Gotta make sure we
don't fall for any traps--
[yelling]
[SUPUSHAN]
What's happening?
Master, help!
Supu, no!
[QUEEN] Ever since
the beginning of time,
the number three has
been said to emanate
a powerful aura
of pure sensuality.
[VENUS] That is a well-known
fact, my dear sister, Queen.
But do you suppose we were
the inspiration for such belief?
[QUEEN]
Without a doubt.
For there's nothing sexier
than a beautiful woman
who's also strong.
[VENUS]
We are the Three Unsho Sisters!
[MADONNA growls]
[VENUS purrs]
[QUEEN chuckles]
I wonder if Taikobo
and his crew have already
snuck in here somewhere.
Hey, Tenka, you doing all right?
Don't forget you've
still got that nasty gash
in your gut.
Try to pace yourself.
I'm good.
I appreciate the concern,
but it looks worse than it is--
nothing I can't handle.
So what's the next step
now that we've made it in?
Come over here and
take a look below us.
These floating spheres
are referred to as stars,
and the stars that shine
brightest are the Juttenkun's
personal chambers.
But that one, the giant
black star at the center?
That's the core.
It serves as the control
center for all of Kingo.
It's safe to assume Bunchu's
hunkered down in there
right now, throwing out
orders and threatening
minions with his glowing eye.
[HIKO]
Bunchu.
So, just what the hell
are the Juttenkun anyway?
[VENUS] They're the top
officers of Kingo Island,
led by a sadistic runt
named Ohtenkun.
What makes them a
particularly troublesome group
of Sennin is their mastery
of the space paopei,
Juzetsujin.
Now I'm more confused.
[VENUS] Just remember, if you
notice an octagonal mark
like this, take extreme caution.
[GYOKUTEI] I'm guessing
this eight-sided mark
is the entrance to
their hyperspace.
What do we do now?
Well, we're not leaving Supu,
so we're going in.
[SUPUSHAN whimpering]
A giant Capybara?
Did we stumble into
some creepy fairytale?
[SONTENKUN]
Hi, guys.
[SUPUSHAN] Ah! Did that stuffed
animal just talk to us?
[SONTENKUN]
I like to play games.
Is there a game
you like to play?
How about the name game?
Tell us who you are.
[SONTENKUN] I'm Sontenkun,
one of the Kingo Juttenkun.
And you're guests in my
hyperspace, Kaketsujin.
[TAIKOBO, GYOKUTEI]
He's a Juttenkun?
[SONTENKUN] I've created
an entire world of toys.
And the two of you,
Gyokutei of the Twelve Sennin,
and Taikobo,
commander of Kongrong,
will soon be added to
my vast collection.
Don't be so sure.
Whoa!
The sonic-speed Zansenken!
It took out a Juttenkun
in a flash!
'Fraid not.
Look a little more closely.
[GYOKUTEI] There was nothing
inside that thing but stuffing.
[SONTENKUN laughing]
Astounding observation
skills, Gyokutei.
Y'see, each and every
toy in this room is me.
Cut 'em up all you want,
it won't do any good.
I know he's taunting us,
but I think it's the truth.
These toys...
None of them
are his actual body.
Which means he's controlling
them from somewhere safe.
Only a coward would refuse
to show himself in combat.
I'll slice this whole
room down to stuffing--
destroy every last toy
you can hide within.
Jeez! I couldn't
even see you move!
What d'ya expect from
one of the Twelve Sennin?
[SONTENKUN]
Argh! Oh, silly me.
I knew I was
forgetting something.
I've also got the ability
to self-destruct!
What?!
The bastard can explode?
[SONTENKUN]
Just play with me already!
How does kuzushi shogi sound?
All right, fine.
Go on, Supu, you play
with the pushy little creep.
But why? You know it's
gonna be some kind of trap!
And besides, aren't we
in a hurry to find Yozen?
The only way we're ever
gonna get out of here
is by defeating him!
[SUPUSHAN]
Uh...
If we're doing this,
I'm hoping you have
some plan in mind.
[TAIKOBO] I'm pretty sure I'm
getting close to figuring out
where this jerk is hiding.
[SUPUSHAN]
Well, if this is gonna help,
I guess I really
don't have a choice.
[SONTENKUN laughs]
[SUPUSHAN] If we're playing
games, I'd rather play go.
Hey, I said go!
[SONTENKUN] Then we agree,
kuzushi shogi it is.
We'll decide who goes
first with a round
of rock-paper-scissors.
[SUPUSHAN]
Uh... Yeah, that's fair.
[SONTENKUN]
One. Two. Three.
[BOTH]
Shoot!
[SONTENKUN]
Yay, I'm already winning!
Why did I play rock?
I never play rock!
[SONTENKUN]
All right, then,
that just leaves the difficult
tiles to take care of.
Let's see, I think
I'll start over here.
Careful now...
Slow. Slow. Slo--
It's about time!
I didn't think I was
ever gonna get a turn!
[SONTENKUN]
Aw, rats!
[SUPUSHAN]
Got it.
Now just one more!
[SONTENKUN]
You're actually pretty good.
[SUPUSHAN chuckles]
[SUPUSHAN] I've never even
played this game before,
but it's almost shockingly easy!
Time to end this.
I'll finish him off
with one big move!
[SUPUSHAN yelling]
[SONTENKUN]
Yipee!
Thanks for breaking up
the tiles for me!
Mine, mine, mine, mine!
I've got more than
half the tiles!
So I win and you lose!
[SUPUSHAN yelling]
Oh, no!
[SONTENKUN laughing]
One thing I forgot to mention.
If you lose to me in a game,
you get to spend the
rest of your life as a toy.
So, who wants to
play with me next?
If you win, I promise to
turn him back to normal.
[TAIKOBO]
I'll play your game.
[SONTENKUN]
And I accept your challenge.
I actually like these types
of games when I'm not in
a hurry trying to save
my friend's life.
So, what do you wanna play?
I'm fine with
whatever you've got.
[SONTENKUN] Well...
Concentration's always fun.
I haven't played
concentration in ages.
Sure, let's do it.
[SONTENKUN]
Yay!
Any luck?
You said you were on the verge
of locating him earlier.
Hush.
Keep your voice down.
He's hidden somewhere
among the toys in this room.
In fact, he probably
even looks like a toy.
That explosion of his?
He only blew himself
up to distract us.
And there's only one
reason why he would even
need to distract us like that.
He knew he was in danger
of getting sliced to bits
at any second.
Just trust me and
follow my lead.
[SONTENKUN]
Ta-da!
I found the deck of cards.
I'll go ahead and
lay 'em out for us.
Hold on!
I'll be the one to
lay out the cards.
I can't just sit back and
risk you cheating, after all.
[SONTENKUN]
I would never cheat!
What a terrible thing
to say to a toy.
Behold!
The amazing and mind-blowing
card-dealing skills
of Taikobo the Magician!
[SONTENKUN]
Wow! You look like a huge dork!
[TAIKOBO]
Chi!
[SONTENKUN]
Whoa!
[TAIKOBO]
That should do the trick.
[SONTENKUN]
That was awesome!
I totally take back
the dork comment!
You ready?
Let's see who goes first.
One, two...
[BOTH]
Shoot!
Wow, what a moron!
You really played paper twice?
[SONTENKUN]
Rats, that was dumb!
This one and this one!
[GYOKUTEI] You got a
pair--on your first try.
How'd you do that?
[TAIKOBO chuckles]
Oh, a magician never
reveals his secrets.
No, really, I'll tell
you how I did it.
I simply looked at all the
cards while I was dealing
and memorized
where they landed.
[TAIKOBO chuckles]
What?
A skill made possible
by my supreme powers
of dynamic vision
and memorization!
[laughing]
[GYOKUTEI]
Pretty cheap if you ask me.
But I guess it's an
impressive form of cheating.
[TAIKOBO]
These two cards! And these!
This card and this card
and this card and this card!
Oh, man! I forgot how
much fun this game can be.
I'm so happy only flowers
could visually represent
my joy!
[SONTENKUN] That cheat of yours
is actually the perfect way
to play this game,
and it's my own dumb fault
for letting you deal the
cards in the first place.
But you know what?
Memory can prove to be a rather
vague and precarious thing.
It has the tendency
to betray people.
Oh, c'mon, don't give me that.
You're just a sore--
What?
It's not a match?
--[SONTENKUN] Lucky me!
--No way!
[SONTENKUN]
I finally get to take a turn.
[chuckles, hums]
And here we go.
Three of clubs.
[TAIKOBO] Yeah, and it's exactly
where I remember it being.
[SONTENKUN]
Let's try this one!
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[SONTENKUN] This looks
like a good one to pick.
And this...
Yay! Look, I got
two pairs in a row!
What? How could you
possibly know where--?
[SONTENKUN] You're not
actually surprised, are you?
Did you forget
that this is my room?
Everything in here is
conjured from my thoughts.
That's how the Juzetsujin works.
It does what I want.
Here, let me show you.
This is how much
control I have in here!
What?
He turned every card
into an ace of hearts!
Now I see.
The game was rigged
from the get-go.
His paopei controls everything,
that's how he can turn
the loser into a toy.
But of course,
the master never loses.
The space paopei, Juzetsujin,
literally manipulates space.
And that's why the
Juttenkun are so powerful.
This entire time,
he's been challenging us
to games we could
never possibly win.
[SONTENKUN laughs]
Way to finally catch on, genius.
I'm already holding
26 cards here.
Gee, I wonder if I'll happen
to find the winning pair?
What do you think?
Are ya ready to
get turned into a toy?
[TAIKOBO]
Gyokutei.
The winning move is up to you.
I've got it under control.
[TAIKOBO yelling]
You just hang in there.
[YOZEN grunting]
[YOZEN panting]
[YOZEN crying]
[YOZEN]
Master...
[OHTENKUN chuckles]