[BUNCHU grunts]
[panting]
[BUNCHU groans]
Huh. Isn't this interesting?
You appear to be capable,
but it's quite obvious you don't
have the bones of a Sennin.
Who're you?
[TSUTEN]
My name is Tsuten Kyoshu.
I am known as the patriarch
of both the Sennin world
and Kingo Island.
[BUNCHU gasps]
[BUNCHU] From that day
forward, I had a new goal.
I would train in the Sennin
world and strive to serve Yin.
[BUNCHU] Under the tutelage
of Tsuten Kyoshu,
my strength rapidly increased.
[BUNCHU] I fought for
one purpose alone:
to protect the Yin Dynasty
no matter the cost.
[BUKICHI panting]
[BUKICHI]
The last team is finally here!
[GENSHI] Excellent! You've
done great work, Bukichi!
Thanks! I'm just following
Master Taikobo's orders!
Guess that's everyone, huh?
Master Genshi.
I believe I owe you an apology.
I left without telling you.
Yozen. It's good to see
that you've returned.
[BUKICHI]
He doesn't look sick.
[gasps] Why are they
all still affected?
Ohtenkun's soul was released!
I saw it!
[GENSHI gasps]
[YOZEN] His mites
shouldn't have power...
...unless they're being
controlled by someone else.
Could Dakki be to blame?
If you have a moment,
there's something
I'd like to discuss.
[GENSHI]
Not now.
This takes precedence.
I just received an urgent
message from Taikobo.
He says they're
going to keep Bunchu
at Kingo Island's power reactor
and he needs the rest
of us to get there
as soon as we've recovered.
Then we'll all attack at once.
When they've recovered?
[gasps] How exactly is that
supposed to happen now?
Killing Ohtenkun was said to
be the only way to heal them
and they're still drained.
[GENSHI]
But hope is not yet lost.
What Taikobo has done requires
us to take immediate action.
It's time!
[YOZEN, BUKICHI gasp]
[GENSHI]
Come here, now!
[SUPUSHAN]
Roger!
We're here and happy
to be of service.
Always glad to provide services!
No! What am I seeing?
That hippo has a mustache!
Well, that wasn't exactly
the welcome I was expecting.
But as a gentleman
and Supushan's father,
I'll excuse it this once.
You may call me Supu Papa.
His... what?
[GENSHI]
Greetings, friend.
Good to see you.
Perhaps it will
help you understand
if you know more
about Supushan's past.
[GENSHI] His story begins in
a land known as Supu Valley,
located far off in the west.
Mama makes the best cupcakes
in all of Supu Valley!
[GENSHI] Supushan's life
with Supu Mama and Supu Papa
was a peaceful,
carefree existence.
[GENSHI] Supu Papa
provided for his family
by serving as my means
of transportation.
He was compensated
most handsomely.
[GENSHI] But then, 1,500
years ago, a tragedy occurred.
[CHOKOMEI chuckles]
[GENSHI] Chokomei attacked
their quiet village.
[CHOKOMEI]
It's no dream.
I'm that noble knight born
under the destiny of the rose!
Now, who's up for a
heroic fight against me?
[laughing]
[CHOKOMEI] Hmm. A threat has
arrived from Kingo Island,
but nary a soul has come
to halt my conquest.
[CHOKOMEI]
Uh? Hark!
That beard!
It belongs to the founder
of Kongrong--Genshi Tenson!
[GENSHI laughs]
[GENSHI] If you know me,
you know I have clairvoyance,
and I've foreseen your actions.
[gasps]
[CHOKOMEI]
Have you?
You are right hand to the man
they call Tsuten Kyoshu,
and I did not want
to leave my pupils
to handle you on their own.
I figure fighting you by myself
will result in fewer victims.
[CHOKOMEI]
Perfectly fine by me.
I look forward to it!
I do love battling
a stronger opponent
and enhancing my skills.
Genshi Tenson!
I challenge you!
[GENSHI]
All right.
Let's go, Supu Papa! Transform!
[SUPU PAPA]
Rogering that, indeed!
[gasps]
Transformation!
[GENSHI]
Adults of their kind
have the ability
to take new forms.
They become magnificent
spirit beasts
with unique sets of powers.
[CHOKOMEI yells]
[CHOKOMEI groans, pants]
[GENSHI]
With Supu Papa's help,
I succeeded in driving that
pompous rapscallion away.
One small bump on
the road to victory.
I'll simply train harder
for the next round!
[GENSHI]
However...
[SUPU PAPA groans]
[GENSHI] Supu Papa was later
seriously injured in battle
and forced into retirement.
[GENSHI] With their sole
provider now out of work,
the family was in danger
of falling apart.
It was with watery eyes
and heavy hearts
that the Supu Family decided
to send young Supushan
to become an apprentice.
[SUPU MAMA]
Supushan!
[GENSHI] Later, he served as
my ride for a period of time,
and finally, we teamed
him up with Taikobo.
That's so sad.
I'm sorry, Supushan.
I had no idea.
[GENSHI]
The past is the past.
Let's go Supu Papa!
Rogering that, indeed!
Transformation!
[gasps]
[SUPU PAPA]
Energy Drain!
[JIKO gasps]
[gasps]
[GENSHI]
Another beneficial power
I find unique to the adult Supu
is that they can absorb
the effects of any paopei
by literally consuming
the energy produced.
I never would've dreamed
he had that kind of ability.
I just thought
he was a flying hippo.
Fortunately for us,
Taikobo remembered this fact
and called Papa here to help.
I finally feel
like myself again!
Thank you so much for
healing us, Supu Papa.
What a fine example you are!
[DOTOKU]
Yeah! We're so grateful!
[GENSHI]
I see.
So you heard all of this
directly from Oh Eki?
Yes, and in the end
they both lost their lives--
Tsuten Kyoshu and your
former pupil as well.
Be honest with me.
Have you been lying
about the Hoshin Project?
Or is there truth in
what you've told us?
[YOZEN] You originally said
it was a plan to defeat Dakki
and create a new order
in the human world.
But Ohtenkun--I mean Oh Eki--
had a different version.
[YOZEN] He said it was a plan
to capture Dakki's spirit.
With the story changing
so frequently,
I can't help but wonder if
anyone is being honest with me.
[YOZEN] If you just wanted
to get rid of Dakki,
wouldn't it have been easier
to simply send every
Sennin after her?
And when questioned,
you have done nothing
but give excuses
or the most roundabout
explanations.
I beg you to stop the confusion.
Tell me the truth right now--
[GENSHI]
Quiet!
Do not say another
word out here.
She is listening.
[YOZEN gasps]
[YOZEN]
There's no one here.
[GENSHI]
The presence just vanished.
She must never hear the true
purpose of the plan, Yozen.
We will go on as though
we know nothing.
Who was it?
The Signpost of History.
[gasps]
[FUGEN]
Hey, Bo.
I was just thinking...
Do you remember that time
we snuck away with Kokin
to head out on a
little adventure?
Yeah! I haven't thought
about that in ages now.
Kind of a random memory there.
[FUGEN] It's funny
we were brazen enough
to slip a sleeping drug
into Master Genshi's food
just so we could
steal Kokin and fly down
to romp around the human world.
[TAIKOBO]
That was such a blast!
You weren't even part of
the Twelve Elite Sennin yet.
[FUGEN giggles]
[TAIKOBO]
Oh, ho, ho! Nice!
I caught a big one!
It's a speckled trout.
[FUGEN]
So,
is this the reason you wanted
to travel to the human world?
[FUGEN]
You shouldn't catch fish
when you're not even
allowed to eat them.
Yeah, I know that!
Here, look! Catch and release!
Actually, I've got
a gift for you.
It's a fishing hook
of my own design.
What? That won't catch anything!
You only go fishing when
you need to clear your mind.
It helps you think, right?
Don't you feel bad hurting
the fish just so you can focus?
Seems a little unfair.
You'll do just about anything
to avoid conflict, huh?
I could say the exact same
thing for you, ya know.
I guess that's why
we get along so well.
[FUGEN]
I really miss those days.
Yeah. I can't help
but feel nostalgic
for the time when we
didn't have to fight.
Well, doesn't matter
now. Here we are.
Bunchu will be here soon,
so we need to be prepared.
Let's have a snack while we can.
Whoa! Sesame dumplings!
--[phone ringing]
--[TAIKOBO chewing]
Yeah? This is Taikobo and I'm
in the middle of a dumpling?
What? Yozen?!
You're still alive?
Yes, and I'm very happy
to hear you're safe as well.
I'm heading your way
and I'll be bringing
a few friends with me.
You and Fugen stay
right where you are.
We'll need you to act
as bait for Bunchu.
Got it.
Get here as quickly
as you possibly can.
The two of us won't last
more than ten minutes
against that guy.
[TAIKOBO]
All right! Let's get moving!
We gotta go destroy
the power reactor.
Then we'll act as
bait to lure Bunchu.
Once Yozen gets here,
we'll attack as a group.
If we know exactly where he is,
we can avoid
breaking up our forces.
Uh... [groaning]
[FUGEN]
Sorry, Bo.
Don't hate me.
What's happening?
Did you put a tranquilizer in
those dumplings or something?
Not just any tranquilizer.
It's the same drug we
gave to Master Genshi
before our last adventure.
[TAIKOBO groans]
[FUGEN] There's no reason
for both of us to wait.
If the only purpose of us being
there is the keep Bunchu around,
I'll do it myself.
We only need one person
to act as bait.
Please don't...
[FUGEN]
Kokinrikishi, go.
[TAIKOBO]
You idiot...
[FUGEN sighs]
[FUGEN]
I did the right thing.
Bo still has to fight
Dakki on his own.
He has to live.
[FUGEN gasps]
[FUGEN]
He's coming!
I can feel it.
Like the air is
filled with rage.
[FUGEN]
This force...
It's overwhelming.
I've never faced anyone
this strong before.
I'm here looking for Taikobo.
[heart beating]
[FUGEN]
Although...
...I can't shake the feeling
you'll devote yourself
to combat someday.
You do have a shining blade deep
inside your heart, after all.
Hm?
But when that day comes,
I promise I'll be
right beside you.
The least I can do
is offer you that.
[TAIKOBO]
In that moment I realized...
...I didn't want him to
risk his life for me.
I could not allow him to die.
[groans] Damn it, Fugen.
What the hell were you thinking
giving me a sleeping pill?
[TAIKOBO pants]
[TAIKOBO groans]
Stay awake! [groans]
Stay awake!
[FUGEN]
I can't show weakness.
Hello there, Bunchu.
I must admit conflict is
something I cannot abide.
I wonder if we might resolve
this by talking instead?
[BUNCHU scoffs]
Speak, then.
I appreciate it.
[FUGEN]
Tell me.
Why is it that you devote
yourself so strongly to Yin?
[FUGEN]
Because of Dakki,
the people have lost all
faith in the Yin Dynasty.
It's been a long road.
Serving as their guardian deity
for more than 300 years...
You've worked hard
to protect Yin,
but the truth is it has been
doomed for a very long time.
The flow of history has
steered in another direction--
toward Shu.
[FUGEN] So, I'd like
to make a suggestion.
Why don't we work
to defeat Dakki--
cleanse the human
world together?
When our mission is complete,
we will each take a vow never
to enter the human world again.
What do you say?
That was enlivening.
But humans have a thing
called "order of precedence."
I've adopted this
way of thinking.
Yin is number one in my order.
[gasps]
[BUNCHU] What does not
benefit Yin must go,
such as Kingo and Kongrong.
They never have and never will
serve any purpose for Yin.
Therefore, I will destroy them.
It's a simple equation really,
yet one you and Taikobo
find difficult to understand.
[FUGEN]
I knew it.
You made your appearance
here for one reason only,
and that is to watch
Kingo and Kongrong fight
until they destroy each other.
[BUNCHU] You are correct.
It's the only solution.
The Juttenkun opposed me...
...and Tsuten Kyoshu's mind
had long since been decimated.
[FUGEN]
How could you?
Don't you feel indebted to him
for all he's done for you?
[BUNCHU]
Of course I do.
But it's a matter of priority.
I was forced to choose
between him or Yin.
[FUGEN]
It's no use.
I'll never break through
such an iron will!
[BUNCHU]
I'm through talking.
Fugen Shinjin of the Twelve
Elite Sennin of Kongrong...
You shall perish along with
your worthless Sennin world!
[BUNCHU] My relationship
with the Yin Dynasty
began over 300 years ago.
I served the emperor at the time
and was working my way up
to a general's position
at a young age.
[KING OF YIN] You wish
to go to the Sennin world?
Yes.
I understand that I was not born
with the bones of a Sennin.
But after the training
I've put my body through,
I believe I may be
developing them.
I see!
If you were to go to their world
and return here as a Doshi,
that would greatly
benefit the Yin Dynasty.
[SHUSHI]
Bunchu.
[BUNCHU]
Yes?
Please make sure
you come back to us.
Promise?
I want this little one to
grow and learn from you.
Understood, Shushi.
I promise.
[BUNCHU]
Everything I am today...
...began at that moment.