[TENKA]
Who will I fight for now?
What's the point of it all?
I'm not even sure
what my purpose is.
[TENKA]
Throughout my youth,
I always had the towering
figures of my father
and Grand Preceptor
Bunchu to look up to.
It was always my goal to be
just like them when I grew up.
Hey, Tenka.
You'd better surpass me someday.
That's how a son shows
devotion to his father.
There you are, Tenka.
Took you long enough.
I was getting bored waiting.
So you here to stop me?
[TAIKOBO] I couldn't shake
this funny feeling
that you just might
try to do something.
I've gone through
the same thing.
And I remember exactly
how it feels.
Regardless, if you decide to
act on those feelings now,
you're nothing more
than a selfish traitor.
And I'm not gonna
let that happen!
[TENKA]
To surpass my father
and to truly gain his respect--
those were the only
things I've ever wanted.
But how can I achieve them
if he's no longer here?
Who do I fight for?
What is my purpose?
[SUPUSHAN]
Hey, Master...
It's great you've become a
strategist for Seiki and all,
but wouldn't it make more
sense to put the soldiers
in combat training
instead of having them
do farm work?
You might think that
at first, but here,
lemme try to explain
it to you in a way
you can understand.
[SUPUSHAN] You think
I'm an idiot, don't you?
That's not what I'm saying.
It's practically the same!
Farming and training?
[TAIKOBO] Farming tools are
handled much like weapons.
If they think of farming
as combat training,
it'll produce the same results.
But tilling the soil actually
requires a lot more strength
and exertion than swinging
some spears around.
[SUPUSHAN]
That's a really good point!
You've put a lot of
thought into this, Master!
Yep!
But I do still plan on us
winning with as little violence
as possible, though.
All right, what's the deal?
Why'dya keep sneaking
around and spying on me?
[BUKICHI chuckles]
My name's Bukichi.
I work as a lumberjack.
Uh, can I help you
with something?
[BUKICHI] Please train
me as your disciple!
What?
Okay, you can't
be serious, no way.
I'm dead serious!
I've heard all about
your heroic acts
and I highly admire
you, great Doshi!
And especially now that
Lord Ki Sho's appointed you
as our strategist!
Wait, how did you
hear about that?
[SUPUSHAN]
And we here are, yet again.
Master wasting another day
fishing for no reason at all.
Still no luck, huh?
Well, why would fishing
be any different?
[SUPUSHAN] He's been so
discouraged for days now.
We need to get back to the
reason we came to Seiki.
[GENSHI] To prevent the
pervasive spread of pandemonium,
we'll need to act quickly
and establish a new emperor
in the human world.
The most aptly suited
candidate for the position
would have to be Ki Sho,
the Lord of the West.
[SUPUSHAN] We need to get
Ki Sho on our side quickly!
We don't have time for
him to mope around
like this pretending to fish!
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
Any bites today?
Actually, I think I
just caught a big one.
[KI SHO chuckles]
[SUPUSHAN]
Lord Ki Sho!
[KI SHO] Mind if I sit down
and chat with you?
I'd be flattered.
One of the four
great feudal Lords
comes all the way out here
on his own to talk to me?
[KI SHO]
Well, Seiki is a safe land.
I've heard you've proven
yourself an honorable Doshi
many times.
Moreover, you've come
to our world solely
to defeat Dakki.
She held me prisoner
for seven years,
but that was the very least
of her monstrous deeds.
Apart from Emperor Chu,
the Lords of the East,
West, South, and North
comprise the Yin.
After receiving
Dakki's invitation,
we all gathered in Choka.
Oh, you're here! Welcome, Lords!
So glad you could make
it to my little party.
We're gonna have a blast!
Is the pool filled with booze?
Look at that!
[DAKKI] We'll eat some clams,
and chase it with some booze!
Chug, chug, chug,
chug, you'll die from fun!
[KI SHO]
This is sick. Tigers?
[KI SHO] Both the Lord
of the East, Kyo Kanso,
and the Lord of the
South, Gaku Suu,
objected to her cruelty.
[KI SHO] But the Lord
of the North, Su Koko,
submitted to Dakki.
While I saw the truth.
This was her plan
from the start.
She invited us here with
the intent of murdering those
who won't fall in line.
A power play to rein
in the growing influence
of the Four Lords.
Regardless...
I need to warn the Emperor
against her machinations.
Even if speaking out in
opposition costs me my life.
That is the price of
loyalty to one's ruler.
[KI SHO]
Your Majesty.
This is a sickening farce.
A devious plot by your Empress.
Ki Sho!
Oh, well.
You know what that means.
[HIKO]
Your Majesty! Empress!
Oh, and Ki Sho!
I didn't know you were visiting!
[KI SHO] The Buseioh saved
my life by playing dumb,
but Dakki held me prisoner
in the nearby land of Yuri
and reveled in my anguish.
While I was captive,
so many precious things
were stolen from me.
Including my son.
[DAKKI]
So then, Emperor Chu!
Hakuyuko's offered up
his family's treasure
in exchange for
Ki Sho's freedom.
Dakki. I have to ask.
What are your first
impressions of this man?
Well, let's see.
He's certainly very handsome.
[CHU]
What, you think so?
More handsome than me?
[HAKUYUKO] She's as beautiful
as the rumors say.
Although, there's something
false about her beauty.
Get out of my throne
room, Hakuyuko!
[DAKKI] My Temptation doesn't
seem to have an effect on him.
[HAKUYUKO] I'm starting to
lose hope they'll actually
return my father to me.
Coming here has felt like
a mistake since my arrival.
[DAKKI]
Hakuyuko.
A little birdie told me that
you're a master of the Koto.
I'd love for you to
teach me how to play.
Sure.
[koto playing]
[music continues]
[KI SHO]
Hakuyuko.
Y'know what's crazy?
Until I met you, no man has
been able to resist my charms.
And I tried so hard with you.
I hate rejection.
[HAKUYUKO]
Father.
I'm sorry I failed you.
Dakki...
And Kibi...
[DAKKI, KIBI]
Present Lunchtime Banzai!
All right!
Today we'll be making
Hamburg steaks!
First ingredient in this fun
and tasty dish is ground meat!
We'll add a slice of bread
and an egg to help thicken it.
But before we throw
it all in the mix,
we'll soak the bread in some
milk and lightly squeeze it out.
While it soaks...
Here! Let's add
some diced onions,
and don't forget the seasonings!
Now we'll mash and mix the
ingredients in little circles
until it sticks together!
Then divide it into portions
of your preferred size,
and toss it between your hands.
Have fun with it!
You'll then press
a dent in the center,
and cook each side
for thirty seconds.
Right! And I think it's just
about time to flip these!
[DAKKI] Cook on high heat
until you've browned them,
then you're ready to cover
them and reduce the heat
so they don't stick to the pan.
And voilà!
Your Hamburg steak
is ready to eat!
And that's Lunchtime Banzai!
All right, back to
you in the studio!
[MALE SERVANT 4A]
Time to eat, Ki Sho.
The Empress herself
made your lunch today.
She wanted you to know that.
[KI SHO]
Oh! How lovely!
How did Lady Dakki know
Hamburg steak is my favorite?
[MALE SERVANT 4A]
Go on and dig in.
[KI SHO]
How could she do this?
[DAKKI] He even said Hamburg
steak's his favorite!
How could the old fool
not even realize?
A man that dumb couldn't
pose a real threat.
Might as well send
him back to the West.
[CHU]
If you think it's best.
Hey, sis...
You sure we should release him?
Seems there's a good chance
he'll start a rebellion.
[DAKKI chuckles]
That's exactly what
I'm counting on him to do.
Someone has to start the war.
[KI SHO]
So I'd like to ask you.
In light of what's happened,
what should be my next move?
Should I continue to pledge
fealty to the Emperor?
Or should I rise up
and wage war against Yin
for the sake of our people?
You know what she's done.
The people have lost all
faith in the Yin Dynasty
because of Dakki.
There's so much more to lose
and nothing to be gained
by letting this continue.
Raise an army and defeat Yin.
Build a new empire in its place.
Become the great
emperor the people need!
Such a burden.
I can feel the weight of
history crushing down on me.
But this destiny may very
likely be heaven's will.
It is.
In that case, Taikobo...
Will you agree to be
Seiki's strategist?
I could use a guiding hand
to lead me through this war.
[GENSHI] The Buseioh has
finally abandoned Emperor Chu.
[HAKUTSURU]
Well that's spectacular news.
He can take up arms
and join Taikobo
now that he's a free man.
[GENSHI] Yes, but it
won't be a simple task.
If the Buseioh has chosen
to rebel against Yin,
there's no doubt that
Bunchu will pursue him.
And Dakki will dispatch
assassins for her own amusement.
[HAKUTSURU]
Here's an easy fix!
Why don't we just send
Taikobo to safely escort
the Buseioh?
[GENSHI] Hmm, it's unlikely
he'll make it in time
from Seiki to help him.
But I know who we can send now.
A man more deeply
connected to the Buseioh
than any other in
the Sennin world.
[TENSHO]
Look! Father!
We've already reached Rintokan!
Here we go.
About time you got here!
We hate waitin',
ya disgraced has-been!
[KOSO]
Listen up, Hiko!
We're here to collect
your treasonous head!
Lady Dakki wants it
for a keepsake.
[HIKO]
That monster.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
Pull him out!
[RYONO]
Gladly.
Father!
Had a feeling
ya might fight back
so we collected some insurance!
[HIKO'S FATHER]
Hiko. I'm so sorry.
If ya wanna save
your daddy's life,
then just give up and die!
Cheap bastards.
How can you stoop so low?
[HIKO growls]
[HIKO'S FATHER]
Hiko.
Don't even think twice about me.
I've lived a full, happy life,
and now you and your children
deserve the same!
Stubborn fool.
It'll be okay.
[HIKO] I refuse to lose
any more of my family!
If my life will
save my father's,
then it shall
be yours to take!
[GENSHI]
What? No!
If we lose the Buseioh now,
all will be lost!
Time's of the essence!
I'm begging, Master!
Make me your disciple!
[SUPUSHAN yells]
[BUKICHI]
What is that thing?!
[TAIKOBO] That thing is
Master Genshi's paopei robot.
Kokinrikishi!
[KOKIN]
I bring a message for Taikobo.
The Buseioh is in danger.
You must head for Choka at once.
What? Hiko's in some
kind of trouble?
Hey. Nice to see you again.
[TAIKOBO]
Taiitsu!
What're you doing here?
The situation's
looking pretty dire.
The Buseioh's turned
his back on the Emperor.
[SUPUSHAN]
Huh?
He renounced Choka?
What brought him to his senses?
Dakki did, by killing
both his wife and sister.
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
[TAIITSU] Hiko's fleeing with
his family to Seiki right now.
But Dakki has sent
assassins to block his path.
If Dakki wants him dead,
she's probably sent
one of her strongest
yokai Sennin after him!
And we all know my
Master's no match for that!
--[whines]
--[TAIKOBO] Thanks.
Yeah, which is
exactly why I brought
some backup with me.
[TAIKOBO]
Backup?
[SUPUSHAN, TAIKOBO]
Nataku!
[TAIITSU] And for the
record, it wasn't easy
getting him to sign on.
[TAIITSU]
Nataku!
You've been given an
order from Master Genshi!
Taikobo is in need of
your immediate assistance!
Head to the human world!
But in the end,
I managed to convince him of how
critical the cause really is,
and I had to give
him two paopei.
So my paopei collection's
running a bit low.
But hey, it's all for
the greater good!
Yeah, he kicked your
sorry ass silly, didn't he?
Well! No matter
how it happened...
Thanks, guys.
I appreciate the help.
I'd better be fighting
a worthwhile foe.
[TAIITSU] Well I'll be
taking my leave then.
[TAIKOBO] You're not
sticking around to help?
[TAIITSU] C'mon, you know
me better than that.
I'm not cut out for fighting.
And even if I wanted to,
the Twelve Sennin
can't get involved.
Not unless we wanna
provoke the Kingo Islands.
Yeah, you've got a point there.
All right, let's get moving.
[KOSO]
Time to collect!
Your head is mine!
[RYONO gasps, yells]
Some real exciting stuff here.
Hope you guys don't mind
me joining in on the fun.
[KOSO]
Who the hell are you?
Heh heh. My father
named me Koh Tenka.
I'm one of Hiko's sons,
ya brainwashed jackass.
[KOSO]
Y-You are...?
[HIKO]
Tenka?
[TENKA]
How's it goin', Pops?
Holy crap, look at you.
The old age is really showing.
Hey! Not funny!
[TENKA laughing]
[KOSO]
How dumb is this brat?
We're in the middle
of a fight here.
But if he wants to turn
his back, I'll take it!
[TENKA yells]
[GROUP yells]
Thanks, son.
[TENKA] Hey, who's this
little guy over here?
[KOH MEI]
That's Tensho.
You're my brother?
[KOH MEI] He was born after
you left for the Sennin world.
[HIKO]
Tenka.
I'm happy to see you.
You better surpass me someday.
That's how a son shows
devotion to his father.
[TENKA] It was those
words my father said to me
that led to my decision to
train on Kongrong Mountain
to become a Sennin.
[DOTOKU]
Right! Left! Uppercut!
[yells]
What? Who are you?
[DOTOKU] I'm Dotoku Shinkun,
but you can call me Master.
Of course, that's only if
you'd like me to train you
in the ultimate artistry
of sportsmanship.
Um, and why would I want that?
Because I'm a Sennin.
[TENKA]
To be entirely honest,
I was somewhat reluctant
to become a Doshi at first.
I was torn between
staying in the human world
to become a Tennen
Doshi like my dad,
and the desire to obtain
my own paopei
and assist my father, much
like Grand Preceptor Bunchu.
But then I realized
if I followed
in my father's footsteps,
I would never be able
to truly surpass him.
So I chose.
I spent years training
in the Sennin world
and finally got my paopei,
the Bakuya no Hoken.
Hey, Coach. What's with the
serious look on your face?
I've got some
heavy news for you.
Your father's left Choka.
[TENKA] The time has finally
come for me to help Dad!
I'm glad you've returned.
However...
[TENKA]
Is it about Mom?
And my aunt?
[HIKO]
Yeah.
They were both
incredible people.
And their lives deserve justice.
I'll make sure
Dakki pays for this.
My boy.
You've grown strong.
[rumbling]
What's that rumbling?
This can't be real!
[TENKA]
Father!
Always someone interfering.
No matter.
We're sticking to
Bunchu's orders.
Kill every last one
of Buseioh's clan.
We, the Shisei,
will see this job through!
Who attacked us?
This may well be worth my time.
Wait! Nataku!
I've got this! They're mine!
[BUNCHU]
The Shisei are powerful.
Hiko, you've brought
this death upon yourself.
No one betrays me
the way you have.
Accept your penance!