[YOZEN]
I admire him.
He has a way of earning trust.
[YOZEN]
People follow him.
They allow him
into their hearts.
[YOZEN]
However...
...with me, it's different.
For I'm a yokai .
[phone rings]
[groans] You got me.
How can I help you today?
[GENSHI]
Taikobo? This is Genshi.
[TAIKOBO]
Yeah, I know.
I haven't gotten the others
and saved the world yet,
but I'm trying, 'kay?
Thanks for checkin' in, bye!
[GENSHI]
Hold on a moment, you fool!
I called to tell you
that Yozen is missing.
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[GENSHI] We've been searching,
but he's nowhere on Kongrong,
which likely means...
Yeah, he's out
looking for Ohtenkun.
[TAIKOBO] After losing Gyokutei
like that, watching him die,
I imagine his heart is filled
with the need for vengeance.
He hates that monster so much
he doesn't even care
about his own health.
Then you need to go and
protect Yozen immediately.
He may be our last hope
to keep Kongrong and
Kingo Island connected.
I'm on it, boss.
Wake up.
Yozen is heading after Ohtenkun
and it's our job to make sure
he doesn't get himself killed.
Right now?
[sighs] Are you sure about this?
Should we really be rushing
into a fight just for Yozen?
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[OHTENKUN chuckling]
[YOZEN gasps]
[YOZEN]
Ohtenkun!
For what you've done
I'll make you pay!
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[YOZEN grunts]
[YOZEN gasps]
[OHTENKUN] I'm not the enemy
you'll be fighting today.
[gasps]
[OHTENKUN]
So sorry to disappoint you,
but I assume you've already
met Yotenkun and Kinko Saybo.
They're superior to
any other Juttenkun
and you deserve the best.
Besides, too many of our guys
have been defeated lately
and I think it's time
we balance things out.
I'm glad you're here.
I spared you because
I wanted to make sure
your death was more harrowing
than your beloved master's.
Thanks for travelling all
this way to entertain me.
I won't let you leave alive.
[OHTENKUN] I love your
unwavering confidence.
It keeps things exciting.
Wait.
I can tell that you're
a very strong fighter.
Time to die.
[gasps] What?
Deflected?
[laughs]
Enjoy killing them.
[NATAKU grunts]
So when I defeat those two,
I get to fight him, right?
Holy crap.
Did that guy just
become more powerful?
[YOZEN]
Come on!
I think it's best that
we stay out of his way.
[IGO]
Uh, yeah.
[NATAKU]
Die.
[IGO grunts]
Hurry up!
[YOTENKUN]
Could you be any more foolish?
What makes you think you could
reach us with power alone?
[gasps]
Don't waste all your
strength on them!
[NATAKU grunts]
[gasps]
[KINKO SEIBO]
How disgusting.
Children really should be taught
that violence is not a
useful form of expression.
I imagine you're the type
who won't understand that
until your limbs have
been ripped clean off.
Nataku!
[IGO]
How embarrassing.
Down in a matter of seconds.
--[NATAKU] Shut up.
--[exhales]
[YOTENKUN] Hmm. He survived a
blast from the light of Rakkon.
Interesting.
He must be a paopei himself.
Now...
...what are we going
to do with those two?
Question for ya.
Why didn't Nataku's attack
work on those guys?
There are a few
possibilities, actually.
My primary theory
is light refraction.
I believe the one
called Kinko Saybo
has the ability
to control light.
And if that's the case,
then you and I are in danger.
This entire space
could be an illusion.
Huh?
How's that?
[YOZEN] Light gives us
the ability to see.
We take it in and what is
reflected through our lenses
is what our mind processes.
Now, if that light were
to be refracted, well...
Even though I think I can see
my hand clearly in front of me,
it might not actually be there.
[IGO]
I get it.
They're avoiding our attacks
by manipulating when
and where we see them.
Nice try.
You just sit tight and
leave this one to me!
[gasps]
[YOZEN]
You sure you can handle them?
Ha.
Oh, yeah, I'm positive.
I don't need my eyes to see.
My mind's eye has
perfect vision.
So, I can detect their locations
and see their true forms.
Maybe you guys should
do a little work
on your mental abilities, too.
[YOZEN gasps]
You just... insulted me.
[IGO]
Aw, toughen up.
Where are you?
I can see the talismans,
and you're closer
than I thought.
[YOTENKUN]
These fools will never learn.
[IGO]
Here it comes.
But that's not the real attack.
Behind me!
[IGO grunts]
[YOTENKUN]
What?
He dodged it!
I have very sensitive skin,
so I can sense
anything and everything
that comes creepin' up.
You just stick with me, Yozen,
and my paopei, Komasho!
[IGO yells]
[YOTENKUN gasps]
What is he?
Amazing. He did it.
You see?
My keen senses won't be
hampered by your little tricks.
[IGO yells]
[YOTENKUN groans]
[YOTENKUN]
An impressive Doshi, indeed.
He uses only sensation
to fight his battles.
[KINKO SEIBO]
Huh. In that case...
What's happening?
Everything's turning black.
[FUGEN] Now that Mount Kongrong
has been drained of energy,
we'll have to find some
way to keep Kokin moving
with our own power.
[FUGEN] I'm at a loss
for a solution, though.
We barely have enough to
get ourselves back home.
So what?
Should we just go and
leave Yozen here to die?
You haven't been the same
since he was captured.
You've been quite
strange, actually.
[gasps]
[FUGEN] Dare I suggest your eyes
are set on the wrong goal?
[NATAKU]
Where are we now?
Not sure,
but I think it may be
Kinko Seibo's realm.
Wait! What's that?
[ALL gasp]
Don't let down your guard.
We appreciate the challenge,
but the more you resist,
the more pitiful you'll
look when you die.
[IGO grunts]
[IGO gasps]
Heh.
--[IGO groans]
--[YOZEN gasps]
Whoa. The hell is this?
[IGO grunts]
[IGO groans]
[gasps]
Shadows?
[YOZEN]
Hm?
[YOZEN grunts]
[YOZEN groans]
Ha. You're not afraid of
your own shadow, are you?
Don't forget, it's
part of who you are,
which means if you harm it,
you're also harming yourself.
The good news is that
shadows are only
one tenth as powerful as
the bodies casting them.
The bad news is that
the body must die
in order to kill the shadow.
[KINKO SEIBO] Enjoy spending all
of eternity fighting yourselves!
And you really think we're
gonna take that bait?
No, don't! Igo!
Of course I can kill it!
[IGO grunts]
[IGO]
Die! Die! Die! Die!
[YOZEN sighs]
That was way too damn easy!
You're weak!
[laughs, groans]
What I was going to say was
damage done to our shadows
comes back to us.
But if you simply
move out of the light,
it disappears completely.
[IGO groans] You have
all the answers, don'tcha?
Where's Nataku?
[IGO] Oh. He's kickin'
his own ass up there.
Stay strong.
[YOZEN] I would prefer
to reserve my power
for battling Ohtenkun.
However, I can't stand idly by.
I'm not sure Nataku can
take much more of this,
but I think I know
how I can help him.
[NATAKU]
Stay back.
[KINKO SEIBO chuckles]
At least that one has the sense
to know when it's time to flee.
[NATAKU]
Hm?
[YOSHIN]
Nataku!
Do not step out of that shadow!
That's neat.
[YOTENKUN] Hmm. He's
transformed into Yoshin
of the four Shisei
of Kuryu Island.
Very clever of him
to use Hekichiju
to manipulate the earth.
Oh, well.
I'm onto you, Yozen.
[YOZEN groans]
[KINKO SEIBO] I can see you
have very little strength left!
[panting]
[YOTENKUN] Unleashing
amulets of destruction!
Huh?
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH groan]
They must've figured
out our tactic
and now they're trying to
run us into the light!
[IGO gasps]
Angry shadows!
[NATAKU]
Not again.
[FUGEN] Perhaps it's the
magnitude of this battle
that's making you anxious.
You want to win, but you don't
want to endanger anyone, right?
[FUGEN] I understand how
important that is to you,
but don't let it get in the way
when there's so much at stake.
[FUGEN] Right now, your help
is needed to end this battle,
even if we must be sacrificed.
That's what's
being asked of you.
--[chuckling]
--Uh--Bo? What's wrong?
[cackling]
[ALL cackling]
[TAIKOBO cackling]
Hey? Are you okay?
I'm not quite sure what
to do with you right now.
Oh, yeah!
You're so right!
I don't know why
I didn't see it!
But now I know.
I've been going about this
entirely the wrong way!
What do you mean?
Trying to fight the
Juttenkun one by one
was never gonna
get us anywhere.
[FUGEN]
Uh...
[TAIKOBO] We should've gone
directly for their leader!
We need to stop wasting time
and fight who we
were meant to fight!
It's time to go after Bunchu!
[FUGEN] That might be
taking it a bit too far.
[TAIKOBO] Doesn't matter!
It's a brilliant plan!
Now, Kingo Island is
currently heading somewhere.
[FUGEN] Yes. It's been heading
directly west for a while now.
[TAIKOBO]
And you know why?
Because Bunchu is
up to something!
He's entrusted the
Juttenkun to handle us.
He's not even paying attention
to what we're doing!
[FUGEN] So we should attack
while he's distracted?
That is exactly right.
I've never been more
grateful for my smarts
than in this moment.
So,
d'you know where Kingo
Island's power reactor is?
I'm fairly certain I do.
[FUGEN gasps]
[FUGEN]
Hold on.
Are you suggesting we
bring Kingo Island down
with Mount Kongrong
still attached?
Yes, exactly.
We'll create a huge distraction
by disturbing the island,
then Bunchu will have no choice
but to come out from the core
to defend it.
Then we won't need these
silly things anymore!
[FUGEN]
And you're doing this all out of
the goodness of
your heart, right?
Step one: find Kingo's power
reactor and blow it up! Pew!
This will cause
all the stars to fall
and wipe out the yokai Doshi!
Aah!
Which means I'll get caught in
the line of fire and die, too!
[FUGEN]
Is that so...?
[TAIKOBO] And that will bring
about the fall of Kingo Island,
which will piss Bunchu
off something fierce!
He'll be too busy being enraged
to even notice us ganging
up on him! [giggles]
It's the best plan ever!
I gotta hurry
and let Genshi know
so we can get started
immediately! [giggles]
One catch.
About the power reactor--
I don't think we have enough
strength to destroy it.
[TAIKOBO]
But you're wrong!
This is the highest quality
Sento that exists.
Eat it and it'll restore
your strength by 40 percent!
It's the only one I've got left,
so we have to split it.
Thank you, Bo.
[TAIKOBO]
You ready? Let's go!
Hey Yozen, what do
we do? [grunts]
[YOZEN panting]
[gasps]
Nataku!
Here we go.
This may be the
last move for me.
He transformed into Chotenkun.
And he's using the sand
to block out our light!
[NATAKU grunts]
Nice try.
[YOZEN gasps]
[YOZEN groans]
[IGO]
Yozen!
[KINKO SEIBO]
The shadows move quickly.
Did you not think they'd
reach you before you finished?
It seems "genius"
was a misnomer.
[gasps]
[NATAKU]
Die.
But how?
Was this all part
of Yozen's plan?
[YOTENKUN]
It wasn't to block the light!
[YOTENKUN groans]
Damn it!
He used his paopei
to blind us with sand!
You did it!
The light is gone!
Rest up.
I'll handle things from here.
[gasps]
[IGO]
Oh, no.
He's not breathing!
[NATAKU]
Is he dead?
[IGO]
No.
His spirit's barely hanging on.
But... we could
lose him any second.
Hey, you can't go yet, okay?
I still need to thank you for
risking your life to protect us.
[YOTENKUN] Ha. How kind of Yozen
to make this easy on me.
Looks like I can still win!
[BOTH grunt]
[YOTENKUN gasps]
[IGO]
You wish!
Let's go, Nataku!
[NATAKU grunts]
[OHTENKUN chuckling]
I'll stay down here and
destroy all the talismans
to keep Yozen safe.
So you're free to
go after the enemy.
You don't wanna fight?
I gotta say I never expected
to hear ya say that.
[IGO]
Thanks, Nataku!
Now, prepare to be impressed!
[YOTENKUN]
Go ahead and try!
[IGO groans]
[NATAKU groans]
[IGO]
Oh, please, this is nothing!
Now... finish him!
But of course, I still
got both arms and legs.
Komasho, transform!
[YOTENKUN]
What's this?
[IGO grunts]
[YOTENKUN]
No! That's impossible!
Rest well.
I had to stop ya or there'd be
no point in my coming here.
[IGO]
Yeah!
This fight is over!
Wait a sec.
Where'd he go?
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[OHTENKUN]
You don't fool me.
It may be weak,
but I can still sense it.
There's a life force
struggling to hold on.
[OHTENKUN] Perhaps you're closer
to evolving into your true form.
[YOZEN groans]