[TAIKOBO]
Kingo Island...
It's on the advance!
No turning back now.
This should be quite fun.
[BUNCHU]
Listen closely.
We're going to war to
accomplish a single goal:
The complete and
total destruction
of Kongrong Mountain.
[TAIKOBO]
No. Bunchu must be insane!
He's bringing half of the
Sennin world into battle
with him!
[SHINKOHYO] Well, I personally
can't think of a better way
to drag the Juttenkun
into this skirmish
than driving their
home to the frontlines.
[TAIKOBO]
Shinkohyo?
I should've expected
you to be drawn to this
like flies to a pile of crap!
How could I miss this?
It's certain to be the
most entertaining thing
to happen to this world.
Approximately one thousand
Sennin and Doshi
call Kingo their home.
Kongrong, on the other hand...
It's only got about 400 or so.
I'm no mathematician, but those
seem like some long odds.
I know what we're up against!
Let's go, Supu!
Kongrong, on the double!
[SUPUSHAN]
Roger that!
[UNSHO] Since the beginning
of time, the number three
has been said to emanate a
powerful aura of sensuality.
[KEISHO]
In general, that's true,
but you're talking about
the three of us, aren't you?
[UNSHO]
Of course I am.
For there's nothing sexier
than a beautiful woman
who's also strong.
I'm the eldest sister, Venus!
The middle sister, Queen!
[UNSHO]
And our baby sister, Madonna!
[KEISHO, UNSHO]
Together, we three are
the princesses of
the Sennin world,
the Three Unsho Sisters!
This is utterly dreadful!
Look at its ghastly progress!
The horrid Kingo Island
measures nearly 10 miles
in diameter, and it's equipped
with several thousand
gun batteries.
The beast is five times
the size of Kongrong.
It's cutting a westward path.
We already know
where it's heading.
They're advancing on
Kongrong, aren't they?
[MALE VILLAGER 7A]
What the hell?
[MALE VILLAGER 7B] It's some
kind of floating mountain!
[MALE VILLAGER 7D]
Run for your lives!
[MALE VILLAGER 7C]
Hurry!
[MALE VILLAGER 7E]
Someone help us!
Well this is an
encouraging sight!
You already assembled before
I could even put out the call!
The Twelve Sennin of Kongrong!
Quite the looming
catastrophe, eh?
Just to be clear,
this immense mass tearing
across my radar is Kingo Island,
is it not?
That's exactly what it is.
This battle's coming
straight to us,
and there's no way
for us to escape it.
Master Genshi.
I think it's pretty evident
that Bunchu intends
to annihilate Kongrong Mountain.
We have no choice but
to prepare for this fight.
Do whatever you deem necessary.
I trust you to capably
lead us through this battle.
Truthfully, I fear we have
little hope of winning
without you.
Sir.
Well, let's get down to it.
I take it that you already
have a strategy in mind?
I do.
First off, we need to
move Kongrong Mountain.
I was unaware of it,
but Taiitsu told me
it's capable of movement.
This central sphere serves
as Kongrong's cockpit.
But its complex control
system will take a Sennin
of the highest possible
level to pilot.
Makes sense.
And if we're looking
for someone like that,
there's only one
woman for the job.
Well, Koshu? You up for it?
Roger!
[TAIKOBO] Do you think we
can use the batteries, Yozen?
[YOZEN]
It will be difficult.
They haven't been fired
in thousands of years.
They're in need of
some heavy maintenance.
And that's going
to take a full day.
If only we had a day.
Actually, hell, I'd even take
half a day at this point.
We just don't have the energy
to pull that off, Taiitsu.
[TAIITSU sighs]
Yeah, we don't have enough
to get a decent barrier up.
Don't worry, I'll figure out
some way to make it work.
You just stay focused
on piloting us, okay?
Looks like we're gonna have to
conserve as much energy
as possible until we engage
in combat with them.
I better go check in with Fugen.
How're things looking?
Have ya figured out a location
for the battle?
The coordinates 72 64 0 25 6
appear to be completely
unpopulated,
so it should be the ideal area.
Good.
It's time to get moving, Koshu!
Kongrong Mountain,
initiate launch!
[YOKAI 7A] Armaments are
99.72 percent battle ready.
[YOKAI 7B] Barrier functional
for approximately 108 hours.
[CHOTENKUN] The 100 flying
paopei, Sokinrikishi,
are fully activated.
Everything is properly
proceeding according to plan.
[OHTENKUN]
Bunchu.
We're close enough to have
a visual of Kongrong now.
[FUGEN]
Kingo's approaching.
Koshu. Make sure to keep
us at a safe distance.
Stop outside the range
of their cannons.
No!
This can't be good!
Listen well, Kongrong.
I am Bunchu, the Grand
Preceptor of Yin
and the acting supreme
commander of Kingo Island.
We've chosen to engage you in
combat with a single imperative,
and that is the utter
annihilation of the Kongrong
mountain range.
You have the option to surrender
and hand over Kongrong,
or you can choose to fill the
Hoshindai with your own souls.
Your call.
You deserve to be severely
punished for using Taikobo
to create chaos
in the human world.
As the other half
of the Sennin world,
we can no longer allow this.
I'm not just gonna sit here
and let you badmouth me,
you got that?
You can act as self-righteous
as you want,
but everyone knows you're
only in this to protect Yin!
[BUNCHU] Heh. I only wish for
the human world to remain free
of Sennin interference.
You freakin' liar!
If you really feel that way,
why don't you abandon
your Grand Preceptor post
and live in the Sennin World?
Huh? How about that?
Leave it to Taikobo to lose
his composure and say
what everybody else is thinking.
[GENSHI sighs]
[BUNCHU] I've said everything
that I had to say, so be ready.
[TAIKOBO]
I'm still talking!
[growls]
Wait! Hey, Bo!
Kingo's preparing to launch
a full missile attack!
Here they come!
Yozen! Do it!
[YOZEN]
Seriously.
I realize we're running
low on energy,
but did they really
have to throw me out here
to act as their barrier?
I mean, that's asking a lot.
Oh, well.
There's not much point
in complaining now.
Partial transformation!
Water barrier!
[TAIKOBO]
Well look at that.
He conjured up Koyuken's
power by only transforming
his hands.
I didn't realize he'd mastered
the partial transformation.
He just might be the best
Kongrong has to offer.
Quite Impressively done,
"genius" Doshi.
Although...
[BUNCHU]
Now launch. Sokinrikishi!
Paopei robots.
They must be similar
to Kokinrikishi.
You know, Bunchu...
You're gonna have to
step up your game here.
These meager attacks
aren't gonna do the job.
That goes without saying.
I'm simply attempting
to buy us some time
until we can reach peak energy.
And after that?
[BUNCHU] We'll employ
Kingo's largest, strongest
paopei weapon.
Tsutenho.
Chi!
[grunts]
[YOZEN]
You showed up just in time!
Wait, are they retreating?
[TAIKOBO]
Something's wrong.
We gotta pull back, everybody!
It's a little too
late for that, Taikobo.
[TAIKOBO] They're firing
their main weapon!
Koshu! Get us
out of here quickly!
Can we outrun that?
We should still be out
of range of their weapons,
so calm down.
We're basing that
on obsolete data.
If Bunchu has the means to
destroy Kongrong Mountain
in one fell swoop, he'll do it.
Those other attacks
were just distractions!
He was just buying time
to reach peak energy!
[BUNCHU]
Tsutenho, fire!
[TAIKOBO grunting]
[YOZEN]
Oh, god, no!
Looks like most of it
is still standing.
[DOTOKU]
We've taken heavy damage.
A large number of souls
are flying to the Hoshindai.
What now, Bo?
[TAIKOBO]
Taiitsu!
How much longer until we
can fire our main battery?
We're almost at full power,
so it should be soon.
[GENSHI]
Is it possible to withdraw?
Or is it too late
for us to flee?
[TAIKOBO] Their main
cannon's range is longer
than we anticipated.
They'll just shoot us in the
back if we try to run now.
Bunchu's got us cornered.
We've only got one
option available to us
if we wanna make it
out of this alive.
Koshu!
Aim us straight at Kingo,
full speed ahead!
We'll fire the Genshiho
at close range
and blast a hole
in their barrier.
We'll then use that
opening to invade Kingo.
Fully charged and ready!
[TAIKOBO]
Koshu! Do it!
Genshiho! Open fire!
Keep on going--
we're almost there!
Why'd you stop firing?
That was all the energy we had.
Well, Taikobo?
Do you finally see just
how helpless you truly are?
Tsutenho, prepare to fire!
[DOTOKU]
Oh, man, this is a nightmare!
They're gonna shoot us
with that monster gun again!
We're gonna be dead
if that thing hits us
at this close range!
Does Taikobo even know
what the hell he's doing?
All right, you two,
enough with the panicking.
Do you really think you could
do any better than he is?
[DOTOKU]
Well, I...
[GYOKUTEI] That first blast
would've wiped us out of
existence if it
weren't for Taikobo.
He saw it coming
and he saved us.
[DOKO]
Yeah, that is true.
Don't lose your faith in him.
We must do what we
can to get through this,
and a big part of that
is believing in Taikobo.
Looks like they're beginning
to charge up Tsutenho again.
What should we do? Any ideas?
[SUPUSHAN]
I know!
Now's the time to
let loose and show 'em
what you've got!
Right.
[TAIKOBO]
Tension in here is suffocating.
There's no room for even
the smallest mistake.
I can't let them fire again.
If we can just take
out that barrier...
We have to.
There has to be
some way to do it.
[FUGEN]
Bad news, Bo.
All right, lay it on me.
From what I can tell,
Yozen seems to be missing.
--[TAIKOBO gasps]
--[SUPUSHAN] Huh?
He didn't die the last time they
fired their cannon, did he?
No, it would take more
than that to kill him.
Wait a sec.
Yozen, I owe ya one, buddy.
All our lives are
resting in your hands.
[YOZEN]
Just as I thought.
These mechs are
capable of freely passing
through the barrier.
It's been about 50 years
since I last infiltrated Kingo.
Of course, this isn't exactly
the time for nostalgia.
So he's going to try to
bring down the barrier
on his own.
You are undeniably
valiant, genius Doshi.
Ohtenkun.
We have 20 minutes until
we can fire Tsutenho again.
Deal with him before
he can cause any trouble.
Yeah, fine.
All right, first things first,
I need to find a way inside
the central area.
What's happening?
[YOZEN gasps]
What is this place?
[CHOTENKUN] Welcome to
the eternal desert, Yozen.
Perhaps you've heard of me.
I'm Chotenkun, of the Juttenkun.
[YOZEN]
The Juttenkun?
[CHOTENKUN]
You now inhabit Kosajin,
a hyperspace of my own design.
Once you've entered,
there's no way of getting out.
[TAIKOBO] With any luck, Yozen's
already infiltrated Kingo.
Let's hope he can manage
to bring down the barrier
all by himself.
He's gonna get himself
killed in there on his own!
If anyone can do it, it's him.
I'm a little sick and tired of
everyone calling him a genius.
But there really is no
better word to describe him.
Hey, Koshu! Taiitsu!
Be ready to charge
into Kingo at full speed
as soon as he gets
that barrier down, okay?
Use every last drop
of energy Kongrong's got!
Drain it dry if you need to!
You're sure putting a lot
of faith in Yozen, huh?
You really trust him.
You're damn right I trust him.
With my life.
[YOZEN]
All of this... it's not real.
It has to be an illusion.
[CHOTENKUN]
Afraid not, Yozen.
It's reality.
Simply put, this dimension
itself is actually my paopei.
[CHOTENKUN] And I control every
single centimeter of this realm
at will.
To be clear, only I
can create an exit.
Basically, you're trapped
in here until I decide
to let you go free.
Is that so?
Well, sorry, I'm not just
going to take your word.
You know I'm running
short on time here,
so I'll have to use
everything I've got...
...to defeat you!
[CHOTENKUN] You'll only
wear yourself out, Yozen.
That's all.
[CHOTENKUN]
What did I tell you?
I completely control this space,
so you're not just fighting me--
you're fighting an entire world.
[YOZEN]
Why have you not attacked?
Are you trying to mock me?
[CHOTENKUN]
Just surrender.
Kongrong's paopeis are
laughably inefficient at best.
They could never
defeat the Juttenkun.
I don't give up.
I would rather die
than surrender to you.
[CHOTENKUN] Your abilities
drastically surpass those
of the other Kongrong Sennin.
It would be wasteful to kill
someone of your caliber.
Not only that, but I can sense
that you're closer to us
than you are to humankind.
Your personality,
your perfection of being.
It's evident you're not a human.
Not to mention your
transformation powers.
They're more reminiscent
of a Yokai Sennin
taking human form.
Or possibly a highly evolved
version of that technique.
You mask the beautiful
visage you're too scared
to show the world.
You look just like us,
don't you?
The nature of a Yokai
is far more cruel
than that of a human,
but they're welcome
amongst their own kind.
Join us, Yozen.
Allow yourself a life
where you truly belong.
It's not too late for you.
[YOZEN]
Thanks, but I'll pass.
[CHOTENKUN]
If that's what you want.
[YOZEN gasps]
[CHOTENKUN]
I failed to mention.
Everything here rapidly
erodes and withers away.
I'm immune to it,
but everything else...
It all crumbles
to sand and becomes
a part of the desert,
including you.
I'm sure you can
already feel the moisture
draining from your bones.
Surrender now, or become
one with the wasteland.
Trust me on this one, Yozen.
You need to maintain
a human form,
or else the bad guys
might find you.
Okay!
I am a human, dammit.
[TAIKOBO]
Nobody's dying.
I won't let you
kill them. I won't!
[CHOTENKUN]
Wait. What is this?
You seem rather
interested in me.
So y'know what?
I'll show you.
[YOZEN]
Though there is one catch,
it'll cost you
your life to see it.
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
Just another 20 minutes
to go before we can unleash
a torrent of hellfire.
Kongrong Mountain will
vanish before our very eyes.
[chuckling]
[SUPUSHAN whimpers]
[OHTENKUN] You'd better
have a brilliant plan
if you're gonna escape
Chotenkun's Kosajin
in time to disarm the barrier.
If you break out
even one second late,
you won't have a
home to return to.
So let's see
the goods, "genius."
Show us what you're capable of.
I'm dying to see if you're
worthy of that nickname.
[YOZEN]
For Taikobo, and the others.
To live up to their trust in me.
That is why I'm
a Doshi of Kongrong.
[CHOTENKUN]
So that is his true form?
[YOZEN] I know what I am,
and it doesn't matter
what I was before.