[DOTOKU grunting]
[YOZEN]
It appears this may be it--
the final battle.
Ha! You'd never know I
was about to die earlier
with the way I'm moving now.
Bam! I bet we can win
this fight in one round!
Against all the odds,
somehow Taikobo
always pulls through.
[TAIKOBO whistles]
I can't believe this encampment
was finished in
just a few hours.
Whatever the task may be,
our guys always
rise to the occasion.
There's no denying that fact.
We've also laid a road along
the path we followed here,
and that will allow us
to send food and supplies
quickly by carriage.
[YOZEN]
Food is especially important.
Besides the obvious risk,
a shortage would cause
a drop in morale as well.
It shows great foresight
to ensure the people
have enough in reserves
before the battle begins.
You truly are a
remarkable tactician.
It also means we get
peaches delivered ASAP.
I suppose it does.
[TENSHO groans]
Taikobo.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[TENSHO panting]
Nataku!
Be careful, Taikobo.
This doesn't look good.
If he's infected with an
illness, he could be contagious.
[TAIKOBO]
How?
And the others are also...
[TAIKOBO]
Tensho!
[YOZEN]
Stay where you are.
If you get too close,
you could be infected.
Let go of me.
[gasps]
[YOZEN]
You never change.
Always protecting your friends,
even if it means putting
yourself in harm's way.
Which is why, this time,
I'll go with you.
[TAIITSU]
Hurry! There's no time to waste!
Unchushi, what are you doing?
I need you to take care of Igo!
That means you.
I'm on it.
All right! It's ready, Igo!
[IGO]
Huh?
This is Bioxin Z, a biological
ointment made just for you!
We rub it all over your flesh
and its filaments sink into your
pores to cleanse your wounds...
...I hope.
--[IGO gasping]
--Ah, there, see?
--Perfect. You feel it?
--[IGO gasping]
--Yes!
How could this happen?
We're going to need
all the help we can get
in order to go up against
Bunchu at this point!
If I could've worked
on this in my lab,
we would've had everyone
done in an hour or so!
[TAIITSU gasps]
[TAIITSU] It looks like Kingo
Island is losing altitude.
Did something happen
to its power reactor?
[TAIITSU]
Hopefully Taikobo is all right.
I wonder if the other
Twelve Elite Sennin
were able to get there in time.
[TAIITSU] The biggest
question of all is...
...how will this battle end?
[FUGEN]
Bo.
What made you fight
to come back here?
Even after I gave you the
strongest sleeping drug
that I had?
I have a more important
question for you.
Why would you
underestimate Bunchu
and think you could
fight him on your own?
If Supu had gotten here any
later, you would've been dead.
And for what?
Heh. You're right.
Don't worry, everything
turned out okay!
[SUPUSHAN]
Papa used his power
to heal everyone
at Mount Kongrong!
[SUPUSHAN] They all left
as soon as he was done.
But since I'm much faster
than Kokinrikishi,
I was able to catch up
with you guys a lot sooner!
Oh, speaking of which,
what ever happened to your papa?
He was already weak,
so he exhausted himself
using his power.
I'm sorry, son.
I believe this is the end
of my Supu usefulness.
Before I go, take this.
[SUPUSHAN]
Papa!
[thud]
[SUPUSHAN] As he collapsed,
he handed me a gift.
Well, what did he give you?
I don't know.
It was blank inside.
How unfortunate.
All twelve Elite Sennin
have fully recovered
from Ohtenkun's mites.
But that is of
little consequence.
A few more moments of life
will make no difference.
[BUNCHU] Enjoy them
while you can, Taikobo!
Here it comes, Bo. Ready?
[whimpers]
Chi!
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
[BUNCHU gasps]
[BUNCHU]
Taikobo's wind is much sharper.
That must mean he's advanced.
I'm curious to see how
long he can keep this up.
[BUNCHU]
Your defense is strong,
but if that's all
you plan to do,
you'll exhaust yourself before
your allies can arrive to help.
Master, just keep
this wind going strong
and the others should
be here to back you up
in just a couple
of minutes, okay?
I remember the plan.
Fugen!
Could you go in for
a B Quick attack?
I think I know that one.
We used it for fun
while training, right?
[TAIKOBO]
Yeah!
I don't know if it'll work,
but it's worth a try!
[chuckles]
Now loading: data for paopei
Kinben's orbital patterns.
Combine paopei Dashinben.
Combine Taikyoku Fuin paopei.
Okay.
It's finished, Bo!
[TAIKOBO]
Great!
Chi!
What's this?
[TAIKOBO, SUPUSHAN yelling]
All right, guys. We did it!
Are you sure about that?
I mean, it was flashy, but...
We succeeded in wounding him.
We've never even been able to
get that close to him before.
Sure, it's just a small scratch,
but the blood on his face
means he's not invincible!
[BUNCHU]
What have you done?
[TAIKOBO]
Ha, ha, ha!
I've blocked your whip attacks
and sent them back your way.
[TAIITSU screaming]
[panting]
[TAIKOBO sighs]
Success feels good, doesn't it?
Oh, yeah, and this thing
was the ultimate defense.
As long as we can keep
using Taikyoku Fuin,
we'll be able to
combine our paopei
against any we come across.
I'm pleased you found it useful.
Of course, I have to
give credit where it's due
and acknowledge
my wonderful paopei.
Yeah, you're the man, Taiitsu.
[TAIKOBO] We can use Fugen's
paopei computer, Taikyoku Fuin,
to record any enemy's
attack pattern.
[FUGEN]
Right.
Then I can transfer that
information to an ally's paopei.
And that's what makes
automatic homing
of the enemy attacks possible.
It seems most of your attacks
are actually distractions.
Only about three to five
of your lashes ever hit.
So if we use Dashinben to change
the direction of your strikes,
those that would hit
backfire and hurt you instead.
[TAIKOBO]
Neat, huh?
And that's what we call
the B Quick attack!
Surely there's a much
more intimidating name
than that one, Bo.
[TAIKOBO] What do you
think of that, Boony? Ehe!
Does it make you wanna cry?
[TAIKOBO cackles]
It felt good to get that out.
But I should let you know this
is the end of the road for you.
[SUPUSHAN]
Master!
It looks like everyone's here!
Hey, you guys!
Sorry it took us so long.
But we're ready to go!
So that's what
Bunchu looks like?
I'm sorry, Grand Preceptor,
but we're doing
all this out of love!
Come on, guys!
Let's pulverize him!
[ALL]
Prepare yourself, Bunchu.
You're about to fight the
Twelve Elite Sennin of Kongrong!
All right.
We're about to perform
the biggest B Quick attack
of all time, together.
[YOZEN]
Greetings, Taikobo.
Uh--Yozen?
How are you here?
I figured you'd be exhausted.
Ha, ha. I wouldn't miss this.
I've made a personal vow
to get rid of Bunchu myself.
What? That's crazy talk!
[YOZEN] Bunchu, I've
come to repay a debt!
[gasps] Wait a second?!
I've never seen that
transformation before!
[YOZEN]
This is Hanyotai, my true form.
Yozen's a yokai ?
Whoa, really?
[ALL chattering]
I'm gonna need you
to provide backup.
Eh?
The rest of you head
out and follow Yozen!
[FUGEN]
I'm worried.
[FUGEN] My nuclear fusion had
absolutely no effect on Bunchu.
[FUGEN] Perhaps... he's using
something else besides Kinben.
[YOZEN grunts]
[YOZEN]
Have at you!
Did I get him?
I know I made contact.
[YOZEN gasps]
[TAIKOBO]
Stay strong, Yozen!
Don't forget,
he's super powerful!
Thank you. I know that.
Man.
Yozen just blew my mind a little
with that secret of his.
But I'm not worried about it.
Where are you, Bunchu?
I'm ready for ya!
Paopei Onmyokyo!
[SEKI yells]
[yells] Here we go!
Banno Bocho paopei!
Attack!
[KOSEISHI]
Bantenin, battle mode!
Go, Bantenin!
[REIHOU]
Paopei...
...Rakkonsho!
[KURYUSON]
Kon...sen...jo!
Rurihei.
[yelps]
[ALL screaming]
You should know
better than to throw
everything at him like that!
Fugen, how is Bunchu looking?
[FUGEN]
I'm sorry.
That last attack created
an errant magnetic field
and I can't use my radar.
[JIKO]
We got this!
Leave it to the close combat
fighters to finish the job!
And if he's dead, we'll
make sure he stays that way.
Hey, Bo.
We had better join them.
What do you mean?
Why are you so eager
to fight right now?
Because Bunchu isn't dead yet.
I'm sure.
What?
[DOTOKU]
Whoa! It's so freaking hot!
[JIKO] No way Bunchu
could survive this.
What do you think, Koryu?
I'm not quite sure.
From the way things look--
Guys, stop! There.
[KORYU, SUPUSHAN]
Huh?
[KOKUKIRIN] I don't mean
to interfere, Master Bunchu.
Forgive me.
No.
You've done very
well. Thank you.
[BUNCHU] It's good to
see Yin again, isn't it?
[KOKUKIRIN]
Yes, though it appears
it's under Dakki's control now.
Damn fox.
[KOKUKIRIN]
Apologies.
I should not have
mentioned that.
No matter.
It shall be under our
control again soon.
You, Hiko, and I will
rule this land together.
[KOKUKIRIN]
Thank you for including me.
I'll always protect Yin.
And I will work to rebuild it.
I won't rest until it
becomes a nation of people
living in perpetual happiness.
[KOKUKIRIN] I'll stand
right beside you, sir...
[KOKUKIRIN]
...for all time.
No way. We couldn't break
through that thick shell?
It must be stronger
than our paopei alloy!
[FUGEN]
It transformed.
That's how he survived.
Let me down somewhere,
Kokukirin.
I don't need to be
mounted to fight.
[KOKUKIRIN]
Understood.
[BUNCHU]
I'm waiting.
Aren't you going to attack?
[TAIKOBO grunts]
[YOZEN] It appears the pressure
coming from Bunchu...
[FUGEN]
It's increased?
[KORYU grunts]
Fine!
You want us to hit
you again, we will!
Ha! Let's go!
Fugen!
We have to go in
and cover them somehow!
Eh--mm-hm.
Hope you feel like dying today!
[BUNCHU scoffs]
I appreciate the challenge.
It's been awhile.
[TAIKOBO]
Chi!
[JIKO gasps]
[KORYU gasps]
[JIKO groans]
[gasps] He broke
through my wind!
[BOTH groaning]
Koryu! Jiko! Answer me!
[thudding]
[TAIKOBO gasping]
[TAIKOBO]
No... It can't be!
[BUNCHU] I realize it was
rude of me to hold back,
especially when my opponents
are racing to their deaths.
But now... I vow to take
this fight more seriously.
The Sennin world
as we know it...
...will end today.
Do you hate them... Lord Ryo Bo?
And do you hunger for revenge?
Well don't even bother.
Trust me, it's not
worth the effort.
Unless you can somehow
change the whole world,
this will keep happening
until the end of time.
[TAIKOBO]
He warned me back then.
He said that we would
never know happiness,
unless we could somehow
change the world.
That moment...
is when it all started.
[TAIJO]
The level of your struggle
has no bearing on the outcome.
[grunts]
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[TAIKOBO]
What do you mean?
[TAIJO]
Even if you were to defeat Dakki
and create a human world
without Sennin or Doshi,
there's no guarantee
happiness would reign.
There will always be
another unfit ruler,
or a nation with
immense military power
to rise up and take
control and bring death.
We won't know the true
outcome until we try.
What I mean to say is
it's already done.
I have seen the future
and it's not the one
you wish to create.
[TAIJO] There will be
endless battles and chaos.
In the end,
everything disappears,
leaving the world barren.
Is this worth your suffering?
[TAIKOBO chuckles]
What?
Tell me why you laugh.
[TAIKOBO]
Because I'm not responsible
for all that happens
that far into the future.
And I'm not arrogant
enough to believe
I can save everyone
for all eternity.
[TAIKOBO] There is one
thing within our reach.
That's leaving the
next generation a world
that we treated with
compassion and respect.
As long as someone
benefits from our work
and humanity continues...
...honestly, that's
good enough for me.