[FUGEN]
Bo.
In order to
accomplish something,
a person has to
make a sacrifice.
And the bigger that outcome
is promised to be,
the more sacrifices it takes.
[FUGEN] But... this doesn't mean
we're throwing our lives away.
We made up our minds to do this.
We don't need pity or sympathy.
Just...
[FUGEN]
...remember us.
Fugen.
You've always been so stubborn.
You're too quick to
sacrifice yourself.
[FUGEN]
I could say the same about you.
[TAIKOBO]
No you can't!
I don't go into any battle
without having some kind of
plan to survive!
[FUGEN]
Right.
[FUGEN] And I have a plan
for everyone to survive.
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[FUGEN]
Goodbye, Bo.
Thank you.
Fugen, no!
[YOZEN]
No!
Fugen's explosion is going
to destroy Kingo entirely!
We have to go, Taikobo!
Listen to him.
It's not safe for us
to be here right now.
[gasps]
[SUPUSHAN]
Master?
[YOKAI 21A]
Page one!
[YOKAI 21B]
Right back at ya!
[YOKAI 21A whines]
--[YOKAI 21B chuckles]
--[rumbling]
[YOKAI 21A, YOKAI 21B]
Huh?
I wonder what's
happening out there.
We've got big trouble
and we gotta leave now!
Kingo's power reactor's
been destroyed
and the stars are
falling from the sky!
[YOKAI 21A, YOKAI 21B scream]
[YOKAI 21C screams]
[sighs]
--[rustling]
--Huh?
--[footsteps]
--[SUPUSHAN gasps] Yozen.
[YOZEN]
Supushan!
Wait--did you transform
to protect Taikobo?
[SUPUSHAN]
I didn't realize I had.
And I have no idea how I did it,
because only adults
of the Supu Clan
can pull of a
transformation like this.
Oh. Well then is it possible
that you used some kind of item?
[SUPUSHAN]
An item?
How?
I don't have anything on me
except this blank piece of--
[gasps] Wait a minute!
This is the Certificate
of Adulthood you get
when you become an adult!
It's making sense.
The heat from the
Twelve Elite Sennin's
combined attack on Bunchu
must've made the
invisible ink appear!
Why would something so important
be written with invisible ink?
[TAIKOBO]
I knew it.
Huh?
All of it.
In the back of my mind, I knew
it would turn out like this.
It was obvious,
given Fugen's personality
and the position of
the rest of the Sennin.
I knew they were prepared to die
in their fight against Bunchu.
[TAIKOBO]
I took advantage of that--
of their selfless hearts.
[TAIKOBO] What a terrible
plan that turned out to be.
[YOZEN] But you didn't
plan for them to die.
And this isn't about failure.
The enemy was just much
stronger than we anticipated.
We needed to defeat Bunchu.
There was no way to
do this without them.
The problem is we
didn't defeat Bunchu.
He's not dead...
...and so the Twelve
Sennin can't rest.
That's impossible!
There's no way he could've
survived that explosion!
I know he wasn't
riding Kokukirin,
and it seemed like he took
the brunt of that attack.
[TAIKOBO] Look at the middle of
the fireball Fugen left behind.
[YOZEN gasps]
What? How is he alive?
[SUPUSHAN]
That damned Bunchu disappeared!
Where'd he go?
My guess is he's heading
straight for Mount Kongrong
as we speak.
I doubt he knows we're
still alive down here,
so he's going to
the one location
that he's sure to find an enemy.
Genshi.
Master needs us. Let's go.
[SUPUSHAN]
Right!
Taikobo, I would strongly
advise against going.
And it pains me to say this,
but if you go,
you'll only die in vain!
[TAIKOBO]
I understand.
I probably won't survive.
Even so, there's no
turning back at this point.
[TAIKOBO] This time...
I gotta fight to win.
I won't back down no
matter what the cost!
Oh, man, that was a
gigantic explosion.
I'm actually kinda impressed
we managed to get out alive.
[TENKA gasps]
[TENKA]
What's that?
Who the hell you supposed to be?
Right now, I'm the guy who's
looking for the
Buseioh, Koh Hiko.
[gasps]
[TENKA]
Wait, you know this creep?
Don't be such an idiot.
Of course I don't.
[BOTH gasp]
You've become quite an
important conquest for me.
I promise to give
you nothing less
than the finest hospitality.
[GENSHI] The Twelve Elite
Sennin... have all fallen.
[SENNIN 21A]
Every single one of them?
[SENNIN 21B]
It can't be!
[SENNIN 21C]
What will happen to Kongrong?
What is Bunchu's current status?
He will arrive here
any moment now.
[HAKUTSURU]
Oh, no!
[GENSHI] Hakutsuru,
go to the treatment room
and tell Taiitsu and the others
they need to be on alert.
[HAKUTSURU]
Understood, Master!
Koshu, I need you to gather
all the remaining
Sennin and Doshi here.
[KOSHU]
And who would you have face him?
I will take him on.
[YOZEN] Taikobo, I believe
Sengyoku and her group
survived the explosion.
Shall we leave them behind?
[TAIKOBO]
Bukichi will take care of them.
I put my full faith in him.
He'll make sure
they're all okay.
Hm?
What's this?
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[SUPUSHAN] Heh. You still
had one of Ohtenkun's
pesky mites on ya.
I removed it free of charge.
You're the best, pal.
Thank you.
[SUPUSHAN]
So, Yozen, I hope you know
we have a zero percent chance
of winning this battle.
You sure you want to tag along?
Now that I've come this far,
I want to see the journey
through to the end.
That's how I feel.
How about you, Taikobo?
Me, too.
[SENNIN 21G groans]
Master Genshi...
[BUNCHU]
What fools.
They barely had
any time left to live
and that was how they spent it.
[KOKUKIRIN]
Master Bunchu.
I happened to notice
you are still wounded
from the last battle.
I suppose it's no wonder
they were called
the Twelve Elite Sennin.
I had long forgotten what
physical pain felt like,
but those warriors
have reminded me.
[KOKUKIRIN]
I see.
But it appears that Taikobo
and Yozen are still alive.
What merit do we gain
by ignoring them
and defeating
Genshi Tenson first?
We're merely making the
best use of our time.
I know exactly where Genshi is
and we'd still have to
locate the others.
Besides, we're already here.
[BUNCHU]
You are Genshi Tenson,
the founder of Mount
Kongrong, correct?
Yes, that's me.
[BUNCHU]
Well then.
For the good of Yin,
I'll need to destroy you.
You are an ignorant fool,
believing you can
get away with anything
as long as it's
"for the good of Yin."
What you are doing is nothing
but senseless slaughter!
[BUNCHU] You have quite the
nerve to say that to me.
What of your charge Taikobo?
Are you not using him
in the same way?
Hypocrite.
You are behind this entire plot
to mercilessly destroy Yin
and give rise to Shu.
And because of this, you're the
one man I will not let escape.
[GENSHI grunts]
[GENSHI] You believe all
the terror you've caused
is for the good of Yin?
The only one you're
serving is yourself.
You've manipulated every aspect
of the Yin administration
to suit your own purposes.
You implanted your ideology
into the mind of the emperor
when he was just a boy.
That is to say,
you controlled him!
You took advantage of his
vulnerability at a young age
and dyed him in your own colors.
[GENSHI] Your focus is purely
on what you think benefits Yin.
But because that is all you see,
you have become a tyrant who
controls Yin from the shadows,
just like Dakki.
[GENSHI]
You hunger for domination
and a world where humans
live by your ideologies.
That is the truth
of your blackened soul
and you can't deny it!
Ha! You don't hold
anything back, do you?
No matter how you
choose to spin it,
I remain true to my
vow to protect Yin!
Yes, my mission includes
the humans as well.
Before Dakki appeared, the
government of the human world
was copacetic, was it not?
I have the power to return
happiness to the human denizens
under the banner of my child--
the banner of Yin.
They'll have peace
for all eternity.
[GENSHI] And your command
will ensure this peace?
The people will live in
a prison of your creation.
[GENSHI] Losing one's freedom
does not bring about happiness
and it never will.
I'm done talking with you.
[GENSHI]
Ryukitsu Koshu!
Please guard the others.
This battle is going
to be quite intense.
[HAKUTSURU]
Are you sure about this?
[GENSHI] You've no need
to waste your worry on me.
Have I given you reason
to believe I will lose?
[HAKUTSURU gasps]
Paopei...
...Muro Kenkonmo!
[SENNIN 21A, SENNIN 21B gasp]
[HAKUTSURU]
Koshu?
[KOSHU gasps]
I hate to admit it...
but I don't have enough power.
I may only have the energy
left to protect you all.
I trust he'll defeat Bunchu.
Be strong, Genshi.
We don't have any more
time to waste, Bunchu,
so I hope you're ready.
Such confidence.
Spoken like the man who is
undoubtedly Taikobo's master.
[BUNCHU gasps]
[BUNCHU]
What's this?
[GENSHI chuckles]
[GENSHI] Have you noticed that
Kinben's movements have stalled?
It's because the
gravity surrounding you
has been transmuted.
[GENSHI]
Paopei Bankohan!
That paopei's familiar.
It's similar to the one
Fugen Shinjin used.
[GENSHI]
Naturally.
After all, It was I who
created Taikyoku Fuin.
[GENSHI]
But they are not the same.
This one is immeasurably
more powerful.
[BUNCHU groans]
[GENSHI]
It's no use.
I've restricted
Kinben's movements
by adding an additional
five Gs of force to it.
Meaning what?
[GENSHI]
It's simple.
Just think of it as
though I've multiplied
the object's weight by five.
Now that you understand,
I will do the same to your body.
Experience for a moment
the power of the founder
of Mount Kongrong--
the power of Genshi Tenson!
Tenfold gravity!
The paopei you wield is truly
a force to be reckoned with!
[KOKUKIRIN groans]
Master Bunchu!
[BUNCHU] I don't need
your help, Kokukirin!
[GENSHI laughs]
[GENSHI] It looks like
you can still move!
What a shame to have to kill
a man of such great ability.
Unfortunately,
you're not an opponent
I can ever be too careful with.
I will show you no mercy!
[BUNCHU groans]
[GENSHI]
Hundredfold gravity!
[SUPUSHAN grunting]
[SUPUSHAN pants]
[TAIKOBO]
What's wrong, Supu?
[SUPUSHAN] Um, for some reason
I can't move forward.
No way.
It's Mount Kongrong.
--[TAIKOBO gasps]
--Look! Surrounding it!
It's Master Genshi's paopei!
Bankohan!
[SUPUSHAN]
What's Bankohan?
It's one of the seven
super paopei.
It controls gravity and if
used by anyone but its owner,
it will drain all of their power
and kill them within one minute.
At the top is
Shinkohyo's Raikoben,
followed by Taijo
Rokun's Taikyokuzu.
There's Chokomei's Kinkosen,
Dakki's Keisei Genjo,
Bunchu's Kinben, Tsuten Kyoshu's
Rikukonhan, and, finally,
Master Genshi Tenson's Bankohan.
[SUPUSHAN]
So... that means right now...
...two of those super paopei
are battling on Mount Kongrong?
We're not gonna be able to
get over there for a while.
[BUNCHU groaning]
[BUNCHU yells]
[GENSHI gasps]
[BUNCHU]
I cannot lose.
[GENSHI gasps]
I will not let you defeat me.
[BUNCHU groans]
[BUNCHU]
I made a vow.
I will fight to protect Yin!
[GENSHI gasps]
[GENSHI]
You leave me no other choice
but to increase the output!
No, Genshi! You mustn't!
Your body wouldn't be
able to handle it.
It's not worth the risk!
[HAKUTSURU gasps]
What kind of risk do you mean?
[KOSHU] Master Genshi is using
the paopei on his forehead
to create a Hoshin
field for protection.
It's draining his strength.
That's the reason
he's been so cautious
throughout the fight thus far.
And so, if he increases the
output of his super paopei
on top of that--!
[GENSHI]
Listen well!
One who fears their own death
cannot defeat the enemy!
I am aware of the risks.
Prepare yourself, Bunchu!
[GENSHI]
Bankohan, maximum power!
[BOTH gasp]
[GENSHI]
Thousandfold gravity!
[BUNCHU groans]
The gravity field is
becoming much too massive
and is now turning
into a black hole!
We must evacuate!
[KOKUKIRIN gasps]
Master Bunchu!
[BUNCHU groans]
[BUNCHU yells, gasps]
[GENSHI]
Did that do it?
[BUNCHU screaming]
[GENSHI]
What's this?
[GENSHI screams]
[HAKUTSURU]
Master Genshi, no!
[KOSHU]
Everyone!
I need you to use all
you have to protect Genshi!
[SENNIN scream]
[KOSHU pants]
[BUNCHU screams]
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
[SUPUSHAN]
The gravity field disappeared!
You're right, Supu.
Looks like it's time.
Let's go, you guys!
That explosion had
a tremendous impact.
Hold on, Master Genshi.
We're coming.
[HAKUTSURU]
Master Genshi, please!
Come on! You have to wake up!
[gasps]
[HAKUTSURU gasps]
We've come to the end, Genshi.
You've made an
impressive effort.
--[HAKUTSURU whimpering]
--But... how is this possible?!
[BUNCHU]
Finally,
the long-awaited
fall of Kongrong!
--[HAKUTSURU whimpers]
--[KOSHU gasps]
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[gasps]
[OHTENKUN]
Excellent work.
Hello, Bunchu.
[BUNCHU gasps]
What are you doing here?
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[OHTENKUN] Looks like we're in
for an emotional confrontation.