[DAKKI]
It's been well over a decade.
This body is just
not what it used to be.
[BUNCHU] You've brought
enough suffering to Yin.
And now you'll burn for it!
[KIBI]
Lo... Loli...
[DAKKI]
Kibi. Kijin.
If only I weren't so powerless.
[DAKKI]
I have the intellect.
And the cunning.
But I need loyal pawns
to bring my plan to fruition.
If that's the case,
why don't you posses a new body?
You do have that
special ability.
So simply go and take
whichever one you see fit.
I only wish that it were
all so straightforward.
But a body that's worthy
of housing my soul is rare.
They're born once
every hundred years.
I firmly believe that
time has come now.
Kibi and I discovered her
by random coincidence.
A stroke of good luck!
[OHKIJIN] The lovely daughter
of Lord So Go, of Kishu.
So Dakki.
[CHU] This is the last
time I'll ask politely.
Give your daughter to me
and I will make her
empress of Yin.
Refuse, and Kishu
will be turned to ashes.
[SO GO sighs]
I would suppose that I
am left with no other choice.
So strange.
Is this truly my destiny as
the lord of Kishu's daughter?
[SO DAKKI gasps]
You're so Dakki, right?
[SO DAKKI]
Oh. Yes.
With your big day upon us,
we're here to make
sure you're fully prepared.
We gotcha!
[KIBI]
Loli!
[OHKIJIN] Don't worry, we'll
take extra special care
with you.
Won't we, sister?
His majesty will wed
the fairest creature
that has ever
walked these lands.
So beautiful, inside and out.
You will mesmerize everyone
who lays eyes on you.
[DAKKI]
Yes.
From this point on all
shall be as I desire!
[laughing]
[CHOTENKUN]
So that is his true form?
This force is incredible!
[SAND KOSAJIN growl]
[YOZEN grunts]
[SAND KOSAJIN shriek]
[CHOTENKUN]
Such extraordinary power.
[YOZEN gasps]
[CHOTENKUN]
Have you forgotten?
We Juttenkun have the
ability to manipulate space.
I've made it so
the closer you come,
the farther away you get.
Your power may be great, Yozen.
But alas, it still won't be
enough to save you here.
[YOZEN laughing]
So it's hopeless.
Whatever shall I do now?
Perhaps I should just destroy
this world you've created.
[FUGEN] Less than four minutes
left until they fire again.
What are your orders?
Taikobo.
[HAKUTSURU]
Well?
You there?
[TAIITSU]
This is pointless, you know!
Even if Yozen is able to
take down the barrier,
it's gonna be too late!
Look, I know that you're
planning to drive Kongrong
straight into the cannon if
his mission is successful.
But the fact remains that
Kingo Island is still
five kilometers away!
Even at Kongrong's top speed
of 100 kilometers an hour,
it'll take three minutes
to get there,
and they're going to be
ready to fire in just
three and a half minutes!
I know how hopeless it seems.
[CHOTENKUN]
What?
My Kosajin cannot be destroyed!
[CHOTENKUN]
He transformed into the sand?
What do you think you're doing?
[YOZEN] I'm going to burst
through your little ball.
It's impossible to
create an infinite space
with even the
most advanced paopei.
So this precious world
of yours has boundaries.
[CHOTENKUN] And you really
believe that you can fill it
till it pops? [chuckles]
[YOZEN]
As I am at this moment...
I know I can.
[CHOTENKUN]
Interesting.
Let's see which
proves to be superior.
My Kosajin,
or your cheap transformation.
[OHTENKUN]
Well? How'd it go?
Did you turn Yozen
into a corpse?
What now?
We can't wait any longer.
We're gonna have
to run on faith.
Koshu.
I want you to use all
the energy we have left
to ram Kongrong
Mountain into Tsutenho
at maximum speed!
Are you sure
about that, Taikobo?
[TAIITSU] But Kingo Island's
barrier is still in place!
Yozen's mission must've failed.
I promise that
I won't let you down.
Now fire up the engines!
[FUGEN]
Distance to target,
5.085 kilometers.
That puts our arrival at
three minutes and one second.
We'll get there just in time.
We got this!
No way Yozen's
gonna let us down!
[RYUKITSU]
All right, Taikobo.
I'm putting my faith in you!
[TAIITSU]
What? No!
We're ready!
Full speed ahead!
Ready...
[OHTENKUN]
Answer me.
Is he dead?
[CHOTENKUN] We won't
have to worry about him.
He begged for his life,
but I ground him into dust.
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
That's not his style.
I know you can lie
much better than that.
Right, Yozen?
So, you were able to break
through his play-land after all.
Well... I'm not all that
surprised, to be honest.
I mean...
You do have his blood
running through your veins.
Let me tell you an
admittedly unflattering story.
It's a tale of two
abandoned children.
A well-kept secret
of the Sennin world.
Only the so-called
"three great Sennin"
and a handful of
others know about it.
About 200 years ago...
[TSUTEN]
Genshi Tenson.
[GENSHI]
Hm?
Kyoshu.
[GENSHI]
What are you doing here?
You know things are tense
between Yokai and humans
at the moment.
We need to talk.
Dakki's strength is growing
at an alarming pace.
Three days ago, she made
an exceptionally bold move.
She used her powers
of temptation to abduct
300 Sennin from Kingo.
[DAKKI]
Lord Tsuten Kyoshu!
It has been so long.
I've been thinking quite
a bit about striking out
on my own.
Naturally, I do expect
to have a few attendants
at my side.
I mean, both Kingo and Kongrong
will be under my
control sooner or later.
So do be prepared.
[TSUTEN] As I said, she's more
powerful with each passing day.
At this point, the only
ones who could stop her
are Shinkohyo and Taijo Rokun,
but there's slim chance
they would deign themselves
to render aid.
With this in mind...
I wish for Kongrong
Mountain and Kingo Island
to forge a non-aggression
pact between us.
As a token of my sincerity,
I offer you my son, Yozen.
[GENSHI]
Very well.
This is no time to be
at odds with one another.
In return, I offer
you my top pupil.
Oh Eki.
[OHTENKUN]
At the time,
I was expected to fill
the role Taikobo now holds.
That's what Genshi Tenson
had been grooming me for.
Later, I learned that the
real reason I'd been chosen
was due to the fact
that I had talents
similar to yours.
Are you surprised by my story?
Did you believe
you were the only one
with those kinds of issues?
But you're far better
off than I am.
You were brought up in a
safe and nurturing environment.
And what I experienced
was the complete opposite.
[TSUTEN]
At least Yozen will be safe now.
Dakki won't be able to
sink her claws into him
on Kongrong.
I realize this is tough for you.
But I cannot allow the
Yokai Sennin to sacrifice you
at any cost.
And so you must remain
here inside this cell.
One which no Yokai can enter.
Until you are fully grown.
[YOKAI 8A]
Looks like a human child.
[YOKAI 8B] Do they not know
how dangerous we Yokai are
to humans?
[YOKAI 8C] If the tasty little
thing happened to get out.
We'd have to eat him alive!
You don't belong!
No filthy human
belongs on Kingo!
I think he was
abandoned by the humans.
He must be a miserable
bastard to be hated
by both humans and Yokai.
[OHTENKUN (OH EKI)]
Why? Why? Why? Why?
Die, die, die, die,
die, die, die, die.
Die, die, die, die.
Die, die, die, die,
die, die, die...
Die, die, die.
Die, die, die, die,
die, die, die, die...
All of you. Die!
What in the hell am I?
Well, you know, don't you?
You know exactly what you are!
[chuckling]
[DAKKI] I know exactly how
you feel, you poor thing.
Heart full of hate.
You want to destroy all of
those who turned their backs
on you.
I'd never hurt you.
Because I'm your friend.
[OHTENKUN]
And soon...
I thought of Dakki as
my very own mother.
I promise that I will
get you out of here.
I'll give you strength.
To feed your hatred.
[OHTENKUN]
I'm broken.
Completely broken.
[YOZEN]
I already knew of this.
About 50 years ago,
I infiltrated Kingo
under somewhat of
a false pretext.
But my true mission
was to discover who I was
and where I came from.
I discovered my
father's identity.
And the reason I was
left on Kongrong Mountain
as a child.
Yeah?
And you still wanna fight
us after learning that?
It was vexing.
Finding out the truth
of who I was.
But now...
Now I am a Doshi of Kongrong.
Are you?
[laughing]
But so worn out that
you can't even maintain
your human form?
I'd expect more from
a prince like you.
Ah...
It'd be so damn easy
to kill you right now.
And a waste of time.
This is the switch to
turn off the barrier.
Have at it.
Exactly what are
you trying to pull?
[OHTENKUN]
Oh, please.
Did you think I was
just gonna tell you?
You'd better act quickly
before I change my mind.
But it'd be wise of you
to consider one thing.
If the barrier were to just
go down at this moment,
there would be a head-on
collision between Kingo
and Kongrong.
And if that happened,
every last Sennin and
Doshi could die all together
in an instant.
However, if the
barrier stays up,
Tsutenho will just blow
Kongrong into a million pieces.
We'd be more than
happy to accept you here
as one of our own.
But if word were to get
out about what you really are
back on Kongrong,
I'm positive that would be
quite a different story indeed.
That's just how humans are.
I'm sure you
realize that, Yozen.
You and I are both
detested creatures.
That's what we share.
You've done more than
your fair amount of fighting
for them, haven't you?
But is that only because
you feel like you're
in their debt?
[YOZEN]
In human society,
pretending to be
something I'm not
has been less difficult than
revealing my true nature.
But still...
I don't consider that
to be a simple task.
[OHTENKUN]
I'll say this.
I've been put through so
much suffering in this life.
So take it easy on me.
[BUNCHU] Kongrong Mountain
is rapidly approaching.
Has he gone mad
with desperation?
No.
Their timing would get them here
an instant before we can fire.
Taikobo has not given up
on this battle just yet.
I see.
Yozen infiltrated Kingo and
they're putting all their faith
in him.
But that's why I had
Ohtenkun ensure that he fails.
I haven't missed a single move.
[TAIITSU yelling]
We're gonna die!
[TAIKOBO]
Yozen.
Nothing has changed since
I first met you, my friend.
I have absolute trust in you.
We've gotta be brave!
Let's go!
Yozen won't let us down!
[OHTENKUN]
There's no denying it.
Like a moth to a flame,
I'm drawn to him.
Yes.
I've always chased something.
Stuck behind a locked door
searching for the key.