[YOZEN] I prefer to hide
behind a human form.
It's always been more
comfortable for me.
To say the least,
it's a lot easier to use
this false form in human society
as opposed to revealing
my true nature.
Although, embracing
this deception,
it meant I could never open my
heart to anyone but my master.
[YOZEN crying]
How about we get you
out of this rain, Yozen?
Don't want you to catch a cold.
[YOZEN] But I've never had
reason to open my heart.
I can do almost anything
you can imagine,
and I've never
needed anyone else.
But then... I met him.
And everything
I believed fell apart.
[TAIKOBO] Listen to me,
Supu, and don't turn around.
What're you talking about?
[TAIKOBO]
We've got somebody following us.
[SUPUSHAN]
What?
And it gets worse.
I'd recognize that
smell anywhere.
[SUPUSHAN]
Wait, their smell?
Oh, no, it smells like Da--
[TAIKOBO] Shh! Calm down!
Calm down, all right?
Listen, we'll turn around
on the count of three. One...
[SUPUSHAN]
Two...
[SUPUSHAN, TAIKOBO]
Three!
[DAKKI]
Ta-da!
[VOICES]
Do as before!
[SUPUSHAN, TAIKOBO]
Dakki!
It's been so long!
[SUPUSHAN, TAIKOBO yelling]
Help. My kness
got weak just now.
You know you can fly?
Hey, there, big boy.
I'm so glad you aren't
dead yet, Taikobo.
Why?
What is she doing all the way
out here in the countryside?
I'm here to kill you,
you silly goose!
Why else would I be
tromping around in the mud?
Oh, sweet Supushan.
[DAKKI] It breaks
my black heart to do it,
but you look too tasty to
not use my new paopei,
Sansento, on you.
You'll make for
a delicious sashimi!
Lay off him, Dakki!
[SUPUSHAN] Wait.
This doesn't make any sense.
The only time Dakki
ever lifts a finger
is to order her servants around.
But she came out here
on her own to kill us?
Is this some other kind of trap?
Well, then.
You've got me all worked up
to see what you can do,
hot stuff.
Prepare to fall to
the ground bewitched
before my sexy figure!
[TAIKOBO laughing]
Sorry, I can't take it anymore!
You're killin' me, you phony!
So she's a fraud?
[TAIKOBO]
Of course she is!
I mean, sure, it looks and
smells identical to her,
but there's somethin' that's
just obviously not right.
The dead giveaway--
the real Dakki?
She's never once referred
to you as Supushan!
Only thing she's ever
called you is "Good Boy"!
[SUPUSHAN]
That's what did it?
[TAIKOBO]
And I know who she is.
I've heard stories
of a brilliant Doshi
who's mastered transformation.
And I believe his name was...
...Yozen!
All right, ya got me.
Seems my reputation's
worked against me.
[YOZEN] Kudos on seeing
through my disguise.
Well done, Taikobo.
I'm exactly who you say.
Yozen of Mount Gyoksen
in the Kone-rone Mountains.
Student of Gyoktei
Shinjin of Kinkdado.
Holy crap!
That is one good-lookin' guy!
Way more of a
convincing hero than you.
Hey, shut up!
You think he's so great,
consider this.
Everything Dakki just said
to us came out of his mouth.
And I think we can all agree
that he was trying his hardest
to seduce me just now.
[YOZEN]
All right, about that--
Can we maybe agree
to not bring it up again?
So... What is it
you want from me?
Because you gotta admit
that was a pretty bizarre way
to introduce yourself.
[YOZEN]
Master Genshi Tenson sent me.
This is all his idea.
[YOZEN]
He ordered me to follow you,
and to assist you
with the Hoshin Project.
[TAIKOBO] That's about the
best news I've ever heard!
I'm more than happy
to let a genius like you
do all the hard work!
[YOZEN]
Not so fast.
I only agreed on one condition.
[TAIKOBO]
And that is...?
[YOZEN] That I first be allowed
to test you to find out
if you're genuinely
worthy of my assistance
on this crucial mission.
If you fail to live
up to my expectations,
well, I'll simply have to
carry out the Hoshin Project
in your place.
And defeat Dakki on my own.
Seriously?!
[YOZEN]
Go on and prove yourself.
Show me you're someone
to whom I can reveal
my true nature. Please.
[CHU]
Bunchu.
I have dispiriting news.
He betrayed us?
Hiko's forsaken Choka?
Your Majesty, there must
be some mistake.
I'm afraid not.
[BUNCHU]
He would never betray you.
Not without exceptional cause.
[BUNCHU]
Could it be...
Hiko.
Hello, my love.
Kashi!
[KASHI] I'm off to pay
my visit to your sister.
I do hate that I can only
see her at the beginning
of the New Year.
So, you're going to
the forbidden palace?
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
Please be careful.
I wish that I could go with you,
but no man is allowed
within the forbidden palace.
I know.
[DAKKI]
Well look at that!
If it isn't the
Buseioh's wife! Wow!
Oh, yeah?
[KASHI]
Dakki?
[DAKKI] It's been so long,
come on, let's have a drink!
[KASHI]
Uh, well...
--Thank you, but I--
--[DAKKI] Loosen up!
[DAKKI laughs]
[KASHI]
She really is a gorgeous woman,
but what's lurking
in that beautiful head?
[KOH SHI]
Sister!
I explicitly told you
to no longer visit me!
Don't you understand what's
happening in the capital
right now?
[KASHI]
I'm sorry, Koh Shi.
This is not what
I was expecting.
[ATTENDANT 3A]
My empress.
Emperor Chu has
arrived as you requested.
[KOH SHI, KASHI gasp]
[DAKKI]
Finally.
It certainly took
him long enough.
The Emperor?
Empress, you know this is wrong!
It's improper for the Emperor
to meet his retainer's wife!
[CHU]
I'm here, Dakki!
The life of the party
has officially arrived!
Who is that?
[DAKKI] This lovely creature
is the Buseioh's wife.
It is?
Please, forgive my intrusion.
Now, wait.
Are you so sure?
Kashi is an extraordinarily
beautiful woman.
I couldn't even dream
of competing with
her staggering beauty.
Well, one look
won't kill anyone.
Dakki!
Why are you encouraging this?
Wait!
C'mon, just let me have a really
quick little peek at your face!
[CHU laughing]
There's nowhere left for you
to run, my lovely Kashi.
Oh, wow.
I wouldn't say you're
as beautiful as Dakki,
but I'd definitely rank
you in the top five.
Don't you dare
lay a finger on me.
I'm the wife of the
Buseioh, Koh Hiko,
and I'm proud of that fact.
He's the only man
I will allow to touch me.
And I refuse to be dishonored.
[CHU]
Such a fine woman.
Now I truly want
to make you mine.
Please, Your Majesty,
don't do this!
[DAKKI] What belongs
to the Emperor's servants
belongs to the Emperor.
And you will belong to me.
If I refuse you,
I know my husband will
be punished as well.
So I acquiesce.
For this moment,
I belong to the Emperor.
[KASHI]
I may be in your possession,
but you will never
claim my heart.
Kashi!
[KOH SHI]
No! Oh, god, Kashi!
I... I'm sorry.
My detainment here has
only shackled my brother
and his wife to your tyranny.
[CHU]
Koh Shi!
This is for you, brother.
Through death,
I gift you your freedom.
[KOH MEI]
Hiko!
I'm sorry, but I
have terrible news!
You're gonna test me?
[YOZEN] To be precise,
you'll undergo three tests.
Well, two more,
as the first is complete.
You faced your greatest foe.
I confronted you
in the guise of Dakki
and you stood your ground.
All while retaining
your composure.
Therefore you passed.
That's great, but you
said I've still got
two more to go?
[YOZEN]
That's correct.
Shall we continue?
--[SUPUSHAN yells]
--Oh, crap, Supu!
Hey, what are you doing?
Leave me alone!
Stop it, let me go, you mutt!
[TAIKOBO]
That dog...
It's not a spirit beast.
[YOZEN]
Right you are.
He's actually my
paopei, Kotenken.
Now then. Kotenken.
Go ahead and sink your
teeth into Supushan.
[SUPUSHAN yells]
[TAIKOBO]
Supu, no!
Here's how this goes.
You fight me in earnest and
show your true power for once,
or Supushan will die.
I need to see how
strong you really are.
This is your second test.
[TAIKOBO]
Come on, Supu, fight!
Just bite the big, fluffy,
damn dog back!
What?! I can't do that!
You know I'm not a fighter!
I'm a hider or a die-er!
[YOZEN] Are you really going to
keep playing dumb and weak?
Quit stalling and fight me!
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you dodge
the attack, Master?
Look, Yozen.
You and I both know it
won't make any difference
who wins or loses this fight.
That's good enough for me.
You stood in the
direct path of danger
and stared it down
without even flinching.
As far as scoring goes,
you passed that test
with flying colors.
And the sun sets over Yin.
[HIKO]
Your Majesty.
I request a training match.
[CHU]
So you've come.
[SHINKOHYO] Seems I've
shown up just in time
for quite the spectacle.
You're here!
Hi, Shinkohyo!
[HIKO yelling]
What happened was
a tragic accident!
I know it wasn't your fault.
But that fact doesn't
change anything.
I have to do this.
It's the only way to
truly settle the score!
[HIKO grunts]
[YOZEN]
This is what Yin has come to.
All of those people have
fled Choka to head for Seiki.
But they have to pass
through the checkpoint,
Rintokan, to get there.
And in all reality, they'll
be refused and sent back.
This will provide the
basis for your third test.
Ensure that these
powerless people safely
make it past the checkpoint.
This will not be an easy task,
but if you succeed, I'll
acknowledge you as my superior.
[TAIKOBO growling]
Who do you think you are,
you arrogant jerk?
Making me jump
through hoops just to get
your nod of approval?!
[TAIKOBO]
You call this a test?
'Cuz it sounds like you're
passing the buck to me!
Why don't you go down there?
Let's see you help
those poor refugees!
But all right.
I'm not gonna run and back
down from your challenge.
Not if I wanna look
myself in the mirror.
Heh heh. But Yozen, you push
me into a corner like this,
I'm gonna get mean.
[TAIKOBO]
Let's do this, Supu!
Uh, roger that!
Just what the hell
is he planning to pull?
[CHU yelling]
Look at that.
The Buseioh's martial
arts skills come close
to rivaling that of a Sennin.
Emperor Chu's doing pretty well
holding his own against him.
[CHU, HIKO grunting]
[grunting]
I take it this means
you wish to leave Choka?
I do.
[CHU]
Then go.
But know that I'll miss you.
Do you plan to
immigrate to Seiki?
[HIKO]
Yes.
[CHU]
I see.
[HIKO]
Kashi, love...
[YOZEN] Whatever he meant,
I know he won't abandon
these poor souls.
[TAIKOBO]
How can you run away like this
when so many of your
people are still in Choka?
Your shameful cowardice
absolutely sickens me!
On principle alone,
I won't let you pass!
[REFUGEES chattering]
--[REFUGEES yelling]
--[TAIKOBO laughing]
That monster wasn't worth
testing in the first place.
It would be one thing to
unleash his cruelty on me,
but terrorizing these people?
Master Genshi Tenson,
you appointed the wrong
Doshi to this project.
And I was wrong.
Wrong to have harbored
any hope in him.
[YOZEN]
Go on and prove yourself.
Show me you're someone to whom
I can reveal my true nature.
Please.
[YOZEN]
Transform!
Spectacular work, great Doshi!
Just look at them all
running for their lives.
Actually, we're not done yet.
Uh, Buseioh?
Why've you come out here?
[HIKO]
To get some answers from you.
Some answers?
Why aren't you letting these
people pass through?
I... Well, sir, uh...
I was given these orders
from the Empress!
The Empress has chosen
to rescind that decree.
Those who want to leave are
allowed to pass from now on.
Yes, sir!
[TAIKOBO]
Don't fall for this!
That man is obviously
not the Buseioh!
Can't you tell that
he's a fraud?
He's an impostor?
Now that you mention it...
Is that so?
Why don't you
think this through?
Are you going to believe
your commanding chief
or this unknown Doshi?
[TAIKOBO]
Huh...?
I want you to apprehend this
suspicious Doshi at once!
[TAIKOBO yelling]
Oh, poor Master.
You have my gratitude, Buseioh.
This insane Doshi nearly had
me fooled with his ramblings.
[YOZEN]
Something's off here.
It's not like Supushan
to go along with this
without chastising him,
but he didn't voice
a word of protest.
Y'know, Master, if you keep
pulling stunts like this,
people are gonna
end up hating you
no matter how much
you're trying to help them.
[YOZEN] The refugees actually
got through the checkpoint.
Not only that, but the
only person who got hurt
was Taikobo himself.
Brilliant.
--Piece of crap!
--Stop! Get away from him!
Leave him alone!
You're a real slippery bastard.
[YOZEN]
Well done, Taikobo.
Tricking me to
save those people.
It was a true stroke of genius.
You aced the test.
You hear that, Supu?
The genius said my acting
was a stroke of genius!
Yeah, you're a Doshi,
but your greatest strength
might be deception.
And that is exactly the problem!
I mean, I'm the one
who's supposed to be
the master of deception.
But you so easily saw right
through my Dakki disguise.
So my acting skills
must be sorely lacking.
I have no choice but to
return to the Sennin world
in order to perfect my craft.
[TAIKOBO]
Wait, what?
Are you saying you're not
gonna team up with me now?
[DAKKI (YOZEN)]
No, not just yet.
I am a diehard
perfectionist after all.
Well then, ta-ta
for now, Taikobo!
[laughing]
[TAIKOBO]
Okay.
He really gets a kick out
of pretending to be Dakki.
[YOZEN] I know what kind
of Doshi he is now,
and maybe he could
understand me.
Maybe even go so far
as to trust me.
Although, that won't make
it any easier to tell him.
But he deserves
to know the truth.
[YOZEN]
Taikobo.
There's a storm brewing
in the skies over Choka.
Hurry to the west
before it's too late.
When the time arises,
I'll appear again
to assist you on your quest.
I promise that
I won't let you down.
[CHU] The Buseioh's
family left yesterday.
They've deserted Choka
to flee towards Seiki.
I'm allowing them to leave
without any interference.
[BUNCHU] If Hiko allies
himself with Seiki,
that could be enough for
the people to acknowledge
Kisho as the true king.
If Seiki gains any more power,
we'll have no choice
but to crush it.
Regardless of the
centuries that I've lived,
you always acted as though
you were my older brother.
But, no matter what I said,
it never bothered me.
Hiko, you were the one person
I could open my heart to.
[KOKUKIRIN]
Master Bunchu.
[BUNCHU]
Kokukirin.
Summon the Shisei
of Kuryu Island.
[KOKUKIRIN]
The Shisei?
Then, you truly do intend
to defeat Koh Hiko.
He must be stopped.
For the sake of Yin
and Emperor Chu.
[KOKUKIRIN]
Understood.
I'll bring them.
[BUNCHU]
Hiko.
I have no choice
but to see you dead.
We once walked
the same path together,
but this is where it splits.