[KOKUKIRIN groans]
Master Bunchu!
We must evacuate immediately!
This acid is lethal.
It's burning right
through my outer shell!
It's time to escape!
[KOKUKIRIN]
Master Bunchu, please.
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[OHTENKUN]
It's been fun, Bunchu,
but all good things must end.
You're not so scary when
your will is shattered
by the reality of
your true weakness.
But of course, I should have
expected that from a mere human.
--[OHTENKUN chuckling]
--[BUNCHU yelling]
He still has that much power?
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[KOKUKIRIN groans]
[KOKUKIRIN]
Master Bunchu...
Ohtenkun! He's down!
[chuckles]
Huh?
What a spectacle
this whole thing was.
Quite the show.
This was undoubtedly worth
giving up one of
my souls to see.
I give you thanks.
It feels so good to
be alive right now!
[TAIKOBO]
All right, listen.
Kingo Island is about to fall.
I know everyone's exhausted,
but you gotta find
the strength to escape.
And you?
I'm staying to clean up.
[TAIKOBO]
It's time.
I have to finish this now.
[KOKUKIRIN]
Master Bunchu, look over there.
The sunset... It's so beautiful.
[groans] Friend.
You've always been there for me.
[KOKUKIRIN]
Forgive me, Master,
but it appears I cannot
serve you any longer...
My sincere apologies...
And mine to you.
[BUNCHU]
Goodbye.
For most of my life,
I was never pained by
the idea of being alone.
When did it first find me--
the agonizing solitude
I know so well?
[BUNCHU]
It was after I met Hiko.
He took my loneliness away...
...and replaced it
with something else.
[TAIKOBO]
You ready, Bunchu?
This will be the final battle.
Bring out Kinben!
[BUNCHU chuckles]
[BUNCHU]
Foolish Taikobo.
I warned you before,
but it seems as though
you've yet to learn.
If you wield that
much confidence,
you ought to have the strength
and skills to support it.
Should you manage to
defeat me somehow...
...I'll affirm your right
to speak with such pride.
[BUNCHU yells]
[TAIKOBO groans, grunts]
[BUNCHU grunts]
[TAIKOBO]
Chi!
[TAIKOBO] Bunchu, you and the
Yin have both grown decrepit.
The human world
needs a young wind.
That's its only hope!
So it's time for you to go!
[BUNCHU] If that's what you
believe, you're delusional!
I won't hand over the human
world to such a myopic brat!
You're just a naive child!
[TAIKOBO yells]
[SUPUSHAN]
Taikobo!
[TAIKOBO groans]
--[panting]
--[SUPUSHAN] Stay calm!
--Don't do anything crazy!
--[panting]
[TAIKOBO]
Not good.
I'm almost out of
strength at this point!
Although, the same goes for him.
All right.
No matter what it costs me
and no matter what I must do,
I have no option here
but to prevail!
Now, Bunchu! Let's finish this!
Heh. Fine with me.
Bring it, Taikobo!
[yells]
[BUNCHU groaning]
[TAIKOBO groaning]
[BUNCHU grunts]
[yelling]
[BUNCHU]
This is it.
My vision is leaving.
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[pants]
He's done.
[clanking]
[BUNCHU gasps]
[TAIKOBO grunts]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[TAIKOBO groans]
[TAIKOBO coughs]
[TAIKOBO chuckles]
[TAIKOBO grunts]
[BUNCHU chuckles]
[BOTH grunting]
[SUPUSHAN] This has
turned into a real mess.
But... maybe this
is how a battle
deciding the fate of
the world should be.
[TAIKOBO grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[BUNCHU coughing]
[BUNCHU gasping, panting]
[BUNCHU] When Hiko died,
I realized... what I wanted.
I was fighting to get back Yin,
but not as it stands today.
I long for the old Yin...
where I knew Hiko.
I wanted another chance
at those times I lost.
Bunchu...
[BUNCHU]
You win, Taikobo.
I surrender the
human world to you.
Do your best to free it
of Sennin and Doshi,
as you pledged before.
[BUNCHU] However... I will
not give you power over me.
[BUNCHU] I regret not
meeting you sooner in life.
Maybe if I had,
I could have found my way
along a much different path.
You were right.
This is the end.
[thud]
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
[SUPUSHAN]
Taikobo?
Hey, Taikobo!
[YOKAI 23A]
Is Bunchu really dead?
[YOKAI 23B]
It's the end of Kingo Island!
[YOKAI 23C] Hurry!
It's crumbling on top of us!
[YOKAI 23D]
Out of the way! That's my ride!
What is that thing?
[YOKAI 23F]
Who cares? Just run!
[KI HATSU]
Oh, really?
That's great news.
I knew he would.
I've just received word that
Taikobo has pulled it off!
Yin's Grand Preceptor, Bunchu,
has been defeated at last!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
Wait just a damn minute!
The score with Kingo Island
has finally been settled?!
Why the hell didn't any
of you fools wait for me?!
[MALE CITIZEN 23A] We're all
starving to death out here!
[FEMALE CITIZEN 23A]
Just some food for the children.
All of you, back away.
If you dare come any closer
to the emperor's palace,
you will all pay severely!
Unlock the gates.
Gather the food from
within the castle
and give it to these
people in need.
Are you giving me orders?
[CHU groans]
[SOLDIER 18A] Who the hell
do you think you are?
[SOLDIER 23A]
Wait! Stop! Step back!
We know that man!
[CHU groans]
[CHU]
This country has no leader.
The emperor...
is no longer fit to rule.
[CITIZENS chattering, laughing]
Whoa! Is this really happening?
You're alive!
Oh, thank goodness! I thought
you were dead for sure!
You're loud. [groans]
What's the update
on our situation?
Well, Taiitsu Shinjin made a
big announcement to everyone
that Kingo Island
was about to fall.
So now they're all
evacuating as we speak!
[TAIKOBO]
Whoa!
We managed to escape.
Everyone made it out safely.
Thank you, Taikobo.
Why me?
Because I know that must've
been a difficult clean-up job.
[TAIKOBO]
He was pretty strong.
It wasn't easy.
Uh--
[VENUS] All the yokai Sennin of
Kingo Island have been rescued!
If you're wondering
who you can thank,
turn your eyes toward the
fabulous Unsho Sisters!
[YOKAI 23G]
Goodbye, Kingo Island.
That's Mount Kongrong.
[YOZEN]
It's falling.
[BUNCHU]
Emperor Chu.
Shushi...
I'm so proud of you.
You did well.
[BUNCHU] I promise... I did
everything I possibly could...
...for the good of our child.
For Yin.
[BUNCHU]
Hiko...
[grunts]
Look, there it is!
The Hoshindai is still standing!
Wait, does anyone
know where Master is?
He'll be back soon.
He needed some time alone.
Master...?
[SUPUSHAN] Ever since the war
ended, Master's been missing.
I can't believe that he just
wandered off to knows where
and left us behind to
deal with all the chaos
that he totally created!
He's lucky we haven't found him,
'cause when we do,
we owe him a beating!
[BUKICHI] Do you happen to
know where our Master is?
[coughs]
I'm sorry, I don't.
Good luck to you.
[BUKICHI]
Excuse me, have you seen...
[TAIITSU]
What? Who?
I can barely hear you.
But if you mean Taikobo,
I have no idea!
Do you have any idea
where Master could be?
Honestly, I haven't seen
him in quite some time.
I do hope you manage to
find him soon, though.
Taikobo?
Sorry, I have no clue.
Neither do I,
but we'll certainly
keep an eye out for him!
Do you know what I think?
With a little more
training you'd be able to
find the boy instantly!
Okay, so he's not here,
but who else can we ask?
Oh! I have an idea!
[VENUS]
Now pay attention!
If you wish to continue
living in the human world,
then you must start
obeying human laws!
The most important rule is
there will be no
consumption of humans!
[YOKAI 23H]
Shut up, ugly!
[YOKAI 23I]
Get off the stage and die!
[YOKAI chattering]
[YOKAI yelling]
[BUKICHI] Doesn't look
like he's here, either.
[SUPUSHAN]
Oh, well.
I remember this place!
[SUPUSHAN]
I think it was right around here
that I first carried
Master into battle!
What a day.
Actually...
...no matter where I look,
all I can see are places
where we flew together.
[SUPUSHAN sighs]
[SUPUSHAN] I don't know
where else we can look.
Tell me the truth.
Do you think we're ever
gonna see him again?
[SUPUSHAN]
I know we will.
He'll come back at some point.
He's just that way!
I'll be so excited to see him!
I'll carry him on my back
to our next adventure!
[BUKICHI] Mm. And I'll be
following you both around
wherever you go,
even into the most
terrifying places!
[TAIKOBO whistling]
[laughs] That was so worth it!
Man, there's nothing I love more
than messing with those two!
But--I'm glad to get
a break from the noise.
Nap time.
[SHINKOHYO]
A nap? Really?
You haven't changed in the
slightest and never will.
[SHINKOHYO]
So, what do you intend to do
after freeing the human
world from the Sennin, hmm?
[TAIKOBO]
No plans.
I wasn't trying to
change human history.
I just wanted to help them
and fight with a team who
felt the same way as I did
about... certain things.
You mean about Dakki?
Yeah.
[SHINKOHYO] You could sense her
this whole time, couldn't you?
[DAKKI]
I have a single, small desire.
I wish to be the one and
only ruler of this planet.
I wish to become
this droplet of water.
I want to quench the earth and
create a life full of blessings.
[DAKKI]
I want to exist within the soil.
I want to be the power
behind the wind.
Just the sort of selfish
desires I'd expect from you.
[DAKKI]
Oh, really?
Joka also intended to
meld with this planet.
If I plan to take control of
Joka and do so in her place,
why would that be a problem?
Finally, my dear Taikobo.
Let me be your new mother.
I'll watch over you and
protect you forever.
I won't forget you.
Bye-bye.
Well, how do you plan to spend
all this free time you'll have?
I'll keep wandering around.
I'm not surprised.
Tell me something.
Do you know this place?
It was on this very
spot that you and I
fought our first battle
against each other.
How about one last fight
for old times' sake?
What do you say?
We'll keep it light and easy.
I was just joking.
Although it might not be
a bad idea for another day.
Besides, if I were
to fight you now,
what would I have to look
forward to in the future?
[yawns]
Now then.
Where should I go next?
[OH EKI] As for me... we will
say I'm Genshi Tenson's pupil.
This plan will come to fruition
in approximately 2,000 years,
when power shifts
from Yin to Shu.
[OH EKI]
At that time,
we will set the Hoshin
Project into motion.