[clock ticking]
Mount Kongrong
and Kingo Island--
the two greatest powers of the
Sennin world are now at odds.
But this conflict
didn't really begin
until you disappeared
from the human world.
[SHINKOHYO]
Bunchu only decided to fight
when he saw Tsuten Kyoshu,
or, rather, the mindless husk
that you turned him into.
Well done.
Your wisdom is a truly
astounding thing.
Not even Joka could
manipulate events
as skillfully as
you've managed to do.
So, you simply must tell me.
Is the return of Joka
finally at hand?
[SHINKOHYO]
Oh, wait.
If she does return,
then what of you?
In her physical form,
she can do as she pleases
and she won't need
a servant anymore.
Surely you have some plan
for how you'll deal with that
when the time comes.
Or perhaps you've no intention
of bringing Joka back at all.
Have you been
deceiving her as well?
Certainly not!
Lady Joka and I are
partners in crime
together until the bitter end!
[BUNCHU]
Buseioh?
Ohtenkun?
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
What's the matter, Bunchu?
You caught off guard?
Don't just stand
there gawking at us.
You could at least
say something.
This makes no sense.
Your soul was released!
Do you really think I would die
such a lame death as that?
One of those fighters must
have hit you in the head.
What's going on?
Where am I?
Huh?
[HIKO]
Is that...?
Bunchu!
Are you responsible for this?
And if I am?
Just admit that you and
your whip are to blame.
[BUNCHU]
That's right.
This is all my doing.
How could you?
[GENSHI groans]
[KOSHU gasps]
[HAKUTSURU whimpers]
Hey.
Long time no see, geezer.
You!
[OHTENKUN]
You've really lost your edge.
Now, now.
I wouldn't do that, princess.
You're totally spent
from keeping that
energy-guzzling Kongrong
moving, aren't you?
[GENSHI]
It's all right.
Both of you stand down.
I can't!
He'll kill you!
[GENSHI]
If this is karma, then so be it.
Now, don't engage him.
That's an order.
[HAKUTSURU]
Master Genshi...
Ha! You of all people must have
known I was still alive, right?
Have you been looking
over your shoulder,
wondering when I'd show?
You're the one who split
up my soul, after all.
Always quite the schemer.
You made it look as though you
were teaming up with Kingo...
...but your goal was
to bring Joka down
with Kongrong's power alone.
[GENSHI] The true goal
of the Hoshin Project...
[OHTENKUN]
Hm?
Fool.
I'm actually grateful to you.
I got to experience
the pleasure of death
and the ecstasy
of killing a man--
the simple things that
make life worth living.
What?
[HIKO gasps]
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
Just wait here, old man.
I'll take my time
ripping out your entrails
after I'm done with the others.
[GENSHI]
So, Nento.
I've heard Taijo Rokun has
taken a strange child in
under his wing.
Is this true?
[NENTO]
Yes.
The boy is quite
a mystery indeed.
There's something odd about
his chi. It's not like ours.
Ah.
[NENTO]
That's him.
[OH EKI] Hello, Genshi
Tenson, Nento Dojin.
I've been waiting for you.
And you are?
[OH EKI]
My name is Oh Eki.
I am one of the progenitors.
[GENSHI] Joka, the
"Signpost of History"...
Such a being actually exists?
[OH EKI] I remained behind,
as last progenitor,
so I could stop Joka
from causing ruin.
[OH EKI] She must not be
allowed to have her way.
[OH EKI]
However, I unfortunately
lack the strength to
defeat her on my own,
which is why I am forced to
ask for your assistance.
Hang on.
You said Joka has destroyed
the world many times, yeah?
So why didn't you defeat
her sooner, in the past?
[OH EKI] Joka's physical
body has been sealed
and she can only move
and act as a spirit.
Because she has exhausted
so much energy in that form,
the wisp of her existence
has grown weak, vulnerable.
On the other hand, due to
her repeated annihilations,
this planet's lifeforms
have evolved into stronger,
more resilient beings.
I have been forced to stand by
and wait for Joka to grow weak,
while the rest of you
grew stronger.
You mean... you've just been
watching the world get destroyed
over and over again?
Do you really think
that's fair?!
[OH EKI] Fairness doesn't
enter into the equation.
What I need you to do
is make a choice.
[OH EKI]
Will you accept that its fate
for Joka to destroy your
world again... or not?
I will join you.
We'll stop her together.
You sure?
Now then, Oh Eki.
Please tell us the best way
to proceed from this point on.
[OH EKI] The first step
is obtaining weapons.
All seven paopei we
created are required.
You must venture out
and find each one of them.
Once the seven people capable
of using them come together,
Joka's end will be at hand.
You mean the super paopei.
Several of them are
on Mount Kongrong.
[OH EKI]
This plan must remain top secret
so that Joka does not
suspect a thing.
As for me... we will say
I'm Genshi Tenson's pupil.
[OH EKI]
This plan will come to fruition
in approximately 2,000 years.
Oh Eki...
[YOZEN gasps]
Mount Kongrong is in shambles!
But how is that possible?
[TAIKOBO]
Yozen, look. Over there.
[YOZEN]
I see it.
That's the space
of the Juttenkun!
Well, it sure took
you long enough.
Glad you could make it.
Ohtenkun?
But how?!
This has to be an illusion!
You died.
I was there when it happened!
[OHTENKUN]
Oh, that's right.
I forgot about this guy.
[YOZEN gasps]
[TENKA groans]
Man...
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[TAIKOBO]
Tenka!
[TENKA grunts]
Taikobo?
What is this?
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
Oh, good, now we have
all the players together.
But first, a rule.
No one can enter
Kosuijin Type-2.
You'll never get in
from the outside.
However, anyone inside
is free to exit
whenever they would
like to leave.
So, without any further ado...
[OHTENKUN]
...I hope you'll enjoy watching
this fascinating show!
[ALL gasp]
[HIKO gasps]
It's the palace.
[BUNCHU]
Not so.
This is no more than an
illusionary hyperspace
created by Ohtenkun.
What a waste of time.
I can't even imagine what he
thinks this could possibly do.
I'll dispense of it quickly
and use Kinben to completely
destroy the fiend.
I see what you're doing,
but I won't allow you to ignore
me and change the subject.
We still have
matters to discuss!
How strange.
I can't think of a single
thing I need to say to you.
[HIKO grunts]
Fine!
But you will listen to me!
Open your eyes and see
what's in front of you.
Do you not realize what
the hell you're doing?!
[BUNCHU]
Enough!
Don't you ever put your
hands on me again!
Beating your opponents
into submission
is not who you are, Bunchu.
It's not who you
were trained to be.
You would never take
the life of someone weaker.
There's more than
just brute strength
that's required of
a Grand Preceptor.
Try to keep that
in mind, will ya?
Is that so?
I can see right through you.
I know what you're trying to do.
Both of our lives
are on the line now
and you're hoping mere
words will affect me.
You think you can stir my heart
with stories from the past
and lead with feelings?
How blind can you be, Buseioh?
I will not be swayed
by sentimentality.
I've long since decided
that I will never open
my heart to another again.
Yin is all I have now
and I will do anything
for the good of its future!
[OHTENKUN]
Can we get on with it?
I'm bored with all this
emotional chatter.
For the good of all invested,
I suggest you finish this.
Give your viewers
what they came to see.
Dad, don't!
Bunchu's acting crazy right now!
I got this, Tenka.
Have faith in me.
Be careful.
I gotta say this
makes me sad, Bunchu.
The man I once knew
doesn't exist anymore.
But at the very least,
I'll slay the monster
you've become!
Yozen.
Transform into Ohtenkun.
Then you can undo Kosuijin.
[YOZEN]
Right.
--Tenka, step aside please.
--[TENKA gasps]
[YOZEN gasps]
[YOZEN]
No.
[TAIKOBO]
What's wrong?
[YOZEN]
Unbelievable.
I won't be able to do it.
Ohtenkun himself has
transformed into Kosuijin,
which means he's
probably the only one
who has the ability
to remove it.
But something feels different.
He's not the same Ohtenkun.
I have to wonder
if it's really him.
What?
[TENKA]
Dad, no!
I'm coming for you, Bunchu!
[BUNCHU scoffs]
[HIKO groans]
You are quite the fool.
Do you truly believe a
mere mortal with nothing
but a calloused pair of fists
has a chance to defeat me?
Damn right I do!
[HIKO grunts, groans]
[HIKO groans]
[BUNCHU gasps]
[HIKO groaning]
[HIKO grunts]
[BUNCHU grunts]
[TENKA]
Damn it!
What the hell is he doing?
No way he'll beat Bunchu!
[TENKA grunts]
[TENKA]
He needs to have this!
[TENKA gasps]
[HIKO exhales]
[TENKA sighs]
I know!
The Twelve Elite Sennin
could help him out!
They're probably the only ones
who could actually do something!
Right, you don't know.
All of them are gone.
[gasps]
All of them?
So Coach Dotoku...?
Out of the twelve Sennin...
...ten of them
are confirmed dead.
The only one we know to be alive
currently is Master Taiitsu.
Master Doko is still missing.
I spoke to him in
his final moments.
He asked me to give you this.
[gasps]
Thanks, Coach.
[TENKA]
Damn it... Why?
I have no desire to take
your life with my own hands.
I'd prefer a dignified
battle between our armies
after we've returned
to the human world.
I'm giving you
the chance to leave.
[grunts]
Shut up, already.
I'm not leaving here until I've
cracked your face
open with my fist.
[BUNCHU scoffs]
[BUNCHU] For somebody
who's on the verge of death,
you're persistent.
[HIKO]
Heh. That goes for you, too!
You haven't changed
at all, you bastard!
[gasps]
You're right.
I've not.
And I never will
when it comes to Yin!
I'll always fight to protect it!
Bunchu!
[BUNCHU grunts]
[HIKO groans]
[HIKO]
What's wrong with you?
You jackass!
[HIKO groans]
[TENKA gasps]
What the...?
[HIKO groaning]
Hiko...
Bunchu's mask just...
...fell off.
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
What an interesting
turn of events this is.
[gasps, groans]
[BUNCHU gasps]
[KOKUKIRIN]
Master Bunchu, we are in danger.
We must depart immediately.
Not even your strength
can withstand this.
Master Bunchu!
[gasps]
[HIKO wheezing]
Listen to me, Bunchu.
You gotta open your eyes.
It's changed.
The Yin you and I
once knew is gone!
[HIKO]
It doesn't exist anymore!
[BUNCHU]
You're wrong.
As long as I draw breath,
Yin will prevail.
It will continue its resilience.
I will not hear such vile words
from the mouth of a traitor!
How dare you try to
tear me from it.
If I were to forsake Yin,
it would be at the
request of its people!
Do you hear me?
Now stop wasting your time
and get out of here!
I'm through staring into
the eyes of a coward!
You are my enemy, Hiko.
I've nothing more to--[gasps]
[chuckles]
There's the face of
the man I once knew.
I see you.
Hold on.
Don't go now.
Please!
Not yet!
Taikobo, are you there?
[gasps]
[HIKO]
I leave the rest up to you!
Goodbye, Dad.
Buseioh...
[JOKA]
Long ago,
I was captured and sealed
away by my own brethren.
But in time I developed a way
to move about as a spirit.
Once I could do that,
I began to rebuild this land
in the image of my lost home.
I led it along the same
evolutionary course
with which I had been familiar,
perpetually building it anew.
And then I would destroy it.
Building and destroying,
for millions of years...
It was all part of my quest to
create the perfect final form.
[JOKA] And at last, I'm seeing
all my hard work bear fruit.
I'm building a perfect world.
And soon, our home
will be reborn.
[JOKA]
Yes...
Yes!
Dakki!