[FUGEN]
Hey, Bo.
I was just thinking...
Do you remember that time
we snuck away with Kokin
to head out on
a little adventure?
Yeah!
I haven't thought
about that in ages now.
Kind of a random memory there.
[FUGEN] It's funny we
were brazen enough to slip
a sleeping drug into
Master Genshi's food
just so we could steal
Kokin and fly down
to romp around the human world.
[FUGEN, TAIKOBO]
Later!
[laughing]
[FUGEN] I really miss
those days, y'know.
It's just...
I can't help but feel
nostalgic for the time
when we didn't have to fight.
Well, doesn't matter now.
Here we are.
Bunchu will be here soon,
so we need to be prepared.
Let's have a snack while we can.
[TAIKOBO]
Whoa! Sesame dumplings!
[munching]
Thanks, Fugen!
That got my energy up.
Wait... Maybe not.
[FUGEN]
Sorry, Bo. Don't hate me.
[TAIKOBO groaning]
[snoring]
Take 'em down, Master!
Looks like we've got a
pretty good sized audience.
Better make this count.
Perfect time to show everyone
how powerful I really am.
[KOKUTENKO]
Hmm...
Well this makes for an
interesting turn of events.
Oh, nothing's ever
interesting enough for me.
You know that it's
my personal mission
to make every situation
more entertaining,
and I've got one last
piece to put in place
before we enjoy this spectacle.
[KOKUTENKO]
You do?
So that guy's the
illustrious Taikobo, eh?
Yep.
I heard plenty of stories about
him up in the Sennin world.
I feel pretty lucky I get
the chance to actually
see him fight.
You can hang back
for this one, guys.
I'll handle this fool on my own.
[KOYUKEN chuckles]
I'm Koyuken, one of the
four Shisei of Kuryu Island.
And you, Taikobo of Kongrong,
will die by my hand!
Whoa, hang on!
I've got a question first!
I've heard about you
and I even know
that you once fought Dakki!
Well she's my enemy too!
Wouldn't it make more
sense for us to join forces
and take her down together?
That's a lovely thought,
but you're also an enemy
of Master Bunchu, and right now,
that's the only thing
that matters.
Not to mention I'm having
too much fun to stop!
I haven't cut loose
like this in forever!
[TAIKOBO] Well, crap. I guess
he's not gonna back down.
[RI KOHO] Now why does Koyuken
get to have all the fun?
I want my turn to fight, too!
[TAIKOBO, SUPUSHAN gasp]
[TAIKOBO] At this rate,
we won't even have a chance
to fight back!
Koyuken's right.
He can easily take care
of these guys on his own.
Hey, Koyuken!
No reason for us
to stick around,
so Ri Koho and I are
gonna attack Seiki.
Just make sure that you
and Yoshin finish off
all of the others after Taikobo.
Wait, Seiki?
--You get all that?
--Of course.
[NATAKU]
I'll deal with those two.
He's clearly the
strongest of the group.
I can smell his power.
[TAIKOBO]
Chase after them!
Up, up, down, down, left,
right, left, right, B, A!
What are you talking about?
[KOYUKEN]
You're not going anywhere.
[BUKICHI yells]
Uh-oh!
Master Taikobo!
[RI KOHO]
I like this plan.
The only orders
Master Bunchu gave us
were to kill the Buseioh
and his clan,
but he never said anything
about not destroying Seiki.
You'd have to be an idiot
to not read between the lines.
Seiki's a major threat to Yin,
so we're helping Master Bunchu
by wiping it off the map.
You keep moving,
I've got this one.
[NATAKU]
Hold it.
I'm after the
strong one, not you.
I'm gonna make you
regret underestimating me.
[NATAKU]
Interesting.
I suppose I'll kill you first,
then go after him.
[YOZEN]
Stop right there.
I know you!
You're the genius Doshi, Yozen!
You came down to get
mixed up in this, too?
I recommend you
turn back now, Shisei.
What's the point of rushing
headfirst into your death?
Don't waste your thousand
years of training.
[KOYUKEN laughing]
That takes care of one of them.
Let's see what
the rest have to offer.
Kick his ass, Master!
[KOYUKEN]
How are you still alive?
[TAIKOBO laughs]
That's all your fault!
You essentially built me
my own escape route
with all that water you
threw down beneath me!
[laughing]
We can finally start
this fight for real now.
You're only gonna hurt
yourself if you try to use
that attack on me this close.
[KOYUKEN] Oh, you prefer
close-quarters combat?
Well, funny enough, I do too!
Ah! I can't get it off!
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
[BUNCHU] What have you
come here for, clown?
I have zero inclination
to fight you.
Really?
Nice to see you're aware of
your own limitations, Bunchu.
I can't help but admire a man
who understands his place.
But you see,
I'm actually here to let you
in on a little something.
Your Shisei assassins are
making a move to attack Seiki.
[BUNCHU]
Don't be absurd.
I gave them orders to kill
Hiko before he arrives there.
[SHINKOHYO]
I know that.
But Ohma has chosen to take the
battle to the skies over Seiki.
Civilians will die,
there's no doubt.
Figured that might
not sit right with you.
[BUNCHU] You'd better
be telling the truth.
[TAIKOBO gurgling]
Fight, Master!
You're gonna look like an
idiot if you drown like this!
We're on dry land!
I'd kill for a
breath of fresh air!
No!
That's enough.
Time to jump in!
[BUKICHI yells]
[HIKO]
Tenka!
Uh... Y'know, Yoshin?
It's kind of in bad
form to kill humans
that aren't Sennin or Doshi.
Not to say that I haven't.
No other choice.
Our paopei attacks are too
large-scale for this fight.
They work perfectly for
annihilating large armies,
but dealing with
targets this small?
It's too difficult to
single them out.
[OHMA]
Yozen. [chuckles]
If I defeat you, it'll make me
the most famous of the Shisei.
Not only that...
Master Bunchu will be even more
feared than he already is.
Listen, calm down.
If you came to fight,
let's do it elsewhere.
There's no reason for
us to risk the lives
of the people of Seiki.
I know you Shisei use rather
haphazard techniques.
[OHMA]
Hey, two birds with one stone.
[OHMA] I came here to
destroy Seiki, you fool!
Now go, Kaitenju!
Are you insane?
You see that mountain, Yozen?
Well you're falling next!
[CIVILIANS yelling]
[YOZEN] You just crossed a line
from which you can't walk back!
[OHMA]
I'm shaking.
Am I actually letting
this guy intimidate me?
[YOZEN]
If you're here to destroy Seiki,
I'll just have to put an end
to you before you can go
any further with it!
[OHMA] Yeah? You think you
can pull that one off, huh?
'Cause I can't wait
to see you try!
[OHMA]
I got him!
I killed the genius!
[YOZEN]
Or so it would seem.
The explosion?
That was just me
destroying your weapon.
[OHMA]
You're alive? Where are you?
[YOZEN] Much closer
than you want me to be.
I'm disguised as
one of your Kaitenju.
[OHMA]
You what?!
Don't give me that crap!
I can tell my Kaitenju are real!
They're connected
directly to my will!
[YOZEN]
I'm aware of that.
How else could I perfectly
transform into one?
This is my true power.
And how I earned my
"genius" reputation!
Fine, then!
I'll just have to launch
every one of them
and destroy you
and Seiki both!
[YOZEN]
Wrong move.
[OHMA yells]
[YOZEN]
I tried to warn you.
No...
[YOZEN]
Let it go.
[OHMA] I can't face Master
Bunchu if it ends like this.
[YOZEN] I must admit,
your tenacity is admirable,
but the smart move
here is to go home.
And that is the last
warning I'll give you.
Need... da beach...
Huh? What're you saying?
Are they your last words?
[TAIKOBO]
Beaches!
What beaches?
[TAIKOBO]
Da beach!
Hey, what's he up to?
[KOYUKEN]
Wha--?!
[KOYUKEN] How did he drink
all of that seawater?!
Behold my master's beloved,
top-secret item, the Sento!
Yep! This little peach here
converts any water into
top-shelf booze!
So thanks for that attack!
I got a nice little
buzz from it.
[hiccups]
[KOYUKEN]
Seriously? I can't believe
you overpowered my technique
with a move that stupid!
[TAIKOBO laughing]
[TENKA] Just so you know,
I'm gonna end this quickly.
I'd rather not risk losing
someone that I care about.
In that case...
My power's a bit depleted.
Hey, Yoshin.
I could use some healing here.
[YOSHIN]
Hekichiju.
Share with me the
power of the earth.
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[KOYUKEN chuckles]
Now that's not fair!
[TENKA]
Taikobo!
I'll help you take
these guys down.
[TAIKOBO]
Thank you!
There's something wrong.
What am I feeling?
No...
Is that...?
He's here!
[YOZEN]
Wait!
It's like the air is
trembling with great power,
and worse, with immense fury.
[YOZEN]
Nataku!
[NATAKU]
Have we met?
We have to go.
Taikobo's in great danger.
[SUPUSHAN]
What's happening, Master?
[TAIKOBO]
Well, I'm not exactly sure.
But you can feel that pressure
building up in the air, right?
[SUPUSHAN] Yeah, it's so thick
I'm having trouble breathing!
[TAIKOBO] Is he already
jumping in the fight?
Not good. None of us are
prepared to take him on!
[OHMA]
Koyuken! Yoshin!
[KOYUKEN]
You're back!
Taikobo! Are you
all right down there?
Oh, hey, Yozen!
It's good to see ya again!
But let's catch up later.
[YOZEN]
Indeed.
I've never encountered
anyone that gave off
such an intimidating aura.
Whoever they are, they're
even stronger than I am.
[GROUP yelling]
The hell is this?
[GROUP gasps]
[grunts]
[HIKO]
It's Bunchu!
[BUNCHU]
This is child's play.
You are the Doshi,
Taikobo, correct?
[SHINKOHYO chuckles]
You see, what'd I tell you?
Vastly more interesting
now, isn't it?
[SHINKOHYO]
Bunchu's paopei, Kinben,
is a simple
yet powerful tool.
One that can attack enemies
a few kilometers away.
Which is precisely what
makes it such a challenge
to contend with.
Is this seriously
your idea of fun?
You need a new hobby.
[BUNCHU]
Tell me, Taikobo.
Why are you bent
on destroying Yin?
You're just as
reprehensible as Dakki.
Trying to manipulate the human
world with the power of Sennin
and Doshi.
[TAIKOBO]
You're wrong!
I'm gathering allies
for one purpose,
and that's to finally expel
all the Sennin and Doshi
who serve Dakki from
the human world!
[BUNCHU]
You say that...
So then why are you trying
to destabilize the empire?
Defeating Dakki
and her underlings
should be more than enough!
I thought the same thing
and I wish it were true!
But the situation's just
not that simple anymore.
If things continue
down this path,
it's only inevitable that
the Four Lands will revolt.
And if a war breaks out?
The Sennin infesting Yin
will take countless lives.
You know that we're already
on the brink of a war.
After everything
they've been through,
the people want a new emperor.
They need one.
So the least I can do is to
get rid of the Sennin in Yin
before the war erupts!
[BUNCHU] The people will be
sated once the true problem
is solved:
when Dakki's been defeated!
[TAIKOBO]
It's too late!
Emperor Chu has already
lost the trust of the people.
Can't you see that?
It's not too late!
Nothing will stop Yin
from regaining its glory!
[HIKO yells]
Hiko!
You okay?
[HIKO]
Look. Bunchu.
You can't deny that the Emperor
is under Dakki's control.
But you choose to
remain loyal to his title.
Is that really enough
to justify this for you?
The country you love
has been corrupted.
Protecting Yin now is only
helping to destroy it!
Bunchu. Please come with us.
[BUNCHU]
Silence! You miserable traitor!
[TAIKOBO choking]
[BUNCHU]
I'll finish you!
[TENKA]
Stop right there!
Leave them alone,
Grand Preceptor!
I don't wanna fight you,
but I can't let you do this!
Grand Preceptor.
I hope that you'll forgive
me for my involvement.
We just cannot afford to lose
Taikobo at a time like this.
If you guys get out of my
way, I can take him myself.
Don't worry, Master,
I'll protect you!
[BUNCHU] Ha! It doesn't matter
how many of you there are.
Speak of ideals all you like.
None of you actually have
the resolve to back them up!
[TENKA grunts]
Resolve requires strength,
and you're weak!
Wow.
Bunchu is like
a force of nature.
[BUNCHU]
Shisei, finish off the living.
Yes, sir!
Hold on!
[TAIKOBO]
No, not yet.
I'm surprised you can move.
[TAIKOBO]
Nobody's dying.
I won't let you kill them.
I won't!
[YOZEN]
Taikobo.
He's almost dead and
he's protecting us
with a wall of wind.
[YOZEN] Honestly,
you really do amaze me.
Now I know... you are
someone I can trust
with my heart.
[BUNCHU] He can't conjure
such a large whirlwind for long.
But still...
[TAIKOBO grunts]
You're finally awake!
You're alive!
[SUPUSHAN]
Oh, I'm so relieved!
I was so scared
you wouldn't wake up!
I don't know what
I would've done! [crying]
It's okay.
Thanks, guys.
[KI SHO]
So, Taikobo.
Yozen told me all about
your encounter with Bunchu.
I'm glad you managed to survive.
[TAIKOBO]
Bunchu.
He was fighting for Yin with
every single ounce of his being.
I can only guess that
something happened in his past
to make him so
fanatically loyal.
His conviction
goes beyond reason.
But I have to ask myself...
Why am I fighting?
[TAIKOBO]
For the Kyo? Against death?
Opression. Isolation.
[OLD MAN 5A]
Do you hate them, Lord Ryo Bo?
And do you hunger for revenge?
Well, don't even bother.
Trust me, it's not
worth the effort.
Unless you can somehow
change the whole world,
this will keep happening
until the end of time.
[TAIKOBO]
I will change it.
I'll make a world
safe for humans.
A world free of
Sennin and Doshi.
[TAIKOBO coughs]
[BUNCHU] You used your paopei
until you coughed up blood?
Taikobo.
[TAIKOBO grunts]
[BUNCHU] I can't let Seiki
have one as great as you.
I don't remember
anything after that.
I see.
You should know.
We have made the decision
to officially declare war
upon Choka.
[SHUKOTAN]
You may be unaware of this,
but one of the
Shisei attacked Seiki.
Many lives were lost.
[KI SHO] They unleashed
an atrocity on us,
and we can't overlook it.
Even if we chose
to remain silent
and just look the other way,
the people will not!
[HIKO]
Forgive the intrusion.
But we'd like to join you in
this fight, if you'll have us.
[KI SHO] Yes!
We welcome you with open arms!
--[HIKO] We're all yours.
--[RYUU KAN] Yeah!
[KOH MEI]
Whatever we can do to help.
[SHUU KI]
Just let us know!
[OHMA]
Master Bunchu.
Not to question you,
but why did you let them live?
I was repaying the debt we owe.
Those people in Seiki.
They wouldn't have lost their
lives if not for our actions,
and there's nothing we
can do to fully atone
for that sin.
I shouldn't have acted
on my own impulses.
[BUNCHU] What's done is done
and there's no taking it back.
I'd better return to Choka now.
I'm certain things
are about to get busy.
What would you have us do?
Well, Shisei.
The approaching war will
be even more ruthless.
There's no doubt I'll call
upon you again, so heal.
Right! Yes, sir!
[BUNCHU]
He fights for Seiki,
and I for Choka.
We travel down opposite paths,
yet both will be
fraught with peril.
We'll meet again soon.