[DAKKI]
It's been 600 years now.
That's when it all began.
I had the same comfy
setup I've got now.
I possessed the queen
at the time, Bakki,
and took my rightful place
living inside the palace.
[DAKKI gasps]
[DAKKI]
He also lived in the palace,
but that should
go without saying,
considering his status
in the government.
[DAKKI] He is the first
emperor of the Yin Dynasty,
Emperor Toh.
[DAKKI] So I decided that
I would make a similar plan
and run with it.
At long last... we finally meet.
[OHTENKUN chuckling]
[OHTENKUN] Oh, the absurd,
tragic irony of humanity.
Gyokutei got himself killed
and Yozen's deepest, darkest
secret has been exposed.
[OHTENKUN chuckling]
This is so damn funny,
my sides are splitting open.
He's lookin' pretty rough.
You'd better hope
that he survives this.
Just forget it, Supu.
We're leaving.
Seriously, Master?
We need to treat
Yozen's injuries.
Oh, right.
Yozen's one of
the strongest Doshi.
How can he be drained like this?
This is your work.
You did something
to him, didn't you?
Hey, I said I'd give him back,
but I never said that
he'd be unharmed.
Oh, c'mon.
I just played a little
trick on him, that's all.
You see that pattern on his neck
that looks like a wicked tattoo?
Well, it continuously
slams him with damage,
just as if I were attacking
him with my paopei.
You should be grateful
that I chose to let
your little "genius" live.
[TAIKOBO] I'm gonna make
you pay for this, Ohtenkun.
Mark my words.
Oh, don't get all
histrionic on me.
I've lost two of
my own guys, y'know.
We're even now.
[YOZEN]
Master...
[TAIITSU]
According to our intel,
all of Kingo Island is governed
from its control room,
located in the core.
Logically, we can safely
assume that's where Bunchu is.
Maybe you should
explain yourself, Taikobo!
Gyokutei's soul was
released to the Hoshindai
and Yozen's on
the verge of death!
[TAIKOBO]
Gyokutei--
He was determined
to save his pupil,
even knowing that he
was walking into a trap.
What happened was tragic,
but Yozen is back home
and being cared for now.
Should we tell them what
we found out about him?
Don't go there, Supu.
Let's leave the decision to
tell everyone up to Yozen.
[SUPUSHAN]
Of course.
Let's avenge them!
Damn straight!
[KOSEISHI] I say we all storm
Kingo Island immediately!
[JIKO]
Yeah!
There's no reason for
us to hold back now!
We must fight--
fight for Gyokutei Shinjin!
[ALL] We'll fight for
Gyokutei Shinjin!
[DOTOKU, JIKO]
Let's make 'em pay, Taikobo!
Slow down.
[JIKO]
Huh?
[ALL]
What?
[DOTOKU gasps]
We need to act swiftly!
We can't sit around and
waste time formulating plans!
I've dealt with the
Juttenkun's paopei
and it's like nothing we've
ever experienced before.
They use space itself
as a weapon.
What's that mean?
It's too risky.
If we all rush in there at once,
we could easily be pulled into
a dimension of their creation
and get wiped out
in one fell swoop.
So instead,
we should divide ourselves
up into several teams,
each one taking a different
root to infiltrate Kingo.
Wait, teams?
Supu! You know what to do!
I'm on it!
[NATAKU]
The hell is this?
[TAIITSU] Maybe he's
picking teams by lottery?
[NATAKU]
That's stupid.
All right!
Everybody, form a line.
[ALL]
Uh, yeah.
[TAIKOBO]
Each of you gets a single spin.
[ALL]
Right.
[ALL chattering]
What's gonna happen?
What're ya gonna get?
What're ya gonna get?!
[DOTOKU]
Hey, I got a blue one!
[ALL gasp, laugh]
[JIKO]
I got a yellow ball!
[BOTH] What color is it gonna
be? What color is it gonna be?
I can't wait to see what it is!
[ALL gasp, laugh]
Whoa! Don't spin it so hard!
You're gonna break
the thing! Ah!
[ALL laughing]
[DOTOKU]
Bull's eye!
Oh, what are you gonna get?
What color's it gonna be?
Let's see what it is. C'mon.
It's red! I got red!
Who else is red?
[DOKO]
Me! I've got red!
Yay! The three of us are
gonna make for a great team!
[KORYU]
Yeah. Let's do this.
[NATAKU]
I'm fine on my own.
[ALL chattering]
[TAIKOBO sighs]
Looks like we've got our teams.
'Kay. So I'm the
only one left to go.
Huh? It's purple.
[FUGEN] I guess that makes
the two of us a team, Bo.
Yeah?
[FUGEN chuckles]
Purple is too plain,
so let's be Team Mulberry.
Uh... yay.
[ALL]
All right! Let's do this!
[TAIKOBO]
Uh, hey, wait.
Let's have a do-over,
just this once!
Sorry, guys, but two
people doesn't exactly make
for that much of
a team, does it now?
Not really.
I suppose not.
I've got a rather
talented pupil named Igo
who's just on the verge of
finally coming into his own.
Would you like me to
send him with you?
Igo?
[DOKO]
Like I said, he's quite skilled,
but he's got some
problems with discipline.
You could help me out
and set him straight.
[YOZEN wheezing]
[TAIKOBO] Master, has Yozen
shown any improvement
since we returned?
[GENSHI]
Mm.
I'm having Unchushi give him a
thorough examination right now.
I have to say,
this is an interesting
experimental subject,
and by that, I mean an utterly
terrifying medical case.
From what I can ascertain,
this mark on his neck
was made by a paopei.
Really?
[UNCHUSHI]
Indeed.
It's a microscopic paopei
creature that resembles a mite
and attaches itself to
parasitically feed off
Sennin and Doshi.
It's remarkable, really.
This little beast?
Once it latches onto a host,
it drains you of your energy
until you're depleted
and the nonstop onslaught of
exhaustion finally kills you.
[TAIKOBO]
I see.
This thing itself is
actually Ohtenkun's paopei.
[GENSHI]
What can we do?
[UNCHUSHI]
I hate to tell you this, but...
...my prognosis is
that it's not possible
to surgically remove it.
It's already too deeply
embedded within him.
[YOZEN gasping]
Isn't there anything we can do?
[UNCHUSHI]
Medically, no,
but there is still
one way to save him...
...and that is...
[BOTH]
Go on.
Someone must kill the Sennin
who dispatched this paopei
in the first place.
[TAIKOBO gasps]
He should be on the
brink of death by now.
[HIKO]
Well, we're here. Now what?
[TENKA] I'd guess we should be
ready to fight before too long.
[VENUS] It'll happen soon
enough. Just remember--
the only enemies we really
need to concern ourselves with
are the Juttenkun, Bunchu,
and Tsuten Kyoshu himself.
The rest of Kingo's
inhabitants are no match
for our strength and skill.
[MADONNA screams]
--[gasps]
--[TENKA] What's wrong?
[VENUS]
No! Grab her!
[HIKO]
Grab who?
[crying]
[BOTH gasp]
[TENKA, HIKO]
Oh, crap, she jumped!
[VENUS, QUEEN]
Madonna!
[MADONNA yells]
What?
She's plummeting to her death
but she's still
stuffing her face?
Her priorities are
a little mixed up.
We've gotta save her!
We'll catch up with you!
[VENUS, QUEEN]
Madonna!
Well, that was dumb.
What d'ya think?
Should we follow them?
I guess.
It's not like we know
where we're going in here.
Yep.
[YOKAI screaming]
[TENKA] Whoa, she just sent a
lotta souls to the Hoshindai.
[VENUS]
Hang on!
[VENUS, QUEEN]
Madonna!
[TENKA]
Oh, man.
Is she gonna fall through
the entire island?
[YOKAI growling]
[TENKA]
Not good!
[HIKO]
It's a nest of yokai !
[YOKAI yelling]
[BOTH gasp]
[YOPIG]
Are they humans?
[YOBIRD]
They smell like humans.
The Juttenkun ordered us
to sit this fight out,
but screw that,
I say we get 'em!
[YOKAI yelling]
[YOKAI 11A gasps]
The weaker ones
are playin' it smart.
[YOKAI gasping]
[chiming]
Hm?
[HIKO]
An octagon.
[TOTENKUN] All right,
everyone, stand aside.
Their actions here demand a
fair yet righteous judgment...
...and I, Totenkun, shall judge!
[BOTH yelling]
[TENKA]
What the hell is going on?!
[BOTH grunting]
[TENKA]
What's with this place?!
Did we get sucked inside
some kind of tornado?!
Tenka!
Grab my hand so we
don't get separated!
[TENKA grunts]
[HIKO]
It's pulling us in!
[TENKA yells]
--[YOKAI chattering]
--[YOPIG] They... They vanished.
[YOBIRD]
Uh-huh.
[YOPIG] We didn't even get
to take our turn fighting
before that thing sucked 'em in.
Yeah.
Ya saw the mark so we
know who's behind this.
Damn Juttenkun.
[YOBIRD] They say no one
ever gets outta there,
so we'll never get
our revenge on 'em.
[YOKAI 11B whimpers]
Stay away from it.
[YOKAI whimpering]
I'm sick of the Juttenkun
bossin' us around!
The hell do they think they
are, snatchin' our prey away?
I'm jumpin' in there after them!
Yeah, I'm goin' in with you!
No, don't do it, you idiots!
--[YOPIG squeals]
--[YOBIRD screches]
[YOKAI 11B]
I'm goin' in, too!
[YOBUNNY yells]
[YOKAI 11C] Guess we're
never gonna see them again.
[TENKA]
What the hell?
Shouldn't we have
gotten pulled into
the eye of this thing by now?
[YOPIG]
There they are!
[BOTH gasp]
[YOPIG] We're gonna
make you humans suffer!
Hurry up and close the distance!
[YOBIRD]
Yeah!
[YOPIG]
Swim! Swim! Swim! Swim!
[HIKO]
Are they serious?
[TENKA] You guys have got
some real freakin' tenacity!
[gasps]
[TENKA]
Look! You see that?
Hey, Dad! Grab onto my back!
[gasps]
[HIKO grunts]
[TENKA grunting]
[HIKO]
Hey! Are you okay?
[TENKA]
I think so.
--[TENKA gasps]
--[HIKO] Whoa!
[TENKA grunts, sighs]
[YOKAI yelling]
[YOPIG] Get ready to part ways
with your souls, humans!
[ALL]
Uh...
[YOPIG gasps] Go back,
go back! Swim the other way!
--[YOKAI panting]
--Swim! Swim!
[YOBUNNY]
It's sucking us in!
[HIKO gasps]
[YOKAI gasping]
[HIKO] Looks like there's
something down there.
[YOPIG panting]
Oh, there's a safety net!
Wait...
[YOBIRD yelling]
[HIKO]
Uck.
[YOBUNNY screams]
[TENKA]
Well that's brutal.
--[VOICE 11A chanting]
--[BOTH] Huh?
[TOTENKUN]
Damn fools.
[TENKA grunts, gasps]
[TOTENKUN] To enter Totenkun's
Fukojin means inescapable death,
and that goes for anyone
who steps within.
There's no choice but to
surrender yourself to the wind
and be sliced into
chunks by the netting
made from a paopei alloy below.
You see him, Dad?
There's our enemy.
That's one big bug.
[TOTENKUN]
I'm not an insect.
Sure.
[TENKA]
Insect or not,
he's clearly the one we're
gonna have to stomp on
if we wanna get
outta here alive.
[TENKA grunts]
[TENKA]
Hang on.
I'm gonna get us close.
[TENKA grunts]
[TENKA]
Up we go!
There!
[TENKA groaning]
So heavy.
It's stupid how
giant you are, Dad.
[HIKO] Hey, you better not be
calling your father stupid!
Sorry, not how I meant it.
We're getting closer, though!
[TOTENKUN]
Let's bring the wind up a notch.
Eighty meters per second.
[TENKA yells]
[HIKO groans]
[BOTH yelling]
[yells, gasps]
[TENKA]
I'm sorry, Dad!
[HIKO yells]
[HITO screaming]
Ouch!
[HIKO sighs]
Looks like we're safe for now.
Hey, Hito, you alive down there?
You haven't talked in ages
so I kind've already
thought you were dead.
Have you ever considered how
abusive this relationship is?!
--[HIKO grunts]
--[HITO gasping]
[screams]
Stop doing that!
you're gonna kill me!
[HIKO]
It's you or us!
Wow, Dad, that's messed up.
How about all three of
us make it out alive?
Go, Karyuho!
[TOTENKUN]
Better raise the wind speed.
One hundred meters per second.
--[HIKO gasps]
--[TENKA] Aw, man!
[screams]
The heat is rising!
It burns, it burns!
Shut up with your
whining, already!
[sighs] I'm not letting us
get cubed like a steak!
Damn it.
That creepy cockroach won't
even bother to look down here.
He's doing all
he can to mock us.
Wait! That's it!
Hey, Dad.
[HIKO]
Huh?
Listen close. I know what to do.
Whisper, whisper, whisper.
[HIKO gasps]
Sounds like a plan.
Hey, Hito, I need
you to lift us up
to the very bottom
of the pillar.
[HITO]
Huh?
If we don't do this,
you'll die right along with us.
Well, damn it all.
Here we go!
[HITO grunts]
--[HIKO grunts]
--[TENKA gasps]
[TENKA]
It's stretching!
[HITO]
That close enough?
Just as I thought!
The spot directly
beneath the pillar
functions like the
eye of the storm.
The force of the wind
is weaker here
so our attacks might
actually reach him now.
Throw everything you've
got at that dung beetle!
[TOTENKUN]
Hmph. Idiots.
[TENKA chuckles]
[TOTENKUN] All you've done is
run out of weapons to use on me.
Just give up and accept
your slice and dice death.
There's no escaping a wind
speed of 120 meters pe--
[HIKO, TENKA laugh]
I doubt you can see it,
since you only seem
capable of looking up,
but have you even
bothered to wonder
what happened to
the other Karyuho?
[TOTENKUN]
What?
[TOTENKUN grunting]
[TOTENKUN]
Too hot.
[TOTENKUN groans, gasps]
[TENKA] The Juttenkun
dismiss humans as nothing
but small and insignificant
pests compared to them,
but look what happens
when you're too arrogant
to even bother glancing down.
[sighs]
So you're saying the
only way to save him
is to defeat Ohtenkun.
[GENSHI] Hm... And
there's no other option?
[UNCHUSHI]
We can extend his lifespan
and relieve some
of his symptoms.
[GENSHI]
Hm?
[UNCHUSHI] This Sento
extract should allow him
to regain a little bit
of strength, at least.
That's helpful, but
it still won't solve
the root of the problem.
I'm afraid the only real
choice left before us
is to kill Ohtenkun.
[UNCHUSHI]
Here ya go. Down the hatch.
Such a truly remarkabale--uh,
no, I mean terrifying paopei.
To think that it grows by
absorbing its host's strength,
literally stealing their life.
To be frank, it's
practically a miracle
he's even still alive right now.
When you think of its latent
potential, it boggles the mind.
[TAIKOBO]
It's worrisome.
But if I'm gonna win this one
for all of us on Kongrong,
I need to concentrate
on the battle ahead.
You take good care
of Yozen, okay?
You know I will.
[TAIKOBO]
Now then.
Master, we've split our
elite force into teams
to strike the enemy's core.
This battle...
I've got a feeling
that it's not gonna end
until more fighters have fallen.
I'm sorry that I've asked you
to carry such heavy burdens
time and time again.
Don't be.
I'm doing this because I know
it's the right thing to do.
So long.
[HAKUTSURU] Just when you think
he can't get any stronger,
he defies expectations.
Losing Gyokutei Shinjin...
It must've been incredibly
painful for him.
[GENSHI] Mm. He's given
all of himself to fight
for a human world free
of Sennin and Doshi.
To achieve it, he's prepared
to lose his own home--
to sacrifice the Sennin world.
His devotion to
such a just cause
is wholehearted and selfless.
It will be painful, but until
he's achieved his ultimate goal,
he knows that he can only move
forward without looking back.
[TAIKOBO]
No matter what,
even if it means the destruction
of the Sennin world...
...I will give humanity
the world it deserves--
one safe from Sennin and Doshi.
[TAIKOBO]
Listen up, guys.
We're dividing into
six teams, A through F.
And we're going guerilla here.
This plan will still give
the enemy the upper hand
in several aspects.
Do not try to engage the
Juttenkun in one-on-one combat.
We'll take them out one
at a time with our teams.
[SENNIN 11A]
Seriously?
[SENNIN 11B]
That's fightin' dirty!
[SENNIN 11C]
No kidding!
Proceed with caution!
Team A rules!
[OHTENKUN]
Now pay attention.
The Kongrong Sennin are
bound to be charging in here
at any minute.
You are to kill every
last one of them,
even if it means
risking your own lives.
You got that?
And those left
standing in the end--
they'll be the ones tasked
with finally defeating Bunchu,
taking down Tsuten Kyoshu,
and destroying
all of Kingo Island.
Right, Bo? That's the plan?
Lady Koshu.
The Twelve Sennin themselves
are about to step forward
and join the battle.
[KOSHU] This war will be
the first and last great war
of the Sennin world.
It will be fierce.
Our tactic is to offer
support from the rear.
This will allow them
to freely advance.
[KOSHU]
Although...
...I can't help but worry
over how many of them
will actually make it out alive.
[KOSHU]
I can only pray--
pray that they will all be
fortunate enough to return.