[TAIKOBO grunts]
[BUNCHU grunts]
[TAIKOBO]
Chi!
Bunchu!
You and the Yin have
both grown decrepit!
The human world
needs a young wind.
That's its only hope.
So it's time for you to go!
[BUNCHU] If that's what you
believe, you're delusional!
I won't hand over the human
world to such a myopic brat!
You're just a naïve child!
[TAIKOBO yells]
[TAIKOBO]
Not good.
I'm almost out of
strength at this point!
Although, the same goes for him.
All right.
No matter what it costs me,
and no matter what I must do,
I have no option here
but to prevail!
Now, Bunchu! Let's finish this!
Fine with me.
Bring it, Taikobo!
[TAIKOBO]
Hello, Master Genshi Tenson.
Your number one pupil,
Taikobo, has arrived.
[GENSHI] Hmm. And how is my
top pupil's training going?
Oh. Uh, y'know,
it's going great.
[GENSHI]
Don't lie to me, you fool!
[TAIKOBO yells]
[GENSHI] You only pretend
to meditate, while in truth,
you're actually just sleeping!
There's no deceiving
these eyes of mine.
You're blessed with the rare
bone structure of a Sennin,
but you choose to goof off
instead of properly training.
With all due respect, Master.
I don't see the point in
training if we don't use it.
Dakki and her minions are
down there terrorizing
the human world.
And all we ever do is just
sit up here in the heavens
and train like there's nothing
we can be bothered with.
It's too depressing to train.
So I'd rather sleep
than worry about it.
[GENSHI]
You better not!
It has become more than
apparent that you are not suited
for our traditional
form of training.
[TAIKOBO]
What's with the scroll?
[GENSHI]
This scroll is the Hoshin List.
I have no intention of
letting Dakki and her minions
continue to wreak havoc
over the human world.
Some years ago,
we three Great Sennin
deliberated over a solution.
Of course, we must
certainly banish them
from the Human World,
but we must not allow them
to return to the
Sennin world either.
Our solution...
We created the world
of gods, a new dimension
between the Sennin
and human worlds.
And it is there that
we will seal them away.
That list contains the
names of those who must be
imprisoned there.
There are 365 Sennin on that
list and it is your duty
to defeat them all!
Wait!
Sennin and Doshi are forbidden
to take the life of another!
[HAKUTSURU] You won't be
doing any killing, Taikobo.
Please, give us some credit.
Take a look over there.
The tower you see before
you is called the Hoshindai.
Once an evil Sennin has been
defeated in the human world,
their souls are magnetically
drawn to the Hoshindai
and then immediately
trapped within.
Uh... How did I never
notice that before?
[GENSHI] If it were enough
for us to simply overthrow
and banish Dakki, we would
mount all of our forces
against her.
But if such a powerful
ruler were to be lost,
the humans would rebel
against the controlling Yin
and the world would
be thrown into chaos.
The chance for such calamity
must be avoided at any cost.
In other words, we'll need
to provide some stability
after Dakki's defeated.
[GENSHI]
Precisely.
To prevent the pervasive
spread of pandemonium,
we'll need to establish a
new king in the human world.
The most aptly suited candidate
would have to be Kisho,
the Seihakuko.
But for Kisho to become king,
he will have to be
the one to defeat Dakki.
So you are to use your
knowledge to move forward
with the Hoshin Project
while ensuring that Kisho
achieves this goal.
And if you refuse...
...you will choose expulsion!
Wait, you'll kick me out?!
[HAKUTSURU] Do you think
Taikobo will accept the mission?
[GENSHI]
Yes. I'm certain that he will.
[HAKUTSURU]
Oh?
[GENSHI] He has his own
personal stake in the matter.
[VOICE 1A]
It was a ruthless manhunt.
[VOICE 1B] They said they
needed to bury the villagers
with the slain emperor
to be his attendants.
[VOICE 1A] They normally
only need five or six.
Why would they murder hundreds?
[VOICE 1C] It was the selfish
demand of the evil empress.
[TAIKOBO]
The Yin empress. She did this.
[GENSHI] The empress of the
Yin is an immortal Sennyo
who once lived in
the Sennin world
and now manipulates
mankind with the power
of her beguiling beauty.
[TAIKOBO]
Unbelievable!
[GENSHI] She descended to
the human world centuries ago
and has lived in the
Imperial palace ever since.
By changing her
name and appearance,
she has deceived
generations of emperors
while indulging in a life
of decadent profligacy.
[DAKKI] The death of our beloved
emperor demands extravagance.
He deserves hundreds of
attendants in the afterlife,
not just five.
We don't want the people
of Yin to rebel against us,
of course, so round
them up from other tribes.
Yes, Miss.
[GENSHI] Dakki seems
to have recently acquired
a dangerous new spell.
Such wicked power attained
through mere beauty
cannot be allowed to continue.
My name is Genshi,
and I have come to summon you.
It is your fate
to become a Sennin.
[TAIKOBO]
A Sennin?
My mother, father, brother,
and my little sister...
The empress killed them all!
If I become a Sennin, can I
punish her for her crimes?
[TAIKOBO]
I've made up my mind, Master.
I'll undertake
the Hoshin Project.
[GENSHI]
Good to hear.
In that case, you deserve
to carry this with you.
A paopei that
manipulates the air.
It's called Dashinben.
A paopei?
I've always wanted a
power amplifying weapon.
And now I've got one!
[GENSHI] And one more thing
to help you on your way.
[HAKUTSURU] This is Supushan,
your spirit beast.
He'll take you
wherever you need to go.
Really?
Hey, it's Taikobo, right?
As he said, my name's Supushan.
It's very nice to meet ya.
You too, buddy!
The Hoshin Project, huh?
Well that's good for a laugh.
I rule over more than
300 slavishly loyal
Sennin and Doshi,
and some novice Doshi
thinks he can overthrow me?
They don't seem to have
thought out this plan.
After all, the extent of your
power is only second to mine.
So, how will you handle him?
I've spent hundreds
of years perfecting
my Temptation spell and thus
obtained the highest status.
Why should I waste
my time entertaining
the ambitions of
one meager Doshi?
I can appreciate your disregard,
but I'd still like to give this
a go and test out his powers
just to be on the
safe side of things.
Lady Dakki just ordered
you to ignore him!
Do you intend to disobey her?
I am here as Lady Dakki's
guest, not a servant.
I warn you not to make
that mistake again.
He speaks the truth!
Well, while we're
on the subject,
I think I'll go ahead and
take my shot at Taikobo.
I'm itching to try out my
Raikoben here, after all.
[TAIKOBO] How much longer until
we reach the capital, Supu?
Still quite a ways.
This country's pretty
huge, y'know.
[TAIKOBO]
Hey, look.
There's a shepherd down there.
[TAIKOBO]
A nomad roaming the west.
He must be of the Kyo people.
Poor guy's clothes
are in tatters.
I'm kinda curious, Master.
Have you taken the time to
look over the Hoshin list yet?
Jeez. No.
Better read it before
we reach Choka.
[SUPUSHAN]
Not a bad idea.
[TAIKOBO]
First name up... Shinkohyo.
What? Did you say Shinkohyo?
This is bad!
They say he's stronger than the
Three Great Sennin combined!
He's the strongest Doshi, rides
the strongest spirit beast,
and he's even got Raikoben,
the strongest paopei!
What? Hold on!
They can't expect me
to fight him!
[SUPUSHAN]
Then don't do it!
Why wake up a
sleeping dog to kill you?
[TAIKOBO] Does this list go
from strongest to weakest
or something?
That's gotta be it, yeah,
let's see who's at the end.
[TAIKOBO yells]
You must be Taikobo.
It's a pleasure to
meet you, truly.
I'm Shinkohyo, an imperial
guest of the empress.
[TAIKOBO]
Speak of the devil.
[SUPUSHAN]
Master Shinkohyo!
How can a person
of your great stature
align himself with Dakki?
[KOKUTENKO screeches]
Now, now, Kokutenko, calm down.
It's not nice to make
murderous threats.
Despite how it appears,
I haven't taken anyone's side.
I only reside in the palace
due to my chronic predilection
for luxury and comfort.
Oh, great,
so you're not my enemy!
See ya!
[SHINKOHYO]
Don't leave! Wait!
My name has gotta be
on that list of yours, right?
So doesn't that mean you
have to defeat me in battle?
Listen, Shinkohyo.
There's something
you should hear.
Uh... Sure, what is it?
That outfit's tacky.
Where's your sense of style?
[SHINKOHYO]
Oh, Taikobo.
You've just dug your own grave.
Insulting my finely
cultivated sense of taste
is an open declaration of war!
It's not fair! Why me?
Why'd I have to get teamed up
with this
big-mouthed idiot Doshi?
[SHINKOHYO]
Raikoben!
No! I'm gonna dodge it!
Stay put and close
your eyes, Supu!
Oh, that's the Raikoben!
[DAKKI SERVANT 1A]
Shinkohyo caused that?
[DAKKI]
Indeed he did.
You don't want to
get on his bad side,
but you couldn't ask
for a better ally.
The Sennin world won't attack
me as long as they fear him.
Believe it or not, I was
holding back on that one.
Scan the area, Kokutenko.
Let's see how Taikobo
fared in that encounter.
Use your clairvoyance
if you wouldn't mind.
[KOKUTENKO] Looks like
he fell to the earth with some
serious injuries.
He only managed to
avoid a painful death
by using his paopei
to distort the lightning.
Thank goodness
he's still alive.
Excellent news.
In the 5,000 years
of my existence,
this is the very first time
I've seen my own blood.
Taikobo's proven himself a
rival deserving of my attention.
He knew there was
a Kyo village behind him
and therefore chose
not to dodge.
Not only did he protect it,
he still managed
to strike back at me.
It would be a waste
to kill such a worthy Doshi.
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
We're still alive!
I was too careless back there.
I can't drop my guard
like that in the future.
Wait, is that--?
[SUPUSHAN] The tomb of
the Yin royal family.
Then my clan is buried
there, along with my family.
Please rest in peace.
Sennin and Doshi treat this
world like their plaything,
and people are
suffering because of it.
I swear I'll create
a safer world.
One free of such monsters.
Well, Supu, let's get moving.
Roger, Master!
[BOY 1A]
'Scuse me, sir, comin' through.
The slaves of this city are fed
the same food as the dogs
while working as hard as ants.
Until they die from exhaustion.
We've arrived at Kinjo,
the enemy's palace.
Uh, Master...
Can we maybe
reconsider this plan?
Why not start small instead
of going straight for Dakki?
It's because
many of the people on this list
are under the sway
of Dakki's magic,
serving her against
their own will.
So if we defeat Dakki first,
we won't have to worry
about her underlings.
Yeah, I get it. Very cunning.
And I'm sure you have
an equally cunning plan
of attack, don't you?
Yup! And the first step is to
kidnap the Yin emperor, Chu.
What?!
[TAIKOBO gasps]
Looks like I've
stumbled upon a Sennin.
Yeah? And who's
doing the stumbling?
I'm Koh Hiko, the emperor's
military strategist.
Also known as the Buseioh.
Are you on your way
to see the empress?
Yes, I am.
And for what, exactly?
I intend to defeat her.
Shut up, don't just
tell anyone that!
[HIKO laughs]
Hey, sorry, man!
Most of the guys who
come through here
just wanna join up
to be her henchmen.
Now if you were
one of them, well,
I would've had to kill ya.
Are you saying
that you're not under the thrall
of Dakki's temptation spell?
You're damn right I'm not.
I repelled her sorcery with
the sheer strength of my will.
So I guess she really
is a Sennyo then, huh?
[TAIKOBO]
Afraid so.
Well then, who are you?
I'm a Doshi from
Kongrong Mountain.
Name's Taikobo.
[HIKO] I wish I could offer
to assist you in your task,
but if I don't do my job,
the nation will crumble.
This may be hard to believe,
but there was a time
when Emperor Chu
was an amazing man and leader.
We of the Koh clan
have loyally served
the Yin Dynasty for generations.
It sickens me to watch
her feed off its ruin.
Well, you come find me
if you run into any trouble.
I'll do what I can to help.
Tell ya what.
I'll pull some strings
and set up an appointment
for you to meet
with the empress.
Wow, thank you, Hiko.
That's great!
[HIKO]
Later, then.
Hmm. I dunno.
You sure we can trust this guy?
Yeah, I think we can.
He strikes me as a man
of great character.
Supu, what's wrong with you?
I didn't expect her
to be this beautiful.
I'd wake up from death just
to catch a glimpse of her!
[TAIKOBO]
Seriously?!
Hiko recommended you to us.
He said that you wish
to work for the palace?
Yes, your highness.
Well, Dakki. What do you think?
[DAKKI] Sounds like a
splendid idea to me!
So tell me.
Did you have any particular
work in mind, Taikobo?
If possible, I'd like
to be a court musician.
I believe that
could be arranged.
[TAIKOBO]
By the way, Emperor Chu.
If you need me to
prove my credentials,
I'm holding a grand party
tomorrow in the western capital
of Shugen, with over
300 beautiful women.
Really? Count me in!
But won't it take us
several days to travel
all the way to Shugen from here?
[TAIKOBO]
For most it may,
but it's no more than a quick
leap with my Supushan.
[CHU]
Brilliant!
I didn't consider
your flying beast.
[TAIKOBO]
Here, hop on behind me.
Consider me your personal
chauffeur for the next few days.
[DAKKI] Oh, that does sound
like fun, I'd love to go!
My, you look awfully
nervous all of a sudden.
Oh, no, please don't tell me.
This party's nothing
but a clever ruse
and you're plotting to kidnap
Emperor Chu, aren't you?
What? Seize him!
[TAIKOBO]
C'mon, Supu!
Oh, no. Dakki's Temptation!
Good boy.
Please, no...
I just can't resist.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Supu...
[GUARD 1A]
Go on and take a look.
[SNAKE 1A hisses]
[DAKKI chuckles]
Behold the Taibon!
He's still under her spell.
[DAKKI] Let's kick things off
by executing these poor devils.
Empress, wait.
Who are these people?
Oh, just a bunch of Kyo
we were using as slaves.
Taikobo here hails
from the Kyo clan.
Which means I can't
trust any of them.
So into the Taibon they go!
Stop it, Dakki!
I'm the only one who
should be punished here!
[DAKKI]
Not listening!
Sorry, but I'm ready to get
this Taibon party started!
Go, run for your lives!
Don't pretend that you care.
It's your fault!
You picked a fight with them
and you're completely powerless.
What'd you think
was gonna happen?
There's no way
I'm dyin' like this!
I say we fight back!
[SLAVES chattering]
[SLAVES yelling]
[GUARD 1C yelling]
[GUARDS yelling]
[HIKO]
Now's my chance!
[DAKKI]
Don't you get any funny ideas.
Surely you haven't forgotten
that your little sister
is my captive, have you?
[SLAVES yelling]
[HIKO] I threw your clothes in
the snake pit when we escaped.
Far as they know, you're dead.
She massacred all
of those innocent Kyo.
Why did you save my life?
Those people are dead
because of my mistake.
[HIKO]
Listen, Taikobo.
I had this feeling
when I met you
that you can actually
do some good.
I didn't rescue
you for your sake.
I saved your life for
the sake of this world.
You need to stay alive.
There's no room for weakness.
Then I'll have to remain strong.
[TAIKOBO]
I've already lost so much
in such a small
amount of time.
[TAIKOBO]
Oh, nice!
I caught a big one!
It's a speckled trout.
[FUGEN]
C'mon, Bo.
You shouldn't catch fish
when you're not even allowed
to eat them.
Yeah, I know that!
Here, look!
Catch and release!
Actually...
I've got a gift for you.
It's a fishing hook
of my own design.
What?
That won't catch anything!
You only go fishing when
you need to clear your mind.
It helps you think, right?
Don't you feel bad hurting
the fish just so you can focus?
Seems a little unfair.
You'll do just about anything
to avoid conflict, huh?
I could say the same
for you, y'know.
Although...
I can't shake the feeling
you'll devote yourself
to combat someday.
You do have a shining blade
deep inside your heart,
after all.
But when that day comes,
I promise I'll be
right beside you.
The least I can do
is offer you that.
[TAIKOBO] Fugen, you were
right about everything,
but I don't want to hurt anyone.
I wish I could create a
safe world without fighting.
But is it even
possible to avoid it?
[SHINKOHYO]
You've disappointed me.
[SHINKOHYO] Must you insist
on smiling in that way?
I find it quite disturbing.
Kokutenko!
[KOKUTENKO]
Coming!
[TAIKOBO gasps]
This little kindness
of mine puts you in my debt.
And I'm expecting plenty
of amusement from you
before I call things even.
[KOKUTENKO]
Meow!
What's happening? Where are we?
You're up.
So we better get moving.
I did a lot of thinking
while you were sleeping off
Dakki's spell.
There's no way I can
defeat her on my own.
So it's time to
find some allies.
[SUPUSHAN]
Partners?
Exactly.
We'll gather up enough new
friends for our own army!
[BUNCHU] Just how many years
have we been here now?
[KOKUKIRIN]
I don't understand.
You could easily quell
a backwoods rebellion
with your paopei.
Why not get it over with,
Master Bunchu?
[BUNCHU]
Well, Kokukirin.
When fighting humans,
it's only proper to face them
as human. However...
It's a different matter
when you're facing
Sennin and Doshi.
As long as there's
life in my body,
no man or god will bring harm
to Emperor Chu or the Yin.