[CHU]
Bunchu...
[panting]
[BUNCHU]
Your Majesty!
What are you doing
without an attendant?
Hold on.
You're pale and trembling.
What's wrong?
Don't know what it is.
It's like my body's...
fighting me...
[CHU grunting]
[BUNCHU gasps]
[CHU grunts, yells]
[BUNCHU]
Majesty.
This must be Dakki.
What the hell has
she done to you?
[CHU]
Please stay by my side, Bunchu.
Don't leave me.
I'm frightened.
Please don't leave me alone.
I feel like all my limbs
are about to fall off.
[DAKKI chuckles]
Evil witch.
[SHUKO TAN] He's still
scarred from all those years
Dakki held him captive.
Since then, he rarely
eats a meal large enough
to keep even a bird alive.
He's a good man.
A while back,
before you were even born,
I witnessed his
kindness firsthand.
Must've been a few
decades ago by now.
[HAKUTSURU] I can't believe
I let you talk me into
sneaking away!
We'll get in so
much trouble for this!
Oh, we're just sightseeing.
And you were pretty quick
to say yes when I offered you
three Sento!
[HAKUTSURU] Ugh, I know,
but it's not worth it.
I didn't realize you were
gonna make me fly all over
this entire country.
[TAIKOBO]
Are they...?
They're Kyo!
Lord Ki Sho, they appear to
be Kyo refugees fleeing Choka.
Open the gates
and allow them inside.
[GUARD 6A] My Lord, just
think of the amount of food
it will take to feed them all.
[KI SHO]
We cannot simply abandon them.
The Kyo face
discrimination in Choka,
whereas Seiki is
built upon compassion.
Feed them from
the castle surplus.
Well, Hakuyuko.
Starting tomorrow,
we won't have as much food
as we're used to,
but we must stay strong.
[HAKUYUKO chuckles]
[TAIKOBO] I've watched this
empire for a very long time.
And I've yet to find a man
who could compare to Ki Sho.
[SHUKO TAN] My father's
just the man you say.
Snacks and sweets were a
luxury I could only dream of
as a child.
It made me so mad.
Taikobo.
I think you should meet
my father's second son.
What's his name?
It's Ki Hatsu.
When my father passes away,
he will take the throne.
I'd like to hear your
estimation of him.
Whether he's worthy
of the honor.
[TAIKOBO] Does he actually
expect me to find his brother
based on this?
I hope the guy doesn't really
look like this, for his sake.
[WOMAN 6A gasps]
[KI HATSU laughing]
Don't run from me!
Hey, c'mon, wait up!
[WOMAN 6A]
Can't you take a hint?
You're nowhere even
close to my type!
That's okay, I can change!
Just tell me your type--
anything you want!
--[WOMAN 6A yells]
--[KI HATSU laughs]
[WOMAN 6A] You creep!
Jerk! Slime! Pervert!
I've got a shot.
He seems to be good with people.
You happen to know this guy?
Why you wanna know? You a friend
of Ki Hatsu's or somethin'?
Lucky for you,
just saw him in that café.
Later.
[TAIKOBO]
Oh, guess he means that place.
[BUKICHI]
Master! Wait for me!
[TAIKOBO] Hey, what're
you guys doing here?
We heard you're lookin'
for Lord Ki Hatsu
and I'm here to help ya out!
I've seen him up close so I--
Oh, wait, this guy here.
Well that was easy.
Thanks a lot, jackass.
Way to rat me out.
[TAIKOBO]
What? Seriously?
That's Ki Hatsu?
Tell me, Taikobo.
Will you remain
here when I'm gone?
Help build a safer
country for our people?
[TAIKOBO]
Mm-hmm.
I'm very glad.
Hatsu.
I'm here, Father. What is it?
My work is done.
I've fulfilled my
duties to Seiki.
Our people need a
strong and stable wind
to guide them forward.
I know you can be that for them.
[KI HATSU]
Of course.
I swear that I'll
honor your vision.
I want you to place
your trust in Taikobo
just as you have in me.
I believe in my heart that he
will lead Seiki down a path
towards a beautiful,
peaceful future for everyone.
How awful it is--
knowing there's nothing left
for one to do in this life.
[HAKUYUKO]
Father.
[KI SHO]
Hakuyuko.
As a man who died
with many regrets,
I can't help but envy you.
Yes, my son.
The life I've lived...
It has been truly blessed.
[HIKO]
No wind.
Not a cloud in the sky.
Such peaceful and quiet weather.
An almost deafening silence.
[TAIKOBO]
Ki Hatsu. There you are.
[KI HATSU] I'm not in
the mood to talk right now.
Well, then try to fake it.
You are about to be an
incredibly busy man.
My father just died, so I
need time to grieve, okay?
[SHUKO TAN]
Brother, Listen.
[KI HATSU]
Tan.
As our father wished, you
will now become our ruler.
Lord of the western lands.
This is the first step
to defeat the Yin Dynasty.
What?!
Really?!
An entire country
awaits your leadership.
This is hardly a time for
anguished introspection.
Now guide us.
What the hell's wrong
with you people?!
My father dies and you
expect me to just move on?
I know how hard it is.
But everyone in this country
is grieving for your father.
And he knew you have the
strength to comfort them.
The wind.
Our people need a
strong and stable wind
to guide them forward.
I know you can be that for them.
[TAIKOBO]
Ki Hatsu.
Let's go.
Time for us to defeat Yin.
[TAIKOBO]
Listen closely.
You've got 10,000
citizens out there.
And they've all shown up
to hear what you have to say.
So stick to the script
and you'll be fine.
[CROWD cheering]
[KI HATSU]
Yeah, so uh, listen.
Uh...
War is an awful thing.
It's not good at all.
The hell's he doing?
Is he just gonna completely
ignore my speech?
[KI HATSU]
I really believe that,
but I'm still gonna
wage war on Yin.
Because I refuse to lie down and
let them abuse us any longer!
I can only ask,
please trust that I'll do
what's right for you
as your leader.
I'm not gonna pretend
I'm as resourceful
as my father or Hakuyuko,
but together we can win this!
[CROWD cheering]
[SHUKO TAN] He may not be an
expert wordsmith, but...
I know he'll ensure father's
wishes are fulfilled.
I've been meaning
to speak with you.
The Sennin of Kingo pose
far too great of a threat.
Their recent attack has taken
a toll on the people of Shu.
If we're going to be
senselessly killed anyway...
...then we're prepared to
die to defeat our enemies.
Dakki, Bunchu, and even
Tsuten, the ruler of Kingo.
Of course.
It's always been a part of
my plan to request the help
of you humans, but I
can only ask so much.
And I won't let you
fight Sennin on my watch.
Humans fight humans
and that's it.
I'd rather not risk any more
casualties than we have to.
Maybe this is just
my pride talking,
but I don't wanna lose
in order to win.
Here's some reassurance for you.
Kongrong Mountain is about
to jump into the fight.
[CROWD cheering]
Lady Dakki!
You're the best!
--[cheering]
--[MEN] Lady Dakki!
Your attention, please.
Our poor, sick Emperor has
asked me to speak on his behalf.
The craven Shu are
planning to invade
and attack our beloved Choka!
[CROWD chattering]
Oh, I don't know what to do!
Will you help me?
[CROWD cheering]
[BUNCHU]
Hey, witch!
What the hell did you
do to the Emperor?
And what's more...
How dare you try to send
the people of Choka to war.
Aww, cheer up,
mister grumpy boots.
Just look how amped up
they are for some bloodshed.
There's nothing wrong
with pulling their strings
if they want to be puppets.
And besides, I'm just playing
the same game as Taikobo.
The same game?
Everything Taikobo's done
has been out of concern
for the humans' lives.
You just want to
see them go to war
for your entertainment!
Uh-huh...
So that's why I'm doing it.
[GENSHI] I'm worried the
Juttenkun will no longer
remain idle.
Wouldn't it be best
for you to strike first
and storm Kingo Island?
'Fraid not.
But I'm thinking about making
a deal with Tsuten Kyoshu.
[GENSHI]
Hm?
[GENSHI, SUPUSHAN]
You what, now?!
One of the primary goals of
the Hoshin Project was this.
To create a safer
world for the humans
by getting rid of Dakki.
Defeating Kingo Island
wasn't part of the plan.
With that said...
I'll be making a trip there
to extend an olive branch.
[BUNCHU] It's been quite a
while since I've been inside
Kingo Island.
Ohtenkun.
I want you and the
Juttenkun to assist me.
That sounded more like a
demand instead of a request.
Have you forgotten
that we Juttenkun
are far greater Sennin
than you could ever be?
The war against Seiki
and all of the Shu
people will soon begin.
Before it does,
the Juttenkun will help me
to bring down Kongrong Mountain.
This act alone will force
the Shu to surrender.
Sounds like a pretty
roundabout plan to me.
[BUNCHU] It's the only real
way to minimize the loss
of human life.
Fine, we're on board.
We're not exactly thrilled
with the Kongrong gang's
plotting and scheming anyway.
I wish to speak with Kyoshu.
You should join me.
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[BUNCHU]
And Ohtenkun?
Yeah?
Do me a favor and keep
your shallow wit to yourself.
Whatever do you mean?
Lord Tsuten Kyoshu.
It's Bunchu.
May I come in?
[BUNCHU]
Lord Tsuten Kyoshu.
I intend to subjugate
Kongrong Mountain.
The Juttenkun will
aid in this endeavor.
I'd like to hear your
thoughts on the matter.
[TSUTEN]
Bunchu.
My Lord?
[TSUTEN] I grant you full
authority in this quest.
I order you and the Juttenkun to
strike down Kongrong Mountain.
Then I have your full backing?
[OHTENKUN] That's all
you're gonna get from him.
You might as well ask the
wall for its assessment.
[BUNCHU] And what exactly is
that supposed to mean?
[OHTENKUN] I guess it
was about 20 years after
you descended
to the human world.
He just started to slip away
until this was all that's left.
He's basically a husk now.
He'll sometimes repeat
what he just heard
as an order, but that's it.
[BUNCHU] I have to wonder if
someone has stolen his soul.
But who?
Who would even be
capable of pulling that off?
[BUNCHU gasps]
This reeks of Dakki's handiwork.
Are you hiding something?
I'm in the dark here.
Why even ask me that?
[BUNCHU] It appears I need
to have a little talk with her.
I'm heading back.
Prepare the Juttenkun
to descend on Kongrong.
Is that what
we're preparing for?
So what, you want us to just
fly in and attack them?
Not at all.
I have the perfect strategy.
Oh, do you?
Bunchu!
[BUNCHU]
Your Majesty.
You look well. Have you
recovered from your illness?
I haven't been sick in ages.
Something wrong, Bunchu?
You almost look like
you want me to be sick.
Majesty.
Do you know where Dakki is?
[CHU]
Dakki?
I don't know a Dakki.
[SHINKOHYO chuckles]
Well, color me intrigued.
[KOKUTENKO]
What do you wanna do now?
Spy on Taikobo's crew?
We don't always need to lean on
your clairvoyance, Kokutenko.
There's plenty of compelling
material right here
in front of us.
[KOKUTENKO]
Huh?
[DAKKI giggles]
Why so surprised? You know
I can do anything I want.
Something I can
help you with, Dakki?
Taikobo's in the midst of
gathering up all his allies
and marching right
towards Choka.
So here's the thing, Shinkohyo.
I want you to lend
your services to Yin
so we can stack
this deck high.
We don't wanna let Yin
capitulate, now do we?
You want to save Yin.
Do you really expect
me to believe that?
Your goal has been
destroying Yin all along.
I'm well-versed in the many
secrets you keep hidden.
You left Kingo Island to
revel in the decadent life
of a vagrant Sennin.
Sure, Bunchu also migrated
from the Sennin world
to live alongside the humans,
but he still continues
to maintain his connection
with Kingo Island.
The exact opposite of you.
You've cut all ties.
Severed every one that
could tangle you up.
And then you established
your own dominion,
bringing half the Yokai
Sennin in under your rule.
Hell, you've claimed
the palace as your own.
And oddly enough, Tsuten
Kyoshu hasn't made a peep,
even though you stole
most of his followers.
Hold on, Tsuten Kyoshu?
Oh, silly me, I remember him.
[YOTENKUN] You have to
give credit to Bunchu.
That's one hell of a bold
plan he's come up with.
[CHOTENKUN] No one ever
said he was to be taken lightly.
[SONTENKUN]
So what do you think, Ohtenkun?
We going along with his plan?
Sure we are.
[crunching]
So we're all on the same page...
We're gonna let Bunchu
do whatever he wants
for the time being.
[SHINKOHYO chuckles]
Take it in while you can.
This country's history's about
to get drastically remolded
by the hands of Sennin.
Do you really want that?
Couldn't you put all
this turmoil to rest
just by defeating Dakki?
Sure, but I can't do that.
[KOKUTENKO]
And why not?
Oh, just because.
Besides, all of the
pieces are in place.
Both Kingo and Kongrong
have chosen to support Yin
and the Shu.
The coming war isn't a
possibility, but a fact.
[SUPUSHAN]
Hey, uh, Master...
You sure it's a good idea
to travel to Kingo Island
by ourselves?
Yep, it's the only way I can
properly propose a ceasefire.
Okay, but I'm
kind of freaking out.
I mean, what if they
just refuse to listen?
A-And then they might capture
us and torture us just for fun!
Oh, no, what if they skin us
alive and dip us in salt?!
Can you try to put
a lid on the neurosis?
[TAIKOBO gasps]
Wha--?
What the hell's going on?
[FUGEN]
Kingo Island.
It's moving.
Kongrong and Kingo.
This is it.
The battle is about to begin.
No turning back now.
This should be quite fun.