[CHOKA CITIZENS chattering]
We're all starving
to death out here!
Just some food for the children?
Show your face, Emperor!
All of you, back away!
If you dare come any closer
to the emperor's palace,
you will all pay severely!
[gasps]
[CHOKA OFFICIAL 18A]
The revolt appears to be
growing more extreme by the day.
Public order in
Choka is crumbling.
Several soldiers have
also fled recently.
This cannot continue.
[CHU]
Uh--
[CHOKA OFFICIAL 18C]
Your Majesty!
The Shu army broke
through Menchi Castle.
They number 250,000.
What?
They're advancing!
Straight toward Choka!
[CHOKA OFFICIALS gasp]
[CHOKA OFFICIAL 18A]
There's too many of them.
How could this have happened?
I have to do
something, but what?
Hello, Chu, darling!
--[CHU gasps]
--Did you miss me?
[CHU gasping]
[DAKKI giggles]
Damn it!
[OHMA]
Calm down, Koyuken.
[KOYUKEN]
I can't take this.
Do we know when Master
Bunchu is due to return?
Instead of waiting
around and wondering,
maybe we should go on up
to Kingo Island ourselves
and help him out!
Don't forget that Bunchu
has entrusted us
to protect Choka in his absence.
I understand that, but...
With the Shu army
heading this way,
our service is needed here.
We cannot leave Choka now
when there is work to be done.
Yes, and what's more,
Dakki has vanished.
No one knows when
she's coming back.
[KOYUKEN grunts]
[DAKKI]
Surprise!
[ALL gasp]
[DAKKI] It still reeks of that
fool Bunchu after all this time.
[KOYUKEN, YOSHIN, RI KOHA, OHMA]
Dakki!
How dare you return
here without approval!
[DAKKI]
Please, no need to yell.
[OHMA] We will not allow you
to cause any more trouble
for Master Bunchu or Yin!
If you persist, we will get
rid of you, just as before!
That's right.
How could I possibly forget
how intolerably rude
the four of you were
to me back then?
What should we do about that?
Chu, darling!
Take care of these boys.
Emperor Chu...?
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[groans]
That's... impossible...
[groans] She's controlling him.
That witch.
We've failed you...
Forgive us, Master Bunchu.
[DAKKI giggles]
[CHU screams, groans]
[DAKKI] I suppose this
means His Majesty Chu
won't be of any use
to me anymore.
A pity.
[DAKKI laughs]
[FUGEN]
Because of Dakki,
the people have lost all
faith in the Yin Dynasty.
But the truth is it has been
doomed for a very long time.
So, I'd like to
make a suggestion.
Why don't we work
to defeat Dakki--
cleanse the human
world together?
[FUGEN]
When our mission is complete,
we will each take a vow never
to enter the human world again.
What do you say?
[BUNCHU]
That was enlivening.
[gasps]
[BUNCHU] But humans have a thing
called "order of precedence."
I've adopted this
way of thinking.
Yin is number one in my order.
[gasps]
[BUNCHU] What does not
benefit Yin must go,
such as Kingo and Kongrong.
They never have and never will
serve any purpose for Yin.
Therefore, I will destroy them.
It's a simple equation really,
yet one you and Taikobo
find difficult to understand.
[FUGEN]
It's no use.
I'll never break through
such an iron will!
[gasps]
[BUNCHU]
I'm through talking,
Fugen Shinjin of the Twelve
Elite Sennin of Kongrong...
[BUNCHU]
You shall perish
along with your
worthless Sennin world!
So Bunchu decided to
make an appearance.
I suppose this means the
entertaining Great Sennin War
is entering its final act.
[KOKUTENKO] Which side
do you think will win?
No doubt Bunchu
will be the victor.
Really?
Even though Kongrong has
Taikobo, Ryukitsu Kosho,
and the rest of the Twelve
Elite Sennin on its side?
It's true he certainly is
outnumbered in this battle,
but I know that Bunchu's power
and his passion
for the Yin Dynasty
will outweigh any number
of foes moving against him.
However...
[KOKUTENKO]
However what?
[SHINKOHYO] While it's a simple
matter to break something,
restoration is a far
more difficult task.
Choka has been badly
damaged by Dakki.
Criminals are running rampant.
Public order is in shambles.
Women and children are
unable to leave their homes
and peace has all but
disappeared from the city.
How do you plan to repair this?
I am well aware of Yin's
current state, you clown.
It will be restored soon.
And yet I wonder how
you can be so certain.
Now that the Buseioh is
no longer working with you,
it appears that
basically the only thing
keeping the Yin
Dynasty alive is you.
[SHINKOHYO] After the many
challenges you've faced,
the sacrifices,
I don't understand why
you cling so tightly to it.
You realize that if
Yin as a concept is lost,
it will mean nothing
to its people.
In fact, I believe it
was Taikobo who said
many are already searching for
a new dynasty to replace it.
[BUNCHU groans]
[BUNCHU]
Silence, Shinkohyo!
I have always felt for Yin
as I would my own child.
I will protect it
unconditionally
just as any parent should.
[BUNCHU]
My history with Yin is long.
It began over 300 years ago.
[BUNCHU] When I was a
younger man, I had a rival.
[BUNCHU pants]
[BUNCHU]
Her name was Shushi
and her strength equaled my own.
[SHUSHI grunts]
[SHUSHI]
Ha!
[BUNCHU grunts]
[BUNCHU] I never saw her
as particularly beautiful
and she was four
years my senior.
That settles it.
Since I know that we
both have the same dream
of becoming generals
in the Yin army someday,
we'll need a lot of support.
So let's promise that we'll
always have each other's backs
no matter what!
Yes. I promise.
[BUNCHU] Although my rival,
she was cheerful and elegant.
I could not deny
she was charming.
Even so, I believed
we would remain at odds
for the rest of our lives.
[BUNCHU]
Then one day...
You're going to be empress?
[SHUSHI laughs]
[SHUSHI]
Not yet, exactly.
But the emperor couldn't let
a good thing like me go!
I'll be his second wife.
The thing is, since his first
couldn't have children,
if I were to have a baby, then
I could legally rule with him.
But you plan to be a general!
I mean, can you no longer
take up the sword?
[SHUSHI]
Don't be ridiculous.
We'll still fight together.
Only now we'll win standing
right alongside the emperor.
I would never let all of
our training go to waste.
The people of Yin need
both of us, remember?
[BUNCHU] That was
the day our paths split,
each in the opposite direction.
[BUNCHU]
In order to free my mind
from the array of
emotions clouding it,
I focused on
self-inflicted pain.
[BUNCHU groans]
[BUNCHU] My entire body began
to rot and grow necrotic.
[KING OF YIN] You wish
to go to the Sennin world?
[BUNCHU]
Yes.
I understand that I was not born
with the bones of a Sennin,
but after the training
I've put my body through,
I believe I may be
developing them.
[KING OF YIN]
I see!
If you were to go to their world
and return here as a Doshi,
that would greatly
benefit the Yin Dynasty.
--[SHUSHI] Bunchu.
--[BUNCHU] Yes?
Please make sure
you come back to us.
Promise?
I want this little one to
grow and learn from you.
[BUNCHU]
You have my word, Empress.
Then ten years went by.
Have you heard?
It appears the Kyo clan has
invaded the capital of Yin.
[YOKAI 18B]
Yeah.
I heard that the emperor fought
back, but was killed in battle.
[BUNCHU]
During that era,
Yin had not yet
gained full strength.
[SHUSHI gasps]
[footsteps]
[gasps]
Shushi!
You came back.
I'm happy to see you, Bunchu.
[BUNCHU]
Please, save your strength.
[SHUSHI]
I fought as hard as I could.
I guess... I've lost
my edge somehow.
Hold on!
[SHUSHI]
I need you to train my son.
Mold him...
...into a leader.
Emperor of Yin.
Promise me you'll
take care of him.
Please, Bunchu...
I shall.
[BUNCHU] And after the battle,
the boy became the new emperor.
He was good at it.
In fact, he made
Yin more powerful.
[BUNCHU]
From that day on,
I oversaw the education
of the royal family.
The emperor's son and grandson,
as well as Emperor Chu--
They were all students of mine.
[BUNCHU] I've trained leaders
both beloved and hated,
but regardless of
the way they ruled,
each one feared me
and idolized me.
That's true.
And it's worth noting that
you've outlived every last one.
[BUNCHU]
That's not relevant.
[SHINKOHYO]
Really, now?
[SHINKOHYO] You are the
father of Yin, Bunchu.
Relish it.
[BUNCHU] No matter the
cost, I will rebuild Yin!
Tsk. Gravity control!
Not bad.
I'm impressed.
[FUGEN]
You goal truly is annihilation.
You destroyed the power reactor
without a second thought.
But hear me, Bunchu.
I will not allow you
to release my soul.
I'm generating repulsion
and your Kinben will not
be able to reach me.
Is that a challenge?
[gasps]
Fugen!
Don't do anything stupid!
[gasps]
[TAIKOBO]
Stalling now?
[TAIKOBO screams]
[OHKIJIN]
Take deep breaths, Sister.
This is a treatment known
as an aromatherapy massage.
Why have I never had
one of these before?
Oh, that feels so
good! I approve!
Look what I brought, Dakki!
It's the legendary
unrefined saké
that Cleopatra herself
used to drink.
[DAKKI]
Is it really?
Wow! I love it!
[laughs]
[DAKKI] It's important
that a lady continuously
refine her beauty with
the most current trends!
Oh, look! We're getting
a call from you-know-who!
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[OHTENKUN] I'm happy to see
you in good spirits, Dakki.
[DAKKI laughs]
Since the boys are off fighting,
I figured I'd have a spa day.
It's the perfect
way to luxuriate.
[OHTENKUN]
Ah, how predictable.
I called to inform
you that Bunchu
has finally made his move.
Oh, so things are going well?
[OHTENKUN]
I suppose.
But if this keeps up,
he'll be the sole victor.
[DAKKI]
You amuse me sometimes.
Bunchu is stronger
than most, it's true,
but don't forget he's
still just a human.
Humans have a simple point of
weakness buried deep within
which they call a heart.
[OHTENKUN]
Is that so?
[DAKKI] It can also
drive them mad... like you.
The trick is to discover
what will make Bunchu
crumble in on himself.
But I have a feeling you
already know what that is.
[OHTENKUN]
I believe I do.
You truly are amazing.
I am humbled.
Oh, stop.
[HIKO]
Hmm...
[TENKA]
What's the matter, Dad?
[HIKO]
Where are those three sisters?
[TENKA]
I dunno.
They got separated
from us at some point.
I'm wondering where
the hell Bunchu is.
Shouldn't he be here by now?
[FUGEN] Taikyoku Fuin's
gravity control isn't working.
Or is it just that
Bunchu's paopei
is significantly more powerful?
Before we continue,
I have a question.
What compelled you
to abandon Taikobo
and fight me on your own?
Did you believe your power
was enough to stop me?
Perhaps I did.
[BUNCHU]
You're lying.
You're ensuring Taikobo lives,
even if everyone else dies,
and attempting to stall me
until your allies arrive.
You offered to be
the one to draw me out,
though it could mean losing
your life in the process.
[BUNCHU]
I'm baffled and amused.
Do you honestly believe I'll be
defeated if you outnumber me?
[FUGEN]
I have to buy time somehow.
They'll be here soon.
How foolish must you be
to think this strategy
could ever be effective?
[FUGEN]
My friends are coming.
And you'll have your answers
when we defeat you together!
What's this?
Must be your paopei's
nuclear fusion ability.
[TAIKOBO groaning]
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[TAIKOBO]
Fugen.
Looks like he attacked.
That was definitely
a direct hit.
I hope it was enough to do
a little damage at least.
[gasps]
[FUGEN]
No. That's impossible.
He doesn't even have
a scratch on him!
You never stood a chance
against my power.
I'll offer one truth
to compensate for
your embarrassment.
I have no weaknesses
for you to find.
The result will be the same
no matter how many come for me.
[FUGEN]
I'm scared.
[FUGEN gasps]
[BUNCHU]
Do you still wish to fight?
Very well.
Unfortunately,
you leave me no choice.
[FUGEN gasps]
[BUNCHU gasps]
Wait.
A wall of wind.
[TAIKOBO]
Fugen?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Looks like we made
it just in time!
[FUGEN]
Bo!
Hey, there, Bunchu!
It's been a while!
Ha! I didn't recognize you
without your tail
between your legs.
[TAIKOBO]
Good one!
But you need to get used
to the idea of losing.
Really?
Then come at me, Taikobo!
[KOKUTENKO]
Ooh! Looks like the battle
between Taikobo and Bunchu
is finally taking place.
We know how it ends.
Bunchu defeats
all of them, right?
Yes.
Unless...
[KOKUTENKO gasps]
Unless what?
[SHINKOHYO] It's possible
the Signpost of History
is not pointed in
Bunchu's direction.
We have no way of knowing
who will reign
victorious this time.
[OHTENKUN] What's your plan
now that the battle has begun?
Let's see. I think...
I'll do whatever I see fit.
[OHTENKUN]
Understood.
The age of myth seems to quickly
be approaching its close.
Therefore, history's archetype,
which is fundamental
to this world,
will end with it.
Dakki...
...Bunchu...
...the people...
They've forsaken me
and now I'm all alone.