[YOZEN]
It's such a faint memory now.
[YOZEN crying]
[GYOKUTEI]
Yozen.
Is someone there?
[YOZEN crying]
[GYOKUTEI]
Yozen.
[YOZEN crying]
[GYOKUTEI]
C'mon, now.
I hate to see you cry like this.
[GYOKUTEI] No. Tsuten Kyoshu
doesn't hate you at all.
That's not why he left you here
with us on Kongrong Mountain.
The truth is, he brought
you here because
he loves you dearly.
He was only trying
to protect you,
and this is the safest
place you can be.
I don't get it.
Protect me from what?
Well, you see...
You have the inherent
qualities of a powerful prodigy,
and some bad people
wanted to exploit you
for their misdeeds.
Fortunately, your father
found out about their plans
before they could.
So he asked Master Genshi
Tenson to watch over you.
Trust me on this one, Yozen.
You need to maintain
a human form,
or else the bad guys
might find you.
Okay!
I'll do the best I can,
and then maybe my dad will come
take me home someday.
[YOZEN]
Although...
In the end,
no one ever came
for me, and I was alone.
[TAIKOBO]
Gyokutei.
The winning move is up to you.
I've got it under control.
[TAIKOBO yelling]
You just hang in there.
[SONTENKUN laughing]
[SONTENKUN] I've got my
own Taikobo doll now.
So, Gyokutei Shinjin, looks like
you're the only challenger left.
What game do you
feel like losing?
No more games.
Playtime's over, you cretin.
Taikobo was setting up a
plan right beneath your nose,
and all that's left now
is for me to execute.
[SONTENKUN] Great, he's
gonna try the sword again.
Did you not hear me?
Or are the illustrious
Twelve Sennin of Kongrong
really this stupid?
I'm happy just to make
these two self-destruct
and explode.
Or, you can extend
their miserable lives
by indulging me in a
game you can never win.
You're the only one
who's going to lose here.
As a matter of fact,
I'll kill you so quickly,
you won't have the
chance to hurt anyone.
[SONTENKUN laughs]
Go on and try it!
Fast as you may be
with that sword,
you don't even know
where the real me is hiding!
That's where you're wrong.
Taikobo showed me where you are.
[SONTENKUN]
Settle down!
Any more sudden
movements from you
and your friends go boom.
That's all I needed.
You're as good as dead.
[SONTENKUN grunts]
[SONTENKUN]
But how? How did you know?
You practically
gave yourself away.
Taikobo narrowed
your location down
to one of the toys
hanging from the ceiling.
So when it came time
for him to deal the cards,
he made a grand show of it
in order to distract you.
And all the while, he was
actually using the cards
to slice tiny cuts
into the toys.
From those cuts,
a small drop of blood
would eventually fall.
Then he kept you
busy with the game
until your blood told
us where you were.
I'm sure you were confident
that you had Taikobo beaten,
but that's exactly
what a skilled hustler
wants you to think, and he's
Kongrong's greatest cheat.
[SONTENKUN]
He tricked me.
Made a complete fool of me.
Compared to your dirty tricks,
it really wasn't much more
than a cute little prank.
The Juttenkun are
quite a devious bunch.
[SUPUSHAN, TAIKOBO grunting]
We aren't dumb toys anymore!
Nicely done, Gyokutei!
Happy to help.
Anyway, we've wasted
enough time here.
Let's find Yozen.
[TAIKOBO]
Yeah, let's get moving.
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
There goes one more.
Add Sontenkun to
the list of corpses.
Talk about pathetic.
Enough of this!
It's time for them to die!
Yeah.
Brilliant suggestion there.
Believe me, I'm aware of the
deadly glares we're getting.
If we don't finish
them this time,
we'll be killed in their place.
Bunchu.
You'd better let me
take this next go-round.
No way in hell.
I already told you
to sit this one out
so I can keep an eye on you.
How many times do you wanna risk
running up against
the same conclusion?
We've already got two guys down
and I'd rather
not lose any more.
Taikobo's dirty little tricks
aren't gonna work on me.
And I'll tell ya why.
He may be a good cheat, but
deception is my very nature.
[BUNCHU]
Fine, then.
Go kill him.
But if you fail,
I'm leaving you on your
own to die a lonely death.
You're one cold bastard.
[GYOKUTEI] You said we'll find
Yozen close to the barrier
control room?
I think so.
Well, at least I hope so.
Let's find him before they do!
[GYOKUTEI]
Right.
[GROUP gasps]
[TAIKOBO]
Who is that?
[OHTENKUN]
Hello, Taikobo.
Nice to finally meet you.
Around here,
I'm known as Ohtenkun,
and I suggest you
remember that, brave leader.
He's one of the Juttenkun.
Pleasantries aside,
I've got somethin'
you might wanna see.
They've got Yozen!
Don't worry, he's fine.
We've got him safely locked
away deep inside Kingo.
And I'll give him back.
You just have to come get him.
We keep a warp
paopei stored in the star
directly to your right.
All you've gotta do
is hop on board
and it'll automatically
transport you to Yozen.
The only catch?
You have to come alone.
[TAIKOBO] I'm gonna guess
this is the warp paopei
he was talking about.
It actually looks like
the same type of system
as Master Genshi's Hiraii.
[SUPUSHAN]
Cool! Let's get on board!
Stop, you idiot!
Jeez! What are you
screaming at me for?
Because this thing's
obviously a trap.
Most likely, there's gonna
be a powerful Juttenkun
waiting wherever
this paopei takes us.
Probably Ohtenkun himself.
[TAIKOBO]
You both saw him.
Just one look at him
and you can tell
that he's insanely dangerous.
He wants to split us up,
which means his strategy
is to kill us off one by one.
[GYOKUTEI] So you're saying
we should avoid this.
[TAIKOBO]
Nope.
I'm gonna do
exactly what he said.
I've got no doubt in my mind
that I'm walking into a trap,
but it might be the only chance
we have to save Yozen.
Taikobo!
I should be the one to go.
[TAIKOBO]
I can't let you.
When it comes down
to it, I can fight
just as dirty as he can,
but you don't think like--
[GYOKUTEI]
I need to do this for Yozen.
You aren't the one he
wants to rescue him.
Of that much I'm certain.
What's that supposed to mean?
[GYOKUTEI]
As you know,
I've looked after Yozen
since he was a child.
And I know things about him.
Certain things he's kept hidden.
It's only natural.
I'm even sure that
you know a side of him
that he's never shown to me.
No one can ever truly
know the full extent
of another.
You would need the ability
to read a person's mind.
You might believe
that you know someone,
but there's more
than you can see.
Some dark secret buried
deep within their heart.
Much like everyone else, Yozen
carries such secrets within him.
And I know he's just not
ready to reveal that side
of himself to another person.
But, if you go after him now,
you're more than likely
to discover the real Yozen.
And then, you might
not say it out loud,
but you'll still think it.
You'll think to yourself,
"Why didn't you tell me sooner?
And he'll know.
He'll see it in your eyes
and it'll hurt him deeply.
So I'm asking you, wait
until he has the strength
to tell you.
Let him decide when he's ready.
Don't force it on him.
Please, Taikobo.
Allow him that.
How can I say no to that?
The rescue mission's yours.
One thing, though.
I don't give a damn
what the real Yozen is.
I'll never abandon him.
I'm not surprised.
But thank you.
This must be it.
Yozen!
[OHTENKUN chuckling]
Come on in, Gyokutei Shinjin.
Ohtenkun!
He's all yours.
Scoop him up and take him home.
He's lying right there.
Master...
[GYOKUTEI]
You fought well.
I'm very proud of you.
Master...
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
You're gonna have
to pay, though,
if you wanna take
him outta here.
Thievery is a crime, after all.
[TAIKOBO]
Are you ready, Supu?
You and I are heading for
the core of Kingo Island.
[SUPUSHAN] Whoa, hold on,
what're you talking about?
Well, the control room
is located in the core, so--
You told Gyokutei we'd wait
for them back on Kongrong!
And you know Bunchu's
in the control room,
so quit acting so aloof!
Think about where
Gyokutei is heading,
and where they
would confine Yozen.
They're probably in the
Juttenkun's barracks,
and that's gonna be
somewhere close to the core.
[SUPUSHAN] Okay, I see what
you're saying, but still.
We have to find them.
I'm not walking out of here
unless they're with us.
We're saving them,
no matter the cost!
[SUPUSHAN sighs]
I know it's pointless
to argue with you.
So fine, but we're getting
out of this creep nest
as soon as we find them.
You got it.
[YOZEN]
Master...
You're here.
Did you come just to rescue me?
Shh. Save your energy.
Kongrong's still intact,
and it's all thanks to you.
And Taikobo's alive and
well, so you rest easy.
You're my greatest pupil,
and I've never been so proud.
That means so much to me.
Thank you.
Just hearing you
say those words...
It's the only salvation I need.
But Master, please
be careful in here.
Ohtenkun is evil incarnate.
I can feel his malice
like a poisonous vapor.
Stay with me!
So...
I think I've given
you enough time
for your weepy
heartfelt reunion.
But now I'm bored.
Hope you don't mind
if I liven things up a bit.
Wha-- What is this?
My paopei, Kosuijin.
The other Juttenkun
are all-powerful
only when they've got you
trapped in the dimensions
they create.
But I force this dimension
to succumb to my power.
And you will perish
in this space beneath
a rain of blood.
A rain of blood?
My god...
Don't tell me these
red clouds are...
[OHTENKUN] I literally just
told you what they are,
but I forgot to mention
my blood is highly acidic.
Stick around long enough
and you'll become a puddle.
You've only got one
option for saving your skin.
Struggle your way through the
rain and escape this space.
There's another option.
A simple one.
[GYOKUTEI]
And that's killing you!
What? Impossible...
You should be dead!
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[OHTENKUN] You're even dumber
than I thought you were.
Try to attack me all you want,
but you're gonna have
trouble killing an illusion.
This whole space is
made from my blood
and I control it all.
I'll dumb it down for you.
I've basically got you
trapped inside my body.
I'm just not a very big
fan of hand-to-hand combat.
[GYOKUTEI grunting]
Go on. The exit
is right behind you.
Grab your mewling, useless
prince and head home already.
At least try.
I wanna see you put some
effort in before your body
dissolves to goo.
[GYOKUTEI grunts]
What's up with that
thing down there?
Everything else in
this place is round,
so why is that a giant square?
I don't know.
But it might as well have the
word "suspicious" written on it.
Let's go and check it out.
Roger that, boss!
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[GYOKUTEI grunting]
[YOZEN grunts]
[GYOKUTEI]
Yozen!
[YOZEN grunting]
[GYOKUTEI grunting]
Please, Master.
Just leave me behind so
you can run for the door!
You can still save yourself!
You've got a long way to go,
so I'd pick up the pace
if I were you.
Or you can both
melt for all I care.
[YOZEN]
Please, Master.
Leave me!
Just put me down and--
[GYOKUTEI]
This reminds me.
I've carried you
like this before.
Back when you were
a child and I found you
crying in the rain.
[GYOKUTEI]
Come on now, Yozen.
Let's get you out of this.
[GYOKUTEI]
I wanted to keep you dry.
So you wouldn't catch a cold.
[GYOKUTEI] You've grown
so much since then, Yozen.
[YOZEN] All this time, the one
who would come back for me
has been standing
right by my side.
What the hell?
[GYOKUTEI grunts]
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
I'm here, pal.
[TAIKOBO]
Gyokutei!
Taikobo.
Take care of Yozen for me.
[TAIKOBO]
He's gone.
[GYOKUTEI]
Yozen.
Wake up, now.
There you are. Look around.
[GYOKUTEI]
It's stopped raining.