[BUNCHU] You're rather
persistent for someone
on the verge of death, Buseioh.
[HIKO chuckles]
That goes for you, too.
[BUNCHU] I have no
desire to take your life
with my own hands.
I'd prefer a dignified battle
between our armies
after we've returned
to the human world.
I'm giving you
the chance to leave.
Shut up, already.
I'm not leaving here until
I've cracked your face open
with my fist.
Is that so?
Well, I tried.
[BUNCHU]
You leave me no choice.
[thunder rumbles]
[BOTH grunt]
Hiko.
I understand.
The true thing I've always
been drawn to protect.
I know what it is now.
[SUPUSHAN] Is this really the
time to be lounging around?
We've seen firsthand
how powerful Dakki is.
As things stand, I'm clearly
not ready to take her on yet.
Which is why we
need to start gathering up
those allies you were talking
about and build an army!
We could do that,
or we could just sit here
on this rock until we
catch us a big ol' fish.
[SUPUSHAN] He's still shaken up
from our last run-in with Dakki.
[HIKO]
What did you say? Bunchu?
[MESSENGER 2A]
Yes, sir.
We've received word that
he's suppressed the uprising
in Hokkai.
I see.
So... When can we expect
his return to Choka?
[BUNCHU]
You can expect me now.
You've put some years
on your face, old friend.
[HIKO]
Oh, come on.
Is that really the first
thing you're gonna say to me?
Better than being some eternally
baby-faced Doshi who never ages.
[BUNCHU] Well, age hasn't
dulled our edges.
That much is clear.
Thanks for holding the empire
together while I was gone.
I can't pretend it was easy.
Not with that shrew
trying to run the show.
[BUNCHU]
Twenty years I've known him.
[MOTHER SPIRIT BEAST 2A] You'll
pay for your crime, humans!
I'll raze this city
and slaughter you all!
That's enough!
[BUNCHU] No vermin threatens
Yin under my watch.
[BUNCHU]
You'll die for this!
The hell's wrong
with you, jackass?
Do you always kill first
and ask questions later?
Who the hell do
you think you are?
I don't owe an introduction
to a savage hothead.
[HIKO]
There, go on.
[BABY SPIRIT BEAST 2A]
Mama!
[MOTHER SPIRIT BEAST 2A]
Oh! My little girl!
[HIKO]
Some heartless punks from Choka
stole that spirit beast's
baby away from her.
Pretty good reason for her
to be so pissed off.
There's more than just
brute strength that's required
of a Grand Preceptor.
Try to keep that
in mind, will ya?
Wait, aren't you--
You've arrived at last,
Koh Hiko!
I expect you'll fully
devote yourself to Yin.
[HIKO]
I will.
Grand Preceptor. Hey.
[BUNCHU]
And before I knew it,
he became an ally I would
trust with my own life.
A true friend.
[LI SEI]
Help! Somebody help me!
My son's trying to kill me!
[LI SEI]
He's found me! That's my son!
Nataku! He's a human paopei!
[TAIKOBO]
That guy's a paopei?
Well I guess that would explain
how he can so effortlessly
wield three at once.
[LI SEI]
No! Please don't!
[TAIKOBO]
That paopei...
I know it!
That's the Kenkonken!
[LI SEI yelling]
[BUNCHU] I see much has
changed, Your Majesty.
Or perhaps not.
In fact, I recall another
mysterious vixen
who once held sway
over the court.
This was about 60 years ago,
during Taitei's rule.
[BUNCHU]
Your reign ends here, snake.
You've brought
enough suffering to Yin,
and now you'll burn for it!
[BUNCHU]
Now that I've returned to Choka,
your deception is exposed.
I'll chase you from
the throne as many times
as it takes, Dakki!
[CHU yells]
[HIKO]
Stop! Idiot!
You trying to kill the emperor?
He'll be fine.
He needs a wake-up call.
What? Bunchu!
Are you betraying me?
Your Majesty.
Your empress is a Sennyo.
A disgusting lie.
Emperor Chu!
I have loyally trained you
since you were no more
than a young boy.
Whose word will you believe?
Your servant or this imposter?
My empress.
[CHU yells]
You need to let it go for now.
[BUNCHU]
Fine.
But I swear that
I'll oust that beast.
And very soon.
[DAKKI]
Oh, will you?
Well I'm just utterly dying
to see you try, Bunchu.
[LI SEI]
I welcome you both to Chintokan.
My name is Li Sei and I'm
the commanding officer here.
I actually once trained with
the Sennin at Kongrong Mountain.
Nataku is--well, my son is
an artificial human
created by the Sennin world.
[INSHI]
You're home.
Welcome back, my love.
[LI SEI]
Ah, perfect time, dear.
Let me introduce you
to my wife, Inshi.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
You were telling me
about Nataku?
[LI SEI] Well, it all began
about ten years ago.
At that time, my wife
had been pregnant
for close to three
and a half years.
Which is unusual,
to say the least.
Don't you worry, dear.
I'm sure our child will be
a healthy ball of love.
I couldn't bear to
tell her the truth.
That deep within,
I harbored the fear
she would give birth
to a monster.
Then one day, she told me
of a dream she'd had
the night before.
[INSHI]
What is this? Who are you?
[TAIITSU]
I'm sorry, Madam Li,
but the child you're carrying
is mortally malformed.
However, you may
still give life to the baby
if you choose to accept this.
The paopei. Reiju.
[LI SEI] And when she
did finally give birth,
it was to a horrifying egg-like
ball of twisted flesh.
[LI SEI]
She must never know of this.
I can't let her
see this monster!
The inhuman child that
burst forth from the mass
was born into our world
with paopei attached
to his body.
Despite his true nature,
my wife never failed
to treat Nataku with anything
but the love of a mother.
--Eat up, now!
--It's good.
Time to study.
--One plus two is?
--Three.
Oh, my perfect boy!
[BUNCHU] Demolish the Horaku
and fill in the Taibon!
[CROWD]
Yes, sir!
Distribute food to the people!
I assume you're hoping to
reverse the many evil deeds
Dakki has committed?
As the Grand Preceptor,
I'm only doing what's right
for the empire.
You truly baffle me, y'know.
I'll never understand why this
empire is so important to you.
This empire.
Well, Yin is very much
like a child to me.
[BUNCHU] You wouldn't expect
that from me, would you?
[SHINKOHYO]
No.
But it does explain this mortal
attachment you have
to Yin, Bunchu.
I think I can handle this.
I just need to help them put
an end to this familial spat.
That's all there is to it.
It's just that easy, huh?
If we can make Nataku our ally,
that alone would give us the
strength of a thousand men.
Our best chance for that
is to smooth things over
so he feels like he owes us one.
[INSHI]
Nataku!
I've chosen to offer my
protection to your father,
Li Sei!
If you really wanna
see him dead,
well, I hope that you're
ready to kill me first!
Are you nuts?!
Of course he's ready!
Pull it together, Supu.
If you're telling me you're
too scared to even fly,
then you're no more
than a hippo.
[SUPUSHAN]
A hippo?!
All right, let's do this!
[TAIKOBO]
Atta boy!
[INSHI]
Please, Taikobo!
Try not to hurt my son.
Of course.
Trust me, I want this
to end peacefully too.
Ready when you are.
[TAIKOBO yells]
Chi!
You stopped its trajectory!
[chuckles]
That's definitely the
face of a man born to fight.
Get ready to dodge!
[TAIKOBO]
I'll admit he's strong.
Yeah, sorry, but I don't
think you're evenly matched
on strength.
Thanks, but I was able to make
that observation on my own.
Somethin' wrong, Nataku?
What, can't you hit me
from that far away?
So he has to fly after the
paopei he shoots to catch them?
[INSHI, LI SEI gasp]
Mother, no!
Whoa, what just happened there?
The Kenkonken is a type of
paopei that uses copper rings
to make direct physical attacks.
I can't stop them when
he fires both at once,
but I am capable of easily
changing their trajectory.
Well that was
certainly a close call.
[TAIKOBO]
Dafuba!
Nataku, no!
What's the matter?
Having second thoughts
about using the Kenkonken?
Hey, you're welcome to do so,
but I'll just change
its direction again
and who knows
where it'll end up.
Why are you interfering?
My fight is with Li Sei.
Our quarrel has nothing
to do with you.
All right. I've gotta ask.
Why is it that you
despise Li Sei?
It's because
Li Sei despised me first.
And I get it.
I was born bearing the weapons
of a Sennin, after all.
So I can understand why he
can't consider me his son.
And I've caused my
mother trouble as well.
Is that all?
I feel like there's a part of
the story you're not telling me.
[INSHI]
There is.
It happened three years ago,
on a very humid day.
We had gone to swim
in a certain river,
even though it was prohibited.
Nataku enraged the spirit
beast that ruled the river.
[SPIRIT BEAST 2A] What fool
dares to wear a paopei
in the waters of my river?
Don't you realize that
your paopei sends out
shockwaves through the current?
Your carelessness has caused
a needless massacre
amongst my disciples!
Please forgive him!
My Nataku is no more
than a child!
I beg you!
[SPIRIT BEAST 2A]
I demand penance!
You will both be executed!
Nataku...
[NATAKU]
I had to.
I couldn't just stand by and
let him kill you, Mother.
[INSHI]
It was my fault.
He was only trying
to protect me.
A few days afterward,
the King of the Spirit Beasts
descended upon us.
[SPIRIT BEAST KING 2A] Which
one of you murdered my son?
Reveal yourself!
I shoulder the sins of my son!
And I will accept
your punishment!
[INSHI] And before I could
realize, he protected me again.
I'm sorry, Mother.
I'll now return this
body back to you.
[NATAKU]
I should have died right then.
But the true essence of my
being continued to survive.
I became a creature
of pure consciousness.
My mother only saw my dead body,
so she built a glorious
tomb for me.
And that was enough
to satisfy my soul.
But then...
How dare she have a
tomb like this built
without telling me about it?
The Spirit Beast King will
murder us if he discovers it!
[NATAKU] At that point,
a Sennin appeared before me.
I'm Taiitsu Shinjin
of Kongrong Mountain.
And you, child?
It is nowhere near
time for you to die.
You will be reincarnated
as a lotus.
[NATAKU] This Sennin has
chosen to keep me alive
for some reason.
I can't say why,
but I do know one thing.
I know that I can
never forgive Li Sei
for what he's done to me.
The body born from
my mother has died.
Which means I am no
longer related to Li Sei.
[TAIKOBO]
Well now I know!
Hearing your side of the story
definitely changes things.
Y'know what?
My mind is changed.
I'm 100 percent
on your side now.
So. Hurry up and kill your idiot
father and let's call it a day.
[SUPUSHAN, LI SEI, INSHI]
What?!
[SUPUSHAN]
What's wrong with you, Master?
Did you change
your mind or lose it?
Well, what're you waiting for?
[TAIKOBO]
You can't do it, huh?
I mean with your power, you
should've been able to kill him
long before
I even showed up.
No, he's very skilled
at running away!
Really? C'mon already.
The truth is, you don't hate
him as much as you want to.
[NATAKU]
You're wrong!
I loathe him with all my being!
Oh, please, no...
Mother!
Time to say thank you.
I just saved both your
parents' lives for you.
And you wanna know why I did it?
I saved them 'cuz
I'm on your side.
[NATAKU]
You're wrong. You're wrong.
You're wrong! You're wrong!
That's enough, Nataku.
Are you really
gonna keep this up?
The power of a paopei
is weakened when anger
dilutes your focus.
You don't stand a chance
of beating me right now!
[INSHI]
Wait!
Nataku, you have to stop this.
If I were to lose you again,
or if I lost your father...
I would die from a broken heart.
[NATAKU]
I've lost.
[NATAKU] I don't even understand
what I mean to those two.
I'm just a paopei.
After being reborn,
I'm not even related to them.
But still, my mother has asked
me to spare Li Sei's life,
so I won't kill him.
Good.
I think you're making
the right call on that.
And whatever your body is now,
it honestly doesn't matter.
The three of you are still
a family and nothing
will change that.
[clapping]
[TAIKOBO]
What the hell?
[BUNCHU]
A rebellion?
Led by the Eastern Prince?
Indeed.
I ordered the execution of the
former Eastern Prince, Kanso.
After that task was carried out,
his younger sister
and my last wife killed herself.
It's only natural that
his successor, Kyo Bunkan,
would seek vengeance.
And so we shall respond.
I want one of you to lead
an army of 50,000 soldiers
to persuade the Prince
to remain loyal.
[BUNCHU]
Hiko.
That cunning fox has devised
this scheme to send me away.
It's precisely why she
had the Prince executed.
You think so?
Devious wretch.
Her intellect is a far
greater weapon
than her temptation spell.
[TAIITSU]
Impressively done, Bo!
You put that little quarrel
to bed quite easily.
I remember you.
Taiitsu Shinjin!
As the creator of Nataku,
I did feel obligated
to intervene myself.
But y'know, I've gotta say I
never would've even considered
stooping so low as to
use his mother as a shield.
I haven't seen you in forever
and that's the first thing
you say to me?
[TAIITSU]
Yeah, that's right.
It's been, what?
Three hundred years?
Well, nice to see you.
So, Nataku.
It's rather apparent that
mentally, you are still a child.
Seems best to have you train
under me in the Sennin world.
Why the hell should
I do what you say?
Convince me.
Piss and vinegar.
All right, then.
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
It's been a while since
I've seen a capturing paopei.
So, uh, Taikobo.
Would you mind if Supushan
gave me a ride down from here?
I climbed up to
make a cool entrance
but I'm scared to climb down.
[NATAKU]
Hey! Let me out!
You don't need to
worry about Nataku,
I promise I'll take care of him.
I'm sure that you will,
great Sennin.
It hurts to lose him, but we
must part ways for now.
Taikobo, once Nataku
has completed his training,
he'll return to the human world
to work as your right hand.
But I don't intend to rush
his training just for you.
[LI SEI] Maybe I should
return to the Sennin world
to complete my training.
I am his father after all; I
can't just let my son beat me.
Next time around, I'll get him.
Sure.
You believe what you need to.
[BUNCHU]
Your Majesty.
I've already quelled
the rebellion.
Bunchu. I have dispiriting news.
You're saying Hiko
betrayed Choka?