[NATAKU]
I was alone...
...as I prefer.
I didn't need anyone.
[footsteps]
[TAIITSU] All right,
time for your repairs.
Get the hell away from me.
[TAIITSU] If I do that,
you'll never move again,
and we wouldn't want
that, now would we?
If I hurt you, raise your
hand and let me know.
I can see right through you.
Since you couldn't
defeat me with skill,
you used your paopei.
A coward only relies
on his weapons.
I know you've always
wanted Kinsen and Kaseno,
and lately I've been
thinking very seriously
about giving them to you.
Really?
Of course, but there's
one condition.
Care to guess what?
[NATAKU] You want me to go
and join Taikobo, right?
Yes. So, let's see how you feel.
[TAIITSU]
Any pain or discomfort?
No.
[NATAKU] Fighting against
powerful opponents
was more than a mission.
It was the breath
that gave me life--
My everything.
[clanking, thud]
Those repairs are exceptional.
No enemy stands a
chance against you.
I'm well aware of that
and I'll destroy
every last one of them.
Goodbye.
[TAIITSU]
Nataku.
You were created to fight.
It fuels your soul--
renews your spirit.
I pray that you will
one day use your gifts
to fight for Mount Kongrong--
no, for this entire world.
[NATAKU grunts]
[YOZEN]
Huh?
You're strong, aren't you?
I can smell it.
Is that so?
You could say that.
[NATAKU]
I see.
I hope I get to
fight you one day.
Well, perhaps we'll
both be so fortunate.
I intend to align with Taikobo.
Stay close to him and we will
meet again quite soon.
[NATAKU]
I will.
His scent.
It's the same as mine.
He thirsts for battle with
the same desperation I do,
doesn't he?
[YOZEN wheezing]
[footsteps]
[TSUTEN]
Who darkens my doorway?
I am a Doshi.
I'm from Kongrong.
[TSUTEN]
Welcome.
Tell me, why have you
traveled so far from home?
[YOZEN] I've come to learn
the truth about who I am.
You know my father.
Will you give him a message for
me the next time you see him?
Tell him:
"I'm human."
Please.
[TSUTEN]
You have my word.
Trust me on this one, Yozen.
You need to maintain
a human form,
or else the bad guys
might find you.
Okay.
[YOZEN]
Master.
[YOZEN grunts]
You fought well.
I'm very proud of you.
[YOZEN]
Master.
I know the blood that flows
through me is that of a yokai ,
but...
[CHOTENKUN]
Chiretsujin!
[CHOTENKUN grunting]
Goodbye.
[CHOTENKUN groans]
[CHOTENKUN]
Impossible!
The Chiretsujin of Chotenkun...
...should not be defeated...
this easily...
[CHOTENKUN yells]
[NATAKU]
Hey, guys. It's over.
Come out.
Huh?
[BOTH panting]
[NATAKU]
Hmm...
[GENSHI sighs]
[KOSHU]
Are you feeling sick?
[GENSHI]
I've been better.
I'm afraid my pupils
have been afflicted
by this illness as well.
However, I am unharmed.
My water veil has protected me.
I don't understand.
What's causing it?
[GENSHI]
Hm?
[GENSHI grunts]
Can I face Bunchu?
Will I be able to fight somebody
who I used to call "friend"?
In truth, I don't
think I can kill him.
[HIKO]
Maybe it won't come to that.
[HIKO] Though that's
pretty hard to believe.
Even if I did find the man,
Bunchu would never listen to
anything I have to say to him.
[HIKO]
Here's an idea.
Let's go after those three
lovely sisters instead.
[TENKA]
I'm good with that.
We can't just leave them
to fend for themselves.
Oh, come on. Really?
How far down did those
plunging beauties fall exactly?
--[thud]
--[TENKA pants]
[HIKO]
Hm? What's wrong, Tenka?
Is that wound bothering you?
[TENKA]
No.
I don't know what it is.
[pants] I feel so weak,
like I'm gonna faint.
[TAIKOBO groans]
[TAIKOBO]
I know after defeating Entenkun
we should be like
"on to the next battle,"
but... I've gotta be honest.
I'm just not feeling it.
Funny you mention that.
I was thinking the same thing.
What are you saying?
You guys can't give up now!
I don't know what
the deal is, Supu.
I feel like I'm coming
down with something.
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[TAIKOBO]
No! How did this happen?
How did what happen?
Looks like they got us, dammit!
I can't believe I didn't
notice it before!
It's so obvious.
The whole reason
all the Kingo Sennin
have been impossible to find
is because they're hiding!
I'm confused.
Me, too.
[TAIKOBO]
I'm pretty sure Ohtenkun's bug
wasn't the only one of its kind.
They're all over Kingo Island,
which means very soon
Kongrong Mountain
is going to be infested with the
damn little bloodsuckers, too!
Well, at least we know
what's causing it.
But if you mean that thing
that was stuck to Yozen,
I'm still scared.
[TAIKOBO]
I do!
I guess Ohtenkun's a lot more
cunning of a tactician
than I thought.
Sorta like Dakki.
Mayday! Mayday!
Anybody alive and listening?
[BUKICHI]
Master! Can you hear me?
Loud and clear!
Taiitsu and Dotoku
both have colds.
It's really bad.
Please tell me what to do!
[TAIKOBO]
First of all, calm down!
Listen to me.
Our allies are
catching an illness
that seems to only
affect Sennin and Doshi.
Here's what you do.
Figure out a way to gather
them together and heal them.
I'm on it!
I don't know where everyone is,
but I promise I'll find them.
[TAIKOBO]
Thanks, Bukichi.
I'm counting on you.
[FUGEN] It sounds to me
like the only ones
even capable of movement
right now are Bukichi, Nataku,
and our faithful spirit beast,
Supushan, over here.
Not sure how that's
fair. [chuckles]
[TAIKOBO]
Not sure why you're laughin'.
New plan!
Bunchu and the rest
of the Juttenkun
will just have to wait.
We shouldn't attempt an attack
when everyone's feeling so weak.
We have to find Ohtenkun first.
If we're one man down,
shouldn't you rest, too?
Not everybody gets to nap
whenever they want like you do.
I'm coming with you.
Just gimme a minute.
[TAIKOBO] Oh, no problem!
Please, take your time!
[IGO] Huh. Looks like
they're headin' this way.
That damn Taikobo just
can't keep still, can he?
[IGO] Thank goodness
Master gave me this radar.
Never would've
found him otherwise.
Maybe he's got somethin' on him
that can help me keep
these stupid bugs away.
[TAIKOBO groans]
I have to draw
the line somewhere
and I can't stand
seeing you like this.
I'm gonna take you back!
[TAIKOBO]
Don't you dare!
[SUPUSHAN]
Why?
Okay, fine, but it's your
fault if something happens.
[gasps]
Who are you?
[IGO] It's good to finally
meet you, too, Taikobo.
Though you're smaller
than I expected you to be.
I'm Doko Tenson's pupil.
My name's Igo, and we-go...
...nna be... good friends.
[SUPUSHAN yells]
That was a dad joke!
The pun was so bad,
it's killing me!
Calm down, Supu!
You're making it worse!
[TAIKOBO]
I heard about you from Doko.
Hey, wait a minute.
Those mites aren't
affecting you at all?
What mites?
Oh, these purple bugs
that keep crawlin' on me?
I try to crush 'em
as soon as they land.
I have very sensitive skin,
so they tickle like crazy.
[TAIKOBO]
You also have very quick hands!
He's swatting them before
they can take effect.
His sensitive skin
is saving him!
Oh, is that the way it works?
[OHTENKUN] So, some of them
aren't affected by my bugs.
I'll need to find some
other way to eliminate them.
But first...
Hello, Yozen!
I've been expecting you.
[gasps]
[HIKO] Looks like we're at
the very bottom of the island.
Those sisters have to be close.
[VENUS] Well, if it isn't
Hiko and his little boy!
Now some might argue that
our beauty is quite wicked,
but how can it be when
it led you gentlemen
all the way down
here to find us?
Unfortunately for
you both, I'm taken.
But I adore a man who's
willing to fight for me.
Should we ignore the fact
that we just crashed
some kinda weirdo costume party?
[VENUS]
Wait! I almost forgot to ask!
How's your health, Tenka?
Are you feeling all right?
[gasps]
[QUEEN]
Look what I found!
One of Ohtenkun's
parasitic paopei!
These little guys attach
themselves to Sennin and Doshi
and suck every last drop
of their strength.
[BOTH gasp]
[VENUS laughs]
It's no costume party, honey.
There's way more than hotness
to our sexy couture!
This paopei fabric is
fashionable and functional.
It's called Mysterious Veil
and it repels any paopei
that would try to weaken us.
[TENKA] Where exactly
were you carrying those?
Just so I understand,
Tenka's sick because
of these insects?
[VENUS]
Correct.
Then please stop wasting
time and help him out.
Dad, what are you doing?
There might not be
much we can do.
Your son already has the mark
of infestation on his arm.
At this point, your best
option is going to be
defeating their creator,
Ohtenkun, himself.
However, in the meantime,
the good nurse Venus
is ordering him to take
two of these Sento extract
pills three times a day.
It's not a cure, I'm afraid,
but he should regain about
50 percent of his strength.
Figures it would be Ohtenkun.
[DOKO]
Nataku...
[DOKO groans]
I'm so sorry, but I'm not
feeling very well today
because I've come down
with a mysterious illness.
You'll have to fight without us,
but don't worry, we'll be okay.
[NATAKU]
All right.
I wasn't finished yet,
you big idiot!
Have you lost all three
of your brain cells?
I'm a sweet, adorable child!
What kind of monster would
just turn and walk away?
I guess his other
personalities are awake.
Listen up, you mindless
human paopei!
When someone says,
"Don't worry, we'll be okay,"
that means, "Worry!
We'll absolutely not be okay!"
--[DOKO yells]
--[NATAKU] Shut up.
You can take care of the
Twelve Sennin yourself.
[DOKO] Ow! There's no reason
to be cruel to someone so cute.
Just wait until I tell Taiitsu!
Oh, good grief.
[NATAKU]
This smell.
That strong Doshi is close.
But why is he here?
His last fight
nearly killed him,
so he should still be resting.
And yet, he's here
deep inside Kingo Island
and giving off a scent
that broadcasts his weakness.
[NATAKU groans]
[TAIKOBO]
So, Igo.
I know you just got here
but I have a request.
I need your help finding Nataku.
That name rings a bell.
The human paopei, right?
[TAIKOBO]
Yeah.
You two are probably the
only ones who haven't been
affected by the parasites
and can fight right now.
Knowing Ohtenkun,
he'll target you guys next.
He won't waste his time
on those of us who are dying.
So it makes the most sense
for you to join Nataku
and fight together.
All right, it's finished.
Here you go.
I modified your radar for you.
You should be able to find
Nataku's exact coordinates.
[IGO]
Thank you very much.
So, about my pay,
uh, what am I gettin'?
Huh?
[IGO]
What's that look for?
You can't get without givin'.
I just met you guys.
I'm not doin'
your deeds for free.
I need compensation.
But wouldn't working for free
make you feel more charitable?
Trust me, you're the only
one who cares about that.
Uh, here, let's see.
I definitely owe you
something special.
Behold! A Homan Sento
of the highest quality
that you can only find
once in a century!
Homan?
Oh, yeah, I know it
well. It's legendary!
I accept!
Of course you do and
I now feel very good
about our working relationship.
You're giving him
a legendary what?
[TAIKOBO]
That reminds me!
Supu!
I have an important
job for you, too.
Yeah?
[TAIKOBO chuckles]
[NATAKU grunts]
[NATAKU]
There he is.
Hey.
Ah, Nataku.
I figured you'd still
be alive and well.
You're not moving.
You must be too weak
to fight at the moment.
I'll defeat you one day
when you're at your best.
But as for right now,
go back home.
[YOZEN]
Thank you.
[NATAKU grunts]
Piggyback!
Yo!
Sorry to surprise you,
but I'm Igo who's Igo-ing
where you're Igo-ing.
[NATAKU grunts]
Get off me!
[IGO grunting]
[gasps]
[YOZEN]
We've arrived.
Kotenken.
Thank you for remembering
the scent so accurately.
Ohtenkun...
...you were a fool to think
I'd give up so easily!
Where the hell do you
think you're going?
[IGO]
That was the genius Doshi Yozen?
Why does he have horns?
[YOZEN gasps]
I don't know what
that symbol is,
but it doesn't
belong to Ohtenkun!
[YOTENKUN]
Welcome, friends.
Ohtenkun couldn't
make it, unfortunately,
but he knew you
would show up here.
He's graciously
sent the two of us
to deal with you in his stead.
[YOTENKUN]
My name is Yotenkun...
...and this is Kinko Seibo.
[IGO whistles]
[IGO] So this is the spatial
paopei I've heard so much about.
You'll die in this
multi-dimensional space,
guaranteed.
I had thought that
we'd only be facing
one member of the Juttenkun,
but it appears two have decided
to appropriate
this space together.
[NATAKU grunts]
What? See something?
What is it?
[OHTENKUN chuckling]
[YOZEN gasps]
[YOZEN]
Ohtenkun!
You destroyed everything
important to me
and now I'll make you pay!
[YOZEN]
Master.
I know the blood that flows
through me is that of a yokai ,
but...
Oh? You certainly
recovered quickly.
But you are the child
of Tsuten Kyoshu.
Wait, what did he just say?
[YOZEN]
I may be his descendant,
but you raised me as
a Doshi of Kongrong!
[BOTH gasp]
[DAKKI]
Salutations, Lady Joka.
It has been far too long
since we last saw each other.
We've been having a lively time
and there's so much to tell you!
[DAKKI]
Just look--
the Sennin World War appears to
have reached a turning point!
In other words,
things are progressing
exactly as you commanded,
so congratulations are in order!