[GENSHI grunts]
[hooves thudding]
[horse whinnies]
[TAIKOBO'S FATHER]
Bo!
Thank god, you're okay!
[TAIKOBO'S FATHER pants]
[TAIKOBO'S FATHER]
I thought I'd lost you.
Oh, Bo.
[sobs] Thank goodness.
[clock ticking]
[OHTENKUN]
So, what's it gonna be?
Big choice to make here.
[TAIKOBO grunts]
[TAIKOBO]
Don't rush me on this, please.
I happen to be a bit attached
to who I am right now, y'know.
This isn't exactly
an easy decision.
[TAIKOBO]
The person I am...
...is who my mother and
father raised me to be.
[TAIKOBO'S FATHER]
Look around, Bo.
All those people down there?
There'll come a day
when you'll protect
this village as its leader
and you'll guide those people.
Wow.
Yes, sir.
[sheep baaing]
--[WOMAN 13A] Oh? Master Ryobo?
--[chuckles]
[gasps]
Now what is the son
of our fine Kyo leader
doing out in a pasture?
I didn't expect this.
Looking after the flock, ma'am.
I'm not a little kid any longer.
I'm more than old enough
to help out and work.
[WOMAN 13A] Sure, but...
all the way out here?
And by yourself?
[horses neighing]
[TAIKOBO gasps]
[TAIKOBO]
Those are troops from Yin.
What're they...?
[TAIKOBO gasps]
The village!
[TAIKOBO]
I lost my entire clan...
...and found myself all alone.
My name is Genshi and I
have come to summon you.
It is your fate
to become a Sennin.
[TAIKOBO] My mother, father,
brother, and my little sister...
The empress killed them all!
If I agree to become a Sennin,
can I punish her for her crimes?
[TAIKOBO]
I have such fond memories
of being in the Sennin world
and training as a Doshi.
Taikobo has a great
natural talent.
In less than 30 years, he's made
truly remarkable progress.
[HAKUTSURU] Sure, but he's
become rather lazy recently.
I think that's a ploy,
because he seems to believe
that we'll try to
engage his attention
by allowing him to train
in the human world.
[FUGEN]
Hey, Bo.
Bo?
You alive?
[snoring]
[FUGEN chuckles]
[FUGEN] You've really got
a lot of growing up to do.
I'm worried about Master Genshi.
Think he'll be okay?
[TAIKOBO]
Of course he will.
Don't you trust yourself?
You're the one who made
the sleeping drug, after all.
That's true.
But I think I might've
made it a little too strong.
There's a good chance
he might be passed out
for a full week or so.
Kinda creeps me out how
you can say that so calmly.
Well, you said you wanted to see
all of the human
world you could.
We're going to need at least
that much time to do it.
True.
I wanna take in every last inch
of that big, beautiful world.
[FUGEN chuckles]
[TAIKOBO]
What?
We've done the same training!
Why do you get a
paopei and I don't?
I put in more effort?
Oh, that is a
gigantic load of crap!
[GENSHI] I leave this scroll,
the Hoshin List, in your hands.
I have no intention of letting
Dakki and her minions
continue to wreak havoc
over the human world.
[TAIKOBO]
You're right about how I felt
when I was given that list.
The first thing I thought
was "I'll show you."
[clock chiming]
[OHTENKUN]
Not to get too poetic,
but I'm the mirror that reflects
the darkness within you.
Conversely,
you're the mirror that
reflects the light within me.
[TAIKOBO]
What the hell are you saying?
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
That damned old man
you serve did this to us.
[TAIKOBO gasps]
Y'see, once upon a time,
I used to be a human
being named Oh Eki.
And this kid was special.
He had the extremely
unique ability
to split his soul
into two halves.
When Genshi Tenson
found out about this,
he promptly divided
Oh Eki's soul in two...
[OHTENKUN] ...and offered up
one half to Kingo Island.
I promise that I will
get you out of here.
I'll give you strength...
...to feed your hatred.
[grunts, gasps]
[OHTENKUN]
As if once wasn't enough,
his soul was
separated yet again.
This portion was then placed
into the body of a yokai
and became the Ohtenkun
you know today.
[TSUTEN]
Genshi Tenson... Taijo Rokun...
...Dakki... Yozen...
...Oh Eki... and Joka.
I gotta say, that was
easier than I thought.
So long as you do
exactly as you're told,
I promise everything
will work out.
Every little thing.
[clock ticking]
You do know why I have such a
deep interest in you, right?
Starting to figure it out yet?
Well, I'm not all that
surprised, to be honest.
I mean,
you do have his blood
running through your veins.
We'd be more than happy
to accept you here
as one of our own.
But if word were to get out
about what you really are
back on Kongrong,
I'm positive that would be
quite a different story indeed.
[OHTENKUN]
That's just how humans are.
[OHTENKUN] But look what
happened in the end.
Take care of Yozen... for me.
[OHTENKUN]
You sacrificed his master.
The two of us, it's our
destiny to be despised.
--And ya can't fight fate.
--[clock chimes]
[clock ticking]
[HAKUTSURU] This is Supushan,
your spirit beast.
He'll take you
wherever you need to go.
Really?
Hey, it's Taikobo, right?
As he said, I'm Supushan.
It's nice to meet ya.
--[TAIKOBO giggles] You, too!
--[SUPUSHAN chuckles]
[TAIKOBO]
First name up: Shinkohyo.
What?! Did you say Shinkohyo?
[TAIKOBO]
Hm?
This is bad!
They say he's stronger
than the Three Great
Sennin combined!
He's the strongest Doshi, rides
the strongest spirit beast,
and he's even got Raikoben,
the strongest paopei!
What?! Hold on!
They can't expect
me to fight him!
Then don't do it!
Why wake up a sleeping
dog to kill you?
[TAIKOBO]
Does this list go from
strongest to weakest
or something?
That's gotta be it, yeah.
Let's see who's at the end.
[screams]
[SHINKOHYO]
Raikoben!
No! I'm gonna dodge it!
Stay put and close
your eyes, Supu!
[clock ticking]
[gasps]
Looks like I've
stumbled upon a Sennin.
Yeah? And who's
doing the stumbling?
I'm Koh Hiko, the emperor's
military strategist,
also known as the Buseioh.
Are you on your way
to see the empress?
Yes, I am.
And for what, exactly?
I intend to defeat her.
[HIKO grunts]
Shut up. Don't just
tell anyone that!
[HIKO laughs]
Hey, sorry, man!
Most of the guys
who come through here
just wanna join up
to be her henchmen.
Now if you were one of them--
well, I would've had to kill ya.
I had a feeling about you!
I knew you weren't under the
thrall of Dakki's Temptation!
You're damn right I'm not.
I repelled her sorcery with
the sheer strength of my will.
[HIKO]
Listen, Taikobo.
I had this feeling
when I met you--
that you could
actually do some good.
I didn't rescue you
for your sake.
I saved your life for
the sake of this world.
You need to stay alive.
There's no room for weakness.
[clock ticking]
[TAIKOBO sighs]
You'll do just about anything
to avoid conflict, huh?
Sure, but I could say
the same for you, y'know.
I mean, that's why
we get along so well.
Although...
...I can't shake the feeling
you'll devote yourself
to combat someday.
You do have a shining blade deep
inside your heart, after all.
But when that day comes,
I promise I'll be
right beside you.
The least I can do
is offer you that.
[TAIKOBO] Fugen... you were
right about everything...
...but I don't want
to hurt anyone.
I wish I could create a
safe world without fighting.
But--is it even possible
to avoid it?
[TAIKOBO] What Dakki did to you
has really led me to thinking...
There's no way I can
defeat her on my own.
So, it's time to
find some allies.
[TAIKOBO] We'll gather up enough
new friends for our own army.
[clock ticking]
[LI SEI]
He's found me! That's my son!
Nataku!
He's a human paopei!
[LI SEI] The inhuman child
that burst forth from the mass
was born into our world with
paopei attached to his body.
Despite his true nature,
my wife never failed
to treat Nataku within anything
but the love of a mother.
If we can make Nataku our ally,
that alone would give us the
strength of a thousand men!
Our best chance for that
is to smooth things over
so he feels like he owes us one.
[sighs]
[TAIKOBO]
Dafuba!
[pants]
What's the matter?
Having second thoughts
about using the Kenkonken?
Hey, you're welcome to do so,
but I'll just change
its direction again
and who knows
where it'll end up.
And if that kind of thing
were to actually happen,
who can say who'll
get hit with it?
You might end up
killing your own mother!
Paopei have their own
limitations, ya know!
And your Kenkonken
can't beat my Dashinben!
[laughs]
[SUPUSHAN]
If you're gonna be a hero,
please don't act like a villain.
My mother has asked me
to spare Li Sei's life,
so I won't kill him.
Good.
I think you're making
the right call on that.
And whatever your body is now,
it honestly doesn't matter.
The three of you
are still a family
and nothing will change that.
[gasps]
[INSHI giggles]
[clock ticking]
[TAIKOBO]
Yozen!
All right, ya got me.
Seems my reputation's
worked against me.
[YOZEN] Kudos on seeing
through my disguise.
Well done, Taikobo.
I'm exactly who you say--
Yozen of Mount Gyokusen
in the Kongrong Mountains,
student of Gyokutei
Shinjin of Kinkdado.
[gasps]
[TAIKOBO] That's about the
best news I've ever heard!
I'm more than happy
to let a genius like you
do all the hard work!
[YOZEN]
Not so fast.
I only agreed on one condition.
[TAIKOBO]
And that is...?
[YOZEN] That I first
be allowed to test you
to find out if you're genuinely
worthy of my assistance
on this crucial mission.
If you fail to live up
to my expectations--
well, I'll simply have to
carry out the Hoshin Project
in your place...
...and defeat Dakki on my own.
Seriously?
[GENSHI]
I've considered many factors
and what is most essential is
that he has the ability to lead.
[HAKUTSURU]
Hm?
[GENSHI]
He doesn't need to be a genius.
All that matters is he's capable
of unifying his subordinates,
caring for the people, and
inspiring others to do good.
[YOZEN]
Well done, Taikobo.
Tricking me to
save those people--
it was a true stroke of genius.
You aced the test.
Ya hear that, Supu?
The genius said my acting
was a stroke of genius!
Yeah, you're a Doshi,
but you're greatest strength
might be deception.
[clock ticking]
So that guy's the
illustrious Taikobo, eh?
Yep.
Heard plenty of stories about
him up in the Sennin world.
I feel pretty lucky
that I get the chance
to actually see him fight.
Taikobo!
I'll help you
take these guys down.
Thank you.
Hey! You're all together!
--[BUKICHI] Hey, Master!
--[TAIKOBO laughs]
[TAIKOBO] Now then.
Nataku, Yozen, Li Sei, Dokoson,
and Sengyoku--you'll all
return to Kongrong with us.
The Buseioh and his family--
you guys'll stay here
in the human world.
[ALL gasp]
C'mon, Taikobo! You know
this is no time to leave--
[TAIKOBO]
Quiet, Tenka!
I'm pretty sure you know
better than anyone
why I'm ordering you
to sit this one out.
Tsk. [groans]
[TAIKOBO]
It was inevitable.
For the sake of those
we wish to protect,
and for the paths we believe in,
we couldn't avoid confrontation.
I must overcome you at any cost.
No matter what happens...
...I can't let you win.
You are the Doshi
Taikobo, correct?
[TAIKOBO groans]
[BUNCHU]
Hm. I'm surprised you can move.
[TAIKOBO]
Nobody's dyin'.
I won't let you kill them.
I won't!
[YOZEN groans, gasps]
[YOZEN]
Taikobo.
He's almost dead
and he's protecting us
with a wall of wind.
[YOZEN] Honestly,
you really do amaze me.
[TAIKOBO]
I will change it.
I'll make a world
safe for humans--
a world free of
Sennin and Doshi.
[coughs]
[BUNCHU] You used your paopei
until you coughed up blood?
[BUNCHU] I can't let Seiki
have one as great as you.
[clock ticking]
[OHTENKUN chuckles]
[TAIKOBO gasps]
Everything that
I've ever done...
Everything that makes me me...
Am I just supposed to
throw it all away?
[clock ticking]
[SHINKOHYO]
So, Dakki.
I think it's time
to come clean with me.
Tell me the name
of your backer--
the one known as the
"Signpost of History."
[SHINKOHYO] Kokutenko here
keeps on bugging me
to find out who she really is.
But what am I supposed
to tell the poor cat?
I mean, the only
information I have
is this "Signpost
of History" business.
It's Joka.
[SHINKOHYO]
Joka?
You don't say.
Interesting.
[DAKKI]
Your turn, Shinkohyo.
Go on and tell me
just how much you know.
To be perfectly frank,
I'm pretty sure
I know everything.
But most of it is
rumors and speculation
so I can't speak with
any degree of certainty.
[SHINKOHYO]
Joka.
A name unfamiliar to
most people in this world.
[JOKA]
You will hear me, man.
I will imbue you
with great power,
and with that power,
you will create a new
empire known as Yin.
[DAKKI gasps]
You're...
[SHINKOHYO] There's no denying
that you were shocked,
but somehow still able
to instantly infer
what it was before you.
Not to mention clever enough
to say something that
piqued Joka's interest.
At long last, we finally meet.
[JOKA]
Woman.
Would you care to make
an agreement with me?
I will give you power surpassing
even that of a Sennin.
In return, you will assist me
in recovering my body.
[SHINKOHYO] At some point, Joka
said she wanted to destroy Yin.
So first you seduced
Emperor Chu
and left the nation
to fall into chaos,
making its decline
appear natural.
[clock chimes]
[SHINKOHYO] And now, the world
seems to be turning out
exactly how you
and Joka want it.
But... I just can't
shake this feeling
that you're on the verge of
doing something cataclysmic.
And I don't think I'm
overestimating you on this.
I know you.
You're willing to
make a sacrifice.
[GENSHI]
Who might you be?
[OH EKI] I've been waiting
for you, Genshi Tenson.
Nice to meet you.