[TAIKOBO]
Supu...
I don't know what to do.
I don't wanna have to
make any sacrifices.
But still...
Is it even possible to
create a human world
free of Sennin without it?
To see this through...
...it could very likely mean
losing the Sennin world.
Am I really capable of that?
Am I, Supu?
[OHTENKUN]
Listen up, all of you.
The Kongrong guys succeeded
in taking out Totenkun.
[BOTH gasp]
[ENTENKUN]
Totenkun's dead?
[CHOTENKUN] Well, Ohtenkun,
what the hell do we do now?
You need me to
spell it out for you?
[YOTENKUN] This goes against
everything we've heard.
Are the Kongrong Sennin
really that powerful?
[OHTENKUN]
No. Judging by all parameters,
you guys are stronger than
they could ever hope to be!
We can't keep losing like this.
So the only thing we can
do about it is kill them,
even if it means losing your
own life in the process.
Got that?
[stomach growls]
[TAIKOBO]
What's the matter, Supu?
You getting hungry?
[SUPUSHAN] Well, we have been
flying around Kingo Island
nonstop for two
days straight now.
Of course I'm hungry.
You must be, too, Master.
[SUPUSHAN sniffing]
[SUPUSHAN] Mm? Are those
peaches that I smell?
I'm onto you.
You've got peaches hidden
in your pocket, don't you?
[TAIKOBO gasps]
Yeah, but you can't have 'em!
They're emergency rations!
This is an emergency.
I'm starving!
[FUGEN]
Hey, Bo, by the way--
No, get back! You
can't have them either!
[FUGEN]
About Doko Tenson's pupil, Igo.
Do you have any idea when he's
supposed to join up with us?
[TAIKOBO]
I'm actually not sure.
The one thing I know about
him is he's super lazy.
Oh, yeah?
The two of you should get
along rather well, at least.
[TAIKOBO chuckles]
[TAIKOBO]
Just as I thought.
There's a whole grove of
peach trees over there!
C'mon, Bo.
Are you really gonna
steal all those peaches?
Shouldn't you at least
do the right thing
and leave a little
bit of money behind?
I don't have any!
You could always try
working for them.
If I have to work,
I'd rather just starve.
Or... I guess I could work
on stealing those peaches
and not starve!
[cackles]
In that case, I guess there's
really no other choice.
[TAIKOBO]
Grab 'em! Eat all ya can!
[TAIKOBO gasps]
We got busted
and ended up having to
do a lot of manual labor
to pay off that debt.
Jeez, Master.
A Doshi stealing peaches?
That's stooping pretty low.
Uh--yeah, I don't exactly
remember it happening that way.
[FUGEN gasps]
[FUGEN]
Look at this.
Is it a distortion in space?
It looks like there's
something in this area.
[TAIKOBO]
What is it?
Wait, do you think
it's the place
where Bunchu is camped out?
The control core?
Well... I can't be certain.
The core... Oh, damn it!
[SUPUSHAN, FUGEN]
Huh?
What's wrong? You
forget something?
Yeah, there's a message
that I meant to send
to the other teams.
Hey. Hey!
Mayday, mayday!
Allies of Kongrong,
do you read me?
This is Taikobo. Do you copy?
This is Taikobo.
[TAIKOBO]
There's a core deep within Kingo
and that's where Bunchu's
giving his orders from.
Only problem, we don't know
exactly where the core is.
However, if you manage
to find it on your own...
...I forbid you from
attacking Bunchu.
In order for this plan to work,
we must first take out the
Juttenkun that surround him.
Violations will not
be tolerated. Over!
Y'know, Bo, you seem to
be a bit on edge today.
What? I'm not on edge.
I'm perfectly calm.
[FUGEN]
Tell me what's wrong.
[TAIKOBO sighs]
I guess there's no use
trying to hide it from you.
You're right. I'm a big
ball of nerves right now.
Bunchu, Ohtenkun, the Juttenkun,
and Tsuten Kyoshu...
They're extremely dangerous
and I doubt we'll get through
this without any losses.
Just try to calm down.
There's no need for you
to shoulder this burden
all on your own.
No, it's all on me.
[FUGEN chuckles]
As stubborn as ever.
It's almost reassuring.
That's not a bad start.
It didn't really
take us too long
to wipe out our first Juttenkun.
So what now, Dad?
Who do we go after next?
We find Bunchu, of course.
It's strange.
I've already turned my
back on the land I served
for so many years,
but I had hoped that things
would never come to this
between the two of us.
[HIKO] I'm just not sure...
if I have it in me to kill him.
[BUNCHU] Kingo Island's
radar may be sufficient
to properly locate it.
There you are, fox.
I found you.
[DAKKI]
Very impressive, Bunchu.
You've certainly got some
powerful friends on your side.
As much chaos as you've caused,
I'll even admit that I'm
impressed with you as well.
Therefore, in order to
demonstrate the lengths
of my respect, I will
finish you off quickly.
[DAKKI]
No you won't.
I'm not ready to die just yet.
I still have one goal
I must achieve.
[BUNCHU gasps]
Ta-ta for now.
I'll fight you as many times
as it takes to finally kill you.
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
Hey! Look over there, Master!
[FUGEN, TAIKOBO]
Huh?
[SUPUSHAN]
There's a tree!
And it's loaded with
tasty-looking fruit!
It's a miracle from heaven!
We won't starve and die!
Hold it, Supu!
Uh--what's the big idea?
Fugen, is that it?
The distortion I had noticed
earlier--that's where it is.
[TAIKOBO]
Figures.
It's probably an
entrance to Juzetsujin.
[TAIKOBO] I'll jump down
first and investigate.
[TAIKOBO grunts]
[SUPUSHAN whimpering]
Fruit looks kinda weird.
Very suspicious.
[gasps] Oh, my god!
Hey! Don't be so
selfish, Master!
--[TAIKOBO grunts]
--[SUPUSHAN groans]
Keep your distance,
Supu, it's dangerous!
Quit lyin' to me!
You're eating it!
You just wanna keep it
all for yourself! [groans]
Uh...?
[TAIKOBO]
Uh? What's happening?
[TAIKOBO, SUPUSHAN scream]
[FUGEN]
So it was a trap after all.
Guess I have no choice here.
Might as well jump in with them.
A field of flowers.
Oh, hey, you got
trapped, too, huh?
They sure are pretty.
[SUPUSHAN gasps]
Why are the flowers wilting?
[ENTENKUN] The lives of flowers
are fleeting and short.
They achieve the pinnacle of
their glory in the warm season,
and when the cold comes
rolling around, they die.
[ENTENKUN]
And I know this cycle well.
I'm Entenkun, and I control this
paopei dimension, Kanpyojin.
In fact, I personally
usher in the frigid cold
that smothers
this land in death.
Those who enter this
space will soon become
acquainted with doom.
Everything wilts and dies here.
You see this thing?
What is this gross,
morbidly poetic creature?
I'm guessing it's
one of the Juttenkun.
[ENTENKUN]
Ah, the first snow.
It's snowing?
There's ice bursting
from the ground!
[TAIKOBO, SUPUSHAN scream]
[ENTENKUN laughing]
He's got the power
to control ice!
[ENTENKUN sighs]
[ENTENKUN]
Oh, dear.
Have they been buried
so quickly and easily?
[ENTENKUN]
Huh?
Hang back behind me, you two.
As much as I loathe fighting,
I can handle this one.
Save your strength.
Considering the bigger fights
you've still got ahead of you,
you're going to need
all of the energy
that you can possibly muster.
[ENTENKUN] They melted
right through my ice,
which can only mean...
...one of them's wielding
a fire-type paopei.
[FUGEN]
You know, furball,
fighting's right at the top of
the list of things I hate.
Why don't we just
talk this thing out?
If we can find some
understanding,
we're bound to come up
with a better solution
than killing one another.
[ENTENKUN]
What a foolish notion.
People and yokai are
destined to kill each other.
And that conflict will continue
until it's determined
who will rule the world.
[FUGEN]
You really believe that?
Well, for what it's worth,
I intend to keep trying
to persuade you.
How's this?
If you still refuse to listen
after I make three attempts,
then I'll assume
that understanding
is completely off the table.
[TAIKOBO]
C'mon, Fugen!
What're you blathering about?
I think it's quite clear.
The little freak has
already tried to kill us!
Be serious here!
[FUGEN]
Oh, I'm very serious.
[gasps]
I can't argue with the
facts of the matter.
People and yokai
are in conflict.
But... I believe
that can change.
We just need to take the time
to understand each other.
Will you take a look around you?
He's got us trapped
in his death dimension!
Perhaps, but this is simply
the way I do things.
Fine, get us killed!
Got a gift for you.
[TAIKOBO] You've never
wavered from who you are.
[ENTENKUN] Taikobo's strategic
flexibility is impressive.
From my brief observation,
his ingenuity appears to exceed
that of the Twelve Sennin.
[gasps]
[TAIKOBO screams]
[ENTENKUN] Your open-mindedness
truly is a treasure,
but... pursuing that treasure
can often lead to
a mortal downfall.
[TAIKOBO]
Supu!
Dodge them! Watch out!
[SUPUSHAN]
I'm trying, all right?
[BOTH gasping]
Fugen!
I thought you said you
were gonna handle this?!
'Cuz now would be the time!
[BOTH screaming]
[FUGEN]
I've got this, Bo. Hang on.
Initiating Forced Phase Change.
Whoa!
[ENTENKUN]
What? The ice!
This paopei of mine,
Taikyoku Fuin,
is able to manipulate
all chemical elements.
Turning ice into steam is about
the easiest thing I can do.
At one atmospheric pressure,
water becomes ice below
zero degrees Celsius
and vapor above 100 degrees.
My paopei broke apart
the water molecules
that had solidified into ice,
releasing them into
a cloud of steam.
Do you understand now?
I control the molecules
that form your ice,
which means that
you can't defeat me
no matter how hard you try.
So come on.
Let's put a stop to
this meaningless fight.
[ENTENKUN chuckles]
[ENTENKUN]
It would seem you've confused
threats with persuasion.
And your point is pure delusion!
[BOTH gasp]
[SUPUSHAN]
I'm freakin' freezin' to death!
[ENTENKUN] You assume
I'm just some simple Sennin
who controls ice.
I'm a Juttenkun, you fool!
I'll pluck out that silver
tongue of yours and sell it!
[TAIKOBO] This just might be
the nastiest blizzard ever!
[ENTENKUN] The simple
truth of this situation
is that you can never defeat me.
You create nothing of your own.
You can only muster
a defensive response,
like turning my ice
into water or steam.
But I'm eager to watch you
fight off this blizzard
with that paopei.
C'mon, let's see what it can do!
As clever as you are,
I'm sure you can figure
out what will happen.
[sighs]
You're pretty clever yourself,
just as I'd expect from
one of the Juttenkun.
Shut up and do
something, will you?
Quit talking and do whatever
you did earlier with this snow!
You really think I should?
Yeah, I do! And hurry up
before we all freeze!
[FUGEN]
All right.
[TAIKOBO, SUPUSHAN gasp]
You pulled it off!
You got rid of
the freezing cold!
I can feel my face again!
Oh, no.
[BOTH scream]
What the hell? It feels like the
steam is freezing to my body!
[SUPUSHAN, TAIKOBO whining]
[sighs] I'm pretty
sure you'll survive.
[ENTENKUN] Let me tell you
something Ohtenkun said to me.
[OHTENKUN]
I want you to consider
why the Juttenkun are losing.
Think about it long and hard.
[ENTENKUN] He said our
three fallen comrades
succumbed to their arrogance
and that's why their
souls were released.
Their own pride did them in.
They were convinced
they couldn't lose
and that's precisely
why they did.
I've learned from their mistakes
and I won't underestimate
my enemies!
It seems we've come down to
a barometric race of sorts,
and from the looks of it,
my blizzard greatly exceeds the
speed at which you can melt ice.
I will happily watch
your life plummet
with your body temperature
until you're nothing
but a frozen statue.
[sighs]
[ENTENKUN]
Huh?
Clearly, there was some
miscommunication here.
My paopei does turn
ice into steam
and I guess I let you think
that's all it's capable of,
but there's far more
to it than that.
[ENTENKUN]
Huh...?
[ENTENKUN] Wha--what
did you do to my snow?!
[BOTH whimper, gasp]
It all just vanished!
[sighs]
Nothing remaining but a
warm, pleasant breeze.
If you want to know
what just happened,
my paopei took your ice
then promptly split it
into hydrogen and oxygen,
so it all vanished into the air.
You should've listened to me.
I told you that my paopei
manipulates chemical elements.
Yeah. I knew that.
[SUPUSHAN] Like you remembered
all that stuff. Sure.
[FUGEN] I really didn't
want to go to these lengths,
but you gave me no choice.
I'm sorry.
[FUGEN] And now, there's
nothing left you can do.
So, we've reached the end.
Might as well talk.
[ENTENKUN gasps]
Hey, no reason to be afraid.
See?
[BOTH gasp]
[ENTENKUN]
Hm?
As proof that I have no
intention of harming you,
I won't use my paopei anymore.
Why are you always like this?
That's just so freakin' naive!
Calm down, Bo.
Why are you so angry?
[TAIKOBO]
What's wrong with you?!
[ENTENKUN] You... To make
a peace offering like this?
[ENTENKUN]
You're an absolute fool!
[SUPUSHAN, TAIKOBO scream]
[TAIKOBO]
I knew it!
[ENTENKUN gasps]
I'm sorry.
This is goodbye.
[ENTENKUN]
Hey! What's it doing?
[TAIKOBO]
Whoa! What is that?
[SUPUSHAN] Did his paopei
just self destruct?
[FUGEN] I programmed it
to automatically do that
if he tried to attack us
with his ice again.
If a large amount of
water were to appear
within a 37 meter radius,
the water would be broken down
and the hydrogen would
be used to make tritium...
[FUGEN]
...which would then result in
a very small-scale
nuclear fusion.
Uh, wait, nuclear fusion?
Glad you chose the
most dangerous option.
To not understand each other--
it truly is a tragedy.
[DAKKI]
The human world is quickly
approaching a crossroads.
It's just about time
for you to make your
first grand appearance.
Please come forward and offer
us your much needed guidance.