[phone ringing]
[NAKANO grunts]
[NAKANO sighs]
It's morning?
Hm?
[NAKANO]
No one's here.
That was a crazy dream.
Must've been pretty
tired last night.
[SENKO]
Oh, you're awake?
[screams]
[NAKANO]
Whoa! You can float?
Good morning,
did you sleep okay?
[NAKANO]
Uhh...
Mm?
[NAKANO]
Nope, still not a dream.
Uh, good morning to you, too.
You're awake so early.
That's impressive considering
how late you worked.
I imagine that must
be hard on your body.
Oh. Maybe.
I dunno.
It's been like this for a while.
[yawns]
I don't know, it seems to me
that your body requires
a great deal more sleep.
[NAKANO]
Nah, I'm used to it.
That's quite unfortunate.
Heh. There's no need to worry.
[NAKANO grunts]
[groaning]
[SENKO] Oh, apparently there
is every reason to worry!
If you're struggling this much,
then perhaps you should
stay home today.
[NAKANO] Look, it's not that I
don't wanna stay home and sleep
more, but I have a full-time
job, so I've gotta go to work.
Okay, then I'll make you
breakfast before you go!
[NAKANO]
No thanks.
I'm running late as it is. Bye.
[SENKO]
Uh. But hold on!
Uh, have a good day!
Uh...
Goodness, he's so stubborn.
I need to figure out
a way to get him to
slow down a little bit.
[SENKO]
That's it!
[KOENJI gasping]
[SENKO humming]
When you get home tonight, I'm
going to pamper you like crazy!
[NAKANO] Wait, I just realized
that I left Senko at home
all by herself.
Will she be okay?
[SENKO] All right, then.
Let's start by tidying up!
There, that should do the trick!
Is that a futon for guests?
And he has a full
set of dinnerware
and lots of cooking utensils.
Even though his current
lifestyle doesn't lend itself
to this idea, there
was a point in time
where he believed he'd play
the part of the gracious host.
Don't worry, from now on
I'm going to put all
of you to good use!
Okay! Less leaning,
more cleaning!
[SENKO] First we start
by dusting off the walls.
And then we follow that up
with a nice, good sweeping!
Goodbye, Mister Dust!
[sighs]
Scrubbity-dubbity-
rubbity-dubbity!
[laughs]
Everything is squeaky clean!
Now all that's left is dinner.
For tonight's menu,
I'll make some inari!
After all, he used to like it.
[SENKO]
I'll make a whole bunch!
I really hope he can
come home early today.
[NAKANO sneezes]
[MITAKA]
Nakano. Nakano!
What?
You're being summoned, man.
Uh?
Uhh...
[exhales]
[sighs] Another terrible
day at work.
Wonder what Senko's been up to.
[SENKO laughs]
Yay! You're finally back!
You must have had to stay
late at the office again.
It's good to be home.
Well, I'll go heat you up
some miso soup right away!
That sounds nice.
[NAKANO]
Thanks for dinner!
[SENKO laughs]
[NAKANO]
That was wonderful.
You sound very refreshed.
To be honest, I normally
just take a shower.
Cleaning the tub
seems like a hassle
when you live by yourself.
[SENKO] I love how you
can heat the water here
with just a button.
[NAKANO]
Heh. Yeah.
I'm sorry you had to spend
your day cleaning my place.
[SENKO]
Why are you apologizing?
[NAKANO]
Well...
I just feel bad that you're
working so hard to spoil me.
Don't you remember?
I said I'm doing all these
things because I want to.
All right.
[SENKO] Next time I'll
scrub your back for you!
I can manage that much.
[SENKO]
What's the matter?
Do you have some water
stuck in your ear?
Well, yeah, that's part of it.
But my boss also chewed
me out at work today,
so there's that, too.
Sounds like some
kind of weird torture.
I'm gonna try cleaning it.
Huh?
Let's see... Where are
the cotton swabs?
Mm?
Hey, wha--?
Come here. I'll give those
ears a proper cleaning.
[NAKANO] Mm. Yeah,
I'm good, thank you though.
[SENKO]
What?! You're "good"?
You'd reject a masterful
ear cleaner such as myself?
No sir, you are most
certainly not good!
Now I can die a happy man!
[NAKANO]
"Master ear cleaner"?
Is that even like a real thing?
There's no reason
to be afraid over
something as simple
as an ear cleaning!
I'm not afraid, I just think
I can clean my own ears.
And having you do it...
makes me feel kinda weird.
Please tell me why!
Uh. Because, y'know,
ears are just...
[gasps] Ears are...?
[SENKO]
Okay. Let's make a deal.
Grant me permission
to clean out your ears,
and in return, I shall
let you touch mine.
No way! You'd really allow
me to touch your ears?
Yes. I would.
Just a bit, though.
Man Senko, you can read me
like an open book.
Yes, almost like
a picture book.
Then it's settled!
Come on. Lie down on my lap.
Trust me, you're in
for quite the treat.
[NAKANO]
Whoa there.
Kinda feels like I'm wading
into criminal waters.
She's 800 years old...
She's 800 years old.
Side note.
I still haven't figured out why
she's doing all this for me.
'Kay, I'm about to begin!
[NAKANO]
Oh, wow.
I never knew having my ears
touched could feel so good.
Let's start by working
our way into this groove.
[sighs]
Now, dipping down
ever so gently.
[NAKANO]
She's so close.
I can hear her breathing.
[exhales]
[sighs]
[NAKANO]
I feel the warmth of her lap.
The soft fluff of her fur.
Ah... That's such
a relaxing sound.
Stay nice and still.
There we go.
[NAKANO]
Think I must be...
...in paradise.
Ahh...
[NAKANO] I wish I could just
stay right here forever.
Please turn so I can get
to the other side.
[NAKANO]
Sure.
[NAKANO humming]
[NAKANO]
The way she hums is so soothing.
Just like a lullaby.
I feel like I'm
a little kid again.
I think I might fall
asleep right here...
What's going on?!
If I didn't know any better I'd
say that you were the one
pampering me just now!
[ANCESTOR]
What's wrong with that?
[SENKO] Everything!
I came here to help you
and you completely turned
the tables on me!
[ANCESTOR laughs] Do you even
know how adorable you are?
[SENKO grumbles]
[ANCESTOR]
Don't fret about it.
Having you around brightens
my mood. That's help enough.
[SENKO grumbles]
[gasps]
You up?
Did I fall asleep again?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
It's no problem!
All are powerless
before my masterful
ear cleaning technique.
You look like a kid
when you sleep, it's cute.
[NAKANO]
Uh, cute?
But, wait...
[NAKANO]
Was that a dream?
It was so vivid.
And somehow, it felt familiar.
Hey listen, Senko.
This is a weird question,
but have we ever met before?
[SENKO]
Hm. That is an odd question.
I can't remember the face
of every child I've seen.
[NAKANO]
Mm.
[SENKO]
So I guess... it is possible.
We may have met sometime before.
I see.
Oh, right! Now it's my turn
to touch your ears, Senko!
[SENKO] Aw. I was sort
of hoping you'd forget.
Just keep in mind
that they're delicate!
Uh-huh.
So make sure that you're
gentle with them!
Sure.
Really gentle!
Can do.
As gentle as gentle can be!
[NAKANO]
Yeah, yeah, I'll be gentle.
[inhales]
Well?! What on earth
are you waiting for?!
Oh. Uh. I'm sorry.
Okay. Here goes.
[SENKO squeaks]
I, uh, uh, uh.
[NAKANO] It's a whole
different kinda fluff.
Even softer than the tail.
Feels like I'm wearing
mittens made of clouds.
I never wanna take them off.
[SENKO]
Mm... Okay. Listen.
You had better control yourself.
I wonder what the inside
of them feels like.
Huh?
[SENKO screams]
[NAKANO] I'm so sorry!
I really am, please forgive me!
I regret my actions deeply.
And I accept full
responsibility,
is there anything I can do
to make it up to you?
Don't be silly. You know what?
I think it's about time
you went to bed.
Yeah, okay.
Or, wait, it seems a
little early actually.
Well it's not!
Go to sleep now and you
won't be so tired tomorrow!
You need to get eight hours
of sleep each night!
There's no way I can
sleep that much.
I'll just end up late for work.
Most nights I sleep for about
four hours and it's fine.
Only four hours,
you must be kidding.
There's no way. Are you
even a human being?
[NAKANO]
More so than you, at least.
[SENKO]
It's become painfully apparent
that you don't get enough rest.
You need to take care
of your body,
it's the only one you have.
[NAKANO] I know that.
I'm just so busy these days.
[sighs] Do you mean to keep
this up till you get sick?
I'm not having it!
If you're busy, that's all
the more reason to sleep.
Exhaustion hinders your ability
to work, which forces you
to spend more time working,
which makes you more tired!
I know some pro sleepers.
If anyone needs me,
tell them I'll be napping
for the next few centuries.
The best of them can sleep
for a few hundred years!
Something tells me that
these friends of yours
don't have day jobs.
Also, I should mention
I've been having insomnia
lately. Not sure I can sleep.
[SENKO laughs]
That shouldn't be an issue now.
I hung this out in the sun.
It's like a whole
new blanket now.
[gasps]
[gasping]
[laughs]
Wow! It's so fluffy and it
smells just like sunshine!
I'm so happy.
Thanks, I haven't had time
to hang it myself in ages.
It does make a difference.
I'm drifting off already.
[SENKO]
Of course you are.
[yawns]
Come to think of it, I'm
pretty tuckered out myself.
Think I'll turn
in for the night.
[gasps]
I'm gonna go ahead and turn
these lights off, kay?
[SENKO]
M'kay. Goodnight. Sweet dreams.
Uh...
[NAKANO] Jeez, even the
way she sleeps is cute.
Little floofball. I wanna jam
my face right in her fur.
[NAKANO] Eh, better not.
She looks so peaceful.
I'll just go to bed.
[NAKANO grunts]
[NAKANO]
I am such trash.
Making a demigod sleep on
the floor while I'm in bed.
That's beyond bad luck!
I may as well attack
a mirror factory.
[NAKANO]
Hey, uh, Senko?
Yeah, what's goin' on?
I'm sorry, I didn't
realize that you'd--
What the--? Are those fireballs?
S'just fox-fire.
[NAKANO]
Fox-fire...?
Ya havin' trouble
fallin' asleep?
I'm okay, I was just
worried about you
on that little cushion; it
can't be very comfortable.
I've got guest futons in the
closet, let me pull one out.
Oh, I get it now.
Is this your attempt at
being subtle? Honestly.
If you wished for us
to sleep together,
you should've just said so.
Now go to sleep, okay?
Um, not to be rude,
but that really isn't
what I was getting at.
You're such a cute little baby.
Come on, silly,
don't be shy now.
This is perfectly innocent.
After all, you're just
like a kid to me.
[NAKANO]
Uhh...
Yeah. Ya know,
it still feels pretty weird to
hear that from a little girl.
Oh, please! Try to remember
that I've been around for
several human lifetimes.
[NAKANO]
Whelp. I guess this is better
than letting her
sleep on the floor.
Uh.
[NAKANO] Pudgy little cheeks.
Fluffy tufts of fur.
Who knew that a god
could be so cute?
And fragile, from
the look of her.
This is just too much.
How can I sleep like this?
Uh.
[NAKANO]
Huh. Is this... better?
Can't really say for sure.
[NAKANO]
Okay, yeah.
This is nice.
[SENKO]
Eat it!
[NAKANO] I'd love to,
but I don't have time.
Then make time!
I'm not letting you leave until
you've had some breakfast,
and that's final!
[NAKANO] All right! All right!
I'll have some, thanks.
[SENKO laughs]
Are you ready to
depart for work?
Yeah, almost.
You're a great guy.
Do you know that?
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'll try.
See ya soon, and thanks
for breakfast.
Of course!
Have a good day at work, okay?
Bye! Make sure and be careful!
Come back home
as swiftly as you can!
[KOENJI growls]
How many friggin' ways
are there to say goodbye?
[SENKO]
Super Senko Time!
Hi there, welcome back home.
You've had a long day.
I'm sure you must be tired.
Why don't you lay down on my lap
and let me have a look at you?
We'll see if we can't get
rid of all that work-stress.
Would you like me
to clean your ears?
Don't be nervous.
I know what I'm doing.
Just settle down
and enjoy yourself.
We'll start with this side.
I hope it doesn't
tickle too much.
[exhales]
Good! Looks like
we're all done here.
That felt pretty nice, right?
Mm-hm! Glad to hear it!
I can help clean your ears again
anytime you'd like me to.
With that being said,
it's still important
that we take care not to
over-indulge ourselves.
So it's best if we wait a bit
before we do this again.
Well, it's time for
bed now, okay?
Good night and sweet dreams!