[SENKO humming]
Today's special
report is all about
must-try gratin from
popular restaurants!
That looks good!
Hey, you need to hurry up
or you're going to be
late for work. Uh?
What's this TV program about?
Uh, food? It just came on
and I got a bit distracted.
So, what do you guys think?
Here's the famous cheese gratin
that everyone's
been raving about!
Many refer to this dish as
"the mouth's paradise"!
She's making cheese gratin?
[NAKANO]
Yeah...
[REPORTER]
Mm! When you take a bite,
the melted cheese
covers your taste buds
and wraps them in a warm,
delicious hug!
Crap! The time!
Shoot, I gotta go!
I'm sorry, Senko!
I'll see you later tonight.
Bye, have a good day!
[NAKANO]
You, too!
[REPORTER] And here's the
next restaurant's gratin!
Check out this spread! Oh!
With all that melty cheese,
it's practically screaming
to be devoured!
That's very interesting.
[KOENJI] Huh? You wanna learn
how to make cheese gratin?
Yes. I've never made one,
so I'm not familiar
with the recipe.
Well, it's really not
that difficult.
Even I know how to do it.
[gasping]
I had no idea you were
capable of cooking Jasuko!
Yeah, a little.
So how come you've never made
anything for me, then?
It's a pain, so I avoid
it as much as possible.
Lazy!
[KOENJI] The pot doesn't get
to call the kettle black, Shiro.
[laughs]
[KOENJI]
You surprise me, Senko.
I kind of thought you'd already
know how to make gratin.
Seeing as you're such
a great cook and all.
[SENKO] Unfortunately,
I don't know much about
western-style food. Japanese
cuisine is my specialty.
Yeah, but nobody can
top your cooking--
it's the best in
the whole entire world!
Please, that's an exaggeration.
It's not, though!
Your food is super delicious.
Thanks for making it.
[SENKO]
You don't have to thank me,
it's something I
truly enjoy doing.
And that's one of the
things I love about you.
Okay. I'm going to help
you cook up some gratin!
Sound good?
As in right now?
But aren't you too busy?
[KOENJI] Yeah, but I have
a bit of artist's block.
So shifting gears might help.
Thank you!
Perhaps I could
help you as well.
[SENKO gasps]
You really mean it?
Thank you so much.
This means a lot to me.
I wonder how many hundreds
of years it's been
since Shiro has offered
to help me with anything.
Now that's an exaggeration!
[KOENJI laughs]
"Hundreds of years," really?
You guys have the
wackiest sense of humor.
Okay. Right! I'll go start
setting everything up.
I think I may already know
the answer to this question,
but does Koenji think you're
cosplaying as well, Shiro?
Of course she does!
Of course.
And the last thing
we need is butter.
All righty! I think
that about covers it.
I'm unfamiliar with a great
deal of these ingredients.
What's this strange food called?
Uh? Oh, those are just
some macaroni noodles.
[crunching]
Yucky, these taste terrible,
I advise against using them.
Yeah, you're supposed to cook
them before you eat them.
You really can't eat macaroni
when it's raw like that.
You should have told me
that sooner, Jasuko!
You cook it by boiling
it in hot water.
Cook it, huh?
Well then, leave the controlling
of the flame to me!
[KOENJI]
Huh?
[SENKO]
Hm?
Aw, that's adorable, I used
to play pretend like that
back when I was a little kid.
I'd be shooting invisible flames
all over the place super
hero-style, it was fun!
[SENKO gasping]
I'll turn it up just a bit.
[laughs] Wow, you've really
perfected your act,
you almost had me fooled
there for a second!
You're always so fun
and care-free, Shiro.
Yes, she's very playful.
It's finally boiling!
Okay, great!
Now just go ahead and pour
that macaroni in there.
As you wish.
Don't worry,
I'll keep the fire going!
Sounds like she's got
everything under control.
[yelps]
[SENKO]
Uhh...
[KOENJI]
All right, now we can move on
to the next part of the recipe.
Chop the onions
into small slices.
And cut the bacon
into thin strips.
Melt the butter in the pan.
Then add the flour and milk,
mixing them in slowly.
Right.
Oh, and I need to
stir it frequently,
so it doesn't get any odd lumps.
[SENKO hums]
Uh... She's so skilled,
does she even need me here?
Is this the right consistency?
You bet, it's perfect!
The next thing you wanna do
is add in the onions, bacon,
and cooked macaroni
noodles from earlier!
Here you go!
Thanks, that's very helpful.
Now, it's time for
some seasoning,
a little salt and pepper
should do the trick.
[SHIRO]
Ahh...
[SENKO]
What are you doing?
This recipe doesn't
call for any sugar.
Huh? Are you sure, though?
[SENKO] It's called cheese
gratin, not sugar gratin.
Fine.
But the sweetness would
only improve the taste.
It's almost like she
has absolute faith
in the power of sugar.
[SENKO]
Okay, what's next?
Uh. Let's see. It's time for us
to pour it into the baking dish.
You got it.
And now you can put
the cheese on the top.
I like this; it's tasty.
Stop that Shiro! It's for
cooking, not snacking.
Okay, I'm all finished.
[KOENJI]
Good job!
Lastly, we need to bake it,
so you pop inside the old oven.
Wait, oven?
But isn't that what you
refer to as a "microwave"?
You can use it for baking
just like an oven!
It's kind of like a tiny
Japanese kiln you know?
[SENKO]
I see!
I was not aware that they
made kilns of this size.
Children have it so
easy this day and age.
How funny, sometimes
you really remind me
of an old woman, Senko.
Uh-oh, better watch
your language, grandma.
Think so?
[KOENJI]
Here we go!
[SHIRO] Hm? Is it done yet?
How about now?
Hurry up Mister Microwave.
I'm hungry.
[beeping]
Awww!
[SHIRO]
Is it done?
[KOENJI laughs]
Sure is!
[SENKO, SHIRO gasping]
[SENKO]
It really is cooked!
[KOENJI]
And it smells amazing!
Well! Let's taste it to be sure!
I'm so excited!
[laughs]
Then I shall have
a bite, as well!
Mm?
All right, here I go!
It tastes great!
Everything is so warm and melty!
I never knew that
this cheese stuff
would be so utterly delicious!
You're really having a special
moment with that food,
I understand those
feels completely.
This is great for
your first attempt.
Not that I'm surprised.
Your husband's gonna be in
for a real treat, Senko!
Uh-huh. Now that
I know the recipe,
I can cook him cheese
gratin whenever he desires.
And you couldn't have
done it without my help!
Yes, you're a very good
special helper, Shiro.
Way to go...
Oh wow, thanks for
doing the dishes.
No, if anything I should
be thanking you.
[KOENJI laughs]
[KOENJI] Whoa. I can
literally see it sparkling.
Your lesson was
extremely educational.
And I really enjoyed cooking
with the two of you.
[KOENJI] I mean, all I
did was read a recipe.
I was able to make it
because you taught me how.
So, would you maybe cook
with me again sometime?
[gasping] Yes, of course!
[SHIRO] Heh! What about me?
I wanna help with something!
You can be in charge
of eating, Shiro.
Good idea.
[SHIRO] I can also be
in charge of the fire!
Yes, that's true, too.
[SENKO laughs]
[GIRLS laughing]
[NAKANO]
Whoa... This looks good!
Go ahead and try some.
So, how is it?
It's amazing! I've been craving
cheese gratin for a while.
Wonderful! When you're
happy, then I'm happy!
[NAKANO] I didn't know that you
could also make western food.
[SENKO] Yes, Koenji was kind
enough to teach me how.
Oh, I see.
Hm? What's this?
You even found a way to use
your famous fried-tofu.
Oh, I actually added a couple
of secret ingredients,
like white miso, ginger,
and a few other things.
[NAKANO]
Ah. That explains it, then.
Even though it's
western-style food,
it still tastes just
like your cooking.
[gasps]
[SENKO]
That flavor... is my love.
My favorite seasoning.
Huh?
[laughing]
Well, that makes sense.
No wonder your cooking
always tastes so good.
Of course. It's one reason.
[NAKANO, SENKO laugh]
Hey, guess what?
I made you some dinner.
[KOENJI]
For real?!
That's instant ramen!
Yeah, so what?
I'll have you know I heated
the water with my own fire!
[KOENJI]
If you say so.
Thanks Shiro, that's
very thoughtful of you.
'Kay, here I go.
It's sweet?
I seasoned it with my
favorite ingredient: sugar!
[KOENJI] I think you and I
have different tastes.
[NAKANO]
I'm home.
[SENKO]
Welcome back.
Thanks for working hard today.
Yeah, of course.
[sighs] Coming home to an
air-conditioned apartment
is the best.
[SENKO] Things are much
easier than they used to be.
Man, it sucks when the
stuffy weather continues
into the fall season like this.
Oh, here.
Thank you so much, Senko.
I'm sure wearing
this heavy jacket
when it's hot outside
must be like utter torture.
Even looking at it
makes me feel sweaty.
It's not that I don't
agree with you,
but it's part of our
office dress code,
so there's not much
I can really do.
[SENKO] Huh? Your hair
has gotten very long,
perhaps that is making
you hot as well!
I'm definitely overdue for
a trim, that's for sure.
But I've been so busy I haven't
had the time to get one.
That's unfortunate,
but it is an easy fix.
Huh?
I shall be the one
to cut your hair!
Wait, right here at home?
Yep! It's no problem at all!
I'm an excellent hair dresser.
Yeah, I dunno, Senko.
I'm not really into
the samurai look.
[SENKO] Don't worry,
I'm not that old-fashioned.
And besides, I've thought you
were in need of a haircut
for a while now. So,
I did lots of research.
Oh, that's cool. You probably
know way more than I do.
Okay then, let's commence
with operation haircut!
[SENKO]
Right!
Okay, ready to get started?
Go for it.
[NAKANO] She seems pretty
comfortable with this.
I should relax and
let her do her thing.
[scissors snipping]
[gasps]
Is there a reason why you
sound shocked right now?
Oh. These just happen to be
incredibly sharp scissors.
[NAKANO]
All I need is a little trim,
not a whole new style, kay?
[SENKO]
I know, dearest.
Trust me, it's going to be fine.
[NAKANO laughs]
All right. Then trim away!
Uh! Just leave it to me!
Okay. I'm starting,
so don't move.
What do you think?
[gasps] We'll try
something else.
And... voila!
[NAKANO]
Mm. Mm-mm.
Wha--? No go, huh?
This one, then.
[NAKANO grumbles]
[NAKANO] Does Senko think
I'm quitting my job
and joining a band?
I'm only teasing!
Don't worry, I promise
I'll be more serious now.
[sighs] Thank goodness.
[scissors snipping]
[snipping continues]
[NAKANO] The relaxing sound
of scissors snipping.
It feels like I've completely
surrendered myself to her.
Mm... It reminds me...
[NAKANO]
When I was a kid,
I think my mom used to
cut my hair like this.
[SENKO humming]
[laughs]
Hey. I'm all finished;
it's time to wake up.
Uh.
Oh, wow! It's so much
lighter than it was before.
It must feel very nice.
It does, thank you. Oh,
I'm sorry that I dozed off.
It's all right! You must have
been pretty exhausted.
[NAKANO] Aw man, I didn't
realize I had so much hair.
I know, but you also went a
long time without cutting it.
[laughs]
Anyway, I should probably go
and wash my hair real quick.
Whoa there. Wait a second.
After all, the fun
is only beginning.
[NAKANO]
Mm... Hold on just a minute,
I think we might be taking this
"at-home-barbershop" thing
a little bit too far, Senko!
How so?
[NAKANO] I'm more than capable
of washing my own hair!
All right. Would this make
it less objectionable?
[NAKANO grunting]
Leave everything to me, 'kay?
Ready for the shampooing?
[NAKANO]
Yeah.
[NAKANO] Oh, man.
I've had my hair washed before,
but it's never felt this good.
[NAKANO gasping]
[NAKANO] Senko's tiny fingers
are so soft and warm.
They're gentle, but also
firm when necessary.
Like she's massaging
away all my stress.
Let me know if I miss any spots.
[NAKANO]
Okay.
[NAKANO] Her fluffy tail
laying gently on my face.
It's totally diffusing
my negative thoughts.
She's doing more than
just washing my hair.
[gasping]
[NAKANO]
She's washing away all my cares!
My troubles are just
disappearing!
Thanks so much, Senko!
My head feels
completely clear, now!
You can wash my hair
anytime you want to.
It makes me very happy that
you enjoyed it so much.
I was only copying what I saw,
but I'm really glad
that I was able
to make you look so handsome.
Uh? Hold on, what
did you just say?
You only copied what you saw?
[SENKO gasps]
What is that supposed to mean?
Well, uh... Oh.
That may or may not
have been my first time
using scissors and cutting
more modern hair.
Wait, your first time?
But how could it be your first?
You seemed so confident
when we started.
Yeah, and it was successful!
Your hair came out wonderfully,
and I was able to reconnect
the part I where messed up.
Whoa, reconnect what now?
[gasps]
[sighs]
Please tell me that you're
just teasing me again.
Is it super obvious?
There's no need to worry
about it so much,
the hair that I reattached
should last
for about two or three days.
What?! Hold on, what
happens after three days?
It's hard to know.
Only the gods can say.
[NAKANO]
Huh?
I'm teasing, the hair will
remain there permanently.
[sighs]
Oh well, I guess it would
have grown out eventually,
so a mistake wouldn't
have been a huge deal.
And when it gets too long,
I shall be more than
happy to cut it for you.
No thanks, I'll pass. Next time
I'll go to a real barber.
Say what?!
[SENKO whimpers]
[NAKANO]
Mm?
[whines]
[laughing]
I'm just kidding.
You are? Oh, you really got me.
[NAKANO]
I had to get you back somehow.
[SENKO]
I should thank you.
Huh?
In the short time
that I've known you,
I've tried a lot of new
and different things.
And I've had so much fun.
[NAKANO]
Me too, Senko.
[SENKO]
Super Senko Time!
Hi, welcome back!
You seem to be getting home
a little later than usual.
You must have worked
really hard today.
Have you had a chance
to eat any dinner, yet?
Oh, no!
You must be on the
verge of starvation!
Wait, you'd rather go straight
to bed without eating?
But if you go to sleep now,
then you might wake up hungry
in the middle of the night
because you skipped your dinner.
I know, what if I made
you a little snack?
It'll only take me
a couple of minutes.
Okay!
All right, here you are!
This is my Special Fox Udon!
I put some sweetly fried tofu
and delicious white
leeks on the top.
Are you feeling more hungry?
Well good, I'm happy to hear it!
I was hoping that
you would be able
to eat something a little
sooner in the evening,
but I understand that
you had to work late.
If eating my food will make you
feel a little bit better though,
then it's well worth the wait!
Now, you need to eat it quickly
or else it'll get cold!
Thank you so much for all
your hard work today.
Goodnight and sweet dreams!