[phone ringing]
[NAKANO] That's weird.
She's not answering.
[phone ringing]
[NAKANO]
Mitaka?
Hey, what's up?
[MITAKA]
N-N-Nakano! Thank god!
The team is in a
boatload of trouble!
Again?
[MITAKA] When is your vacation
over? We need your help ASAP!
Hey. Calm down.
I can head back home tomorrow.
Then I'll come into
work the next day.
Really? You're the best, man!
Seriously, we'd be
screwed without you!
[BOSS 07A]
Mitaka!
Uh! Be right there!
I'm sorry. I gotta let
ya go, see you soon!
[CAT purrs]
[NAKANO]
Time to go home.
[CAT meows]
[KITTENS meowing]
That's everything, right?
Yep.
[phone ringing]
[NAKANO]
Still no answer.
Seriously. That girl
and technology.
[NAKANO'S MOM]
Who? Your girlfriend?
Uh! No! Jeez, Mom.
[NAKANO'S MOM]
What?
[NAKANO]
Mm... What indeed.
I never know what's
going through his head.
[meows]
'Kay. Will you give
my best to Dad?
[NAKANO'S MOM]
Yes.
Thank you for
coming home, dear.
It meant a lot.
For you, enjoy.
[NAKANO laughs]
[NAKANO] I really wish I could
have gotten in touch with Senko
before I made the trip back.
[NAKANO] I wonder if she'll be
surprised that I'm home early?
Hello, I'm back!
[NAKANO]
Senko?
She didn't see my calls.
That's so weird.
Where did she go?
Did she go to that supermarket
over in the next town?
Uh?
A bento box? Maybe that's it!
Is Senko here?
Sorry. I haven't seen her.
Oh, you haven't?
So, she's not home?
No. She isn't.
Don't tell me. Did you two
have a lovers' quarrel?
No!
Mm... Or did we?
[KOENJI gasping]
Uh. No! Everything's fine!
[laughs] Hey, I'm just kidding.
I mean, can you imagine
anyone getting into a fight
with sweet little Senko? I would
literally murder that person.
Uh-huh.
Thanks.
Oh, now that I think about it,
I did see her yesterday,
and she said something
about going out.
[NAKANO]
What? Yesterday?
Uh-huh. She had like this
bag thing and her umbrella.
"Just for a little bit!"
So she said.
Seems kind of strange
though, you know?
Totally, she just sorta stood
right outside your apartment,
looking at it and stuff.
I asked her if something
had happened,
but she shook her head and told
me to bring in my laundry.
Oh, and Senko had a kind
of sad look on her face.
It's hard to say, but something
definitely seemed off.
[NAKANO grunts]
You wanna know what
else is kinda strange?
Shiro has been MIA for
a few days, as well.
Shiro, too, huh?
Uh-huh. Today's the last episode
of Little Yoko, Inari Girl .
"Goodie! I can't wait to watch!"
That's what Shiro said.
Yeah, now that you mention it,
Senko was excited
about that, too.
Well, who isn't?
Still, I wonder what
happened to them.
[NAKANO]
Hm...
A true fan watches it live!
Yoko fans unite!
You're a true Yoko fan,
aren't you, Shiro?
Anyway, I'm pretty sure
they'll both be back.
[NAKANO]
Yeah.
It's delicious! I've missed
your cooking so much!
I wish I could eat it every day!
Okay, I'm all finished!
I should have enough
fried-tofu and saké
to last me for
quite a while now.
Are you leaving?
I am. But before I return,
there's something important
I must discuss with Lady Sora.
What is it?
[SENKO]
Lady Sora?
[SORA]
Hmph.
I think I know what you mean
to ask, but I am curious.
Is it concerning that matter?
Concerning what?
He is kind of cute though.
[SENKO]
I don't understand.
Why does it keep getting bigger?
It would seem that you
are struggling to rid
the young sir completely
of his darkness.
And it preoccupies you,
does it not?
Yes.
It has been a quite a while
since you began to care for him.
An entire year, to be precise.
You do understand what
all this means, yes?
[SENKO gasps]
No, what does it mean?
[SORA] It means you
cannot do it, right?
Sen, you have been unable
to rid him of the darkness.
Please don't say it.
As such, you need
not return there.
If you cannot help him,
then your presence
has become arbitrary.
Aw! But the last episode
of Little Yoko airs today!
--[thunder claps]
--[SHIRO screams]
[sighs]
Uh! Oh, it should
be about that time.
I guess I'll see if it's on yet.
♪♪♪
[YOKO laughs]
[YOKO] Little Yoko,
Inari Girl ! Kon, kon, kon!
Hurry up, Shiro. It's on.
[YOKO gasps]
[TANUKIMAN]
Well, well, well...
No, not you again!
Now what are you up to?
Oh, just defeating you.
No biggie!
[YOKO gasping]
[laughing]
How's it feel to finally lose?
Hm?
What is that thing?
A meteor! If it hits, the earth
will be completely wiped out!
Huh?! Seriously?!
Kon, kon, kon!
Okay! Here I go!
[TANUKIMAN] Hold on!
You can't go into space!
Let's do it!
[CROWD gasping]
Oh, Yoko.
[YOKO grunting]
She did it, Little Yoko
stopped the meteor!
But what happened to her?
[TANUKIMAN]
Stupid fox.
I'm not ready to say goodbye!
Come back!
Say goodbye?
No way, can't be. That's crazy.
[thunder rumbles]
Otherwise, I fear something
bad may happen to you.
So I hope that
you'll be careful.
[NAKANO gasps]
No. It couldn't be...
[SENKO]
No matter how far away you are,
I promise I'll always
watch over you.
[NAKANO grunts]
When that happens, maybe you and
I could have a viewing party.
Where are you?
[NAKANO panting]
[NAKANO]
Senko!
Please don't tell me that I'll
never see your face again!
Senko!
[SENKO cries]
Ow...
[NAKANO'S ANCESTOR]
Are you all right?
[gasps]
[SENKO gasping]
--[SORA] Sen.
--Yes?
It is no secret you have long
wanted to return the kindness
that man showed to you.
And now you think you finally
have the opportunity to do that,
so I understand your feelings.
Still though. No matter
what the outcome may be,
a sad parting is
what awaits you.
Tell me, are you really willing
to suffer like that once again?
[SENKO]
Master! Please, say something!
Don't leave.
I'm so sorry, I still haven't
done anything for you.
[SENKO cries]
[gasps]
Oh, Sen.
It's time. Just let it go.
Lady Sora. I understand.
Huh?
[SENKO]
Most likely,
events will happen
just as you say.
[SENKO]
Still...
[NAKANO panting]
[SENKO] I'll keep helping him!
For as long as I possibly can!
[NAKANO panting]
[SENKO]
That may be selfish,
but I am going to do it anyway!
I might refuse you.
So, then what?
Listen to me, Sen.
Everything ends eventually.
[SENKO]
I know.
I know that.
But I still want to pamper
him to his heart's content!
That's great!
[SENKO laughs]
Could this be what she meant?
It's definitely something bad.
You said you wanted to view
the cherry blossoms together.
Remember that?
And we never went
to that supermarket.
If you had stayed,
we could have gone there.
[NAKANO gasps]
Is that you, dear? You're back
earlier than I expected.
Senko. You're...
Whoa! Hey!
Goodness, you're drenched!
Have you been out
in the rain all night?
[SENKO] Oh, dear.
Your clothes are such a mess.
[NAKANO] I thought...
I would never see you again.
[gasps] Why would
you think that?
Cause I called you.
Over and over again,
but you didn't answer.
I'm so sorry,
I didn't know that!
I had to go back to
the other world for a bit.
Why did you go there?
Because we were running
low on fried tofu and saké.
But now, we're stocked
and good to go!
Then I came out here because
I wanted to scout out
some good flowers
for our viewing.
I was quite surprised
to find you here, too!
Our viewing? [gasps]
[SENKO]
I know! Let's do it right now.
When there's cherry
blossoms in full bloom,
you must celebrate with saké!
[NAKANO]
Uh...
[chuckles]
Her resolve is strong.
I suspect they'll be fine now.
Wait, so you were only
testing her before?
[SORA laughs]
They're quite the pair.
I look forward to seeing
what happens next.
Man a drink sounds great,
thanks so much.
Wait, hold just on a second!
I mean, don't we
kinda stand out?
Like, what if we get reported
to the police or whatever?
Why would we?
[NAKANO]
'Cause you have fox ears.
And it looks like there's little
girl with a grown man in a park
gulping down booze
like nobody's business.
I'm the little girl, am I?
You worry too much.
As always, I was
prepared for this.
I've put up a magical
barrier around us.
[NAKANO]
Really, you did?
[SENKO] Yes, so the only people
who will be able to see us
are the ones who
already know me.
Wow, you never cease
to amaze me, Senko.
As a bonus, no one
will bother us.
It's kind of like we get to have
our own private flower
viewing party.
That is pretty cool.
[SENKO] Don't be shy,
go ahead and drink up.
Right, okay then. Here goes.
[NAKANO]
Heh! Tastes great!
[SENKO] It's a sacred drink that
contains my spiritual energy.
And...
Ta-dah!
I prepared us some light
snacks to go with the saké!
Feel free to help yourself!
Whoa! That is a ton of food!
Heh!
It's amazing!
It's the first catch
of the season!
I think that it tastes
great with saké.
[NAKANO] It does! Here,
let me pour you a glass.
[SENKO laughs]
My, what a gentleman!
I'm so jealous.
You're much better at holding
your liquor than I am.
[SENKO laughs]
Yeah, you think so?
[NAKANO]
Wait, are you drunk right now?
That was so fast!
[SENKO] When I'm in the mood to
drink, I'm in the mood to drink.
Is that a problem?
Uh no, guess not.
'S good to hear.
Since I'm drunk,
you're responsible for
making sure I pamper you.
[NAKANO]
I'm not sure that makes sense.
And besides, you pretty much
always pamper me, don't you?
Uh!
That may be true,
but I'll spoil you even more!
Uhh...
Didn't we come out here
for cherry blossom viewing?
I think we should
just focus on that.
You think I'm not?
This was all part of my
flower-viewing plan!
Look up and you'll see why.
[NAKANO gasps]
Not that bad of a view, is it?
It's very beautiful. I've scored
the best seat in the house.
Uh?
Is something the matter?
[NAKANO] Well, your hairpin
reminded me of a memory.
Hey, Senko. Uh.
Maybe I'm wrong, but...
You've been watching over me
since I was a kid, right?
[gasps] I don't know, have I?
Look, I'm not completely
sure what I should even
say to you here.
I guess... I wanna say thanks.
[SENKO] I can't say I know
what you're talking about.
But there is one
thing I'm sure of.
Huh?
I'm doing all these things
for you because I want to.
So honestly, there's nothing
you need to thank me for.
Now lay down, I'm still not
done pampering you, yet.
[NAKANO]
Hey!
[SENKO] Here, is that
more comfortable for you?
You just lay there
and focus on relaxing.
[NAKANO chuckles]
[SENKO] It's not every day
you get to fall asleep
to the beautiful sight
of cherry blossoms.
You've got a good point.
Although, I forgot to mention I
have to go into work tomorrow.
We need to go home
soon so I can sleep.
My goodness.
You still don't know
how to just let yourself
be pampered, do you?
Sorry, Senko.
It's okay.
Because it's a part
of who you are,
and I think that
makes you lovely.
But you must be careful not to
wear yourself down too much.
Take the time to relax.
And if you keep getting better
at letting yourself be pampered.
What were you saying?
She fell asleep?
Looks like she can't
handle her liquor!
Uh, hey Senko,
you need to wake up!
The park is no place for a nap!
Let's just go home
and get some sleep.
[SENKO]
Eep...
[NAKANO gasps]
[NAKANO] If I were still
the person I used to be,
I never would've have considered
staying out here
a little longer.
[NAKANO]
But I don't think it can hurt.
[KOENJI]
Hey, it's Senko!
It looks like you
found her, huh?
Uh, yeah.
[SENKO grumbles]
And look! There's a feast!
[KOENJI, SHIRO]
Let's dig in!
[KOENJI]
It's good!
So yummy!
Hey! I wanna watch Little Yoko !
Oh, yeah? Lookie
what I have here!
Wow! You're awesome, Jasuko!
[BOTH]
Hooray!
Yoko! Come back! Please!
Gold coins. Could it be...?
Look there! It's Yoko!
Hello! I'm back, kon!
Yay! Yoko's alive!
Man. This part
always makes me cry!
[wails]
It's such a lovely night.
Yeah. It really is
something special.
Senko...
Huh?
No matter what, I want
us to stick together.
[SENKO gasping]
So do I!
Hello, and welcome home!
My goodness.
You must have had a
terribly long day, huh?