[WOMAN A]
I'm done for the day!
Wanna go grab some food?
[WOMAN B]
Yeah, sure!
--[keyboard clicking]
--[WORKERS chattering]
[sighs]
[NAKANO]
Finally done.
[NAKANO] I'm leaving,
see you tomorrow.
[MITAKA]
Nakano wait!
Sorry!
[NAKANO]
Huh?
A project got messed up.
Can you help out?
[NAKANO]
Me? But I want to go home.
Please, man?
All right.
Seriously? Thank you!
[sighs]
[YOZORA] Harboring such despair
can bring one's world to ruin.
[YOZORA]
But, before that happens,
we must attempt to
save the young sir.
[SENKO]
Please, send me.
[gasps] Why you?!
[SENKO] His poor heart
is very troubled,
but I can help free him.
All right. I shall grant
you permission, then.
Thank you!
[SHIRO]
No way! That's not fair!
Just wait and see.
I shall pamper him well.
[NAKANO'S MOM]
Kuroto. It's your mother.
How are you?
We observed the
sixth anniversary
of Grandma's passing today,
but everyone's doing well.
Will you make it home
for the Obon Festival?
Give me a call, okay?
[sighs]
[train rattles]
Huh?
[COMMUTERS chattering]
[COMMUTER B sighs]
[NAKANO] I'm sick of
riding the last train.
And I had to skip dinner, again.
[NAKANO]
Wait.
Did I eat the last of
the instant ramen?
Whatever...
[NAKANO] I wonder how
much longer I can do this
before I just collapse
from exhaustion?
Huh?
[NAKANO]
Man, something smells good.
[NAKANO] Weird. Did I leave
the lights on this morning?
Hi, welcome home!
Oh my, you must have had
a terribly long day.
Uh... I'm sorry!
Uh, wrong apartment!
[NAKANO]
Hm? Wait. I totally live here.
Hi, welcome home!
Oh my, you must have had
a terribly long day.
A dream?
Uh, nope. So...
Yay! You're back!
You've certainly had a long day.
[NAKANO sputtering]
I'm glad you're here.
I've prepared you
a nutritious dinner.
[NAKANO] Why is there a
little girl in my apartment?
More importantly, what's up
with the fluffy ears and tail?
Maybe she lives nearby?
But if someone were to see
her in a grown man's place...
[SENKO]
Mm?
[ONLOOKERS whisper]
He always gave off a real
creepy vibe, you know?
[NAKANO'S MOM]
I'm so sorry.
Hopefully my son
gets proper help!
[NAKANO grunts]
[exhales] I'll pretend
like that didn't happen.
[sighs] I need some sleep.
Poor thing, you must
be so exhausted.
[screams]
You can seriously
pass through walls?
Are you like a ghost?
[NAKANO whimpers]
Oh no, this is even
worse than I thought.
Um, hey. Aren't you going
to eat your dinner now?
Uh... Huh?
[SENKO]
It's nice and hot!
You've had such a long,
hard day of work.
You must be starving.
[stomach growls]
Yep! So, shall I
make you a plate?
Whoa, I can't eat
at a time like this!
Who the heck are you?
And what are you doing
in my apartment?
Uh!
[SENKO cries]
That's fine.
I only put my heart
and soul into this meal.
But that's okay.
I will discard it for you.
[NAKANO]
Uh...
No, don't do it!
You win! I'll eat it!
[panting]
[SENKO]
Heh!
Excellent!
[sighs]
Looks great.
[SENKO]
Freshly made!
Oh!
Uh?
[NAKANO] I can't eat
that huge mountain of rice!
Well, try!
Thank you for the meal.
Eat up!
[NAKANO]
This is awkward.
[slurping] Mm!
How is it? Good, right?
It is.
[SENKO] I'm glad! You should
try some of the stew next.
Wow, it has such a rich flavor.
It reminds me of something.
Like the food my
grandma used to make!
Is that your way of
complimenting dinner?
Yep!
[SENKO]
Heh! Well, in that case then.
I'll have some, too!
[NAKANO] For some reason,
this takes me back.
How many years has it been now?
Yum! Delicious!
[NAKANO] I actually can't
remember the last time
I came home to a hot meal.
[NAKANO] It's kind of nice
not eating alone.
Would you like to have seconds?
Uh. Sure. That sounds great.
[NAKANO] Wait, I still don't
know anything about this kid!
I don't wanna be rude
or anything...
[SENKO]
Hm?
[NAKANO]
But can you tell me who you are?
Yes. Of course.
I go by the name of Senko.
And I'm an 800-year-old
servant of the gods.
A fox demigod!
[NAKANO]
A fox... demigod?
Let me get this straight.
You're a... demigod?
That's right!
And you're supposedly
like 800 years old?
Uh, but you look
more like a little kid.
Would you please quit
with the rice mountains?
But you need to eat to
regain your strength!
You should have some
more stew, as well.
Uh, question.
Did you get these
ingredients from my kitchen?
[SENKO]
No, I brought them with me.
Ah...
They are delicious.
Where did you get them from?
Oh.
They were just some offerings
that people left at the shrine.
[NAKANO]
Uhh...
[NAKANO] Is it okay for me
to eat their offerings?
Is something the matter?
[NAKANO]
No, it's just...
To be honest, I'm still not
quite sure why you came here.
Heh! I simply couldn't stand
to see you looking so worn down,
so I decided to help you!
Worn down?
Look, it's not that I
don't appreciate it--
I just don't get
why you chose me.
Listen to me carefully.
Uh. 'Kay.
If you must know the truth...
[NAKANO]
Yeah?
[gulps]
You're just the type of
young man that I prefer!
Are you kidding me?!
Do I look like I'm joking?
Uh. No.
Sorry I guess gods don't
need a real reason, huh?
Perhaps it's because I'm
indebted to your family.
[NAKANO]
Huh?
Look. I just want to pamper
you for a little bit.
Is that so bad?
No.
[NAKANO]
Thank you for dinner.
[SENKO]
It was my pleasure.
Was everything to your liking?
Yes. I'm so stuffed
I can barely move.
[SENKO]
Then, mission accomplished!
Ah... This tea's great.
From now on, I shall serve
you tea after every meal!
It'll be much better for
you than all that coffee.
I'm sure that your poor
stomach could use a break.
Uh? You know about that?
I've been watching
you for a while.
Watching me...?
Oh! I'll take those!
No, I've got it.
You just sit there
and focus on relaxing.
[NAKANO]
But I--
Better drink that tea
before it gets cold!
A good luck stalk.
[NAKANO'S GRANDMA]
Kuroto? Would you like a snack?
Yeah!
Huh? Ooh! Look, Grandma!
Good luck!
[NAKANO'S GRANDMA]
Ooh... Heh, heh.
Hey, were these tea leaves
that I had in my cupboard?
No, I brought them
along with me.
[NAKANO]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Now, why don't you
tell me some other ways
you'd like to be pampered?
I guess I don't really know.
There must be something!
[NAKANO]
Mm!
[NAKANO gasping]
[NAKANO]
Well, maybe...
[SENKO]
Go on.
Um, would it be okay for me
to touch your tail?
[gasps] Say what now?
I-It's fine. Never mind, sorry.
[SENKO] Well, if that
will make you happy.
I... rarely allow this, but...
[SENKO]
My goodness.
This is truly a strange request.
Uh, is it really?
You may proceed.
[NAKANO]
Incredible!
The color is breathtakingly
beautiful.
It's like an explosion
of golden, shiny, fluff!
And just to be clear,
you really don't mind?
It's okay!
[gasps]
[NAKANO]
It's so fluffy.
Eep!
[NAKANO]
Your tail is so soft.
I feel like I could
do this all day.
This is next-level luxurious.
Like if a hug materialized
in the form of fox fur.
Honestly. The commentary
seems a little unnecessary!
[gasps]
Oh, I'm sorry!
I didn't hurt you, did I?
I'm fine.
There's nothing for
you to worry about.
You may pet my tail
as long as you want.
Thanks!
[SENKO whimpers]
[NAKANO exhales]
[SENKO screams]
[NAKANO sighs]
Thank you so much!
Uh. Do you feel better now?
Yeah, probably
better than ever!
That's wonderful; it pleases
me to see you so happy.
Uh? Crap, I messed up
your pretty tail!
It reminded me of petting
our family's cat.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay!
Because now it's
just nice and fluffy.
Ugh, I feel bad that you've
done so much for me tonight,
but I haven't done one
single thing for you.
[laughs] That's so cute.
What?
There was only one thing
I wanted tonight,
and that was to see your smile.
Is that really enough though?
A little girl like you
shouldn't have to help out
a grown man like me.
How funny!
Need I remind you that
I am 800 years old,
so you're the little one!
Okay. But if this goes on,
I'll be a lazy bum.
You say that like
it's a bad thing.
[gasps]
[SENKO] Every person in the
world has their faults, even me,
and I've had 800 years
to figure them all out.
For what it's worth,
I already think you're
working hard enough.
I did these things for you
tonight because I felt like it.
So, please stop
worrying so much.
[NAKANO]
Uh...
Might I add, you're overlooking
a very critical detail
concerning demigods.
Oh, and what's that?
[SENKO] Care from a fox demigod
is considered priceless.
No amount of good deeds
could ever earn it.
That's why you need to
stop being a worry-wart
and let me pamper you!
[NAKANO]
Mm.
Lie down.
[NAKANO]
Uh...
You must be so exhausted.
[NAKANO whimpers]
Now come here and
let me spoil you.
You deserve to rest a bit.
[SENKO]
I'm here to take care of you.
[exhales]
Where are you? Grandma!
[SENKO]
Over here.
Huh?
[SENKO]
This way.
Come back!
[NAKANO'S GRANDMA]
Kuroto!
[NAKANO]
Huh? Grandma!
[gasping]
There.
Whoa. Did I fall asleep?
Possibly.
There's no way.
Your skin tone. It looks much
brighter than earlier.
And your body appears to be
much more relaxed than
when you got home.
[NAKANO]
Uh. Hey. Yeah, you're right.
It feels lighter somehow.
Honestly, I can't
thank you enough.
Please. You don't
have to thank me.
Besides, believe it or not,
this is only the beginning
of your new pampered life.
You're going to be so spoiled!
[laughs]
[NAKANO] Does that mean I
can touch your tail again?
[SENKO] We're going to have to
put a daily limit on that one!
[SENKO]
Super Senko Time!
Uh? Hello, welcome home!
Oh my, you must've had
a terribly long day.
Please, come in.
Just relax and I'll
handle everything.
Here. This is my favorite
tea, called "Houjicha."
[slurping]
I think it has a
very nice flavor.
And a lovely aroma, as well!
[cup clinking]
Oh, would you like to know
how to brew a pot yourself?
Great! Let's get started.
So, first you pour the
hot water into the pot,
then you let the roasted
tea leaves soak.
Okay, then. Think,
"I want this to be delicious!"
as your pouring it into the cup.
That make sense?
Good!
Hot tea's perfect to
have right before bed.
Not only will it
bring you lots of joy,
it'll also soothe your soul!
I highly recommend it.
Thank you for all of your
hard work today.
You should head to bed.
A full night of sleep will help
you feel fresh in the morning!
Okay. I hope you rest well!
Good night and sweet dreams.