[birds chirping]
[vacuum whirs]
All done!
Now everything is
nice and clean!
Thanks for your assistance,
Mister Vacuum.
Okay, then. What should I
make for dinner tonight?
[gasps] This is...
[NAKANO]
Where are you? Grandma!
[SENKO]
Over here.
Huh?
This way.
Wait come back!
[NAKANO panting]
[NAKANO'S GRANDMA]
Kuroto!
Huh? Grandma!
Uh?
[NAKANO gasping]
Thanks so much!
Uh?
Sweet.
What a nice memory.
Uh? Huh?
[SENKO] It's going
to be a rough night.
I should prepare.
Hey, I'm back.
Uh?
[NAKANO]
Mm?
I'm so glad that
you're finally home.
It looks like you've
had another long day.
Uh? A noren ? Man, you've really
taken things to the next
level today, haven't you?
[SENKO laughs]
Uh-huh! I thought you'd like it.
Your new apron is
also very pretty.
If you're trying to
flatter me, it's working.
So, is tonight a special
occasion or something?
No, sometimes you just need
to change things up.
In fact, I was thinking about
serving some alcohol
with tonight's dinner.
[NAKANO]
Heh! That sounds good!
A drink would really hit
the spot right about now.
[SENKO]
Then consider it done!
[NAKANO]
Uhh...
[NAKANO gasping]
Wow. Awesome!
Thank you!
[NAKANO]
Okay.
[SENKO, NAKANO]
Cheers!
[BOTH sigh]
So good!
Yes, I agree!
It really hits the spot,
doesn't it?
Here. Would you
care for a refill?
Oh, sure, that'd be awesome.
This is delicious! And it pairs
with the saké perfectly.
Thank you so much, I've been
simmering it all afternoon.
Would you like to try a
different type of saké?
[NAKANO]
Yeah, lay it on me!
Give that a try.
Bottoms up!
Tastes like rice!
It even has the same
aroma as rice!
[SENKO laughs]
[NAKANO]
"The Fox's Cherry Blossoms"?
That's right.
The cherry blossoms
should be blooming soon,
so it seemed fitting.
When that happens, maybe you and
I could have a viewing party.
Yeah, sounds nice.
It's been quite a while
since I've done that.
Last year at work,
we had a deadline.
And of course you weren't here.
That's true.
[NAKANO]
When I was little,
I looked forward to doing
it every single year.
Yes, I'm sure you did.
[NAKANO]
Hm?
[SENKO laughs]
This particular saké tastes
better when you eat it
with cooked fish.
Why don't you try it out?
[gasps] I can't believe I get
to eat traditional food
like this in my own home!
You never cease to amaze me.
Really?
Then you'll be pleased to know
I also made some inari zushi!
Yum!
[SENKO giggles]
[NAKANO sighs] Can I have
one more drink, please?
[SENKO]
There's no need to stop there.
Drink all you like!
[NAKANO chuckles]
Okay! If you insist!
Huh? This looks pretty good.
Did you make this
plum wine, Senko?
[SENKO]
Uh-huh.
It's one of my favorite things
to do during the rainy season!
Ooh!
The plums taste so sweet,
kind of like a dessert!
It tastes super delicious.
Hey, whaddya call dis
fruit in it? Ah, uh.
Do you mean the plum?
You literally just said it
not even a minute ago.
[laughs] Right, thassit!
A plum. What a funny word.
[SENKO]
Uhh...
Oh my, I didn't think you
would get drunk so quickly.
It might be best if
you had some water.
Yeah, good idea.
Okay-- Uh.
[gasps] It's all right.
I've got it, so you
just stay put.
Sorry I'm so clumsy.
Did any of it spill
onto your clothes?
[NAKANO]
Please, I'm help-y to hap you.
[SENKO] I don't think your
business card will help here.
[gasps] I really am a giant
ball of useless, aren't I?
I shouldn't even be alive.
Don't be ridiculous.
But...
You're all over
the place tonight.
[NAKANO]
Today was kind of a disaster.
We were s'posed to
deliver the product,
but then the client
started making
all these new requests that
weren't in the original specs.
They even said that it
should have been obvious
from the beginning.
I tried talking to
my boss about it,
but he said, "the customer
is always right"
and that I had to do whatever
it took to get the job done.
I worked overtime for free
and still got in trouble.
It sucked. Like, what else does
the company want from me?
My goodness, that all
sounds rather frustrating.
Uh. No, I'm sorry.
My stupid problems must
be boring to hear about.
It's fine.
I feel terrible.
Complaining about work so much.
There are folks who have it
worse; I should be grateful.
Just because others
may have it worse,
doesn't mean your feelings
are any less valid.
What's more...
All I want is for you to share
those feelings with me.
[NAKANO gasps]
And I want to know everything
about you, the good and the bad.
If it's just the two of us here,
then there's no need to worry
about what other
people might think.
You can be yourself.
There's no need to
hold anything back.
Today was hard, and that's okay.
I'm sorry it was bad.
You must be very frustrated.
[NAKANO]
Yeah.
[SENKO]
But you still did a good job.
[NAKANO cries]
Yeah.
[NAKANO]
Senko...
Yes? What is it?
[NAKANO sighs]
Uh, hey! What are you doing?
[sighs] The little scamp
passed out on me.
He is kind of cute though.
[SENKO] I don't understand.
Why does it keep getting bigger?
[NAKANO] "The Fox's Cherry
Blossoms" is the good stuff.
Oh, no! How gross, I think
he's drooling on my tail!
[exhales] Now I have to
move him to the futon.
[SHIRO] Jeez! It's been
a whole year already!
Just how long is Nakano
gonna hog Sen for?
A year, huh?
The time went by
faster than I thought.
Ugh! At this rate I'll never get
to eat Sen's cooking again,
this whole thing is so unfair!
Oh, but that seems
like an odd complaint.
Have not been there eating
her food on several occasions?
Well, yeah.
But that doesn't count, I wanna
eat it here, not there!
[SORA laughs]
I understand.
But in any case, I doubt you
will have to wait too long.
I suspect your wishes may be
granted sooner than you think.
Perhaps you only need be
a bit more patient, Shiro.
Wha...?
[SORA] After all, everything
must come to an end, eventually.
Hey. Are you really
taking paid leave?
What do you mean?
Like taking time off when
we're trying to hit all these
delivery deadlines!
That's what I mean.
[BOSS 07A]
Nakano!
Yes, sir?
[BOSS 07A]
My office, now!
Sure, I'll be right there.
[MALE BOSS 07A]
Ha.
[MITAKA]
Mm... You're in for it.
Huh?
[NAKANO]
Jeez.
I got chewed out for having
too much paid leave.
Now I have to take it even
though the timing sucks.
[SENKO]
So, your break starts tomorrow?
Sure does.
That is truly wonderful to hear!
You've been working hard lately.
I'm sure that you
must be exhausted.
It makes me glad that
you're finally taking a break.
Self-care is very important!
[NAKANO] Since I've got some
time off, I thought maybe
we could take a trip
somewhere fun together.
Okay! Oh, this would be my first
time going someplace
special with you!
Hey, don't forget about that
mystic beach or whatever.
And the supermarket!
Uh yeah, I'm pretty sure
I wouldn't count that
as a fun trip.
Hey, Senko. If you could pick,
where would we visit?
[SENKO]
Me?
Perhaps the supermarket
in the next town over?
You're serious, aren't you?
Of course, Koenji
recommended it to me.
She said they have
excellent fried tofu.
Right, as you wish.
If you want, we can
go there tomorrow.
Sounds good!
Also. I know it's still
a bit early, but...
Cherry blossom viewing?
You knew?
[NAKANO] You mentioned it just
the other night, remember?
[SENKO] Yes, but you were
rather drunk at the time,
so to be honest, I sort
of thought you wouldn't.
Well, I definitely
remember that part,
but anything after that is
an entirely different story.
[SENKO laughs] At least you
can be honest about it.
Right. Would you like
to celebrate the start
of your much-needed
vacation, then?
Senko's bar is back open!
Would you care for a drink?
[NAKANO]
Uh... Sure thing!
[SENKO]
Okay!
[phone ringing]
[NAKANO]
Yeah, hello?
[NAKANO'S MOM]
Kuroto?
I'm so sorry to
wake you up, dear.
[NAKANO]
Mom? Is something wrong?
[NAKANO'S MOM]
I'm sorry, dear. Your father
was just taken to the hospital.
[NAKANO]
What?
[NAKANO'S MOM]
I'm pretty sure he'll be fine.
But I still felt like I should
call and let you know.
[NAKANO]
Okay. Thank you.
That reminds me...
Otherwise, I fear something
bad may happen to you.
So I hope that
you'll be careful.
[NAKANO]
Something bad, huh?
That's crazy. No way.
Maybe you should go to see him.
You think?
It has been quite some time
since you've returned
home, right?
Yeah, that's true.
At least a few years.
I think this is the perfect
way to use your time off.
And besides, seeing their faces
might be good for all of you.
[NAKANO]
Uh... Maybe it would.
Wait, but I already
promised I would take you
to the supermarket in
the next town over today.
I suppose you'll have to
take me another time then.
The supermarket's not
going to disappear.
You're right.
[NAKANO] Okay. I think
I'm just about set.
[SENKO]
Yep!
Hey, Senko?
Are you sure that you'll
be okay here by yourself?
Don't worry, I've been here
by myself lots of times.
Like when you sleep
at the office.
Yeah, you've got me there.
[SENKO]
It's fine!
No matter how far away you
are, I'll still be with you.
I promise, 'kay?
I'll always watch over you.
Okay. So I'm gonna
leave you my phone.
Just in case you need it.
[SENKO]
What about my heartfelt speech?
Your phone, huh?
But don't you need this
for communication?
It won't be a problem. I'll
have my work phone with me.
[beeping, ringing]
Oh, my!
[NAKANO] You press the green
button to answer incoming calls.
I've got it.
Like this, right?
Hi, Senko? Can you hear me okay?
Uh. Well, of course I can--
you're standing right
in front of me.
Right, then.
Now, if you wanna call me...
Yes, I get it. More importantly,
you need to get moving or
you're going to miss your train.
Okay.
[SENKO]
Bye, have a safe trip!
I'll see ya later!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Welcome to Nagoya Station.
Thank you for riding
with us today.
Track 11 for Hida Takayama
will be departing soon.
[ANNOUNCER B]
The Wide View Hida Number 11
at 12:48 will be
departing momentarily.
Please take your seats.
Huh?
[gasps]
[NAKANO]
Mom?
Kuroto!
Uh...
[NAKANO'S MOM]
I'm so sorry to make you
worry like that, sweetie.
It turns out your father
took things a little too far
at his class reunion.
The big goof got drunk and then
broke a bone while dancing.
Well, I'm just glad it's
not something serious.
You need to be careful, too.
[CAT meows]
Right, I promise.
What's this?
It's been quite a while,
but it seems they're
finally back together.
Well then, I should
probably get going myself.
[doorbell rings]
Uh. The door?
Hey, Senko? It's Koenji!
[SENKO grunts]
Thanks for feeding me.
And as usual, your cooking
was super delicious!
Oh good, I'm happy to hear it.
Are you going somewhere?
Uh! Yes, just for a bit.
Did something happen?
[SENKO]
Mm-mm. It's going to rain.
So it'd probably
be smart for you
to go ahead and bring
your laundry in.
[KOENJI]
Hm? Uh. It is?
[SENKO]
Farewell!
I'll see you later! Bye!
--[KOENJI laughs]
--[rain falls]
It's raining?
Whoa. Amazing.
The weather report said
it would be sunny.
Uh... Ah! My laundry!
[NAKANO]
Mom, I'm gonna take a walk!
[NAKANO'S MOM]
Have a good time, sweetie!
[NAKANO]
Mm?
Hey, Grandma. I'm home.
[gasps]
Plum blossoms?
[NAKANO gasps]
[NAKANO gasping]
[NAKANO]
Back then... It was Senko.
[CAT meows]
[footsteps]
[NAKANO] If that really
was my ancestor...
[SENKO] I'll still be
with you. I promise, kay?
I'll always watch over you.
[NAKANO]
Senko. She was there.
Always.
[phone ringing]
That's weird.
[SORA]
Super Sora Time.
Welcome home.
I have been awaiting
your return.
It would appear you have had
another hard day of labor.
Unfortunately, Sen is
not available today.
But I am a demigod fox who has
lived for thousands of years.
So perhaps, I, Lady Sora,
could be of service to you.
Please, help yourself.
I sincerely hope that you will
find the taste to your liking.
[SORA laughs]
What's the matter?
I should inform you that I
did not prepare this meal.
In fact, this was
all Sen's doing.
Don't be wasteful.
Now. Allow me to feed you.
Oh? Are you not hungry?
I see, you're too lustful,
so you cannot eat.
Pardon. You said you're too
stuffed full, my mistake.
[laughs]
But if that's the case...
Well then, you must
be feeling tired.
Would you like to go to bed?
[SORA]
My goodness.
I did not think you would
actually want to go to sleep.
You really are
quite the scoundrel.
Goodnight and sweet dreams.