[yawns]
Uh?
[gasps]
[SENKO]
It snowed!
[sighs]
It's really piled up out there!
And if I recall correctly, it's
quite unusual for this region
to accumulate so much snow.
[NAKANO] Yep, it's the most
we've had in decades.
Indeed!
Though, I can't help
but notice...
...that you seem to be putting
on your office attire!
Yes well, that's what
I do every morning.
And if I don't hurry up
and get on the road,
then I'll be late for work.
[SENKO]
You can't!
There's simply no way you can go
to the office in all that snow!
I definitely agree
with you there.
[SENKO]
Then stay!
[sighs] Unfortunately my
company sees it differently,
and they haven't sent anything
out saying we're closed, so...
Are you serious?!
Wait, how do you even know
if the trains are running?
They are, but they
might stop soon.
So I need to leave early.
[SENKO grumbles]
[door opens]
[NAKANO]
See you later.
If the trains stop running,
then how will you get home?
Well, I dunno, I'll just
stay at the office.
Come on now, Senko, if you're
going to be out in public,
then you need at least to
put on your hat and coat.
I'm not letting go!
Besides, nobody else going be
outside in this kind of weather!
[NAKANO]
Yeah, I guess.
[SENKO] Look, I really
think you should take
a little more time
to relax or play!
Well, I really think you need
to go back into the apartment.
[phone vibrates]
[NAKANO]
Of course.
We just got an e-mail saying
the office is closed.
Oh good, that's wonderful news!
Still though, it's a little bit
frustrating that your work
waited so long before
letting everyone know
that they were
closed for the day.
I know. At least it's
settled, though.
Man I had no idea it was
going to snow this much.
Well then, wanna
go back inside?
Nuh-uh! Here.
I say that we play
outside for a while
[NAKANO]
Hey, wait!
It's deep!
[SENKO laughs]
Let's go back inside. There's
no reason to be out here.
Yep, this snow is
definitely high-quality!
Uhh...
Oh.
[NAKANO]
It is really pretty.
Now that I think about it,
it's been a while since
I've seen this much.
[SENKO]
Oh? [laughs]
Well, if that's the case,
I think we should
have a little fun!
Uh, I'll pass,
I think I'm a little old
for that sort of thing.
But it's important to get up
and move around sometimes.
[NAKANO] I don't know,
maybe that should be
reserved for warmer weather.
[SENKO grumbles]
My, you're such a wet blanket.
I'm sorry, Senko.
Hurry up, slow poke.
[SENKO humming]
[NAKANO]
The snow might be pretty,
but it pales in comparison
to her tail swishing
in a world of white.
The snow outlines
her ears beautifully.
[NAKANO] This winter wonderland
serves as the perfect frame
for her gorgeous golden fur.
[exhales]
[NAKANO] I'm a bit worried
that she's not hiding
her ears and tail,
but since no one's around,
I guess it's okay this once.
--[SENKO laughs]
--[NAKANO gasps]
Why are you so quiet?
Have you finally given up
on going back inside?
No, that's not it.
I was just thinking about
how pretty you look.
Guess I got lost in my thoughts.
[SENKO]
Strange, I suddenly feel
the need to burn
off some energy.
Man, you must really
wanna play in the snow.
[SENKO groans]
Hm?
[NAKANO]
To be honest though,
I'd be lying if I said I
didn't want to play in it.
But I'm too old for
stuff like that.
[NAKANO grunts]
Uh. Hey! Senko!
[SENKO] Let me guess,
you were thinking about playing
but you're worried
about your age.
But take a look at me,
I'm over 800 old,
and I'm about to start a ruckus.
Now, then, stop worrying
about your age so much
and come enjoy
this snow with me!
[NAKANO]
Mm.
Well. If you insist then.
All right, prepare
for war, Senko!
You asked for it!
Ah!
Oh no, I've been hit! [laughs]
Having fun yet?
I must say, you look
rather relaxed, dear.
I am.
You should give it a try,
believe it or not--
the cold snow actually
feels pretty good.
[SENKO]
Is that so?
Well, in that case...
Here goes!
[SENKO grunts]
[laughs] Excellent dive, Senko.
Very fox-like of you.
Maybe because I am a fox!
Yeah, that's true!
[laughing]
[SENKO]
Come on, it's not that funny.
Are you sure?
I've never seen anyone dive
into snow head-first before.
That's just silly.
No, silly was seeing your
face in a snow mound
and your tail in the air.
That's not silly!
It is, too! [laughs]
To be honest, that's
actually the first time
I've done it in
hundreds of years.
[BOTH laughing]
Empty as usual.
Off to the store, then.
Whoa, seriously?
That is an unholy
amount of snow.
But on the bright side, I could
build a snowman if I wanted to.
Uh?
[NAKANO] Hold up!
Don't you think that's too big?!
Please be careful with
that ball of death, Senko!
[KOENJI] It's hard to believe
that a mere human could
make a snowball that large.
No way, it can't be!
Senko must be from
a snowy region!
Aw man, it's cold out here!
[NAKANO sighs] We played
outside for quite a while!
Yes, it's nice to let your
inner child out, isn't it?
Sure, every now and then.
All right, I think I'm gonna
try and do some work from home.
[SENKO gasps]
[NAKANO]
Uh. What's wrong?
Did you hurt your back?
[SENKO]
No. It's perfectly fine.
How's your back?
[NAKANO] Good. Maybe you should
take it easy tonight, though.
Maybe.
You must be cold
from our adventure;
shall I heat up the bath water?
Yeah, that'd be awesome!
My hands are so cold
right now, they're numb.
'Kay!
Uh. Wait, Senko?
Is something wrong?
Listen. This may
sound kind of weird,
but I have a favor
to ask of you.
Go on.
[NAKANO] Would it be all right
if I warmed my hands up
in your tail?
[gasps]
I suppose, but just for today.
[NAKANO]
Seriously?
My, you're incorrigible.
I really appreciate
your indulging me, Senko.
[yelps]
[NAKANO] Feeling my cold
fingers gently warmed
in the embrace
of majestic floof.
This is what heaven feels like!
[gasping]
[SENKO sneezes]
I'm sorry, I never meant
to make you sick.
Are you feeling any better now?
[SENKO slurps]
I'm afraid there'll be a ban
on fluffing for a while.
--[NAKANO] What?!
--[SENKO] A ban!
[NAKANO]
Fair...
[CHILDREN chattering]
[NAKANO]
Mm?
[NAKANO] Senko has somehow
turned into a kotatsu.
She also said there was
a ban on tail fluffing.
If I touch it now,
I'm sure she'll be livid.
Uh.
[NAKANO]
What is this?
Is she giving me
the green light to fluff?
To fluff a kotatsu -heated
tail would be pure bliss.
[NAKANO]
It's so warm and soft!
Eep!
[NAKANO]
Kotatsu plus fluff.
It's the ultimate combination!
I don't want this to end!
Well, have you
had your fill, yet?
No, I want more.
But if you don't let me up soon,
I'm not going to be able
to start on dinner.
[NAKANO]
Just a little longer?
That's enough, I've only
just lifted the ban.
Besides, maybe I'll let you
fluff it again, later.
Uhh.
[SORA] Why don't you let the
young sir do as he pleases?
Yeah, that's right!
You should listen to--
Uh, wait. Who's that talking?
Eep!
You scoundrel.
Ah! Holy crap, I am so sorry!
It was a mere accident.
It's all right.
[NAKANO] Wait. Haven't
I seen her somewhere?
[SENKO]
Lady Sora?
Why is it that you've come here?
[SORA]
Why, indeed?
A fair question.
I suppose I wanted to toy with--
Oops. Uh, to come and meet you.
[NAKANO] I'm pretty sure
she actually meant "toy."
Uh?
Heh.
[gasps] Hold on.
Stop me if I'm wrong,
but weren't you the lady I met
in the snack shop at the beach?
Oh, good! So, you
remember me, do you?
How flattering.
I knew it!
I wanted to thank you for
the wonderful gifts.
Yes, thank you. They were
exceptionally delicious.
We really appreciated it.
Ah.
I'm afraid I had to punish
Shiro for that stunt.
She should know better
than to use the beach
without my permission. Yes?
Please! I beg your forgiveness,
I won't ever do it again and I
especially won't take anymore
of your stinky seaweed,
I promise!
[NAKANO]
Poor Shiro.
[SENKO]
Eep...
[SORA]
I shall introduce myself.
I am a demigod fox who has lived
many thousands of years,
and I go by the name of Sora.
To put it all rather simply,
I am what one might
consider Senko's boss.
It is my pleasure to make your
acquaintance, young sir.
[NAKANO]
So this is who Senko reports to?
Now that she mentions it,
I do get a sense
that's she a powerful
source of authority.
Right. My name is Nakano.
[NAKANO]
Whoa! She's like, travel-size!
Despite that,
she has a certain...
...larger-than-life feel.
[SORA gasps]
Oh my, it would seem your
wicked eyes have a terrible
habit of wandering. Do you
perhaps find me alluring?
Sorry, I didn't mean to
be boob-- I mean rude!
Heh. But what if I gave
you permission to look?
--[NAKANO] Uhh...
--[SENKO gasps]
[SORA]
I don't mind in the slightest.
Whoa! Hey!
Uh L-Lady Sora!
Please, I'd like to request
that you do not toy
with him so freely.
Oh, would you now?
But the poor boy cannot help
it if his eyes should wander.
You refuse to indulge him.
Hold on, that's not completely
true, I mean it's a little true,
but I still indulge
him in other ways,
just probably not in
the ways you're thinking!
It's completely true.
[NAKANO]
Uhh...
It would seem Sen has been
unable to satisfy you thus far.
I, however, am quite different.
There are many things
Sen cannot do.
But I possess talents that
I'm sure would please you.
Please, there's no need
to restrain yourself.
You want to, do you not?
[gulps]
I want to...
[SENKO gasps]
Heh.
I wanna jam my face right
into your huge, fluffy tail!
Just smother myself with it!
Please!
Of course you do.
Huh? My tail?
Yes!
Huh?
He doesn't need you!
Not your tail,
or any other tails,
for that matter!
[laughs] Well, isn't
that adorable?
This is quite
the delightful sight.
Even with my body on display,
all you can think
about is my tail.
How odd! You're a man
of strange tastes.
[NAKANO]
Uhh...
He's always been that way.
It's time that I bid you adieu.
Lest the boy touch my tail.
[SENKO grunts]
[sighs]
Oh, before I forget.
I do have some advice for you.
Regarding that perpetually
tired look on your face--
Do tread lightly.
Otherwise, I fear something
bad may happen to you.
So I hope that
you'll be careful.
Uh. What's that mean?
Don't make Sen sad.
That would be very
unwise of you.
What'd she say to you?
Farewell. Until we meet again.
Your boss is a real
force of nature.
Yes.
Still though,
I kind of enjoyed seeing
that new side of you.
It was interesting.
[gasps] I'm still no
match for Lady Sora.
You know, I wish you would
have at least told me
you knew the person I ran into
when we were back at the beach.
Man, I'm so happy
she's not a ghost.
What are you saying?!
Lady Sora is on a completely
different level
than a silly old ghost!
Compared to her,
a ghost is harmless!
[NAKANO]
'Kay.
More importantly, I've always
taken care of you, right?
Then why are you so enamored
with another fox's tail?
[NAKANO]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I even let you fluff my
tail whenever you want.
But I guess that's not
enough for you, huh?
Uh. Wait.
Hold on just a second.
What now?
Do I detect a hint of...
...jealousy?
[gasps] Whoa!
What are you talking about?
There's no way I am jealous!
I would never act so immature!
You don't get it.
Lady Sora is an immensely
powerful being!
Touching her tail could
have been real trouble.
Who knows what
would have happened?
Oh.
Therefore, I am not jealous.
It is nothing more than
motherly worry, so there.
[NAKANO]
Uh...
[NAKANO] For a mom,
you sure are adorable.
[SENKO]
Ugh. Don't patronize me!
I will take away your dinner,
young man!
[NAKANO]
I'm so sorry, Mother Senko.
[SENKO groans]
[NAKANO] She didn't put a lot
of effort into this meal.
Uhh...
[SENKO]
Hmph.
[NAKANO]
She's definitely mad.
Uh.
Otherwise, I fear something
bad may happen to you.
So I hope that
you'll be careful.
Uhh...
[SENKO grumbles]
[NAKANO] Is this what she
meant by something bad?
[SORA]
Don't make Sen sad.
That would be
very unwise of you.
--[NAKANO] Okay.
--[cutlery clinks]
[SENKO]
Huh?
Uh. This looks delicious!
Thanks for dinner!
Oh, wow.
Heh. As I recall, you've
always disliked this dish.
Uh?
I expect you to eat every bite.
Right.
Jeez, what's his problem?
That silly boy.
He's as clueless as ever.
[SORA]
Indeed he is.
Let us hope that it does
not go beyond that.
[SHIRO]
Huh?
[SORA laughs]
[SENKO]
Super Senko Time!
Hurry up, over here!
Look, I made us
an igloo. Ta-dah!
It's surprisingly cozy
in here, isn't it?
Yep!
Oh, try some amazake !
It'll warm you up in no time!
Even with your drink,
you might still be a bit cold.
Would you like
to use my fox-fire?
Uh?
I'm so glad that you're happy!
To be honest, it makes my whole
day to see you smile like that.
It makes me want
to smile, as well!
I really appreciate all the hard
work that you've done today.
Sleep well and sweet dreams!