[keyboard clacking]
[NAKANO yawns]
All done!
I can finally go home.
[NAKANO] I wonder what we're
having for dinner tonight?
[NAKANO] I feel like Senko
just up and appeared
out of nowhere one day.
But now I'm kinda used
to having her around.
It certainly has its perks.
With Senko around so much, I've
gotten used to having access
to fluffy fluff 27/7.
[NAKANO] I need to find a
way to show my gratitude
for all this special treatment.
Uh, Senko?
Permission to fluff fur?
My goodness,
you're incorrigible.
[NAKANO]
You know.
Maybe I've been
too indulgent lately.
[NAKANO]
I'm back.
Uh.
Hello, and welcome home!
[NAKANO]
Uhh...
Another one?
So you're him, huh?
Nakano?
Uh, yes?
My name is Shiro!
And I am renowned as
an Inari demigod fox!
[SENKO]
I'm sorry I didn't ask.
She said she'll leave right
after she eats dinner,
is that okay?
If you don't mind the
cramped space, then sure.
Besides, food is always
more delicious
when you're with good company.
I agree. I appreciate
your understanding.
[SENKO]
Here!
[NAKANO]
Thank you, Senko.
Let's dig in!
[NAKANO]
Wow...
Aah...
Twice the floof
under just one roof!
[SHIRO]
Excuse me?
Is there a reason you're staring
at me with such wicked eyes?
Uh, no, I'm sorry!
I was just admiring your tail--
it's so pretty and white.
Oh, I see. Naturally.
I suppose I can't blame
you for staring at it.
I'm not surprised that
it captivates you.
My snow-white tail, serves
as proof of my pure lineage!
[NAKANO gasping]
[SHIRO laughs]
[gasping]
The rice stuck to your face
makes it a little
less impressive.
[NAKANO]
She's not wrong.
Thank you for dinner!
Yes, thank you!
As usual, Sen, your fried tofu
was cooked to perfection!
For real. It was delicious!
Good, I'm happy to hear it!
Hardly surprising. Sen's
the best fried tofu cook
of all the fox demigods!
Oh, she is?
I could see that.
I'm sure she's just
exaggerating.
[SHIRO]
I most certainly am not!
Trust me, I love fried tofu and
yours is exceptionally good!
I stuffed myself silly!
And who's fault might that be?
I guess foxes like
fried tofu, huh?
I didn't know it was
such a favorite.
I wouldn't say it's our
absolute favorite.
[NAKANO]
Oh?
We are foxes, so technically
we're both omnivores.
Believe it or not, we're
a big fans of most meat.
[NAKANO]
I didn't know that.
Yes, fried tofu is
actually a substitute.
Cause people used to
give us mouse tempura.
Well that's an interesting
way to cook a mouse.
I'm surprised you didn't
know about that, Nakano.
Uh, sorry.
It wasn't that uncommon for us
to get a ton of fried
tofu as offerings.
Wow, that's a ton!
We didn't want to be wasteful,
so I'd find new ways to cook it.
And I guess after
so much of that,
it felt weird if
we didn't eat it.
[NAKANO]
I see. And now it's a habit.
Yep. I suppose, anyway.
Oh, but cooking it every
day must be a bit much.
I'm sure that you're tired of
eating it all the time, huh?
I'll find some other
things to make you.
[NAKANO]
It's fine.
Yeah?
You don't have to change
anything for me.
I'd feel weird if I
didn't eat your tofu.
Guess I've gotten
used to it now.
[SENKO] Are you sure
you're not secretly a fox?
[NAKANO]
Pretty sure,
I'm definitely lacking the
ears and the tail part.
Well, good! Because you'd look
silly with those things.
[SENKO]
Now that you've eaten,
isn't it about time for
you to head back home, Shiro?
Not quite yet.
You see, there's
more to my visit
than the desire to eat
your cooking, Sen.
[gasps]
Right. I also have
business with Nakano.
Me, really?
[SHIRO]
Now then...
Those who worship me
are always happy.
However, you my dear,
look particularly worn out.
Poor thing.
You must be exhausted
from your long day at work.
And that is why I'll
give you a treat.
Just this once,
you may pet my head!
--[SENKO sighs]
--[NAKANO] U-Uh...
[NAKANO]
Are you sure this is all right?
You're not going to get
mad and smite me, are you?
Of course not, I would never.
[SENKO grumbles]
Well, okay.
Yes, good! Just like that.
[NAKANO]
Whoa. This is amazing.
She looks so happy.
And it's like that happiness is
flowing into me when I pet her.
[SENKO]
Uh...
You can pet me. If you want.
[SHIRO laughs]
Uh, here goes.
You like to get pet, huh?
Sure. Once in a while.
[NAKANO]
I can't believe it.
It's double the fluff!
[NAKANO]
Wow.
I feel like I've died and
gone straight to heaven!
[NAKANO gasping]
[SENKO, SHIRO laughing]
[NAKANO laughs]
[SHIRO laughing]
[gasps]
What lovely petting!
I like you, Nakano.
Okay. Thank you?
I shall give you a reward.
Tell me what you'd like.
I'm not really sure.
Whoa! Hold on just a minute!
[SHIRO]
Stay out of this, Sen.
I wouldn't even be here if you
were actually satisfying him.
[gasps]
Uh. Hang on.
Senko's doing a great job!
She's been a huge help.
Come, there's no need
to restrain yourself.
Just relax and give in.
There's nothing you can hide
when you're around me.
My eyes see all.
More importantly,
my eyes know all.
Shiro! [gasps]
[SHIRO] Release the desires that
dwell deep within your heart!
Tell me what they are!
[NAKANO]
The desires... in my heart...
Now!
[NAKANO]
Let me.
[SHIRO]
"Let me"?
[BOTH]
Fluff your...
Hold on, you want
to fluff my tail?
That beautiful fur as
white as the driven snow.
It's so pretty. I've wanted
to pet it all night.
You have to let me fluff it,
just a little!
No way! Don't touch it!
Listen to me! Wait, Nakano!
No! Don't touch me!
Stay away!
[NAKANO moans]
[SHIRO whimpers]
Sen, please help me!
No.
[SHIRO]
Sen!
[gasps]
Fluffy fluff!
[SHIRO screams]
[whimpers]
Did you see that, the fluffy
fluff went through the wall!
--It's gone forever...
--[SENKO] Please calm down.
[KOENJI groaning] I am beyond
done with this stupid drawing!
I just wanna pet cats for a
living, is that so much to ask?
I'll get an imaginary cat!
Who's a good kitty, Tama?
[screams]
Hi!
Hi.
Uh. Tama?
Who's Tama? I'm Shiro.
My apologies.
[door opens, closes]
I guess I'm hallucinating
now, so yeah, that's cool.
On second thought,
I'mma sleep now.
G'night.
[SENKO]
Come on, it's not so bad.
It'll be okay, I have
a tail too, you know.
[NAKANO]
True.
Aww, Shiro's tail.
I wanted to fluff it so badly.
[SHIRO] Look after that boy?
You must be kidding.
There's no way I'll be
pampering him anytime soon.
Bleh!
[NAKANO]
I'm home...
[SENKO]
Hello and welcome back!
[water running]
[VOICE]
Your bathwater is now ready.
Good.
[SENKO] Are you okay?
The bath is all ready to use.
Right. Thanks.
Do you mind if I go first?
No, be my guest!
Actually, now that
I'm over here,
you do have a bit of a
strong scent to you.
I'd prefer you don't smell me.
I'm sorry Senko. I had to spend
all night at the office
and there's no way for
me to shower there.
That must have been
very hard for you.
Well, after you've
had your bath,
you can go straight
to sleep if you'd like.
I'll go take care of it
right now, thank you.
[NAKANO groans]
[splash]
[sighs]
[NAKANO]
I love baths.
The heat does
wonders for my back.
I could fall asleep right now.
[knocking]
[SENKO]
Excuse me.
Yeah, what's up?
You must be tired.
Would you like for me
to scrub your back?
[NAKANO]
Hard pass.
Please. There's no
need to be shy.
[gasping]
It's going to take way more than
a silly door to keep me out.
So you might as well
just give in, already.
[sighs] Right, you
move through walls.
[SENKO]
Don't worry.
I'm only going to
scrub your back.
It's all innocent, okay?
[NAKANO] Even if she is
over 800 years old,
she's still a woman.
[NAKANO]
Hang on a second.
What's the matter?
Can you at least
put a towel on?
Do I really need to?
I'm built more like a
plateau than a mountain,
so there's not much to see.
Well, if it doesn't matter
to you, then whatever.
Uh. But maybe in return, you
could let me scrub your back.
As a thanks for
always helping me out.
[SENKO]
Heh. You're so thoughtful!
[gasps]
[NAKANO] I'll be able to
see the base of her tail!
[NAKANO laughs]
[SENKO]
Huh?
[SENKO humming]
[NAKANO] It kinda feels weird to
be in this tiny bath with her.
But nothing ventured,
nothing gained!
Okay, it's all soaped
up and ready to go!
[NAKANO gasps]
[NAKANO]
Her hands are so warm.
The scrubbing is rough
but also gentle.
A perfect balance
between the two.
Having someone else scrub
these hard to reach places
so thoroughly feels
simply amazing!
If you don't mind, can you move
to the right a little bit?
Is this better?
Yes, it feels wonderful!
Thanks so much.
My pleasure.
[NAKANO]
Now that I think about it,
I feel like this moment should
be really uncomfortable,
but it's not.
Instead...
I just feel utterly at ease.
[NAKANO]
I guess in a way
it reminds me of my
childhood a bit.
It's like...
bathing with my family.
[SENKO] Any other spots
in need of scrubbing?
I'm good.
Okay then,
I shall rinse you off.
[sighs]
It sounds like that was
rather relaxing for you.
Yes, it was, you've got a real
knack for back scrubbing.
Well that's good to know,
I'm very glad to hear it.
[NAKANO] Okay, let's switch
places so I can repay the favor.
[SENKO laughs]
All right, sounds like a plan.
Okay then, are you ready?
Yep!
Hey, you're pretty
good at scrubbing!
Thanks, I'm trying.
[NAKANO]
It seems so odd.
But I never noticed how small
her back was before now.
Her skin is so
incredibly soft.
And her tail...
Wow. It's so cool
to see it like this.
Ready to rinse off?
[SENKO]
Sure!
[NAKANO gasps]
[SENKO]
Is something wrong?
Your face looks like you've
just seen a ghost.
[NAKANO]
Rest in peace, fluff.
[sighs]
There's nothing better
than a hot bath.
True.
It feels kinda like we're
a family bathing together.
Yeah? If that's the case,
I guess that makes
me the mother.
[laughs] It reminds me
of something.
A trick we used to do.
Oh, will you please
show it to me?
[NAKANO]
Prepare to be amazed!
[gasps] That was very amusing!
When I was a little kid,
I'd shoot water with
my hands constantly.
[SENKO]
Hm?
Give it a try, Senko.
'Kay! Just like this?
Yep.
And go!
I win!
Your shooting is quite superior.
Uh.
[NAKANO] Did I just get
excited over winning
a water shooting contest?
[SENKO]
To be honest.
[NAKANO]
Hm?
You just seemed so out of it
when you came home earlier.
I thought you might
fall asleep and drown.
I wanted to check on you.
Please don't push
yourself too hard.
I'm sorry to make you
worry about me.
I promise I'll try to be better.
[SENKO]
You've got it all wrong, silly!
Uh?
Have you forgotten
what I came here for?
If your job is wearing
you out that much,
then you should
just tell me that.
So I can take care of you.
Do you really mean it?
Whether it's work or a bath,
no matter what,
I won't let you drown.
[gasps]
[NAKANO]
I appreciate that.
Although to be fair,
this bath is a little
small for two people.
I suppose.
Oh, I know!
I should take you to the secret
magical hot spring sometime!
Oh, like a fox hot spring?
Yep! It's quite large
with a lovely view!
[NAKANO]
Cool! That sounds really fun.
I look forward to it.
[SENKO]
Noted!
[hair dryer whirrs]
[sighs]
[NAKANO]
That was an awesome bath.
But I wonder if her tail
will go back to normal?
[SENKO]
Ah, that's better.
You know what?
I'm starting to grow quite
fond of your "hair dryer."
[gasping]
Whoa, it's a miracle,
your tail is back to normal!
[SENKO]
Yes, of course it is.
As I'm sure you
probably already know,
tails are very important
to us demigod foxes.
That's why no matter
how busy I get,
I always take the time
to properly maintain it.
Gotta make sure
it's in tip-top shape!
--It's so fluffy!
--[SENKO] Easy!
Uh. I'm sorry,
I couldn't help it.
My goodness, I'm starting
to think your love for fluff
is a little troubling.
Oh, is it okay?
[SENKO]
Mm-hm.
Um. Earlier I was thinking...
that maybe I indulge in
this a bit too much.
[SENKO]
Maybe, but...
If it's something that
makes you feel better,
then I'm happy to oblige!
Thanks.
[SENKO]
Of course.
[NAKANO]
So I'm free to pet it?
Yep.
[NAKANO]
Mm! Fluffy fluff!
[SENKO]
Eep!
Be careful, okay?
It's sensitive!
[NAKANO] I was able to fluff
to my heart's content.
All thanks to Senko.
[SENKO]
Super Senko Time!
Hi, welcome home!
You must have had
a terribly long day.
It seems as though we've had
nothing but rainy weather
these past few days.
I'm afraid it's made a real
mess out of my tail.
As you may have already noticed,
it's not quite as fluffy
as it usually is.
So I thought I'd give it a
good old fashioned combing!
♪ Combing my tail,
get out the knots, ♪
♪ brushy brush brush,
So it's nice n' soft ♪
There! How's that?
Would you like to fluff
it a little bit?
I should warn you my
tail is sensitive,
so touching it startles
me sometimes,
but I don't want you to worry.
As long as it relaxes you, then
that's all that matters to me.
If it helps you after
a long day of work,
then you have my
permission to fluff away!
Thank you for all of
your hard work today.
Once you're done fluffing,
it's off to bed with you.
Good night, and sweet dreams.