[door opens]
[NAKANO]
I'm home...
Yay, I'm so glad you're back!
[exhales]
[SENKO]
Oh, my!
You look even more worn
down than you usually do!
Sure, that makes
me feel better.
Well, at least
tomorrow is Sunday!
Now you can finally
rest a little bit.
Oh.
The thing is, I actually have
to go into the office tomorrow.
[SENKO]
You do?! But why though?
I don't understand why
you must go into work
on your only day off!
You know. I don't
understand it, either.
[SENKO]
Your work must be terrible!
If you keep working this much,
I'm certain it will
be the end of you.
Can you not take time off?
[NAKANO] There are people who
have to work way more than I do.
But that has nothing
to do with my complaint.
It sucks, but it'll be okay.
Thanks to all your help,
I've been able to relax a
lot more than usual lately.
[SENKO grumbles]
I do have to be careful that I
don't accidentally sleep in.
Better set my alarm
before I forget.
Yes, well, I've been
thinking about that.
Is it not difficult to be awoken
by such a crude sound?
That's it!
I've just had the
most wonderful idea!
I shall gently awaken
you in the morning
using my tender love and care!
Yeah, okay. But you do have
to actually wake me up.
[SENKO]
Yes, of course!
Are you insinuating
that I wouldn't?
I promise you have
nothing to worry about!
Us old folks are great
at waking up early!
That's an old person thing?
Well... It's something
that I do, anyway.
[NAKANO]
You're like an old woman
and a little girl combined.
Okay, then.
I officially dub thee my alarm
for tomorrow morning.
Got it!
Man, I'm wiped.
[SENKO]
Are you okay?!
Fluffy fluff.
So soft.
[SENKO]
My goodness.
He's so stubborn.
He really fights being pampered.
But somehow all that
makes him even cuter.
[SENKO yawns]
Whew!
The weather outside is
simply gorgeous today!
It's perfect for
drying the laundry!
Oh. That's right,
I almost forgot,
I promised I would be
his alarm clock today.
[SENKO] He looks so peaceful
when he's sleeping.
It almost seems cruel
to wake him up.
But it must be done!
Wakey, wakey. It's morning.
Time to greet the day.
Uh...
Wha... I...
C'mon, out of bed, sleepyhead!
Yeah. But... I just
wanna keep sleeping.
Uh.
I know, but you told me
you have things to do today.
Uh. But five more minutes.
All right then.
Per your request, I shall wake
you again in five minutes.
[NAKANO]
Hooray.
Thank you, Senko.
[SENKO]
Hold on just a moment.
Could it be the mornings
actually make him weak?
He's usually so resistant
when I try to pamper him.
This is my chance!
Hey.
Didn't I have to go into
work today or something?
[SENKO]
You always work so hard,
even on the days you
should have off.
That's true.
Work's stupid,
and I don't wanna go.
I want more sleep.
Then why don't you stay home
and relax a little bit?
[NAKANO grunts]
[SENKO]
Wow. This is great!
Things are so much easier
when he just gives in
and lets me spoil him!
Ugh. I should probably
get out of bed already.
But it's Sunday, remember?
There's no need to get up
or work on your day off.
That's a fair point.
Not to mention, it's important
for you to get plenty of rest.
True...
It's healthy to sleep
all day sometimes!
In fact, I'll go back to sleep!
Let's indulge in the
extra rest together!
Huh...
Here, I'll even let you
cuddle with my tail!
Go ahead and fluff it
all you want!
[NAKANO]
Fluffy-fluff?
[SENKO]
Mm-hm!
Man, I wanna bury
my face right in it.
Please do!
[chopping]
[NAKANO]
Crap! Why is it so late?
How long have I been asleep?
Oh, man...
There's no way I can
just go into work now.
At this point, the day's
practically already over.
[SENKO]
Are you awake?
You were sleeping pretty deeply.
Just like a lil' baby.
[NAKANO]
Uhh...
Y-You know, earlier, I didn't
know what I was doing!
I wish you would act
that way more often.
[NAKANO] Yeah, well...
I wouldn't bet on it.
Can we just forget
about this morning?
No way!
C'mon, pretty please?
[SENKO]
Not a chance!
There's nothing wrong
with how you acted.
You're biased. Doesn't matter.
Tomorrow things
go back to normal.
I don't understand.
Well, I have to make up
for slacking off today.
Both at my job and as
a person in general.
[SENKO]
Do you really?
Uh.
Please don't push yourself.
'Kay.
Right. Do not fret,
for tomorrow I shall be sure
to wake you up properly!
No, that's okay.
Wait. I promise that it won't
be a repeat of this morning.
Really, it's something I can
probably manage by myself.
[SENKO] But I won't let
you go back to sleep!
[NAKANO]
Your eyes are creepy.
No they're not!
--[NAKANO] Heh.
--[SENKO grumbles]
[SENKO]
Hm?
Uh?!
Look, you don't need to rely
on that noisy contraption,
I'm going to do my very best
to wake you up tomorrow
so please leave
everything to me, okay?
Fine, if you insist.
Excellent!
[NAKANO] I'm going to do
my best tomorrow, too.
So, can I maybe fluff your
tail a little bit more?
[SENKO] I think you've done than
more than enough for one day.
[SENKO humming]
Senko, Hey.
Is that fox fire your using?
Yep! That's right.
[NAKANO]
Not a fan of the stove, huh?
No, it's not that.
I'm sure the stove works fine.
But I prefer fox fire, because
then I can control the flame.
[NAKANO] I've noticed it makes
a great night-light, as well.
[SENKO]
Yes, it's a bit of a habit.
[NAKANO]
Isn't it dangerous, though?
[SENKO]
There's nothing to worry about!
You see,
I've been using fox fire
for over 800 years!
So, no matter the style
of stove, hearth, or bath...
...I can handle all of them!
Except those things don't
really matter anymore.
It seems very few things
run on fire now.
Yeah. These days we use
machines for everything.
True. I do suppose
the times have changed.
Anyway.
It's still important that I
don't fall out of practice.
Additionally, this flame serves
a much bigger purpose.
Huh?
More than anything,
it's the embodiment
of my burning love
for you! Fa-woosh!
Take it!
And we save
on the gas bill, too!
[SENKO]
So practical.
Well, it would seem the rainy
season is upon us once again.
I dunno, all this rain and
humidity really wears me out.
I kind of miss the sun, ya know?
The rain has never
bothered me that much.
Uh. It's pouring out here.
So, hey. Any chance
you can fix it?
Control the weather, huh?
All right, here goes nothing.
Wait, I'm just kidding!
I didn't think you
could actually do it.
I sure can!
Listen, if it gets too
hot at any point,
feel free to use the AC.
AC?
[NAKANO]
Yeah, it's that box on the wall.
[SENKO]
Oh, that thing?
[NAKANO]
We talked about it before.
Remember how to turn it on?
Yeah, it's more like
I'm not used to it.
Oh, machines. Your one weakness,
who would have thought?
Sometimes you're like
a cute old lady.
[SENKO grumbles] How dare you
call me an old lady!
[NAKANO]
Hold on, but you called yourself
an old person just
the other night!
Yes, I'm allowed to
say those things,
but you on the other hand,
are another story!
Right. Message received.
Well, I should get going.
[SENKO grunts]
Have a good day at work,
see ya later!
[SENKO]
Machines, huh?
Perhaps I shall
attempt to use them.
I believe it's this one...
Here.
Wow! It did something!
Ooh, I can feel the wind,
it's so nice and cold!
It's almost like fox magic!
That was actually simple.
He explained the basics,
but next I'll master them!
Reading glasses... on!
[SENKO]
Let's see...
I believe he referred
to you as "the vacuum."
However, I don't
much care for you.
[vacuum whirs]
[SENKO] As I recall, you are far
too noisy for your own good.
Regardless, I must
face my fears!
Okay. I shall conquer you!
--[vacuum whirs]
--[SENKO screams]
[SENKO whimpers]
That's enough!
I command you to turn
off this instant!
Be quiet! I don't understand
why you must be so noisy!
[SENKO muffled] Stop it!
Bad Mister Vacuum!
[KOENJI]
Sounds like cleaning sucks...
I understand those feels.
[vacuum stops]
[SENKO panting]
See there?
I told you I'd conquer you.
Who needs silly machines?
I can handle the cleaning
all by myself!
Unacceptable.
And just what would
he think of me?
You're so useless.
[sighs] Dumb floof-ball.
[ringing]
Yes. He'd say that.
I know it!
Snap out of, Senko!
No way he'd ever say
something so mean!
Right, I nearly forgot!
I can do the laundry
in the washing machine.
So, you'll take care
of the laundry for me?
We shall be fast friends!
Huh...
It says to load in the dirty
clothes from the top.
Then pour in some detergent.
This machine sure does have
a lot of buttons. Uh!
This one!
[SENKO]
Neat, it's already spinning!
This isn't so hard.
Oh, no. Watching it
makes feel all dizzy.
[beeping]
[SENKO]
Wow. Is it already finished?
How efficient! Okay!
Let's see now... Uh...
They're very sudsy.
Bad machine!
It's easy to see these
are not properly washed!
You are not very
good at your job.
♪ Scrubity dubity
rubity dubity! ♪
[SENKO humming]
[SENKO] Now all that's left
is to fix dinner.
Perhaps I shall try to
use the stove this time.
Twist it like so.
Where is the flame at?
Oh my goodness!
Well then, Mister Stove,
perhaps I was wrong about you,
it seems you're
also quite capable
of controlling your
flame, aren't you?
And with the refrigerator,
everything is nice and cold.
Food stays fresher
much longer now.
Wait, this rice cooker
can really make stuff
with a push of a button?
Ah. You're doing splendidly!
[SENKO sighs] It's nice not
having to watch the fire.
Life is so much easier
than it used to be.
Well, since I have
nothing better to do,
I guess I could make
some plum wine.
This is something you
can't use a machine for.
Plus it's one of my favorite
rainy season pastimes.
[SENKO humming]
[SENKO hums]
There, it's all done!
[gasps] Oh, my.
Now it feels a little
too cold in here.
Better turn it off.
--[music plays]
--[TANUKIMAN laughing]
[SENKO] The TV has turned
on all by itself!
Uh! A dead end?
[TANUKIMAN] At last, you're
right where I want you! [laughs]
[YOKO]
You again?!
There's no escaping me
this time, Inari Girl!
[gasps]
[TANUKIMAN]
Take this!
[YOKO screams]
[TANUKIMAN laughing]
Oh, no! Please be quiet!
[TANUKIMAN] You're finished!
Say goodnight!
[SENKO]
Why is it getting louder?!
[hissing]
[SENKO gasps]
What was that?
The rice cooker?
[beeping]
That noise... Uh... What now?
[air blowing, beeping continues]
[gasping]
Eep, I'm under attack!
[screams]
Help me! The machines
are all so angry!
Would you all just
be quiet already?
[gasps]
[SENKO muffled shouting]
[KOENJI]
What's goin' on?
What do I press
to turn it all off?
Is it this one?
Or this one? Or this one?
[laughing]
That's enough! Stop it!
I command you!
[gasps]
Weird, I guess she's okay.
I'm home.
Huh? Uh, Senko?
[light switch clicking]
[NAKANO]
The lights won't turn on.
Hey, Senko?
What the heck?
What on earth happened to you?
Please forgive me, I...
I really am nothing
but a dumb floof-ball.
[NAKANO] I'm confused,
why are you sitting in the dark?
[SENKO] All of the machines got
really loud and stopped working.
Just try and settle down.
I'm sure everything's fine.
See, the breaker tripped.
Nothing to worry about.
[SENKO grumbles]
Right.
Uh. I am concerned
about any food
we had in the fridge, though.
Good, it looks like
everything survived.
[SENKO]
Yes.
But we should probably cook the
meat tonight, just to be safe.
[NAKANO]
True.
Better check the stuff
in the freezer, too.
[NAKANO]
Whoa!
It's like some kind
of fried-tofu stash.
[SENKO] I guess we'll have
to cook all these, as well.
Uh. Like all of it, all of it?
[SENKO]
I am ashamed.
I can't believe I have managed
to cause you so much trouble.
[NAKANO] Cheer up,
it's not that big of a deal.
[SENKO]
Uh?
Besides...
Just seeing your smiling
face is more than enough.
It always brightens my mood.
My goodness.
That moment would have
been much more tender
without the tail
touching, you know.
This also brightens my mood.
[SENKO]
Oh, no.
It looks like the rice
never finished cooking.
Do you feel like
eating rice porridge?
Yeah that sounds really good.
[SENKO] All right!
I'll have it ready in no time!
Cool.
[SHIRO]
Hmph. What is Sen doing?
She made such a big deal
about going to help Nakano,
only to go and screw it up!
I can't believe her.
[YOZORA exhales]
Indeed. I fear at this rate,
we won't be able to rid the
young sir of his darkness.
Well then, there is
no other choice!
I, the great Shiro, will have
to go and pamper him myself!
To his heart's content.
[SENKO]
Super Senko Time!
Hello, welcome home!
Oh my, it looks as though
you've had another long day.
[gasps] You poor dear, you seem
a little more tired than usual.
At times like this, it's best to
try and go to sleep a bit early.
Actually, I was thinkin' about
heading to bed early myself!
[SENKO]
Can't fall asleep?
Well okay, then. How's this?
You can always fluff up
my tail if you want to.
Better?
Do you feel like
you're tired yet?
You're not? You still can't
fall asleep, can you?
Let me see.
If you would like, I can
sing a lullaby just for you.
All right, go on and
close your eyes.
♪ Rock a bye baby,
in the tree top, ♪
♪ when the wind blows
the cradle will rock ♪
Sleep tight.
And as always, sweet dreams.