Hello there!
I, the Great Shiro,
have come to pamper you!
[KOENJI]
Huh?
Oops, this is the
wrong domicile.
If you'll please excuse me.
More hallucinations?
Okay.
Time for a nap.
Hello there! I, the Great Shiro,
have come to pamper you!
Again?
Do as you please, but he's
probably going to try
and fluff your tail, Shiro.
Come on, Senko, I'm not
gonna force myself on her.
Did you just wake up?
Look, if I'm going to be here,
you have to at least
pay attention to me.
I can't believe you're still
laying around in bed.
Well, he hasn't had a proper
day off in quite a while,
so I told him to take
it easy today.
What? I took time out of my
day for this! Laying about
instead of accepting my
pampering is just rude!
He's tired, plus he's
been working a lot lately.
Thank you, but
I'm sure I'll be fine.
Do ya wanna play
some video games?
What're those?
They're a modern
leisure activity.
That sounds fun, count me in!
Machines can be pretty tricky,
are you sure you can
even handle them?
Oh, I'm quite positive.
It'll be a cinch.
I, the Great Shiro, shall play
with you until you drop!
♪♪♪
[SHIRO]
Boing!
[SHIRO laughs]
I rather enjoy
these video games!
I do not find it so difficult.
Yes, you seem to have
a real knack for them.
You managed to clear the
tutorial stages rather quickly.
It's a simple task, really.
When your brain isn't
stuck in the past.
[gasps]
Aw. I guess you're
too old to keep up
with the latest trends,
arent' you?
[SENKO]
Eep...
[NAKANO]
She's been called out.
Is something the matter?
No, I'm all right.
Uh... I have other games
if you wanna change it up.
[SHIRO]
Hm...
I'm not sure which one
I should play, though.
They all look like fun.
How odd.
I didn't realize you liked to
play these video games so much.
I do. In fact, I buy
them frequently.
The real problem is
I don't have time to play any
of them, so they just pile up.
[SENKO]
What a waste.
[SHIRO]
Here! I have picked one.
[NAKANO]
"Fluff Bros Melee"?
Careful, as I recall, that
one is especially tough!
I'm not worried about it.
Okay, we're all set.
Excellent, now why don't you
take a seat right here?
'Kay.
Good boy.
[NAKANO gasps]
Ta-dah!
Behold my brand-new
human backrest!
[NAKANO gasping]
[NAKANO] And it comes
with a petting mode.
[laughs] I approve of this mode!
You make an incredibly
comfortable chair!
I feel as though I could sit
here and play games all day!
In that case, I'm happy
to be of service.
[NAKANO] It's kinda like
playing with a kid.
[SHIRO]
What? That's against the rules!
The machine is cheating!
[NAKANO] You have to resist
the urge to attack there.
Victory!
[NAKANO]
Nice comeback.
[SHIRO giggles]
Fair warning, the next
guy'll be even stronger.
Oh? I will crush them!
[NAKANO]
I'm actually enjoying this.
Watching her play is fun.
[SHIRO]
Prepare to be slain!
[SENKO]
Okay you two.
It's time for a snack break.
It's my specialty, ohagi !
Oh, boy!
Uh, hey, are you all
right over there?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh! Your ohagi is
always delicious!
I'm so excited!
[NAKANO]
This is too much.
She looks so happy
when she's eating.
Yum!
Sen's cooking is on an
entirely different level!
I'll have another!
My goodness, you're getting
crumbs everywhere, Shiro.
Stop mothering me!
You're hopeless.
No matter how old you get,
you're still like a little
kid sometimes.
Now the other side.
[NAKANO] You know,
hanging out like this is fun.
I'm going to put your
tea down over here.
Thanks a lot!
[NAKANO]
It feels like we're a family.
Just spending our day off at
home and relaxing together.
Here's yours. Drink up.
Wow, thanks a lot,
I really appreciate it.
No problem.
♪♪♪
[SENKO] Oh my. There's only
one ohagi left.
And you haven't had
one yet, have you?
No, but I sure was
thinking about it.
Hey. Any possibility
we could share it?
No way, so back off!
You've already eaten
most of them!
--Aww!
--[NAKANO chuckles]
[SHIRO]
I have a proposal.
I say we play for it, and
whoever wins the next match
in the video game gets
the last ohagi !
Oh come on, Shiro, don't
you think you're being
just a little bit greedy?
So the winner takes all, huh?
Okay, I'm down.
But don't expect me
to go easy on you.
That's fine, it's more exciting
when you play for real!
I, the Great Shiro,
am not the kind of coward
to back down from a fight.
And besides, I may be new to
video games, but didn't you say
you haven't had time
to play lately?
Yeah. I guess I did say that.
[NAKANO] But that doesn't
mean I intend to lose.
I haven't been able to play
much since I started working.
But back when I was a student,
I'd stay up all night
playing the previous
title. Plus...
...I really wanna
eat that ohagi !
[NAKANO]
Get ready!
I will crush you!
[SHIRO laughs]
Huh? Wait. Oh, man.
[MALE GAME VOICE]
Winner: Maki!
Dude, I barely even
touched you.
I know! You made
it easy for me.
[sighs] You're pretty good, huh?
It's almost like you knew
what I was gonna do
before I even did it.
Oh, you think so?
There, there now, it's okay.
Try not to get upset.
It's not your fault
that you lost.
Huh?
She only won the match
because she used her inner eye
to read your mind while
the two of you were playing.
[gasping]
Hey! Some people call that
cheating, you know!
But I was simply using all
the tools at my disposal.
Poor Nakano.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you were just outfoxed.
But I appreciate the ohagi !
[gasping]
[NAKANO]
Okay. Now it's starting to feel
like she's rubbing it in.
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
I actually have some
leftover bean paste filling.
I'll use it to make
some sesame ohagi.
Give me just a minute
and I'll whip it up.
[gasps]
[SHIRO] No fair, I want
some sesame ohagi, too!
I think you've already
had more than enough.
Well, I'd argue otherwise!
I haven't had any of your
delicious food lately!
Do you want me to
waste away to nothing?
All right. One more.
[SENKO, SHIRO]
Hm?
Are you serious, way to go,
that's the warrior spirit,
and whoever wins this round gets
to eat all of the sesame ohagi !
Got it! I'll definitely
win this time.
[SHIRO]
You heard the man.
The winner gets dibs
on the treats!
Okay, I'll go get
started on them.
You know, even without
the mind-reading thing,
I gotta say, you're surprisingly
good at video games.
Duh! I, the Great Shiro,
am a genius, after all!
Although I have to admit
you do make it easy.
I mean, all you do is
think about the things
you don't want to
happen in the game.
[NAKANO] Okay, I'm getting
ready to attack,
I hope she doesn't
see it and counter!
[SHIRO laughs]
You fool!
I just do whatever
you're afraid of.
[NAKANO]
Huh?
Yep, you're a victim
of your own fears.
[NAKANO] So, I'm basically
losing to myself...
♪♪♪
[MALE GAME VOICE]
Winner: Maki!
[SENKO whimpers]
I should probably
be heading back now.
That was a lot of fun.
Let me know if you're ever
up for another beating.
Uh, Shiro wait, that wall
leads to our neighbor's!
Uh. You don't say?
Oh yeah, I think I accidentally
barged in on her earlier.
[BOTH gasp]
Heh! Bye!
[door creaks, slams]
[NAKANO] Poor Koenji.
I bet that was confusing.
[SENKO] Yeah. Guess we
should go apologize.
[KOENJI]
My name is Yasuko Koenji.
I'm a manga artist, and
I'm also a college student.
Finally done!
[KOENJI] Sometimes it's hard to
balance my time between the two,
but I feel like I still
have a pretty full life.
However... I do have
one small problem.
And that's...
[KOENJI]
Coming!
Good afternoon.
[KOENJI] My neighbor
is too freakin' cute!
Hi Senko, you look
lovely, as always.
[SENKO]
Flattery won't get you extras,
but it will at least
get you this.
Thanks so much.
I really appreciate it!
I'm happy to be of service,
although I am sorry
that we bothered you.
[KOENJI]
Huh?
[SENKO] I heard that Shiro
dropped in on you a few times.
Shiro?
--Hi.
Uh. Tama?
Who's Tama? I'm Shiro.
Hello there!
I, the Great Shiro, have
come to pamper you!
So it wasn't a
hallucination, then?
Uh... Would it be all
right if I came in?
[KOENJI]
Yeah, for sure!
[SENKO gasping]
You've managed to make quite
a mess in here, haven't you?
I haven't had time
to clean lately.
[stomach rumbles]
And judging by the sound
of your stomach,
I doubt you've been
eating properly.
Maybe?
If it pleases you, perhaps
while you enjoy your lunch,
I could tidy up your apartment.
Okay, knock yourself out.
Oh, wow! Thanks so much, Senko!
My pleasure.
Delicious!
[SENKO laughs]
Look at all this trash.
My goodness.
I guess I'll need to sort it
by burnable and non-burnable.
[KOENJI] Senko is a pretty
mysterious person.
On the outside, she looks like
a super cute, young cosplayer.
But she's actually super
helpful and responsible.
And even though she
looks really young,
she's got this sorta
motherly vibe to her.
The craziest part of all is,
she claims to be an adult,
and I think she and my other
neighbor are a couple.
She's like a Lolita, but legal!
I'm mad jealous.
Her ears and tail
are so life-like,
sometimes I think they're real.
[SENKO] Oh. I see, so this
is the "manga" thing
you told me about?
How neat! It's fascinating.
[KOENJI] Her speech is a little
old-fashioned, and there's a lot
she doesn't know about
the modern world.
[KOENJI] It's weird, but
there are times I suspect
that she may be
an actual fox girl.
But this is real life,
not a manga.
So yummy!
[KOENJI] Whatever, there's no
way she could be a bad person
when she makes food
this delicious.
[SENKO]
Well, that's a start, at least.
Huh?
[sighs]
You call this a "start,"
seriously?!
That's right!
Wow, thank you!
I didn't realize my
room was this big.
I'm sure all the clutter might
have contributed to that.
I put your smaller things
into this box here.
I'm really sorry, you shouldn't
have to take care of me
like this. First food,
now cleaning?
Think nothing of it,
pampering you brings me
a great deal of pleasure!
[gasping]
[KOENJI] Having an adorable
cosplayer around is one thing,
but she cooks and cleans
on top of that, bonus!
I wish I knew how to thank her.
Uh.
[KOENJI]
Cosplay!
[SENKO]
Uh?
[KOENJI]
S'gotta be in here somewhere!
Uh, you're sort of making
a big mess again.
[KOENJI]
Found it! Here, Senko!
For you! Why don't
you try it on?
[SENKO]
Huh?
Go on, I think it's your size!
[SENKO] Dare I ask why
you possess an outfit
in a size other than your own?
I originally bought it as
a reference for my manga,
but I don't use it anymore!
That's very generous, but I'm
not interested in a new outfit.
Just think about it,
I bet your husband would love it
if you changed up your costume!
Plus you'll look crazy
adorable in it!
You really think so?
[KOENJI]
Absolutely!
I promise this outfit is
going to blow his mind!
[KOENJI]
Blow his mind!
[KOENJI laughs]
How's it goin' in there,
Senko, you almost ready?
[SENKO]
Uh. Almost.
[gasping]
[SENKO]
Am I wearing this right?
Yes! You're slaying!
Incredible! No, better
than incredible!
The perfect fox-maid combo!
Would you mind giving
me a little pose?
Uh, will this suffice?
[KOENJI]
Oh-em-gee, I'm dying!
[KOENJI screams]
Wow! That was amazing.
Well, I'm happy that
you enjoyed yourself.
[KOENJI]
You can keep the maid cosplay.
It's my gift to you.
Really, are you sure?
Totally, I don't
need it anymore.
You're always helping me out, so
this is my way of saying thanks.
[SENKO] In that case,
I promise I shall cherish it.
If my company really
pleases you that much,
then perhaps I'll
visit again soon.
Goodbye then.
[KOENJI]
Come by anytime.
Will do.
[door shuts]
[exhales]
Ah! Senko is so freakin'
cute it's not fair!
I hate you, Nakano!
If she wasn't your wife,
I would've been all over her!
My self-control is top notch!
Go me!
Aww, I'm insanely jealous.
I wish I had a cute
cosplayer wife, too.
[NAKANO]
I'm home.
Uh.
It is a pleasure to see
you again, dear Master.
[NAKANO gasping]
[SENKO]
Eep! Why did you run away?
[NAKANO]
Senko! They'll see you!
[SENKO]
But why did you go outside?
Well, you just kind of
took me by surprise is all.
So I needed a couple of
minutes to compose myself.
Wait, are you trying to say
that you do not approve
of my change of clothes?
No, I... Uh, it's not
that I don't like it,
if anything,
I think it suits you.
You look wonderful.
[sighs] Good, that
makes me very happy.
And actually, Koenji is the one
who gave me these clothes,
she said that every man
loves a girl in a maid outfit.
You are gonna blow his mind!
[NAKANO] For some reason,
I'm not surprised.
So, do I even wanna
know why our neighbor
has a maid outfit in your size?
She said it was reference
material for her manga.
Oh yeah, that's right,
I completely forgot
she works as a manga artist.
[SENKO]
Yep!
I wonder what kinda
manga she draws.
[SENKO] She showed me
some of it earlier,
and it appears to feature
quite a few maids.
[NAKANO]
That makes sense.
Here's an idea, though.
I think it'd be interesting to
see a bit of Japanese taste
mixed in, like a maid outfit
from the Taisho era.
Is that a fact?
Uh, I mean!
It's just a thought!
Right.
[NAKANO] Listen, while I am
glad that I got to see you
in a maid cosplay, I think I
prefer your normal clothes.
You do?
I mean...
How do I put this?
I guess it doesn't feel
much like home this way.
Does that sound weird to you?
[gasps]
[laughs]
Uh, is something funny?
No, you've made me very happy.
If being around me relaxes you,
that means having me here
has become normal for you.
[inaudible]
[NAKANO]
I'm not sure if "normal"
is the appropriate word.
But yeah,
I guess I have gotten used to
you being here all the time.
Well, of course you have,
that's no great surprise.
In that case, I'd like
to make a request.
May I fluff your tail?
You know, to show my gratitude!
[SENKO] I think you just
want to fluff more.
What the heck?
How adorable! That outfit
is simply amazing!
--[SENKO] Super--
--[SHIRO] Shiro Time!
Took you long enough!
I, the Great Shiro, have come
to grace you with my pampering,
so hurry up and get
in here already!
Ta-dah! What do you think, isn't
my maid outfit beyond adorable?
It's frilly and cute, right?
Yes! Feel free to
praise me even more!
Huh? You think that the contrast
between dark and
light is pretty?
I know, my, you have an
excellent eye for fashion!
Welcome back home, Master,
did you have a nice day?
I've prepared you some hot tea.
Wait, what was that,
"You must be dressed like
the Taisho Era Nostalgia Maid.
The Japanese elements
suit you perfectly.
It's just what I prefer"?
How dare you give her
more praise than me!
Be careful, you almost made
me spill the master's tea.
Yeah, but... it's not fair!
It's late and
the master is tired.
So please try and keep
your voice down, okay?
Fine, drink your dumb tea.
Oh, once you're finished
we can play some
video games together!
After this it's bedtime.
[SENKO] Thank you for all
of your hard work today.
I hope that you're able
to sleep well tonight.
[SHIRO]
Yeah, have sweet dreams!