[MIKI] I never really mastered
the art of playing around.
[MALE 01]
Come on, you slowpoke!
[GIRL 01]
I don't think I can.
[MIKI]
Fun was just a word to me.
I never really understood
what it meant.
But I like to think
there are things
in life worth waiting for.
[MIDORI]
Miki!
[AYA]
Look up here!
[MIKI] And that sometimes
it takes other people
to teach you to
have a good time.
Without meaning to,
I found those people.
[AYA screams]
[MIKI]
Oh my gosh!
[MIKI] Aya was the first
to cross my path.
And later that same day,
I was introduced to
tabletop games by Midori
and her manager
at the Saikoro Club.
[MIKI]
But that would mean...
Yep! We're the
indisputable champs!
[MIKI]
Eventually, we met Emmy.
The school festival followed
this fateful encounter,
and with it came maid
outfits and lots of fun!
How's it going?
Kind've an early bird today.
Were you waiting long?
[MIKI]
Mm‐mm.
Shall we make our way to school?
Right.
[PRINCIPAL]
What you do today...
[MIKI] It's the final day of
our first year at Kamogawa
North High School.
[PRINCIPAL]
...by giving your best,
realizing they can never
come back again.
You only get one life, so
choose to make it a success!
[MIKI] I guess it's out with
the old me and in with the new.
All right! Bring on the
second year of awesomeness!
You sure seem psyched.
[AYA laughs]
Typical. Seriously, though.
I can't believe this
year's already over.
Yeah. I'm with you there.
Transferring made it
feel even shorter!
That, and because
it was so much fun!
Something on your mind, Miki?
Uh.
Whatever it is,
it's making you happy,
Oh. Yeah.
I was just remembering this past
year, and how much fun I had.
This has been
the best year... ever.
Miki, I'm so glad
I got to know you.
[EMILIA] Ja! Meeting you
helped make this year
a good one for me, too!
Emmy!
[MIDORI]
She beat me to the punch.
I'm also grateful we were
able to meet each other!
Same here. Thanks, Aya.
[MIKI] It'd be nice... if it
could always be like this.
If these fun times never ended.
[AYA] Omigosh! I just
thought of something!
How cool would it be
if all four of us
were in the same
class next year?
I'm sorry to burst your bubble,
but that won't be happening.
What? No chance at all?
Classes separate by major
starting from second year.
I would've thought
you knew that.
Emmy and I will be
focusing on science.
You and Miki will
be in humanities.
‐‐[MIKI] Huh?
‐‐[AYA] Wait! Are you for real?
Then, two of us are going to
be separated, no matter what.
Or even worse! What if
none of us are together?!
Don't think that way!
Maybe we could take
a trip somewhere
during spring break if
that's how it turns out.
Good plan!
Absolutely.
All right!
I'm sorry, but I can't join you.
Huh?
This year, I'm spending my
spring break in Germany.
It's been ages since I've gone,
and I'll be seeing my
grandma this time around.
Both of my parents
are going as well,
so it will be a
whole family affair.
Aw, okay.
You shouldn't miss out on
quality time with your family.
That's right!
Your family should come first.
Plus, your grandma must be
really looking forward to it.
True! Thank you
for understanding.
Uh?
But that's not the
only reason I'm going.
I have another motive.
Huh?
My Papa is well acquainted with
an editor at a game publisher.
And I have every intention
of showing him my game.
[GIRLS gasp]
In Germany, aspiring
game authors must first
bring their games
to an editor‐‐
which is typical for
any kind of author.
If they happen to like what
they're shown, the editors,
more often than not,
will publish the games
just like that.
[MIKI]
I had no idea.
If you're setting up editor
visits, you must've made a game!
Ja! The dedication Midori
put into prepping her game
for that competition
was inspiring.
Was it really?
Ja, of course.
It made me want to work
that much harder to
realize my dream, too.
Emmy.
Actually, the results for said
competition are right here.
[BOTH gasp]
Okay! So is it good or bad?
You cool with us taking a look?
Sure.
"To the fledgling game
designer it may concern..."
[EMILIA, GEORGE]
First of all,
thank you for applying to
our company's competition.
My team and I thoroughly enjoyed
playing the game
you submitted to us.
The board's design was
outstanding, as was the concept
of freely arranging
furniture around it.
Several team members rated
your game remarkably high.
Wow! That's pretty
impressive, Midori!
Well done!
You haven't finished
reading it yet.
"However"...
[GEORGE] ...I still believe
some indispensable pieces
are missing. This sentiment
was especially strong
in regard to the mechanics‐‐
they're in need of
some improvement.
Unfortunately, due to
these shortcomings,
your game has failed.
[GIRLS grunt]
[GEORGE]
But please don't be discouraged.
If you are serious about
becoming a game designer,
improving is just
part of the job.
This is my way of pushing
you to new heights
you never even knew you
were capable of reaching.
[GEORGE] I recommend that you
come visit us here in America
if you've taken anything
I've told you to heart.
[EMILIA] "Observing how games
are actually made
should be an
invaluable experience
for a promising designer
such as yourself.
This invitation won't expire,
so take as much time as
you need to consider it.
I look forward to
seeing your growth
as well as your next game.
George Beresford."
So, then, your game
didn't make the cut.
Yeah but he still thinks
she has potential!
And he invited you to visit.
Are you going to
take him up on that?
That's a good question.
I generally prefer
Euro‐styled game designs,
if I'm being completely honest.
That can't be what's
really bothering you.
Are you moving to Germany
after you graduate, Emmy?
[MIKI, AYA gasp]
I haven't decided yet.
My Papa is planning on staying
in Japan for a little while.
But I might not
benefit from that.
Living in Germany might be more
suitable for my career path.
That's accurate.
It's not located in Germany,
but George's company
does make a decent amount
of Euro‐style games.
So... I am considering it.
Bad Dwarf might not
be such a bad idea.
[MIKI]
Uhh...
[MIKI] Midori and Emmy are
really admirable, aren't they?
[AYA]
Without a doubt!
Both of them are
so goal‐oriented.
They're living proof that
hard work pays off.
Hey! You know,
walking along the Kamogawa
River just the two of us
reminds me of the
day we first met!
Yeah! I'll never forget
a scare like that.
Or how you took your bike
for a test drive on the water.
That is true. I saw my life
flash before my eyes!
[AYA laughs]
[MIKI]
I'm relieved.
She's the same now
as she was then.
Hey, Aya?
[AYA]
Hmm?
Is there anything
that you want to do?
Any dreams you have?
[AYA]
Yeah! You bet!
Oh?
My ultimate dream would
be to live someplace
where there are tons
of animals roaming free!
I'll be a photographer,
like my dad,
and capture epic
shots in the wild!
Or I'll become a
veterinarian who knows
just what to do when an injured
critter comes along!
‐‐I've got lots of options.
‐‐[MIKI] Quick question!
Shouldn't you major in sciences
if your "ultimate dream"
is to become a veterinarian?
I guess so! Then again,
I wanna try and do so
many different things!
Living in South America
sounds cool, too!
Huh? No way!
[AYA] Hmm? What's the matter?
You okay?
Uh. Yeah. I was just thinking
how fitting that was.
[AYA]
Right?
[AYA laughs]
[MIKI] They all have ambitions
they're striving to achieve.
Midori and Emmy.
Even Aya.
So is it just me, then?
Am I the only one who wants
things to stay the same?
[MIKI grunts]
Hey, thanks for answering.
[FEMALE VOICE] You have
reached the voicemail of...
[AYA]
...Aya Takayashiki!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Please leave a message aft‐‐
It's good to see you.
Why hello there.
Oh! Hi, Miki. My apologies.
Emmy is out and about
shopping at the moment.
She should be back
in an hour or so.
You could wait for her here.
Oh! That's all right!
I just sort of came here on a
whim, nothing urgent to report.
I'll be back.
Huh.
[YUTO] Sorry I kinda forced
you to go shopping
for games with me. I owe ya.
Well, it's not for nothing.
I seem to recall you
promising me cake.
[YUTO laughs]
You got it! A deal's a deal.
[REN] I may be small,
but my appetite is anything but!
[YUTO] That's fine. If I can
afford it, you can eat it.
Hey. Welcome. Are you
flying solo for a change? Hm?
Where's Midori?
I'm sorry, kid. Midori
isn't scheduled today.
[gasps]
Why does no one seem
to be around today?
Are you feelin' all right?
You're lookin' a little pale.
[MIKI]
No. I...
I'm feeling fine.
Sorry to bother you.
Hey, hold on!
[MIKI]
Huh? That game...
[MAKI] Hey, it's me. I just
pulled up to the complex.
It's a great day to be outside!
I guess we lucked out, then.
I'll be right down!
[MAKI] Better hurry!
Just kidding. Take your time.
Oh, good morning, Hana.
Is there any breakfast?
Breakfast? Sis.
It's midday already.
[gasps, laughs]
Well, I'm on spring break,
so cut me some slack.
I might, if you acted
your age once in a while.
[AYA]
I missed a call from Miki!
[phone ringing]
Why is he calling?
Hello, Ono speaking.
[TAKERU] Hey, Midori.
How's it goin'?
[EMILIA]
What? Miki stopped by?
Ja.
I wonder if something happened.
[SHOUTA] Dude! Come on and
get the lead out, will ya?
We're gonna miss
the previews, man!
You're blaming me?
I hope you know you
were the late one.
We should just nix
our movie plans.
It's such a waste
of a nice day. Huh?
[SHOUTA]
Uh... What's the hold up?
Mm? Is that Takekasa?
[RYUJI] Yeah, it is.
But why does she look so sad?
It was an impulse buy.
But this little guy kind of
looks like the stuffed doll
my dad bought for me
a long time ago.
So fluffy!
From now on,
your name is Mojarin!
Here! Drink up!
[MIKI] Something as simple
as giving him a name
made me feel like
he was actually alive.
At least he was easy to talk to.
What a silly face.
This one is just a baby.
This one is an incurable
prankster brimming with energy.
This one is a spoiled brat.
And this one is a shy introvert.
[MIKI]
Just like me.
She won't answer her phone!
[MIDORI] Think ladies.
Where would she have gone?
I'm worried about her.
[phone rings]
Ah! I bet that's her now!
Or not.
Hi, everyone. Looks like
you're on your way out.
Yes! We're going on
a picnic together!
I've been looking forward
to stuffing my face all day!
Is that how you keep
your bulbous physique?
You know, you're
welcome to join us!
I don't want to impose,
but that would be nice.
Well, then tag along!
I need someone to help me
enjoy the extra food I made!
Wow! I mean, when you
put it like that.
Hey, you guys!
I want to go on the picnic, too!
What's stopping you?
There's no reason
we can't all go!
Yay! Thank you bunches!
What's this?
Yo! You there! You should
totally come with us!
Hey, uh... Don't bother
with that one.
What? But why?
[CARD CHARACTER D]
Because that one doesn't want to
join the fun. Let's get going.
The hill I picked is a bit far,
but the view is
well worth the trek.
Yeah! Let's go see
this crazy‐awesome view!
[CARD CHARACTER A]
I can't wait!
[CARD CHARACTER D]
Is everyone ready to head out?
Hold on. Please don't go.
I thought we could
stay here forever.
We'd never part ways or
allow things to change.
So please come back
and stay with me.
Forget about your plans.
Just stay.
[MIKI] I get it. I'm nothing
but a weakling.
I'm afraid to move forward.
But... What's wrong with
being content where I am?
For the first time, my life is
full of fun people and things,
and I don't want it to change!
[MOJARIN]
Come on now.
[MIKI]
Huh?
[MOJARIN]
That's a bad habit.
You letting your thoughts
turn into a sea of negativity
you can't help but drown in.
Mojarin.
[MOJARIN]
They're your friends, right?
You should want the best for
them. If you like 'em, that is.
[MIKI cries]
Yes. I love them.
[MOJARIN]
Then there's no problem!
Love and support them like
friends are supposed to.
Besides, I'm sure the
feeling is mutual. See?
[AYA]
Hey! Miki!
[MOJARIN]
See?
[MIDORI]
There you are!
You came!
[AYA]
We looked for you everywhere!
[MIKI]
How did you find me?
Tanoue spotted you
and gave me a call.
[MIKI]
Tanoue did?
[AYA] Speaking of calls,
I'm sorry I missed yours.
I tried calling you back,
but it wound up turning into
the most one‐sided game
of phone tag ever!
Huh? But I didn't
even hear it ring.
That's why... The battery died.
I also received a call.
My boss told me you weren't
exactly acting like yourself.
When I got home from shopping,
my Papa told me that you
dropped by while I was out.
You didn't answer your
phone the entire day.
So we were worried
something bad happened.
We formed our own search
party as a result.
[MIKI]
A search party for me?
[MIKI cries]
[GIRLS gasp]
Hey! What's with
the waterworks, Miki?
Sorry. Really.
I wish I wasn't so weak.
It's just that... this past
year has been amazing.
But I felt like everything
we built was crumbling down
because of the different paths
we're beginning to take.
You'll all working
towards your dreams.
Meanwhile...
I'm dreading the day the
future becomes the present.
Because... I just want
us to be together!
More than anything
else in the world!
Miki.
[MIKI]
If you three aren't around,
I don't know what I'll do!
[AYA] It's all right.
I feel the same way.
[MIKI gasps]
You do?
[AYA] Remember when I had
that fight with my dad
and ran out of the house?
Your friendly face
saved me that night.
You helped me, too!
That plan you made?
It bridged the gap
between Midori and me!
Emmy's right.
I kicked my pride to
the curb and opened up.
I don't think I could've done
that if it weren't for you.
Happy to help. Anytime.
You're indispensable to us.
I thought you knew.
And nothing is going to
change that fact, ever.
Even if we're not in the
same class, or continent,
our friendship'll withstand
time and distance!
You're not alone. Suffice it
to say you're stuck with us.
Yeah. Thank you
for cheering me up.
Uh. That's Toddles‐Bobbles.
Is it yours?
Yes. I bought it
from the Saikoro Club.
I know this one!
It's a Russian memory
game in which you give
funny‐looking creatures
nicknames.
I'm into it! Let's play!
Sound good?
Excellent!
Put your game‐faces on.
[MIKI]
Right!
[AYA]
On and ready!
This is a unique game,
so pay attention.
First, shuffle the cards
well and make a deck.
The moment your
turn rolls around,
flip a card from
the top like this.
You then say a random
name like "Bob!",
thus naming the creature
depicted on the card.
You repeat this process
until eventually you see
a creature someone
already named.
That's when you shout...
[MIDORI]
That's Bob!
Or whatever it was called.
The first person to say
its name out loud
gets all of the flipped
cards up until that point.
Got 'em!
Whoever collects the most cards
by the end of the
game is the winner.
Boy, oh boy! Sounds fun!
Why don't you go first, Aya?
[AYA]
Roger that!
Hmm... Mamekichi!
I'll go next if no one minds.
Madam Curl!
Okay, my turn now.
Grießing Nars!
Um. Greasy?
German names might make
the game a little trickier.
Uh? Mojarin.
It's time for round two!
Another new one!
And he's cute, too!
I think I'll call him... Mon!
What kind of a name
is that, Aya?
It was my pet flying squirrel's
name from when I was younger!
What? You had a flying
squirrel as a pet?
Yep!
Somehow, that's not surprising.
[MIKI]
Mojarin!
[AYA, MIDORI]
Huh?
Oh.
That... was fast!
Because Miki's a pro!
[MIKI gasping]
[MOJARIN] You see?
Everything is like I told you.
[MIKI] It is.
Thanks a lot, old friend.
Well don't stop now!
The fun's just starting!
Right! Let's keep going!
Ladies! Give it your all!
[MIKI]
...18, 19, 20, 21!
Miki won by a landslide!
Aw... She dominated
the whole thing!
[MIKI laughs]
[EMILIA] Even if we're
in separate classes,
we'll always find time
to play our games.
We can meet up after school,
and it'll be just like this.
That's true.
I know! We'll make our own club!
Something special, just for us!
[MIKI]
Uh!
Count me in!
But what should we call it?
Let's see. Maybe...
"The Analog Game Group."
No way. That's too bland.
[MIKI]
What about "Dice Club?"
[BOTH]
Huh?
We'll call it "The After
School Dice Club."
And we'll stay connected through
the club if nothing else.
Hey, I like that.
"After School Dice Club."
We've got a winner!
No need to deliberate further.
I agree!
I guess that means
from this day forward,
we're official members
of the ASDC!
[MIKI]
I'll be okay.
I've outgrown the
person I used to be.
And I'll continue to grow
because I'm not afraid of
making changes anymore.
This newfound courage is
thanks to my friends who,
without even realizing it,
helped me master
the art of "fun."