[GIRL A]
Hey, over here! Pass it to me!
[MIKI]
No! Give him back!
[GIRL B]
Go long!
He might rip. Please stop!
[GIRL A]
Whacha gonna do?
[GIRL C] Think we'd listen
to a scaredy‐cat like you?
Psh. How annoying.
[GIRL A] If you want it back,
come and get it.
[cries]
[GIRL C grunts]
[GIRLS laugh]
[gasps]
[MIKI]
Just a dream.
I always thought it was
better to be alone
than risk getting
hurt by someone.
That kind of mentality served
as my own unique armor.
It's what protected me
when I was young.
[MIKI] Goodness.
That was such a long time ago.
All the way back
in elementary school.
[GIRLS laughing]
[GIRL D]
You can't catch me!
[GIRL E]
Oh, you wanna bet?
[MIKI]
Uh?!
Oh! Something's wrong!
Uh... Someone.
[MIKI]
Um. Excuse me, miss.
Are you all right?
[HANA]
Uhh...
[gasps]
That... a yes?
[HANA]
Take a look.
[MIKI]
What? You mean through there?
That's right.
[HANA]
That's my kitty cat.
She refuses to come out, though.
[MIKI grunts]
We were on our way
to the vet's office,
and she's hiding because she
must have figured it out.
She's not the biggest fan.
Come out, Sakura, sweetie!
We need to get going!
[MIKI]
That's it!
Wait here. I think I have
an idea that might help.
I know that feeling,
when you're scared.
But there's no need to be.
You can come out.
Not so fast there!
[meows]
[HANA]
You really saved the day!
You're my hero!
Please, it's nothing.
So tell me.
Where did you learn your cat
whispering techniques?
Huh? What do you mean by that?
It's something special.
Sakura's kinda fussy.
She's the princess
and never lets anyone
besides me touch her. My little
sister would be jealous.
Uh? She's that picky?
Poor baby. She was
startled by some children
playing nearby and ran
straight for a hiding spot.
Uh.
[MIKI]
Those children?
Sakura.
Were you drawn to me
because I'm shy like you?
[gasps]
Oh! Nothing! But...
But what?
I, um. I sympathize
with your cat.
I know firsthand how scary it is
to approach someone
you don't know.
[HANA laughs]
Like me?
I'm someone you don't know.
Oh. I'm not afraid!
Just being around you is
putting me at ease somehow.
Good! I was hoping so.
I can see what you mean
about you and Sakura, though.
[MIKI]
So it's not just me?
We may both be shy
compared to most.
But we're content,
just sitting here
together like this.
Oh! Time sure flies.
We still have our appointment.
Uh! That's right!
Were you on your
way somewhere, too?
I was.
I had planned to meetup
with some friends.
Oh. Sorry. I guess
I held you up.
No. I really enjoyed
talking with you.
Goodbye. Thanks so
much for the tea!
And thank you so
much for the save!
[AYA]
Oh, here she comes!
Yay! You made it!
Did something happen to you?
[MIKI panting]
Sorry I kept you waiting.
You seem distraught.
[MIKI]
Um, well. I'm fine, but...
Come on.
She can tell us about it later.
For now, though,
let's head to my place!
Yes, let's.
[MIKI] It's been ages since
the last time I visited
a friend's house.
I'm kind of nervous.
[MIDORI]
I see. So that's what happened.
[MIKI] Yeah. Now you know
why I was late.
I'm proud of you! That's great!
You helped someone out!
She's right. At least you
didn't hit the snooze button
on your alarm clock
over and over.
[AYA whistles]
It's odd.
I've never heard of a cat being
so unresponsive to its owner.
They're called
scaredy‐cats for a reason.
Scaredy‐cats?
Something wrong, Miki?
Just caught up
in my thoughts.
Y'know, my kitty cat freaks
if I get anywhere near her.
[MIDORI]
You have a cat?
[AYA]
Mm‐hm. And a sister.
I just don't know where she is.
She better hurry! I wanna
play a four‐player game!
[door clicks]
Wow! What perfect timing!
[gasps]
That's...
Sakura! My fluffy
little baby! Sakura!
[AYA]
Aw... Always the ice queen.
That would mean...
[HANA]
I made it home, Aya!
Hey, sis! These are
the friends I mentioned.
[HANA]
I think I recognize one!
[BOTH gasp]
[AYA]
What are the odds?
Never would've guessed my sis
was the one you helped!
It's fate!
It's something, that's for sure.
I really can't thank you enough.
By the way, I'm Hana Takayashki,
Aya's big sister.
Surprise!
[gasps] I'm Miki Takekasa.
I guess I should've said that
the first time I met you, huh?
[HANA] I'm so glad our paths
crossed again, Miki!
Yes! I feel the same!
Hey, Aya. Are you sure
she's related to you?
She's way too pretty.
What are you trying to say?
[HANA]
And your name is?
[MIDORI] My apologies.
I'm Aya's classmate, Midori Ono.
I appreciate you inviting
us to your home.
You're very generous.
My! How polite you are!
It's nice to meet you, Midori.
Thanks. Nice to
meet you as well.
[HANA] That just leaves
one more introduction.
This is my best friend‐‐
The name's Maki! What's up?
I thought the more people we had
to play these games‐‐the better!
That makes sense to me.
It would seem we have a case
of polar opposites attracting.
[MIKI]
Mm.
I might be in trouble.
She's the type that
really puts me on edge.
I'm Aya! AKA, 'lil sis.
[MAKI] Hm... So you're
Hana's little sister, huh?
Well you sure do act like her!
Not a single ounce
of fear in your eyes.
Hana's always been there
for me through thick and thin.
I'd love to return the favor,
so I'll be there for you, too!
Cool!
Um. How exactly did the
two of you first meet?
It all started at the
restaurant I work at.
I was being harassed
by a drunk customer,
but Maki jumped in
and stood up for me.
That was the highlight
of the night, for sure.
Hana is like a magnet.
Leave her be and she attracts
all sorts of creeps and weirdos.
But my magnetism flips
when Maki's around.
That's right.
One look at me an‐‐ Not cool!
Jeez...
[AYA, MIDORI laugh]
[MIKI] I guess looks
can be deceiving.
[AYA] Oh! Does Sakura
wanna come and play?
[MAKI]
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty!
Come 'ere, kitty!
Okay. Guess that's a hard pass.
[AYA]
Don't take it personally, Maki.
She won't even let me touch
her and I live with her!
[MIDORI] It must have been love
at first sight with Miki, then.
[AYA gasps]
You're as heartless as the cat!
Honestly, she was
purring on her lap!
I almost didn't believe it.
That's not fair! Miki, you gotta
teach me your wooing ways!
Uh. I don't have those.
It's a true talent
that can't be taught.
[MAKI] Mm. Don't know why, but
you look oddly familiar somehow.
[gasps]
[MAKI]
You said your name was Miki?
Which middle school
did you go to?
I, uh, spent middle
school at Kamogawa‐West.
[MAKI]
Get out!
Same as me!
I'm Kamo‐West, too!
Ha! Small world, amirite?
I must've seen you
somewhere around school!
But all three of
them are still in
their first year of high school.
There's no way you could've been
enrolled at the same time.
What?
Hmm. Then where do I know her?
[MIKI] I have this sinking
feeling she's right‐‐
we have met before.
A long time ago.
Somewhere.
Ah, well. Are we gonna
reminisce or we gonna play?
Maki is what you'd
call an ace gamer.
Yup! Mainly when it comes
to the fighting kind!
Fighting?
Video games, Hana!
Better put your fists away.
You're not gonna need
'em for board games.
Board games, huh?
That's your cue, Midori.
[MIDORI]
Understood.
But calling it a board game
is a little misleading
since we won't be utilizing
an actual board.
[MAKI]
We're playing Incan Gold?
The heck is this?
[AYA]
Something fun from overseas!
Lately, Aya's been raving about
how much she enjoys these
European board games. We might
as well try them for ourselves.
Is that a fact?
I've never seen
anything like it.
They aren't that rare, y'know!
They make boatloads
of them in Germany!
Okay, then, Aya. Tell me,
how's the game work?
Well. I mean, obviously...
Midori, why don't you
do the honors today?
Sure thing.
The point of Incan Gold is to
explore the ancient ruins
and escape with as many
jewels as possible.
It should be self‐explanatory,
but the player with
the most jewels wins.
The rules are simple.
First, flip the top card
of the deck face‐up.
If you're lucky enough to get
one of these treasure cards,
it means you've found the number
of jewels listed in the corner.
That's a good thing.
In this case,
the number is 11.
The jewels found are
then split up evenly
amongst all of the players.
It's simple math.
Since there are five of us,
we each get two.
Then, the remaining jewel
gets left on this card.
I gotcha.
We're collecting
these little guys.
Right. The expedition continues.
We keep flipping our cards
and stuffing our pockets
with these precious gems.
Uh.
A snake?
[MIDORI]
This is a hazard card.
The standard deck in Incan Gold
is only made up of 30 cards.
Fifteen of them are hazards.
But... that's half!
So what do hazard cards mean?
The first card is
a "premonition."
Nothing happens.
However, if the same type
of hazard shows up twice,
the expedition is
marked as a failure.
When that happens, the explorers
are forced to escape the ruins.
In addition, they lose every
last piece of the treasure
that they've gathered
on their journey.
No exceptions.
What?!
Oh...
[grunts]
There are five types of hazards.
Snakes, spiders, mummies,
flame traps, and falling rocks.
There are three copies of
each for a grand total of 15.
Of course, there's only one way
to retain all of your jewels.
And that's by retreating.
You make your choice
after each card.
Continue or go home?
We decide out loud?
Not quite. You use this
little explorer token.
When you're ready, hold
the token in your hand
to symbolize your desire to
retreat with your loot in tow.
Keep your hand empty
to keep going.
You reveal your
choices together.
Easy enough.
Let's recap real quick.
You can either take the risk for
more treasure or go home because
you're too scared to press on.
What this boils down to...
...is a game of Chicken.
How very astute.
This is similar to Chicken.
The further you go,
the more dangerous it gets.
But the more explorers
who turn back before you,
the larger your share of
the treasure becomes.
You just have to be careful
when deciding to withdraw.
Hm?
[MIDORI] Unearthing the jewels
doesn't make them yours.
In other words, they don't count
towards your final score.
What does that mean?
Only by retreating to safety
are you allowed to claim
whatever jewels you find.
You then place them
in your tent to properly
display your earnings.
Oh! So there's a chance
you could lose
all your jewels and points
if you get too greedy.
You got it. Weigh the outcomes,
make the best decision,
and stay one step ahead
of your fellow explorers.
I like the sound of that.
[HANA]
Uhh...
Also, do you remember
those jewels
that get left on the cards?
You can take those
if you retreat.
There are a lot of perks
to running away!
[MIDORI] One game
consists of five rounds.
The player to successfully
gather the most points
within those rounds
is the winner!
Incan Gold has three
types of jewels.
The turquoise one
is the most common,
but is only worth one point.
Obsidian is worth five points,
and then the gold
one is worth ten.
And those are the rules.
Understood?
Yeah.
Somewhat.
It's not exactly rocket science.
No worries, sis. Just pair up
with Maki if you're confused.
Wait. We can team up?
I'm game if you are.
Sure, that's cool.
All right, then.
Let's play some Chicken.
[laughs] Been a while since I've
been this pumped for a match.
[MAKI laughs]
Uh. Lighten up, please.
[AYA]
Whoa.
One more fire or mummy
and we're cooked, or wrapped.
'Kay, time's up!
Make a choice!
[MIDORI]
Miki is the only one going back.
For real? What a party pooper.
Yes. I'm sorry.
If we draw the wrong card,
Miki will be the smart one!
C'mon, Hana!
Go big or go home!
So that just leaves
three of us.
Let's see if our
gamble paid off.
[MAKI] Boom, baby!
Five pieces of obsidian!
Just as I thought.
You get goods if you got guts.
Hm?
Yo, Miki. You used to
be bullied a lot, huh?
[gasps]
I could tell almost instantly.
Bullies have this
basic instinct.
It lets them seek out weaker
people and prey on them
like it's open season.
With that meek attitude,
you might as well wear a
sign that says, "Bully me."
[MIKI gasping]
[GIRL C] Think we'd listen
to a scaredy‐cat like you?
Psh. How annoying.
[MIKI] Wait a minute,
one of those girls...
She was older than the others,
but I don't remember her name.
Could it be...?
[AYA]
Maki!
Huh?
Listen here! I won't allow
my friend to be bullied.
[MIDORI]
Same here!
I'll stand by Miki's
side no matter what.
[MIKI]
Thank you, you guys.
Huh. Cute speech.
But can you match it
with your courage?
[ALL]
Let's go!
[AYA]
What the...?!
Well. Time to bounce!
Oh, you're heading back
to your campsite.
Guess you're not brave enough
to hang with Midori and me.
Isn't that right?
Absolutely. Now that it's
just the two of us,
we'll be swimming in riches
before we know it!
Just watch!
[MIDORI]
[AYA]
No! We're completely mummified!
[laughs] Man, I got
you guys good!
That means our team
sweeps this round!
Way to go, Maki!
Oh, it's in the bag! I came
to win, just like I always do!
[AYA grumbles]
Come on, you two!
You've gotta hold it together!
I swear, my jewels
will be avenged!
[MAKI] Sweet! The finish
line is in our sights.
Time to claim my rightful
spot as number one!
[gasps]
I respectfully withdraw.
[AYA]
What?!
And now there's spiders?
Four of the five types.
That's way too hazardous!
Aw, cut the whining!
Make your choice!
If you're out, who'll
avenge your jewels?
[whines] My poor jewels!
[MAKI]
And then, there were two.
Yeah, it's you and me.
Sure you don't wanna just call
it quits? I'd still let you.
Um. I'm sure.
[MAKI] Gotta say, never thought
I'd be going head‐to‐head
with you in the final matchup.
[MIKI]
Just her and me.
One on one.
[MIDORI]
Miki.
Let's continue! Here goes!
Falling rocks!
Now all five types of hazard
cards have been put into play.
One more spells instant
death to all explorers.
[MAKI]
Yo, Miki.
You wind up failing here?
You end up dead last.
Bow out now.
I'm sure you realize retreating
means you won't beat me,
but you'd still snag second
place. That's not bad.
[MIKI]
I do realize.
I mean, it's no secret
that I'm a coward.
Even if I left now, nobody
would think any less of me.
Huh? So warm.
Sakura, are you sensing all
of my troubled thoughts?
[MIDORI]
Miki.
[AYA laughs]
[MAKI]
Come on.
[BOTH gasp]
Go or stay?
[MIKI gasping]
[MAKI]
Moment of truth!
No way!
She stayed!
Well, you've sure
got some spunk.
But what a time to show it!
Say good night!
[MIKI] It's risky. But I
finally have the courage
to go further,
thanks to my friends!
[MIDORI] If she draws a hazard
card, it's all over for her.
So nerve‐racking.
I don't think I can watch!
[AYA]
You've got this!
Omigosh! Jewels!
[MIKI gasps]
‐‐That was unbelievable!
‐‐[MIDORI] How cool!
Wow. I did it!
All 15 of those jewels are
for you and you alone, Miki!
[gasps]
[MIKI]
Alone? No. Not alone.
Not at all.
I was able to push forward
because I had all of you
right here beside me.
[MAKI]
Dang! That upset was huge!
Who'd'a thunk it?
Kyoko Maki lost
a test of courage.
Hey, good game.
Sorry if all that stuff I
said got under your skin.
Please, forgive me.
It's okay!
There's no need for that!
[MIDORI]
Hm? Kyoko? Hold on.
I thought that Maki
was your first name.
Nah, it's my last name.
But I prefer Maki.
Kyoko just never had
the same ring to it.
Why? Kyoko sounds nice!
Kyoko Maki...
Kyoko... Maki.
Uh!
Kyoko!
[MIKI cries]
Please give him back.
He's mine!
[GIRL C]
Not anymore!
That's right!
Yeah! It's ours now!
[GIRL C]
What the‐‐?
Watch it, jerk! Uh.
[ALL whimpering]
[MAKI] Don't middle schoolers
have anything better to do
than pick on helpless little
girls in their spare time?
Your moms must be proud.
No. Not her!
It's Mad Dog Kyoko!
You're ticking me off!
So beat it!
[GIRLS scream]
[MIKI cries]
[MIKI]
Mad Dog Kyoko.
[gasps]
Wait. Miki.
Did you just call me what
I think you called me?
[gasps]
So, then, we have
met before, huh?
Yes!
Where was it, though?
[MIKI] Painful memories
are a lot like caves.
They're dark and scary, and I
hate being trapped inside them.
But, if I muster the courage
to push through,
I just might come across
something else.
Something as precious as jewels.
[MIDORI]
It's a faceoff against
the student council
vice president!
If she loses, she has
to give up on me.
I, too, have a dream I
want to see realized.