[MIKI] Our first term of high
school has come to an end.
And summer break
is in full swing.
[AYA]
I feel like I'm melting.
Ugh, I heard summers
in Kyoto were hot,
but this has to be
some kind of record!
[MIDORI] Hate to be
the bearer of bad news
but it gets way hotter
than this, Aya.
[AYA]
No! Say it ain't so!
I know! If we want
to beat the heat
we've gotta leave the street.
We should go to
the beach instead!
Good plan, but the closest
ocean is miles away.
What? For real?
Yeah. A one‐day trip
might be tough.
Then let's make it more than
one day and stay overnight!
Wishful thinking.
I hope you realize
vacations like that
aren't exactly bargains.
Who's paying?
[AYA]
Um. That's a good question.
But I can't just not go to
the beach during summer break!
Talk about depressing!
[MIKI]
I have an idea.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MIKI]
Okay, I'm heading out!
Make good choices!
All right!
[MIKI]
And just like that,
Aya, Midori, and I were off on
our first big vacation together.
Our destination was
the city of Kanazawa.
Not only does my aunt
Miyabi live out there,
she runs her own inn!
I never thought I'd see the day
when Miki went on
a trip like this.
Will she be all right?
[TOMOE]
Please, Miyabi.
Take good care of Miki
and her friends.
Now this kind of weather I like!
It's hard to believe the three
of us are actually here.
I've never been
to Kanazawa before!
Same goes for me.
We really lucked out!
None of this would've been
possible without Miki's aunt!
[MIDORI]
Mm‐hm!
Speaking of my aunt,
the inn she owns is
close to the beach,
and she said we'll have
a room all to ourselves.
[AYA]
You're the absolute best!
Have I told you lately
how much I love you?
Is our destination
within walking distance?
It's about a 30‐minute
train ride from here.
Then let's squeeze
some sightseeing in
before we take the train, 'kay?
But... What about the beach?
It's great! But the city
has other great things!
We'll go to the beach tomorrow!
[AYA] Mm‐hm! So much to see,
yet so little time!
I do love a good adventure!
Fair enough. If that's
what you two really want.
Yay! Our Kanazawa
exploration starts now! Heh!
[MIKI, MIDORI]
Yeah!
[AYA] Wow, what a jam‐packed
day! We saw so much!
Shall we head to the inn now?
Good idea.
It's just about the
time I told my aunt
we would be arriving.
[laughs] Wonder what's on
the dinner menu tonight!
She says as she stuffs
her face full of ice cream.
It's fine. 'Cause this is an
appetizer, not the main course!
[MIYABI]
Why hello, girls! Welcome!
I trust your journey here
wasn't too difficult.
[MIKI]
Not at all. It was nice!
What a relief!
I'll have to let your mother
know you made it safe and sound.
She was worried about you.
Oh. She was?
[MIYABI] And these two
must be your new friends!
I'm Midori Ono.
Thank you for your
hospitality and generosity!
I'm Aya Takayashiki,
how d'you do?
Such polite young ladies.
Don't be shy, come on in,
and I hope you came hungry,
because dinner is ready!
[gasps] Everything looks
positively delicious!
[MIYABI]
Eat to your heart's content!
This doesn't feel right. You
should feed this kind of meal
to guests who pay to be here.
[MIYABI]
What kind of hostess would I be
if I simply allowed
you girls to starve?
You're Miki's friends,
after all!
It's nothing to fret over.
We really appreciate it!
[MIYABI]
Anytime, sweetheart.
Well, you can
color me convinced!
[GIRLS]
Thank you so much!
Yummy!
[MIDORI] This just might be
the best sashimi I've ever had!
It's so fresh I could
practically taste the sea!
Uh? You seem happy.
What's making you
smile like that?
It's just... you used
to be the kind of girl
who would hardly talk to people.
Yet you've made such
delightful friends.
I'm happy for you!
My niece can be stubborn.
So please continue to
show her your kindness.
Hey! Aunt Miyabi!
Oh, no worries in
that department.
We're besties!
Yeah.
There's a warm bath waiting for
you girls when you're ready.
But please take your time.
[GIRLS]
Okay!
Thank you very much.
[AYA sighs]
That was delicious!
I'm liking this city
more and more!
It has great food and
stylish architecture.
It's really the bee's knees!
"The bee's knees"?
You sound like a grandma!
[MIDORI] Does a grandma have
the strength to do this?
Well? Does she?
[groaning]
[clattering]
[ALL gasp]
[AYA]
Whoopsie!
What's this? The back side
of these pieces are blank.
I wonder why.
[gasps]
Huh?
[AYA]
See? Check it out!
[MIKI]
You're right. How peculiar.
Right?
Shogi pieces are supposed to
have markings on the back, too!
Take the dragon behind
the rook, for instance,
or the gold behind the silver.
[MIDORI] That's because
these aren't for Shogi.
[AYA, MIKI]
Uh?
I think they're GOITA pieces.
[MIKI]
GOITA?
Wanna elaborate on that?
It's an old game from a
port town named Ushitsu.
You know, the one on
the Noto peninsula.
My, oh, my! So you've
heard of GOITA, eh?
I'm impressed that you know that
game, despite not being a local.
Midori knows more about board
games than anyone I've ever met.
She works in a store
that markets them.
[MIYABI]
Oh! Is that so?
That's correct.
GOITA's unique rules caught the
attention of game specialists.
They made it into a card game.
We now sell it at the
store Miki mentioned.
Though, I'm ashamed to admit
I haven't played it
for myself yet.
But still, a proper set made
of bamboo intrigues me.
Would you mind if I
studied it for a while?
No. Not at all.
If you're studying a game,
we should probably play!
I would, but this game requires
us to have four players.
Oh. It does?
One. Two. Three. Four.
Who, me?
Wait! Don't drag Miki's
aunt into this!
My bad.
[laughs] I don't mind.
I have time to play with you.
‐‐[AYA] Huh?!
‐‐Huh? Are you certain?
Aw, yeah!
I, um...
I match your bishop
and play a gold.
I can't play a thing.
There! I win!
Almost unopposed!
[MIYABI laughs]
Ah! Another loss!
This game is hard.
[MIDORI] I thought it
was really engaging!
I just wish I would've
buckled down
and played it sooner than this.
I agree. Who knew such
an entertaining secret
was hidden away in
a place like this?
[MIYABI] You say that like
you've never played before.
Uh?
Miki, you know you played GOITA
when you were younger
and came to visit.
I did?
[MIKI] Actually, I get the
feeling that she's right.
But I can't quite
place the memory.
[laughs] Don't worry about it.
Uh.
[AYA]
Mm! Just what I needed!
That GOITA game was pretty fun!
I know.
So why is such a fun game
exclusive to the Noto region?
Similar games were made.
They just have different names.
[AYA]
Really?
Could you explain?
[MIDORI] There's Maru‐Shogi
and Imo‐Shogi for example,
which are essentially
the same as GOITA,
but they of course make
use Shogi pieces.
Iro‐Kammuri is
also very similar,
except it utilizes
Hyakunin Isshu cards
and plays to a
different hand size.
Also, another parallel,
was that these games were often
used as a means to gamble.
And in the Edo era,
gambling was banned by law.
As a result the games became
less and less popular.
Huh! Pullin' out the
smarts card! As always.
That explains why GOITA
didn't spread
much farther than one small
part of the Noto peninsula.
[AYA] I definitely wanna
give it another go!
[MIKI]
Me, too!
[MIDORI]
Agreed!
[MIDORI] Okay, I'm turning off
the light.
[sighs] We're finally
going to the beach!
You're really excited
about this beach trip.
Yes. I'm filled to the
brim with excitement...
So much so... I might...
not sleep...
Hey, Aya.
No way! She fell asleep!
[MIDORI] She looks so blissfully
unaware of the world.
But I know one way
to change that!
[sighs]
Hey. Come on now, Midori!
Let's let her sleep. She's
earned it, don't you think?
True. We should get
to bed as well.
Good call.
[MIDORI]
Miki. Thank you.
Huh?
Really.
I could only ever dream of going
on a fancy trip like this one.
But here I am, thanks to you.
That's backwards. I should
be the one thanking you.
If I were never
introduced to you,
then I wouldn't have been
introduced to games either.
I would've lived my life without
ever knowing how much fun
I was missing.
I mean it. Thank you.
[MIDORI gasps]
Miki.
Let's play a lot.
All of the games. Together.
Deal?
Sweet dreams.
[MIDORI] Oh, great. How am I
supposed to sleep after that?
[AYA]
Move it or lose it, ladies!
You slowpokes better
hustle! It's beach time!
I'm gonna need you
to tone it down.
Did you even put on
some sunscreen?
I can do that stuff later!
Later as in when you're burned?
Relax. You're acting like the
ocean might disappear on us.
I'm sorry, girls,
but I'm too hyped to stop!
So let's get going!
[thunder cracks]
[AYA]
Huh?!
[AYA] How is this
scientifically possible?
The sun was just out!
It's not fair!
It's not like we can change the
weather. Just accept it already.
[AYA]
No!
[TAKASHI]
[cries] But the beach!
What'd you want me to do?
Magically clear up the rain?
[TAKASHI] Yes! Whatever it
takes! You said we were going!
You said we were going!
Oh geez, Aya.
What do you think we should do?
What can we do other
than stay in?
Oh, yeah!
We can play this!
Genius!
Great idea!
[TAKASHI]
What's going on?
[MIDORI]
Uh, hello.
Oh hey, what's up?
[MIKI] This is a tabletop
game called GOITA.
You're welcome to
play if you want to!
Really?
Come on, Takashi.
Please don't be a bother to
these nice young ladies.
Let's go back to the room.
Daddy! I wanna play the game!
It's okay buddy.
Pardon me, but the game
we we're wanting to play
actually requires four players.
[AYA]
That's right!
Your son won't be a
bother‐‐he'll be our fourth!
Y'see? There's no game
if there's no me!
A‐Are you sure about that?
You bet! We were
rained‐out, too.
Might as well make the most
of it with a fun game!
Are you ready to play?
[TAKASHI]
Mm‐hm!
Well, if you're sure it's okay.
First, you have to know
the rules before we begin.
For GOITA, you must
have two teams
made up of two players each.
There are 32 pieces total.
Two Kings, Rooks,
and Bishop pieces.
Four Golds, Silvers, Lances,
and Knight pieces.
And ten pawns gives us 32.
[TAKASHI]
Cool!
[MIDORI] All of the pieces
are turned facedown,
and each of the four players
is dealt eight of them.
Let's break it down.
The dealer starts it of
by playing one of their
pieces facedown.
This is followed by a second
piece they play face‐up.
The second piece
is the "Attack."
If the next player has the same
piece as the dealer's attack,
they can put it into play.
This is what's
known as a "Match."
If you match successfully,
you then become the dealer
and initiate another attack.
This process is repeated
until one of the four players
has put all eight pieces
of their hand into play.
The team with that
player wins the round.
The winning team scores the
value of the last card played.
You play several rounds and
keep cumulative scores,
and the first team to rack up
150 points wins it all!
In addition, if the
last move you make
has two of the same tiles,
you receive double the points.
Double points? Right on!
There are a few other
rules we should go over.
The King pieces are special.
They can match with
the Rook, Bishop,
Gold, Silver,
and Knight pieces.
Basically, the Lances and Pawns
are the only exception
when it comes to
matching with Kings.
However, you can't attack
with King pieces
until someone first plays
a King as a match.
I gotcha!
That covers just
about everything.
You have any questions?
Sure don't! Let's play!
Right! Let's pair off!
Since it's his first time,
Takashi should team
up with Midori.
You'll like her! She's a real
whiz when it comes to games!
Let's do this. Are you ready?
[TAKASHI]
Mm‐hm!
[MIDORI] Why don't you
go first, teammate?
[TAKASHI]
Okie‐doke!
I will... play my first
piece facedown. And...
I'll attack with
a nice Gold piece!
[AYA] I match your Gold
and attack with a Silver.
[MIDORI] I match your Silver
and play a Knight.
Matching your Knight.
Attacking with Rook.
[MIDORI]
I'll have two Pawns left over,
but this is the game‐changer!
I match your Gold,
and Attack with a Bishop!
I pass.
[TAKASHI]
Yeah!
[MIDORI]
Eh?
[TAKASHI] Match the Bishop
and attack with Silver!
Uh...
Awesome! Match your
Silver, and that's the round!
Ten points!
Man. What a total bummer.
I would've passed if you'd
let the Bishop through.
Huh? You would've?
Takashi, I wasn't expecting you
to counter the play I made.
What? Why not?
Me winning is the same
as you winning.
So there's no need to
interfere with what I do.
A basic GOITA strategy is to let
your partner's attacks
go unmatched.
[TAKASHI]
Oh, I see!
I don't wanna match
my teammate's attack.
Okay! I got it now!
[AYA]
King matches, Rook attacks!
[MIDORI] She matched my Silver
with a piece as rare as a King.
Which means she probably doesn't
have any Silvers in her hand.
[MIDORI] King is matched,
Silver is played.
I have to pass.
[MIDORI]
Miki doesn't have one either.
So Takashi must have
the only Silvers left!
[TAKASHI]
Hm... I'm gonna pass!
[MIDORI]
What?
[MIKI] I play another facedown
piece, finishing with a Rook!
That's 40 points!
Which makes 150!
Miki and I win the entire
kit and caboodle!
Aw! Losing's no fun.
Takashi. That one round
you had two Silvers
in your hand.
You should've matched
them with mine.
That would've clinched
a victory for our team!
What? No way!
Earlier you said
the exact opposite!
[MIKI gasps]
[MIDORI] Earlier I told
you the basic strategy,
but this was different.
You learn that difference by
paying attention to the pieces.
[TAKASHI]
Huh?
[MIKI]
I remember now.
[BOY] Why didn't you think to
match my Gold piece, Miki?
Your two Golds were
all our team needed
to win this round,
but you blew it!
[MIKI]
Um. I thought that matching
my teammate's attack was bad.
Not in this situation!
Why don't you understand?
I'm sorry. This game
is really hard.
So, I don't think
I can play anymore!
[MIYABI]
Miki! Please come back!
[MIKI]
Takashi is like me.
He's going through
the same thing I did.
Sometimes you match,
but then there are
times that you don't.
What's the difference?
[MIKI]
Hey, Takashi.
Would you like to play
on a team with me?
It might be fun to
switch up partners.
[AYA]
Uh?
[AYA] Matching your Lance and
attacking with a Silver!
[MIKI] Your Silver is matched
and my Knight is attacking.
[MIDORI]
Pass.
[TAKASHI]
I, uh, pass, too!
Hm! Aw, fine then!
I play my King and my Rook.
[MIKI] It's pretty obvious Aya
doesn't have a Knight.
But what about Midori?
[MIKI]
It's a risk I have to take!
[MIKI] I match with my King
and attack with a Knight!
I'm passing.
[MIKI] As I thought. Midori
doesn't have a Knight either.
Which would mean the
last two Knight pieces
are in Takashi's hand.
[TAKASHI] Both of the Kings
are already in play.
And Miki attacked with two
Knight pieces back‐to‐back.
There's only four Knights total,
and I have the other two!
[TAKASHI]
Did she set me up?
[gasps]
[TAKASHI] I match my teammate's
Knight, and attack with my own!
[TAKASHI] This was the best
move. Right, partner?
[MIKI]
He got it!
He figured out what I was trying
to tell him all on his own!
[MIDORI]
Well played, Takashi.
I pass!
Same!
Me, too.
Booyah!
Now... Let's see...
I'll play this piece facedown
and end it with a Lance!
And victory is ours!
Aw. My winning streak is over.
But you made an
awesome final move!
She's right. It really was.
[TAKASHI] And I couldn't
have done it without you!
[ALL laughing]
Thanks. That was a lot of fun!
Now that I got the hang of it,
I wanna take you guys
on in a rematch!
Thank you so much. My wife
and I are truly grateful.
You turned what could've
been a disappointing day
into a precious memory.
No trouble at all.
[MIKI, AYA]
Right!
What else have you
got planned today?
[GIRLS]
Uh.
[MIDORI] Well, we're kind
of playing it by ear.
I know!
[OTHERS]
Huh?
Come hang out with
us at the beach!
[TAKASHI'S FATHER] Uh, the rain
ruled that out for us, kiddo.
But it stopped!
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[MIKI, AYA, MIDORI]
Wow!
[AYA]
It's beach time!
[MIYABI] I guess it was
a passing shower.
Skies should be clear for
the rest of the afternoon!
Yes! Beach!
Hey! Let's go for a swim!
[TAKASHI, AYA laughing]
Stop and think for
a second, Aya!
You still don't have sunscreen!
I said stuff like that
can wait till later!
No, it can't!
[MIKI giggles]
[MIYABI]
Miki really has come a long way.
And I suspect those
two played a part.
[MIKI]
Hey, Aunt Miyabi!
It's perfect out here now!
[MIYABI]
Tomoe, it seems your daughter
is doing just fine these days.
[TOMOE]
A message? What's this!
[MIDORI] What? You wanna
play the game I made?
No way! It's not even done yet!
Wait. What do you mean I'll
never finish at this rate?