[MIDORI] What? Did you
say George Beresford?
[TAKERU] Yeah. Do you
remember him from before?
Like I'd ever
forget that guy.
He was so annoying.
Well, that annoying guy's
big‐name company,
Bad Dwarf, has a competition for
unpublished games coming up
in the very near future.
The best games in the bunch
have a serious shot
at getting published
and made official.
Okay. But why tell me this?
Because I was asked to.
Just so happens George
recently got in touch with me.
[GEORGE]
Ah, that's right.
Could you relay something
to that would‐be designer?
"Such a shame. I still haven't
been able to play your game.
Yet."
[MIDORI]
Emphasis on the yet.
So he's calling me out now?
Is this a challenge?
Uh, I mean, it's up
to you if you do this or not.
It's totally your call.
School starts back up
tomorrow, though.
That won't leave much time
for designing your game.
[AYA] Say what? You're
gonna be in a competition?
Yes.
I might not
know what that means.
[MIKI grunts]
It's a contest. They're
accepting unpublished games.
They'll play‐test and
analyze all of them,
then choose which
game is the best.
And I have every
intention of competing.
Oh! I gotcha.
How impressive, Midori!
But which competition is this?
The one put on by
Bad Dwarf in the US.
Oh‐ho! You don't say!
Yeah, but contests like this...
Professional authors are
bound to be interested, too.
[MIDORI] That's why
I don't think I stand
any chance of winning.
I might even be
completely overlooked.
That said, I refuse to run away.
Whatever happens,
I'll see this through.
Your mind's made up?
More or less.
But I still need to give my
revamped version a trial run.
So will you help me test it out?
I kinda thought
that was a given!
Truly. I'm very much
looking forward to this!
[MIDORI]
One Room, version two.
I improved the
overall mechanics.
Wow.
It looks even more
like a game than before!
How cute.
They're furniture cards!
[MIDORI]
Right.
The main objective is to collect
furniture for your own room.
The first thing you do
is draw ten cards from
the top of the deck.
And there you have it.
That's how One Room is played.
Did you follow all that, Emmy?
Ja! I pretty much have it.
You work to make money
and buy furniture and trinkets
to fill your room with.
Furniture items have points,
and bonuses are given
by getting multiple pieces
of the same color, or by
completing an entire set.
[MIDORI]
Sounds like you've got it.
There is one huge difference
from the first version, though.
You can score points
in a lot more ways now.
Buying pricey stuff
is still a good idea.
So not everything has changed.
One thing I noticed
is there's way more
furniture types than before!
And we have pets now!
I like the new
work schedule.
Having it as a chart
is a nice touch.
[MIDORI] Yeah. I
figured fixing the values
might make the
choices more difficult.
Nice work.
With just one small change,
players are forced to act more
strategically when deciding
to go to work or go shopping.
Way to put those brains
of yours to use!
Thanks. You'll find
I made a lot of adjustments.
The basic flow is the same.
But I can already tell it's
come a long way from
the game it was before.
Oh, this is going
to be so much fun!
The sooner we start, the better!
Okay. Guess that means
it's time to give it a try.
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
We've all placed our workers
where we want 'em to be.
[AYA] Which means
I get to go first!
It was pay‐day for me,
so I'll buy this table!
I got paid, too,
so I'll be taking this sofa.
Then I'll accept my
seven gold and end my turn.
Just like that,
round one is complete.
[MIDORI] Finally, we factor in
the bonus points for each score.
Aya, 92 points.
Emmy, 84 points.
Miki, also 84 points.
And Boss, 79 points.
That's the game.
So what are your
honest opinions?
Well?
That was amazing!
It actually feels like
a real game now!
Yes! I genuinely had
much more fun playing it
‐‐this time around.
‐‐And you liked it, right?
Ja! It's neat
and clean design
made it evident that this
was a trademark Midori game.
It's super‐duper‐mega awesome!
You're gonna knock their
socks off in the competition!
[MIKI]
Um, Midori?
Boss, what are your
final thoughts on it?
Truthfully, I'm surprised.
First time
I tried your game,
it was full of holes
and problems.
It substantially improved.
[MIKI, AYA giggle]
‐‐[TAKERU] However...
‐‐[MIKI, AYA] Huh?
[TAKERU] I don't see it getting
very far in the competition.
[AYA]
Uh?
[TAKERU]
The game is too neat 'n' tidy
for better and for worse.
What? Since when is being
neat and tidy a bad thing?
You really think this
game can't compete?!
[MIDORI]
It's okay, Aya.
Yeah, but what
about your dream?
[MIDORI]
It's fine. Honestly.
I felt like there was something
off while I was making it.
I can't put my finger on it.
But my game is still missing
a very crucial element.
[AYA]
Midori...
That may be,
but you don't need
an instant solution for this.
You're still in your
first year in high school.
You have plenty of time
to make it further
than you already have.
Forget about the competition for
now and just focus on taking‐‐
I can't do that.
[gasps]
Forgetting the contest would be
the same as running away.
Running from him.
[EMILIA] I feel like
you're overthinking this
when you don't need to.
[MIDORI]
Emmy.
It happens when
I make games as well.
Moments where things don't turn
out like I thought they would.
So, I start thinking
in simpler terms.
Meaning what?
[EMILIA] Well...
Just do what you want to!
It doesn't get
much simpler, does it?
Just do what I want, huh?
Okay.
[MIDORI gasps]
What was my motivation?
What did I want to accomplish
by creating this game?
Think back...
[MIDORI] For some reason,
ever since I was a little girl,
the showroom for the furniture
company my dad owns
has been my favorite place.
[SAKAMOTO]
Hello, Miss Midori!
Ah. Hi, Sakamoto.
Are you alone today,
or is your father here?
I came alone.
But it doesn't
matter if he's here.
Oh, dear me.
You must've had
another disagreement.
In that case...
Perhaps I can cast a spell on
you to make you feel better.
You must be joking.
Jeez. How old do you
think I am, anyway?
I'm not a child anymore.
Child or not, please
indulge me for a moment.
Give this armchair a try,
if you would be so kind.
[MIDORI] I have one
just like this at home.
So.
Can you describe
how it feels, Miss Midori?
[MIDORI]
It's not bad.
I am so very delighted
you find it to your liking.
Your recommendation
is on point once again.
Dad always brags that
you're the best floor master
and interior coordinator
he's ever known.
Not just here,
but in the industry.
I'm unworthy of such praise,
but he's very kind.
You don't have to be
modest around me, y'know.
Anyway, is this a new piece?
Yes. It came to us
all the way from Germany.
What's striking about
this piece is how,
in pursuit of
functional perfection,
it has arrived at a
bold new aesthetic and‐‐
[MIDORI] You really love
furniture, don't you, Sakamoto?
Yes. I would even
go so far as to say
it's my true calling.
Gosh. Talk about
an exaggeration.
[SAKAMOTO] Oh, no! I wasn't
exaggerating in the slightest!
One may love furniture,
but there is only so much
a solitary person can afford,
no matter how great
that love might be.
However, in my profession,
I have access to all of this
furniture and I can arrange it
in any way I see fit.
In truth, it is
the kind of luxury
no ordinary person could enjoy.
I know how fortunate I am.
That's why my occupation
is‐‐without a doubt‐‐
what I live for.
Your true calling.
[MIDORI] All of this
furniture was picked by
my dad according to his tastes.
But if I had a say
in the matter...
...I'd choose this
desk‐‐and this chair!
[gasps]
But it costs‐‐270,000?
And the desk is‐‐450,00?
[sighs]
Well, that's an eye‐opener.
Good furniture is so expensive.
I was clueless even
though I grew up with it.
[MIDORI]
Sakamoto has a valid point.
So, someday, if I have a chance
to pick out the furniture
I want as well as
place it where I want,
I would get to experience
that rare luxury firsthand.
If I could arrange
everything how I wanted.
[gasps]
Hey! What's with
the sudden outburst?
You really scared me just now!
[MIDORI] That's it. How could I
forget something so basic?
The thing that
I really wanted to do...
[MIDORI] At this point,
my game is only half‐finished.
[TEACHER 11A]
If the remainder is 13X...
[AYA]
Really? I know it's math class,
but she should be counting
numbers, not sheep!
[TEACHER 11A] Why don't we
hear an answer from Ono?
A equals open
parentheses 4X cubed
minus X squared plus
4X squared minus
X minus 12X plus 3
close parentheses.
Plus 13X minus 5 would
have to equal 4X cubed
plus 3X squared minus 2.
[TEACHER 11A]
Well done. That's correct.
[CLASSMATE 11A]
Whoa! Nice one, Ono!
[CLASSMATE 11B]
Impressive!
[snorin]
[EMILIA] Midori isn't
acting like herself?
[AYA]
It's horrible, Emmy!
She won't play
any games with us.
And she always seems
sleepy or like she's off
in her own little world.
Every thing she does
puts the "weird" in weirdo!
I want the old Midori back!
[EMILIA giggles]
It'll be all right.
[AYA, MIKI gasp]
[EMILIA] Let's give her
some space for now.
Before you know it, she'll have
a really fun game for us!
Greetings to you, Miss Midori.
I've been awaiting your arrival.
[MIDORI] I apologize for
bothering you during work hours.
I just need to grab
a few more photos.
[SAKAMOTO gasps]
Good gracious!
You haven't hurt
yourself, have you?
I'm fine.
I just tripped over
my own feet, is all.
[SAKAMOTO]
I hate to be presumptuous,
but I must ask...
Are you getting the proper
amount of rest lately?
You appear to be rather
unwell, young miss.
[MIDORI] I might've gone
a few days without sleep.
Then you're sleep deprived!
[MIDORI]
I'm all right.
Believe it or not, I actually
feel sharper than ever.
[SAKAMOTO]
Even so...
Can I tell you something?
[SAKAMOTO]
Of course.
[MIDORI] You once said that
furniture is what you live for‐‐
your true calling in life.
I used to think that was just
hyperbole, but now I understand.
[MIDORI]
I found one, too.
A "thing to live for."
[MIDORI]
I thought a professional game
had to be a certain way.
I was trapped in that mindset,
without an escape.
And thanks to
those imaginary rules,
I never bothered to factor my
own desires into the equation.
[MIDORI]
Emmy was absolutely right.
This is my game.
I can do whatever I want to.
There's nothing holding me back!
[MIKI] I'm worried.
You think Midori's okay?
She's been out with a cold
for three whole days now.
Not to mention how
strange her behavior was.
[AYA] That does it. I'm gonna
go check on her myself!
Then I'm coming with you!
[EMILIA]
Both of you. Calm down.
I'm sure Midori is doing fine.
For some reason, the snow
is really heavy this year.
Well, that worked out.
The three of you
are already here.
[AYA whimpers]
‐‐[sobbing]
‐‐[MIDORI yelps]
What in the world?
What's gotten into you, Aya?
You're such an idiot!
We've been worried
sick about you!
‐‐[sobbing]
‐‐Please, don't cry!
Does this mean that
you're feeling better now?
Miki. I'm sorry.
I suffered a case of tunnel
vision on top of my cold.
But I'm on the road to recovery.
[EMILIA] Sounds to me like you
successfully managed to finish.
Way to go!
Thank you. Finally.
What do you mean by "finally"?
Wait! Are you talking about...?
[MIKI gasps]
[AYA] Furniture tokens!
How cute is that?
It's amazing that you
made all of these by hand!
Yes. They're based
on some pictures I took.
I can only imagine
the amount of work
you put into making them.
[MIKI] That hard work paid off!
So, this is what we choose from?
Yep! You're looking at the shop!
It's still a little
awkward, though.
Oh, and there's this!
[EMILIA] Ah! These boards serve
as the players' accommodations!
[MIDORI] Right! So you
get the gratification
of buying something
from the "shop board,"
and finding a place for it
on your "room board."
Pretty soon, you'll have your
own personalized living space.
[AYA] Whoa! It's just like
building a dream home!
It's a game that enables
you to choose things
you like and customize
your own unique room.
That concept was what first
inspired me to make this.
The point is to give
you creative freedom.
So what do you think?
I think it looks super fun!
Ja! It's amazing
how much difference
the new boards and tokens made!
Heck yeah! Let's hurry
up and play it now!
[MIDORI]
So enthusiastic.
Okay.
The basic flow is essentially
the same as before.
When your turn comes, determine
your income and purchase order
for that round by placing your
marker on the work hour board.
Next is shopping.
[AYA] Huh? This little
black piece is new!
[MIDORI]
It's an existing shopper.
If a customer is in the store,
you have to find
somewhere else to shop.
The black piece moves
every single round.
Be sure to time your
shopping sprees accordingly,
otherwise you
might be in trouble.
Does that rule mean we
can't go in the same stores
other players are in?
It does. Pretty sharp.
If a store is occupied,
it's off‐limits
to everyone else that turn.
Aw. I had a feeling.
It's first‐come‐first‐serve,
so if you don't act fast,
you won't get what you want!
In other words,
it's a shopping race!
[MIDORI]
This time around,
you're aiming to
collect ten items total.
As soon as someone does,
the game ends.
By the way, the person
who purchases ten items
also receives a ten‐point bonus!
Now that there are
so many choices,
I'm having a hard time
deciding where to start.
I had a similar thought and
developed these as a result!
[AYA]
Ooh! Show me! Show me! Show me!
Catalog cards.
They list a bunch
of things you can buy.
If you manage to get everything
written on your card,
you receive an additional
bonus to your score!
I bet you had a tough time
coming up with these cards.
Didn't you?
[MIDORI gasps] You can tell?
Just by looking at them?
I knew you'd understand!
Adding in catalog
cards was‐‐by far‐‐
the most difficult thing I did.
But... they should be worth it!
[MIKI]
Midori and Emmy really seem like
they're on the same wavelength.
Well. Let's get this
play‐test underway!
[EMILIA] If you're ready,
let me hear you say "Oh, ja!"
‐‐[AYA] Oh, yeah!
‐‐Oh, yeah!
'Kay! I'm going first!
I'll collect my six gold,
and I'll buy this cute rug!
Wow, reminds me of when
I originally moved here!
I didn't have a single
piece of furniture,
so it made my room seem huge!
[MIKI] Since it's my turn next,
I'll grab this chair.
Oh! You've got
some good tastes, Miki!
Affordable, yet stylish!
[EMILIA]
Midori and I will earn our pay
and end our turns this round.
What? But how can you
pass up a chance to go shop?
Easy. I'm trying
to save my gold
so I can buy the expensive
furniture and earn more points!
[AYA, MIKI]
Huh?
[AYA]
Ah! She's right!
[MIKI]
I didn't even notice.
[AYA] Wait! This girly pink
cabinet is‐‐14 whole points?
[MIKI]
I should start saving now.
You both get excited so easily.
[AYA, MIKI]
Huh?
Going for the more
costly items is a big risk.
How so?
[EMILIA] Well... Since the
game is over when someone buys
ten things, time is against me.
In other words...
So then, if the game
ends while you're saving,
all that hard‐earned
money goes to waste!
Right. It's not
an outcome I'm hoping for.
Also, there's another
nice bonus up for grabs
that goes to the person
with the most furniture
at the end of the game.
Huh? No prob! Just buy
a bunch of cheap stuff
and you'll win before anyone
else knows what happened!
[MIKI]
Mm‐hmm! That could work.
Oh, but what about these?
Ah! I forgot about
the catalog card bonuses!
These points would make
or break a victory, no doubt!
So... I need to save up, ASAP!
Okay. I'll start by
getting what's listed
in the catalog.
Will I have enough time...
[MIDORI]
They're all strategizing.
They're totally absorbed
in my game!
[EMILIA] I'm pretty sure
I know what I want to buy.
[MIDORI]
This is great!
I'm just so incredibly
happy right now!
[MIDORI]
Game over!
[AYA groans] That cabinet just
wasn't meant to be mine.
Let's add up the bonuses
and see who won.
Miki got 82.
Emmy got 84.
Aya got 84 as well.
And I managed
a whopping 92 points.
What? Midori won by a landslide!
It's not fair!
Well. I am
the game's creator.
I'm bound to be fairly decent
at playing, y'know.
[GIRLS gasping]
[MIDORI]
What? What's wrong?
‐‐I forgot.
‐‐Me, too.
[AYA] We're best friends
with the person
who invented this game!
That important fact
must've slipped our minds
since we were so
wrapped up in playing!
Ah! Stop. You really
don't have to flatter me.
[EMILIA] I assure you,
this isn't flattery.
[gasps]
This game has so many choices‐‐
so much creative freedom!
You did a great job!
She's right.
The previous version didn't have
nearly as many ways to play!
It's cool!
I still can't get over
how you made such an
awesome game all by yourself!
[MIDORI]
By myself?
No. You're wrong.
There is no way I could've
made this on my own.
[AYA]
Huh?
Not without you three.
Thank you for everything.
Whaddaya mean?
Silly.
We didn't know what you were
doing while you were gone.
We had no idea you were
working so hard on your game.
Yeah. We didn't help at all,
so I don't think we're
very deserving of your praise.
Of course you are!
You took time to
play‐test it for me.
We're besties.
That's normal, isn't it?
[MIDORI] Just because
it's normal doesn't mean
that I expect that of you!
I would've been stuck
without people to play it.
You guys are the reason
I was able to move forward.
[AYA, MIKI]
Aw, Midori.
[MIDORI] A while back...
I was given some advice.
This guy said I'd never
complete my game.
Not if I kept my guard up
and refused to let others play.
I thought he was just being
a jerk and snapped back at him.
But after sharing
One Room with you,
I think I get it now.
So this guy... Who is he?
His name's George Beresford.
One of my goals for this
competition is to make him
play my game. Call it
a hidden agenda, I guess.
You said Beresford?
As in the designer
from Bad Dwarf?
Midori... You're so lucky!
[MIDORI]
He's my boss's friend, not mine.
I can tell you
he's as pretentious
as he is stubborn, though.
But you're that much closer
to becoming a real game author!
You're ahead of me.
Not quite.
I wouldn't have remembered
what I wanted on my own.
That one was all you.
That's why I think it's fair
to say you're ahead of me.
Midori...
You both have amazing dreams!
It's really cool! Right, Miki?
Uh, yeah. Definitely.
[MIKI]
Why am I feeling like this?
I'm happy for her,
but also a little... sad.
[MIKI]
This past year was lots of fun.
But am I the only one who
wouldn't mind if things
stayed just like this forever?