[PA chiming]
[ANNOUNCER 10A] Announcing the
arrival of Japan Air Splendor,
flight 1‐1‐2‐3,
arriving from Seattle.
I repeat, announcing
the arrival...
[KENJI laughs]
[AYA screams]
[CROWD gasping]
[KENJI]
Calm down! It's just me, Aya.
[HANA]
Hey, Dad! Welcome home!
Thanks, hon. Good to see ya!
[gasps] Daddy!
[KENJI, AYA laughing]
[MIKI]
For the first time in two years,
Aya's father traveled
back to Japan!
So tell us. How amazing
was Patagonia?
Well, for starters,
there were a ton of animals
that Africa didn't have.
Here's a sneak‐peek!
[AYA]
Wow! A whole pack of alpacas?
No, not alpacas.
They're guanacos!
Huh?
[HANA laughs]
[MIKI] Aya's father is a
famous wildlife photographer.
His job takes him
all over the world.
[KENJI] Whoa. Look at the way
this guy carries himself!
And he knows how to
work the camera, too.
My kinda kitty! Oh, that's good!
[laughs] He never
wastes an opportunity!
Ugh! What, do we have to be
animals to get your attention?!
[MIDORI] Huh? Your dad
hasn't made it home yet?
[AYA]
Mm‐hm.
I'm sorry.
I was under the impression he
was back in Japan right now.
He is.
But as soon as his plane landed,
he left for a meeting in Tokyo.
He hasn't gotten around to the
"home" part of coming home.
Okay. But lots of
fathers are like that.
And think of all the
catching‐up he has to do.
Aber. I bet you missed him in
the two years he was gone.
[AYA]
I sure did.
Plus, I was thinking it'd be
cool for him to meet you guys.
Ah! If you want to introduce us,
then why don't you invite your
papa to the Christmas party?
Oh! What a great idea!
[AYA]
Party?
Remember?
Emmy's throwing a Christmas
party at her house.
To get us in the holiday spirit.
And the party's on a weekend,
so your dad should
be able to make it.
That's true!
Most publishers close up shop
on the weekends, don't they?
This plan is bound
to work! All right!
[EDITOR]
Thank you kindly.
That should be everything we
need regarding the contract.
And hopefully, this
contract won't be the last.
[KENJI] Hopefully.
But I have to get going.
My daughters are waiting,
so excuse me.
Actually, before you go,
we could use your help
with something else.
I'm listening.
[bell chimes]
Wanna hit up the arcade?
I don't know.
[phone chimes]
[SHOUTA] Mm?
It's a text from Takayashiki.
Wonder what's up.
"Do you have any plans
for tomorrow night?
It would be really cool if
we could hang out and...
I could finally introduce
you to my dad?"
Hey. Is this real life?
Fortunately, yes. Congrats.
[SHOUTA] I can't meet her
dad before we even date!
Ryuji! I'm terrified.
Please come with me!
[KENJI]
I'm home!
[AYA] It's about time!
You must be pretty hungry, huh?
Lucky for you, I've been
cooking up a storm!
Thank you, but I'm
actually not hungry.
I ate something on the train.
You what?
Too bad.
Maybe give us a heads‐up
the next time you do that?
Guess I'm not used to
home‐cooked meals these days.
You're in a good mood.
What's got you feeling so happy?
Well, I just landed
an awesome new gig.
I guess it shows.
Is this new gig
for photography?
You know it!
And this time your pops will
be shooting bears in the wild!
Ha! We're following
a local hunter
so we can get some great shots!
Awesome, right? Tomorrow.
I'm leaving for the mountains.
What? Tomorrow?
But Daddy, tomorrow is Saturday!
What about the Christmas party
you promised you'd go to?
Oh, yeah, that.
Must have slipped my mind.
But I'd be crazy to pass up
an opportunity like this!
[AYA]
I see. So you forgot about me.
Don't think that way.
I'm really sorry, sweetie.
As soon as we're finished‐‐
[AYA]
I don't care.
Huh?
Do what you want!
I don't care anymore!
[KENJI]
What? Hey!
Come back, Aya!
Aya!
[HANA] She had every right
to react like that.
Why?
You should know.
This wasn't just some
random Christmas party
for you to blow off.
She wanted you to meet
all of her friends.
Ah, so that's why.
Dad, she loves you
and wants you to be
a part of her life.
So stop disappointing
her like this.
[MIKI]
Hey there, Aya!
[gasps]
[cries] I'm so glad you're here!
Um. What's going on?
Now rain?
[MIDORI] The first place
you thought to bring her
was the Saikoro Club?
I'm sorry.
It's fine, I guess.
[KENJI] Excuse me. Have any
of you seen my little girl?
[AYA]
Huh? Daddy?
[KENJI]
There you are.
[AYA]
What are you doing here?
Don't be mad.
I messaged Hana and
told her where you were.
We should get going.
Your sister's waiting for us.
No! Get away from me!
But, I...
That's harsh.
[TAKERU]
Okay then.
[BOTH]
Huh?
If you'd rather not
make your way home yet,
why not partake in a game?
For once, I'm not
in a gaming mood.
[TAKERU]
You're currently in a game shop.
If you're gonna stay here,
you're gonna play here,
otherwise you know
where to find the exit.
[MIDORI]
Read the room a little, boss.
What could he
possibly be thinking?
Fine, then. I'll play.
[TAKERU]
Hmph. Sir, would you be so kind
as to take the seat
across from her?
Me? I'm playing, too?
What? That's not
part of the deal!
Ah. But tough luck,
we need four players.
Midori and Miki should
have a seat, too.
Why can't you play with us?
[TAKERU]
This is Blokus.
It's a territorial strategy
game from France.
There are varied shapes of block
pieces in four sets of colors.
Everyone picks a color
and takes turns
putting their blocks
on the board.
The one who manages to put
down the most pieces wins.
You're required to
place your first piece
on your own corner
of the Blokus board.
Every piece after that
should touch a corner of
a previously placed block.
Your edges are not
allowed to touch.
That's pretty much the game.
You can begin with whatever
piece you want to.
And feel free to touch
the other players' blocks.
Let's see what the
four of you can do!
I'll start us off this time.
You'll notice the Blokus pieces
are composed of
one to five blocks.
For every piece you're
unable to play by the end,
you lose one point per block.
That's why most people play
the bigger pieces first
and foremost.
Also, they want to extend
to the center of the board
and invade the other players'
territories early on.
I'm gonna steer clear
of my dad's territory.
[MIDORI]
Not smart.
If you play pieces in
your own zone like that,
you'll run out of
space really quickly.
Like I care.
[KENJI]
Wow, she must really hate me.
Uh! What's the big idea?
I don't want you on my side!
Let's talk.
At least hear me out.
I have zero things
to discuss with you.
Just leave me alone.
I'm selfish. Always
doing what I want to.
I've been this way for
as long as I can remember.
[gasps]
Whenever I find
something fun and exciting,
I lose sight of
everything else around me.
Yeah, that's right!
You couldn't be more selfish!
You leave your family at the
drop of a hat and go wherever!
That's the reason Mom left you!
[BOTH gasp]
Easy there.
You're right.
Everything is 100% my fault.
Because that's who I am.
It's the essence of
Kenji Takayashiki.
[KENJI]
If I gave up that lifestyle,
I wouldn't
be me anymore.
Maybe that'll make you hate me,
and there's nothing I can
do about it. But I know,
even if I become the most
hated person in your eyes,
doesn't matter.
I will always love you.
And that'll never change.
From now until forever.
I just wanted to make
sure you knew that.
[AYA]
You know what's funny, Dad?
Uh?
[AYA cries]
[AYA] When I was little, I was
a completely different person.
Everything scared me,
right down to my own shadow.
And I cried nonstop.
But one day‐‐you
decided to take me
along with you
to see the sunset.
That's when you told me‐‐
the world's not a scary place,
so keep your chin up.
Because some of the
best days of your life
haven't even happened yet.
[gasps]
Some of the best days of your
life haven't even happened yet,
so gotta keep your chin up!
At least that's
what my dad says!
[laughing]
Your words gave me courage
and suddenly I wasn't
afraid of anything.
The world became a place
I could explore and live out
more of my best days in.
So hating you just
isn't an option for me!
[gasps]
I've filled my life with so many
fun things and experiences.
I just wanted to show
some of them to you.
You did?
[KENJI]
This shop. Your friends.
They're all a part
of that, aren't they?
[AYA]
Yep!
[laughs]
Let's play one more round.
Okay, Daddy?
[TAKERU]
Hope to see you again.
You, too.
I‐I'll make sure to have
my wallet though next time.
You guys rock!
Seriously. Thank you
for everything you did!
Of course.
We'll see you tomorrow.
[AYA]
'Kay. See ya!
[BOTH sigh]
What a relief.
I'm glad they made up.
But did you see
the Blokus board?
By the end of the second game,
they both managed to
play all of their pieces!
[TAKERU]
It's called Blokus,
but it's a smarter strat
not to block anyone.
You have a better chance
of playing more pieces
if you let other players in.
They focused more on opening
up and less on blocking,
so they won.
Is that why you
made them play it?
Were you thinking that message
might get through to them?
Yeah, okay.
'Cause I'm really
the type of person
who would do
something like that.
Gimme a break.
I just thought if they
were going to fight,
a board game was a
better battleground.
[EMILIA] Thank you for coming!
Merry Christmas!
[PARTY GOERS]
Let's eat, drink, and have as
much fun as we possibly can!
Everyone's feeling festive.
And I'm right there with them!
That's great, but what
happened with your father?
Oh, that. He went
off to photograph
the bears in the end.
It's all good, though!
He and I were able to talk
some stuff out last night.
He may be gone, but I
won't miss him as much.
Besides, he met my best friends.
Out of everything I
wanted to share with him,
you two were top priority!
[SHOUTA]
So that's what she meant
by introducing me to her dad.
And here I thought I was gonna
have to win his approval
or something. Honestly,
I'm kinda relieved it
turned out like this.
But... Because I
jumped to conclusions,
I dragged Ryuji to this party.
Huh?!
It was nice of you
to drop by, Yoshioka.
I hope you have fun
with the games!
Absolutely!
Play on, playa.
[EMILIA]
Papa can handle the rest,
which means I'm officially
off hostess duty.
So it's game time!
Ja! If no one's opposed,
there's a game I've been
wanting to try for a while.
This one! Ladies & Gentlemen.
[MIDORI] Oh, the one where
you pair up and compete
over a whole week to see who can
dress the nicest for a party.
Leave it to Midori. Of course
you'd know this game!
It already sounds fun!
Let's give it a go!
Yeah! I'm in!
Mm... I'd play, but it
sounds like a girly game.
And you are incorrect
in that assumption.
Girls and boys pair up to
play this game together!
Girls and boys?
Pair up?
That's right! In
this board game,
the ladies are in charge of
purchasing the ensembles.
What about the gentlemen?
The men are responsible
for making money
so the girls can
buy their outfits!
Sounds a little bit like
a racket to me, but okay.
How about we divide
into pairs now?
I'll join the guy side since the
ladies outnumber the gents.
Sure thing.
Let's play rock‐paper‐scissors
to decide the pairs.
[SHOUTA, RYUJI gasp]
[MIDORI]
Here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
And the results are in.
Pair one is Tanoue and Aya.
It's in the bag, right Tanoue?
Uh. Right!
[MIDORI]
Then Yoshioka and Miki.
Um. Good luck to you.
Thank you. Same to you!
And, the third pair
will be Emmy and me.
Sehr gut! Please earn
lots of money, ja?
[SHOUTA]
It's a miracle!
[RYUJI]
We are not worthy.
[EMILIA] In this game,
the ladies and gentlemen
will be playing
at the same time.
To start things off‐‐
the ladies play a craftsman
card in front of a shop.
This will determine what's
available for purchase.
There are four categories
for these cards.
First is the "dress,"
with four types.
The second is "accessory,"
which has five types.
The third one, "jewelry,"
also has four types.
And 20 different "maids"
make up the last category!
We buy these things, dress
ourselves up for the ball,
and show up looking stunning!
[BOTH gasp]
Our role is a crucial one.
We have to make a profit
in the futures market.
Meaning?
We need money to provide
for our ladies.
There are 15 tokens with one of
six different goods on them,
and we place all 15 facedown.
The gentlemen then
simultaneously flip them over,
and collect three of
any type they choose.
Next we sell these
hard‐earned goods
for the rate
indicated on the card.
Keep in mind there's something
called a Contract card,
and the first player to
draw it gets a bonus.
I guess it's every
gentleman for himself.
It's first come, first serve.
Better bring your A game.
I'm counting on you,
so don't screw up!
Um. Just do your best.
[RYUJI, SHOUTA]
Yeah. Okay.
Are you boys ready to play?
[RYUJI, SHOUTA]
Yes!
[MIDORI]
Get set, go!
Right! While they're busy doing
that, we get to go shop!
[MIKI, AYA]
Yay!
[AYA]
Wow! They're all so cute!
[MIKI] And it's hard to pick.
There are so many choices!
It sure would be nice if
we could have all of them.
[AYA]
It really would!
[EMILIA] So, has everyone made
their selections by now?
All right, girls! Try to be
cute when asking for money.
[AYA] Okay! Hey, Tanoue!
Please buy this.
[EMILIA]
You can do better than that.
Speak to Shouta as if
he were your husband.
Ah, I got it!
I really want this.
Pretty please?
[gasping]
Your wish is my command!
I'll buy anything you want!
[AYA]
Thanks, babe!
Let's see here.
[SHOUTA]
We're way outta my price range.
Um. Would you divorce me if we
settled for just the dress?
What?! That's what I get
for marrying a bum.
[gasping]
Wait, are you sure?
This is all you want?
Yes. That's right.
May I please buy it?
Yes! Of course you may!
[RYUJI] Man. She's really
being modest here.
Really modest.
Uh? Thank you for my accessory!
[EMILIA]
Please, Midori?
There's no denying that
this tiara and necklace
are a match made in heaven!
It's too expensive to buy both.
You can have one,
and that's final.
[EMILIA]
Oh, but darling.
Huh?
If you buy them for me,
I promise to make it
worth your while.
Please?
[MIDORI grunts, chuckles]
You drive a hard bargain.
I'll pay 100 pounds
to keep it for you.
Wunderbar!
I love you very much!
And that brings us to
the end of day one. Cool.
Five more days, and we'll be
on our way to a fancy ball!
Yeah!
Wait. We repeat this
nightmare five times?
That's right.
I said the party was in
seven days, didn't I?
Good luck, my darling!
Um. Please try not to
overwork yourself.
Make tons of money
that I can blow!
[SHOUTA]
Ah, man. This isn't just a game.
[RYUJI]
It's a test of masculinity.
[SHOUTA]
I'm not gonna lose!
[RYUJI]
I'll win this!
It's day two!
Ready, set, make money!
I'm rich.
[PARTY GOER B]
I'll be honest. You're cute.
[AYA]
Why, madam!
[MIKI gasps]
That dress you're wearing
is absolutely fabulous!
Where on earth did you
find such a treasure?
[MIKI]
A favorite emporium of mine.
I must say, that
tiara is gorgeous.
[AYA]
Oh, do you recognize it?
Lolo Laverne came out
with it not too long ago.
[EMILIA] I'm pleased to
see you're all together.
[BOTH]
Uh?
Fine party, isn't it?
Whoa...
Pretty...
[MIDORI]
...22, 23...
Plus three from
the maid makes 26!
Emmy and I win!
We won because the power of
our love could conquer anything!
Oh, darling! I love you!
I, um, uh...
It's my fault that we lost.
If only I could've
made more money.
Oh, please don't say that!
You did a lot for me.
You deserve nothing but thanks.
I'm happy. This was just enough.
[RYUJI]
Mm!
[RYUJI] I will provide for her
for the rest of my life!
Aw, shucks. We lost again.
[SHOUTA gasping]
I guess someone has to
end up in last place, huh?
[AYA laughs]
[SHOUTA]
Takayashiki...
[AYA]
Later, alligators!
Make sure Miki gets there
safe and sound, okay?
[RYUJI]
Right.
[MIKI]
Thanks, Aya. See you later!
Well. You wanna get going, too?
Yeah. Let's go.
[SHOUTA] I really let her
down during that game.
[AYA]
Ooh!
It's freezing!
I'd give anything for some
hot cocoa right now!
Oh! Almost forgot.
Here, take this!
Uh. I got you a
Christmas present.
A Christmas present?
But why me?
[SHOUTA] Was that too much?
Dang it! I'm so dumb!
[AYA]
Thank you!
[SHOUTA]
Huh?
I was surprised because I didn't
expect you to get me something,
but then I remembered,
"'Tis the season to be giving!"
Right. 'Tis the season.
[laughing]
[SHOUTA]
Crisis averted!
[AYA]
Can I open it?
Yeah. Go for it!
[rustling]
[AYA]
Wow, what a cute pair of gloves!
They're warm, too!
You've been giving me stuff all
night tonight, haven't you?
Thanks a lot.
I couldn't be happier!
[gasping]
So! Does this mean you found it
in your heart to forgive me?
[AYA]
Huh?
[SHOUTA] I couldn't buy
you any gloves earlier.
I hope this makes up for it.
[MIKI]
I appreciate you walking me
all the way to the
station like this.
Just a second!
Huh?
[RYUJI]
I, uh...
[RYUJI] C'mon, say it! Tell her
"I want to see you again!"
[RYUJI] I hope you have
a happy new year!
[RYUJI]
I failed!
Yeah, see you again next year.
[gasps]
[RYUJI]
Again?
[MIKI] Mm? Oh, wow!
Would you look at that!
[AYA] How cool! It's really
starting to snow!
[MIDORI] I think it's about
time I headed home, too.
Darling. I love you so much!
Huh? What?!
[MIDORI] I've decided to submit
my game to a competition
all the way in New York!
I'm not running away anymore‐‐
whatever the results may be!