[MIKI] I never really mastered
the art of playing around.
[BOY]
Come on, you slowpoke!
[GIRL]
I don't think I can.
[MIKI]
Fun was just a word to me.
I never really understood
what it meant.
But I like to think
there are things in life
worth waiting for.
[MIDORI]
Miki!
[AYA]
Look up here!
[MIKI] And that sometimes
it takes other people
to teach you to
have a good time.
[MIKI]
It was a usual morning.
In my usual classroom.
[AYA]
What? That rule is so silly!
My old school wasn't like that.
[MIDORI] Well, Kamogawa
is your new school,
and that's how it is.
[MIKI] Everyone is
always so talkative
and lively right before
homeroom starts.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Of course, that's only
weekdays. Remember that.
[grumbles]
[MIKI] Our teacher sure is
taking a long time to get here.
[MIDORI]
Takekasa.
[gasps]
Uh. Hey, Class Rep.
If you're free this Sunday, you
should come do karaoke with us.
It'll just be the girls
from our class.
Kind of a nice way to bond.
[MIKI]
Uh! Sorry, I have plans.
But thank you.
[CLASSMATES chattering]
[MIKI] I don't like
what most people like.
If it piques someone's interest,
it won't even catch mine.
If there's a crowd,
I'm the one avoiding it.
One thing I do enjoy
is walking by the water.
[MIKI inhales, exhales]
[MIKI] The refreshing air
of the Kamogawa River
somehow eases my body and
gives me a sense of peace.
[AYA screams] Watch out!
Watch out! Watch out!
[MIKI gasps]
[AYA screams]
‐‐[MIKI gasps]
‐‐[splash]
[MIKI]
Oh my gosh!
Uh. Can someone help her?
[laughs] I'm sorry.
I hope you're not hurt.
[MIKI] I'm not the one who
just crashed in the river.
[AYA]
Talk about the ride of my life!
The brakes suddenly
stopped working!
Serves me right for
renting a cheap bike!
Thanks for standing guard.
Sure. Don't mention it.
[AYA] Oh wow, I'm soaked
right down to my undies!
Guess I'm going commando.
Hurry up before someone
walks by and sees you!
[AYA] Do people normally hang
out under the bridge?
I just moved here recently,
so I don't know the
popular spots yet.
I thought you might be new, too,
since you're always alone.
I guess we haven't been
properly introduced.
Oh, yeah. You're in my class.
Sure am! My name
is Aya Takayashiki.
It's a pleasure!
Nice to meet you.
Uh. I'm Miki Takekasa.
[MIKI] Do you always carry
a change of clothes?
[AYA] Since I'm new to
the area, I wanted to do
a little sightseeing and
exploring after school.
I brought extras to change into
so I'd be more comfortable.
Although it is a little breezy
without underwear on.
So you got any plans
for the afternoon?
Uh. Oh. I actually...
[AYA]
Cool! Mind showing me around?
Well, to be honest.
I, uh, don't really
get out that much.
I'd be a terrible tour guide.
[AYA]
Even better!
[MIKI]
Uh!
Right! Let's get going!
We're going further
than the bus stop?
Oh, you betcha!
We should start by
heading in this direction.
Wait. Hold on.
We can't just walk around
or we'll end up getting lost!
Lost huh? Ah! That's a
fantastic idea, Miki!
[MIKI]
Huh?!
We should get lost today!
[MIKI]
On purpose...?
[AYA humming]
Um. We've been
at it for a while.
[AYA]
Hm?
I kinda don't feel
comfortable traveling
much deeper into the forest.
We should head back‐‐
Hey, Miki! Look over there!
[laughs] What is it?
Some type of guardian?
Uh! Ah!
Look! Duckies!
It's getting late.
Don't you think?
This is great.
Baby ducks are so cute!
Please. Listen!
You've never been out
here before, right?
We don't know where
we are right now,
and we don't have
any kind of map.
If we keep wandering
around like this,
we... really will end up lost.
[cries]
[AYA] Hey, it's okay.
Please don't cry.
[AYA] I get the feeling that
you're lacking the sense.
Lacking sense? Sense of what?
Adventure!
Huh?
Like, you remember our
destination, don't you?
Uh, we, we never decided on one.
Right! Miki,
in order to get lost,
you have to have a destination.
Since we don't have
one of those, we're okay!
Uhh...
[AYA] Say it's your first
time going to a shop
you've been wanting
to check out,
but you take too
many wrong turns
and eventually end up on
the opposite end of town!
Now that would definitely
classify as "being lost."
So you see,
without a goal,
we can't possibly get lost!
That is a very valid point.
[AYA laughs]
One of the many secrets of life!
We're not lost‐‐not even close.
We're just adventuring!
[MIKI]
Adventuring?
Yup! Exploring the un‐explored!
Stressing over how we're going
to get home is just going to
take the fun out of
everything for you.
You should take it in.
All of it.
The sights,
the sounds, the smells.
There's beauty everywhere,
so try to enjoy it!
Okay.
[AYA]
Let's go adventure!
[AYA, MIKI panting]
[AYA, MIKI gasping]
[AYA]
Awesome! What a find!
[MIKI] I think it's
an old water bridge.
[AYA]
Wow, how cool!
[MIKI]
Yeah, much better than pictures.
Uh? Hey, check it out!
[MIKI]
It's gorgeous.
I was born and raised
in this town, but...
I've never seen
a sunset like that.
[AYA laughs]
Just you wait!
Huh?
Some of the best days of your
life haven't even happened yet,
so ya gotta keep your chin up!
At least that's
what my dad says!
[laughs]
Uh?
[MIKI] I truly believed
that I was immune
to any and all types
of fun in the world.
But for the first
time in my life,
I was starting to
second‐guess that theory.
Because, at that moment,
I was smiling.
See? That wasn't so bad.
You had fun, right?
Yeah.
[laughs] I knew you would!
An‐‐ Uh!
Huh? Hm?
That girl on the sidewalk
there. It's our class rep!
[MIKI]
What's she doing here?
Isn't this the
entertainment district?
So?
So she's a pot who likes to
call the kettle black, is all.
And don't forget to
mind the curfew.
No places of entertainment
or cafes after six pm.
Of course, that's only weekdays.
[AYA] It's already way past six!
Let's trail our rule‐breaking
class rep and see what
she's up to. C'mon!
Uh...!
[AYA] Seems like a pretty
boring building to me.
Be prepared for anything.
Uh. Kay.
[AYA]
Saikoro Club?
She went in here?
[gasps] Look at all
the pretty pictures!
[AYA laughing]
[MIKI]
Weird. What language is this?
[MANAGER]
It's German.
[AYA, MIKI yelp]
Hey, ladies. Welcome to
the Saikoro Club.
[AYA, MIKI scream]
Hold on!
Don't freak out!
[MIDORI] I've told you
time and time again
not to sneak up on
customers from behind!
[BOTH gasp]
You own a mirror, so you
know how scary you look.
Huh?!
[BOTH]
Oh, no way!
They're... my classmates?
How did you two even
find this place?
What is it you want?
[MIKI] Well, we happened
to spot you walking past
our bus stop and we‐‐
[AYA]
I call shenanigans!
How can you go around slapping
people in the face with rules
when you aren't even
abiding by them yourself!
Not to mention the company
you like to keep.
What?
He's my manager
and this is my job.
Not that it's any of your
business, but I got special
permission from the school
to work here after six.
Unless you have
similar permission,
you two need to leave.
That's not fair!
Yeah, well.
Life isn't all that fair.
Whoa, take it easy
there, Midori.
Your friends just
stopped by to say hi.
No harm done.
My friends? They're
only my classmates.
Since you two are here,
you should stick around.
Have a little fun
before you head home.
[AYA] I like fun!
But what would we do?
[laughs] We're in the middle
of a game store,
so why don't we bust out
some games, eh?
A game store?
So, you're saying...
All of these pretty boxes
are different games?
[MANAGER] Wait, you didn't
realize that already?
Yeah, this shop specializes
in tabletop games.
[MIKI]
Games? But there are so many!
[MANAGER]
It's mostly European merch
with the majority of
our stuff imported
all the way from Germany.
Your store is so cool!
[MANAGER]
It's the definition of cool!
Wanna give one a try?
Oh, yeah! You bet!
Let's see...
What? Really?
[MANAGER]
Right.
The name of the
game is Marrakech.
[MIDORI grumbles]
[AYA]
Come on, Class Rep!
You should play with us, too!
[MANAGER]
I picked one of your favorites.
No thank you.
Alrighty then, guess that
just leaves us three.
Woo!
[MIKI]
Thank you for letting us play.
Now the best asset
you can have
for a game is your imagination.
[MANAGER]
So imagine you're in Morocco.
The board represents
an exotic, thriving city.
Its name? Marrakech.
And the three of us are
competing to become
the best rug merchant
in the land!
Midori, why don't you
explain the rules?
You were doing fine!
This is Mr. Assam.
First, you decide which
direction our little wooden
friend will travel, and
then, you roll the die.
By the way, this die only
has values one through four.
Two and three are
both on here twice.
Mr. Assam moves the number of
spaces indicated by the die,
then you're free to place a rug
tile adjacent to where he lands.
You can put the rug
anywhere around him,
you just can't
completely cover up
another merchant's wares.
If Mr. Assam lands on another
player's rug during your turn,
count the squares that
their connected rugs
cover and pay one
dirham for each.
Lather, rinse, repeat.
Metaphorically speaking.
And then the player
with the most money
at the end of the game
is dubbed the winner.
Oh, I gotcha.
So you want to lay out
as many rugs as possible
to up your chances of making
more money and winning the game.
[MIDORI]
That's basically it.
Do you have any questions?
Of course!
If this is one of your
favorite games,
why don't you play us?
I don't want to.
[AYA] Then what's the point
of working in a game shop?
Know what? I should probably
go back to dusting.
[AYA]
Yeah, but you're missing out!
Perhaps I need to
spell it out for you.
That it? This is my
place of employment.
It's my duty to make
sure it functions
at the highest levels
of productivity.
Make sense?
Um. Yeah. I guess so.
Now. Back to the wonders
of Marrakech.
Choose your colors
and we'll get started!
[MIKI, AYA]
Sure
[MANAGER]
All right.
Rock‐paper‐scissors will
decide who goes first.
[AYA] Ooh! Mama needs
a new brown rug!
One or four... One or four!
No whammies, please!
No! [whines]
For landing on my
turquoise textile,
it's three dirhams, my dear.
[AYA sighs] The universe
must hate me today.
Y'know, sir, you should
go easier on us.
This is our first time
playing after all.
[MANAGER]
Your name is Takayashiki, right?
Uh!
[MANAGER] If I'm playing a game,
I'm playing to win.
Doesn't matter if my
opponent's an adult,
a child, or even
a high school girl.
I don't hold back.
[BOTH gasp]
So then, Miss Takekasa.
Where's Mr. Assam heading next?
[gasping]
What's wrong?
The clock's ticking!
What are you doing?
Stop messing with them, boss.
You know it doesn't sound
funny when you say such
intimidating things. If you
go that way, you'll be safer.
Go ahead and roll now.
Ah, okay.
[MANAGER]
Midori. Such blatant disrespect.
[gasps]
[MANAGER] Jumping in on
someone else's game like that
is forbidden. It's at the top
of the Saikoro Club rulebook.
How odd.
You never quite struck
me as a rule‐breaker.
Point taken.
[MIKI]
Wait! I...
I'm terrible at games
and that sort of thing.
I have no idea what I'm doing
and it's really
stressing me out.
So maybe, could you... maybe...?
Are you okay?
[cries]
[MIDORI]
Hey, boss.
[MANAGER]
[MIDORI]
After some consideration,
I've decided to join the game.
Huh?
But I will be joining
as her teammate.
Talking strategy with
a fellow team member
isn't against any Saikoro
Club rule I'm aware of.
Correct?
[MANAGER grunts, growls]
If you had any kind
of super power,
it would be finding loopholes.
[MIKI] Thanks a lot. Really.
[MIDORI] No worries. I'm in it
to win it now. So...
Thing is,
I don't think winning is even
an option for us at this point.
Your boss has a huge lead.
Very true.
We definitely have our
work cut out, don't we?
But the rug layout
isn't too complex yet.
We still have a fighting chance.
[MIKI gasps]
You think?
Absolutely. Stick with
me and you'll be
the best merchant that
Marrakech has ever seen!
[grumbles] No fair, guys!
I wanna be the
best merchant, too!
[MIDORI]
Rival merchants won't sway me.
You'll have to rely
on your own strength.
[AYA] What strength?
I'm the weakest link!
[MIDORI]
You need to be able to predict
what comes next if you
want a leg up in this game.
Things like how
your rug placement
affects the other
players' decisions.
And what kind of traps the other
players are trying to lure
you into. Let's change
things up a bit.
We'll focus on our profits and
gain back any money we spend.
The best defense
is a good offense.
Here, you roll.
Kay!
[gasps]
My oh my, what to do?
I will admit, that was a
pretty smooth move, but...
[MIKI] Wait a second.
That's enemy territory.
I know that. Look, though.
The payoff is too
good to not risk it.
Yeah, but if we
land on his rug...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
We'll owe 7 dirhams!
Which means, our defeat
would be inevitable if
that were to happen.
This turn will make or break us.
If we roll a 3 or 4,
we can turn this bad situation
into something good, though.
[gasps] "Turn a bad situation
into something good"?
Avoiding the problem
isn't solving it.
It'd be best to
face him head‐on.
I mean, you never
know unless you try.
[MIKI]
You never know unless you try.
[MIDORI] It all boils down to
you and your luck, Takekasa.
[MIKI]
Uh...
[MIDORI]
No pressure.
Miki, I'm rooting for you!
Thanks. You're too sweet.
All right. Here goes!
[MIKI] Three or four.
Please. Three or four!
[AYA]
A four! Miki, you did it!
Way to go! Knew you could!
Well, it appears the
tables have turned.
[MANAGER]
No matter which way I go,
I'll have to roll a four,
or I pay eleven dirhams!
We're waiting.
[MANAGER grunts]
[gasps]
[MIKI]
A two! But that would mean...
Yep! We're the
indisputable champs!
[MIKI]
I can't believe this. We did it.
We beat your boss!
We sure did! All thanks
to you, you lucky girl!
I wanna join in on the
victory celebration!
You're still the enemy. Sorry.
‐‐Don't be so mean!
‐‐Stop it.
I was rooting for your team,
too, you know!
[MANAGER] I didn't know
Midori had such good friends.
Ha! Today was so much fun!
I really liked that game.
I kinda want to try some more.
So long as it's okay with Class
Rep, I'd love to visit again!
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to advise you against it.
Tonight was all my boss's fault.
[AYA]
Huh?
[MIDORI] If I catch either
of you loitering around
this district at
this hour ever again.
I'll have no choice but to
report it to the school.
[gasps]
That said, if you ever
want to have a rematch...
[MIKI, AYA]
Uh?
The weekends and
holidays are an exception
to the school's rule.
You don't say.
But I honestly don't
care either way.
Just throwing it out there if
you ever want to play again.
[AYA]
Round two is a go!
And we're back to the clinging.
What? Clinging?
[MIDORI]
Never mind.
Ah‐ha! By the way, it's
just an observation,
but you act pretty cute
when you get excited!
[MIDORI]
I highly doubt that.
[AYA] What? Being cute
is a good thing!
[MIDORI] I suppose you think
you're being cute right now?
[MIKI]
She was right.
I'll keep my chin up,
because some
of the best days of my life
haven't even happened.
Hey, Miki! Put some
pep in your step!
[MIKI] I hope there are more
days like this, though.
Because I finally
learned what it was like
to have fun with friends.
[MIKI] We decide to
try playing a game
with Ono's childhood friend,
and things start
out well enough.
But I'm sensing
something strange.
Don't tell me!