[MIKI]
After the school festival,
it was time for midterm exams.
We decided it would be best
to postpone any game‐playing
so we could concentrate
on studying.
Luckily the hiatus
was short‐lived
since exams came and went
in the blink of an eye.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[AYA sighs] It's been a hot
minute since I could relax.
[MIKI]
I'm with you there!
If you're relieved, just
think how Emmy must feel.
She took all those
tests in Japanese!
Where'd you learn how
to speak it so well?
I was taught by my grandmother
after I moved over here.
She's Japanese.
I learned from the best!
Wait.
How long have you
lived in Japan again?
It's been four years!
But I moved to Kyoto when
my papa finally opened
his board game shop.
The rest is history!
That makes sense to me.
Now that I'm thinking about it,
where exactly is your game shop?
[MIDORI]
It's right here.
[EMILIA] Uh. I don't think
I know where that is.
[MIDORI] Considering how new
you are to the area,
that's understandable.
But you know,
Kyoto streets aren't all
that hard to remember.
They all just so happen
to cross at right angles,
which is similar to a Go board.
If you know which
direction north is,
you'll always be able
to find your way.
A "Go board"?
You're overthinking.
She's talking about
the game board in Go.
Oh! Ja! I know Go!
At least the title.
The rules are another story.
But that still helped me get it.
I should be able
to read that map now.
It looks like Midori's shop is
north of our current location.
So it's this way!
That's west, not north.
[laughs]
Wow.
I wonder...
Is Emmy...?
[GIRLS]
Directionally challenged?
[AYA]
Howdy‐ho!
All together as usual, I see.
Wow. This shop is
unbelievably cute!
[TAKERU]
Hm? Who is this?
She's our friend, Emmy!
Born and raised in Germany!
Oh, wow. You don't say.
Nice to meet you. I'm Emilia.
This might be small
and underwhelming
to someone from Germany,
but I hope you still enjoy it.
Nein! There's no need
to be so modest.
I'm honestly just
happy to be here!
This whole place
fascinates me!
Elfenland!
What's an "Elfenland"?
It's been ages.
This was a game I used to play
a lot back in Germany.
Only I think the box
got a little smaller.
[TAKERU] It did.
But the board and pieces
remain the same as
they always were.
Care to play and see
for yourself?
[MIKI, AYA, EMILIA gasp]
Is that really okay?
[AYA]
Cool!
[MIKI]
The board is so pretty!
You're reacting like I did
the first time I played it.
You might wanna
brace yourselves.
We're about to embark
on an adventure
through a fantasy world,
that happens to be inhabited
by trolls and elves.
See this little boot here?
It represents your
current location.
And, as you travel
around the board,
you recover these markers
from every town.
Yay! Traveling is
one of my favorites!
So to move, you use
these "vehicle tiles"
as well as these cards.
Tiles and cards each
have an illustration of
a vehicle depicted on them.
At the start of the game,
each player receives
eight cards and four tiles.
No more, no less.
Okay.
So players take turns placing
a tile on the individual roads
at the beginning of each round.
This decides which vehicle
can travel that path.
The important thing to make
note of here is the terrain.
Why?
[MIDORI]
Because there're five types.
Grassland, Forest, Desert,
Mountain, and River.
Depending on the terrain,
a vehicle may or
may not be supported.
[EMILIA] Boars can only go
on grasslands and forests,
while unicorns can go
everywhere but two terrains.
Even dragons‐‐one of the
more versatile vehicles‐‐
are barred from rivers.
[MIKI] What do these
ones and twos mean?
Those show the number of cards
it would cost to travel.
[MIKI]
Cost?
For instance,
if there's a boar tile on a
grassland road, the cost is one.
So you pay one card.
If you traverse a
desert via unicorn,
you pay the cost of
two unicorn cards.
I see!
Can you not travel if you
don't have the right cards?
Nope. In that case,
you can pay any three cards you
like and still be good to go.
This is known as a Caravan.
But, only use Caravans
as a last resort
since that kind of
strategy is so wasteful.
[MIDORI] The round ends
one of three ways.
You run out of cards,
you can't play your cards,
or you just don't
want to play them.
Before the next round
can start, you select tiles
and draw until you once again
have eight cards in your hand.
The player who picks
up the most markers
at the end of four rounds
is dubbed the winner.
And that's all there is to it!
Thank you!
I think I understand!
This sounds like fun!
Well, shall we get started then?
Yeah!
[AYA cheers]
[MIKI laughs]
[MIDORI laughing]
[EMILIA laughs]
[MIDORI]
That's the end of round one!
This game is great!
It feels like I'm really
traveling the world!
[MIKI]
Mm‐hm!
Come on, let's keep
this adventure going!
You bet! There's three
more rounds to go!
Let's visit as many
towns as possible!
[AYA]
You know it!
Huh?! That was supposed to be
my unicorn mountain pass.
Uh. Nice move there.
[EMILIA chuckles]
[AYA]
Hm...? Oh, yeah!
[AYA laughing]
[MIKI]
I can't go on.
But there are still four
of my markers on the board.
Same for me.
But check Midori out.
That a girl!
She got all but two!
So close yet so far
from domination.
After Emmy goes,
the game'll be over.
Right! Then here I go!
How about one with a troll,
two with the elves, three with
a boar, four with a dragon,
five for another dragon,
and I'll pay a Caravan
of cards to make six!
[BOTH gasp]
[AYA]
Whoa, Emmy!
You got all of your markers!
Ha! Ja, I'd say
that went all right.
What a finale.
It appears your
sense of direction
doesn't apply to games.
[JOHANN] Wow, Emmy!
You snagged all of them again!
Your sense of direction in
games is great! Lucky you.
And yet she still gets lost
in her own neighborhood.
That is true.
Emmy.
Are you really going
to Japan next week?
[EMILIA]
Ja.
We're going to miss you.
We'll still be your friends
no matter where you wind up.
[gasps]
Just don't forget us.
Sound like a plan?
There's always email, right?
Oh, Hans. Johann.
I won't forget you all.
I promise you that.
[ANNA]
Liar!
Anna...
You're such a liar!
Oh, no!
Hey. Why the tears?
It's because you made fun
of her sense of direction!
What?! Wait! That's not it!
Really, I'm not crying
because of that.
I just happened to
remember something.
Elfenland was the very
last game I played
with my friends in Germany.
I couldn't keep a promise
I made with those friends.
A promise that would
make you cry?
[EMILIA] Mm. Anna. She was
my closest friend back then.
The two of us grew up together,
and we loved games
wholeheartedly.
We loved them so much that
we both promised we'd make
a game together one day.
[gasps]
Distance can be tough,
but I hope it doesn't spoil
the promise we made.
Even if we have to achieve
our dreams separately.
[MIDORI]
Your dream?
Well, you see.
I would like to design
a game of my very own.
And make children all over
the world smile because of it!
[MIDORI gasps]
[MIDORI]
She has the same dream I do?
That's so fitting!
Another gamer‐turned‐
game‐author in the group!
You and Midori should‐‐
[AYA whimpers]
Not kill me!
Are you all right?
You look disgruntled. Ja?
Uh! It's nothing!
[chuckles nervously]
I just completely forgot
I had something important
I needed to do today.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
Better go before I forget again!
[AYA]
That was weird.
Such a shame.
She'll be a fledgling
for longer than I thought.
[MIKI]
Midori...
So Midori is also aiming
to be a game designer, ja?
Who told you a secret like that?
Well, from her!
That's when my dream
first formed.
It made me so happy
to hear someone in Japan
say she had the
same dream as me.
I can see why!
Ja, but... I don't think
Midori feels like I do.
I thought it might be nice
to talk with a person
who had the same dream.
Emmy.
I, um...
I need to talk to you
two about something.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[MIDORI]
Emmy wants to make games?
She grew up in
the culture's capital.
What would she come up with?
It would be nothing short of
amazing‐‐it's Emmy, after all.
I know I would want to play
it just like everyone else.
But what if her game
turns out to be
a million times
better than mine?
I'm afraid of a game that
doesn't even exist yet
thanks to my stupid pride!
[GEORGE]
I'm sorry.
[MIDORI gasps]
You are not a game designer.
[MIDORI] Shut up!
You think I don't know that?
I know it better than anyone.
[MIDORI] Huh? Stuff we
did when we were younger?
Ja! I would like to learn
whatever traditional games
Japanese children play.
Wow.
And that sort of thing
actually interests you?
We refer to fun things like
playtime and board games
as "Spiel" in Germany.
The key word in that sentence
being fun, of course.
And exploring Japanese Spiel
might provide a hint
for making games.
Huh... Games we played as kids.
Would things like tag or
hide 'n' seek count?
I don't think those are
authentic Japanese games.
Like Daruma‐Doll Fell Down?
‐‐Oh!
‐‐There we go!
We've got a game,
but how does it go?
Let's explain it by
trying it out right now!
Great!
[MIDORI]
So, basically the rules are...
Truth be told,
I haven't actually
played this game that much.
I'll take over then.
[EMILIA]
If you could please, Miki!
When playing
Daruma‐Doll Fell Down,
you first need to pick
someone to be the Oni.
I don't think I know
what that word means.
It's a Japanese monster!
Real big and scary, with two
sharp horns that look like this!
Ooh!
We'll play rock‐paper‐scissors
to decide the Oni.
And then, the Oni will
go over to that tree.
I'll make a mark here.
That's where
everyone else starts.
So then... Let's get
back to the Oni!
She hides her face and chants
"Daruma‐Doll Fell Down,"
while everyone approaches.
Daruma‐Doll fell... down!
The moment the Oni finishes
saying this and turns around,
everyone else has to
freeze where they are.
So long as the Oni is looking,
no one can move.
Try really hard to stay still.
Because if you don't,
you get captured.
Oh, no! What happens
if you get captured?
[MIKI] You have to hold
hands with the Oni
and wait for someone
to come to your rescue.
Performing a rescue
is a lot easier
than you might initially think.
Just touch the Oni
while she's chanting,
and you've freed the prisoner.
[MIKI]
Daruma‐Doll...
[AYA]
Tag!
[MIKI]
One, two, three, four, five!
Once tagged, the Oni
has to count to ten.
The other players then use that
short timeframe to run away.
Get as far from the Oni
as you possibly can.
[MIKI]
Stop!
[MIKI] When the Oni says stop,
you do just that.
Right. I think I'm
remembering now.
From here, I think
the rules tend to vary
depending on the
region you're in.
Like how the one who touched
the Oni decides the steps.
[EMILIA]
Steps?
[MIKI] Like five big steps,
or maybe ten small ones.
[AYA]
Five big steps!
[MIKI] If the Oni can't touch
anyone after the steps
are taken, she's "it" again.
Lastly, if the Oni is touched
before she manages
to capture a prisoner,
then that would also
result in a rematch.
And that is everything
in a nutshell.
Danke schon!
I'm kind of fascinated.
I have heard of games
like this before,
but they were European versions!
[MIKI]
Huh?
So there's Ox on the Mountain.
That's the German one.
I think Red Light,
Green Light is England.
Both involve approaching
and tagging a player
while that person's
back is turned.
I never knew!
I assumed it was
a Japanese game.
There are some details that make
yours its own unique version.
And it seems a
little more complex.
So what are we waiting for?
[AYA]
Not a thing!
[MIKI]
Ready when you are!
[AYA]
Start! Just one step!
[MIKI]
Daruma‐doll... fell down!
[MIKI
Ah! Midori moved!
[MIDORI]
What? Are you sure about that?
[MIKI]
Mm‐hm. Your left arm!
Don't stress it, Midori!
Your rescue team is coming!
Take my hand.
[gasps]
All right! Here we go!
[MIKI]
Daruma‐doll... fell‐‐
[AYA]
Tag! Run!
[MIKI] One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten! Stop!
[MIKI] Aya, were you
the one who tagged me?
[AYA]
You got it!
[MIKI]
How many steps can I take?
How 'bout three big ones!
[MIKI]
What? Just three?
One, two, three!
[MIDORI]
Well, naturally.
They may have been big, but
three steps isn't that far.
That's cheating, Aya
Uh? My bad.
I thought I got to decide
whatever I wanted.
It is kind of odd that the
person who tagged the Oni
gets to decide how
the steps are taken.
Let's enforce a minimum number.
Maybe between ten and fifteen?
I think some other regions
already play that way.
So what did you think, Emmy?
Was this a good
enough game for you?
Did it help you
figure anything out?
[EMILIA]
Hmm. Hard to say.
I do have a few
questions, though.
Like, exactly how does
this sort of game end?
I don't know.
I honestly don't
think it has one.
Whenever the bell rings and
everyone goes inside, I guess.
If you really stop and
think about it for a second,
a lot of children's games
go on forever like that.
Just look at tag
or hide and seek.
Das ist true. No ending.
Is something wrong, Emmy?
[EMILIA] I'm fine, but these
rules are certainly not.
That's because they were
designed to amuse children.
We're used to the innovative
rules of modern games.
I refuse to believe
that's the case!
All games can be fun.
No matter who's playing
or what age they are!
Our new mission for today:
Find ways to make Daruma‐Doll
Fell Down more interesting!
Is that something we can do?
Where would we begin?
Well, we could start with one
of the problems that I noticed,
which was this game doesn't have
any kind of a reward system.
[gasps]
Rewards?
[EMILIA] As of right now, the
rules state the other players
have to try and touch the Oni.
But all that tagging the Oni
does is begin another round.
[EMILIA]
Go again?
[AYA, MIKI, MIDORI]
Hmm...
[EMILIA]
You just repeat the same thing.
There's no incentive at all!
Also, the capture‐and‐
rescue mechanic
could use some work,
too. Think about it.
[AYA]
Tag!
[EMILIA]
Stop!
The one who touched the Oni
is at a clear disadvantage.
You see, the players face risks
but aren't given any
incentive or reward.
There should be some kind of
motivation to touch the Oni.
Yeah!
[MIKI] I've never even
thought of it that way.
[MIDORI] You're kidding me.
All that from just one round?
It's an easy fix. If we think
of some sort of ending
and a reward, we'll be set!
Like if a player manages
to touch the Oni,
she could receive one point!
On the other hand, if the
Oni can reach a player
within the given number of
steps, then she gets a point!
Another thing. Why don't we
take turns being the Oni?
The game could end after
everyone has been
the Oni one time each.
And the player who accumulates
the most points is the winner!
Is that really enough to
make this game more fun?
The changes aren't very drastic.
Ja. Well... We have to test
it out to know for sure!
Here I go!
[AYA]
Okay!
[EMILIA]
The Daruma...
[AYA]
Gotta tag her.
[MIDORI]
For one point.
[MIKI] Huh? It feels
different from before.
[EMILIA]
...fell down!
[ALL gasp]
[EMILIA]
The Daruma‐doll fell down!
[AYA gasping]
Aya's out!
Aw, dang it!
[MIDORI] Implementing a point
system makes the players
want to compete to
reach the Oni first!
As a result, we're moving
faster, which makes stopping
more difficult and
capturing us much easier.
[EMILIA]
The Daruma‐doll fell down!
Oh! You two are
doing much better
than I thought you would!
[MIDORI]
Impressive, Emmy.
The changes you made were small,
but they had a powerful impact.
Daruma‐Doll Fell Down
is a rea l game now!
[EMILIA]
The Daruma‐doll fell‐‐
[MIKI]
Tag!
[EMILIA] Eins, zwei,
drei, vier, funf, sechs,
sieben, acht, neun, zehn!
Now stop!
You three must have
your running shoes on!
We decided the Oni should
take a minimum of ten steps.
Eins, zwei, drei, vier, funf,
sechs, sieben,
acht, neun, zehn!
Aw! I'm so close,
but that's too bad.
The only one to receive
a point is Miki!
Having points must be nice.
You were right about this
being more motivating!
[EMILIA]
Well then, let's keep playing!
[AYA]
Here I come!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Gotcha! Yay! That's
three points for me!
[EMILIA] Which makes you
the winner! Congratulations!
Amazing. Who knew a little kid's
game could be so much fun?
[MIKI] Mm‐hm. It just took
a few modifications.
I would say all games
are works in progress,
but I'd be paraphrasing
Alex Randolph.
[MIDORI gasps]
[MIDORI]
Alex Randolph.
That god among men in
the board game world.
[EMILIA]
Soccer and rugby were born
from an ancient
form of football.
Chaturanga began in India,
then transformed
into chess and shogi.
Games constantly evolve,
and then new games emerge
thanks to that progress!
They're continuously improving.
I think that this concept is
very important for aspiring
game designers such as ourselves
to understand, ja, Midori.
You're right. It is
very impor‐‐ Wait what?
You, but... How did you know?
Of course! You two told her!
Nuh‐uh! She knew about
it from the beginning!
[MIDORI]
What?
She's been wanting to talk to
you about your shared passion
for game designing. She just
hasn't had the chance to.
[EMILIA] But Miki had
an even better idea!
Huh?
Leave it to me!
We'll fight fire with fire
and spiel with spiel!
If games are the problem,
we'll make them the solution!
‐‐[AYA] Huh?
‐‐But how?
What are you planning?
You'll just have to
find out tomorrow!
Ah. I was super curious
about what you meant by
all that and what was
gonna happen today,
but I guess I forgot because
it wound up being so fun!
I liked it a lot!
[MIDORI] This whole Daruma‐Doll
thing was because
I couldn't open up and tell
Emmy we have the same dream?
You guys. You're so nosey!
Are you mad at us?
Not one bit.
Heh!
[MIDORI] I'm sorry I didn't
tell you sooner, Emmy.
More than anything, I want
to become a game designer.
Maybe you could try my game out,
if you had time, that is.
[BOTH laugh]
I'd love to! I can't wait
to play! It'll be great!
[AYA]
Ugh! I hate you, Dad!
You told me you were going
to the Christmas party,
but then you broke your promise!
I won't forgive you, even
if you play games with me!