[MIKI]
Same old morning.
Same old route.
And same old me.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT A] Hey, how'd you do
on the math test?
[STUDENT B]
Bad. Like super‐mega bad!
[exhales]
[MIKI]
I just don't get it.
Having fun seems second
nature to everyone but me.
[AYA laughs]
Top of the mornin' to you, Miki!
Oh, hi, Takayashiki.
Hey. I thought we were past
the point of formalities!
Just call me Aya from now on.
Your... first name?
Yep! C'mon, we're gonna be late!
[MIKI]
That's right.
Not everything is
the same as before.
[AYA]
Hey, what's up, Midori?
Uh! What? Did you just...?
Hi. Good morning.
You seem well.
Hold up. What's with the face?
You miss breakfast?
That's not it.
What made you decide to start
using my first name?
[AYA]
Because it didn't feel right
to keep calling you "Class Rep."
You're more than that.
[MIKI]
I agree.
Even so, being on a first
name basis, that's a big step.
No worries.
I'm an ace at skipping stairs
and it's great cardio!
I meant a proverbial staircase!
All stairs aside, I owe you one.
For helping me yesterday.
So thank you.
But I will be joining
as her teammate.
Oh. That wasn't a big deal.
[MIKI] It was. I had
no clue what I was doing
and the longer we played,
the more anxious I got.
But thanks to you, Ono,
I was able to relax
and actually have fun!
[gasps] You really mean it?
Well, I suppose it
can't be helped.
Uh?
Call me Midori, and I'll
start calling you Miki.
[MIKI, AYA gasp]
It's only fitting.
Fellow champions should be on
a first‐name basis, right?
I guess.
Right!
[MIKI]
Oh. In that case, um...
Then Midori it is.
[MIDORI]
That sounded nice.
Very nice.
Uh.
Say what? Okay.
So, how many steps were
skipped for that level?
[MIKI]
I have to admit I was surprised.
I had no idea you were so
knowledgeable about games.
Let alone that you work in
a shop dedicated to them.
That's thanks to my family.
I've been exposed to all sorts
of games since I was little.
I may have lost,
but it was fun!
I really liked Marrakech!
We should try it again!
[AYA] Yeah! You got any games we
could play right this second?
Please say yes!
Impeccable timing.
Class will be starting
in just a few minutes.
Oh. I forgot.
We can play one of my games
when class lets out.
[AYA]
So you did bring some?
Wait. Then the school doesn't
mind you having them?
[MIDORI] As long as we partake
in them after school hours,
we're in the clear.
I can't wait!
Bring on the games!
How psyched are you?
[MIKI] Very! I wonder
what kind she brought.
Uh?
[MIKI] Is he spacing out?
Or is he staring at us?
[AYA]
Hey, Earth to Miki.
[gasps] Sorry about that.
So! What type of games
did you bring?
[MIDORI] Classified.
You'll have to wait and see.
[SHOUTA]
Wow. That smile of hers
really lights up
a room, doesn't it?
[AYA]
Ooh! Looks like I found my seat!
I'm Aya Takayashki.
Nice to meet you, neighbor!
You as well.
Same goes to you,
my other neighbor.
Uh. Sure. Back at ya.
[laughs]
[SHOUTA]
I can count the number of words
we've exchanged since
then on one hand.
She barely even knows I exist,
and I sit right next to her!
I can change this!
I will change this!
[TEACHER A]
So in this case,
you want to focus
on a specific numeral.
Take a look at the order
and coefficient.
[SHOUTA]
Now's my chance.
Huh? No!
Here.
[SHOUTA]
Oh, you're the best.
[AYA]
Oh, no! I forgot my dictionary!
Uh, hey, if you want...
You can just share mine!
You're a lifesaver!
[SHOUTA grumbles]
[AYA] Finally! Once we clean,
we're home free!
Then it's game time! You ready?
[SHOUTA]
Failure is no longer an option!
Perfect timing! Hey cleaning
crew, here's the dustpan!
[AYA]
Yay! Let's get to work!
[sighs]
[GIRL A]
Time to head home.
Wanna grab a snack first?
[exhales]
[SHOUTA] I didn't mange
to get a single word in.
What the heck?
How'd I screw this up?
She was right there
in front of me!
Ah, well. Tomorrow's a new day.
[gasps]
[SHOUTA]
It's Takayashiki!
And Takekasa...?
[MIKI]
But he was quite nice...
[SHOUTA] Why are they
hanging out after school?
Ah, who cares?
This could be my shot!
[MIDORI]
What are you doing?
[yelps] Oh. 'Sup, Ono?
"What's up" is your weirdness.
Do you mind stepping aside
if you're not going in?
Um... Whoa, chill out. I just
remembered I forgot something.
Oh, there she is! Hey, girl!
Huh? You brought a friend?
Oh. Hey.
[MIKI] He was the boy staring
at us earlier today.
Wait. You're one
of my neighbors!
Midori, do you two
know each other or...?
I know you can ignore
him the way I do.
[SHOUTA]
Harsh!
He's just some guy I've
been stuck in classes with
since pre‐school.
Oh! He's a childhood friend.
[MIDORI]
More like childhood pain.
[AYA]
Hmm!
[SHOUTA gasping]
[SHOUTA] Oh, man.
She's the epitome of cuteness!
[MIKI]
This guy. Don't tell me...!
Huh? Practicing catching
flies, or what?
Uh!
Remember what you forgot?
Grab it and go home already.
[growls]
[SHOUTA]
Dammit, Ono!
This is the closest I've been to
making any progress whatsoever,
and yo'u're ruining everything!
[AYA]
Aww. Don't go now.
Stick around and
play a game with us!
[SHOUTA, MIKI]
Uh?!
Hold on. Are you
sure about that?
Of course!
Things like this are more fun
with more people, y'know?
Hey, do you like board
games and stuff like that?
I do! Absolutely, 100% love 'em!
What? Since when are you
a game enthusiast?
Since shut up!
I'm playing, and that's that!
Tanoue, you're such a headache.
All right!
So, um. Could you remind me
what your name is?
Yeah. Sure.
It's Shouta Tanoue.
That's right! Tanoue!
I felt like a horrible neighbor
for not remembering your name.
To make up for it, I wish you
the best of luck, in this game!
Thanks, good luck to you, too!
The cutie across
from you is Miki.
[MIKI]
Hi. Pleasure to meet you.
Same here.
Nice to make it official.
That leaves...
game master, Midori!
But I know you two go
way back so... Duh!
[SHOUTA] Just when I thought she
couldn't get any more amazing!
She's every bit as sweet
as she is adorable!
Oh, be still my heart!
So, game master.
What are we playing today?
[MIDORI]
Right. Just a sec.
Ooh!
Wow. You've gotta be kidding!
[MIKI]
You carry all of these with you?
[MIDORI] Yes! Card games
are easy to transport.
I've never played a
single one of these.
And they all look
pretty different.
[MIKI]
Yeah.
Card games come in many forms.
There's poker and
Uno, and, well,
they even make
trading card games
featuring anime and
game characters
you might be familiar with.
And in Europe, especially
Germany, new tabletop games
are created every year
due to popular demand.
There're lots of genres
and types, too!
Some require things like
intellect and strategy,
while others are based
on pure, dumb luck!
[SHOUTA]
Man.
Just how big is the
library of her brain?
Then again, she's always
been like this.
Ever since we were kids.
Okay then. How 'bout...
...we give this one a try.
Kakerlaken Poker.
I've never heard of
that one, but okay.
Interesting. That name...
Yeah. It means
"cockroach" in German.
But that's not the only pest
we'll have to deal with!
Flies, scorpions, spiders,
toad, rats, bats, bugs.
If it creeps you out,
chances are there's a card
for it in this game!
The best advice I can give?
You have to be really good at
bluffing with a straight face.
That's how you force your pest
cards on the other players.
You said bluffing?
Never heard of that.
To put it more simply, bluffing
means the same thing as lying.
[gasps] What? Lying?
This might get a
little tricky, huh?
[BOTH]
Uh...
Let's break it down!
The first player hands
another player a card,
making sure to keep it
facedown on the table.
They then say the name
of one of the eight creepy
crawlies featured in the game.
It's a cockroach!
[MIDORI] They can be honest
and say what it really is,
or they can bluff and say
the name of a different pest.
The one receiving
the card then guesses
if that was a lie or not.
If the receiver makes a verbal
decision, they flip the card.
Liar. This is not a cockroach!
Uh!
[MIDORI]
If the guesser gets it right,
the card is returned
to the sender, faceup.
If the guesser gets it wrong,
the card is placed
faceup in front of them.
The one who ends up with
the pest begins the next turn,
choosing a receiver and
playing a new card.
Better believe it's a toad!
You don't have to make
a guess, though.
You can also decide to pass.
If that's the road you take...
This is a bat, for sure.
I'm passing.
[MIDORI] ...you declare the pass
and then look at the card
without showing it
to anyone else.
You then claim the name
of one of the eight pests
and hand the card, facedown,
to any player who
hasn't seen it yet.
This is a spider.
Here's the fun part.
You can say the name
of whatever pest you want no
matter what was said before.
If you end up with four of
the same pest cards faceup
in front of you, or if
you manage to collect
all eight types of
pests, you lose.
See? Pretty easy, right?
I guess.
I think I get it, but
I also think I don't.
Uh?
[MIKI]
Mm!
You'll get the hang of it
once we start playing.
Let's begin!
[AYA humming]
Okay.
So, Tanoue, why don't you start?
Uh, sure!
[SHOUTA]
This is it!
Time to make my move
and truly bond with my dream
girl through this game!
My card's comin' to you,
Takayashiki!
Fine! Bring it on!
[SHOUTA]
This is... a cockroach.
[AYA] Uh, okay. So now
I'm supposed to guess
if this is a cockroach
or not, right?
Right. If you suspect
it's a cockroach,
say, "This is a cockroach,"
and flip the card.
If you suspect it's another
pest, you still flip the card,
but first you say,
"This is not a cockroach."
[AYA]
Hmm...
It's a total shot
in the dark, huh?
I'll just guess, then!
This is not a cockroach!
Oh, no! It is one!
[gasping]
You got me this time.
Pretty slick!
[stammers, laughs nervously]
[SHOUTA] Way to make a first
impression, Shouta, you jerk!
What the heck are you doing?
Since you guessed wrong
this time around,
make sure to keep that card
faceup in front of you.
[AYA]
'Kay...
[MIDORI]
Don't be too bummed, Aya.
The one who fails gets
to start the next round.
Right! It's payback time!
Here, have a fly, Tanoue!
Oh. Um. Let's see here...
[AYA]
We haven't got all day.
Is it a fly, or is it not?
[SHOUTA]
I'm at a total loss.
But she doesn't
seem to be lying.
I say fly...
[gasps]
No! But what gave me away?
Nothing did!
I was just guessing!
[SHOUTA]
I mean...
It's really hard to picture such
a sweetheart lying to anyone.
[AYA grumbles]
Now I have two.
[MIDORI] You failed again, Aya.
So you know whose turn it is.
Oh, I sure do!
How 'bout a lovely,
little scorpion?
[SHOUTA]
Oh, crap.
I'm pretty sure it's a scorpion,
but I can't keep beating her.
She'll really start
to resent me.
Man. That's a tough call.
[MIKI] I think he's
head over heels for Aya.
That would explain this morning.
Gee. You're really good
at this bluffing thing.
Guess I'm gonna have to pass it!
Sha‐bam!
[SHOUTA]
Knew it was a scorpion.
I pass to Takekasa!
Okay. This is... a fly!
[SHOUTA]
What's with that look?
[MIKI]
This is not a fly.
[AYA] Whoa! Awesome!
Miki, are you psychic, or what?
[MIKI]
Not at all.
I was just getting weird vibes,
like he might be lying.
You idiot.
If you hesitate before
declaring a card,
it's extremely obvious
that you're bluffing.
[SHOUTA] Ooh. This chick
is a real piece of work!
Hey. Ono!
This is a stink bug!
It's a stink bug.
[SHOUTA yelps]
You realize
this is your first time
ever playing this game.
That would mean it's your first
time seeing all eight creatures,
and memorizing them
is a bit harder
for newer players to manage.
'Stink bug' is not
a common insect.
If you wanted to fool me,
you should've said something
like a fly or a cockroach.
Those are
extraordinarily common.
[SHOUTA]
Good grief.
I didn't know we were playing
the Kakerlaken Poker
world champ over here.
Got it? If you do, then go ahead
and play your next card.
[SHOUTA]
Fine. Here, Takekasa.
This is a toad.
[MIKI]
I choose to pass.
Here you go, Aya.
This is a toad.
[AYA]
This is not a toad!
No! Foiled again!
[AYA]
This is a rat!
[SHOUTA]
I pass. Want a nice, fat rat?
[MIKI]
It is a rat.
[SHOUTA]
Gah! You're good at this!
This is a stink bug!
[MIKI]
It is, indeed.
[SHOUTA]
Wha‐‐? No fair!
‐‐[AYA] It's a fly!
‐‐[COACH] Here we go!
‐‐[MIKI] Yes, it is.
‐‐[ATHLETES] Left, left...!
‐‐[AYA] Aww!
‐‐[ATHLETES] Right, right...!
[AYA] Okay, Miki!
Believe this is a cockroach?
I do, as a matter of fact.
[AYA]
What? Stop it!
That's quite impressive.
You're on a roll!
Thanks. I really like this game.
It's right up my alley.
[AYA]
No! What a disaster!
[SHOUTA]
It's looking grim.
Takayashiki has
three cockroaches
as well as three flies.
She gets either one
and she loses the game.
It's not her fault!
She's so angelic she's
incapable of deception.
She's too precious
for this world!
Cheer up, Aya.
It's your turn again,
so choose well.
Roger that.
[SHOUTA]
What can I do to make sure
she doesn't lose this round?
The time has come!
This is a cockroach!
[SHOUTA]
Whoa. Talk about a gutsy move.
If I agree that it's a
cockroach and it turns out
she's telling the truth,
that's game over man!
She loses!
That's way too risky.
Oh, I get it.
She's finally lying.
This must not be a cockroach.
She really is the worst liar
I've ever seen in my life.
But I can't exactly
call her out.
That would be just as mean as
making her lose at this point.
I should play it safe and
pass like the nice guy I am.
Wait a minute! I'm on
the verge of losing, too!
If this card turns out
to be a bat, I'm toast.
That's it! I figured
out her strategy!
That must be why I'm her target!
I could always pass and
have a showdown with Ono.
If I want to be crushed
like a stink bug!
And Takekasa has a
damm near perfect score.
It'd be just as
tough beating her.
[MIKI] I bet he's considering
every possible outcome
in hopes of saving Aya.
[SHOUTA] Her intuition is as
sharp as a scorpion's stinger.
I'm practically an
open book for her
to skim through
whenever she likes.
What play do I make?
If I pass to protect
Takayashiki,
I could be next on
the chopping block!
No. I refuse to lose!
[MIDORI]
Hurry up!
So what'll it be?
A showdown? Or a pass?
Uh. I'm still thinking!
[SHOUTA] If I trust my gut, then
that card is definitely a bat,
which means I can send
it back to Takayashiki
without any repercussions.
She doesn't have any bats yet!
Here goes nothing!
You're lying!
Huh?!
[SHOUTA]
This is... not a cockroach!
What the heck? A fly?
You have four flies.
Meaning the loser is...
No! It can't be!
It can be.
If you put the card that loses
you the game into play.
But I thought for sure he'd pass
just like all those other times.
I thought getting rid
of it was so smart!
Wah! Why, Tanoue?
[AYA cries]
[SHOUTA] I passed her cards
for the entire freaking game,
yet the one who dealt the
finishing blow... was me!
How could I be so stupid?
[SHOUTA cries]
Why are you acting like
you're the one who
lost the game?
[MIKI]
Aw, poor Tanoue.
He was trying so
hard for Aya's sake.
[sighs] I guess... I should
be heading home now.
[AYA]
Not so fast!
Uh...
Could I talk to you for a sec?
So, what's up? Are you okay?
[AYA] Please feel free to
correct me if I'm wrong.
Before we played the game,
you said you forgot
something in the classroom.
That was a bluff.
Huh? Um. I, uh...
[AYA laughs]
What gave you a
crazy idea like that?
Then show me what
you left behind!
Like... Right now?
Lighten up, will ya?
I already figured it out.
You did what now?
There's no need to
keep it secret.
I kinda stink at games.
As you know.
But my keen women's intuition
more than makes up for that!
[SHOUTA]
No way! There's just no way!
She figured out that
I have a crush on her?
[gasps]
[SHOUTA]
She's taking it remarkably well.
Is it because she likes me back?
Tell me.
And answer honestly.
You're totally hung up
on Midori, aren't you?
Huh? Midori?
You... You can't
possibly be serious!
Never in a million years!
Ono and I barely
qualify as friends.
It's a tale as old as time.
You fell for you
childhood friend!
Know what gave it away?
The only time a boy
plays a silly game
with three girls is
when he likes one!
[SHOUTA] Well. You might
be onto something there.
What is taking them so long?
Must have a lot to say.
[AYA]
I can see why you fell for her!
She is a little weird,
but she's super pretty.
And I know she tends to keep
her guard up around everyone,
but I'll try to help
you out with that okay?
‐‐Listen! It's not like that!
‐‐Eh, love will endure!
We'll get through this together!
On that note, I'll see ya!
Ah! Hang on!
[AYA]
Hey! Let's play another round!
I'm feeling lucky!
[SHOUTA]
Absolutely unbelievable.
Her woman's intuition is about
as keen as her card playing!
[AYA]
Wow. Two fun days in row!
I hope we're starting a trend!
[MIKI]
Mm‐hm.
Wanna know a secret?
It turns out that Tanoue
has a thing for Midori!
It was kind of obvious.
[gasps]
Think we've got a
heartbreaker on our hands.
Hey, Aya, did you
say something?
Nope, not this time!
Say. How about the next
time we play games,
we invite Tanoue!
Ugh. But why him?
[AYA]
We've been through this before!
The more the merrier!
[MIKI]
I suppose
hanging out with classmates
was as foreign to me
as the wonderful games
Midori introduced us to.
I never knew it could be...
...so fun.
[AYA]
Miki! Don't fall behind!
Gotta keep up!
[MIKI]
Coming!
[MIKI] I hope the way home
is always this much fun.
Always.
[AYA] We're breaking out the
games at my house next time!
My sister's friend, Maki,
even gets in on the action.
Huh? Miki, do you know
her from somewhere?