[MIKI] The school festival
is just one week away.
Coincidentally,
a brand‐new board game café
opened up near our school.
We decided to check it out
in hopes of learning
something that might better
prepare us for the festival.
[MIDORI]
This is it.
Café Geschenk.
[MIKI]
Yes, seems like the place.
Good afternoon!
[gasps]
[AYA]
There's nobody here.
[MIDORI]
That seems odd.
Perhaps they haven't opened yet.
[gasps] Um. I found someone!
[MIDORI, AYA]
Huh?
[MIDORI]
She's sleeping?
You think she works here?
[EMILIA grunts]
[GIRLS gasp]
Hello, welcome.
[ALL gasp]
[MIKI] She's so pretty!
And she's from overseas!
[gasps]
[MIDORI]
Uh. Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
The three of us‐‐
This isn't the first
time we've met!
[MIKI, AYA, MIDORI]
Huh?
Nice to re‐meet you!
Kleine welt!
[AYA] Huh? You remember us from
just passing us on the street?
That's right.
You three made quite the
first impression with me.
I happened to overhear your
discussion about board games.
[MIDORI]
What a strange coincidence.
I know. Small world.
I'm Emmy!
It's short for Emilia, but
I prefer using my nickname.
I'm Aya Takayashiki,
but Aya's fine!
I'm Midori Ono.
And I'm Miki Takekasa.
[EMILIA] It's nice to put
names with your faces!
Tell us, where do you
come from, Emmy?
I'm from Hamburg, Germany.
What? I am so jealous‐‐
that's board game central!
Ja!
Basically everybody in Germany
enjoys board games!
Unfortunately, the same
cannot be said for Japan.
But that's why
we made this café!
[AYA] What? That would make
you the owner, right?
Not quite. The owner
of the shop is my papa.
[GIRLS gasp]
Um, thank you for having us.
Of course. Welcome!
You see. I may not run the
place, but I do help out!
[MIKI]
Your game selection is huge!
[MIDORI]
Right?
And it ranges from kids' games
to core gamer favorites!
It's really remarkable.
Your father knows his stuff!
Choose a game that
stands out to you. Bitte.
I'll gladly explain the rules if
you aren't familiar with them.
What? Don't just explain it.
We'd have more fun
if you played!
Uh! You want me
to play with you?
You do not mind?
Not at all! We're usually
in need of a fourth.
True!
[EMILIA gasps]
Emmy, what's the matter?
Nothing. I just haven't
gotten to play games
with girls my own
age in Japan yet.
So it would be the
first time for me.
I'm a little touched. Danke!
This means so much to me.
[AYA, MIKI, MIDORI]
She's too cute!
[MIDORI]
Keltis!
[EMILIA] Richtig! It is my
absolute favorite game!
[MIDORI] Nice! I'm a fan
of this one, too.
The board looks so pretty!
It does! These patterns
are beautiful!
These specific patterns
are called Celtic Knots.
"Celtic Knots"?
The Celts were a people.
Europeans from the BC era.
The stylized knots they
used for decoration
became a symbol
of their culture.
I've heard of Celts before.
They say modern‐day Ireland
was built by them, right?
Correct! Just so happens,
my mama is of Irish decent!
Oh! So then...
The necklace you're wearing.
[EMILIA] Good eye!
This is a Celtic charm.
It was a gift from meine Mutter.
This tiny keepsake
holds the great power
to make any wish come true.
Oh, wow! It's so lovely!
[MIDORI]
It really is!
[EMILIA]
Okay! Let's go over the rules!
Everyone is going to
start with eight cards
as well as five pieces.
Wow! The cards are
pretty like the board!
The pieces look like
clovers! How cute!
[EMILIA] There are five
different card colors.
When your turn comes,
you play a card.
You then put a piece on a
space with the same color
as the card you just played.
The cards are numbered
from zero to ten.
As you can see.
For your first card, you can put
down any card number you'd like.
However, the next
card's important.
It decides what card
you can play next.
[BOTH gasp]
[EMILIA] Like this! You play
cards that have the same color
on top of one another.
First I had a four,
then I played a six!
Which means the cards
I play from now on
will have to have a
value of six or greater.
On the other hand,
if I had played the
six before the four,
I could only play cards
equal to or less than four.
I gotcha! When you play
cards of the same color,
you can only go up
or down in number!
So no backsies!
Das ist prima!
Also, every time
you play a card,
the piece on the path with
the corresponding color
advances by one space.
There are five paths.
And you can only have
one piece per path.
You may go down
all five if you want.
But notice that the
first three spaces
give you a negative score.
Pick your paths wisely!
Yup, it says negative on
the board, right there!
[EMILIA] Your points are
determined by where your pieces
end up once the
game has finished.
Which would mean...
If we don't play four cards,
we'll be negative in that color.
Also, be careful where you
put your big piece, ja?
It gets double the points.
[BOTH]
Ooh!
Same for negative points.
That's why I told
you to be careful.
[AYA, MIKI]
Uh!
[EMILIA] There are three
types of tiles on the path.
Numbered tiles provide
you with points.
The points received are equal
to the numerals shown.
Clovers grant extra movement.
If you land on this tile,
you can move one more space.
That's not all.
You could move a piece
that didn't land on
the clover instead.
Ja! Precisely right!
You can move lots of spaces
if used strategically.
Please keep that in mind,
as it is important.
[AYA, MIKI]
'Kay...
[EMILIA]
The third and final type of tile
is the Wishing Stone.
There are nine of these total.
This tile is first‐come‐
first‐serve.
That means the person who
lands there first receives
the wishing stone.
Collecting stones is a
good way to earn points,
but if you don't obtain at
least two, you'll lose points.
Huh?! We can lose more points?
[MIKI] Oh, the point
values for wishing stones
are displayed right there.
What? You get negative four
points if you don't have any?
[EMILIA] The darker green area
of the board is the goal zone.
The game is over as soon
as five total pieces
cross into this territory.
And that's how you play
Keltis. Any questions?
Nah, your explanation
was on point!
[EMILIA] Wunderbar!
Let's get started then!
[MIDORI, AYA, MIKI]
Yeah!
And the person who's
been to Ireland
most recently goes first!
[MIKI, AYA]
Huh?
Gee, Emmy. You're all
about this Celtic theme.
Maybe dial it back?
Great! I went on a
trip just last year!
What? What kind of
a rule is that?
Well, it's more of a joke
than an actual rule.
But a rule nonetheless,
so I go first.
Yellow ten! I think... I'll
use my big piece for this.
‐‐[AYA gasps]
‐‐Isn't it a bit too soon?
Well, I'll follow suit.
[AYA]
Your big piece, too?
I'm just trying to plan
ahead. I'll get pretty far
if I have a lot of cards
that are the same color.
Oh. Good strategy.
But... my colors are
all over the place.
I'll stick with a small piece
and play it safe for now.
Same here.
No way! I think I have
to forfeit already!
I can't play the
red nine anymore.
And the other cards wouldn't
get me much further.
You can discard a card
and draw a new one.
So all hope is not lost.
[AYA]
Really?
[MIDORI]
However, the discarded card
can be picked up
by any other player,
so make sure you're tossing
one that nobody else wants.
Huh? A card none
of you want, huh?
Hey, Aya.
Try looking for what other
people have played,
not what you have in your hand.
For example, a person who played
a blue nine, seven, and six
won't take any blue
cards greater than six
because they've no use for them.
If that's the case...
Got one! There!
Good job! That card
doesn't work for anyone.
Thank you for the advice!
I guess that makes
it my turn now!
I play a green three,
and get one point!
It lands on a clover,
so I'll move this other
piece for two points.
But I land on another clover.
So I'll move this piece‐‐
for three total
points this round!
Amazing! You moved three of
your pieces in one turn!
I should've warned you,
but I've never lost this game.
I'd believe that
in a heartbeat.
That clover chain was proof.
But I'm fairly confident
in my own abilities.
One point here,
but let's add two more.
You managed three points, too.
Which makes it my turn.
I'll play this green four.
Then move this one.
This one. And this one.
Huh?! Makin' clover chains
like no big deal!
Well, it is fun!
I know the feeling.
Nothing like a good
Keltis clover chain!
Hey, Emmy, you okay?
[EMILIA]
Oh, I'm way more than okay!
[MIDORI]
Huh?
[EMILIA] The Japanese.
They enjoy cute things, ja?
I am no different
in that respect.
Being able to play a game with
cute girls makes me so happy!
[BOTH]
Huh?
‐‐Cute?
‐‐Seriously?
You're so sweet! Takes
a cutie to know a cutie!
[MIDORI grunts]
[MIDORI]
I didn't think it possible,
but these two are definitely
on the same wavelength.
[MIDORI]
I'll put a blue one in play.
Now,
if one more piece enters
the dark green goal zone
the game will be over.
What? Over already?
Three of my pieces are
still in the negative area!
[MIDORI] That's because you
played all five of your pieces.
You should've focused
on a select few
if you wanted to get past
the negative spaces.
Since this might be it,
I'll move my big piece
one more space.
[sighs] Me, too.
[EMILIA] Super! With five pieces
in the goal zone, it's over!
[AYA cries]
Why don't we tally up
everyone's scores now?
I ended up with 31 points!
Midori's final score... Uh...
...34 points?
I lost a game? Unbelievable.
I lost at my favorite game.
Hey, there's no need to be‐‐
Fantastisch!
You're the first person who's
ever beaten me, Midori!
Okay...
[MIKI] I've never seen
someone so happy to lose.
Twelve points.
That's my final score
'cause I have more minuses
than a math test.
[EMILIA] That's not bad
for a first‐timer!
Really?
You'll do even better
the next time you play.
Aw, Emmy!
Just let it all out.
Hey, Midori.
[MIDORI]
Hm? What's up?
Wouldn't it be nice if
the café at the festival
is this much fun?
Oh. What are you
talking about?
A festival!
Our school is putting one
on a week away from now!
And get this‐‐we'll be
running a board game café!
Ah! Das ist wunderbar!
I love festivals so much!
Come to think of it,
I also like your uniforms.
What school do you go to?
Kamogawa North High School.
It's not too far from here.
[gasps]
[GIRLS]
Hm?
You serious?
I'm set to transfer there
starting in September!
What? You're gonna
go to our school?
Meine Mutter told
me this pendant
would grant me wishes
if I kept believing.
Turns out she was right!
What was your wish?
I wished to see
the girls I walked by
the other day and actually
introduce myself this time.
I also wished to be
friends and play games.
My wishes came true!
[MIKI] Finally, the day
of the festival arrived!
Some students worked
in food stalls.
While others performed
their hearts out onstage.
As for us...
[AYA]
Nobody's coming.
[MIKI]
Yeah.
I should have known.
I didn't think the vice
president would back down
without a fight, but geez.
[YUTO] Second floor
of the old building?
Why'd you put 'em in
the middle of nowhere?
They turned in their
application way late
and it was the only spot left.
You can't be serious.
That project had so much
promise. Such a waste.
I agree to disagree.
Success doesn't hinge
on that group.
[AYA cries]
It's not fair!
So what do you think
we should do?
[sighs]
What's something we could do
that would let people know
to look for us out here?
[door opens]
[EMILIA]
I finally found you!
[GIRLS]
Emmy!
Guten Morgen!
Thanks so much for coming!
You're the best!
[EMILIA]
Of course!
Though, it took me a
while to find you all.
Why did you choose such a
remote location for your café?
[gasps] It's terrible, isn't it?
By the time we actually
get a customer,
the festival will
be all but over!
[EMILIA]
Don't fret too much, Aya.
Huh?
Because... I brought
a secret weapon!
‐‐Uh?
‐‐Huh?
[SHOUTA] Where's this
board game café anyway?
What?! The second floor
of the old building?
[FANGIRL A]
Yoshioka! You're so hot!
[FANGIRL B]
Please notice me!
[SHOUTA]
Oh, it's just Ryuji.
Slayin' the ladies
like he always does.
Too bad all he cares
about is kendo.
Hey, yo! Shouta!
[SHOUTA]
Why are you following me around?
[RYUJI] I'm just trying
to shake the fangirls.
Don't hafta brag!
[BOTH]
Uh?
[SHOUTA]
Must be the place. Right on!
Seems like business
is really boomin'.
[AYA]
Welcome to our café!
[SHOUTA]
Huh? T‐Takayashiki?
I appreciate you two
taking the time to stop by!
[SHOUTA]
So, what's with the outfit?
[AYA laughs]
Cute, huh?
Anyway, you guys came
at a really great time!
So don't be shy and come on in!
I apologize for the long wait.
All right, boys. Let me
explain how the game works.
[STUDENTS]
Right! Thanks, head maid!
[SHOUTA] This is awesome. It's
almost like a party in here!
Just a little while ago,
it was the exact opposite,
but then this happened!
[SHOUTA]
Huh? What's the‐‐?
Wait. That girl. She's
the cute transfer student
all the guys won't
stop gushing about!
Emmy told us about the
school's social network.
We put one picture up and boom!
[SHOUTA]
Emmy?
She's right over there!
I know you've been waiting,
so let's play without delay!
[SHOUTA] I see. So she's the one
attracting the male demographic.
Hey, Tanoue!
Here ya go!
[SHOUTA]
Huh?!
Wanna manage this table for us?
What?!
"Manage" as in sit here and
explain the game to people?
Pretty please? We're super
short‐staffed right now!
Help me, Tanoue,
you're my only hope!
Fine. You win.
I'll do my best for you!
Thanks! You rock!
Ha, ha. So I'm her only hope.
[STUDENT B]
Is this some kinda joke?
Why'd we get the
boy band wannabe?
[SHOUTA]
Uhh...!
[GAMER A]
Come on, three!
[GAMER B]
What do I do here?
[EMILIA]
You want to play like this!
‐‐[GAMER C] I don't have any.
‐‐[GAMER D] Got it! Goal!
[REN]
They've got standing room only?
Man, oh, man!
This has gotta be the
most popular event!
You're right. And I
chalk that up to you.
Your idea to share the info
on social media was brilliant.
This place is the proof!
Nah. That's not the only thing.
Gotta give credit
where it's due.
I think those girls and their
games more than earned it.
See, VP? I was right
about this café concept!
[MIDORI] Look. That customer
over there seems bored.
Talk to him.
Huh? Why me, though?
[YUTO]
Excuse us!
[BOTH gasp]
Any chance we could get
a game going over here?
But, President, we can't.
Ease up a little there, VP.
It's part of the job.
The president...
And the vice prez, too. Miki!
Be a doll and take care of them!
[gasping]
[MIKI]
Oh. Hi, Yoshioka.
I was just wondering
if you might
wanna play this game with us?
Oh, um. No harm in trying.
Could you show me how?
[MIKI] Okay. I'll go ahead and
explain the rules for everyone.
Today, we'll be playing a French
card game called Dobble.
Now, take a moment and
examine both of the cards.
Between these two cards,
there's only one shared symbol.
Can you pick it out?
[GROUP]
Hmm...
The clover.
[MIKI] That's correct.
What about these two?
Oh, they both have
a purple cat!
Yes! I think you've got it.
There are 55 cards in Dobble,
and anytime you take a card
and pair it with another,
they'll always share just one
matching symbol, no matter what.
What? I don't even see
how that's possible.
Me neither.
[KIMURA]
Whoa! She's right!
[YUTO]
That's kind of awesome!
To win, find the matching
symbol first.
Having a keen eye for
detail will help you out.
While there are five different
games we could play
using the Dobble cards
that are all equally fun,
I will be teaching
you how to play
the one known as "Hot
Potato" this time around.
First, play your card
facedown like this.
When I say "go," everyone
flips their cards face‐up.
If you find a symbol
on your card
that matches a symbol on an
opponent's card, shout "Cat!",
or whatever it is you
happened to match,
and put your card on top
of that player's hand.
This is called forcing
your cards on someone.
If you're the last remaining
person with cards in your hand,
you lose the game.
A speed game sounds
exciting to me!
I'm ready to play!
When do we start?
[MIKI] Oh! As soon as I
deal the cards out.
[RYUJI]
Uh...
People have fun with this?
[MIKI] On my mark, flip your
cards over. Ready, go!
‐‐Raindrop!
‐‐[YUTO] Key!
‐‐[TANAKA] Stop sign!
‐‐[REN] Bomb!
Next round. And... go!
The Bomb!
‐‐[REN] Chess piece!
‐‐[YUTO] Chess piece!
[KIMURA]
Target!
Impressive!
It's almost like your reflexes
were built for this game.
I practice kendo.
That might be why.
Let's start the next round.
Ready? And go!
‐‐[RYUJI] Raindro‐‐
‐‐[REN] Tear!
‐‐[YUTO] Sunglasses!
‐‐[TANAKA] Anchor!
[KIMURA]
Light bulb!
Wait! That can't be right!
Huh?
She called it a tear,
but it's a raindrop.
Oh, it's okay. You can make
up any name you want.
The other player
just has to get it.
That's what's most important.
What? Oh, okay. That's fair.
[RYUJI] Is it, though?
That's such a confusing rule.
Especially with such
weird things to name.
Right. Moving on.
Ready, go!
[RYUJI]
Found one!
‐‐But what is it?
‐‐[REN] Cheese!
I have no idea!
The other player
just has to get it.
That's what's most important.
[RYUJI]
Got it! Smiley urchin!
Smiley urchin?
Hold up.
[laughing]
Ah‐ha! I see it.
I wanna see a smiley urchin.
Pfft. Now I have!
Oh, wow. Too funny!
Uh. Huh?
[MIKI] Don't worry.
You played the right way.
That's why it's fun!
That was the best
festival ever!
[STUDENT E]
Yeah! No kidding!
[YUTO] I think it's safe to say
today was a huge success!
Yeah, if it didn't suck so much.
How is it you always know what
the right thing to do is?
C'mon, VP. Now's not the time
to be down on yourself.
If you did something
wrong, learn from it.
Don't let it take away from
all the things you do right.
You made a lot of
people smile today.
Nothing wrong with that.
[REN]
There you go again.
I mean, now you're just
stating the obvious!
[YUTO chuckles] There's the
Ren Shibusawa I know!
[exhales]
[GAMER A]
That was so fun!
[GAMER AA]
Let's play again sometime!
[MIDORI]
Thanks for coming!
[MIDORI sighs]
[ALL]
All done!
I'm taking a nap, 'kay?
Good idea!
[MIKI] The festival may
have been a lot of work,
but the fun and laughter we
shared playing board games
all day more than
made up for it.
With the addition
of a new friend,
my world grew a
little bit bigger.
And a little bit
goes a long way.
[EMILIA]
I very much want to find out
what games Japanese
children like to play!
But what in the world do you
do to end a game like that?