Dear Mom and Dad,
I hope this finds you well.
I'm here at Yokai Academy.
It's just like any
normal human school.
We still have stupid exams.
But for some reason, they
happen earlier here,
so I wasn't exactly prepared...
Check it out, guys,
I came in 201st!
I'm 222nd, alright all dueces!
Ah man, I'm so jealous
I can't stand it!
W-Well, I suppose
it could've been worse.
But compared to her...
She's so much smarter,
it's ridiculous! Whee!
Moka sure is something!
Not only is she smart
she's the hottest girl
I've ever seen in my life!
Yeah, she's got
brains and beauty, huh?
Tsukune!
Wow, Moka, you're so smart!
Ah, it was just a fluke.
Hey, maybe next time,
if you want we could um...
We could what?
You and I could study
together, if you'd like to.
Thanks Moka,
that sounds really great.
Oh, Moka.
Oh, Tsukune.
Moka.
♪ opening song ♪
Wow.
She's amazing.
Congratulations
are in order, Yukari.
It's the guys from my class!
As expected, you're
the undisputed
number one student this year.
I guess somebody knew what
they were doing when
they let you skip all
those grades, huh?
But you hear this.
Don't press your luck or
you're gonna pay the price!
Press my luck?
Huh?
Yeah, that's right!
For example, that stupid
witch costume of yours!
Hmmm...
It's against school rules.
You'd better take it off.
Yeah, but this is my--
As your class president,
the fact that you're even here
is enough to give me a headache,
so spare me the sob story.
It serves you right,
you stupid jerks!
Why, you little brat!
Don't you know who I am?
I'll teach you,
you prepubescent piss-ant!
Hey, stop it!
Who the hell are you?
Back off!
You shouldn't go
around hitting girls.
Moka?
Huh?
What the--?
They're from class 2.
What the hell's going
on over there?
Whaddaya say we leave it
at this for the time being?
C'mon guys, let's go!
Disgusting witch!
I swear, just being in the same
class as one of your filthy
kind is enough to make me wanna
puke all over the place!
Thank you so much, Moka!
You really saved
my neck back there!
I should introduce myself.
I'm Yukari Sendo.
Yeah, I've heard of you.
You're in the same
grade as we are,
but you're four years
younger, right?
Four years younger, huh?
So wait, did you skip a few
grades or something?
Whoa!
I guess that means you're
like super smart, aren't you?
And your outfit rocks!
Well...
...that's very nice
of you to say,
but I'm not the impressive one.
You're by far the most beautiful
girl I've ever seen, Moka.
And you're kind hearted,
and smart, and cool...
--Huh?
You see...
I, uh...
You should know...
I love you more
than life itself, Moka!
Every time I pass
you in the hall,
I fall more and more
in love with you.
And since you saved
me from those jerks,
I've decided that
you're the one!
Huh?!
What are you saying?
What do you mean the one?!
Well, duh!
I want you to be my girlfriend!
Your what?!
Uh... I think...
Well, I...
I can be a girl and a friend ...
Yippee!
Oh, I'm so excited about this!
Yeah, no kidding; I can tell!
Uh, listen...
Yukari, could you--?
Has anyone ever told
you that your boobs
are even bigger than they look?
Look at her grabbin' and
squeezin' Moka's fun bags!
It's just not fair!
I'm flat as a pancake
myself, so getting to
squeeze ones like yours
is a dream come true!
Uh, Yukari,
could you please let go?
I'm starting to
feel a little weak.
Noooo!
Stop it!
What are you doing,
you're both girls!
I knew you'd show
up at some point.
Tsukune Aono.
Your grades are simply average.
Your athletic ability
is well below par.
You have no
useful skills at all.
I couldn't imagine a
more half-baked guy.
[echo] Half-baked guy...
half-baked guy...
Now you listen and
you listen real good!
I don't want my darling
Moka sullied by
the likes of a creep like you.
[echo] Creep like you...
Creep like you...
So... I'm declaring
war on you!
Magic wand, brooms
and buckets...
Abracadabra!
Tsukune!
These cleaning supplies
are possessed!
It's magic you simpleton!
Magic?
Yep!
You see, I'm a witch,
it's sort of my thing!
And if any dirty boy tries
to get close to my Moka,
well then, they're gonna
have to answer to me
and my magic wand here.
Did you guys hear that?
This girl is way out of control;
revealing your monster
identity is definitely
against school rules!
Well... Looks like
you pushed your luck
a little too far this time.
Yukari Sendo?
Yeow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
I swear, I really don't
know what to do.
Hey! What's
the big idea, huh?
Here we are in the very
next episode right after
my big debut, and
you guys can't get
around to me any
sooner than this?
Who exactly is she talking to?
Whee!
I'm so sorry about that.
It sounds like you had a really
rough experience, Tsukune.
Oh, you have no idea.
She won't even
let me talk to Moka.
I mean, just look
at the state I'm in!
Yahoo!
That means it's
just the two of us now!
Way to go, Yukari!
As far as that girl's concerned,
I've heard some things.
Really?
What did you--
Supposedly,
she's some sort of genius.
But apparently
she's childish and bratty.
And everybody in
her class hates her guts.
R-R-Really?
She's probably really full of
herself because she's so smart.
You know how
those brainiacs are.
Tsukune, my most
despised and hated rival,
I'm gonna beat you so bad
you'll never walk again!
This is my voodoo doll!
And it's got your
name all over it!
Just tuck this strand
of Tsukune's hair inside...
And pow!
Whoa!
Are you alright?
Pow! Pow!
A guy like you doesn't
deserve a pair
of perfect breasts like Moka's.
Might as well give it
up and get grabby
with Miss Tittie-Pie
there instead!
Whew!
Man, I didn't think I was
ever gonna lose her.
No, it's not what you think,
I can't control myself!
Hey, what do you two
think you're doing?!
You did it again!
You used your love charm
attack on him, didn't you?
Wait... You know
I wouldn't do that!
Then what's going on?!
And yank!
Uh, Tsukune?
I... I didn't mean
to, really!
It worked!
I did it!
It's Yukari!
Busted, whee!
Look, I can't take this anymore!
You guys have got
to do something here!
Well she's not really
bothering me that much.
Relax, she's just a little kid,
it's not that big of a deal.
Oh, come on, that's no excuse!
She needs to understand
she can't go
around messing with
people like that.
I think it's about time
she learned her lesson!
I suppose you're right, but--
Yukari, look!
If you keep this crap up,
nobody's gonna like you, okay?
And before long you'll end up
alone with no friends!
Who cares?
I'm a genius, alright?
As far as I'm concerned, if
people aren't at my level,
then why the heck
should I waste my
time being friends
with them anyway?
Plus...
What's the big deal?
I've been alone
from the very beginning.
Oh Yukari that's...
Oh man, you totally
fell for that one!
You little brat...!
Hey calm down, you
can't go around losing
your temper with a little
kid like that, okay?!
And what about you?
You need to stop hanging
around with that brat!
Yeah, but Tsukune...
You know I heard
that girl is a witch...
What a pathetic loser.
How'd we get stuck with a
girl like that in our class?
And all that stupid cutesy talk?
I mean, come on, who the
hell does she think she is?
Yeah well it's not
like she can help it,
she is a witch after all.
A snot-nosed kid like her is
nothing more than a nuisance.
Besides, witches are
closer to humans
than they are to
monsters anyway.
There's no reason for her to
even be at this school.
I know, right?
The only reason she
makes good grades
is because she uses magic.
Who needs friends?
I don't care.
Ow! That hurt,
you moron!
Why don't you watch
where you're walking, you jerk?
Well I suppose compared
to you almost anyone
could be considered a
moron, couldn't they?
The class president?
Well, if it isn't little
Miss Rule-Breaker.
You've gone and made
our president angry.
Well, that doesn't have
anything to do with you guys,
so leave me alone!
Oh, but it does.
You see...
Whenever a student
does something to
disrupt class discipline,
it's our responsibility
to teach them a lesson.
My point is you're way too
lenient when it comes to Yukari!
But still, when you stop and
think about how she must feel...
If that's the way you look at
it, think about my feelings,
'cause I'm the one getting
pummeled to death over here!
Don't you get it?
Look. You of all people know
what it's like to be different.
I know you do, Tsukune.
No, that's not the same thing!
Don't you understand?
I won't abandon her!
She did say she didn't
care if she was well liked.
I mean, let's be honest,
that is so like a witch!
Uh wait, what do
you mean by that?
You mean you don't know?
Look, witches are halfway
between monsters and humans,
but they're not
really either one.
A long time ago,
people used to say
witches were the link
between monsters
and human beings.
Nowadays, they just
think they're
nothing but half-monsters.
Half-monsters?
They aren't exactly accepted
by the humans, either.
Back in the day,
things were pretty bad.
They had "witch trials"
and "witch hunts."
They've always been
a hated people.
She doesn't feel
accepted by anyone.
She's probably always
felt like she's alone,
from the very beginning.
That's just like me.
Oh come on, you're not alone;
you've always got me, right?
Hey, wait!
Hey, what's your problem?
That hurts!
"It hurts," "It hurts," why
don't you go cry about it?!
Your voice is disgusting!
Yep...
"Disgusting" is exactly right.
It makes me sick!
Quick monster fact: These guys
are lizardmen--a subhuman,
yet highly intelligent
species that
look just like lizards, whee!
You're nothing but a
disgusting snot-nosed,
shrimp-ass punk bitch!
A thing like you
doesn't belong here!
I wish we didn't
have her in our class.
What's her deal?
The dirty witch.
Actin' like she's all hot shit,
just cause she's good
at school and stuff.
Why do they even let
stupid little brats
like her come to school here?
I know, right?
It's like, you're a
total pain in the ass,
why don't you just leave?
Hey!
What happened?!
I'm so embarrassed!
Well, that oughta teach you!
It was that bitch!
That was mean this is
why everyone hates you,
you dirty witch!
I don't even wanna be liked by
stupid girls like you, so there!
What's wrong,
cat got your tongue?
Magic wand, attack!
Magic wand, attack...
Oh shut your damn mouth!
Oh no, he ate my magic wand.
Blech!
Gross, I've never
tasted something
so terrible in my life!
So, what should we
do with this one, eh?
I say we eat her.
There's plenty of fog, there's
no way anyone would see us.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
She's a prepubescent
little runt.
But at least she'll
take the taste
of that wand out of my mouth.
Oh, no!
Please help me!
Get away from her right now!
Oh, Moka, it's you!
Well, well, look who it is.
I just had a great idea, boss,
how 'bout we eat both of them?
I second that motion.
I gotta admit, this one
looks pretty damn tasty,
all plump and juicy,
and most of all--
She's got those!
And this!
And that!
I'm fine, just get out of here!
As far as monsters go,
these guys are a joke!
Trust me, I can
handle them myself!
You've gotta stop
doing that, Yukari!
Don't act so tough.
If you're scared there's
nothing wrong with
asking others for some help.
You really should try being
more honest with yourself.
But I--
There's no reason to push
yourself so hard, Yukari.
Why bite off more
than you can chew?
You're still a
little girl, you know?
I'm not pushing myself too hard.
The truth is, you've been
alone your whole life, right?
If you feel lonely, and if you
don't like being all alone,
why don't you say so?
I was the same.
All alone, all by myself.
You too, Moka?
That's why I'll never
give up on you.
It's why I wanna help you
and be there for you,
Yukari, no matter what.
Thank you, Moka.
Hey!
What gives?
Did they forget about
us or something?
Yeah, what are we?
Chopped liver?!
We won't stand for it.
You understand me, fellas?
We're not gonna put up
with this crap, are we?
I say it's hightime
we chow down on some
of that yummy-looking
rump roast!
No!
Wha--?!
What the hell do you
think you're doing,
you miserable little brat?!
Wait, I don't get it,
why are you here?
I'm sorry about before.
I get how you feel; I know what
it's like to be all alone, too.
No, you liar, you
don't know anything!
So come on, please let me do
what I can to help you, okay?
All right, that's enough!
This is getting ridiculous!
For the last few minutes,
it's been nothing
but a bunch of sappy melodrama!
It's time we step in and
take care of these wimps!
Mister Class President,
you do the other girl!
No, Yukari!
Tsukune look out!
Tsukune are you okay??
Kurumu!
You guys are heavy.
Thanks for helping
us out back there.
I did it for you, you know?
Give me a break
another do-gooder?
This is getting annoying.
Whaddya say we round em' up
and eat every last one of them?!
You want some, bring it on!
Tsukune...
...you're--
Ooo yeah, Tsukune,
will you be my protector
too, pretty please?!
Tsukune, no!
It's time boys attack!
Let's eat!
Dinner is served!
It's blinding!
What's happening?
That giant blast of light!
What is it?!
When the rosary seal over
her breast is removed,
Moka's innocent self vanishes
and her inner vampire awakens!
Get back you filthy trash!
This...
...is this...?
Moka's vampire form?
Look... her hair!
Don't you know
that getting your
hair dyed is against
school rules?!
That skirt is way
too short, too!
That's a clear violation!
The legendary S-class monster...
...a vampire!
She knocked them
out that easily?
I can't see her, what the
hell just happened?!
You're not worth my time; the
only way you pathetic losers
can wield any power is by
ganging up on the weak.
Having such strength is
against our school's rules!
Know your place!
Okay, you win,
I'll stop, I promise.
This episode's fight was over
in a mere fifty seven
seconds, whee!
That was amazing.
I guess we can
always count on Moka.
But why?
What do you mean?
I was so bad and I did
mean things to everybody.
I don't get it, why did you
guys come and save me?
Did you hear anything
we said, Yukari?
We came to your rescue
because we all want
to be there for you,
no matter what.
You don't have to
be alone anymore.
From now on,
we'll be right by your side.
And just like that,
a few days passed by, whee!
About Yukari, I heard
she completely
cleaned up her act after that.
She got up in front of the
whole class and apologized
for the mean tricks she pulled.
Everyone started to
feel guilty for all
the things they said about her.
Little by little, they
started to open up to her.
That's really great!
Oh, my Tsukune!
I just love you to death!
Yukari, what's up?
Hey guys!
Our classes are right
next to each other,
I should come over
and play sometime.
Come over and play?
Yeah, it'll be fun!
Because I already love
you, Moka, and now
I've fallen madly in
love with Tsukune, too!
Isn't that great?!
Eh?
When I got pushed down
by Tsukune that time,
for some reason, it made me feel
like I wasn't a kid anymore!
What I mean is, I want him
to push me down over
and over again!
You know, I really don't
think that's a good idea.
Oh no you don't... Tsukune is
mine and don't you forget it!
Hey, you let go
of him, he's mine!
Both of you are just
wasting your breath.
Tsukune belongs to me!
Oh, no, don't bite me!
Cut it out!
Ah, come on Moka,
you're gonna suck me dry!
♪ closing song ♪
Welcome to Yukari's
magical classroom!
And now I'm going to pull a
pigeon out of this metal bowl!
Yukari, stop!
This is no time
for fun and games!
Get serious for a second!
It's about Tsukune!
Next time: "Farewell
and a Vampire" and another...