Whoa!
Who the hell is that?!
The hot math teacher,
Ririko Kagome!
You've never seen her?!
She was in the last
episode, dude!
Hold it pal, that kind of
commentary is my job, whee!
I wanna learn math under her!
Yeah, so do I!
Oh, no...! Pi r squared!
♪ opening song ♪
Right...
...now let's take our formula
for the area of a circle,
and use it to derive
the surface area
for this cone on
the board, 'okay?
'Kay!
I don't get it!
I don't understand how to
do this kind of math at all!
Why don't we get
an answer from...
Mr. Aono?
Yes, ma'am?!
Tell us how to do it...
Solve this problem.
Um...
I don't know how.
What an idiot!
Tsukune...
Bad boy, Tsukune;
you're supposed
to listen to your teacher...
Zone out again...
and I'll give you a spanking.
We're getting close
to finals, you know...
...and you need
to focus on those.
Oh, no!
Crap, I forgot all about finals!
And at the rate I'm
going in this class,
I'm gonna get an
F and flunk out!
Tsukune...
What?! You want me to
tutor you in math?!
Exactly!
It's taken all my energy just
to get used to this school.
And on top of that, with
all these crazy mix-ups
I keep getting dragged into,
I've been way too
distracted to study.
Please help me, Moka!
I'm begging you here!
Okay, Tsukune...
I just hope that I can
be enough help.
Really?!
Yeah...
...and since we're
gonna do this...
Um...
Will you come
to my room tonight?
'Cause we need
a place to study...
And if we do it in my room,
I can help you with your
math and anything else you
might need help grasping.
What the?!
"Anything else?!"
If I go into Moka's room
after hearing her say that,
I won't get any studying done!
I'll have a nervous
breakdown instead!
Tsukune, I'll do everything
I can to help you!
You will...? Thank you...
You can always count
on me, Tsukune...
Because...
Oh, Moka...
I always count on you to
let me suck your blood...!
Not again!
Now wait just a minute!
I've got something to say...!
Sine, cosine, tangent...
I learned all that
in Math class...!
So I'm the one you
should be studying with!
No, don't listen to her!
If you need a math study buddy,
I know everything, Tsukune...!
Things like the cylindrical
shell method...!
And stuff such as
PV equals N R T...!
The final's comin' up soon
and you need help in math,
so come on, what do you say?!
Speaking of help...
I'm in the same boat 'cause
I've missed a lot of school,
so is it okay if I study
with you guys, too?
Um, yeah, sure!
Uh well I really
appreciate the offers but
Moka and I have already
decided to study together.
Although all of us studying
together is a great idea!
Huh?!
Well, shall we get out of here
and start hitting the books?
Yeah...! You betcha!
And this is a derivative,
a measure of how
a function changes as
its input changes.
It allows us to compute a line
or plane tangent to that
function at that point.
In contrast, an integral,
geometrically
speaking, looks...
Well?
Do you get it now?
Yeah...! Thanks
to you, I do...!
You're a first-class tutor.
Please, I am not!
Well, it's great that
you understand it now,
but I still don't...!
Would you please be my special
private math tutor, Tsukune?!
So...
...all of these derivatives
and integrals...
...how exactly are
they any different
from addition and subtraction?
Incredible...
Huh?
Wow, you must take
the most thorough
notes in the world, Moka.
They're easy to follow,
your handwriting's great;
everything's organized
by topic, too.
Stop, you're embarrassing me...
If you'd like, I'd be
more than happy to copy
a set by hand for you.
Thanks...
...that's so incredibly
kind of you, Moka...
But making a photocopy
would be easier...
...wait, I forgot this
school probably doesn't
have anything useful like that.
Oh I don't mind; you're my
friend...! Anything for you!
Moka...
Oh, Tsukune...
Oh, Moka...
Tsukune...
Oh, brother, not all this
garbage again, whee!
Attention, the main
school building
will be closing in
ten minutes...
Ya know it's been a
really long time since
I've studied for a
test this hard...
I'm beat.
It was worth it if you
learned something, though.
Oh, Mr. Aono...
Miss Ririko...
Why are you here
so late; a club?
Uh...
...no, Moka and I were just
finishing up a study session.
A study session?
Well that's not good
I'm sorry to hear it...
Huh?!
Well, it is good you're putting
in some effort, but when
students get together to study,
they spend more time goofing off
than learning the material.
But we didn't!
We really studied!
Tsukune was actually beginning
to understand some--
I doubt it...
You're just a student, Miss
Akashiya; you're not a teacher.
Though you may be
good at schoolwork...
Teaching students
is a task that is
best left to
professional educators.
Huh?
Tsukune!
And that's why...
...tomorrow after class...
...you'll meet me
in the tutoring room.
You'll never forget the
lessons I'll teach you...
I'm looking forward to them...
I...
...can't...
...wait.
I bet you can't...!
It's the next day, and
it's tutoring time, whee!
Well...
I guess I'd better
get going, guys.
To get tutored by Miss Ririko,
huh...? I did talk to some
older students who took
Math from her before...
They said she's so
crazy about teaching
that she goes
overboard with it.
Yeah...? Anything else?
Well there are two
more problems...
...they just make me so angry...
...the boys won't stop
staring at her tits!
Um, really?
Aw, are you jealous that
your own huge honkers
aren't as massive as hers...?
You're acting like
a child, Kurumu.
Well actually, Yukari...
The only child
that's here is you...
And the proof is your
flat-as-a-pancake chest...!
I'd rather have mine than
your big, fat balloons!
Mine are big, but what
makes them really
nice is how squeezable
they are, unlike yours.
You're so superficial.
Guys prefer mine 'cause they
offer quality over quantity
and they're all wrapped up
in a cute, tiny package.
Yeah, they're still
flat as a board.
You shut up, Miss Milk Jugs!
What did you say, Little
Miss Flatty Flat Chest?!
Big ones start
sagging, you know!
Come on... why don't you
two just knock it off already?!
Hey, Tsukune...
I know you're not
really looking forward
to these tutoring sessions...
...but it's still better than
having to take make-up classes.
Moka's right.
If you get a 50 or less on your
final exam, then you flunk
the subject and you have to
take intensive make-up classes
before they'll let you
out for summer break.
Wait!
Tsukune?
Oh, man... I'd almost
forgotten about that...
Huh?
Yeah...! It's summer break
once finals are done!
I'm gonna do it, Moka...!
I'm gonna work hard
and pass Math...!
Then we can do
something together
for summer break, okay?!
Alright...
No... Go to the beach
with me instead and
we can play with
some beach balls!
Nuh-uh...! He's gonna
have a deliciously
sweet summer romance with
me, right, Tsukune?
No, have a snowcone with me...
As we watch the sunrise...
Hello?
Is anyone there?
I'm Tsukune Aono from Class
1-3 and was told to report here.
I've been expecting you...
Tsukune.
Holy crap!
Um, I mean, what are you
doing dressed up in
an outfit like
that, Ms. Ririko?!
I just thought it
might help you get up...
...the motivation
to study harder.
Are you nuts...?! The only
thing it'll motivate me
to do is to have
crazy fantasies!
This is just too weird...!
You're my teacher and
I'm your student!
"Weird?"...
I don't find
this weird at all...
But your right ,
I am your teacher...
And when it comes to an
education, the teacher is
the master who must
be respected...
...while the student
is the submissive
who must obediantly obey.
Um, hold on, Ms. Ririko,
you're kind of scaring me...
I can smell that,
and you give off an
incredibly luscious scent...
It's almost like
that of a human's.
No...
I mean...
It must just be
your imagination!
Even so, you're the first
student I've taught
who's given off such a
delightful scent...
It makes teaching you all
the more yummy for me.
Let's get started, shall we?
I should warn you that my
private sessions are
very intensive.
Tsukune...
I hope that tutoring
session is helping you...
You're just a student, Miss
Akashiya; you're not a teacher.
Still...
As far as what I can
personally do to help you out...
I guess this is about it.
What a tough game today!
Are you guys ready
for final exams yet?
All of them except math...
I'm not, either,
so please be my tutor!
I'm gona have to refuse...
You can't take
me hostage...! No!
Tutor me in math
and I'll let you go!
I've just gotta pass that final!
Oh...! Tsukune.
If we say that alpha
equals the cosine of
one hundred twenty degrees
plus twenty degrees,
then alpha squared plus alpha
plus one takes on the following
value: alpha minus one...
Wait, I've heard of that!
He's reciting mathematic
formulas from memory!
Huh?!
They're advanced ones that
we haven't even
covered in class yet!
Awesome!
So that tutoring's
really paying off, huh?
Teach me...! You've got
to so that I can pass!
For an arithmetic sequence with
a first term of six and a
Oh, good morning, Tsukune!
Um... Listen...
I know what Miss Ririko said
about me not being a teacher...
...but still...
I really wanted to
do something to
help you understand
math better...
Okay...? So I
copied all my notes
and compiled them in
this notebook for you...
I know they're not much,
but maybe they'd...
...be helpful.
Tsukune?
What are you doing?!
Ohh... Well...
I see you're trying to
undermine me, aren't you...?
And trying to seduce
Mr. Aono with this drivel...
How dare you?!
I was just helping
him study--!
You've got some nerve...!
It's obvious to me that
Mr. Aono hasn't been able to
focus on his studies
because of you.
Come on Tsukune
let's go study...
Tsukune...
Is that true...? Tsukune can't
study because of me...?
Is it really all my fault?
♪ montage song ♪
Given f of x equals x cubed,
plus x squared minus
My private sessions
with you have
really made a difference,
haven't they?
Little by little, you've
started to see how
wonderful it is to study.
Where's Moka?
Still having impure
thoughts, huh...?!
Get on your hands and
knees right now!
I love your scent!
it gets me so worked up
and puts me in the mood
for a night of
red-hot educating!
Go on, study for me, baby!
Do it harder;
do it like you mean it!
Oh, that's it!
Don't stop, Tsukune!
You do it so good that I'm
gonna give you another
one of my special sessions...
...so...
...here...
...we...
...go.
I'll pump you full
of learning again...
Yes...
I...
...will!
Tsukune!
Yes, that's it, right there...!
It feels so good,
Keep it up for me, please!
You want some more, don't you?!
It's okay; go on, suck in
as much as you want!
This is how I make it so you
don't think about anything
except for what you've
learned studying with me.
Estimate the...
...probability distribution
based on a parametric model!
Oh, yeah...! Keep talking
mathly to me, baby!
Let him go!
Miss Ririko, what are you
doing to poor Tsukune?!
Miss Akashiya...
your such a little pest...
If you must know, we're in the
middle of a learning session...
And you won't get
in my way again!
Known from the annals of Greek
mythology, this terrifying
monster has the torso of a human
and the tail of a snake...!
And it's Ms. Ririko's
monster form...
A lamia, whee!
My whole reason for being in
life is educating students...!
And if you think I'm gonna
let you come between me
and one of them, you've
got another thing coming!
Now... Tsukune...
...let's get back to
our studying, shall we?
You know you can trust me.
Everything that we do
here is for your own good.
No, don't...!
You have to resist her!
See how strong the
bond between teacher
and student is,
Miss Akashiya...
Ooh, isn't it wonderful the
things that education can do?
What's going on here?
Mizore!
What are you doing here?!
Since it looks like you've
gotten all hot and bothered...
I thought I should come
here and cool you off.
Go on, get Tsukune out of here.
Truant slacker!
I'm going to teach you a lesson
that you'll never forget!
Take this!
Mizore!
How dare you attack me,
you bad influence of a bitch!
I'm a teacher, so I
deserve to be treated
with the utmost respect...!
But what would an undermining
tramp know about that...?!
Nothing, that's what...!
Therefore I'm gonna have to
teach you some respect!
This handwriting...
It's one of Moka's notes...
I'd be more than happy to
copy a set by hand for you.
I don't mind; you're my
friend...! Anything for you!
Now suck on some
educational guidance!
You saved me...
It's the least I could do...
...after all you've done.
Oh, Tsukune...
Tsukune, no, what
are you doing...?!
You made a copy of your
notes for me, didn't you?
And you did it by hand...
That was so kind of you, and
look, I've got 'em right here.
Tsukune...
Then both of you get
educational guidance!
When the rosary seal over
her breast is removed...
...Moka's innocent
self vanishes...
...and her inner
vampire awakens!
You call what you do
"educational guidance?"
Don't make me laugh.
What...?! How dare you?!
I'm a teacher!
No, you're just a
poor excuse for one.
What did you say?!
All you are is a
small-minded narcissist...
You always hammer the importance
of learning into others,
so allow me to return the favor
and teach you your place.
Well, did you learn anything?
Yes, ma'am, and I appreciate the
guidance that you've given me.
This episode's big
showdown only took
a mere thirty-one
seconds, whee!
What can I say...? I just don't
seem to know how to hold back.
On the day of the math final,
Tsukune's stressing
out again, whee!
Crap!
I'm toast!
All the knowledge Ms. Ririko
pumped in me is
completely gone now!
Good luck, Tsukune...
Well, how do you think
you did on the final?
I dunno.
I did try my best, but still...
Oh, well, regardless
of what grade I get,
I've got no regrets.
Why?
Well, 'cause the best
thing about it is that
I got to study with you, Moka,
even if it was only
for a few days...
You never once gave up on me...
You kept tutoring me
right to the end,
and those notes you gave
me were a huge help, too.
I'm really lucky to have
someone like you in my life.
I don't know what I'd do without
you; you're the absolute best.
I really mean that,
Moka, and thanks again.
Hey, is something wrong?
Tsukune!
But I still have
another final today!
And finally, our
summer break began...
Well, at least
for most of us...
Ahh, crap, now I have to
take make-up classes!
And after all that
tutoring I gave you...
Yay, it's finally summer break!
Look at my bikini, Tsukune!
Look at mine, too!
Check mine out as well...
Next time...
"Summer Break and a Vampire"...
and another...