Rubi.
There's no reason to cry.
You're not alone anymore.
I'm going to be right here...
...forever.
♪ opening song ♪
Go away pain, go away pain,
fly away right away!
Come on, you really
think that's gonna work?
Yes, we witches
are experts at healing!
But when people say that,
don't they mean adult witches?
Why, you...!
Okay, okay, enough, you two!
I think I'm gonna be alright.
There's nothing to
worry about, I'm fine!
Just calm down,
don't push yourself!
--No, really, I'm okay.
--Shh! Quiet!
Oh, Your Ladyship!
Hey, Rubi. You up?
Where am I?
Thirsty?
We've got you some
tea if you want.
Oh, and don't worry,
everyone else already has one.
If you think you can
buy me off with tea,
you've got another
thing coming.
That's not what we're doing!
We just wanna hear your story.
You do?
Yeah.
Tell us about that hill.
Okay.
That hill's a place
where witches
have lived for a
very long time.
And we lived there in peace
together, never bothering
or hurting anybody, just
minding our own business.
Well at least until they
came barging in on us.
They destroyed
everything in sight.
They ripped the
place to shreds,
treating our home
like it was nothing!
Explain this to me!
The human scum!
Why should we trust them?
What possible good
could that do us now?!
We will never trust
the humans ever again!
Rubi.
Please, Yukari.
You of all people should
understand what I'm saying.
We witches called
this place home.
In order to keep
that place safe,
our only option is to destroy
every last one of them!
But I...
I don't feel that way...
But...
We've no choice.
We have to kill them!
Come on.
Do you really think
it's okay to kill off
everyone just to
protect a hill?
The only ones I kill are humans!
Whether you're
human or a monster.
There's no difference in
the value of someone's life.
What's so wrong
about killing humans?
So what if I kill them off?!
Who cares about stupid humans?
Isn't there something else?
Some other way to go about it?
A peaceful solution?
No way.
There's no other
alternative for us.
Her Ladyship will
bring retribution.
Wait!
"Her Ladyship?"
Come on, you can't be serious.
That's pretty arrogant of you...
Saying that it's fine
to hurt other people
as long as it serves
your own purpose!
No kidding.
That's very selfish.
That makes you
no different than them.
I think that it's--
So?
That's the "witch way," huh?
You witches are a scary lot.
Hey, no, we're not!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
sure you little "kiddie
witches" aren't... whatever!
There you go again!
All of you shut up!
If they take that
hill away from me,
I'll be left without
anywhere else to go!
Wait a second!
If that's what this
whole thing is about,
you should come with us.
He's right.
It could get lonely being
uprooted from the place
you've always known,
but Yokai Academy
has a lot to offer
a girl like you.
So, whaddaya say?
Oh, wait!
Let's get her to join
the Newspaper Club, too!
Good call Moka!
Eh?! So now we'll
have two witches?
That's right!
We will!
Come on, knock it off, you guys!
Do you want me to
cool their heads off?
No, no!
No, don't, you'll end up
freezing everyone solid!
♪ montage song ♪
There's no way.
It's just too late,
I can never change.
Y-Your Ladyship, I just...
N-No, forgive me,
Your Ladyship, please!
I'm yours... I promise you!
I would never
turn my back on you!
Guys, where did Rubi go?
Rubi.
Yukari!
What the...?
Rubi!
Go back...
No one's allowed on this hill!
No matter who you are...
...leave or perish!
Stop it!
Rubi, there's gotta
be another way here!
Please, listen to her!
If we work together,
we'll figure it out!
I've heard enough!
Oh, holy crap!
It turns out a whole
bunch of plant monsters
were being cultivated under
this sunflower field, whee!
What you see before you
are Her Ladyship's brood,
a loyal army of plant soldiers
bred to defend Witch Hill!
Go get outta here, Tsukune!
Good job, Mizore.
Stay back,
it's way too dangerous!
But, Yukari, I...!
Stop it.
You're just a kiddie witch,
so who do you think
you're impressing?!
Kurumu, you...!
If they hurt you, then
they'll have to answer to me!
But, Mizore, I...!
I can fight too...!
Don't worry, we'll protect you!
They won't touch you, Tsukune!
No, they won't!
Moka, no!
Tsukune!
Moka, nooooooo!
Tsukuneeee!
Tsukune, no!
Now I'll turn them
into a blood offering!
Rubi, please,
stop this insanity!
Get those things
off her right now!
Dammit.
I know I'm up against
monsters, but still!
Here I am all tied up, with
Moka's cries for help ringing
in my ears, and I can't
do a thing about it!
Please, Moka.
Tell me what to do.
Anything I could do to help...
Something even a
human like me can do!
That's it!
What the...?
Is that a...?
A Vampire?
Moka...
She looks mad...
You fool...
Doing too much, like always...
Still...
You saved my ass.
Hey, look out!
I'll take blood over peace.
And this episode's showdown
was over in a mere--whee?
Rubi!
Rubi, please stop all of this!
No, I can't!
I'm gonna defend Witch Hill
because it's my wish.
Also, because
Her Ladyship demands it!
Huh?
Oh, no, they're even
bigger than before!
Tsukune!
I'm begging you.
Please, just let Tsukune go.
Don't do this!
Her Ladyship wants it,
so it must be done!
I must do everything
Her Ladyship desires.
My only purpose here is
to execute her every request!
Who is "Her Ladyship?"
Tell me...
A house?
Damn you little bitch!
Moka, hold on a sec!
Wait!
Listen up, guys.
Take care of Tsukune!
Tsukune!
The house.
Right!
Tsukune!
Hold on!
Where are you going?
To find "Her Ladyship!"
Yeah, but you...
Tsukune!
Wait! Kurumu!
"Her Ladyship."
She must be there.
Tsukune, it's really dangerous!
Dumb twit!
You're the one in danger!
Kids should stay outta the way!
Just give it a rest!
Tsukune, now's your chance,
hurry and go!
Alright.
Thanks, guys.
I'll be back!
Hey.
You did a good job.
For a snot-nosed brat.
You're not too shabby yourself.
I'm amazed you can
move so well,
having to lug those two
heavy honkers around.
Good point.
You know for just
a second there
I was actually envious
of your booblets.
We'll finish this later,
my big-titted rival.
You certainly don't
have to tell me
cause right now we've got
bigger fish to fry, don't we?
Mizore!
Thank you!
What the...?
I see.
These roots are
pulling the strings
that are driving
those monsters.
And worse...
Rubi, too!
What's this?
It's you.
You're the one...
"Her Ladyship," aren't you?
If so, I have a request.
Rubi.
Let her make her own choices.
Set her free.
How much longer
do we hafta keep
pounding away at
these damn things?
Until we kill all of them.
Compared to us
and what we can do...
These goons are like nothing.
Oh, come on,
you call this nothing?
We're just staying positive.
There's still so
many of them left...
Hey, everyone, look up there!
Moka.
Moka!
Rubi, don't!
Look, we've had enough!
We'll leave this hill right now
and never come back again!
You'll never hear
from us, we promise!
So please!
Just forgive us and
let us go our way!
You might as
well save your breath.
Just take a look at her,
there's no getting through
to her in that state.
DIE!!!!
This is payback
for defiling Witch Hill!
Now lap it up!
Stop it!
Rubi, stop this.
Let them go!
Tsukune!
Tsukune, no!
Get out of here!
Rubi! Doing this
won't help anyone.
Nobody will care anymore!
Shut up!
Everything I'm doing
is for Her Ladyship!
I do this to...
Just who are you kidding?!
I went to see "Her Ladyship"
and there's no one's there!
What are you talking about?!
Her Ladyship's inside the house!
No... look!
I went inside the
house just now to see her...
...and she's dead she's
been dead this whole time!
That can't be... No.
Rubi.
Your Ladyship?
I'm afraid that I...
I may have acted very foolishly.
Don't you see?
All the things that
I set out to do
were no different
than the humans.
Your Ladyship!
Please forgive me.
I'm about to leave you
all by yourself again...
But remember, Rubi...
I will always be by your side,
no matter what happens.
Forever.
Rubi, please.
Deep down, you must
know it's true.
Don't you see?
Her Ladyship's
no longer with us...
But you don't want to admit it.
You don't want
to accept it, do you?
And all those feelings
inside you created
a false image of Her Ladyship,
and it's been haunting you
ever since, hasn't it Rubi?!
No.
No!
No!!
No!!!!
No. Rubi...
...please don't do it!
Wait, what are
you talking about?
If she uses
that forbidden spell...
There'll be no hope for her,
and she'll never return to
her normal self again!
No way.
Rubi, no!
What the hell?!
Die, all of you!
Everyone!
Time for you to die!
Do you know you just went
off the deep end, Rubi?
What are you gonna do?
Don't you understand,
it's over for you now?
No one will be able
to help you anymore.
You don't want to do this!
Trust me!
Tsukune!
My wand!
Go get my magic wand
and throw it to me!
Oh, right!
Here you go!
I got it, thanks!
You ready, Kurumu?
Yeah go for it!
Kurumu, look!
Foolish girl!
Just 'cause you're giant now,
don't think you've defeated me!
There's much more
to this magic than size!
Don't you see?
In my current state, I can
absorb the powers of other
creatures and use them
as if they were my own!
That means...
Since you're a vampire,
I have vampire powers, too!
Please, just let her go!
Don't worry, guys, we're fine.
Yukari's here, so just leave
this problem up to me!
It's time to fly, cards.
Time to fly!
Mizore, you're up!
Now's your chance, Moka!
Grab her wand!
Without our wands, witches
are completely useless;
we can't even perform magic.
It's probably too late for her
to go back to her normal self.
But do what you can, Moka.
Please.
She needs help.
Please, save Rubi
by making her stop this!
I'll do my best.
But I have to
be honest with you,
this idiot is better off dead!
Stupid bitch!
All of you...
I want all of you to die!
I'll take blood over peace!
Rubi, what's your
favorite thing in the world?
My favorite thing?
Well, let me think.
Ooh, ice cream!
That's not all.
There's more?
Oh, yeah!
I like it here on Witch Hill.
And I like Your Ladyship!
Hey, guess what?
I love you!
In the end, we just couldn't
do anything else, could we?
If only I would've been
a little bit stronger.
Tsukune, what happened
wasn't your fault.
Meow-ha!
I'm sorry I kept you
waiting so long guys.
But look here, look at all the
yummy fish I managed to get!
It's time to go back already?
Sorry I'm late, everyone!
I know that voice.
Gin, it's you!
Whoa, you guys, what's up with
the "deer in headlights" look?
Your club prez just
miraculously freed himself
from summer school hell,
so try acting excited, will you?
What the hell's with you guys?
It's Rubi!
What, you guys know
her or somethin'?
Yeah.
Hmm...
...so there's a
story behind her.
Well, I found her
floating in the ocean...
Just floating along
like something was
keeping her safe from harm.
Oh, wow...
Keeping her safe, huh?
What's this?
Aww, man.
This is the wrong road...
Well let's head back.
Can you believe this?
It's the most beautiful
hill I've ever seen.
This sunflower field is special.
It's a place that
witches on this hill
have treasured for
many generations.
Well, then I'll take
real good care of it.
I swear, I'll watch over it.
Forever and ever!
Good.
Shall we go back
to the house now?
Back to our little home?
Yeah!
♪ closing song ♪
Oh, summer
break's over, you guys!
The moving scene from
this episode's all ruined now!
I could freeze you and then
it'll be summer break forever.
Please don't do that!
Next time: "New Term and
a Vampire" and another...