I'm not gonna let
you score this time!
Here goes! I'm going
to dedicate this shot to Moka!
And it's good...!
Morisaki just missed that one!
Tsukune.
Alright!
Are you really
okay with this...?
You're sure?
Yes.
Oh, I'm so happy!
Moka.
Wow...
Thank you so much.
It's the first time
you've ever offered
to let me suck your blood.
It was delicious as always;
thank you Tsukune!
Uh... Yeah, sure,
no problem.
Moka...
I wonder if she has any
idea why I do this for her?
We'd better get a move-on
or we're gonna be late!
Guess not.
His blood...
it's so yummy!
♪ opening song ♪
Okay, everyone.
It's time for you
to join a club!
A club?
And it's good...
Morisaki just missed that one!
Tsukune.
Moka.
The primary objective of
this academy is to prepare
our monsters to adapt
to human society.
Through participation
in these clubs,
you'll learn to act just like
humans, appreciate arts
they've developed,
and deepen your
understanding of the
human culture...
Now...
...In order for your
transformation to the human form
to be perfect, you
have to have a
firm grasp of
humans themselves.
And always remember this:...
You must never reveal your
monster form, no matter what.
Um...
Excuse me?
Yes?
Your tail.
Wow...
There's a ton of different
clubs to choose from, huh?
Hey, I've got a good idea...
Let's join the same club!
Come and take pictures
of ghosts with us!
Acupuncture Club?
Mummy Club?
Make love potions with
the chemistry club!
Moka, drink this!
Mine's better!
Please, drink mine!
This is nuts,
doesn't this school
have one normal club in it?
Of course not, whee!
My name's Tamao Ichinose...
Come join me and my friends
in the swimming club, guys.
Chicks in bikinis!
And every single one
of em's a hottie!
The swimming club seems normal.
At the moment, the Swimming Club
doesn't have any boys...
That means any fellas
who join up now stand
to get a lot of personalized
service from us.
Eh?!
So whaddaya say, huh...?
Who wants to sign up?
I think we've found
a winner, Moka.
I used to do soccer, uh,
I mean, I used to take
swimming lessons at one point.
Swimming's perfect...
It's something I can
impress Moka with.
Wow, you're so cool!
Plus, there's that...
Well...
You like?
Oh, yeah!
Tsukune?
Uh... Yeah, we
should check it out!
But, you see...
I can't...
Water is--
It doesn't look like your
girlfriend's too interested...?
Why don't you join us anyway?
I promise that I'll take
real good care of you...
Whaddaya say?
Eh...?
Uhh--
We're both joining!
Oh man, would you look at
the legs on those chicks?
Don't waste your
time on their legs,
look at their tits, bro,
always look at the tits!
But what about Moka?
Do you think she's gonna swim?
We can't give up just yet...
She'll take her shirt off,
you just watch!
Man, I can't wait!
Stupid Tsukune,
acting all flirty with her!
Good.
Okay.
That's the idea.
Excuse me?
Something on your mind, Tsukune?
D-Don't you think
you're way too close?
What am I making
you uncomfortable?
Oh, Tsukune.
You're so cute.
Let's give this one more try...
Just pull your
arm back like this.
Oh...
So soft!
That's enough!
Moka?
Tsukune... You joined the
swimming club so you
could meet new
girls, didn't you?
No wait, you don't understand!
Oh, no, don't you dare tell
me I don't understand...!
I won't put up with this crap!
Please, Moka, just listen!
Goodbye!
Moka, wait!
You're like two
little kids fighting...
It's ridiculous.
The only thing men and
women really need from
each other is to take
and be taken...
I'm sure you get my meaning.
This is the Swimming Club,
you know...?
If you're not going to swim,
why don't you just leave...?
...go bother someone else.
I gotta get out of here!
Whoa...!
Moka, wait up...!
Moka!
Ya hoo-hoo!
Hey, Tsukune...!
I just joined the swimming club,
too, isn't that great?!
And so did I!
She's gonna pop right out!
Dude, stop crying,
you're ruining it for me.
Little Yukari...
So cute!
It was totally worth the wait!
So...
Uh...
...will you show me...
--Teach me how to swim, please!
--Kurumu... Your umm...
Your...
Your breasts!
Buh-buh-buh...!
Hmm?
Yeah...
My breasts are
kinda hurting right now.
This is my chance...!
Today's the day I finally
make Tsukune mine!
It's my suit...
I think it may be a little
small or something.
Tsukune!
Hey, I want you to
teach me how to swim!
There's no way I'm gonna let
Kurumu have her way with him!
You let him go; Tsukune's
mine and that's that!
Well, I don't see your name
written on him, so there!
--Give him up,
you flat-chested twit!
Damn I so wish I was him.
--That Yukari... So hot!
--Bigger isn't always better!
That's interesting, cause
when I was your age mine
were already about this size,
so don't get your hopes up!
Oh, don't you worry, I won't,
cause the bigger they are,
the faster they sag!
You're trying to
tell me my breasts
are going to start sagging?
You brat!
You'd better take
that back right now!
I don't take orders
from you, Miss Milk Cow!
Guys, cut it out!
Shut your mouth
and let us settle this!
I bet you don't even
wear a bra yet, do you?
What difference does
that make, you slut?!
Why you--?!
Moka...
You idiot...!
Why'd you get so
close to the pool...?!
Getting wet like that,
it's no wonder this happened...
You know vampires
are weak against water.
In case you haven't
picked up on it,
water is a vampire's weakness.
It hurts them 'cause
of its purifying power,
Water reacts with a vampire's
energy and ka-pow!
That's why, when
Moka needs water,
she neutralizes it first
by adding some herbs,
and then uses that to wash
her face and stuff, whee!
This body of yours...
It's also my body...
Because I'm your other half...
So don't push our luck...
And don't let yourself get
strung along by that jerk!
Tsukune...
Here we go!
Boy, can't you see what I do
To get your attention
and your time
I don't bear these fruits
For just anyone
They bounce and bounce for you!
Uh-huh!
I won't let go of the hope
That one day your
heart could be all mine
So I'll play it cool
Be smooth
I guess having a flat chest
does have some advantages, huh?
Strike a sexy pose
and wait for you to see
Notice me
Amazing!
Totally!
But then again it seems
you're such a shy boy
Scared to look my way
When I'm tryin'
to show you I care
Yahoo, yahoohoo!
Sun sun sun
Think of us together
under parasols
Lying on the beach
without a care at all
And I'll be, whispering
--I should be happy about this,
--Sweet nothings in your ear
but for some reason
I just wanna cry.
No no no
No one else could ever
love you more than me
I love you so much
that it's embarrassing
Don't you see
Look me in the eyes
--And tell me
--Yeah, alright!
This...
...sucks!
You don't wanna give these
melons of mine a squeeze!
Awesome!
You got that right!
Okay, everyone!
My turn!
When you look at me you
think you see a little girl
Treat me like I'm fragile
and you handle with care
Ya-hoo! I won!
You'd see, my heart...
--Stellar! You betcha!
-- has much to bear!
So I use my charm and try
to wave my magic wand
Aim directly for your heart
and hope you'll play along
So I try, and I try
But still, but still
(You) never notice me
Magicu magical, magicu magical
I've tried so hard to
put you under my spell
Why can't a miracle,
just make us...
Hey...!
Why don't you and your stupid
boobs get out of my way?!
--Oh, sorry, I didn't notice.
--Say that you'll be mine
It's time...!
We're gonna settle this
thing once and for all!
Charge!
--Hey!
--Ya-hoo-hoo!
Hey, cut it out,
that's against the rules!
Well, these things
are in the way!
Stop biting me!
Stop blocking me!
--Ouch, that hurts!
--Oh, Moka...
You look down in the dumps.
You're surrounded by sunshine,
games, and beautiful girls
in bikinis, is this
not what you wanted?
Oh, no...
That's not it at all.
Then how about you
and I go for a swim...?
I don't know what's
bothering you,
but I'll make you forget it.
Who's saying "yahoo" now?!
Don't even think of going
back to the Swimming Club.
You wanna go
through all that again?
End your relationship
with the human...
He doesn't understand
a single thing about you...
He doesn't give any thought
to you or your needs.
That's not true...!
He's not like that, not Tsukune!
Even if you do go back there...
You won't be able to
swim with the others;
you know that, don't you?
I don't care...
I-I just want...
I want to be with Tsukune!
Are you really this hung
up on that Moka girl?
Why don't you stop
worrying about her,
and look at me instead, huh?
But, Miss Ichinose--
Call me Tamao, would you...?
The truth is, I've had my
eye on you since I first
saw you at the opening
ceremony for new students...
Since then, I can't stop
thinking about you.
Listen, I'm so
sorry about this...
But I really need
to leave now...
I just have to go find Moka!
No so fast.
We have no intention
of letting people leave.
Huh...?
What's going on?
Don't think too badly of us...
We do lure innocent
men to the water
and suck their life force...
...but we are
Mermaids after all.
It's sort of our thing.
Quick monster fact Mermaids
are terrifying monsters
whose very presence
portends calamity at sea.
Tales of these
inauspicious creatures
are well known among sailors,
In some legends, they entice
male sea-goers with their
alluring looks, and then
drag them, boats and all,
down into the depths
of the ocean, whee!
B-But Tamao!
Didn't you hear me...?
I've been watching you
since you first came here...
I caught your scent.
You have such an irresistibly
delicious, human-like smell.
It's no fair hogging
him for yourself.
Let me have a taste.
I want some, too!
Tsukune!
No!
Back off!
If I were you, I'd move aside!
What the--?!
Tsukune!
Just hold on,
I'm coming to save you!
No, don't...!
Do you have a death wish?!
Well, well, it looks like the
rumor was true all along,
Little Miss Moka is a vampire.
Water is a major
weakness for vampires!
We've gotta do
something right now!
Moka, no!
I won't let you go...
Don't you get it?
You're all mine now.
No...! No!
Hurry! Now's your
chance, Tsukune!
Moka...
You came back for me...
You knew it would hurt you...
...but you still jumped
in the water...
When the rosary seal over
her breast is removed...
Moka's innocent self vanishes...
...and her inner
vampire awakens!
Now listen...
You've been nothing
but a giant pain in my ass.
She's so powerful...
I never expected this...
...but she's still, a vampire...
Drink this!
Drink it... drink
it... drink it--!
Drink it yourselves,
you bitches!
Heh...
Take that!
Look, I don't need your help.
Come on, we're helping you
'cause you're weak in water,
so swallow your pride
and deal with it.
You look awful...
You're sparking like crazy,
and I imagine you're in
quite a bit of
pain right now...
Stop pretending it doesn't hurt,
and admit you've lost.
Don't flatter yourself;
a pathetic minnow like you...?
I could beat you in my sleep.
Minnow...?
You'll pay for that!
Vampires are weak in water.
But for a Mermaid like me,
being in the water is
home territory...
No way in hell you have
a chance of winning here!
Oh, you think so?
Too slow!
I can't believe you
took the bait like that...
That's just like a fish!
Die!
...know your place!
Aww...
damn it...
How could she
defeat me so easily?
This episode's big
fight took a mere
eighty-five seconds
to complete, whee!
Well, she shoulda' known...
If a mermaid's in midair,
that's not exactly
home territory, is it?
Stupid fish.
Are you okay?
Even with all her vampire
strength unleashed...
The water's still making
Moka really weak...
Huh?
You listen to me...
You don't understand a
single thing about her,
so don't pretend like you do...
You're a little boy who can't
think of anyone but himself...
Consider her feelings sometime.
She was crying her eyes out.
As it turns out...
I was the one who
didn't understand.
You see...
Unlike Vampires...
Mermaids thrive in the water,
which makes them
very dangerous...
The next day...
Moka didn't show up to class.
They're scary...
Now if their favorite food was
fish, and not the souls of men,
it might be a different story.
Moka, I'm sorry!
I was wrong.
Well if you really
wanna be in it,
then let's just join
the Swimming Club...
I won't be able to
swim, of course,
but at least I can
cheer you on!
You can't...!
What if you got water on you?
Listen...
I just don't want you
to put yourself in any
kind of danger for
my sake, okay?
No, I'm fine, really...
Don't worry about me.
Well there's no way that we're
joining the swimming club.
But there's no need to do--
Well, in that case, what do you
say to the Newspaper Club?
Newspaper Club?
Yep... See,
I'm the faculty advisor.
Sounds like a perfect fit to me.
I finally got someone
to sign up!
You two hold on, you're not
joining that club without me!
Yeah, yeah,
I wanna be in it, too!
Woo...!
That makes four...!
This is totally awesome!
We're in the
same club after all...
Yeah!
♪ closing song ♪
Oh, no!
Tsukune's been accused
of being a peeping tom!
What?!
Well, I wouldn't mind it
if he was peeping at me.
What?!
In that case...
We've gotta go prove his
innocence; come on girls!
Next time...
"Newspaper Club
and a Vampire"...
...and another!