Just the start of another school
day at Yokai Academy, whee!
Dear Mom, Dad,
and cousin Kyoko:
I hope all of you
are doing well.
Pretty soon, it'll be
a whole month since
I enrolled here at
Yokai Academy.
Time's really flown.
I haven't had a
chance to mail them,
but I've written you
a bunch of letters.
There are so many piled up,
in fact, that I've lost count...
This school,
well, it's a little...
...no, make that a lot weird.
At first I was pretty
unsure about this place,
but I've managed to
make some friends
and actually, to be honest,
I'm having a pretty good time.
Even so...
Should I keep attending and
hide the fact that I'm human?
'Kay.
Well, now let's move onto
the next page, shall we?
Please read it out
loud for us, Mr. Aono.
Mr. Aono?
Tsukune!
What the hell am
I supposed to do?!
It's simple, just read
this page out loud for us.
♪ opening song ♪
What was wrong with you
in class today, Tsukune?
Uh, nothing, I just
wasn't totally awake yet...
Oh, okay, that's good
to know, but look,
if you're ever in trouble,
you can come talk
to me about anything.
Because...
...you and I...
Moka...?
Tsukune...
Moka...
...you smell good.
Thanks...
Wait!
Just a little taste 'Kay?
No!
Look...!
You've been sucking Tsukune's
blood way too much, Moka!
And that's gotta
be why he was so
spaced out in class
this morning!
I didn't suck too much
from him yesterday...
Yeah right! You must have
if he's acting this way!
No that's not the reason.
Besides, Moka's a vampire
that drinks blood so I...
...don't mind meeting her needs.
Oh, Tsukune!
Oh, yeah, well
I have needs, too.
No!
Stop it!
You're a succubus,
Kurumu, so if you kiss him,
Tsukune will become your slave!
It's kinda weird we're friends.
Moka being a vampire,
and Kurumu being a succubus...
And me, being a human...
You're him, aren't you?
Tsukune Aono, right?
Yeah, and you're--
Fed up with you!
Why?
It's because you're
our number-one enemy!
Hold on, wait a second!
Your enemy?!
You don't know why?
Then allow us to explain...
...formation...
...set!
Start!
Gimme an "M," gimme
an "O," gimme a "K,
gimme an "A;" and
what does that spell?
Moka!
I've got a cheer for the girl
of my dreams, too, pal!
Kuru, kuru, she's my love, touch
her and you'll get a shove!
Yeah!
Y--U--K--A--R--I!
Yukari, yay!
I don't understand.
Why are you guys cheering
for the girls that way?
Wait, don't tell me--
Oh we will!
I'm the president of the
Moka Akashiya fan club.
Kozo Kasahara!
And me.
I'm the president
of the unofficial
Kurumu Kurono fan club,
Bosaburo Tye'ra!
And me.
I'm president of Yukari Sendo's
private fan club,
Kubisaku Nagai!
The three of us form...
The Cute Girl
Fan Club Coalition!
I'm drunk as a skunk!
Whee!
That's nice,
but I've got things to do!
Hold it!
The only thing you're
going to do is
face our fearsome
fan club wrath!
--Fearsome wrath...!
--Ow! Ow--ow--ow--ow!
What a wuss!
I know he's in human
form right now,
but this guy's a real crybaby!
Yeah, like he was an actual
human being or something!
A pathetic do--nothing weakling
like you isn't good enough
to be friends with
Moka, you pantywaist!
What the?
This guy's using
some kinda weird trick!
No, it's not a trick,
it's magic!
Hey, cut it out!
You buncha creeps stop
picking on Tsukune right now
or I'll kick your butt!
Oh, yes!
It's...
...my love!
Tsukune!
Are you alright?!
Look!
It's my sweet Kurumu!
And my Moka!
Hey!
What the hell are you
jerks doing to Tsukune?!
I'll tell you!
All three of 'em ganged
up on poor Tsukune there
and they were beating
the stuffing out of him!
Why?
That's mean!
I won't tolerate anyone
picking on Tsukune!
Magic Wand...
Clean up!
Wait... no I'm okay now...
...that's enough.
Oh, no, Tsukune!
You poor thing!
Guys!
This is our chance!
Right... but this isn't over!
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry I hit you!
Don't blame yourself;
it was their fault!
If it's me you're worried about,
don't be, because I'm fine.
Oh, man.
How did taking the trash
out become such a mess?
If only I'd been a little
stronger to begin with.
Then the girls wouldn't have
to have gotten involved.
A pathetic do--nothing weakling
like you isn't good enough
to be friends with
Moka, you pantywaist!
Maybe that guy's right...
Uh um, hello?
I doubt anyone can hear me,
but is anyone listening?
If there is, well, what do
you think I should do?
I'm a human and a weakling
and a pantywaist, too.
I rely on girls to protect me.
Is it really in everyone's best
interest that I stay
at this school?
The only thing standing between
us and the loves of our lives
is you, Tsukune Aono, so
come tomorrow we're going
to plant you right
into the ground!
I wish this was the real
Yukari, not just a picture.
If it was...
I'd be kissing that
gorgeous face of hers!
And I would do the same if
this was the real Kurumu!
Damn!
If it wasn't for that parasite
Aono, we wouldn't be
making out with photos of
our goddesses, but with the
real things; and this is why
we have to take him out!
If we do that--no, when we do
that--you'll belong to me
and nobody else, Moka!
You'll be mine!
--Yukari, you'll be mine, too!
--And you mine, Kurumu!
Yeah, right, guys, whee!
Hey, have any of you
noticed those three guys
from the other day
hanging around a lot?
Uh! Now that you
mention it, I have!
Wow, this AV equipment
is so heavy...
Hey, creep!
What the heck are you doing?!
Uhh...
Just taking pictures of
our ever--changing school!
See, I'm in the photography club
so this is part of my duties!
These photos are for
the yearbook and
not for my personal use at all!
Me, too!
Let's see.
I need vanilla extract, baking
powder, and a bottle of liqueur.
Great!
Ya--hoo--hoo!
I really hope Tsukune's
gonna like this!
Huh?
Wh--What the...?
Again?!
He's here, too?!
He's still staring!
Getting stared at is way worse!
I mean I'd rather get my
picture taken than have
some pervert gawking
at me like that!
Yeah...
...me, too...
Well, either way, those
guys give me the creeps!
We can kick their asses if
they try anything with us
but Tsukune is the
real problem.
So what do we do?!
Maybe we should talk to
a teacher about all of this...
There's no need.
Instead, the three of us'll
be Tsukune's bodyguards.
You girls?
We'll not only protect you, but
take them out at the same time;
it'll be like killing two
turds with one bone!
Ya--hoo--hoo!
I think what you meant was
killing two birds
with one stone...
Thanks, but I'll be fine.
No, you won't!
If they attack you,
you're gonna get the
crap beaten out of you again!
Uh--huh.
You're just not strong enough.
It's because you're a hu--
I'm sorry!
What I meant to say is that it's
because you're not that strong
in your human form,
but you probably are
when you change into
your monster form!
I mean, I don't really know,
but I'm sure you are!
Right, yeah and I've gotta go.
So... see ya.
Wait up, Tsukune!
Tsukune, please!
I'm sorry.
I almost spilled the
beans about you
being human and for
that, I apologize.
No, it's not that.
It's that I'm really weak.
I should be the one
protecting all of you girls,
but you're the ones
protecting me.
Tsukune...
Maybe I should just--
Sorry!
No wait!
Tsukune...!
Sweeping up, sweeping up,
it's so fun when
sweeping up, sweeping up,
sweeping up, it's so--
Where's he going?
Tsukune...
are you still mad at me?
Moka, come quick!
Yukari, what is it?
Just now, as I was sweeping up,
Tsukune was walking away.
It looked like he was
leaving campus and
he had this really serious
look on his face!
But that's not the only thing he
was also carrying a bag, too!
Wait, he had a bag?
That new student.
I wonder how
he's been holding up?
If Tsukune had a bag that means
that he's planning
on leaving school!
4:44 pm...
It's almost time.
Well Moka?
Where do you get off
calling her "Moka?!"
She's one of our sacred
goddesses so how dare
you say her name so
lightly, you punk?!
We don't know where you're
planning on going, buddy...
...but you're off of
school grounds now!
That means the three
of us can do this!
Yeah!
Umbrella!
Ooh...
Ooh Ooh...
Neckie--neck!
Blob!
So... those...
...are your monster forms?!
What was that?
Wait no!
Even you're dissing us now?
Ah damn it!
Um, no, it's just that...
It's just that we're pretty
dorky--looking monsters, right?
We know!
And it sucks!
The chicks at this school
always go for the cool, flashy,
badass monsters that go here!
Looking like this,
we don't stand a chance!
And you!
You don't even try but
somehow you still get girls!
That's why we hate you
and why you're gonna die!
Struggle all you want,
but you won't squeeze
your way out of this situation!
Not after you've rained
on our parade by trying
to steal the women we love!
You'll never get
to sit down and
chew the fat with our
darlings ever again!
We won't stand by and let you
take them away from us!
Take your hands--
I mean neck--off of him!
It's them!
Girls!
Um, question?
Why do I always have to
carry you two everywhere?
I'm sorry, this is my fault.
I can't remember what magic
spells to use to make us fly.
Guys, this stuff can wait!
Tsukune can't!
Yeah you're right!
Magic Wand...
Love seat!
Tsukune!
See?
And once again I got
saved by you three girls.
Moron!
Why don't you get it, Tsukune?!
All of us...
...we're friends, aren't we?
We're supposed
to help each other.
That's what friends do.
You know that...
...so accept it.
Yeah, but again, why am
I the one always getting saved?
That's not true at all!
Nope! Just take
me for example;
you saved me through
your kind words.
It's the same with me, too.
You saved me
from that other Moka.
Yukari...
Kurumu...
See? Look, that
makes us even.
Yeah...
That guy!
He's so mean!
He's stealing all our women...
...and he's doing it
right in front of us, too!
He's hogging all the love!
Tsukune Aono, you're
in violation
of the Romance Antitrust Act!
I'm going to blob you
into a blob even
if it's the last
thing blobbing I do!
Heads up, guys!
Yukari, my love...
I'm gonna wrap myself
so tight around that
smokin' hot little
body of yours!
You're a ripe fruit ready to
blossom and I want a taste!
Gross, no, get away!
Kurumu, I have an enormous
abundance of love for you,
so what say you and I gaze
lovingly at each other, huh?
Ughh...
...what am I
supposed to look at?
Your face? 'Cause you don't
have one you big, fat freak!
Oh, Moka!
No matter how hard the
rains fall, no matter how
fierce the rays of
the sun become--
which, by the way,
are the archenemies
of your lovely alabaster skin--
I will be your
umbrella of love!
Um, thanks, but I've
got an umbrella!
Ew, no, stop!
That's not good!
I've gotta end this now!
Hey!
You three!
Hm?
You call yourselves a
fan club, but all you
really are is a bunch
of creepy stalkers!
You're pathetic!
Wait, you're calling
us pathetic?
And not just that, but
also ugly, no-good,
disgusting pervert
monster trash, too?
I...
...didn't say that last part...
You think that, though, right?
You won't have to look
at us much longer
'cause we're gonna...
Destroy you!
Now it's time for the
Fan Club Coalition's...
...super secret...
...Angry Amalgam Attack!
Amalgam!
What the--?!
Holy crap!
Not so pathetic now, are we?
In fact, the only pathetic thing
around here is you, tiny!
Tsukune, no!
Oh, my gosh!
Please!
Please be alive!
I'm alright...
But I...
...have to protect all
of you from that thing!
No you can't!
Maybe not...
...but I have to try--
What the--?
Guys...
...what just happened?!
Where'd that weird,
bright light come from?!
When the rosary seal
over her breast is removed...
...Moka's innocent self vanishes
and her inner vampire awakens!
You three!
You woke me?
Look! Those cold,
yet beautiful eyes!
And that silky, silvery hair!
Those fangs!
It's her!
The one we've been waiting
to worship all this time!
Our true idol, the goddess
who descended from
the heavens above!
We adore you!
And we hope that
you'll return our love!
Never.
Not even if you were the last
amalgamated monster
trio on Earth.
Such cold--hearted words,
my goddess!
Yes!
Thank you, ma'am,
may we have another?!
Kurumu.
Yukari.
We love how you
torture us this way...
Yes, ma'am?
The two of you
have to help me out.
Roger that!
Sure thing!
Take this, dorks!
Magic Wand!
Let's rock!
Whoopsie!
Oh, no! Watch it
or we're gonna fall!
Now get lost, losers!
Yes, ma'am, of course.
Right away.
But...
she was the one...
...the one we've
been waiting for...
...the true idol...
From this day forward we're
now the Vampire Fan Club, 'kay?
Aye.
Wow, what a long showdown!
This episode's
climactic fight came
in at a whopping
eighty seconds, whee!
Well, I guess I wound up getting
saved by you again, huh, Moka?
Tsukune.
Uh?!
Yes, ma'am?!
You leaving doesn't work for me.
Because if you weren't around
anymore that would mean
no more food for yours
truly now, wouldn't it?
And also it would make her cry.
The other Moka, that is;
it'd break her heart.
Uh what?
Moka not sinking her
fangs into you would be
a good thing, but
still, you can't go.
She's right, Tsukune,
please don't leave!
Leave?
I'm not leaving... what
made you think I was?
Eh...?!
But you had a packed bag!
Yeah, and it's to
carry all the letters
I'm mailing to the other side.
I came here to ask
the bus driver
if he wouldn't mind
mailing them for me.
Wait a minute, so then
that whole business
about you wanting
to leave school...
...it wasn't real,
but a matter of
Moka jumping to
conclusions instead?
...so if you don't mind,
I'd really appreciate it, sir.
Sure, no problem,
kid, I don't mind.
That all you need?
Yep!
Keeping in touch with
your folks is commendable.
Take care.
I swear.
You're so confusing.
I don't want you to
go anywhere Tsukune.
Please stay.
I will and I'm gonna find
a way to make myself
strong enough to protect
you and everyone else.
I promise, Moka?
But until that day, it's
time to say goodbye
to this useless phone.
That you chose this path on your
own makes it more worthwhile.
But, kid, you've picked a
long and twisted one, too.
Hang in there.
There were some construction
delays that took a little
longer than anticipated, but at
long last, class, I'm happy to
announce that there's now a
payphone in the campus store,
one that will connect to
you to the human world!
What?!
Additionally, the bus that used
to come here only once a month?
Well, due to
overwhelming demand,
it will now be coming
here once a day!
Isn't that great, Tsukune?
Moka...
Tsukune...
Ah!
You smell good!
--Huh?!
--Tsukune!
But we're in
the middle of class!
Owwwwww!
♪ closing song ♪
It's a pool, and swimsuits,
and swimming!
Hey, wait, your
skimpy swimsuit's
pretty risqué, Kurumu!
Ahh yours is cute, it looks
like a kindergartener's!
Shut it, titty pie!
Next time: "School Swimsuits
and a Vampire," and another...