Dear Mom and Dad:
I'm still hanging in there.
As it turns out, here in the
dorms at Yokai Academy,
students get their own rooms.
That was a relief...
For several reasons...
I slept like a baby.
Dude, you do realize that you're
out of your human form right?
Aw, dammit, I must
have transformed
while I was sleeping!
And it looks like you
did, too, bud!
Wha--?
Oh crap you're right!
Yep.
Yokai Academy is a
school of monsters,
by monsters, and for monsters.
♪ opening song ♪
The bus to take me back to the
human world doesn't come
for another month.
Until then, I've gotta make sure
no one finds out I'm human.
Dude, check it out!
It's her!
Oh, yeah,
that new student, Moka!
She's so hot,
it should be illegal!
Morning!
It's so nice to see you!
Good morning to you, too, Moka!
Ah man,
what the hell is that about?!
It's that damn Tsukune guy!
He doesn't look like much,
but apparently he was tough
enough to beat the crap out
of that jerk Saizo Komiya!
Hey! The Expository
dialogue is my job, whee!
How did the story
become that I beat him up?
What's with you this morning?
C'mon... let's go!
Now she's holding his hand?!
Oh, the jealousy!
Oh, the misery!
Why couldn't that be me?!
That bastard!
This sucks!
So, Tsukune...
I imagine you're feeling
kinda lonely being
surrounded by monsters.
So if you ever need
anything, just ask.
I'll help however I can.
Thank you.
It freaked me out
the other day when
Moka unleashed her
scary vampire self.
But this version of her
is incredibly sweet.
Tsukune...
Moka...
It's too much!
Huh?
See, I overslept and didn't
have time for breakfast.
Hold on, I've got you.
What is it?
I'm sorry...
Hey, you can't treat me
like I'm your breakfast!
I'm sorry!
It doesn't hurt all that much,
and she doesn't leave a scar...
...but still, there's no
getting around the
fact that Moka's a vampire.
And what if that scary Moka,
the one from the other day,
is actually the real Moka?
Between her and the
other students,
how am I gonna make it in
this scary-ass place?!
Please, help me!
Are you okay?
It just hit me... I'm so dizzy.
I'm really sorry, but would you
mind giving me a hand, please?
Oh, sure, of course.
Will you be all right?
What is something wrong?
Uh, no, nothing at all!
Let's get you to
the nurse's office!
Aw, thanks so much.
I'm such a bad girl...
but he smells so good...
I just can't help myself.
I should go apologize to him.
I'm sorry to put you
out like this, Tsukune.
Don't worry about it. Wait, how
do you know what my name is?
Oh... Don't be silly!
We are in the
same class, after all.
Oh, really, we are?
Yeah, of course.
You see?
"See?" What am I
supposed to be seeing?
She is really cute and all...
But she's gotta
be a monster, too.
Whoa!
You okay?!
I'm so sorry!
It's because of this weird
condition I have with my body.
Every now and then,
my breasts sort of cramp up.
Your breasts?!
Yeah, you see,
they just get all tight like
they're being
squeezed or something.
It feels like they're
gonna pop open!
They get so swollen...
and they get so tight;
don't you see
how full they are?
They... feel like...
She's a monster just like
everyone else around here.
But monster or not,
when something feels good,
it feels good!
Tsukune?
Um, yes?
Look into my eyes.
Listen.
My name is Kurumu and
I want you to be my friend.
Whoa her eyes are beautiful.
And there's also...
Those ridiculously
awesome boobs of hers!
Be your friend?
Sure, I'd love to be
in yo-- friends with you!
Ooh, Tsukune, you're
such a naughty boy!
It's like I can't
control myself!
Tsukune?
What's going on?
Who is that?
Who am I?
I'm in his class.
We're friends now.
Right, studmuffin?
Right. We're in
the same class... Babe.
I've lost control again!
Well, we should get
going, Tsukune,
because class is
about to start.
Wait up, Tsukune!
No... I don't
wanna wait for you.
I'm tired of being used as a
substitute for your breakfast.
Why did I just say
those things to her?
That's just awful!
To think she'd use
you for breakfast!
Let's go before she
has you for lunch, too.
Yeah, that's a good idea...
Wait, no, it's not!
But, Tsukune...
Dean Koontz and Stephen King
are just two recent examples,
but there are scores
of other authors
who've featured cats
in their work.
Lewis Carroll is another
example of an author
Miss Nekonome has a
specialized interest...
in cats featured in
literature, whee!
That girl...
I do recognize her.
But what is she to Tsukune?
Why did I say all
that stuff to Moka?
I've gotta talk to her after
class and try to explain...
She's looking at me...
I am so winning!
...this is a superb
way of relating
feline qualities to humans.
Oh, look at that!
I guess we're out of time.
Well then, that'll be
all for today, class!
Meow, meow, meow.
Hey, Moka...
Moka...
Jerk!
I can't believe he was
flirting with her like that!
So apparently you're
a vampire, huh?
Well, that's what people are
saying... So is it true?
Dude, did you just see that?!
Yeah, and they
were totally white!
What's even better:
look at the boobs on her!
Damn! Those are
some fantastic tits!
Those're amazing!
See, I came here to
make a declaration of war.
A declaration of war?
Yeah, that's right.
I've got this big plan,
but you keep getting
in the way and
messing it up, Moka.
What plan?
Oh let me explain: my plan
is to turn all the boys
in this school into my
personal love slaves.
And it's been working
thanks to my Booby Trap!
Eh?
Plenty of guys
were falling into it.
And why wouldn't they?
I am a succubus, after all...
Hey, wait a minute.
You shouldn't reveal your
monster identity to me;
it's against school rules.
But--!
You came along!
And all of the stupid boys
fell for you instead of me!
I've had it with
your man-stealing!
Wait... I didn't
steal anyone, I swear...
Alright, I think a cat fight's
about to break out, whee!
I've had enough!
So the other day I vowed that
I wouldn't lose to you anymore!
Are those babes gonna fight?!
For our sakes, I really hope so!
I knew I had to beat you
and turnabout's fair
play and that's why
I've stolen Tsukune
away from you.
That's stupid!
Tsukune has nothing
to do with this!
Oh, there you are! I've
been looking for you, Moka.
This'll be good.
Major cat fight.
Oh, baby...
What Tsukune?
Listen, I want to talk to you
about those things I said...
Hey, Tsukune!
I'm sorry but I need to
talk to Moka right now.
Love Charm!
...but now that
I think about it.
I guess I really
don't have to...
Tsukune, get away from her now!
Huh?
Why would I do that?
You have to believe me!
She's dangerous!
I think she's sweet...
Hey, there's something
I just noticed.
Tsukune... smells really good,
doesn't he Moka?
Yep... Almost like a human does.
His blood must
taste really good.
That's the only reason why
you hang around him, isn't it?
So you can use him as
a substitute for breakfast?
That's not true!
And I don't "use him," either!
Yes, you do.
The only reason you want to
be my friend is because
you want to suck my blood.
God, it's just
like this morning!
Why do I keep saying
stuff I don't mean?!
I see.
All I am to you is
a substitute for
breakfast, lunch,
and dinner, Moka.
That's not true, Tsukune!
Yeah, run away, you loser!
Yahoo!
I did it!
I managed to make Little
Miss Moka cry her eyes out!
I don't get it.
Why did I say
those things to Moka?
And that look on her face,
it was so freaking awesome!
Even so, I've gotta apologize.
What are you doing?
Moka... I have
to apologize to her.
No, wait!
Huh?!!
Kurumu, what are you--...!
Aw, you're feeling down
in the dumps, aren't you?
Well don't worry.
Your bosom buddy'll
make it all better.
They're so huge!
Wait, what's this feeling?
Oh, no, what's happening?!
Uh-oh!
Sorry, but we're starting to
get into some scenes that
might be a little too
adults-only, whee!
Tsukune.
Is she right?
Am I only friends
with you because
I want to suck your blood?
I just don't know what
to think anymore.
You don't have time to mope.
Tsukune fell prey to
the succubus's magic.
It's called "Love Charm,"
and now she's got him
eating out of the
palm of her hand.
You're talking
through my rosary?
When a man is kissed
by a succubus,
he becomes her prisoner,
and she'll proceed to suck the
life out of him until he dies.
Oh, no!
You must hurry.
But hurry where?
Tell me!
Tsukune no!
Kurumu... um?
Don't move, okay?
My heart...
Yeah, mine, too.
It's beating incredibly
fast right now.
You'll be my first, you know.
The first boy I've
used this magic on.
Please Tsukune...
Don't run away.
I'm trapped; I can't get away...
I told you this
was my first time!
You can't be so rough!
Be more gentle with me, alright?
Let's stop.
I can't go through with this.
Impossible!
I'll try another Charm!
I said some terrible
things to Moka
and can't leave
things like this.
Besides...
You like her more than me.
Don't you?!
Even though I've
thrown myself at you!
Truth is... I've even done stuff
to you that embarrasses me!
Jerk!
Now I'm really mad!
I'm gonna take everything
that Moka likes
and smash it all to pieces!
Don't do it!
Moka, run!
Get away!
Now!
Go, before she
recovers from that!
Moka... Why'd you save me?
That girl is a succubus.
A strong one.
She can bewitch men
just by looking at them!
So that's why I said
those terrible things to you!
Tsukune!
Tsukune,
are you okay?
Yeah.
Excellent!
Now I get to kill
both of you at once!
Watch out!
She cut through those
trees like they were butter!
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine.
If you were, I don't know
what I would've done...
But Moka...
If we don't do something quick,
we're both gonna get killed.
My rosary... hurry...
Please pull it off!
Damn!
It's not budging!
Oh, no!
But it came off the other day!
Well, well, Moka!
I guess that stuff
about you being
a scary vamp was just talk!
If you were a vampire, you
could've fought me off,
but since you're not, you
and Tsukune are gonna die!
No!
You can kill me,
but please spare him!
Are you seriously
prepared to go that far?!
I mean come on!
All he is is your food!
He's not!
And I'm not doing
this because of his blood!
It's because I care for him!
He's the world to me!
Tsukune's the first
friend I've ever had,
and I'll gladly die for him!
Moka!
What the hell is with all
this stupid friend crap?!
There's only one use for
men and that's as slaves!
They're just playthings
to bend to your will!
I feel for Moka the same way
that she feels about me!
So I'll gladly die
for her, as well!
What's the deal
with that light?!
And the sky; what's going on?!
When the rosary seal over
her breast is removed,
Moka's innocent self vanishes
and her inner vampire awakens!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you one of those rare
S-Class Supermonsters?
Is this the true
power of a vampire?
Why don't you come
down here and find out?
What's wrong?
Afraid that you'll lose,
Little Miss Succubus?
You must be joking!
I'm not gonna lose!
No, I can't!
I'm on a very important mission.
The fate of my race is at stake!
A very important mission?
Right!
The reason we
succubi seduce men is
so we can meet our
destined one.
My kind are few in number, so in
order for our race to survive,
we must carefully choose our
destined one from a large pool
of men that we've bewitched
with our Love Charm.
I'd almost done it, too...
But you got in the
way of that, Moka!
That's why I can't let you live!
So that's it?
That's why you
picked a fight with me?
Big mistake.
Look out!
You're fast!
And you're slow!
Now you'll experience
the power of
an S-class monster first hand!
I'm sorry I'll stop I promise!
This episode's showdown took a
mere seventy-six seconds, whee!
I've got no guarantee of that.
So to be safe,
I'm going to tear them off.
Your wings
and your tail, that is.
No!
Please!
Don't do that...
I'm begging you!
What do you think you're doing?
Step aside.
Is her vampire self
the real Moka?
Not only did this
succubus bewitch you,
she tried to kill you as well
I think she's had enough.
Besides, you heard her;
she didn't do what she
did to be mean...
And what makes you so sure?
Well, 'cause
Kurumu... deep down,
she seems like a nice person.
Let's be friends with her, okay?
Y'know, like you and
I have become friends.
"Friends?" You and I?
Listen, Tsukune, you've got
the wrong idea about me.
I only rescued you
so that your blood
wouldn't get swiped from me.
That was it.
I'm not like the
other Moka you know.
So then... Who's the--
I've got ya.
The rosary spoke to you?!
It's weird, huh?
Maybe the seal's getting
weaker or something.
Really...
She may not think it...
...but you're both my friends.
I couldn't bear to be
without either Moka.
And you know what?
If you guys wanna suck
my blood it's fine by me.
Tsukune...
I wanna apologize
about yesterday.
Moka...
Tsukune...
How'd we go from bouncing
boobs to this crap, whee!
Morning!
Hi, Tsukune!
I baked some cute
little cookies for us.
How 'bout you and
I eat 'em together?
Wait, why are you asking me?
Oh, come on, I already told
you that I was looking for my
one-and-only destined
partner for life, didn't I?
Yeah...
Well...
I've decided that it's you!
Hey, it's all your fault
since you risked your
life to protect me the
way that you did.
Now I'm totally
in love with you!
--Well they do smell good...
--Take one!
They're real yummy like me.
Stop it! Tsukune is
mine and mine alone!
♪ closing song ♪
Yahoo!
I'm Kurumu Kurono!
Did you enjoy this episode of
"Succubus and a Vampire?"
If so, I'll be showing up on--
That's not the
title of the show!
But we are introducing a new
character on the next episode!
Next time "Witchling and
a Vampire," and another...