What...?! You're telling me
not to do anything at all?!
But, Mr. Director...!
I've made my decision,
Miss Nekonome.
But, sir, what about
poor Mr. Aono?!
Assuming that he is indeed
put to death as it seems
he will be at this point...
It means that it was his
fate to die at this time.
Sir... you can't mean that!
He's the enemy of all monsters!
Don't let him off the hook!
Hey, hurry up and put
that damn human to death!
Oh, man...
How'd I get myself into this...?
Oh, right, by being
a human that enrolled
in a school for monsters...
Should I have left a long time
ago when I had the chance?
I could have tried to
go to a normal school...
...and made some normal
friends who are human like me...
But then...
...if I'd done that...
I never would have met Moka,
...or any of the others
for that matter.
Are you so afraid to die
that you're cracking up?
Promise me something.
And what's that?
That after you're
done killing me...
...you promise not
to hurt anyone else
in the Newspaper Club.
For a wretched human,
that's a remarkably noble
sentiment, my friend.
Very well.
Never let it be said that
I'm not without mercy.
So, you'll mean you'll--...?
Yes...
You needn't worry
about your friends
in the Newspaper Club
suffering at all...
Their deaths will be
quick and painless.
Please, I'm begging you!
Please don't hurt my friends!
You can all meet on
the other side and
make a newspaper
no one'll read!
It was here...
This is where you
saved my life...
Tsukune.
Now it's your turn
to do the saving.
Who are you?
Kurumu please we
have to do something...
Hey, um, listen...
I didn't get the chance to
finish saying this last time...
But I do have an opinion...
I don't think it matters if
you're monster or human,
just if you're good or bad...
and I say this from
personal experience, too.
I mean, when I first
came to this school...
...the ones who picked
on me were monsters,
and the first person who
stood up for me was Tsukune,
and, he was a human,
the very thing that
I was taught to be afraid
of since I was little.
Yeah, I know...
and I get it.
'Kay, well, in that case-...!
But you don't get it...
I'm upset for another reason.
We're all friends...
...but Tsukune...
...and Moka, too...
They didn't trust us enough
to tell us what was going on.
But Kurumu...
I mean...
Come on!
It's frustrating!
If they'd just told us the
truth, think of all the
ways we could be helping
them out right now!
Idiots...! Tsukune
and Moka are idiots!
Why don't you come and tell
the both of them that in person?
I'm so sorry...
Tsukune...
Giving up already?
No, I'd do anything
to save Tsukune...
It's just, in this form, I don't
have the strength to do it.
Tell me.
You don't think you're
all alone in this, do you?
A crow?
Stand back.
It's been awhile.
Rubi!
What took you guys so long?
We got hung up
knocking out the guard...
Kicking his ass took awhile.
Yeah, that guard sure
put up one heck of a fight!
Wow, all you guys came, too!
What are you just
standing around for?
Shouldn't we be
off saving Tsukune?
Kurumu...
I'm still really mad at you.
You shouldn't have kept
Tsukune's secret from us.
Sorry.
Now's not the time
for apologizing.
It's a new wand?!
You've got one...
How?
It's a long story...
However, it's gonna hafta wait!
Yeah!
We've gotta save Tsukune...!
There'll be plenty of time
for Moka to beg our
forgiveness after that.
Whether you're
human or a monster,
there's no difference in the
value of someone's life...
You said that, didn't you?
Sure did...
It's good to see you've
learned a few things.
Alright then let's go!
Come on!
Everyone...! The time has come
to put this human to death...!
Before you hangs the
mortal enemy of our kind...
Shall we send him
to meet his end...? Well?
Just hold on!
We've got you!
Rubi, Kurumu!
We can handle this;
get Tsukune out of here!
Well, well...
Those fools from
the Newspaper Club!
I'm warning you...
All of you are
committing a serious act
of treason against
Yokai Academy...
Don't you realize that?
Yes I do, but Yokai Academy
doesn't matter anymore!
The only thing that
does is our good friend!
He's more important than
this school, you creep!
You're making the same mistake
as last year's Newspaper Club.
Back then, Ginei Morioka said
something quite similar to me.
He said he couldn't tolerate
what we were doing
so he was going to
expose us in print.
He said the truth mattered
more than this school.
Gin said that?!
Really?!
A mistake...
That's what allowing the
Newspaper Club to continue was,
and a grave one on my part,
but I plan on correcting
that with your deaths!
You three, wipe them out!
Our glorious leader
has given us an order!
Now you law-breakers
are gonna die!
Die, I don't think so!
Magic wand...
Golden washtub!
What can I say...
I just don't know
how to hold back!
Wow, they're beating
the Committee!
Man I'm so excited
I can't hold it in anymore!
Dude...
...calm down.
Hmph...
Go ahead, run.
It won't do you any good
against someone of my power!
Oh, no!
Hey... you guys...
Go help Tsukune!
Go on hurry!
...you sure?!
Let's just say that
you owe us one!
Okay then!
You're safe now.
Kurumu... Rubi...
Thank you.
Tsukune!
Oh, Moka!
What's the big deal about her?!
I'm the one who
just saved your butt!
Oh shut up, Kurumu, and you get
away from my Tsukune right now!
Hey, the only one who
needs to get away is you!
Um... Ya know, I really thought
I was a goner back there...
Well, now you're
a goner up here.
Tsukune?
It's a real shame the
rest of the students
couldn't be here to see this...
...but the execution
was finally carried out.
As for "monster-human
coexistence"...
I hope that ridiculous
idea dies with that fool!
...please...
You can't do this, Tsukune!
You can't die on me like this!
Tsukune, please...
Life without you...
...isn't a life at all...
Moka...
I'm glad...
I really am,
and about everything I...
I'm glad I came to this
school and met everyone...
...and I'm glad I met you.
Don't talk like that!
I just have one last thing...
...to ask...
Protect the Newspaper Club...
...keep them...
...safe from Kuyo...?
Save our friends...
Tsukune...?
No...
Well, well...
So the "S" Class
Supermonster is upset
over the death of her
little human pal, eh?
You bastard!
I'm gonna kill you!
I'm sorry it took us so long.
We finally took out
all of his minions.
What happened?
I'm sorry...
We were with him but
then Kuyo showed up...
Move back.
Tsukune's lifelight
hasn't gone out yet.
He's still alive,
but just barely.
If I hurry, he might make it.
Wait, what are you
gonna do to him?!
Give him my blood...
Inject it in him.
Vampires have incredible
regenerating powers so if you
gave him some of your
blood, that might work.
Does that mean Tsukune's
gonna be alright?!
His chances are slim...
But at this point,
it's the only option we--...
Is that monster Kuyo?
So he's...
...a fox demon?!
A demon?
Yes, a powerful one!
His kind were sometimes
worshipped as gods
in ancient times!
Your powers don't
disappoint, vampire!
But as you'll see, they pale
in comparison to my own!
He's channeling his
monster energy into his tails!
Have a taste...
...of my Fire Wheel!
--Oh-no!
--Mizore, put up an ice wall!
It won't be strong enough!
Yeah, well, standin'
around gawkin'
like that won't,
do anything either!
I was gonna call ya morons
for doing that, but honestly...
...there's a bigger one here...
That would be me...
But the thought of all
my clubmates getting
killed again...
...well, that was just...
...too much!
Gin!
He shielded us from the blast!
I guess he can really act like a
leader when he wants to, huh?
Well, yeah, I guess so...
...but what's the point if
he just winds up dead?!
Morioka.
Of all the people to step in.
Oh, well, he saved me the
trouble of killing him later.
You bastard!
Don't worry, Moka, you can
count on us to hold him off!
Do your thing and save Tsukune!
He could kill you all!
Don't you think we
already know that?
I'm sorry.
Tell me...
who wants to die next?
Everyone, listen:
we can't let him
step one foot past this point!
Gotcha, so how do we do that?
By working together
as a unified team.
We will; Tsukune's life
is on the line here,
so we'll use everything
we've got to protect him!
Tsukune...
I give you my blood...
Take it and live.
Tsukune...
Tsukune?
Damn...
I guess it's still
not enough yet.
Hey, asshole...!
Just chill out!
I barely even feel that!
Give me a break with all this
"Friends" sticking
together bullshit?!
Monsters and humans are
enemies and always will be...
Mizore!
Oh, no!
Yukari I need you
to stay focused here!
Yeah! Right!
You're just a
close-minded bigot!
Monsters and humans can
be friends if they want...!
And we're living
proof of that fact!
Not for long!
Ready?!
Let's do it.
Our Unified Magic!
And the Dark Ring
of Containment!
Now!
Hmph!
You think you can hurt me
with a bunch of paper cards?!
No, but we can trap you
in a ring of spirit birds!
If you think you can
break free of that,
you're in for a
very big surprise!
The only one who'll be
surprised here is you, witch!
So much for your trap...!
It didn't work!
Oh, yeah?
Wow...! It worked after all!
You bastards...
I can't believe some
weaklings like
you actually managed
to hurt me.
I think he's changing
back into human form.
That spell you guys used
must've really banged him up!
Wait, look...
You're wrong...
He's not changing back
into human form!
It seems his monster
energy's transformed
him into another
one altogether!
You should all feel
quite flattered...
Not many foes are
ever fortunate
enough to see me in
my ultimate form.
Now die!
What the hell is
happening up there?!
Dunno, but that felt
like an earthquake!
Hey, get the line movin'
up there, would ya?!
It's jammed at the top,
you dumbass!
Oh, I really hope my kids
are alright...! Mee-ouch!
Someone's stepping on
my tail; please get off of it!
He's just...
too strong...
So much... power...
You lived...
I'm impressed.
I see now...
Your little snow woman
friend saved you, eh...?
She used the last of her
strength to build an
ice wall to protect all of you.
And now...
You're defenseless.
Wrong...
They've still got me.
And I'm gonna kick your ass
from here to Kingdom Come.
Moka Akashiya?!
I see that your efforts
to revive the human
have been a complete and
utter waste of time.
Killing a vampire will boost
my reputation though,
so come and get me!
Once it's known I destroyed
an "S" Class monster...
...my position of power
on campus will be
stronger than ever, and I'll
have you to thank for it!
Moka...
Wait a minute...
What happened with Tsukune?!
There's nothing more I
can do for him at this point!
So then--...?
Does that mean that he's dead?!
No, this can't be happening!
He can't be dead!
Oh, please...! You're
supposed to be strong;
is that all that you've got?
This is child's play!
I guess I gave Tsukune
too much of my blood!
Aha... I see...
You shared your blood with
your pathetic human friend
and look what it did to you...!
It made you weak!
Humans are
petty-minded creatures.
They're selfish and lazy...
They betray...
They lie, cheat, and steal.
And they hurt other living
things without a second thought!
For fraternizing with that human
scum you deserve to die as well!
You're going to burn until
there's nothing left...!
And not just you, but your
dead human pet, too!
Good riddance.
Moka's dead...
So is Tsukune...
That can't be true...
You're right, it's not!
See, up there!
Um, Moka...?
How did I...?
You sure took your own sweet
time waking up, didn't you?
Huh?
You sleepy-head!
No...! He lives...?!
But that's impossible!
I saw what my flame did to him;
his body was burnt to a crisp!
Thank goodness
they're both alive!
Alright...! Her vampire
blood really did the trick!
What an outrage...!
There's no way I'm letting
you two get away with this!
Uh...
we should run!
Don't worry,
I'll take care of him.
Give me a break!
I preserve order and protect
the peace at this academy!
Your pathetic!
Do you really think
you can take me
out with your ridiculous
excuse for power?!
Damn right she can, ya prick!
Where the hell did
you come from?!
Don't'cha know anything
about werewolves...?!
We are quite famous
for our speed!
You've been swallowed up
by your own vile ambition,
and both you and your
Security Committee
goons are out of control,
Therefore you've
lost the right to preach
about "preserving order"
and "protecting the peace!"
Shutup!
So, Kuyo, I think it's time...
you learned your place!
Alright yeah!
Oh man, what happened up here?!
What's that huge hole?!
--Hey, look!
--What the?!
--Holy crap!
--Kuyo?!
--I don't believe it!
--Somebody kicked his ass!
--Who did it?!
--Yeah!
Who?
Well, you see...
it was, uh...
Tsukune...
Moka, hey what's wrong,
are you alright?!
Ohh, you're okay?!
Uh...
Yes, ma'am, we are.
I'm so glad to hear it,
and you certainly
showed that Kuyo a thing
or two, didn't you?
I'm not one to condone violence,
but it appears that you giving
Kuyo a thrashing has cleared
your name, wouldn't you agree?
Well, actually the one
who beat him up was--
Cleared my name?!
Of course it did...
A human couldn't have
beaten Kuyo up,
only a monster could've!
We're all really sorry,
Tsukune...
I'm so embarrassed that we
suspected you of being a human.
Yeah, you're awesome,
and you gave Kuyo a
much-deserved ass-kicking!
I guess I can finally
say this now,
that damn Security Committee
made my life a living hell!
Yeah, and mine, too!
You've made things better
for all of us, Tsukune!
Hey, guys, whad'ya say we hoist
our new school hero in the air!
Yeah!
No, hold on a second!
Guys, wait, hang on!
Hip-hip-hooray...!
Hip p-hip-hoo oray...!
Hey, guys...
Think you could come help me
before you start doin' that?
This episode's showdown took...
Ah...
Who cares, whee.
After all the
commotion died down,
I finally managed to talk to
a very reluctant Kurumu...
She told me
everything, about how
I got wounded and was
close to death...
...and how everyone stood
together and put their
lives on the line just
to protect me...
And yes...
...she even told
me what Moka did...
...and how she saved my life.
Tsukune...
Look, Moka...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
About what you did for me.
You had to use up all of your
power to save my life.
It was worth it.
Huh?
And I'd do it again
if it meant that
you came out of everything
safe and sound.
Oh, Moka.
Hey...
Please don't cry.
You sleepy-head!
What the...?! Hey,
what's the matter with me?
Why's my heart beating so fast?
Oh, man, don't tell me...
I'm not falling for
the other Moka, am I?
Stop it...
When you look like that...
It makes me want to say...
Oh... Tsuku... ...ne...
Oh, Moka...
Hey Tsukune sup...!
I knew they'd be doing
something behind our backs!
Nasty boy.
Hi, everyone!
What was that we
interrupted just now?!
Um, it was nothing, I swear!
--You can finish it on me.
--No, finish on me!
--I was here first!
--No...! Me!
No, me!
Not them, Tsukune...!
Just kiss me!
All five of you?!
Yeah, me, too,
so pucker up, baby whee!
♪ closing song ♪