My name's Tsukune Aono.
I'm fifteen years old.
Starting this spring,
I was going to be a new
high school student.
Well, at least
that was the plan...
Here we stand together now...
I'm so screwed...
I've got three years of
nothing but dudes in school.
You're gettin' off easy.
I've got a one-hour
commute to school.
Oh please!
Everyone knows that
school has lots of cute girls.
Right, Tsukune?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
Dude!
Drop it!
Well, it's really not
that big a deal,
flunking the entrance
exams this year.
Don't worry,
you'll pass 'em next year.
Yeah, that's right!
Hang in there.
You guys wanna
stop by the arcade?
Sure sounds good.
The one that just opened?
Yeah.
Tsukune!
Yeah, Mom, what is it?
--We've got wonderful news!
--Huh?
Yeah, your old man
here just happened to
run into someone today, and it
turns out he was a lucky find.
Ooh, yeah!
Best dad ever!
So thanks to me, you now get
to go to high school after all!
You got this off the street?!
Oh I'm so happy!
Now he won't have to
wait a year to try again!
Hey, kid.
Are you a new student
at Yokai Academy?
Uh, yeah.
In that case,
you better prepare yourself.
That's one scary-ass
school you're going to.
What do you mean by that?
Um, hi, Kyoko, how's it going?
Fine.
Listen, Tsukune,
I talked to your mom...
She said you were going to some
school called Yokai Academy.
Yeah that's right.
Well, since my favorite
cousin's gonna be going there,
I decided to do some research,
and you should know--
Hello?
Kyoko?
Are you there?
Wow, it's like a completely
different world here
on the other side
of the tunnel...
Is that the school over there?
I'd watch your
back if I were you.
I should call Kyoko again.
That's strange I had
a signal before
we went through the tunnel.
I hope I'm going the right way.
Whatever that is,
it's getting closer...
Oh no what the
hell is following me?!
Just me!
A bat!
Whee!
Aw, man...
...it was just a ba--
Ow... Ow, that hurt...
Oh, I'm sorry!
I just suddenly got all dizzy...
She's...
...gorgeous.
I... I, uh....
It's not what you think, really!
I'm sorry!
Oh, you're bleeding!
I can't.
I shouldn't...
but that smell....
Huh?
Smell?
Ahhh...
her hair smells so good!
Sorry...
I can't help it!
'Cause I'm a vampire!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to!
You bit me!
Wait... huh?
It's not that bad.
Are you going to Yokai, too?
Uh, yeah.
It's my first year.
That's great!
This is mine too!
Oh... what do you know...
I have to ask...
what do you think about...
...well about vampires?
It's a joke.
It's gotta be.
They're fine by me.
I don't have a problem
with vampires in the slightest.
If you wanna call yourself
a vampire, more power to ya.
Thank you!
Well, if that's the case,
maybe we could be friends.
What do you think?
Yeah... sure.
Oh, fantastic!
I was nervous 'cause I didn't
have any friends here yet... Oh!
Yeah my name's
Moka Akashiya by the way.
And mine's Tsukune Aono.
I can't believe I get to go
to school with a girl this cute!
This is my lucky day!
Well, good morning, students.
If you're new here,
welcome to Yokai Academy.
My name is Shizuka Nekonome,
and I'll be your teacher.
Wow!
The teacher
seems really nice too.
I really lucked out!
Well I'm sure that everybody
already knows this fact,
but Yokai is an incredibly
unique school!
One that's exclusively
for monsters.
--Yep!
--Sure...
...sure... monsters, why--
Currently, this planet is well
under the control of humans.
So, in order for monsters like
you and I to survive, class,
the only option
that we have is to
learn how to coexist with them.
Whoa... Teacher...
...what?
And that brings us to...
our first rule!
Except in special circumstances,
as long as you're on campus,
you must always remain
in your human form.
Everybody got that?
Rule number two:
never, ever reveal your
monster identity to
another student.
I'm sure you can see why!
Everyone will follow
these rules, right?
Buncha boring rules.
And you are...
Aha, Saizo Komiya
If we do happen to spot
a human, why not just eat him?
That's what I would do, anyway.
He's gotta be joking!
Well, now. There's no chance
of that happening because
at this school, all the students
and teachers are monsters.
So, no exceptions.
Got it?
You see this school's enclosed
in a giant secret barrier
but even if a human got
through it somehow
and wandered in here... they
would be killed immediately!
Say whatever you
want, but I swear
I've been smellin' a
human this whole time.
I'm so sorry I'm late!
Oh don't worry, it's alright!
Go ahead and introduce yourself!
Hi!
I'm Moka Akashiya.
Whoa!
--Man look at her!
--She is so hot!
Totally I think I'm
in love with her!
Tsukune, it's you!
I'm so glad we're
in the same class!
Huh?!
I don't get it.
What's going on?
Is this a dream?
It has to be...
A school full of
nothing but monsters?
That makes no sense!
Oh, I'm sorry!
What the?
Oh you're silly!
She's... strong.
This is fun, huh?
Uh...
Really... This cute girl is
a real-live vampire?
Hey there, sexy.
You said your name was
Moka Akashiya, right?
No let him go!
So tell me... what's a smokin'
hot chick like you doing makin'
friends with a
numbnuts like this guy?
I mean come on?
Tsukune!
Hey...
Forget about that punk-ass and
hang out with me instead, babe.
No way, I prefer to hang out
with nice people, thank you.
Tsukune!
Are you okay?
Uhh... yeah... I think so.
Wow...
...that was pretty scary!
Are you sure
you're okay after that?
Yeah, I'm alright...
He was really strong, though.
So that was monster power...
Crazy strength.
Oh Tsukune, you're so funny!
Back there, you
acted almost like
you'd never seen a
monster before!
Well...
So what kind of a monster
are you, anyway?
Oh, wait, we're not
supposed to reveal
that to each other, are we?
Sorry, never mind
you don't have to tell me!
But I already know
what you are Moka,
since you told me that
you're a vampire.
Yeah, I know but
when I told you,
I had no idea that
was a rule here!
You know, you don't look
like a vampire very much...
Well, not right now, but...
Look.
L-Look at wha--?
No, I can't look there!
It's okay...
Look at the rosary on my chest.
If I were to take this
off I would change,
I'd turn into my true form:
a powerful and
terrifying vampire.
So...
A real vampire?
That's why I wear it: as a
charm to seal my powers away...
I can't even take it off myself.
Well that's okay!
Even if you get a little
scary sometimes,
I'm sure you're still
the same Moka...
I knew you'd understand!
You're my first friend here!
And also... I feel I should
tell you that you're
my first in another
way, too, Tsukune.
In what way?
'Til now, all I've ever had
was tomato juice and
transfusion bags...
I had never sucked anyone's
blood before yours today.
It tasted so sweet.
So rich...
That feeling...
I'll never forget it!
Uh, yeah, I'm sorry!
But I have to go!
See you later!
Why'd he leave?
This can't be happening!
How can she be so cute
and still be a vampire?
But are we really
that different?
So her... And her, too...
And all of them?!
I don't think
this school's for me.
Tsukune!
You were acting kinda
weird back there...
I just...
I think I should go
to a human school.
A human school?
Why?
Look I really like you, Moka,
but I just can't stay here!
No way! You can't
go to a human school!
You can't!
Moka, please!
I'm sorry it's just that
I really don't like
humans very much.
They can be cruel.
I know because I
attended human schools
all the way up
through junior high.
I was lonely...
Because humans...
...well, they don't
believe in monsters.
I felt so different... it was
like I shouldn't even be there.
That's all I ever thought
about when I was there...
But then you said
you didn't mind
if I was a vampire, Tsukune.
And for the first
time in my life,
I didn't feel alone anymore.
But still...
What if I turned out to be
one of those humans
you hate so much?
Would you still feel the
same way about me?
I'm a human.
I'm sorry, but that's what I am!
And the only reason
I'm even here at all
is because of a major mix-up!
You're lying.
You have to be... no human
could have gotten in here...
I should've known you'd
look at me like that!
It's really true, Tsukune?
Just stay away from me!
You hate humans, right?
Don't you?!
Well, that's okay!
I don't need you!
I don't need monsters
for friends anyway!
Tsukune wait!
Where's the bus stop?
This way?
Tsukune...!
So where do you
think you're goin'?
Stick around, babe.
Sorry, but I'm busy now.
How 'bout gettin' busy
with my true form?!
I'm an orc!
Noooo!
Oh, no that jerk again?
But if I go back,
I'm still just a human.
Come on, babe, what's the deal?
I showed you my true form,
so why don't' you show me yours?
Don't tell me a sexy
little thing like you is shy!
For one, it's against
school rules!
We're outside of school now,
so that rule doesn't
mean crap to me!
No don't!
Stop it!
You! Get the hell
away from her now!
Tsukune...
What was that?! Beat it!
What the hell are you,
a monster or a mouse?!
You're pathetic!
Tsukune!
Huh?
Hey, you!
Get back here!
The bus stop.
So this is where it is!
Tsukune!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Forgive me!
I guess monsters and humans
are too different to get along.
Don't cry...
Look at me--I'm a vampire.
We suck people's blood
and hurt them in the process.
The truth is... back at my
old school all I ever
wanted was a friend,
whether it was a
human or a monster,
I didn't care.
But now... I think
maybe it isn't possible.
Well... I think--
What's with all
this lovey-dovey shit?!
Please, you should
get out of here!
But Tsukune!
I know I'm weak...
And nothing but a
piece of human
garbage to you...
I don't care if you're a
monster and I'm a human;
that doesn't matter
anymore, Moka!
'Cause I still want
to be your friend!
All your yappin' is
getting on my nerves!
Tsukune!
Even if you are a vampire...
Well, I still...
I still like you Moka.
My rosary... it came off!
Hey... what the hell's this?
She looks different...
...and scary.
That's not the same Moka!
She transformed!
If I were to take this off
I would change, I'd turn into
my true form a powerful
and terrifying vampire.
So that's...
...the true form of a vampire?
Oh, man.
The tales... they're true!
The red eyes...
The silver hair...
The overwhelming energy...!
She's an "S"
Class Supermonster...
A real vampire!
So then, I suppose the one
who woke me up was you, huh?
What the hell?!
What's wrong with me!
I mean... she's only staring
at me but I can't stop shaking.
No, this isn't right!
Hey, pull it together, man!
'Cause if you took
down a vampire...!
It's time for you
to know your place.
Yes, ma'am, I'll remember that.
So quick, whee!
It's like she's not even the
same Moka that she was before.
She's so strong...
I wonder... Which one of
them is the real Moka?
But her sweet smell...
It's the same...
Just like before.
Oh, thank goodness!
You're finally awake, Tsukune!
Hey, are you alright?
You aren't hurt
anywhere are you?
What's happening?
Did I dream all this?
The bus it doesn't come
at different times,
but different days?
What?
Am I reading this right?
The bus only comes
here once a month?!
Mmm-hhh... didn't you know?
Oh, no!
You're bleeding!
Here, let me help you!
Dear Mom, Dad, and Kyoko...
I know this letter
won't reach you
for a while because of
the weird bus schedule,
but I'm writing it anyway.
My new school, Yokai Academy,
turned out to be an
odd sort of place.
To tell you the truth,
I even considered leaving
and heading home right away.
However, I've decided
to stick it out
for a while longer to
see how things go.
You see, I've made a new
friend and, well, she likes my--
Oh no...! I'm sorry, but I
just can't resist this smell...
Uh, what do you mean?
Sorry, Tsukune!
I think I've enrolled in a
pretty dangerous school here!
You're gonna be fine,
Tsukune; let's kiss!
But I'm gonna be sucked
on even more next time!
Oh, and, what's a succubus?
Next time: "Succubus and a
Vampire," and another...