- [gasps]
[coughs]
Did I just die?
[shudders]
Elsa. What was she
doing in the mansion?
[groans]
I'm in the graveyard.
So maybe it's
right after the trial, then?
Or is--[gasps]
Emilia!
- [whimpers]
- [gasps]
- [murmurs]
[sighs]
Subaru, is that...
- I'm right here.
- You're okay now.
- [gasps]
I-I swear to you, it wasn't me!
- I know that.
- It wasn't!
- It's all right.
Just don't worry.
- [sobbing]
Subaru.
- [sighs]
EMILIA: Sorry about that.
I've finally calmed down.
- Emilia.
- Are you sure
that you're feeling okay?
- Mm-hmm. I think it's 'cause
Subaru was there for me.
Anyway, we need to talk
about the trial.
- Oh, yeah.
I bet I have a pretty good idea
- what you're gonna say.
- [gasps]
- Don't tell me.
You saw your past, right?
- [gasps]
- Your what?
- Wait a minute.
How the hell do you know
what happens in the trial,
anyway?
- You saw the ruins
glowing earlier, right?
That's 'cause
I was qualified, too.
And what's more...
- I passed it.
- [gasps]
- Hmm.
Young Su passed, did he?
RAM: Quite an achievement,
if he's not joking.
This means
we can remove the barrier.
Garf, how does it look?
- No changes so far.
- How dare you lie
to all of us like that?
- Okay, way to jump
to conclusions!
[gasps] What's wrong, Garfiel?
- Are you kidding me?
There's not a damn thing wrong.
- Huh?
- Subaru, if that's really true,
then what did you see?
- Well it's less about
what I saw than what I realized.
And the thing that I've
come to understand
is there's more than one
of these sadistic trials.
Turns out
there are actually three.
- So two more?
- [gasps]
Emilia, I have
a suggestion for you.
But I have to warn you,
there's a chance
you're not gonna like it.
- A suggestion?
- Mm. If it's all right,
I'm prepared to take on
the other trials in your place
- and pass them for you.
- [gasps]
- I want to try
and be your strength.
I have no idea what awful things
you saw in your past,
but if it made you cry that hard
and put you through
so much pain,
- then I want to help if I can.
- GARFIEL: Hang on!
You're spewin' all this garbage
and expect us
to sit here and listen to it?
Well, it's time for you
to hear me out now.
I don't want anybody
but the princess, Miss Emilia,
to go through the trial,
all right?
In fact, you're the last person
I wanna see
gettin' rid of the barrier,
so you need to stay
the hell away from it!
- [gasps]
- Simple.
You already did it,
then that means
you can go through the trial
in Emilia's place.
- Hey, uh, wait a second!
- What? You're not
actually surprised
I have a problem with it,
are you?
Man, you're even
more of a dumbass
- than I thought you are.
- No, I mean, why would you--
- Subaru...
- [gasps]
so are you saying...
you don't trust me
to do this myself?
- Huh?
- Because you saw me struggling
and felt that I was failing,
now you'd rather do it
instead?
- No! But you shouldn't
have to face your past if--
- Stop it! If I don't face it,
then I'll never pass the trial!
No. I can't just avert my eyes
from things I don't like,
leave them all to you,
and run away.
That would only leave me
with nothing.
- [sighs]
RAM: Let's change the subject.
[footsteps shuffling]
SUBARU: You got a minute?
Why were you so against
what I was saying back there?
And tell me the real reason.
- Because it's--
- Because it is what
Young Roz wants us to do.
- Huh?
- He believes Miss Emilia
should be the one
to liberate the Sanctuary
and stands rather firm on it.
- Seriously?
And both of you guys
actually back him up on that?
- Listen, I never said that,
and I hate that son of a bitch
every bit as much as you do.
But even so, don't you get it?!
- So I guess,
even if the barrier vanished
and the Sanctuary officially
became part of his domain--
RYUZU: This land is completely
overseen by Young Roz.
None of us dare defy him
and endanger our position.
I apologize to you
and the others.
- I see. Man...
trusting Roswaal just keeps
getting harder and harder.
- Yeah. Anyway, the princess
has to go through the trial.
Even if you are qualified,
I'm not gonna let you
give it a shot, no matter what.
- Damn it. Emilia.
No. Come on, focus.
I need to figure out
what to do about the mansion.
There's no way
that demented woman
won't do something awful
to Rem and the new maids.
It's Frederica
I'm worried about.
Does she have ties
to Elsa somehow?
In any case, I need
to get back to the mansion
as fast as I can.
- How fascinating.
And what is it you would
like me to do about it?
- Get the people
of Arlam Village back home.
And I want you
to bring up this idea
to Ryuzu, Garfiel,
and all the others,
'cause this time around,
I don't think I'll be able
to get them on my side.
- "This time around?"
Oh? And why would that be?
- That Garfiel punk
has made no secret
of the fact
that he hates my guts.
He's way too impulsive.
I'll never convince him
to go along with me.
Oh, yeah,
and there's one other thing.
I wanna go and tell the people
who are still in Arlam
that their families are safe,
and I plan on heading back there
myself to tell them that.
But of course,
I'm goin' to the mansion,
where Frederica's
planning something, too.
- Indeed,
Ram's informed me of this.
But given what I know about her,
Frederica would
not be so hasty in--
- And what do you know?
Frederica handed over
that glowing stone to Emilia,
which is all the proof I need
that she's up to no good.
- And if she turns out
to be an enemy of yours,
what are you going to do?
I'm sorry to say this,
but you stand
no chance against her.
- [gasps]
Emilia's dealing
with the barrier,
you're seriously injured,
and Otto won't take part
in any of this.
We're stuck.
- That is true,
with the exception
of one person.
- If I may be blunt,
I don't like this.
- You're still
talking like that, huh?
Are you serious right now?
- Then let me
spell it out for you.
With the current condition
that Roswaal is in,
it doesn't feel right
to leave his side.
- Well, yeah, but it isn't like
you can do anything
for him, right?
I couldn't believe it
when I heard that Garfiel
was the one who put
all those bandages on him.
- Don't be a fool.
What if I had applied them
and then made his injuries
even worse than they were?
- Oh, show some guilt!
GARFIEL:
Makin' your triumphant return
with a pretty girl
on each arm, huh?
You've really got some nerve.
You know that?
- I didn't think
you would come out
so early in the morning
to see me off. So you heard?
- Frankly, it pisses me off
that this entire thing
was pretty much decided
behind my back,
but I ain't gonna fight it.
- Oh, yeah?
I'm glad to hear you say that.
If you'd tried to stop me,
I would have
had to throw Ram off
into the distance as a decoy.
- As if that would ever work!
Wait. Would it?
- Eh, how would I know?!
You should
say something to, uh...
Ram, what's wrong?
- This stupid conversation
gave me a headache. That's all.
- Well, I'm out of here.
Guess I'll see you.
I should be back tomorrow,
so look after things until then.
- Hey, hold on a minute.
You're leaving
without saying goodbye
to the princess?
- Wow, I'm surprised you're
actually concerned about Emilia.
But don't worry. It's okay.
I left her a letter
explaining things.
Uh...
by the way, don't you have
something you wanna give me?
- Eh, what the hell
are you talkin' about?
- [sighs]
- All right, then, how about
showing concern for me?
The woman you love is leaving
to fulfill her duty.
Have you no desire
to offer assistance?
- Guess you're only nice to me
when you think you'll get
something out of it, aren't you?
- [stone clinks]
- Happy now?
Take care of Emilia.
And try to make it clear to her
that I'm genuinely sorry, okay?
- Why don't you
tell her that yourself?!
I don't work for you, you know!
- So, Barusu,
will this thing Garf gave us
be of some use?
- I don't know.
What do you think?
'Cause after all,
you've known him
a whole lot longer than I have.
- I'm honestly not sure,
but since it's part
of a matching pair,
I assume it means
something important to him.
- [gasps] Doesn't seem like
you're very happy today.
- What you were
saying earlier...
- Huh?
- when you told Garfiel
that you'd throw me as a decoy.
For some reason,
that bothered me
more than I would have
expected it to.
It's as if...
that had actually
happened before somehow.
Barusu?
Look, Ram...
there's something important
I need to tell you.
In fact, it's about
what's most important to you.
- Well, the only thing
that truly means
that much to me is Roswaal.
- No, it's something else.
Now listen to me. This is
something that you need to hear.
There's a girl. Her name is Rem.
SUBARU: Please don't
let anything happen.
I'm here two days earlier
than last time.
If things
still go wrong somehow,
I'll have to take off
on Patrasche
the minute I wake up
in the graveyard.
If Frederica
turns out to be an enemy,
it's crucial for me to know
when she's gonna take action.
- Barusu?
- Should I attack or run?
If it's Elsa I'm dealing with,
I'd better just get
the hell out of there.
Which means--
- Barusu!
- [gasps]
Oh, yeah, hey. What is it?
I was just thinking about, uh...
- It's a pleasure
to welcome you back, Mr. Subaru.
And I must say,
you returned here
much sooner than I expected.
[giggles]
[gasps]
What is it?
Is there something wrong?
- Oh, man!
- No, you're just so cute!
- [gasps]
- Sorry. I can't help it.
- Wait!
Uh, Mr. Subaru!
- I just--[crying]
You've no idea what kind
of hell I've been through.
Seriously. Damn it.
Uh...
Is that a...
- Uh-huh.
It matches the one I gave you.
- [gasps]
- [shudders]
You're not hurt, are you?
- Not a bit.
From the bottom of my heart,
I'm just incredibly relieved
to see you again.
I'm really happy
to be back here, Petra.
RAM: If I may be blunt,
I don't like this.
- Why does that sound familiar?
- 'Cause I'm being direct,
as always,
the adorable quality of a Ram
who's been quite forgotten
and left at a loss.
- Uh, hi. I guess
you must be Miss Ram, right?
I was recently hired
as a new maid
in service
to the lord of the mansion.
I'm Petra, and it's truly
a pleasure to meet you.
- You seem to know your place,
unlike Barusu.
Very good.
A passing grade, then.
Needless to say,
- you fail, Barusu.
- Huh?
- You may not cross
this mansion's threshold.
- What was the point
of even coming back
- in the first place, then?!
- [giggles]
- Oh, hey, uh, Petra,
has anything weird happened
here while we were away,
like with Frederica,
for example?
- I haven't seen anything.
She seems pretty normal
if you ask me.
- Is she inside now?
- Frederica's out patrolling
the forest barrier.
It may be a while
before she gets back.
- Our timing's
either good or bad.
What's our next move, Barusu?
- I want to see
what she's gonna do,
so let's wait with Rem
in the meantime.
- I should probably
get back to the cleaning now.
Please call for me
if you need anything.
- You're nervous, aren't you?
- That is ridiculous.
Well, to be honest,
you should be,
'cause it'd be
a natural reaction.
I want you to be nervous.
[door opens]
SUBARU: I'm so glad
you're all right.
- Barusu.
- Yeah? What?
- Could you leave us alone
for a bit?
- [grunts]
[door opens]
Well, it's a start,
a really good start.
- Ah! It seems you've returned
sooner than I anticipated.
I must admit
I'm rather surprised.
Since Emilia wasn't able
to come along and join you,
might I assume
the trial isn't completed yet?
- Uh-uh, but there are
a few things
I wanted to ask you about.
First, there's this.
[stone clinks]
- [gasps]
But that's...
- Huh?
- [stone clinks]
- That's Garf's stone, isn't it?
- That's right.
So you do know him.
I mean you really
are related, then?
- I'm a little confused.
Garf didn't tell you that
himself, did he?
- I can see it in your faces.
And I'd guess that he's
your younger brother, right?
- You are indeed correct.
[sniffs]
See, the truth is
that I'm Garf's--
I'm Garfiel's older sister
by blood. So now you know.
- Then answer me this.
Why did you use
that glowing stone
to set a teleport trap?
And I want you
to be honest with me.
- [stammers]
- Can't tell me that
because
of your oath, either,
huh?
Too bad, 'cause this is
one thing you need to--
- Wait. I have no idea
what you meant by "teleport."
- [gasps]
- I'm not sure
how to respond to that look.
- Aw, come on! Give me a break!
You don't fool me!
I know you're working
with the conservatives
who don't want
the Sanctuary to be freed!
- Wait. Who?
Afraid I don't understand.
Maybe it would be best if you
just started from the
beginning.
- [gasps] You're really
not acting? Or signaling?
- Private time with Frederica
in my absence?
It would appear you have no need
for your life, Barusu.
- Uh, no, I was--
I see your tea-making skills
haven't improved at all
since we left. What a shame.
- Oh, no. In fact, making tea
is the one thing
I truly excel at.
My, what a hateful creature
you are.
- Nonsense.
I'm perfectly lovable.
Any more so, and the world
would be in danger.
- Always ready with
a sharp retort, aren't you?
Honestly...
it's so typical.
- And? If you don't know
about the teleporting,
why give Barusu
that stone, then?
- Well, I...
- You can't tell us
because of your little oath.
Is that it?
If so, that's a feeble excuse,
Frederica.
- [sighs]
Yes, you're exactly right.
I'm truly sorry,
but I cannot tell you
anything about it.
- Sticking to it, I see.
All right. Then there's
nothing more to discuss.
- Uh, hey, take it easy!
- Your refusal
to answer the question
makes your betrayal
crystal clear.
We'll restrain you
and take you to the Sanctuary.
Then we can finally determine
who's been giving you
your orders this whole time.
- Yeah, but this--
- If you insist on taking me
to the Sanctuary,
- then I won't resist.
- There. You see?
Even Frederica--Wait. What?
- I don't have any intention
of resisting you, none.
- Oh, you won't, huh?
- And why not?
- How slow can you be?
Frederica isn't able to break
the oath of her own free will,
so obviously you'll have to use
force to make her, Barusu.
That's the kind of excuse
she needs.
- [cup clatters]
- Uh...
Wow, you two are
in perfect sync.
- Well, naturally.
- We've known each other
for ten years now.
- [sighs] If that's
all it's gonna take,
then frankly I'm relieved,
'cause I wanna get out of here
as soon as poss--
- ELSA: Goodness.
- [gasps]
- That seems
like a rather hostile thing
- to say, doesn't it?
- [whimpering]
[slurps]
Now, then, let's keep
that promise we made.
It's only fair.
PETRA: Please, all of you...
[inhales]
hurry! Run!
El Fula!
[metal clangs]
- Oh, I see.
You're a demihuman. Lovely.
- FREDERICA: Petra.
- [gasps]
- I'll shred you!
Her arm is...
- My, my, that hurt.
[slurps]
I thought
I was a goner for sure.
Yes, I like it.
Maids in large,
medium, and small
and one delicious young boy.
I'll put you all on a table
and compare
what's in your bellies.
- Wow, even Garf
has better pickup lines.
- Barusu.
- I know! I know!
Shamac!
[gasping]
[wails]
- We're leaving!
- [gasps]
- Subaru!
SUBARU: Frederica!
- [gags]
- Ul Fula!
[Frederica and Subaru groaning]
- [gasps] Are you okay?!
- [gasps]
Seems I underestimated
our opponent.
- [groans]
Damn it. Did we get her?
RAM: It doesn't feel like it.
Who was she?
- Rem and Beatrice...
we have to save them.
- RAM: No, we don't.
- Huh?
- The four of us
will be making our escape
and leaving them here.
That's our best option
right now.
- What did you--
Do you have any idea
what the hell you're saying?!
- Just calm yourself.
- That's Rem inside the mansion!
She's your sister!
You love her, and she loves you,
so you have to stay
and protect her,
- no matter what, damn it!
- I made the proper judgment.
Surely you know that losing
you
along with Frederica and me
would be a far greater loss
for our side.
- There has to be a trade-off.
- But you'd be
sacrificing your--
- Yes, she may be
my younger sister.
I could sense
that the same blood
flowing through my veins
flows through hers, too.
But her existence itself
is a blank, a complete mystery.
Still, if she is my sister,
this is what she would say...
"If the day should ever come,
please sacrifice me
to save Master Roswaal's life."
- I-I didn't bring you here
to make you say that.
FREDERICA: I believe
we should save the two of them.
We have to. Listen to me.
Both Beatrice and Rem
are also vital to our side.
If we just leave them behind,
we're done for sure.
- Yes, me, too! I believe we
should rescue them both as
well!
I agree with her.
- We're not taking
a majority vote on this.
Now be quiet, child.
- I may be young,
but I'm plenty grown-up!
In fact, Frederica even told
me
I'm more useful than you are!
- Well, Frederica,
what else did you say to her?
- Since it was my idea,
I'll assume the task
of stopping the enemy.
- [gasps]
- [cloth rips]
- So you're
deliberately choosing
to draw the short straw
again, I see.
You are just like Garf.
- I see you girls as
my precious junior colleagues.
Also, it's incorrect
to say I'm just like Garf.
After all, Garf is
the one who's imitating me.
[stone chiming]
[winces]
[groaning]
- So this
is a beast transformation?
- [roars]
- [gasps]
- Petra, I'm sorry
for frightening you.
- You can still talk
when you're like that?
- Of course.
I'm still me, after all.
Well done.
You fought the urge to scream.
- [grunts] Right.
Please be careful, okay?
- Good girl.
Ram, I leave the rest to you.
- No need to remind me.
But don't fall behind,
'cause if you do,
I'll make you regret it.
- [roars]
- [snarls]
- Hmm.
- Snap out of it!
- [gasps]
- Let's go.
- Right. Okay.
Then we need to start with Rem.
[glass shatters]
[footsteps echoing]
[metal clatters]
SUBARU: This is bad,
bad, so bad.
We've gotta get upstairs!
- [roar]
- [maids gasp]
[rumbling]
[music playing]
- [growling]
[small creatures chittering]
A mabeast?!
- [roars]
PETRA: This way!
- [growls]
- El Fula!
- [roars]
- What's it doing here?!
- There's no time now.
It's here. Deal with it.
I'll fetch the ground dragon
from the stable.
- Wait. Patrasche?
- [growling]
- With a mabeast here,
we'll need transport.
Now go and retrieve the two
of them while I draw it away.
Fula!
- [roaring]
- This way!
[glass shatters]
- [gasps]
- [chittering]
- Okay. Now's my ch--
[groaning]
- Subaru?!
You're bleeding!
[both gasp]
- This'll hurt, so be strong!
Three, two...
- [screams]
[gasping]
Thanks, Petra...
but whatever happened
to "one," huh?
- I figured
you'd be less tense that way.
[gasps]
- Your hand.
I'm sorry.
It seems like I'm always
putting you in harm's way.
- No! Are you kidding me?
Now don't be silly.
I'm grateful to you,
because whenever I'm in danger,
you're the one
who always comes to rescue me!
So this time, it's my turn.
We'll get Miss Rem
and Miss Beatrice out of here,
and then we can escape with
Miss Ram and Miss Frederica,
all of us!
- You're amazing.
Man, am I pitiful or what?
- You're not--
- No.
It's not like I'm complaining
or anything.
I meant I've gotta try harder
to be as awesome as you.
- [gasps]
- Now let's go.
You said it yourself.
We're all gonna get out
of this place, aren't we?
- [gasps]
Uh-huh!
- Oh!
- [gasps]
Wh-What's the matter?
- What I really meant was,
"Yes," and not just, "Uh-huh."
After all,
that's the appropriate response.
- [giggles]
- I'll have Ram or Frederica
scold you later--
[heart beating]
- [echoing] Barusu. Barusu!
[Subaru groaning]
- That was a mistake.
I should've come
to check sooner.
[rumble]
I must do what I must do.
It has to be carried out.
That's it. Very good.
- [Patrasche coos]
- [heartbeat continues]
[Patrasche galloping]
SUBARU: Patrasche.
- [roar]
- [glass shatters]
- [Subaru screams]
- [bones cracking]
- [gagging]
[panting]
This is...
[groaning]
Talk to me, Petra.
Are you oka--
[gasps]
[silence]
[singing in Japanese]
[Subaru gasping]
[wails]
["Memento" continues]
[singing in Japanese]
[gasps]
ELSA: Ah! Good.
You finally found me.
- Where's--Where's Frederica?
- Oh, you mean
that big, blonde maid?
Now, don't you worry.
She proved to be
quite enjoyable.
- I want to know who sent you
to come after all of us.
- Sorry, but I never
speak of my clients.
At the very least, I do have
that much professional
courtesy.
Though, since you came back
sooner than anyone expected,
this didn't play out exactly
as my directions specified.
- What does that mean?
- I'll elaborate for you.
Two maids and one shut-in,
and it was supposed to be
precisely timed to your return.
- [gasps]
Stop. Stop. That's enough.
- Too true.
I really don't want Maylie
taking any more credit from me.
So let's end this now.
I'll send you
to meet the angels.
Even if this world won't last,
I refuse to let her hurt Rem!
Rem!
["Memento" ends]
[gasps]
Why...
Why did you save me?!
Beatrice!