[mysterious music playing]
[Ryuzu gasps]
[groans]
[Garfiel shuddering]
[Ryuzu panting]
[Garfiel moans]
- [grunting]
- [pounding]
- Young Gar, stop that!
- [grunting]
[grunting and pounding continue]
[sobbing]
- Please, Young Gar.
- [wails]
SUBARU: Otto, you idiot.
Guess you did do
something crazy, didn't you?
- I never realized the little
pipsqueak had it in him.
And on top of everything else,
he even won Ram over.
Now here I am lookin' like this!
- Wait. Ram?
What happened to them?
- Listen, whatever
you guys are plannin'
don't mean a damn thing to me.
- You didn't kill them, did you?
- It don't mean a damn thing!
I told you!
Get out of the way.
I'm gonna smash up the entrance
to this stupid place
and put an end to this bullshit
once and for all.
- You can't be serious.
If you do that, the Sanctuary
will be closed off forever.
Is that what you want?
- Hell yeah, it is.
Every other thing around here
is what's causing the problem.
[wind blowing]
Huh?
Now just what are you
tryin' to pull, huh?!
- I'm curious.
Garfiel, what is it
that you're so afraid of?
- [gasps] What are you sayin'?
You think
I'm scared or somethin'?
EMILIA: I know you are.
That's why
you're always shouting
and trying to make yourself
look bigger, isn't it?
- Is that right?
Well, I don't wanna hear it!
What do you know
about me anyway?!
- More than you think.
Because I was just like you.
I've been afraid of many things
throughout my life.
I lived in fear...
right up until today.
I left the bad things
in Puck's hands
so I could forget them,
but now
I've finally remembered.
- Shut your mouth.
- I'm still not sure
what I need to do,
at least, not yet,
but my goal is to find
out
just what that something
is.
Although...
- Shut the hell up.
You know nothing.
Don't you--
Don't you dare pretend to--
- But you might be ahead of me,
since you've already found
that one thing for yourself,
haven't you?
- I said
keep your damn mouth shut!
- You're just
way too half-assed, Garfiel.
It's true Emilia
has failed the trial once.
I can't deny
that she cried her eyes out
when it showed her a past
she didn't want to see, either.
But she's still gonna
keep on trying over and over,
unlike you, the guy
who gave up and ran away.
- [Garfiel growls]
- Garfiel...
you have a grudge,
and it's holding you back,
one against your mother,
who deserted you.
[Garfiel gasps]
SUBARU: Sorry, man.
While it may be kinder
to beat around the bush,
it's the Natsuki family way
to be blunt
and tell it like it is.
No hard feelings.
Your mother left you.
You and Frederica were
abandoned in the Sanctuary.
Then after that,
what did you do?
[Garfiel gasping]
SUBARU: Frederica left
the Sanctuary, too.
She believed that you'd
eventually liberate it,
so she left to make
a place in the outside world
for the people living here.
But, you, what have you
been doing on the inside?
You want to keep it
all closed off,
because you hate your mother
and the outside world
that made her leave you?
Is that what's
really been going on?
Is it 'cause you
don't want to be hurt here?!
- No. What in the hell
do you think you're...
- I'm not gonna know
until you tell me,
so make me understand,
and say something!
If you despise your mother,
then bust out of this place now,
and get revenge on her
or whatever,
but stop taking it out
on every single person here!
- [gasps]
- You must hate your family,
'cause if you didn't,
then you'd--
- You're wrong!
- [gasps]
- I wanted...
I just...
- Go on and tell me the truth!
- [shudders]
I just--
just wanted my--
I just wanted my mom
to finally be happy.
We were in the way.
My sister and I were in the way
of her happiness, weren't we?!
It only makes sense!
[sobs]
We were bringin' her down.
She couldn't even stand
to look at us.
If you're carryin' around
baggage like that,
then what's wrong
with dumpin' it somewhere?!
Mom took a chance.
She left so she could find
some joy in her life,
so I'm not holdin'
anything against her.
But I saw it.
I saw it in the graveyard.
Right after Mom left here,
there was a landslide.
And she died.
Why? It's just not fair.
Didn't she take off so
she
could find somethin'
better?
Wasn't the entire point
of leavin' us behind
so she could be free
to find herself again?
If she abandoned us
just to end up dyin'
before she even had the chance
to have what she
was lookin' for out there...
then just what in the hell
are we supposed to do?
There's nothin' that I wanted
more than for Mom to be happy.
I wanted her to make me believe
that our sadness and loneliness
had a purpose behind it,
that everything we went through
was the price
to help her chase her dream!
I wanted that to be the reason.
I wanted her
to make me hate her!
There's no way I'm lettin' you
get back to the outside world.
- [gasps]
- Things changin'
ain't gonna make everyone happy.
For a lot of us,
nothin's ever gonna get better.
I'm gonna protect them.
You hear me?
I'm gonna defend everyone
and everything within my reach.
I'll use all the power I have
to become a barrier,
a real barrier,
one that can separate
the inside from the outside!
- Garfiel, don't!
- The Sanctuary,
the people, the old hag,
I'll guard 'em all!
No one can do it but me!
No one will know but me,
and no one else needs to!
[chorus vocalizing]
[growls]
[roars]
- [groans]
EMILIA: Subaru.
- It's okay, Emilia. Thanks.
[grunts]
You're so damn stubborn.
I guess I'll just have to
force you into total submission
to make you realize that you're
just a big, sweet idiot!
- [roars]
- You'd better
survive this, body!
Shamac!
[heart beating]
Thanks for being there.
- [grunts]
- Come down to my level,
Garfiel!
[chorus vocalizing]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
[vocalizing ends]
[gasping]
Wh-What the hell jus--
[groans]
[gasps]
Is this my sister's?
But it doesn't make
any damn sense.
- Oh, I don't know.
I mean, who's to say
that there isn't
a really hungry cat
hangin' out inside of it?
PUCK: That's all the help
I can give you.
- Apparently,
even when you can't talk,
you can still find a way
to annoy me by glowing.
All right, look at me.
- Huh?
- If you wanna stop me,
do it with your own hands.
Don't wuss out
and hide behind your blood,
you sniveling,
pathetic coward.
When are you gonna stop
treating me like a fool?
We're going
to the outside world,
Emilia's taking on the trial,
and the Sanctuary
will be liberated,
whether you like it or not.
- You don't have any right.
Who said you could do that?!
This place
doesn't need to change!
- You know it's not
gonna stay like this forever!
In the same way
we've all been cornered,
there's gonna come a time
when you'll be
completely helpless on your own,
maybe tomorrow
or maybe even right now.
Learn to accept that, Garfiel.
Then discover what
"strength in numbers" means.
- So that's the point
you've been tryin' to make?
What a waste of time!
[blow echoes]
[gasps]
- [gasping]
[chuckles]
- [gasps]
- [coughs]
- [tooth clatters]
Take a good look.
The wall you've been
so desperately afraid of
doesn't even exist.
- It does exist,
'cause I am the wall!
Understand? I stopped here,
and so did the old hag
and everyone else.
And that's the end of it,
which means it's over!
- Don't just give up
on yourself!
Whenever that voice
inside your head
says, "I wanna do it!
I wanna change,"
that's the beginning!
That's where
your starting line is!
When you decide to lift
your head and walk again,
no one has the power
to stop you for any reason!
["Realize" playing]
Isn't that right, Garfiel?!
Isn't that right, Emilia?!
And...
isn't that right, Rem?!
- [growls]
Damn you!
- [gasps]
- [yells]
[heart beating]
- [gasps]
[heartbeat grows louder]
[sputters]
[yells]
- [gasps]
[groans]
Man, talk about
a bad first impression
for a new technique. [gags]
Aw, come on.
You've gotta be kidding me.
You're really standing?
- How tough are you?
- [panting]
I still got some fight left.
Don't underestimate me.
As long as I don't break,
I can...
[panting]
SUBARU: Damn.
No way I can deny
you're strong now.
- This is...
the end of it.
You'll never--
[Patrasche grunts]
- [groans]
- [snorts]
[wailing]
- [laughs]
So, Garfiel, what do you think?
Believe in the power
of "strength in numbers" yet?
- There had to be...
a better way to show me.
And when I get back up,
I'm gonna kick your ass.
- How about seeing it as all
our feelings coming together
and that bond
won us this battle?
- [groans]
I still don't like any of this,
but I suppose
it's just like they always say,
"Nobody can lift
a quain stone alone."
- There you go.
Whatever way you wanna say it
that works for you.
[mysterious music playing]
SUBARU: This power...
that nasty witch
was probably behind it,
the Sloth Witch Factor
that she talked about.
- Rawr!
[yelps]
- Unseen Hand?
Unperceived Impact?
No. What should I call it?
- Invisible Providence.
- [insects chirping]
That's it.
- Huh?
What are you talking about?
- Oh. Uh, nothing.
Uh...
looks like you're actually
letting me use your lap
as a pillow again.
Is that a reward for overcoming
my biggest battle yet?
- [chuckles]
Maybe.
- [laughs]
- [Patrasche grunts]
- [gasps]
- [sighs]
You're finally awake, Mr. Nat--
- [grunts]
- [yelps]
Hey, that hurt!
What'd you do that for?!
- Shut up, you stupid idiot!
This happened
because you went off and
did your own thing, you jerk!
'Course, I might have been
in trouble without your help,
so I'm still sorta grateful.
Just take that
however you like.
- I don't know
what you're talking about!
- [chuckles]
- [groans]
[gasps]
- I'm really glad
that you're all right.
- [chuckles]
Same to you.
- [grunts]
- [grumbles]
- [groans]
- Do you need a translation?
I assume she said, "Don't
worry me like that," right?
- And also, "Don't be so cocky,
'cause that won't happen again,"
which is where
the extra rage is coming from.
- [chuckles]
Thanks for the help.
- [coos]
- So where's Garfiel?
- Over there,
but I don't think
we should interrupt just yet.
SUBARU: Interrupt?
- [giggles]
[peaceful music playing]
- [groaning]
- Garf, are you awake now?
- Kinda.
Yeah, I guess I am.
- Then get off me already.
- [yelps]
- Hmph.
My feet are going numb.
- [sighs]
Even after all this time,
there still ain't a shred
of niceness in you, is there?
- When there's someone
who's worth being nice to,
then I can be.
- [gasps]
[sighs]
So in other words,
I'm not worth it, huh?
- Sorry.
To find out
a lady's true feelings,
you must try harder.
- [sputters]
Garf, you're just too stupid.
There's no use
attempting to think.
- Huh?
- From now on, clear your mind.
Fight with an empty head...
for myself and Miss Emilia, too.
- Buh!
Look, don't be so dumb!
I can admit that I lost,
but admitting and surrendering
are two different things,
and I'll never surrender!
I could pick up
right where I left off--
- Stop yammering!
- [gasps]
[growls]
- You lost, Garf,
you perfect loser.
How long must you carry on
in front of the woman you love
before you're truly satisfied?
- Th-Then you want me
to just fall in line
beside the rest of you
with a smile
like nothin' happened?
I accept that I lost, okay,
but I won't ever believe
that I was wrong! You got that?!
Because I wasn't,
and that's all there is to it!
So don't expect me to make
some half-assed attempt
to--
- If you don't want it
to stop at half-assed,
then you simply need to prove
that you're not standing
still.
- Huh?
Uh...
The trial.
- Are you capable of change,
or are you going to be
a little cowering child
stuck in one place forever?
You have to find out
with your own two eyes.
- Now don't say that in a way
that makes me wanna deny it,
all right?
[sighs]
- Don't just give up
on yourself!
- [sighs]
RAM: You look determined,
like you've made up your mind.
- You'll be fine, Garf.
- Huh?
And if anything frightens you
to the point of tears,
I'll comfort you as a favor
to an old friend of mine,
'kay?
[mysterious music playing]
[footsteps echoing]
- [breathes deeply]
[shuddering]
Damn it all.
[door creaks]
[breeze echoing]
GARFIEL: First you need
to face your own past.
[groans]
Eh?
[birds chirping]
Huh?
- [baby cooing]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
- [peaceful music playing]
- [cooing]
- [gasps]
Mom?
RYUZU: So you insist on going?
- Yes.
Although I know that doing so
will impose
such a burden on you.
- Ease your mind.
I am not concerned with that.
But the greater issue is
how these two little ones feel.
- [giggling]
- [gasps]
Shut up! You piece of shit!
[grunting]
- Uh, Mother,
I-I, uh...
- I'm sorry, Frederica.
Sweet girl, I know this
is causing you to worry, too.
- [grunts]
I'm okay,
but it's just that I--
I feel bad for Garf.
- I wish we could go together,
but I'm just so clumsy.
I know that it would be
a terrible experience for him.
Frederica...
for a child of mine,
you're quite responsible.
Look after him.
- No!
Don't!
Mom, please!
Don't go outside!
- Here.
For you and Gar.
- [sighing]
- Now, sweetie...
your mommy has to go away
for just a little while.
- No! Don't!
- When I return,
I'll be bringing
your father back with me.
I promise you.
Wait 'til then, okay?
- [gasps]
- [coos]
- [giggling]
- Mom, I--
[gasping]
That's a lie. That's wrong.
You left to find a life
that would make you happy.
- FREDERICA: No.
- Huh?
- She wasn't being selfish.
Mother loved us both
dearly, Garf.
The only reason
she left the Sanctuary
was to better her family.
So what's the matter, then?
Don't you
feel content with that?
- Like hell, she did!
What a load of crap!
If she loved us,
then why did she--
- It probably
made things easier for you
to believe
that she didn't love us.
If you thought
your feelings were one-sided,
you could justify
the pain it caused you.
- No! No! Wrong!
You don't even understand!
When Mom leaves this place,
she's gonna--
- You're speaking
as if I don't already know.
- Huh?
- There's no way I wouldn't.
If Mother was unlucky enough
to meet with misfortune
after leaving here,
don't you think Grandmother
would inform us
about something like that?
- Then why?
Explain to me what happened.
- Surely you must know
why you weren't told about this
at such a young age.
But you're much older now,
so it's time for you
to hear things frankly.
- [sobs]
- In truth,
you wanted to forget,
but you remembered that Mother
loved you, didn't you?
You have that scar
on your forehead
because you wanted
to forget her kiss.
You needed to make it disappear,
so you gave it to yourself.
- [crying]
- This is the end,
the end of your past.
- Wait.
No, wait a minute!
What happens now?
What am I supposed to do?
- If you rely on your sister
for guidance
even when she's still so young,
you'll never find your answer.
- Listen, I know
it might seem pathetic,
but you're the only one
I can count on.
So, please...
- Now tell me.
What do you want to do, Garf?
- [gasps]
[sighs]
- I want to know.
What do you want to do?
- Exactly what it is
that I'm expected to.
- Go on.
Who has these expectations?
- Everyone, all the people,
the ones in my life who need me.
I want to be there
for each of them.
- I see. And what is it that's
bringing this feeling about?
[no audible dialogue]
- It's because they...
they made me remember...
something precious...
that Mom
really loved me after all.
- [laughs]
EMILIA: Is Ryuzu Shima
the older sister
or the younger one?
How does this work?
- Uh, it's actually
kinda confusing,
so let's save it for later.
[all gasp]
- [gasps] Young Gar!
You okay?
So about what happened,
you see, we did not--
- Don't make that face,
old hags,
'cause it don't suit you.
[both gasp]
- I made you worry,
and I'm sorry.
[both cry]
RAM: Garf, how did it go?
- Huh?
Well, honestly,
can't say I got much
you can really see,
but still,
I did get some answers
to a whole lot of things.
- [sighs]
- Right. Okay then,
let's do the rest
of the trial while--
- You can count me out on that,
'cause it ain't my job.
- He's absolutely right.
It's my job and mine alone.
Don't just hand it off.
- Uh...
yeah, I also wanna say...
I think the reason I was
able to take on the trial
was because of all of you guys,
so thanks.
- Wait. Did you
actually just thank us?
- I'm not gonna say it again!
Listen up!
I realize I lost, okay?!
Are you happy now?!
But if you guys
liberate this place
and the old hags suffer,
I won't go easy on you!
Understand?!
- Of course. You got it. Y-Yeah.
- Which means I'm gonna be here
watchin' your every move
to make sure
you're not just a bunch of talk!
So make sure you do it
and get it right, boss!
- [sighs]
- His face was pretty red,
wasn't it?
- Did he call me "boss"?
'Cause between the two of us,
you definitely outrank me.
- I bet you must feel as if
you've gained a new brother now.
You're older than he is,
so try to be lenient.
- Well, if that's the case...
Hey, wait a minute.
Are you tryin' to tell me
that Garfiel is
actually younger than I am?!
- Huh? Garf's only turning
14 years old this year.
- Huh?!
So he's just an eighth grader?!
Are you going?
- Yeah. If I stand around
too much longer,
I might lose my confidence.
Subaru...
about what happened earlier
when we were in the graveyard...
[sighs]
- Uh, what do you mean?
- You know, when we, uh...
- [sputters]
- Um, it really
meant a lot to me,
so when the trial
and everything else
is taken care of,
why don't we talk it over, okay?
- Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
[inhales]
[exhales]
Already talking about what
you'll do when it's finished.
You must be feeling
pretty confident, Mili.
- I don't know.
Maybe I'm only trying
to convince myself.
- I know it'll work out.
In fact,
I feel so sure of that,
I'll even bet
a date with you on it!
[chuckles]
- Yes, of course.
It's time for me
to be going now.
- Go get 'em. You can do it!
Watch out for cars and boys!
- [gasps]
Whatever that means.
[giggles]
GARFIEL: A giltylaw
that came one step short?
Can't be much of a man if you
keep lookin' all worried,
boss.
- The way you talk
makes a lot more sense to me
now that I know
you're in the eighth grade.
I rattled off
a bunch of famous quotes
- when I was your age, too.
- Hey, listen.
As long as I'm
turnin' over a new leaf,
there's somethin' I ought
to apologize to you for.
- Well, that's
very admirable of you.
Go on, then. You can talk
to your boss about
anything.
Oh, man. I'm embarrassed
even sayin' that.
- I saw you earlier.
- Huh?
- You know, when you, well...
got a little...
desperate?
["Memento" playing]
[chuckles]
- [gasps] Uh, oh, crap.
I completely forgot!
But I mean, I wasn't expecting
you to come in! Aww, man!
- Look...
- [wailing]
- that made me
realize somethin'.
You may be a complete
dumb ass--
and you gotta admit
you are one--
but if I had
to lose to somebody,
I sure am glad it was you!
- Just shut up!
- [laughs]
Forget you ever saw that, okay?!
You're not a kid,
so pretend you didn't--
- Wait. You are a kid! Agh!
- [laughs]
- You're such a dummy, Subaru.
SUBARU: Give it your best.
I know you can do it.
Puck and I
are both rooting for you.
When this is over,
let's go on a date.
He really is...
just the biggest dummy.
Dummy. Dummy.
You nincompoop.
How could you break your promise
to stay with me?
I'm never going to forgive you.
Well, not until you apologize,
that is.
ECHIDNA: Welcome back.
I've certainly had
a lot of visitors lately.
I must say,
it's awfully bold of you
to stroll in here after
that disgraceful display before.
Audacity like that
surprises even me.
You've proven to be
a pathetic and loose woman.
Kissing up to the first man
who offers to comfort you
when you're sobbing in despair,
a shameless fool who's soiling
the world that is mine alone,
a selfish hedonist
who hides her true self
and embraces the you
that he's forgiven.
Well, don't you have
anything to say for yourself,
witch's daughter?
- My name is Emilia,
nothing more or less!
And I was born in Eilor Forest!
I'm the Frozen Witch!
I won't give in to the
malevolence of a fellow witch.
After all, I'm quite
an insufferable woman.