- What? "Instead"?!
- Yeah.
- Where's the old hag?
- I wasn't sure
how all this would turn out,
so I asked her
to go somewhere else.
- Then why the hell
are you still hangin' around?
You wanna talk, but the one
you wanna talk to ain't here.
- That's true.
I suppose you could say
I'm buying some time
so a certain boy and girl
can be alone for a little while.
Understand?
- Huh?
- Oh, really?!
- [groaning]
- Piss off. Cause you ain't
got what it takes, small fry.
[growls]
[gasps]
The stone.
[yells]
Damn it.
[growls]
- Is this
what you're looking for?
A good merchant
always keeps one step ahead
to try and improve
his chances of success,
and that's exactly what I am.
- You little shit.
- [chittering]
- Eh?
- I've never had
very many human friends,
but I did happen to make lots
of nonhuman ones along the way.
- [growls]
- The entire forest
is against you now.
So enjoy this warm welcome
from the zodda bugs!
[buzzing]
- [sputters] Get--Damn it.
Go away!
Get off me!
[music playing]
[overlapping noises echoing]
OTTO: When I was a young boy,
the world around me
felt like a hellish cradle.
- [squawks]
[animal noises overlapping]
- No matter where I went,
I heard a barrage
of endless voices,
but I had no idea
what any of them were saying.
At such a young age,
I had no way of knowing
that this was the blessing
I was born with,
the soul-of-language
divine protection.
- [distant laughter]
- [faint] Hey. Wait up.
[animal noises overlapping]
I'm gonna get you.
- [faint] Otto,
what are you doing?
Don't you want
to play with them, dear?
OTTO: My parents did their best.
They tried their hardest
to understand our differences,
but for people who
don't have a divine protection,
that's practically impossible.
[animal noises overlapping]
[both gasp]
- Come on, Otto. You can do it.
- Eh?
[animal noises overlapping]
[grunts]
It was my brother,
seven years my senior,
who realized written words
might finally bring about
that understanding
when spoken words couldn't.
[animal noises overlapping]
- [shuddering]
- [gasps]
[Otto gasps]
[shudders]
[sighs]
[Mrs. Suwen crying]
Otto!
- [whimpers]
[sniffles]
[crying]
[sobbing]
That moment
might have been the first time
I'd cried out since I was born.
[music playing]
Later on, when I turned ten...
[gasps]
[woman vocalizes]
- [jabbering]
- Huh?
ZODDA BUG: Big light...
went that way.
OTTO: ...those
strange, random voices
started to transform
into sounds with meaning.
- You can understand
what animals say?
- Yeah.
ZODDA BUG: Rain fall soon.
Rain soon.
- They say it's gonna rain soon.
- Huh?
[gasps]
[thunder rumbles]
Otto, that's an amazing power,
and because it's so
amazing,
you should make it a point
not to talk to zodda bugs
when any people are around.
- Why not?
- A divine protection
is truly a gift,
but there are those
who could take advantage of it.
You have to keep
your power hidden.
- That's the reason
why I can't talk to you
around other people
anymore, Fulfew.
- As you wish, Young Master.
- [gasps]
BOY: Liar! Yeah, right!
- Just admit it.
- That's a lie.
- Try telling that to dumb kids.
- I'm not lying!
Big brother Otto,
he really can talk to animals!
- [gasps]
- Huh?
- Tell them it's true!
- Uh...
[grunts]
Zod wunasun zabada!
- [gasping]
- Huh?
- [chittering]
- [gasps]
- Whoa, it's true!
- Those are zodda bugs!
- Huh?
- Eh?
- [gasps] Look out!
It's a swarm!
[all screaming]
- You're such a little freak!
- [gasps]
After that, I sealed
my divine protection
and swore to myself
I'd never use it again.
Then when I was 15...
[groans]
- Admit it!
I know you were
with my girlfriend,
you little son of a bitch!
- W-Wait a minute. I--
- Shut up! Just stay away
from her, you freak!
- Th-This is all
just a misunderstanding.
I've gotta get
to the bottom of this.
- DOG: I saw.
- [gasps]
Eh?
- [meows]
- [sighs] Eh?
- [meowing]
[both meowing]
- [gasps]
[grunts]
- Listen up!
- Eh?
- I know the truth!
You're the eighth guy
she's been with!
[both gasp]
- You jerk!
I'll have you killed
for saying that!
[music playing]
I made an enemy of the daughter
of the most powerful person
in town, and they ran me out.
After that, I managed to find
true independence
as a merchant
and worked harder
than I ever had in my life.
I made up my mind,
setting a goal to run
a shop of my very own one day.
I knew I could do it!
I just
had to believe in myself!
[gasps]
[ground dragon bellows]
- Well, what do we have here?
And where exactly
are you off to in such...
a hurry?!
[ominous music plays]
[breeze echoing]
- [sighs]
- [blade scrapes]
- [gasps]
Huh?
- You're one lucky boy.
You know that?
You would've
been killed right here
if I hadn't found you first.
So if I were you, I'd show
my gratitude to the boss-kid.
- Wait. Do you mean
you've got a kid as your boss?
- That's exactly what I mean.
And he also happens to be
the guy who saved your
life.
- I-I understand.
Thank you very much.
And I should thank him, too.
Look, if you're gonna cry,
then you should cover your face.
No man should start blubberin'
in front of anyone.
- Huh? But I'm not...
[gasps]
Oh, man.
What is this?
It--It's...
[crying]
I-I'm so glad I didn't die.
It was then that I realized
every time I cry,
it marks a rebirth in my life.
My first one happened
as a baby after being born,
the second after
witnessing
my family's love for me
and realizing
where my heart is,
and this day, the third,
when I had a brush with death
and gained
an understanding of my purpose
and true reason for living.
[running footsteps crunching]
If I'm being honest about it,
I wasn't actually asked
to buy time this way,
but it's all in the name
of helping my friend!
[Garfiel roars]
[birds squawking]
Coming! Coming!
Bad one coming!
- Yeah, I already know!
ZODDA BUG: Right behind you.
Getting close.
- I said I already know that!
I planned for it, so
it's
all part of the
calculation!
HAMSTER: You're going to die.
Poor thing.
- Could you please stop
being so pessimistic
and have a little faith in me?!
[gasps]
["Realize" playing]
[panting]
Is this what happens
when I keep using my ability?
[gasps] This divine
protection of mine
can really be annoying.
I wonder if...
Mr. Natsuki's gotten a chance
to talk to Miss Emilia yet.
- [singing in Japanese]
- [groans]
[music playing only]
[groans]
[gasps]
- I found you, punk!
[yells]
[grunts]
- [groans]
[growls] Damn you!
- I was given a pretty exciting
role to play for once,
so I'm not gonna let you
catch me that easily!
- [growls]
[grunting]
- ♪ Realize ♪
[Otto coughing]
- [growls]
- Really?
I can't seem to catch a break.
- That's enough!
[yells]
- [sputters]
- I'm not lettin' you
pull any of that again!
Do you understand me?!
I-I wouldn't be so sure.
This fight isn't over
ye--[yelps]
- I told you.
It's not gonna happen!
But I gotta admit
you surprised me.
- [wails]
- I seriously never
would have thought that you
had it in you, Otto.
[winces]
Guess you're just
gonna have to forgive me
for doing something
so shitty to a man.
- At this point, I think
I've done about all I could do.
- Give me the stone back.
You hear me?!
I'm finished
playing games with you!
- [groans]
- [sighs] Well, all right, then.
When you wake up,
this entire thing'll be o--
- Let's just say
that my personal battle
might end here,
but it's far from over.
- [gasps]
- Ram, no!
- El Fula!
- Cocky bitch!
- Not that I didn't know,
but you're so pathetic,
I couldn't watch.
- Come on. Isn't that comment
a little harsh
toward someone who just
gave everything he had fighting?
- You're still
moving and talking.
That's "everything"?
- I always thought maids
were supposed to be
sweet and reassuring!
- Did I miss something,
'cause it seems
like joinin' their side
means you're goin' against
what that bastard
Roswaal wants, aren't you?
- I'd give my very soul
to fulfill my master's
fondest desire. However...
I'll do it in my own way.
- Now cut the shit already!
What exactly
do you think is happenin'
while you're keepin' me
held up out here, anyway?!
I mean, you don't
honestly believe
he's worth trustin'
that much, do you?!
OTTO: Is Mr. Natsuki worth it?
If we're talking about whether
he's much of anything as is,
- I suppose not.
- Huh?!
- But I look forward to seeing
what flowers bloom from him,
so I keep pruning
and brushing off the bugs.
At least, that's
the best analogy I've got.
- Hmph. Is that so?
Quite frankly, I have no idea
what's giving you
such high hopes for Barusu.
He's weak, useless,
completely incompetent,
and he can't even make
a decent cup of tea.
- That's going a bit far,
but it's not like I can say
that you're wrong.
- Although when things
are do-or-die,
he does have
extraordinarily good timing.
- [gasps]
- [growls]
- If nothing else,
Barusu has that going for him.
Despite the situation,
if he believes
he sees an opportunity
and acts on it,
then rest assured that's
the only path to victory.
- Guess when
all's said and done,
you trust Mr. Natsuki as much
as I do, don't you, Ram?
- "Miss Ram."
- [gasps]
Just because you feel awkward,
don't take it out on me!
- That's it!
[roar echoing]
[growls]
- Keep your distance.
- Wait! Ram, don't!
- [roaring]
[groans]
- As a reminder,
you haven't even beaten me
one time in a fight.
- [snarls]
- No way.
- [groaning]
- [gags]
- [gasps]
- It seems you've gotten
stronger, haven't you,
Garf?
- [roaring]
- [yells]
- [grunts]
- [roaring]
- [yelps]
[Garfiel grunts]
- Al Fula!
- [shriek echoes]
- I'm counting on you, Otto,
so please
don't do anything crazy.
Now...
it's time for me to do my part.
[breeze echoing]
[footsteps echoing]
Ah, good. I finally found you.
- [gasps]
Subaru?
[breeze echoing]
- You really thought
this through, didn't you, Mili?
You knew
that no one would find you
if you holed up in this place.
- Why--why are you here, Subaru?
You don't...
- "...get forced back
as hard as Roswaal."
- Is that it?
- [gasps]
- I mean, I'm here,
as you can see,
but I'm fighting
pretty hard to hang on.
- Is that so?
- When I left for this place,
half of me
believed you'd be here,
and the other half
just wished for it.
- Half and half.
- I'm so relieved
that I found you.
- Just relieved?
- Huh?
- Does this mean
you're not angry?
- Hold on.
What are you talking about?
Were you actually afraid
I'd be mad at you?
Well, I'm not.
Though I did panic,
and frankly,
I wasn't even sure I was alive.
- I see.
You're not angry.
- Emilia?
- After what's happened,
you don't feel that way at all.
You won't even get angry at me.
Why? Why won't you, Subaru?
What I did was really selfish,
wasn't it?
It caused you trouble,
didn't it?
I left on my own
and then didn't tell you.
Are you not angry
'cause you knew better
than to expect anything?
You're this kind to me
even when I mess up,
because it doesn't faze you.
You're not even disappointed,
are you,
because you know
I'll never do anything right.
- Is that it?
- Emilia, wait a second.
That couldn't be farther
from the truth, I swear!
- Then why?
I don't get it.
Why didn't you
keep your promise to me?!
- [gasps]
- You and Puck,
you broke your word
and went away.
[crying] You headed out,
and then you left me
behind.
You're a liar.
Puck is a liar.
Both of you.
You lied.
- Emilia.
- You shouldn't break a promise.
Why would you do that?!
It's just wrong!
[sobbing]
- Listen to me.
I love you so much, Emilia.
- Huh?
[gasps]
- Night after night,
you rush into
the same damn trial, don't you?
And all it amounts to
are some scenes from your past.
There's no need for you
to keep moping about stuff
that's over and done with.
When I tried to do it for you,
you told me no
and said only you could do it,
so when you blow it, that
just means you were all talk!
- [gasps] Subaru.
- And then when your guardian
and pet takes off,
you abandon your duties
and run off to sulk
and cry your eyes out?
Sorry, but I just
can't put up with it anymore!
- [gasping]
You're right to say that.
And if I'm being honest,
it makes sense
why you'd think of me that way.
- Still...
I truly love you, Emilia,
completely.
- [gasps]
- And I won't ever
stop loving you.
I care about you so much,
I don't know
what to do with myself.
- Wh-Where did this come from?
- I love that beautiful
silver hair of yours
and those sparkling purple
jewels you have for eyes.
I love your voice and how
just hearing it mesmerizes me.
Your slender arms and legs
and your porcelain skin,
even your height
is something so perfect to me,
I can hardly stand it.
Just being with you
makes my heart race.
It's scary, honestly.
I love how you're
a little absent-minded, too,
the way that you try
to give everything your all,
and I respect how you always
do your best to help people.
It's hard to leave you alone
when I see you
putting others before yourself.
I want to see all the beautiful
expressions you make
from right here beside you.
- Th-This is no time for--
Stop playing around!
Why are you
suddenly telling me this?!
It has nothing to do
with what we were talking about!
You were saying I'm
completely useless, remember,
and that you
couldn't put up with me!
- You're right about that.
- So what would make you
ever forgive me
for being so hopeless?
- I've already answered that
over and over again!
Listen to me very closely!
It's because I love you!
- [gasps]
- That's not gonna change!
In my eyes, every single thing
about you shines like the sun!
Yeah, of course there are
parts
of you that aren't perfect.
You're not an angel
or a goddess.
You're an ordinary girl.
You'll feel so bad
you want to cry sometimes,
and you'll want to run away
from things that hurt!
I get that!
But even with those weaknesses
and the parts of yourself
you might even consider ugly,
I love every fiber
of your being, Emilia.
- [gasps]
That's just...
too selfish!
You named all the things
that make me worthless,
and you still say you love me?
How am I supposed
to believe you?!
- No, you're wrong!
You've got everything
completely wrong!
So I'm going to make this
crystal clear.
It's not because I
believe in you that I love you.
Don't you understand?!
I believe in you
because I love you!
- Just feeling that way
isn't a reason
to believe in someone!
- [gasps]
Then if that isn't enough
to have faith in you,
why don't you tell me who
in the hell would voluntarily
go through all this
never-ending pain and suffering
to come and help a gigantic
pain in the ass like you are?!
I love you so much,
it makes me crazy!
It's never-ending!
I love you so much I could die!
That's why I put up with
everything that comes with it!
Even now,
I feel like I might puke,
but I'm still
standing in front of you!
- [gasps] Wait a second.
I never asked you to do that!
As far as I'm concerned,
you're only being selfish
and narrow-minded!
You're not thinking
about me at all!
You have no idea how I feel
every time that I see you,
see you out risking your life
and getting hurt
just because of me!
- Well, how would I
even know that?
I don't think about it!
What I do think about is
how to look good in front of you
and be a hero in your eyes!
I am absolutely
suffering for you here!
'Least try to look as cute
as I hoped you would!
- Don't talk
like I'm just some doll!
Why did you break your promise?!
If you'd just done
what I asked you to,
then that would
have been enough!
Why wouldn't you even do that?!
The truth is
you really hate me, don't you?
- 'Course not!
- You're a liar!
- Listen! I love you!
- Then...
why?
Why did you break your promise?
- [sighs]
I can't say.
If you'd stayed with me
until morning
like you said you would...
I think--I think
I could have believed you.
I could have believed you and
entrusted you with everything.
But you just abandoned me.
[sobbing]
Since Puck left...
I've been
slowly regaining my memories,
things in my mind
I don't recognize,
conversations I don't recall.
More and more of them
keep coming back.
I thought
I remembered everything
- this whole time, but...
- [song playing in
Japanese]
- I went and
forgot them entirely,
like they never existed at all.
When the memories
finally return,
then what will I become?
Is this me, really me?
I forgot
so many important things.
I even failed
to remember my mother.
And yet I'm not wrong?
How is that possible?
- [gasps]
NAHOKO: What matters
isn't how you start
or what happens in the middle.
It's all in how it ends.
SUBARU: Yeah.
You're absolutely right, Mom.
No matter
what memories you get back,
it won't change anything,
'cause I'll love you
just the same,
and I always will.
- [crying]
I can't believe that.
If the me--If the me
you say you love...
if she goes away,
are you still going to feel--
- I am.
And regardless
of what might happen,
I know you're
not gonna go away.
I'll love you
'til my last breath.
- Just stop it. You're a liar!
All of this time, you've done
nothing to make me believe you.
- Okay, then I'll
make you believe me now.
- [gasps]
What are you...
- If you don't want this...
then dodge.
[song continues]
I love you.
No matter what you say or do,
even if we argue like this,
nothing will ever happen
to make me stop caring for you.
I'll feel this way
until the end of time.
I will love you more every day.
And you have my word that I
will always believe in you.
By now, you should know why.
- 'Cause you love me?
- With all those unfamiliar
memories flooding your mind,
it's only natural that
you'd
feel anxious and
scared.
But every single one of them
is a part of you...
so I know that you're
gonna be just fine.
- But how?
How can you be so certain?
- What matters
isn't how you start,
but how it ends.
The woman I respect
more than anyone in the world
told me so.
You'll be okay, Emilia.
I'll be right here by your side.
Feel free to remember it all.
And if you're still afraid,
don't be.
We'll find it.
- What do you mean? Find what?
- In the same way
my feelings for you
make me able
to keep on moving forward,
you'll find
that most precious feeling
that makes you able
to blow away all your anxiety.
Then you can keep moving
forward.
And even though it might
come across as a little selfish,
I'm hopin' that feeling's
gonna be for me.
[chuckles]
- My most precious feeling, huh?
I wonder,
maybe it's among all these
memories I've been getting back
and it'll come to me.
- Yeah. I'm sure it will.
Your reason
to keep moving's in there.
- [gasps]
[music ends]
Yeah.
[leaves rustling]
- Hey. Sorry about the wait.
- Whatever. Ain't like
I was waitin' for you.