ECHIDNA: It's terrible.
And, no, I'm not referring
to your behavior.
I simply can't help
feeling overwhelmed
with a sense of rage
toward the one who put you
through so much hardship.
- Do you mean...
- Yes, the Witch of Envy.
- [shudders]
- I'm certain you're well aware
the power you possess
is undeniably that of a witch.
You've known for some time.
Thing is,
I've had plenty of people
tellin' me about a witch,
but I still don't have any idea
why she's gotten
so fixated on me.
- And why should you?
No one's capable
of understanding
just how her mind works.
Though, honestly, even
if
I could, I wouldn't want
to.
[cup rattles]
- Hey...
- Eh?
Do you think there's a limit
to how many times
I can use Return by Death?
- Ah, yes. I suppose that is
the obvious question to ask.
I'll tell you in advance
that I'm only
speculating...
but I would presume...
there isn't.
ECHIDNA: Vexing as it may be,
the power that lets you
Return by Death
is the witch's
intense delusion.
As long as that delusion
persists, so will your power.
- Do you have any clue
why she passed it on to me?
- I would assume
it's to keep you from dying.
It forces you
to redo your destiny
and doesn't let you
make any mistakes.
- In that case,
something's wrong,
because I...
[gasps] I still
couldn't get Rem back.
If she's making me
change the outcomes,
why am I stuck
where that's irreversible?
- Because she was
never taken into account
as a part of your destiny.
- Huh?
- The Witch of Envy,
she hopes you will
never be trapped
by the dead end
that is true death.
Anyone who is not you
isn't a part of that plan.
The decision
to use the witch's power
to save someone else
is yours and yours alone.
- [gasps]
- You'll overcome destiny
through countless challenges
from this point on.
However, if you manage
to change its path
at the expense
of too many sacrifices...
- Then I won't have
a chance to get back
the ones who were sacrificed
in the process.
- I'm afraid
that's just how it is.
[faint singing]
[vocalizing]
- All right, fine.
If that's how it's gonna be
and you're reserving that favor
for me alone,
I know what I have to do now.
I'll use this Return by Death
power that you gave me
'til there's
nothing left to use!
Yeah, that's it.
I've made up my mind.
I can betray expectations
like a pro!
There's nobody
who does it better!
- You certainly bounced back
with a surprising
amount of ease.
- It wasn't easy at all.
Normally, I would've just
tried taping my broken
heart
back together
out of pure desperation,
but this time around, I...
[sighs]
- [chuckles]
Aren't you going to finish?
You can speak freely.
- Well? Go on.
- [grumbles]
Look, you know damn well
what I was gonna say.
Anyway, getting your input's
been really valuable,
and it helped me
make up my mind, too,
so thanks. I appreciate it.
- Just for that part?
That was all
you intend to thank me for
after sharing your deepest
and darkest secret with me?
- [gasps] Ah, shut up!
Think I've shown you
enough gratitude, all right?
You should be trying
to make me ask you questions,
like the last time I was here!
I'll pay whatever you want,
'cause you're the only one
who I can depend on.
- [sighs] All right.
I'm convinced you must have
some kind of knack
for seducing witches
So what would you like
to ask me, then?
- There's still
so much I don't know,
but first and foremost would be
what happened earlier...
when I died by being eaten.
Those rabbits
could've fit in my hand.
- Ah. You mean the Great Rabbit.
- How's it called that?
- In this case, it's great
not in size, but in number.
It's but one
of the Three Great Mabeasts.
- Wait. The what?
- There's the White Whale,
the Black Serpent,
and the Great Rabbit.
They were created 400 years ago
by Daphne,
the Witch of Gluttony.
They're her legacies
of misfortune
that still wreak havoc
upon the world.
- You've gotta be kidding me.
I only recently managed
to take down the White Whale.
- There's more
to this unpleasant story.
In terms
of overall fighting strength,
the White Whale
is definitely stronger.
However, the Great Rabbit
is infinitely
more difficult to eliminate.
To its way of thinking,
other living things
serve only as food,
and its single desire is merely
to keep satisfying that hunger
until all that's left behind
is a deserted field.
- If that's what happens,
then...
everything that I saw was...
- What makes the Great Rabbit
so resilient is its viability.
A single one is capable
of multiplying indefinitely.
- Indefinitely?
What is it, an amoeba?!
- To truly eradicate
this creature,
you would have to kill
every one of them
at exactly the same time.
That would be
like trying to evaporate
each raindrop as they fall
from the sky
simultaneously.
- All we can do is run, then.
Hang on. That won't work,
'cause the barrier's there.
As long as it is, Emilia
and the others can't leave.
The Great Rabbit
in the Sanctuary,
the attack on the mansion...
I have to break the barrier
and free them
before any of that happens.
Then I'll gather everyone
at the mansion
to defeat Elsa
and the mabeasts. So I have...
ELSA: Though,
since you came back
sooner than anyone expected,
this didn't play out exactly
as my directions specified.
- Four days? Shit.
[gasps]
Echidna, do you know
if there's a way?
- The risk is so substantial
that I hesitate to suggest it.
But what if I told you
I could give you an opportunity
to spend time speaking
with Daphne,
the Witch of Gluttony?
- Huh? I thought you told me
all the other witches are
dead.
- You do realize you're
talking
to one right now, don't you?
In this castle of dreams,
the souls of the dead witches
reside within me.
In other words...
- You're saying
you can call her out here?
- I'd let her
temporarily inhabit my presence.
During that time, the two of us
would quite literally
trade places.
- [gasps]
- But I must tell you
I don't recommend it.
In the dimension we're in now,
there is no death,
but if your mind sustains
an injury causing it to break,
it will remain shattered even
after you return to your body.
- Do you mean I'd become
some kind of invalid?
That's a way bigger risk
than I'd be taking outside.
- Do you decline, then?
- [sighs]
Well, she did create
the Great Rabbit,
so if I wanna know
how to defeat it,
she'd be the best one to ask.
[inhales]
All right, do it.
- If you're sure
about this, fine,
but I just need to tell you
one thing first.
No matter what you do,
never release
Daphne's restraints.
- Her what?
- In addition to that,
you are not permitted
to touch her,
and if possible,
you should avoid eye contact.
- Great. If I follow
all of these rules of yours,
she's gonna end up
thinkin' I'm a total jerk!
- Very best of luck to you.
- [gasps]
- Ah! We meet at last!
- Huh?
- Hold on.
What do you mean by, "Huh"?
You should know that saying
such a thing is very rude!
Hmph!
- So, you're a--
I mean, I take it
you're also a witch, right?
- Chidna already told you,
didn't she?
And you're...
Let's see here.
Baru! Yeah, that's it.
- Baru?
- Now tell me something.
Are you bad, Baru?
'Cause I've been wondering
about that this whole time.
- Am I bad?
- [grunts]
- Do you want me
to hold your hand?
Hang on a minute!
There's something
I wanted to ask you fi--
- [laughs]
- Okay, okay!
Fine!
- There is only one way
to pay for sins,
and that is through pain.
- Huh?
- Ah!
If you don't feel pain,
that means
you must not be a bad guy!
That's really great to know!
- [gasps]
[wailing]
- But it doesn't hurt, does it?
- You took my arm!
If you make too much noise here,
Chidna's gonna hate you,
for sure.
- You're a psycho!
G-Give it back!
- Sin is a dividing wedge
that nobody can escape.
- [grunting]
- You see yourself as a sinner,
even though you're really not
a bad guy at all. Is that it?
You have
such a good heart, Baru!
You poor thing.
Well, I guess that's really
all I came out here for.
And that would leave...
- First! To strike
all that defies reason!
Second!
Who cares about committing
every heinous evildoing?!
Third! Whether things
are ugly or beautiful,
if you're here
in this fleeting world...
don't ever expect
to make it back unscathed!
The strike of my fist
will restore the world!
My anger will follow behind
and cleanse it!
The fury of my two fists,
the frenzy of my rage,
they are the answers to it all!
- Why are you crying?
- I'm not crying!
I'm just angry!
That's right!
It's intense anger!
This is all Typhon's fault
for hurting you like that!
Stupid Typhon!
I hate this world
for making her do that,
- every bit of it!
- Uh...
I appreciate you saving me.
So who are you, anyway?
[sighs]
I'm the Witch of Wrath, Minerva!
But giving my name isn't
what's important right now.
- You just did, though!
- [groans] Listen up!
If you've learned your lesson,
then don't be careless!
Next time around,
I'll just heal everyone!
- Why'd you make it
sound like a threat?
[gasps]
What's going on here?
Typhon and Minerva?
This isn't what we agreed to--
[winces]
Oh, come on.
- Daphne has arrived.
What would you
like to ask me...
Subarun?
- [gasps]
- I'm here because
Chid-Chid asked me to come,
but I don't want to be
awake
any longer than I have
to.
so please don't drag this out
with dull conversation.
[sniffs]
Ah. Oh, no.
This scent might be
quite dangerous for me.
[bonds clanking]
- Wh-What the hell?
- My body is throbbing!
Oh, this is so hard to take!
You give off an odor
that I really, really love...
- [gasps]
- and it's making me
want to eat you.
[slurps]
- Gotcha.
Then why don't we
make this quick?
I wanna talk about the
Three
Great Mabeasts you made.
- Great Mabeasts, Subarun?
- Yeah, you know,
the White Whale,
the Great Rabbit,
and the Black Serpent
or whatever.
You did make them, didn't you?
- Oh, of course. I get it.
You mean the whale,
the bunny, and the snake.
- Now, why in the hell did you
make all those things, anyway?
- Huh? What was that again?
- You heard me! I wanna know why
you set those damn things loose
on the world!
Do you realize what they've--
Why did you do it?
What's the point in unleashing
monsters like that
in the first place?
- Ah, the White Whale.
It's very big, isn't it?
If people just ate it,
it would sate so many appetites,
- don't you think?
- Huh?
- And when it comes
to the Great Rabbit,
it can copy itself forever.
- [gasps]
- With those two around,
people could eat and eat.
No one would ever go hungry.
I'm saying
that your Great Rabbit
is the one eating everybody!
These mabeasts
are taking more people away
than they're feeding--
- Don't you think
it's a bit selfish
to try and eat another
without at least
considering the possibility
that the predator
might become the prey?
The same goes for you.
Now, wouldn't you agree
that everybody takes gluttony
much too lightly?
After all, the appetite
is the most important
of all the desires
that keep people alive.
Because even
if the heart is full
and the mind's
completely at ease,
people will die if they
don't eat something, right?
- Listen, I'll admit what
you're saying is partly true,
Even so...
- You'll understand,
too, sometime,
if you ever find yourself
starved to your very limit.
Then you'll see
just what sort of world
my bunny and I live in.
- If I told you I wanted
to get rid of your Great Rabbit,
would you give me
any tips on how to do it?
- The Great Rabbit
relies on its ability
to detect mana
to track down and find its prey.
- So you don't mind?
- We must all eat
to stay alive, correct?
Knowing that
is an absolute truth.
It wouldn't make any sense
to deny
that we must kill to survive.
The Great Rabbit
is naturally drawn
to places
that have a lot of mana,
so you could use a powerful
magic user as a lure,
then wipe them all out at once
when they gather there.
- But it can multiply
over and over,
so won't there be some
that separate from the group?
- There may be
quite a few of them,
but they all share
one consciousness.
They don't have the wisdom
to avoid being killed,
so it won't make a difference.
[yawns]
I'm getting really sleepy.
- Are you finished with me now?
- Yeah, sorry.
I still don't get
why you created those things,
but I've learned a lot.
Thank you for the help.
But just know...
I will destroy the Great Rabbit.
I already killed
the White Whale.
You'd better not come crying
to me like a grieving mother.
They've run wild
for over 400 years,
and that's
more than long enough.
I'll wipe them all out
without a trace.
- If you think a human...
[bonds clanking]
is capable of such an act,
then go ahead and try it.
- [gasps]
[gasps]
Man, seeing your face
is such a relief.
It's almost like being
back home with family.
- That's a rather confusing way
to describe it,
but honestly,
I was disconcerted, too,
when Typhon jumped in
the moment I tried
to give my body to Daphne.
- Oh, you were, huh?
- Yes, the Witch of Pride,
just a child, as you saw.
- She was so eager to meet you
that she jumped right out.
- [groans]
- And the one who saved you,
that was
the Witch of Wrath, Minerva.
- Uh...
- So, then,
did the time
you spent with Daphne
bring forth
any useful information?
- Sorta, yeah. First of all,
I learned that,
compared to those other witches,
you are definitely
the most normal one.
- Oh, please. Just stop.
That's quite enough.
I can tell
that you're only trying
to butter me up
with those pleasing words.
Don't go underestimating me
like that.
- Man, you don't have
a filter at all, do you?
Anyway, think I'll pass
on the bodily fluids
and cookies.
- It's not like I put
a hair in it or anything.
- You may be
the most normal witch,
but I still can't trust
a single thing you say.
[gasps]
What the...
- Well, it would appear
that it's almost time
for you to wake up now.
Perhaps there's something
outside rousing you faster.
[wind blowing]
[vocalizing]
- You're talking
about Emilia, aren't you?
Hang on a minute.
How could I have forgotten this?
Weren't you the one
passing yourself off
as the examiner for the trial?
So why are you here, then?
She ought to be going
through it right about now!
- Because frankly the end result
is already in sight.
- And what exactly
is that supposed to mean?
- It means
I have no interest at all
in the outcome of her challenge.
After three days
of trial and error,
I can't hold out hope that
she'll break out of her shell.
So maybe...
you could go through it instead?
Since you've decided to continue
repeating everything,
perhaps you would
consider giving wings
to the cowardly princess?
- I can't stand that I'm
letting you provoke me,
but I am not gonna let you
make Emilia cry any more.
- Oh, no. You're mistaken.
I'm not the one making her cry.
- Yeah, whatever.
I'm going through
that sadistic trial of yours.
That was my whole plan
from the beginning.
- I really don't think
it's necessary
to refer to my trial
as sadistic.
- Tell me. How can I
come back here again, Echidna?
- What?
- I know that I'm being selfish,
but you've helped me out a lot,
and there's a good chance
I'll need more of it.
You have so much information.
And besides...
- I know all about your
secret Return by Death power.
- That's right. Exactly.
- I have to admit it feels nice
to be depended on,
but I think that would be
a rather difficult request
for me to fulfill.
The conditions
to attend my tea party
grow stricter each time,
and as I'm sure you're aware,
you've already
been invited twice.
If you cry out,
"I want to know,"
from the bottom of your heart,
rest assured
your voice will reach me,
but it must be even louder
the third time
than the second one.
Think you can do that?
- [sighs]
- Then again,
if you undergo the trial,
as you've already
committed to doing,
that won't be the only way.
- [gasps] That's right!
I can see you
while I'm in the trial, too!
I doubt our conversation
will be over tea, though.
- Well, if you truly insist,
I can al--
- Nope! That's totally fine.
[gasps] Whoa. Holy crap.
I'm starting to feel
pretty lightheaded right now.
Oh, one more thing before I go.
- Hmm?
- The payment to make sure
I don't forget
what happened here,
you need that, don't you?
- Oh! Of course, the payment.
So this time,
you won't leave and forget.
Let me see.
I think I'll take that.
- Really? You sure?
I mean,
it's only a handkerchief.
Besides, I swore that I would--
- No need for you to worry.
This world exists
within the mind,
which means the physical one
won't be gone
when you're back outside.
- Right.
How does it serve
as your payment, anyway?
- The one
who gave you this token
did so out of heartfelt concern
for you, correct?
It would be wrong
to ridicule that sentiment.
This payment is recognition
of their existence
and perhaps
a bit of meddling as well.
[woman vocalizing]
- [gasps]
- Now it's done.
- [groans]
[sighs]
Okay, thanks again.
See you in the trial, I guess.
- Subaru Natsuki...
if you do attend the witch's
tea party for a third time...
- Huh?
- remember this.
During our conversation,
there'll be
something in particular
I'd like to tell you.
- [coughing]
Do I always
have to go through this?
I remember.
I guess Echidna managed
to keep her promise, then. Good.
I swear, that so-called witch
is just a big fraud.
Thanks again.
I'll be counting on you.
Eh?
So Emilia wasn't the one
who was waking me up?
Hold on a second.
She didn't panic
and run outside, did she?!
[running footsteps echo]
Huh?
[energy warbling]
[women vocalizing]
A shadow?
Hey, Emilia!
Where are you?!
Please, answer me!
Ram! Ryuzu! Otto!
You're there, right?!
Say something!
- [shadow whooshes]
- [gasps]
[faint moaning]
- I know you.
- I love you. I love you.
I love you.
- [gasps]
- I love you.
I love you. I love you.
- [vocalizing resumes]
- I love you.
- [whimpering]
I love you.
[soft moaning]
GARFIEL: All right!
Quit screwin' around!
- [gags]
- We're gonna jump!
- [gasps]
[shadow whooshing]
[Garfiel grunting]
- [coughs]
Of all people...
- What's that?
If you got some kind of problem,
then you better tell me now.
- Uh...
no, I don't have a problem. I--
I guess I just wasn't
expecting
you to save me. That's all.
- Can't you see
what's goin' on here?
The important thing right now
is findin' a way to bite off
that damn thing's head,
nothin' else!
- What the hell is this?
And why now, of all times?
Answer me! What the hell
are you doing here...
Witch of Envy?!
Think, damn it!
You have to come up with a way
to try and keep her
from destroying everything!
You have to beat her somehow!
- Hang on.
So that creepy-ass bitch
isn't tryin' to follow us?
[chorus vocalizing]
What?
She's gonna leave the barrier?
- [gasps] It's the mansion.
That must be it!
That witch isn't stopping
until she gets
to Roswaal's mansion!
- The hell'd you say?
- It ends now.
I'm not gonna let you do this!
["Memento" playing in Japanese]
ROSWAAL: Goodness me.
What terrible luck.
And here I am, not even knowing
the outcome of the trial.
If you wish
to walk through Hell,
then I will
gladly accompany you.
If instead,
you wish to live in Hell,
then I'll make certain
that is what I strive for.
One request.
No mistakes next time...
Subaru Natsuki.