[metal clanging]
- [yells]
- Wonderful.
You're simply wonderful.
- Hearin' that from anybody
but Ram don't make me happy!
[yells]
[groans]
[gasps]
- [chuckles] You're amazing.
[metal scrapes]
- I told you,
I don't wanna hear it!
[chorus vocalizing]
- Yo, Big Sis!
- [gasps]
- Why you still standin' there
like some kind of damn statue?
- Sorry. I just--
- Now don't forget,
the boss is countin' on you
to do your part, too,
so do it, all right?
[metal clanging]
- [grunts]
- [yells]
- I believe in you, Garf.
- Damn straight, you do!
- [chuckles]
- [yells]
[yells]
[winces]
[grunts]
[door closes]
[running footsteps]
Looks like Big Sis
finally got movin'.
[blade slices]
- [chuckles]
I am the Bowel Hunter.
[slurps]
My name is Elsa Granhiert.
- And I'm the strongest
damn shield in the Sanctuary.
The name's Garfiel Tinzel!
[grunts] My first big battle's
gonna be one hell
of a show, Boss.
And that means you better
be doing your part, too!
BEATRICE: Why are you here?
SUBARU: I'm getting you
out of here, Beatrice.
But this time, things are
gonna be different than before,
'cause I intend to drag you out.
We're heading into the sunlight
to play in the mud
until that dress of yours
is covered in it.
- You're what?
Getting me out of here?
Mind your own business,
I suppose.
No one asked for you to do
such a thing in the first place.
- We don't have time
to argue about this, all right?
'Cause in case
you haven't noticed,
things are
gettin' bad out there.
- Do you mean the intruder?
I'm aware, I suppose.
But this is a great spirit's
forbidden library.
No matter
what threats exist outside--
- No, you're wrong.
I know that Door Crossing
only works on closed doors,
and she does, too.
- Now, how does the enemy
know that particular weakness,
I suppose?
- [murmurs]
- Because Roswaal told her,
didn't he?
- [gasps]
- So that's how it is, huh?
Then this means
my demise was written
in Roswaal's Tome of Wisdom,
I suppose.
[sighs]
- H-Hold on.
Why do you have
that look on your face?
I accept that my fate's
already set in stone.
- Seriously?
Does that book of yours
say you have to let
that psycho kill you?!
- It doesn't say anything,
I suppose.
My destiny's blank,
just as it's always been.
- Then this
"already set in stone" crap
doesn't make sense!
Why let yourself end up
the way Roswaal wants?!
Come on. Why don't you decide
for yourself what you wanna do
the same way
that you always have before?
- Decide for myself?
I'm not sure what you mean,
since I can't ever remember
a time when I've
actually done that.
I've continued
to obey Mother's orders
throughout my stay here
at this mansion all alone.
What part of this
did I get to choose?
What has this Beatrice done?
Who is she?
- Uh, Beatrice, I...
- My life is pure white,
I suppose.
It's completely blank,
well and truly.
This one book
was really all that I needed.
After all, I do have a soul.
As time passes,
I think about so many things.
I worry and cease to believe,
I suppose.
There were moments
when I couldn't remember
Mother's smile,
so I scraped
all my memories together
and did whatever I could
to try and cling to them.
Sometimes I was afraid!
I was scared to be alone
and longed for companionship!
But everyone--
everyone just leaves me behind,
Mother and Roswaal...
and Ryuzu also!
- [gasps]
- The spirit Beatrice
is fated to be alone,
meant to be left behind
by everybody else forever.
- But...
- [gasps]
- I do feel a tiny bit
relieved now, I suppose.
If it's true
that I was mentioned
in the Tome of Wisdom,
then I feel relieved,
'cause that's definitive proof
Mother didn't forget
about me after all.
- [gasps]
- Give me a break.
- Huh?
Listen to yourself.
You're such a fool.
You know that?
This is pathetic!
I can't stand it anymore!
- [stammers]
- You've had 400 years!
Why is something so extreme
the only answer
you could come up with?!
Haven't you ever even once
considered the possibility
that your mother gave you
the wrong book by mistake?!
- You would dare insult Mother,
I suppose?!
She would never make
such an idiotic blunder!
- Oh, yeah? What makes you
so sure about that?
With all her powers
and infinite wisdom,
you actually believe she
gave you a book about the future
that was completely blank?
- That's not--
Must you put it that way?
What exactly is it
that you're trying
to get me to say, I suppose?
- Okay, I'll come
right out with it then,
and I hope your stupid mother
can hear it, too.
Don't let something
like a blank book
and a 400-year-old promise
rule your life forever,
because you're better than that.
You can choose what you want
to do for yourself, Beatrice.
You know you can!
- [sighs]
- 400 years? After that long,
I'd say you've
more than earned the right
to have at least one
rebellious phase by now.
No matter what you tell me,
I'm still under a contract,
and it cannot be changed,
which means that--
- Pretty strange hearing this
from the one who tried
to find a back door out of it,
then wanted to die
when they couldn't.
If keeping a promise
means that you have to stop
living altogether,
then I'd rather break it
and keep you alive!
Is it so weird
that I'd make that choice
and try to save you?!
- Th-That's a very defiant
and selfish way to think,
I suppose.
- You're absolutely right.
It is defiant,
and it is selfish.
But...
I won't compromise
on something important to me.
- Is--Is it you?
If you really mean
what you're saying...
- [gasps]
i-if you're
really "that person,"
then would you be "that person"
for me, too?
- Have you lost your mind?
You've gotta be kidding me.
There's no way I could be
whoever "that person" is to you.
[yelps]
[groans]
Unbelievable.
[groans] She's such a moron.
Damn that loli and her
jumping to conclusions!
[running footsteps]
OTTO: Mr. Natsuki?
- What are you doing here?
You should be far away by now!
- I know, but mabeasts
are all over the place.
- Maylie.
We already accounted
for that, though!
- Even so, there's one
that this didn't work on at all!
[no audible dialogue]
- Seriously?
But how is that...
- [rumbling]
- [gasps]
[all gasp]
[both scream]
SUBARU: Petra!
FREDERICA: Don't move!
- Stay exactly as you are!
- [yelps]
[both grunt]
- Wh-What just happened?
- I'm sorry,
but it was an emergency.
You didn't get hurt, did you?
- [whimpers]
[crying] Big sister!
[Otto groans]
O-Ow!
First you save my life,
and then you drop me
flat on my face?!
- I-I sincerely apologize,
Mr. Otto.
The order of priority suddenly
became very clear to me.
- Yeah, it's the usual--
women, children, the elderly,
the men, and then Otto.
- Now you're just rubbing it in!
You didn't even put me
in the men category!
- Mr. Subaru,
I brought her along with me,
just as you had requested.
- So you did.
I appreciate you
getting her out safely.
And I mean that.
Thank you so much.
- I only did
what had to be done.
But it appears
there's another matter now.
[ominous music playing]
- [snorting]
[growling]
- [gasps]
MAYLIE: Wow, I'm so amazed!
I honestly couldn't believe it
when none of you died
in the middle of all that.
SUBARU: Maylie.
- Wait. That's it?
You don't really seem
too surprised to see me.
Well, how disappointing.
Anyway, I think it's time
for me to take those maids
off your hands, okay?
I promise to be
especially gentle with Petra.
After all, she's my friend.
PETRA: Y-Yay! I'm so glad.
If we're really friends,
how about just letting me go?
- And why would I wanna do that?
Because true friends play
'til the very end, right?
- Uh...
sorry, Subaru!
I did my best,
but it didn't work.
- [sighs]
[gasps]
- This little girl--
No, this little assassin
needs to be taught
a lesson in decorum.
Get out of here.
I'll handle her.
- Y-You can't,
Big Sister Frederica!
I mean, what happened before...
I don't wanna lose you again.
- [gasps]
Don't worry, 'cause it'll
be much different this
time.
As you may remember,
previously I was
fully prepared to die.
- [gasps]
- But that isn't
how I feel anymore,
because now I've finally
been reunited
with my little brother Garf,
and I have
such an adorable assistant.
I've never known
greater happiness.
Understand?
So I'm not going to lose.
- [grunts]
- Okay, Frederica.
We'll make our way
up to Roswaal's room!
All right, then.
Do as you wish.
[Petra gasps]
- Wait a minute! You can't
just decide that yourself!
Come back, Petra!
- [grunts]
- [growls]
- Honored guest...
you are about to be enveloped
in the finest hospitality
the Mathers house has to offer.
- [wails] I won't let you
get away with this!
Attack! Get 'em, Rock Piggie!
- [roars]
- Please,
do feel free to come at me.
I'm in a bit of a mood,
and I'm feeling harsh.
Now get ready!
[all panting]
- What are we supposed to do?!
- I know that there's
a hidden escape route
in Roswaal's office!
We'll use that to--
Huh?
[mabeasts squealing]
- [gobbling]
- It's here!
OTTO: That's it, Mr. Natsuki,
the guiltylowe!
The mabeast ward
doesn't work on that one!
We're in big trouble!
- [roars]
- It was my teacher and I
who started it all.
That's the one little detail
you got wrong, Miss Emilia.
[energy surges]
- I've seen the past,
so next up should be...
[footsteps echoing]
[breeze echoing]
EMILIA:
Behold an unthinkable present.
[chorus vocalizing]
FORTUNA: Now, now, Lia.
Don't move your head around
like that.
Hold still, okay?
Honestly, what am I
gonna do with you?
- [gasps] Hmm?
Wait a minute. Is it really...
- [grunts] What's the matter?
Did you fall asleep?
[vocalizing continues]
- [gasps]
Uh, why are you so dressed up
today, Mother Fortuna?
Because you look so beautiful.
- Oh! I was wondering
what you were about to say.
Now don't tease grown-ups
like that.
- [laughs]
[sighs]
[vocalizing continues]
- There. Absolutely lovely.
- Thanks, Mother.
I appreciate it.
[sighs] Think I'll take a look.
[gasps]
- What's wrong, Emilia?
[knock at the door]
- [gasps] We've got a visitor.
- Miss Emilia.
Good morning to you.
It's awfully nice of you
to greet me at the door.
- I was just...
Good morning to you, Geuse.
FORTUNA: Right on time.
Well? Shall we go, then?
What is it?
- Well, I-I do hope
it doesn't offend you
to say this, but--
- How long
have we known each other?
I assure you,
there's nothing you can say
that would offend me, all right?
- Well, then, Miss Fortuna,
I think that outfit you're
wearing looks so lovely on you,
and if I'm being honest,
I find myself captivated by it.
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
GEUSE: I don't understand.
Was that rude?
EMILIA: Oh, no, not at all.
She just feels embarrassed.
Mother's so cute, isn't she?
- You can't just blurt out
anything you want!
Pretty mean-spirited
if you ask me!
- Ah! Miss Fortuna!
- And Emilia and Geuse
are with you, I see.
- You three are such
a close-knit family, aren't you?
- We're not--
- You're loved dearly
by so many.
- [whimpers]
Well, I guess that's true.
- [laughs]
GEUSE: Huh?
[Fortuna sighs]
[Emilia gasps]
[giggles]
[peaceful music playing]
[all laugh]
GEUSE: Isn't this nice?
[chuckles]
- Eh? Come on now, Lia.
There's more to being grown-up
than height, you know.
- [giggles]
- It would appear
that the two of you
are just as close as ever.
Simply watching you both
is so heartwarming.
- Why don't you join us, Geuse?
The three of us
could live together!
- [coughs]
- Uh...
- Emilia, you...
- Are you feeling all right?
- [gasps]
- Thank you for the offer,
Miss Emilia.
It's very kind.
And I wish
from the bottom of my heart
I could actually do so.
- I'm not sure what you mean.
Why couldn't you?
Is it 'cause I'd be in the way?
- No, not in the slightest.
- Oh, absolutely not.
- See?
You two get along so well.
- Miss Fortuna
has been entrusted
with a very important duty.
If somebody like myself
moved in and it led to rumors,
then that would be
rather problematic for her.
EMILIA: I think
it's too late for that, though.
Remember what Aunt Tanse
and the others
said to us on the way here?
We all looked
like a close-knit family!
- Uh...
I-I thought she was just
talking about you two, not me!
- You understood her,
didn't you, Mother?
- [sighs]
- Well, I think
it's a great idea!
Really, it would be wonderful!
And the people of the forest
won't think it's weird at all!
Every one of them
would support us.
In fact, I'd never let anybody
say it was a bad thing!
Okay. I guess
that about covers it.
So now I'll just leave the rest
of the discussion to you.
- [sighs] Honestly, Emilia,
where do these little ideas
of yours come from?
- [grunts]
[both gasp]
[both laugh]
- Oh, I swear,
you are way too cute!
- Yes, indeed.
Miss Emilia's grown up
to be so healthy and happy,
which brings me endless joy.
- She is my daughter,
someone I'm truly proud of.
- But of course.
How could she not be?
[both laughing]
EMILIA: Huh, that's weird.
I think I've got
something in my eye.
I'd better go wash it out.
- Oh, are you all right?
Just be careful not
to hurt yourself in the process.
You did get
those beautiful purple eyes
- from my brother, after all.
- I know.
And they're the same pretty
color as yours, too, Mother.
- Uh...
[chuckles]
- W-Wait for me, okay?
Don't leave,
and stay really close
forever and ever.
FORTUNA: Of course we will.
You're such a worrywart.
GEUSE: We'll wait
as long as it takes,
all right, Miss Emilia?
- [sighs]
I love you both...
so very much.
[birds chirping]
- Emilia?
- [gasps]
- It's dangerous for you
to be up here alone.
- Hello, Archi.
- I take it the bishop is
in the forest today, isn't he?
You're not with--
Eh?
He's over there, I see.
Were you
giving them some privacy?
- Mm-hmm. I was.
So what do you think
of the two of them?
- I think
they suit each other well.
Miss Fortuna has a tendency
to be quite harsh on herself,
and I just wish that she'd
give a little more thought
to her own happiness.
It may be difficult right now,
but with time, they could
find that bliss together.
- They won't.
- Huh?
- 'Cause such a world
doesn't exist anywhere, does it?
- Emilia...
- [sighs]
- Having beheld
an unthinkable present,
does living here not seem
a preferable alternative?
I'm certain that you wanted
the two of them to be happy.
This is your ideal present,
the future you've often
thought about and dreamed of.
- You're right. It is.
- Miss Fortuna
has already passed,
it's unknown if the bishop
is still alive,
and the people of the forest
are ice statues.
- Yes.
- Your homeland is frozen,
you're persecuted
by people from the outside,
and you had to say goodbye
to the spirit
who was like family to you.
- I know.
- But here, in this place,
you could live in happiness.
Seeing you continue to wish
for that other world
pains me greatly.
- I'm sorry, Archi.
- Why do you desire that future?
- I want to be
an admirable person.
- What do you mean?
- Like Mother Fortuna,
who's my role model,
or Geuse,
who's so kind and strong.
Like Archi, who kept smiling
until the very end,
- just so I wouldn't be scared.
- [gasps]
- Or Puck,
who always protected me
and never left me alone.
Like Ram, who wished
to do the one thing
that would be most helpful
for someone
who's truly precious to her.
Like Otto, who does
his very best for his friends,
or Garfiel, who never
once
uttered a word of
complaint.
Like Subaru,
who says he loves me
and does reckless things
even when he's
wounded and hurting.
I want to earn
the respect of each of them.
From now on,
I want to be the one
reaching out to help someone.
And I know
that I'll be just fine.
So I'm not afraid
of the outside world
or of what the future holds.
- [gasps]
- I understand
that you're worried.
But believe me, I'll be fine.
Thank you, Archi.
- [gasps]
[chuckles]
You're such a stubborn girl.
You know that?
And you don't have
any idea how crazy
you always made things
for Miss Fortuna and me.
- I, uh--I'm sorry about that.
- [chuckles] It's okay,
'cause after all, a big brother
should always spoil
his little sister.
Don't you agree?
- Thanks, Big Brother,
for everything.
And thank you.
You showed
this whole world to me...
Echidna.
I never thought I'd get to see
the two of them like that,
Mother Fortuna and Geuse,
Father Geuse,
laughing together and
spending time with each other.
So again, I appreciate it.
- You simply...
- [gasps]
What was that?
- You simply disgust me.
I just--
I hate you so much.
[mysterious music playing]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
- Don't come near us!
Go away, witch!
- Filthy woman!
- [gasps]
[sentimental music playing]
[gasps]
Just how much...
have I been protected by others
all this time?
[grunts]
[wind whipping]
Oh, look at that.
I don't resemble Mother Fortuna
half as much
as I thought I did.
Too bad.
[insects chirping]
What's this?
- [villagers murmuring]
- There she is!
- I'm so glad you're safe!
- You aren't hurt, are you?
- The margrave
was on the verge of death.
[Emilia gasps]
[sighs]
Thank you for worrying about me.
I'm perfectly fine.
I wasn't hurt at all.
- But I'm sorry.
- [villagers gasp]
- Turns out,
after all this time,
the trials
still aren't over yet.
Even so, Subaru and the others
probably told you
the news, right?
There's no reason
to keep each of you
here in the Sanctuary anymore.
I'm going to stay
and get rid of the barrier,
but you can go back
to where your families are
- and finally be--
- Mr. Subaru and the others?
Strange. I don't remember them
telling us anything.
Me, either. None of that
seems to ring a bell.
- Huh?
- As you can see, Miss Emilia,
we'll be waiting right here
as promised.
[sentimental music playing]
- [sighs]
- But we're far
from being the only ones
who have high hopes
for your success.
There are many others
who share that feeling.
- Huh?
Miss Ryuzu and the people
from the Sanctuary.
- Since you have emerged again,
it seems safe to assume you
have overcome the second
trial.
I must first offer
my gratitude.
And after hearing from Young Gar
about the situation,
as well as the villagers,
the voices representing
both the inside and the outside,
we were finally able
to get up and move on our own.
- In truth, we're struggling.
We can't make up our minds
about whether or not
we can trust you.
- [gasps]
- But we all heard Garfiel,
such a hardworking young boy,
shouting in anger.
When I thought about
how he must have felt,
I don't know. It--
It just makes me
feel so pathetic inside.
He's a child,
barely 14 years old,
yet he was bearing so much.
He's deserving of our praise.
And the same goes for you.
We're just--
All of us are in such awe.
So, please, let us bear witness.
- All right, fine.
I'll come through this trial
in one piece,
and after that, we'll sit down
and talk things over.
- Yes. It's a promise, then.
Whatever may--[yelps]
- You should be ashamed.
That was too long
and too serious,
and your tone kept bouncing
between polite and crude
the whole time.
- I-I'm really sorry
about that, Elder.
- Hmph.
Regardless, you have now heard
where we stand on the matter.
So this is--
Huh? What is that look for?
- Oh, uh...
when I heard him
referring to you as "Elder,"
I suppose it just sort of...
surprised me.
[villagers laughing]
- I'm still not satisfied
with this, but...
[chuckles] Thank you all.
Feels like I can do my best now.
- If we have been of help,
then we could ask
for nothing better.
I understand the next trial
will be the last, right?
- Yes, it is,
and I'm going to start soon.
But tell me,
do you happen to know
where Ram is, Miss Ryuzu?
- She had a task to do
that could not be put aside.
- Sounds serious.
She said, "Miss Emilia
has her job, and I have mine.
We will both see it through."
And then she left.
- [sighs]
[breathes deeply]
All right, then. I'm going in.
[villagers murmuring]
[breeze echoing]
EMILIA: Face the disaster
that is yet to come.
[music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I believe, I believe in you ♪