- Ryuzu Shima,
are you feeling okay?
- [moans]
- I believe I have explained
this before, Young Su.
Our bodies are in
a constant state of depletion,
the same way that the energy
of a spirit's is.
- I know there are
three of you Ryuzus
that always take turns,
but since you were removed
from the rotation,
there hasn't been a replacement.
- [moans]
I am unsure if I will be
able to make myself last
until Miss Emilia returns,
so I will go ahead
and say what must be said.
- Now hold on. You don't
have to push yourself like that.
The healthy old hag right here
can step in and--
- You're making this
way too confusing.
Just call them
Old Shi and Old Ryu!
Besides, I understand
what you're saying,
but in this case,
it wouldn't work.
Shima's the only one
who can tell us this.
Yes, that is correct.
Only I, the one
who has entered the graveyard
and attempted the trial,
can truly speak of it.
- Huh?
- The tale you are
about to hear now
concerns the memories
of Ryuzu Meyer,
the ancestor
we copies are derived from.
It involves events
that happened many years ago,
a long time before this place
became known as the Sanctuary.
At the beginning
of this unknown memory,
there was a young girl
with a lovely face,
with porcelain skin
as white as the snow
and very pale blue eyes.
- [gasps]
- What is it, I suppose?
You can look at me that way
to your heart's content,
but I'm not giving you anything.
- Uh...
- Hmph! Still silent, are we?
What a boring, cowardly girl
you are, I suppose.
[door opens]
- ECHIDNA: Beatrice...
- [both gasp]
why the negative attitude?
- Miss Echidna.
- What's gotten into you?
Did I teach you
to behave that way?
- Uh, I don't know what you're
going on about, Mother,
'cause I haven't
done anything at all.
It's just...
- this girl was...
- [gasps]
- Ah, I see.
Well, then why don't we listen
to what she has
to say for herself?
- What?
Um, well...
I, uh--
I'm sorry about this.
I saw her standing there,
looking so elegant and wistful,
and I was captivated.
- Oh, is that so? Interesting.
Well, Beatrice?
You did hear Ryuzu, did you not?
RYUZU: Huh?
- [moans]
- Referring to you as childish
wouldn't be accurate,
since you are a child,
but you've yet
to learn tolerance.
While there's no question
that you're rather special,
you don't have the right
to look down on others.
- [moans]
- I'm sorry
to have startled you.
This is Beatrice.
I suppose you could say
she's like a daughter to me.
- I'm not just
"like" a daughter to you.
I am your daughter, I suppose!
- Yes, well, there you have it.
I believe,
from this point forward,
she'll be accompanying me
here quite often.
Please do be kind to her.
- Yes, of course. You can
count on me, Miss Echidna.
- I don't need her.
If it's all the same to you,
I'm perfectly fine on my own.
SHIMA: And that was it.
That is how the two girls met.
Afterwards,
the witch and her daughter
visited the settlement
occasionally,
just as she said they would.
- [sighs]
- Why are you
just standing there, I suppose?
I see that you've remained
your usual dull self.
- Miss Beatrice.
- Mother's busy
having a discussion inside.
- She'll be back
when she finishes,
so hurry up, and put
that irritating laundry
in the basket, I suppose.
- Huh. Of course.
Excuse me.
Um, Miss Beatrice?
- Don't mind me. It's nothing.
I'm just killing time,
I suppose.
- Eh?
[grunts]
Miss Beatrice...
u-um, I was just curious.
If you don't mind,
I was wondering
if you would help me
fold the laundry.
- Huh?
- [gasps]
Oh.
- If it's too much for you
to handle alone, then fine.
I guess I have no choice but
to lend a hand with the
folding.
- Huh?
- I won't say it again,
I suppose.
Well, get going, then.
Let's go, I suppose.
Hmph! Hmph! Hmph! Hmph! Hmph!
- [panting]
U-Um, if it'd be all right,
as long as you're helping me,
would you carry
a little bit of it?
- Okay, listen.
I'm feeling generous,
but don't go pushing your luck.
Just this much, I suppose.
SHIMA: So during the moments
when the witch
had her own business
to attend to,
the young girl
would find herself
spending more and more
of her time with Ryuzu Meyer.
- You, there. Pardon me.
I do believe Miss Echidna
is here somewhere.
Have you seen her?
- What?
M-Mr. Mathers!
- My family name.
I'm not fond
of being addressed that way.
So with that in mind,
would you
call me Roswaal instead?
- SUBARU: Hang on a minute!
- [panting]
- Are you saying Beatrice
was in the Sanctuary,
and Roswaal, too?
- More accurately,
the Master Roswaal
of several generations ago.
But from the sound of it,
Miss Beatrice
hasn't changed that much at all.
- Yeah, yeah, look.
I'm more interested
in the witch.
I mean, sure, I know
this is the facility
where she was doin'
her experiments and everything,
but other than that,
I've never really heard
her story before.
- What? You didn't
run into her even once
when you were
going through the trials?
- The only reason I went in
was to settle a score.
She didn't cross my path.
When you put it like that,
it sounds like maybe...
- So can I assume you have
met the Witch of Greed, Barusu?
- Yeah.
- Huh.
- To one who was not alive
during that time,
I do understand the dilemma,
as the witch may indeed seem
quite out of reach.
Of course,
even my own memories
are actually those of another.
Therefore I do not
know her personally myself.
- Seeing one who looks
identical to me saying that
makes me feel as if I have
gone mad. How frightening.
- Okay, it is now official.
Things are getting
pretty surreal around here.
- Miss Beatrice continues to be
an exceedingly common presence
in the memories of Ryuzu Meyer.
Those two
had quite an interesting
and heartwarming friendship.
Go ahead,
and finish up the story.
This place seemed
so peaceful on the surface,
so what happened here exactly?
- Eventually it collapsed.
It was then that the true
reason
for the Sanctuary's existence
came along
and made itself known.
- Wait. The true reason for...
the Sanctuary's existence?
- [moans]
[ominous music playing]
I'm the Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's Cult,
representing Greed,
Regulus Corneas.
- Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's Cult?
GEUSE: What are you
doing out here?
I've already been given
the assurance that nobody
could ever get involved
with this forest except me.
- "Assurance," huh?
Well, I think you
completely fabricated that rule
and simply offered it
to yourself.
And now you're trying
to force other people
to go along
with this foolish notion?
I must admit that's pretty cocky
for a worthless spirit.
- If you truly dislike the rule,
then my suggestion would be
that you talk it over
with the church!
I ask again, why are you here?!
- WOMAN: Why?
- [gasps]
- It was something
I ordered him to do.
- [gasps]
[Emilia gasps]
- Do you have some sort of issue
with that command,
Bishop Romanée-Conti?
- Wait. No.
What is that woman doing here?!
I want you to answer me!
What is the meaning of this?!
- Hah! Take it easy.
This was entirely her choice.
Why are you blaming everything
on me, anyway?
You got something
against me or what?
- Easy, Bishop Corneas.
It would appear
that he's rather confused.
Do try not to be
so critical of him.
- [grunts]
Now bring the key and seal to me
so the Witch's Cult can fulfill
its long-cherished desire.
- Damn you, Pandora!
[ice rattles]
- What's this?
- Enjoy being skewered!
Apologize to my brother
and his wife!
Now begone forever!
REGULUS: Hey, come on.
You weren't even aiming
anywhere near me,
but you used
a crazy, wide-burst attack
that you knew would hit me, too?
I take such a careless affront
personally.
That's the same
as trampling on my life,
on my existence,
on my authority,
on my humanity itself,
now, isn't it?
[chorus vocalizing]
[both gasp]
- [grunts]
- Miss Fortuna,
please take Miss Emilia,
and leave this place.
- Mother, I'm scared.
- Don't worry, dear.
- It's all right.
Have no fear.
I wouldn't remain here
if I didn't have a plan.
- [grunts]
Okay, I'll do it.
But I'm coming back to help you!
- I swear it!
- No, wait! Geuse!
- Keeping the trial in mind,
I presume you'll be
following yourself, right?
Or will you?
REGULUS: Hey, that was
pretty admirable of you.
A shame, though.
No one gave you permission
to let them get away.
I consider you
acting out on your own
a direct violation
of my actions and authority.
- I don't need your permission.
And even if it means
risking my life,
I will never allow the two
of you to get past this point!
- Eh?
Wait. You're not
actually planning on...
- I must confess. I don't have
the knowledge to adapt to this.
For that reason,
I've merely held it
since I was entrusted with it,
but this moment
is what it was meant for!
- Well, then, Bishop
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti...
have a good journey.
- [shudders]
[energy humming]
Please, forgive me...
Master Flugel.
But it must be done!
- [energy humming]
- [gagging]
- [sighs] What an idiot.
- [clapping]
- [gasps]
[Geuse screaming]
- Truly magnificent.
Bishop Regulus Corneas.
- Yes?
Prepare yourself.
- Whoa!
[screaming]
- I told you, you witch.
What you're
witnessing now is hope,
a great debt,
an unforgettable one
to the people
who made me what I am.
I won't back down.
So if I'm worthy
of spitting up blood...
- After such a transformation,
I have to ask.
What do you see
with those crimson eyes,
Bishop Romanée-Conti?
Love itself.
You will go no further.
You will not pursue them.
I swear you won't
get past me, never!
[gagging]
- Geuse, what's happening?!
Wh-What did you do?!
PANDORA: A splendid show
of your determination,
Bishop Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti.
And in the name
of the Witch of Vanity,
for your resolve and
steadfast force of will,
I grant you the title of Sloth.
- Do you really think
I would want such a title?
There's only one thing
I desire right now,
peace for that mother
and her child
for the rest of their lives!
- Ah, yes.
Love. How wonderful.
- Keep that word
from your mouth.
Your lies are a warmth
that shouldn't come to pass.
Face me!
[rumbling]
- What is with you?
This is far beyond
even my comprehension.
I showed up, I'm standing here,
and then you're
just going to ignore me?
- What are you thinking?
- How did...
- Regulus Corneas!
- You're really pissing me off.
There's no way you should be
chosen by the Witch Factor,
but you're holding on to it
with no regard
for the payment it requires?
- I don't care what you say!
Now stay away from them!
- [bones grind]
- [laughs]
[rumbling]
[pounding]
- ECHIDNA: A repetition draw.
- [gasps]
- While everyone here
is locked in a stalemate,
something of great significance
should be happening
with the other two.
- Look at everything Geuse
is putting himself through.
Are you actually suggesting
that we leave?
- It seems quite debatable
whether or not
sheer force of will
could have had
an effect on the outcome.
Then what's the harm
in just standing here, watching?
- I want to find out what--
- [chime rings]
[gasps]
- Looks like even
with your insufficient brain,
you've realized which of these
scenarios is the wiser choice.
[music playing only]
- [grunts]
- All right,
time for a change of location.
We're moving to where
you and your mother fled.
[snap echoes]
- No! No, Mother, don't!
FORTUNA: Please, Emilia.
I'll be right back, so just...
- No! You can't!
You have the same look
on your face that Geuse did!
Don't go! Don't leave me behind!
I'll tell the truth from now on!
I won't break my vows
and always be a good girl!
I swear! Just don't go!
[sobbing]
- Emilia.
Please, don't cry.
Emilia.
- [wailing]
- Why didn't I realize it?
Mother Fortuna...
she--she was my real mother.
[wailing continues]
- Mother Fortuna...
I love you.
- Miss Fortuna!
[crying stops]
- [gasps]
[sighs]
Tell me,
are the villagers safe, Archi?
- The news isn't good.
Our people are trying
to stand their ground,
but they're all fighting
Bishop Corneas' men.
If we stay in the forest,
they'll find us for sure.
It seems
they've come here to take--
- The seal. That's it, right?
How did they find out about it?
[music playing only]
Even that woman was...
Fine, then.
I'll be right there.
- I beg you,
let the rest of us fight.
You need to take Emilia and
leave the forest immediately!
- And what would happen
if I were to go now?
If they manage to get
their hands on the seal,
then the world
will come to an end this time!
- [gasps]
- I'm so sorry,
sorry you went through all this
just trying to protect us.
- Please don't say that!
Who would show such disdain
for a family member?
- Do forgive me.
Listen.
I need to go back for a bit.
I have an important duty
to fulfill
by protecting
the people of the forest,
and that means
I'll need to leave you
- for a little while, all right?
- No, please!
You can't! I don't want you to!
Please don't go!
- Emilia, now do as I say.
I want you to leave
this forest with Archi.
- Understand?
- [cries]
Miss Fortuna, I...
- There must be a--
- Archi...
it's a bit early,
but I'm entrusting you
with the mission
of the forest dwellers.
Please take Emilia
away from here.
This world
isn't easy to live in,
but I know there's hope.
I'm sure of it.
- But I can't do that!
I must stay
with everyone until--
- Take Emilia.
I beg you.
She's the daughter
of my brother and his wife,
but she's my daughter as well.
- It's not fair.
When you put it that way,
you know it's impossible
for me to refuse you.
- I apologize.
We're unfair,
but please forgive us.
- Emilia--
- No, you're not
leaving me behind!
I wanna stay with you!
I promise I'll be good
and I won't be in the way!
Just don't leave me!
I don't wanna be alone!
- Come now.
You'll never be alone.
- Listen, sweetheart.
I will always
be right here with you
in the memories that come forth
each time you close your eyes
and picture me...
in dreams,
where you hug yourself
and feel warm,
in the echoes you hear
when you shout into the sky.
I'll be with you
every step of the way,
forever and ever, my little one.
- You're lying. No!
That's nothing
but a lie, Mother! [crying]
- Emilia, I promise you...
- [gasping]
- No matter what, you
and I
will always be together.
That's the oath I'm making
to you right here and now.
- You really mean it?
You'll stay with me forever?
-Yes, really.
It's a solemn vow.
I love you more than anyone.
You hear me?
You mean the world to me, Lia,
the whole world to me.
- [crying]
Mother Fortuna, I...
I love you, too,
Mother Fortuna!
I really do!
- I love you.
I love you so much, Mother,
so very much, so very much!
I love you! I love you!
- [crying]
- Lia, my precious girl.
I love you, Emilia.
EMILIA: Why? Why did
everything turn out this way?
Was it because I broke
my promise and left my room?
- No! None of this
is your fault at all!
No one is to blame for this!
- Then if that's true,
why do we both
have to leave the forest?
Would it be better if I'd
stayed
locked up in my room forever?
Maybe then,
no one would have to go,
and we could have
stayed together!
- You're wrong, Emilia.
- Am I bad?
Is that why everybody hates me
and why I just end up alone?
- No! Nothing could be
farther from the truth!
No one hates you! We love you,
and we're trying
desperately to keep you safe!
Everything in this world
exists to bless you!
[groans]
- [groans]
- [gasping]
- [hissing]
ARCHI: The Black Serpent?
That diseased,
plague-bearing mabeast...
Fula!
[grunts] Huma!
- Archi?
- It's nothing but a scratch.
I'm okay, really.
Everything is...
all right.
[chuckles]
- [hissing]
- [grunts]
Listen, Emilia.
Over there.
Do you see those white flowers
right between the two trees?
- Uh-huh.
- Could you head
toward those flowers for me?
I'd like you
to run through them
and then just keep going.
- Okay, I'll run.
I can, but...
- No, don't worry. I'll be fine,
and you will never be alone.
- A-Archi...
- Now start running!
Don't look back,
no matter what you hear!
- Yes, that's right.
Keep on running,
just like the way we're
always running after you.
[winces]
- [growling]
- Face me. You think
I plan on letting you go?
Don't worry, Fortuna.
I know your daughter
will be just fine.
[rumbling fades]
[Geuse panting]
Even after all of that, you--
- Persistent.
Look, why don't you
just admit that
it's hopeless and give up?
- [wailing]
- [thuds]
- In the end,
while you do have your resolve,
your determination
and all that,
it isn't enough to make up
for your overall weakness.
Believe me, I'm not doing this
because I'm a sadist
or anything.
It only looks
like I'm tormenting you,
because you're
so painfully feeble.
- Take a moment to reflect,
and don't criticize him
too harshly, Bishop Corneas.
You're more special
and perfect than anyone...
- [sighs]
- which makes you wonderful.
Those who stand against us
are also wonderful
in their imperfection.
- [groans]
- You just keep on giving me
more and more work to do,
you incompetent fool.
- Enough! Al Fula!
- [yelps]
- Geuse! Hang on!
- Miss Fortuna...
is--is Miss Emilia...
- I sent her
out of the forest with Archi.
Because of you, she's safe.
- Thank goodness.
It's such a relief to hear.
- [gasps]
REGULUS: And why is that?
There's nothing good about it.
Who the hell
do you think you are, huh,
coming back here like that?
I had won our battle
and was about to crush his head
under my foot, me!
What gives you the right?
Who gave you permission?
Now speak up! Answer me!
Answer me!
Answer me! Answer me!
How dare you
come back here and--
- Wait a moment, Bishop Corneas.
- Huh?
What was that, Miss Pandora?
- Relax. Calm your anger.
I will not allow you to simply
lash out and kill them here.
Tell me. Do you feel nothing
when you see those two?
- [sighs]
Did you just order me
to relax and calm my anger?
Don't get cocky
with that snide grin
and unassuming attitude, woman!
[projectiles strike]
- No way.
- That's what you get
when you mouth off to me.
Don't get in my way.
Don't interrupt
when I'm talking, either!
- [winces]
Miss Fortuna, please,
you need to run away
and get out of--
- Come on now.
Don't be so foolish.
I left Emilia
to come back here and fight.
- But why would you--
- To try and
keep you from dying.
- [gasps]
- And so that if you did die...
I'd be right here at your side.
- [shudders]
- If you were
no longer in this world,
if you stopped coming
to this forest,
then what would I have
to wait around for?
I couldn't endure such a long
time without you beside me.
I suppose I'm weak that way.
- You're not weak.
Don't ever say that.
- No, I am.
- Truth is, I was
only acting tough
in front of you and Emilia.
[chuckles]
- [groans]
[Regulus scoffs]
You want to ignore me,
take a moment
to talk to each other,
then just stand up and face me
whenever you're ready?!
Fine! I'll crush the both of you
into nothing but a shallow pool
of blood, bones, and bits!
- I said to wait,
Bishop Corneas.
- [gasps]
- In fact, I was quite clear.
[rumble]
Through my compassion and grace,
I'll forgive
your violent actions
and rash hysterics.
Honestly, my goal
in bringing you here
has already been fulfilled,
so consider yourself
free to leave now.
- [gasps] You brought me here,
but now you're satisfied,
so you're telling me to
go?!
What kind of idiot do you
think I am, you little--
- I see. Well,
I'll take it upon myself then.
- I believe Bishop Corneas
shouldn't be with us any longer.
- [gasps]
- He'll be in his own mansion,
- surrounded by his wives.
- Wai--
- [both gasp]
- There.
I've sent that noisy young man
far away from us.
And now we'll be able
to talk much more leisurely.
- Uh, could I start
by asking you a question?
You were blown to pieces
and died earlier,
so how are you still here?
- Sorry?
Perhaps from duress,
your eyes have deceived you.
[both gasp]
- Now that
Bishop Corneas is gone,
the results of his actions
are gone, too.
Why not take a look
for yourself?
- Impossible.
- But I won't rewrite
your being overtaken
by the Sloth Witch Factor.
Whatever happens,
I wish to commend you
on your behavior
and the behavior of this woman
who came back for you.
- [gasps]
- Miss Fortuna...
- let's get moving.
You and I
will defeat her together.
We have to do everything
we possibly can for Miss Emilia.
- [grunts]
Freeze the fluctuation
of time to white.
Demon Ice of antiquity
bringing eternal sleep
to the soul...
come forth!
- For my mission, for my life,
for the entirety of my love,
here and now,
for this very moment!
- Now come and embrace me.
Hold me close so I can feel it,
feel the full extent
of your resolve.
[Emilia panting]
Mother Fortuna...
Geuse, Archi...
I have to--
I have to do something, too.
I need to help!
- Bring the key and seal to me.
- [gasps]
["Believe in you"
playing in Japanese]
The seal?
If that's that you want, fine.
I'll just--I'll give it to you.
It's where that thing is.
But, uh...
[stammering]
[crying]
- ♪ I believe,
I believe in you... ♪
- The fairies?
Hold on. Are--
are you showing me
the way to the seal?
You're saying it's that way?
I can rescue Mother
and everyone else, too?
- [singing in Japanese]
- [panting]
[no audible dialogue]
I'll do it! I want to be
with all of you again!
I'll be a good girl! I promise!
[song ends]
[panting]
- Welcome, child.
- [shudders]
- I've been waiting for you.
[chuckles]